Hey, it's Beach Festival today,
do you think Yim Wing Chun will come?
Sure, she'll be here.
Wow, look at all these people!
My information is always accurate.
That's true.
If Wing Chun is not coming,
why would there be so many
merchants here?
Aren't they afraid of the bandits?
Waiter, is Master Yim here yet?
Yes, she's been here for a while.
Let's go in.
Alright.
A man should be more decisive...
Yes or No.
Why are you so wishy washy?
Are you still thinking?
It's getting late!
How about this.
I'll give you another discount...
You aren't very sincere.
How about this...
Master Yim is really shrewd.
No, that's Master Yim's aunt,
Abacus Fong.
Oh, she is? She's notorious!
I heard that she grew up
eating stinky tofu,
that's why she has bad breadth.
Yes, it stinks!
I'm very sincere, look!
Bastard! How dare you!
What's so funny?
Forget it. I'm leaving.
Don't go!
She's leaving?
There she is...
Master, how come Yim Wing Chun
is dressed like a man?
Stupid. She dresses like a man
but she is still impressive.
Good. Let's hire her
to be the head of security.
Wait...
But Master, those bandits
are after our family fortune.
We cannot wait any longer.
I have a better idea.
It will cost a fortune to hire her,
but if I marry her,
I'll just have to feed her, right?
Master, are you kidding?
Of course not! Let's go.
Run! The bandits are coming!
Bandits! What should we do?
Hurry. Let's leave!
Oh, I've got an idea.
Maybe it'll work.
You bandits rob our residents
and the businesses.
I, Wong Hok Chow and
Yim Wing Chun are here today.
How dare you stir up trouble!
Listen, we are not here
to disturb your businesses.
We just want to invite you to
our fortress to discuss a joint venture.
How dare you blackmail us
in broad daylight!
Shut up! I think we'll have to use
force to reason with you.
You have a bad mouth!
Who's calling me?
None of my business.
Go to hell!
I'll protect you!
Master...
Master, are you alright?
I've driven the bandits away.
Scholar, your courage has
driven the bandits away.
You have my utmost respect.
Thanks for your help.
I'm very grateful.
It's our pleasure to help you.
I will visit you soon
to show my appreciation.
It's not necessary.
Go before the bandits return.
Yes.
Good-bye.
We'll be very safe if she is with us.
Master, women who fight are no good
even if they're beautiful.
Master, you should be careful.
Narrow-minded.
Good-bye.
I think this scholar is
really something.
Are you interested in him?
Didn't you say
you would not get married?
Yes, I did.
Your dad will be upset at me again.
Where is he?
Who hit me?
You must have offended many people.
Let's go.
I've been trying very hard to be
a matchmaker for your family.
You are very lucky to have someone
marry your second daughter.
Thank you. You have worked hard.
They are over there.
My youngest daughter...
Oh, I must leave now.
Dad.
Why did she leave in such a hurry?
To her, you are scarier than a ghost!
You...
Now that my daughter
is working with you,
you must be making a lot of money.
My brother,
you and Wing Chow are set for life,
But Wing Chun and I
have to take care of ourselves.
Shut up.
You have spoiled her.
I didn't teach her kung-fu.
Can't you be quiet?
It's all your fault.
Aunt Abacus, let's stop quarreling.
I'm getting married tomorrow.
Let's have a happy Beach Festival Day.
Alright, I'll forget it,
It's not going to kill me anyway.
The River God has possessed
the sorcerer's body.
Yes. Governor,
we the three Southern Masters...
from the Brilliant Kung Fu School
are here to pay our respect.
What a beauty!
What are you looking at?
Why can't I just look?
I'm Charmy. My husband is very ill
and I have come a long distance
to beg for some divine water.
Divine water is not for outsiders.
Please don't send me away.
Please have mercy!
I've come a long distance,
my husband is very ill.
What a pity!
Wing Chow,
if your husband becomes like him,
your life will be ruined.
Watch your words.
I'm telling you the truth!
Let me finish...
My brother,
if her husband gets syphilis, then...
I'm fine! I'm not hurt!
Here comes the bandits again!
Don't worry.
Bandits...
Let's get that beauty
for our 2nd Fortress Lord.
Help!
Go help her.
Why don't you go?
Help!
What should we do?
Don't worry, don't worry.
Good. Wing Chun is here.
Old Yim, keep an eye on your daughter.
Yes.
Make sure she doesn't mess
in our affairs.
We won't put up with it any longer.
Come on, lady.
It's too late. They're here already.
Help!
Let's go.
Hit them!
Yim Wing Chun.
I don't care who you are. Get her!
Alright!
Shut your bad mouth.
Nothing good happens
when you are around.
Bravo!
Hey, it's only the back of the sword!
Help!
Don't be afraid. The bandits are gone.
Hey, you! Watch out!
I'll be back for you!!
Yim Wing Chun rescued the girl.
Your husband is over here.
My husband, are you alright?
Waiter.
Yes, Master Yim.
Take him to the guest room
and find a doctor for him.
Yes.
Your dad doesn't need
your sister to do her chores today
because she's getting married tomorrow.
So he's making you do it?
What's so special about
getting married?!
I bet you, she'll have to work
like a dog after she's married.
Shall we hire someone to help you?
Are you feeling generous?
In that case, you do it all.
Since you're not getting married,
you have to do it.
What about you?
The bridegroom is very ugly.
It's all my fault.
We're leaving.
Sister, let's go.
Let's go.
Wing Chow, if your husband yells
at you... What are you looking at?
I'll pluck your eye balls out!
...you should come home immediately.
Don't lose face for the family.
You be quiet!!
My brother, you should be
more careful on the road.
You're old and may die
before you return.
You should watch your mouth.
I meant well.
But he doesn't like to hear it.
Congratulations! Congratulations on
your daughter's wedding day.
I'm Scholar Wong Hok Chow.
I've brought some musicians
to celebrate with you.
Stop.
Thank you. That's very nice of you.
I came to show my gratitude to
Miss Wing Chun for saving my life.
I'm really fond of her.
That's marvelous, that's marvelous.
It's getting close to the lucky hour.
Let's go.
Good. We don't have to wait for
you fiancee Leung Pok To anymore.
If we miss the lucky hour,
it'll ruin the peace in our family.
Let's go.
Good-bye.
Uncle Yim, don't worry.
I'll take care of Wing Chun.
We are going to be rich! Look at all
these customers waiting for us.
Excuse me...
Yim Wing Chun,
we're are going to shame you today.
We have invited the renowned
Master Wong to teach you a lesson.
Fat chance!
When it comes to martial arts,
men are always better than women...
but when it comes to bearing children,
that's a different matter.
I'll win for sure today.
Wing Chun, after my lesson today,
go home and bear children.
This guy's mouth is worse than yours.
But your dad didn't want you to fight.
But Dad is not here.
That's right.
Kick his butt.
If you can smash the tofu,
you are the winner.
I'll beat you
until you surrender.
Master Wong!
Looks like I have to get serious.
I want you to crawl out of here!
You had enough?
No.
He won't surrender.
Hit him until he does.
No, not "hit". "Teach".
Master Wong, why...
why don't you go back to your farm?
Get out of our way! Come!
A beautiful girl is selling herself
to bury her husband.
Let's go!
Who could that be?
The husband of this woman died without
leaving any money for his burial.
She is willing to sell herself.
Bid starts at 10 taels.
The highest bidder can take her home.
10 taels.
11.
12.
12.50
13 taels.
15 taels.
Look at you!
You're drooling.
No, I'm just touched
by her faithfulness.
I don't want her to fall into
the hands of lustful men.
30 taels.
Scholar Wong, you must help her.
You must have some money to spare.
No?
Don't force him.
Not at all. How much?
100 taels.
You think I'm a millionaire?
Thank you, Scholar Wong.
Don't mention it.
This 5 taels is for the rent.
Thank you, Master Yim.
Use this to bury your husband,
and use the remaining to go home.
Thank you.
My name is Charmy.
I'm homeless now.
Would you take me in please?
In this case, come with us.
You can stay with us.
We'll pay for the burial.
The rest of the money will be for food.
Let's go home.
Please.
Let's go back to our fortress.
Let's go.
Hail, 2nd Fortress Lord.
Those two men want to join us
in the fight against Yim Wing Chun.
Yes.
Tell them to come over here.
Come.
Since you two were not killed
by the arrows,
this proves your loyalty to us.
Let's go upstairs.
Give them the Fearless Wine.
No...
What have you heard
about Yim Wing Chun?
The woman bought Yim Wing Chun.
No, Yim Wing Chun bought the woman.
This is ridiculous.
This bloody woman
takes whoever she wants
and now she's taken my woman.
I must save Charmy
and kill Yim Wing Chun!
Kill Yim Wing Chun!
Hey Wing Chun!
Look at you.
Since you've taken up kung-fu
you've lost all your femininity.
Now you're muscular all over.
No wonder nobody buys
our tofu any more.
We still had some customers
when your sister was here.
If I depend on you,
I'll starve to death.
Don't worry, our tofu is made
with the finest ingredients.
Nowadays, customers look for more.
The men won't buy from us
if we aren't attractive.
Therefore, I've trained another
Tofu Beauty.
Come on out.
I have dressed her up
in your old clothes.
If she can't attract those men,
I'll write my name upside down!
Not bad, eh?
Your clothes are very pretty.
Turn around. Doesn't she look like you
when you were younger?
Yes.
Really?
You will start selling tofu tomorrow.
You'll be the new Tofu Beauty.
Okay.
Let me show you a couple of my moves.
Give me a sexy pose.
Chest up, stomach in.
It's alright to show some cleavage.
Start practicing.
Are you alright?
Time flies.
So many years have gone by already.
If you put on those clothes again,
you'll look just as good.
I'm used to this look already. Every
thing will be fine now that we have her.
You know I didn't mean to hurt you.
I know. You're just brainless.
Tofu Beauty, please sell us some tofu.
I've come very early this morning.
Please don't push.
I can't serve you if you don't line up.
We've come early to wait in line.
Excuse me.
You guys can line up now.
Boy, that stinks.
Get in line if you want tofu.
Yeah, line up.
She's such a seductress.
Is it sweet?
Very sweet. Give me another.
Bastard!
One per customer, follow the rules.
I want two bowls.
Okay.
I want three bowls.
I'll stand in line again.
Wonderful.
She's doing even better than you did.
People used to be more polite.
We're going to be rich!
You have a sweet smile.
Really? Thank you.
I don't want fresh tofu.
I want preserved tofu.
Okay.
Soy Bean Milk is all sold out!
I have some...
You do? We don't think so.
Is he flirting with me?
It's been so long.
I'm not used to this anymore.
No, not that one, the one up there.
No, over there.
Oh, your idea really works!
Further.
Over there.
You guys are so bad!
Told you it's not that one,
it's the first one!
Charmy!
Scholar Wong.
Let me help you.
That's okay.
It's alright, I'll hold on to you.
Okay.
Master Yim, let me help you.
Thanks, I can do it myself.
Let me help you.
I'm alright.
I got it.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Master Yim, you are really strong.
I really admire that...
Scholar Wong, since you're so helpful,
why don't you help me grind the beans.
Come on...
It's a pleasure to help others.
Thank you very much.
We're running out of time.
Here, let me help you.
Harder...
I'm exhausted.
Stop! I have respect for you.
Don't do this to me!
I thought you enjoyed it.
I'm a respectful scholar.
If people see us like this,
my good name will be ruined.
Confucius! Mencius!
Give me your guidance!
Sooner or later you'll be mine.
Yim's tofu is really sweet and soft.
I think the Tofu Beauty's
fragrance is much sweeter.
Excuse me
What?
Did you buy that from the Yim's store?
Even people from other places
have heard about the Tofu Beauty.
No, I've known her
for more than 10 years already.
Now so many men
are interested in Wing Chun?
You're nuts!
It smells so good.
Tofu please.
Excuse me.
Excuse me please.
Who dropped the money?
Hey, who dropped the money?
I did!
She's such a beauty.
We haven't seen each other for
ten years. Do you recognize me?
You are Mister...
I came from Fook Chow.
You've come so far to buy
soy bean milk?
Yes. I'm out of bowls.
Let me get some from inside.
Don't bother. Put it in here.
Fine.
It's full.
Yes, yes.
It smells good.
Tofu Beauty, fill my hands too.
You really are the Tofu Beauty?
They're just joking.
Five cents please.
Here.
Are you tired?
No.
She has a lover already...
Thank you.
Watch your step.
Okay.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I am Scholar Wong.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I'm Leung Pok To,
I've come to pay a visit...
Visit? Are you a government official?
He's ranked higher than you.
Officer, why are you visiting so late?
What are you talking about?
I'm here to visit Wing Chun.
So we came for the same reason.
See you later.
Let's go.
Wow, he's good!
Hurry up.
I don't want to miss anything.
Fabulous!
Who are you?
I'm Flying Monkey.
Don't you dare touch me.
Yim Wing Chun is here!
I've come to invite you
to our fortress.
Smells good!
What's going on?
Charmy, what's the matter?
A bandit tried to abduct me.
Bandit?
Be reasonable.
We're all here to have fun.
Why do you want to fight with me?
Wing Chun is my fiancee,
don't you dare touch her.
I'm leaving!
Stop. It's not him.
I've got this back for you.
Sir...
It's not him?
No, you're mistaken.
Flying Monkey must have raped Charmy.
Stay here.
You risked your life
to save me last night.
Why won't you talk to me now?
Please tell me what's wrong.
I studied martial arts for six years
to protect you,
but was beaten by your lover.
The one who fought with you last night
is not my lover.
He's not? Thank God!
Then who is he?
She saved my life and she is my master.
I respect her.
How confusing.
Did you repay him with your body?
I belong to her already.
There goes my chance.
I'm only kidding.
Wing Chun is a woman.
What? You are not a virgin anymore?
Oh my god.
Master Yim, the doctor is here.
She's here. I must go.
Are you alright?
You are secretly seeing a man.
I must tell Wing Chun.
You won't...
I won't if you and I...
Whatever.
Let's see what's going on inside.
My friend, I'm sorry about last night.
I can't blame anyone,
my kung-fu isn't good enough.
You're too humble.
What is your name?
You don't need to know
the name of a loser.
Your wound is not that serious
but your sorrow can make it worse.
Frankly speaking,
my lover has left me.
Love hurts.
I wish them happiness.
Wing Chun really admires
your graciousness.
Admires me? It would be better
if Wing Chun marries me.
Pardon me?
I'm talking about how I feel.
Do you know how I feel?
Not now.
I'll kill myself
if you don't believe me.
Don't open the window.
Fresh air is good for your health.
I really would kill myself.
I don't want to die.
That hurts!
I was only joking...
I didn't mean it.
Leave her alone.
Your husband just passed away
and already you have two men.
The whole town is talking about you.
You have not only
embarrassed yourself,
but you have also ruined our reputation.
Put it down.
Let me ask you, are all men
attracted to widows?
You're just jealous.
Yes, I am.
Charmy, tell me,
is it true that
you can't live without a man?
Yes.
I'm not as smart as the two of you.
Wing Chun, you're brave and strong.
And Abacus, you're a business woman.
I'm just an ordinary woman.
My only wish is to marry a man
who loves me,
bear children for him, raise them,
so that they'll take care of me
when I'm old.
But ever since I got married,
my husband has been ill.
I've searched many years for a cure.
I sold everything
and spent all our money.
He asked me to leave him.
I thought about it,
but I stayed until he passed away.
I feel that I don't owe him anything.
She is indeed an ill-fortuned woman.
Don't you have any sympathy?
No.
If I'm given a second chance,
I'll make full use of it.
Right. You think so too?
I have two choices,
one is rich and mature,
the other is romantic and good-looking.
I can't make up my mind.
Men are disgusting.
I know, they really are disgusting.
Yeah.
Really?
Do you want to try it?
No, I'm still a virgin.
Come on. It feels really good.
Told you, she likes it.
Wing Chun, you should try it too.
No.
Try it.
You'll love it.
The bandits are causing
trouble in our village.
Our lives and properties are in danger.
I suggest that
all able bodied men join forces...
Mr. Leung, you should be in bed.
I'm much better already.
I'm just feeling a little down.
Is something wrong? Please talk to me.
We used to be much closer
when we were kids.
When we were kids?
Yes, we used to be like
brother and sister,
we talked about everything.
But now you've changed so much.
Why is that, Wing Chun?
Oh, you've mistaken...
We should discipline the bad.
Rapist!
Horny bastard!
How dare you push me?
A gentleman does not reason
with his fist.
Fine, then I'll use my mouth.
A gentleman does not reason
with his fist or mouth.
Then I'll use my foot.
This isn't the behavior
of a gentleman either.
Stop it.
Meet me in the backyard tonight.
I'll explain everything.
Please go.
Be careful.
You don't even know where he's from.
Just go.
You'd better go now
before my men kill you.
Am I right, Charmy?
Charmy has fallen for another man.
She's dumping you.
I feel sorry for you.
I just care about Charmy.
I'm not in love with her.
Stop pretending.
You and I are the same.
Greedy and cheap.
I'm better than Leung Pok To.
I can't lose to him!
Let me help you.
You're such a friend!
Are you helping me for free?
100 taels.
Wow!
That's the price for a gentleman,
but for you...
10% discount.
You guarantee I'll bed her?
Guarantee you'll have
children with her.
Okay, we have a deal.
Give me my change.
I owe you 10 taels.
They have a date tonight
in her room.
If you show up earlier,
you'll be able to...
That's immoral.
Which room?
The one in the middle. Have fun!
We both want money and sex.
Wing Chun will be out of town
for two days
Really? Are you sure?
Here she comes.
Tell 2nd Fortress Lord
that we can get Charmy tonight.
Okay.
Here I am, Charmy!