Takashi...
...what's the safest place in the
jungle?
On the lion's back.
The fleas there enjoy
the most peaceful life there is.
Hey...
Hey!
Shit!
Where are you bleeding?
You need protein, or you won't heal.
Put these on.
That's all there is here.
Hurry up!
It suits you.
What are you doing?
Throwing these out.
You saw Mr Kidokoro?
Takashi... be careful of him.
Did you hear about Sugimoto?
He's dead.
Murdered.
I'm leaving this country.
There's happiness somewhere.
You just have to go there.
Who's that?
A guest.
A guest?
So you've found happiness?
Take care.
Call me if you want to come.
Thanks.
Why did you come back?
What's happened now?
Don't want to say?
It's probably safer for me
if I don't know.
Does it bother you to kill someone?
Why do you kill people?
For money?
My body moves.
When I hold my sword and close in
on a target, my body just moves...
...before I can think why.
Aw, you poor dear!
Some king stops paying his guards...
...so they put their skills
on the market.
You kill people for no reason.
Not to defend your country,
not to defend yourselves...
You have nothing to defend.
You just kill.
But I had...
...a reason.
I had a reason.
I'm sure I had...
...a reason to kill.
Come with me.
My sister.
When she was eight...
...I came home from school
to find blood everywhere...
...and just her alive.
The guys who did it were let off
for lack of evidence.
So I killed them myself.
I was caught, tried, and sentenced.
Four years later when I got out,
I couldn't see things...
...the way I had before.
Everything looked completely
different.
Then I met someone...
...who said he wanted me to be
as happy as I'd been before.
No one else said that.
I've done things,
and been pushed into doing things.
To get back to being happy,
I've rationalized everything.
Renkyo?
Yes.
I need to talk to you.
About what?
Can we really kill Yuki?
Without her, we have no leader
of Takemikazuchi blood.
- And then...
- Then what?
We've already lost just about
everyone of Takemikazuchi blood.
But what reason do we have to exist...
...without that name?
- We don't need a reason.
Now we have nothing left
to guard any more.
I venerated our ancestors,
I believed in the motherland.
But when the monarchy fell...
...our swords were taken from us.
Those who were caught had
their memories erased with drugs...
...and to slow their arms...
...needles driven into their elbows.
We fled, without turning our swords
on the motherland.
Remember, Renkyo?
Those tanks on that southern island
we saw as we went?
A group of ruined tanks...
...all eaten away by acid rain...
...and stinking of corpses.
But there were no corpses.
The stench was coming from us.
At that time...
...we were dead.
Hello?
- Hello?
- It's me.
Mr Kidokoro...
Why are you phoning?
I sent you a schematic.
Can you take a look at it?
Sure.
Be right back.
Did you see it?
I want to move in ten days.
Are you there?
Ten days...
I can't.
OK, when?
Never.
No?
No.
All right. I'll be in touch.
You always look so sad...
And you have no expression at all.
Have you ever been sad?
I make it go away. Just like pain.
And that's how you can kill people?
When you're sad you should grieve,
and when you're happy, celebrate.
Have you ever laughed?
When I'm sad I grieve.
For hours...
For days...
For years...
Have you ever heard of
a miki-ishi?
No.
It means 'beautiful precious stone'.
They're rare.
You can look all year
and be lucky to find even one.
When you grind it on a whetstone,
you get a little green crystal.
My mother collected them.
When she found one,
she'd carefully polish and save it.
When she had 30,
she was going to make a necklace...
...for my wedding day.
She said she'd put it around my neck
the day I got married.
She started collecting them at 18...
...had me at 22...
...and died at 27.
...in a little treasure box.
Not enough for a necklace.
Soon I'll pass the age
she was when she had me...
...and then her age when she died.
But I haven't collected anything
I could leave...
...to anyone.
I don't have anyone
to leave anything to.
There's no one...
...I feel like I want to treasure.
Let's leave here...
...leave this country.
There's nothing holding us here.
Somewhere there must be a place
we can forget everything.
Let's go there.
Mother...
...now...
...I'm happy.
You think you'll ever be happy?
Even if you kill me,
you still walk the path of blood.
You can't avoid it.
Mr Kidokoro...
Your sister looks well.
What do you want?
Oh...
If it's about that schematic...
No. I changed plans.
This one's a great idea.
I'm sure you'll like it.
What is it?
We find common ground
with the government.
We achieve our ideals,
and very few people get hurt.
What do you think, Takashi?
Good plan, huh?
You're selling me out?
It's a deal. We respect the law,
and our ideals are realized.
Traitor!
In spirit we will continue.
The plan I sent you was to be the
last.
Because we'd all be killed?
Don't talk like that!
Isn't that what you've wanted
all along anyway?
- But this way you're safe.
- I said it was a deal!
A fair deal.
So why did we do all that?
Why all those victims?!
It meant something. We all acted
because we believed in our ideals.
No. We believed in you!
...Mimura blown up...
They all believed in you!
You said we'd be happy again.
You're the only one who did!
Happiness will come.
Of course it won't be free.
I told you the price would be high.
All we can do is pray for the victims.
But you don't have to pray, Takashi.
You're one of the victims
we'll be praying for.
You bastard!
I am Azora's daughter...
...Princess Yuki
of the Takemikazuchi.
In the name of my mother,
I take your life!
Don't you understand?
It's over! Get lost!
I'll keep this.
Live.
Be happy.
Live for me.
Takashi...
International Distribution
Kadokawa Shoten Publishing Co., Ltd.
English Subtitles
Ian MacDougall