What's this?
Excuse me
The lady's so lovely
She deserves some wind effect
You look gorgeous
I know
Well?
A vintage wine, from '82
But I can also tell
The grape—picker was born in '60
Let's order
You order
You do Chinese Pot Rice?
Just kidding
Thank God!
You got a thing about people
watching you eat?
We don't want to be crowded
Excuse me
You booked the whole place?
Just you and me
I was hoping
To run into celebrities
You must really...
hate crowds
What about your friends?
Here comes one
Mr. Lo, you can't go in
Why'd you do it?
Dump my company's shares?
call me tomorrow
You're hurting me
And yourself too
Mr. Lo, please leave
Sir
You look intelligent
lam intelligent
Then stay home and think
Devise a way...
to save your company
Who are you?
C.N.'s friend
He booked the whole place for me
You're disturbing us
That's so rude
Let's talk outside
We've talked enough
See you outside
That signal means "Follow me"
Wrong again?
You're snooty
So are my friends
it rubs off
You have to go?
It'll just take a minute
C.N.
Watch your back
I called,
cleared it with your boss
I'm meeting Mr. Chan
Close the parking lot for us
Relax, I'm footing the bill
Fine, Mr. Lo
You heard Mr. Lo, move out
Have fun, Mr. Chan
LW
What's up?
I want you to meet someone
I hired him from overseas
Ladies and gentlemen
Alan
An undefeated light—weight champion
He'll fight you one—on—one
But...
I'm a middle—weight
Too much of an edge
But if you lose
Think of the disgrace
Grow up
Nuts
Play this music for me
No problem
You have no choice
Why the gloves?
This is a boxing match
I'm not...
into crippling people
With gloves, it won't hurt?
Sure it'll hurt
But much less
All set
Watch your head
Music
Knock me down anyway you can
But no dirty tricks
They say you're a great fighter. Come on
Look! They're not gonna
let you leave here without a fight
You ask for it
Are you ready?
Of course
Alan's losing bigtime
No, Alan's just testing him
He's wearing Chan down
Wait Good
Changing gloves, why?
Even the odds
Bigger the glove,
bigger the handicap
Chan's punches are soft
I've come a long way,
I don't want a short game
Every boxer trains...
to his own music
When he fights,
it give him rhythm
And rhythm paces his steps
Chan has no rhythm
He's controlled by Alan
You're an expert
You should be fighting
Right
C.N. and I used to box
But I always lost
So I quit and became a...
Commentator
Wow!
You like that better?
Sure. I sound so invincible
But I'm just like you guys
Helpless
Chan used to have brilliant moves
Now he's a mess
Buying companies...
instead of training
Loser!
Chan's nervous, it's over
Good hit, but not enough power
Come on
Yo u o kay?
You win
We won
Let's kick him while he's down
Good idea
Don't be...
such cowards
Ganging up on a downed man
There's no honor in that
You're good
Get the car
My joy is done. He's good
C.N., you okay?
You must be delighted
No, but I thought I would be
You need help?
Damn it
C.N., call me
You didn't leave?
You asked me to wait
I came to find you
Did they gang up on you?
No, one—on—one, I lost
You'll get used to it
Just kidding
Start training tomorrow,
you'll beat them
I'll train, but not for them
For what then?
A strong body, a quick mind
I haven't trained in ages
Your huge gym, what a waste
I hate training alone
I'll join you
Why be so nice to me?
You're rich
You're cute when you smile
You looked grouchyjust now
That's why you lost
Stick with smiling
These clothes and makeup don't fit you
Take tomorrow off
VVhy?
Say yes first
Yes, now why?
Play!
Memories are so many
Anticipation I now dare to indulge
I sketch a hazy future
Knowing this illusion is love
The tides of a lifetime
Widen the shores slowly
Quietly you and I meet
Our love proves life is ever changing
Shooting stars change courses
(We fall in love)
Miracles catch up with us (Finally)
Like eternity
Is the night really still young?
Currents change courses too
(We fall in love)
The crowds catch up with us (Finally)
I can think no more
But this love
Links the sea with the sky
My eyes have been raining
I can't hold on with both hands
I cry as we seek happiness
You're just like a shooting star
Those happy moments
Lock you between my brows
No matter how the world dazzles
It pales next to your eternal splendor
Shooting stars change courses
(We fall in love)
Miracles catch up with us (Finally)
Like eternity
Is the night really still young?
You love me?
I think you're quite...
Answer the question
The fact is...
C'mon
Answer in 4 words or less
I love you
Or I don't
When did you slip in?
I'm in love
Love's a dream
that leaves only emptiness
So don't get fooled by love
You're such an optimist
I have news for you
What?
Longyi's here
He almost strangled me
But I calmed him down
He's been drunk ever since
My fault
No way
Listen, love is not sympathy
You're tangled up...
with Chan
Don't let Longyi see you
Wine please No
Wait
Let go
No
Kitchen time
Kitchen
I need...
What?
I need a glass
I'll get it
Go inside
No pushing
Albert
Where's the opener?
Smooth move
So cold!
Albert
Now what?
I need the opener
Where is it?
Hurry!
What's that?
The family above us
Has a brat
It's from above us?
Where else?
It's from above us
It's that brat again
Opener
Forget it
Drink it this way
Wait Come
Drink with me
Yo u o kay?
I must tell C.N.
A game...
is fun
Till its secret is revealed
I know he loves me
He skips work to be with me
I'm like a child again
Getting so attached to him
I see something beautiful
I want it for him
Something happens, I want to tell him
I'm so happy
And...
so cold!
You're in love
Need something?
Sake
Finish your wine first
I want sake
Just wait outside Sake
Hang on
Excuse me
Let's sing
This is not a Karaoke bar
We don't have time
We'll split this
Too much
Not at all
Enough
Cheers
You'll get drunk
Drink it
1... 2... 3...
Down!
Still kicking. Thank God
She's safe here
Here she is
Gloria, Bu
Gloria's a good friend
She's the one impersonating me?
Yes!
Not bad
You knew all along
Why con me?
You started it
All the love I felt between us
That was just an act?
Our happiness was no act
If you like,
stay in Hong Kong
What am I?
One of your women?
The bottle sent me to you
A fairy tale becomes...
a nightmare
My big mouth
No
Get her back
Weren't we on the same plane?
Back to Taiwan?
Yes
You had fun?
It was okay
I bought a lot,
what about you?
I bought a story
A story!
Is it in an office building?
The government passed a law...
prohibiting the use...
of non—bio—degradable
styrofoam
LW's stock...
dropped drastically
From $6.80 to $1.20 a share
Major stockholders,
are dumping them
You knew...
the law would be passed?
It was only a matter of time
Should we borrow money?
Up to you guys
Mr. Chan,
you shouldn't buy a company
that's going down the drain
Just to...
get even
I won't
That's all for today
The acquisition...
is a go?
I'll let you know
Love is like falling maples
Like what?
Like falling maples
What does that mean?
I don't know
I've never seen you like this
Paper everywhere
Just do...
what you have to do
Again?
Forget it
What?
Nothing
Leave me alone
Fine, be that way
You broke it?
Good guess
Sir
Call 911
They'll stop me
Just call
See
What do you want?
You ruined our boss,
lost us our jobs
We came for payback
Mr. Chan
I heard you're back in training
Yes, lam
Rematch?
Mr. Lo sent you?
Mr. Lo is broke
It's not about money
Not now
You got no choice
You really enjoy fighting, don't you?
Only with the best
What are they talking about?
You never learned English...
in school?
C'mon, tell me
No
Okay
Rules?
No rules
Anything goes, but no dirty tricks
You like white
Are you sure?
I'm sure
Good training
Wait
Now what?
"What's you okay?" In English?
Are you okay?
Okay
Pretty good
I'm coming
Ready?
Come on
Smile, don't worry
Are you ready?
Come on
Don't worry, be happy
Let's dance
Let's finish
Get up
On your feet
Yo u o kay?
Yes
You won
I lost
VVhy?
Pound for pound
He'd have beaten me in no time
See if he's all right
You smell turpentine?
The boss is setting a fire
Fantastic
But we'll go to jail
Prison!
This is nuts
Watch it
No sweat
Hey, jail sucks, boss
You checked there's nobody inside?
Sure did
Good
Give this to dad
Tell him I love him
Give this to C.N.
Tell him I hate him
This is for the cops
I'm claiming all responsibility
Really?
You're going to jail, not us?
Me neither
Stand aside
C.N. and I go down together
Don't do it, boss
My eyes hurt
But so what?
I'm going to die anyway
Bye, Mary
Calm down, LW
It's all your fault
You took it too far
Dad kicked me off the Board
I have nothing now
I'm finished
What about us, boss?
Are we finished too?
You're asking me?
Yes
Shut up
Boss
O kay n ow?
Warmer still
How's that?
Just right
Your eyes still hurt?
Why be so nice to me?
You wanted to ruin me
Styrofoam's bad...
for the environment
It needs to be regulated
That motivated my acquisition
Let's be partners
In recycling paper
That's not like you
Ever since grade school
You've had to beat me
In whatever we do
You stole my girlfriends
And then dumped them
Never really loved them
I hated you so
I hated you too
Really? What for?
For always laughing
For being born so rich
For your name
Low Wow is a stupid name
I hated you most
For stealing my puppy love, Ann
So it boils down to Ann
But she dumped me
She married that...
Andy Law Andy Law
That nerd
So dull
We fought for so many years
But we each haven't committed
To loving only one woman
But what about Mary?
She's nothing
But you yelled "Bye Mary" just now
Weren't you engaged?
What happened?
I copped out
but she's one great dame
We were so happy together
Wish I could turn the clock back
But she moved overseas
I lost track of her
What's wrong?
See you later
Did I say something?
Skipper
Your Bu is back
Yes, she is. Cheers
Skipper, cheers
What's that?
Going to college?
Considering it
You've changed
Love changes people
Don't rush...
to forget him
Or it'll get worse
One day
You take a shower
Listen to music
And suddenly remember him
Then you've forgotten him
You're pretty when you smile
Bu
Albert
Where have you been?
I was so worried
You're not...
really my type
I like older men
I'm older than you
I mean here
Here?
If I were your girl
We'd break up in 3 days, tops
You'll get it
I miss you so
I was so worried about you
This must be your mother
This is...
Albert, my pal
Can you be my adopted brother?
Good idea
I'm the adopted mother?
Wait
Why not? Mom
Son
Mom
My Albert
Bu! Bu!
I missed you
You miss me?
Come back
Bu!
Scram
It's you who bullied my daughter
No, I didn't
You did too
She used to laugh all the time
Now she hardly smiles
My heart aches for her
What did you do to her?
Nothing
Then why is she like this?
Please let me talk to her
Just...
leave her alone
I don't speak Taiwanese
He said leave her alone
Beat it
Bu!
Get lost
Bu
Hit the road
It's all right
You bullied my niece
Sir
I'll just sit here
Don't walk past me
You dad's a cool dude
Sir, you okay?
Are you hurt?
Leave us alone
Just 5 seconds with her, okay?
Waste of time
Bu, I...
Shut up
Bu!
I'm warning you
Either you kill me
Or let me talk to her
All right, come
Speak up
Now or never
Don't disturb them
I want to hear
Why bother?
You left these
I have plenty
I brought Chinese pot rice
It's cold, but it's your favorite
some old clothes and a pot of rice?
There's more
I put a note in each one
Saying what?
I love you, I miss you
Never over 4 words
took me hours
Too much work
Just put $1,000 in each
And you have me
So do you love me?
I love you
Since when?
Since you stole my name—card
What wish did you make...
on the boat?
It's already come true
Why do you cry?
Kiss her
I'll say it in Cantonese
You're...
Xiaojun
Do I know you?
I'm your neighbor
Wow, fantastic!
VVhy?
Oh, weather is fine
Look at them
The women here are gorgeous
I should have...
Go to hell
I want you to meet my dolphin
Really?
Bu! Bu!
Wow!