Mmm.
Get to the point already!
Okay. Alan, Jackie and
Lorelei are in a rock group together,
but when Lorelei got engaged to
Alan, it broke Jackie's heart.
So he left the group and
became a soldier of fortune...
known as the "Asian Hawk."
What the hell does
this story have to do...
with the missing pieces
of the Armour of God?
Well, the formidable
Asian Hawk has acquired...
some of the world's most
important art treasures.
I think I found a way
to persuade him to help us.
I'm convinced he can find
the other two pieces of armour.
Ah, I see.
Well, if we offer
him a good price, then maybe there's a chance
we'll get back the Armour of God.
You shut up.
He hasn't finished the story yet.
I'm trying to tell you that
Jackie's still in love with the girl,
and we can use her
to help us get the armour.
- What do you mean?
- Well, if Jackie brings us the
sword in exchange for the girl,
then we'll really have what we wanted...
we will then possess all five pieces.
Kidnap this girl immediately.
# Can you feel the rumble
in this feeling #
# of that thunder inside you #
# Feel the earth is quaking
the air is softly shaking #
# around you #
# Shadows on the moon,
summer's coming #
# It's she that you are meeting #
# The midnight rider comes for you #
# Now is the time.
You know it's right #
- # And it's your destiny #
# And there'll be
no more turning back #
# so take your place in history #
What are you doing?
# Something has got to change #
# When we ride, ride, ride #
# you know that nothing
will be the same #
# Midnight rider #
# When we ride, ride #
# Ride across the sky, you know
that something has got to change #
# When you ride, ride #
# When we ride, ride, ride #
# See human life, you know
that nothing can be the same #
# Midnight rider #
And now the main item in today's auction:
The legendary Sword of God said
to have been used by King Arthur
during the Crusades.
We'll start at 30,000.
I'll accept bids in increments of 5,000.
And now may I have
an opening bid, please?
Thirty-five, 40, 45.
Forty-five,
and then to 50.
Fifty, 55, 60.
Sixty-five. Now you understand this is
a priceless sword, gentlemen.
Do I hear more?
The gentleman bid 70.
Seventy. Do I hear more?
Yes? More? Gentlemen, 75.
- Do I hear more?
- 100,000.
The lady bids 100,000.
Excellent taste, madame.
100,000. Do I hear five more?
Five more?
- 105.
- 150.
One-fifty. Very generous.
At last we are approaching the true
value of this extremely precious sword.
Do I hear a bid of 155?
- Okay. Okay.
- Any advance on 150,000?
- 300,000.
Incredible.
Any advances on 300,000?
Any advances?
Ladies and gentlemen,
it has been my honor and privilege...
to have been present
at such a historical moment.
- I thank you all for your generosity.
- You're crazy!
Okay. Not 300,000!
As a formality, I am closing
the bidding at 300,000.
Going once, going twice...
- 400,000.
The lady had just
upped the price to 400.
Going once, going twice, sold!
Hi.
- Pretty nice auction, huh?
- You were lucky, too, to have sold it for so much.
- You are right.
- Nice car.
- Want a ride?
- All right.
Wait!
What's the matter?
I've changed my mind.
I really have to be going now.
My driver's waiting
over there.
- How about dinner?
- Go.
Thank you.
Room 206, please.
Thanks.
- Oh, Mr. Chan. Your messages.
- Huh?
Thank you.
Urgent. Please call back.
Need help.
Why haven't you called?
I'm booking a plane ticket.
They've got me on standby.
Imperative that you wait.
I'm on flight 101,
landing in one hour.
Waiting for cab at airport.
Hope you've received messages.
Where have you been all day?
Waiting in lobby. Matter of life or death!
"Going to sleep. Wake me when you arrive."
Jackie!
She been kidnapped?
How much they want?
I've got money.
It's not that.
If they don't want money,
how the hell can I help you?
You've come
to the wrong person.
Not when I tell you what they're after.
They want the Armour of God.
Armour of God?
Yes, and if they don't get it,
they've threatened to kill Laura.
I just sold the sword this morning.
Well, we've got to buy
it back immediately.
Look, I told you.
I already sold it.
- But I know who had two other pieces...
- Great! Even better!
They belong to Mr. Bannon.
He's a major collector of antiques.
Let's go get them.
After what you did to me,
why should I help you?
Jackie, where's your compassion?
We're talking about Laura.
Everything's over between us.
How can you be so coldhearted?
We're friends.
What makes you think
we're still friends?
What's this?
We grew up together,
played the same games, dated Laura.
We're just like brothers.
How can you treat me like a stranger?
As far as I'm concerned,
I wish we never met!
We've been through this before.
I'm not interested in talking about this anymore.
You never treated me
as a friend.
Oh. I understand.
You're jealous 'cause she's with me.
Can't stand losing?
Hmm. I really didn't lose.
Sorry. I never realized
it was that bad.
I'll just have to come up
with another plan.
The only question is,
will she be alive when I find her?
Come on! Hey, this reminds me
of that time on the beach.
Wait a minute.
I wasn't drowning.
You didn't have to throw me
that life preserver.
I was doing perfectly all right,
and you know it.
Yeah, yeah.
But didn't you call out for help?
I've told you.
It was a secret...
- Hey, what does this say?
- "Vorsicht, Rau..."
- Not sure.
- I guess we'll find out.
Is there a bell?
- Anybody home?
- Let's keep on going.
Don't move!
Down! Heel! Heel!
Easy, now. Easy.
Sit. Sit!
- Shouldn't we run?
- Just... relax.
Excuse me.
Please follow me, gentlemen.
Bye-bye.
Well, now we know what the sign says.
You sure this is the right house?
I sure hope this Bannon's in a good mood.
Otherwise, we could end up like that.
You weren't scared, were you?
Oh!
Don't worry.
He has a chain around him.
He's only let loose at night.
Gentlemen, please follow me.
This place is a zoo.
Why are they so important to you, Jackie?
Did you find a potential buyer?
- I wish that was it...
- If I might...
My fiance's been kidnapped. In exchange
for her life, they've demanded the armour.
- Kidnappers, you say?
- I'll pay you anything.
You know, you guys,
I've heard a lot of stories in my day.
But this one...
I'm not really interested in parting
with any Armour of God pieces,
but there might be a few
similar items in my collection.
- May I show you?
- No. We don't want anything else.
Uh, I'm very interested.
I'm sure there's something you'd like.
- Please come with me.
- Mmm.
Wait.
Gentlemen, follow me.
Oh, my!
This is amazing.
I've never seen such a collection.
Actually, museums
from all over the world...
frequently borrow from me
for their exhibitions.
Oh, where's the Armour of God?
Think we can have a look?
Over here.
There you are.
You've got to be kidding!
It's just lying here unguarded.
Oh, to me they're merely
simple acquisitions.
Not that everyone shares my opinion.
So tell me about Armour of God.
If it's not that important,
why keep it?
Hmm. Sit down.
Sit down.
Long before the birth of Christ,
dark forces roamed the earth.
Barbarians held power and terrorized the masses,
thus beginning the Dark Ages.
And so it remained for centuries
until the Crusaders emerged...
to wage war against
these evil cults.
Needless to say,
the Crusaders were victorious.
As a remnant of their victory,
the armour and weapons have been
handed down through the ages,
regarded as symbols of power
and much sought after.
This brings us back to the present.
Only five pieces still exist.
That's the Armour of God.
So you believe all this?
It's been rumored...
there are many groups of men
living deviously in encampments.
These men believe that, if they can obtain
all five pieces of the Armour of God...
and destroy them,
they will obtain great power.
And what do you think, Mr. Bannon?
Do you think it's within grasp?
I'm sorry. I'm afraid
I don't know the answer to that.
Well, time is moving on, gentlemen.
I was not prepared for your visit.
So if you will excuse me, please.
It's getting rather late, and you've come
such a long way, why don't you spend the night?
- I don't think we sh...
- Ah, this is such a beautiful place!
- I love it here. It would be our pleasure.
- That's fine.
Since you like it so much,
the matter is settled.
If there's anything you need,
just call my servant.
Be sure that our guests
receive the best attention.
- You two just make yourselves at home.
- Good night.
- Follow me.
Thanks.
There you go.
Well, it's too bad
we already ate...
because there's no way
we can finish all this food.
Well, maybe you're not so hungry,
but the dogs and leopards are.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- We can use the food to distract the animals.
You're kidding.
Are you suggesting we steal something?
That's exactly what I'm suggesting.
Don't even think about it.
I'm taking that armour
with or without you.
Have a little respect, huh?
Ha! Respect.
What about the kidnappers?
Do you wanna see Laura killed?
- Hey!
- Then wake up and respect our situation.
We have to get that armour back
at any cost.
Good night!
Shh. Stay.
Well, what are you going to do now?
If I move, they'll bite me.
You can relax. If I wanted them to bite,
I would have already told them to attack.
Besides, they don't eat Chinese food.
Come on!
Go on. Good boy.
It's you.
This is my daughter May.
Yes. He's the one from the auction.
Oh! You two know each other.
Well, let's open the champagne.
Hey, Jackie!
Is this what you brought
back from Africa?
- Well, is this the one? Is it?
- Put it down.
So, you captured the sword,
brought it back here,
then took it to the auction
and drove the price up.
Sir, if I knew you wanted the sword,
I would have brought it to you.
Oh, so you're accusing him
of cheating. Hmm!
And you were stealing
from my father.
He's so desperate
he cannot see straight.
Scout's honor.
I will return it in perfect shape
after I use it to rescue my fiancée.
- What now?
- I guess this is it.
Open up the gates.
I'd like to let this go, but, uh...
What if your daughter
got kidnapped, eh?
Haven't you done enough?
Go on. Tell him, Jackie.
I've had enough of these games.
There's nothing left for us to say here.
Come on. Tell him what we
talked about, remember? Hey.
All right. I'll get you a complete
set of the armour.
Um, tell them I'll be right there.
Go ahead. Do it.
The set consists of five pieces.
The kidnappers have asked for only three.
That means they may already have two.
Oh, really?
That's nothing I don't know already.
If I could prove to them
that I have three pieces,
it might entice them into
showing me the other two,
and then I'll bring you
a complete set.
- No deal.
- You know, I've got an idea.
- Mmm?
- I go with them.
- No.
- Hey. Mr. Bannon, that's a brilliant idea.
- Nothing to worry about.
- Daddy?
- Yes?
- Hmm?
All right.
But my daughter must be
in charge of this operation.
I guess there's always
a price to pay.
- I think we're going to make a great team.
- Hey.
Oh! Oh!
- Wow. It's great.
- What is it?
You won't like it.
- Let me try some.
- Go ahead.
Come on.
Don't get so depressed.
Tomorrow we'll meet those kidnappers
and free Laura, huh?
Don't forget.
I'm coming too.
Don't give me that look.
I think I can be of some help to you.
I happen to be
an excellent marksman.
I came in third
in the European pistol shoot.
Tell me, in the competition,
were there only two women?
Ooh! God! Mmm!
You don't like it?
Tastes awful.
Well, I love Chinese cheese.
Excuse me.
Jackie, this stuff's spoiled.
Sure. I know.
- What do you mean?
- Mine's real butter.
Oh.
Hmm?
Well, how will the kidnappers know we're here?
I'm not quite sure.
All they said was go to the marketplace.
Okay. Alan, you've got
to look like you're alone.
So, Jackie, don't follow him
too closely. You got that?
- Yes, May.
- Everything will work out just fine. Trust me.
I'll stake out a good spot.
Move out.
Oh, she sounds like a real professional.
She has no idea what she's doing.
They'll kill Laura if they
discover it's all a hoax.
They are not going to kill Laura.
Don't worry.
You keep forgetting.
I've done this before.
Come on.
Okay. This is it.
I'm over here.
Hey. Don't go too far.
I may need your help.
Don't worry.
Oh, nice to see you.
Hey! Hi!
Do you believe in God?
I'm waiting for someone.
Laugh off!
You must believe if you want
to see her alive again.
Laura!
Brother Mark.
So good to see you!
It's nice to see you.
Keep walking.
- All right. Where's the armour?
- Hmm. Right here.
- Give me that!
- Hey! Hold it!
You'll have it
when I get my fiancée.
- It's not here!
- What?
Oh. It was there in the car.
It must have been switched!
- Come on!
- Someone m... Help! Let go!
No! I had the stuff! I had it all!
They were...
Let go!
- What are you doing?
- Huh? Mmm.
Come on.
Huh?
Oh! Fight here.
Eh? Yeah.
Hey, Jackie.
Come over here with me and stand.
Co- me on! Right here!
Shoot him! Quick, shoot him!
Whoa!
What's she doin'?
She's trying to kill us.
What kind of plan is that?
- Let's go!
- Come on. Let's go.
- No, wait. After them.
- Huh?
Hold it.
Why are you standing there?
Get 'em!
- What do we do?
- Run.
Run? That's your idea?
Coming through!
Look out!
Go!
We should have given the real armour.
Think what they're going to do to Laura now!
- Stop whining! It won't save her.
- Shut up! I'm fed up with you!
What are we going to do now?
Laura.
Think of something,
and it better be fast.
Hey! Look out!
Watch out!
Hey! Watch out!
Over there!
No!
Hold on tight!
They're gaining on us!
Go faster!
What are you doing?
Okay, that's it!
They asked for it. Hold on!
Hey! Hey, back off!
Go! Go!
Hurry up!
Oh, my God!
They're on us! Stop!
Jackie!
That was great!
Did we lose them?
Oh.
- Oh, no.
- We're okay.
- Are you kidding me?
- I'll show you.
What? Show me what?
Jackie, what are you doing?
Jackie!
Bye-bye!
- Hurray!
- Hurray! All right!
That was just terrific!
Lucky you've got this car.
I never leave home without it.
Any table is fine.
- Three beers, please.
- Oui, oui, Monsieur. Three beers.
I think that's the guy.
You're kidding.
You think he knows something?
What the hell are we gonna do now?
The whole day is gone,
and we haven't gotten anywhere.
Yeah. You're right.
We should do something.
Three beers.
Nine hundred dinari, s'il vous plait.
- Here. Keep the change.
- Merci, Monsieur.
- Can I ask you something?
- Hmm.
- What are you saying? I'm not sure I understand.
- Try this.
Oh, 100 U.S. dollars.
Whenever I visit a new place,
I always like to ask a lot of questions.
- Am I making myself clear?
- Oh, I think I know what you mean.
This morning at the market,
I saw a few men in black robes.
How do I find them?
- They're from the monastery south of here.
- How do I...
- How far south?
- Mmm. Up the mountain.
- Oh!
- Mmm?
Hey. I think that's enough.
What do they usually do when they come,
come down from the mountain?
Oh, every Monday they come
into town to buy food,
and when they leave,
they take some of the girls with them.
- Some girls?
- Alan, okay. That's enough. Come on. Let's go.
- Oh, nothing else?
- Hey, wait!
- Jackie, what is he talking about?
- They're hookers.
Hold on.
One more question for me.
- Yes?
- Hmm!
If anyone happens to ask,
we were never here.
- Hmm?
- Hmm.
- Who are you?
- Exactly.
Here you are.
See you next month.
- Bless you, brother.
- Right. Bye-bye.
Let's get back. Oh.
Whoa!
Hey, don't! Stop that!
- How did you get here?
- What are you doing here?
Do you realize you might ruin our plan?
You're putting yourself in great danger.
I'm all right.
Don't worry.
We're going to be caught.
This means nothing to me.
The monastery.
- Oh, hi!
- Come on, ladies. Here.
Let's go.
Right this way.
No pushing.
- Hi.
- One at a time.
Blessings in the name
of wealth and power.
Using our wealth and fortitude, we must
establish a kingdom from the power of Satan.
We are gathered here as mortal beings
to follow Lucifer's path...
in search of the power that is known
as the elusive Armour of God.
I will now recite from the fourth chapter,
fifth verse of the book of Megon.
There are intruders on the grounds.
What?
Are you sure?
Yes. Move along, ladies.
Move along.
"Stoop not down, therefore,
for an abyss lies beneath the world,
reached by a descending ladder
that has seven steps,
reached by a descending pathway
that has seven gates.
There is established a world
of an evil and fatal force.
For from the canopies of the world
leaps forth the evil demon...
the evil god, the evil genius,
the evil devil.
Sir, there's strangers among us.
And the dead will rise
and smell the incense."
Carry on here.
Go forth and rejoice!
You. Come with me.
Hey, he's taking May away.
- So maybe we should just go and hide.
- What are you doing?
- Stop fooling around.
- Okay.
Remember to be happy.
Come on. Be happy.
Oh, happy day! Rejoice!
- Stop it, already!
- Hey!
- What's your problem? I was rejoicing.
- Back!
Would you knock it off?
We gotta get serious.
I'll get serious
when you get serious.
Come on. Really.
Let's find May.
May's gonna be all right.
I'm worried about Laura. Let's go.
You're still not serious.
- Don't worry, my sweet.
- What is that?
- It's now time for the plan.
- What do you mean? Leave me alone!
Inform the chief lama that we now have
successfully administered the serum...
to allow the girl to leave
the monastery as soon as possible.
Understood?
How long do you think
the drug will last?
Three days,
and during that time,
she'll be completely
under our control.
- Good.
- You will give your life to serve.
- I give my life to serve.
- You must find Jackie and bring him to us.
- Make him follow the brothers' code.
- And I must also find Jackie.
Steal the Armour of God,
and then we will set you free.
And steal the Armour of God.
Huh? What are you doing?
Oh, can I fill up
your glass for you?
- You're not a prostitute.
- Oh, yes. Yes, I am. Trust me.
- Who sent you here? Tell me.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
Come to bed.
You wanted to hit me with that bottle.
Who the hell are you anyway?
Nobody! I'm just a small town girl.
Huh?
Don't move.
How about that drink, huh?
Uh, oh, okay.
Yes, sir.
- Hey, what are we going to do?
- Act like you belong.
- What do you mean?
- Just watch.
All right.
Praise almighty Buddha.
- Buddha?
- Ha! Did you like that?
- You gotta admit that was pretty great.
- Wait.
He's right behind us.
Don't turn around.
Hey.
- What the hell did you do with the girl?
- What girl?
- Chinese girl!
- She's down there.
There's some guard by her room.
- Hey!
- Me?
- He's all yours.
- Oh!
Come on. Wake up, sir.
Come on. Wake up!
Wake up?
How about I just take these, hmm?
That's a good one.
Yes, it is.
No way.
The most I can handle is two of them.
What about the third guy?
Don't expect me to fight.
- My hand still hurts.
- What good are you?
- Damn!
- Come on!
- Will you quit fooling around?
- Oh.
This is for you.
A two-by-four?
What, you don't think I can handle them?
No, of course you can handle them.
You can soften them up,
and I'll finish them off.
Ah! Okay, but I'm using
the board under protest.
- Go!
- Hmph! Follow me.
Get the other two!
What happened?
All righty. Oh.
Thanks a lot.
- But I softened them up for you.
- Yeah. Why didn't you...
Shh!
Someone's coming.
Oh!
Ow! She hit me!
- Christ!
- How was I supposed to know?
- You okay?
- Yeah. All right.
Did they...
Are you all right?
- I can take care of myself.
- I'm glad you're okay.
Let's look for the keys.
Maybe these are what you're after?
You're fantastic!
- Aren't you glad we brought her?
- Sure.
- Help me tie 'em up?
- All right.
Lorelei!
Talk to me, Laura!
- Laura! I've been so worried!
- Laura.
Don't you recognize me?
Lorelei, talk to me.
Just tell me you're all right.
Uh, okay.
Everything's okay.
I'm taking you back with me.
- I think she must be in shock.
- You guys, we gotta hurry.
If we don't go soon,
they'll find us.
And the truck's about to go.
Come on. Let's hurry.
- There ya go.
- Here. Wear this.
- Come on!
- Let's go.
- See you next time.
- Thank you!
- Here, let me help you with that.
- I'll remember that!
- Bye! Bye!
- See you next time.
- Come back soon.
- Yeah. Bye!
- Bye!
Hmm.
Thank you.
Okay. I've booked your tickets for you.
You leave tomorrow.
Yeah.
I think we better stay here tonight.
Yes. A good night's rest will
do her good. All right, love.
You know, we still haven't gotten
what you promised my father.
Can't we talk about this later?
- About what?
- Oh, uh...
Uh, it's nothing. We'll take care of it
tomorrow. Go up and take a bath.
Yeah, yeah.
Good night.
- Good night.
- Come on.
- I'll be right back.
Hey, thanks for everything.
Hey, that's all right.
I'm just glad everything worked out.
Hey, it means more to me
than you'll ever know.
- Thanks, Jackie.
- Good night.
Good night.
Come on. Let's go.
I'm still really worried about her.
- There is something about the way she was acting.
- She'll be okay.
You know, for a while there,
I was worried something might happen to you.
Is this gonna cost me?
Sorry.
Good night.
You're kidding.
- You want to see the Armour of God now?
- Mm-hmm.
Why don't we wait
till tomorrow, all right?
- I want to see it now.
- All right, all right.
I'll be right back, okay?
What's up? I thought you were going
to bed two hours ago.
- Uh, Lorelei is, uh...
- She's what?
- What are you talking about?
- She's different.
Yeah, I noticed.
Something was wrong.
I don't know what she's been through,
but she just woke up, and she...
- Well, she woke me up, and...
- Get to the point.
Well, she says she wants to see the Armour of God.
How'd she know about it?
She could have overheard us.
She could have talked to May.
Kidnappers might have told her.
What's the big deal?
Right. You made your point.
So, should we show it to her?
I don't know.
It's in May's room.
May's bedroom.
You're fast. Oh, yeah!
- Let's go. Do you want the Armour of God or not?
- Jackie.
Go on.
Go ahead.
No answer. She must be busy.
Let's come back later.
Let's take a look, shall we?
Hey. Hello!
- She's not here.
- Let's wait outside till she comes back.
Hey, come on. Let's take it.
Lorelei's waiting. May won't even miss it.
Alan, hurry up.
- Huh?
- Uh...
Jackie,
what do you think you're doing here?
May.
Uh, oh... Mmm.
You have no business being here after what
you said to me. You're rude and inconsiderate.
You were planning to steal
the armour, weren't you?
Uh, uh, me?
Now I see why you were trying
to get close to me.
- Uh...
- Just to get your hands on the armour.
Uh, May... Oh!
I came here to apologize.
- I realize what I did was wrong.
- Why should I believe anything?
- Why not?
- Mmm! You're hopeless!
Oh, May! You know I was only joking.
- Is that all?
What do you want from me?
Why didn't you kiss me before?
- Well, I didn't think I should. Uh...
- Don't touch me!
Oh! What happened?
Uh, you're right.
I made a mistake.
I don't understand you.
Maybe we should go back
to the living room and start over again.
Well, why can't we just stay here?
It's more romantic.
Let me show you.
Come on.
The fireplace, the view.
- You know. Oh, Jackie.
- Whew!
L-Laura! Uh, uh...
Jackie?
Alan and Laura
have taken the Armour.
Why?
I'm going to find out.
- Well, can I help you?
- Yes. Here's what you do.
Alan. Alan!
They must've heard something.
All right now! Quiet!
- See anything?
- No.
No, it's nothing.
Goin' back.
Alan. Shh.
- Jackie!
- Cowboy.
Hi.
Don't worry.
You'll be all right.
I will get you out.
- What did you call him?
- Cowboy.
That's what
she used to call me.
Super.
Isn't this special.
Look.
Let's not get into this right now.
Well, here we go again.
You're always being the hero.
I'll tell you what.
Do you really want to be a hero?
You bet.
How do we get out of here?
I'll go with Lorelei.
Guess you have to find your own way out.
My own way out?
I promised that I will try to save Laura.
I didn't say I'd save you.
So. You backstabbing pig you.
This is the chance
you've been waiting for, isn't it?
And after all we've been through.
I can't believe this is it.
I thought that,
after all these years,
you and I would always be friends.
That's enough of your sob story.
Let's get out of here quick.
We must help him.
We can't leave him here.
Laura, forget about me.
Get out.
No matter what,
I still love you.
Jackie, how can you do this?
You must understand,
when you kissed me the other night,
I realized that we
were meant to be together.
The only real thing
standing in my way is Alan.
So I have come to claim
what's rightfully mine.
Yes, you're right.
I'm sorry I ever came between you.
I'm truly sorry
for what I put you through.
You deserve her
far more than me.
Laura, leave me alone and go.
Follow Jackie.
I want you to lead a happy life,
my darling.
That's all I want.
Please go.
Alan, I love you so.
You have a good heart.
I'd rather die with him
than go with you.
Great. You know,
ever since I left the group,
I wondered if you really loved her.
For years, it bothered me.
Now I'm happy to see your love is true.
Come on, you two.
Let's go.
All three of us,
back together again?
Yeah,
three of us against a hundred of them.
Well, I can hardly wait.
Look, I came to get the Armour of God.
You know that we only borrowed it,
and I promised to bring it back.
Forget about the Armour of God.
We should get out.
We'll get out, all right,
with the Armour, and I will show you the way.
Great. I hope we make it.
- Stay close behind me.
- I'm ready. Stay close...
I'm ready.
Hey, hey. I think this way's better.
- Fine. Go that way.
- See? He never listens to me.
Where are you going?
Now, as soon as you get out of here, look for May.
She will be waiting for you.
- You'll be there?
- Me?
We'll just have to wait and see.
Don't you listen to him, Laura.
He's already working on a plan as we speak.
You take the tunnel on the right
and find your way out.
- Find our way out?
- May's waiting.
- You really want me to give a knife to May?
- Very funny.
What are you trying to say?
You never take me seriously.
We've been through this already.
You're hopeless.
I didn't ask you to come untie me.
I can take care of Lorelei.
First it's a two-by-four,
then you stick a knife in my face.
Take it back.
I don't need this knife!
Jackie.
Down there?
Stand back! I have a knife.
Get back!
Go on. Go!
Some of you men search.
See if there are
any more intruders. Go.
Ooh.
Heavy.
After him.
- Go after him!
- Jackie!
Let go!
Don't fight!
Those are my good pants!
Let go of me!
Let go!
Get off!
Now tell us how you got here!
On with it.
- Jackie!
- Take Laura with you!
Go! Get out!
Quick, behind you!
- Jackie! Be careful!
- Come on! Let's go!
After him.
All right.
Surround him.
Wait! Hold on.
No, no. Wait!
Aah!
Quick.
Back! Back!
- Back!
- Here.
- Oh.
- Aah!
I'll keep them busy.
You run for it.
Shouldn't we take some time
and think it over?
When I count to three, run.
One, two, three.
Let's get out of here!
Grab my hand!
Quick!
Easy! Easy!
Where do you think you're going?
I was just getting started!
- Hey!
- Come on. Let's get him.
Come on. Don't let him get away.
- See anything?
- No.
I looked upstairs.
I can't see a thing.
- How about over there?
- No. Where is he?
- Heading up.
- Hello.
- Wait! There he is!
- Get him!
I'm so glad
that you could join me.
- So you are the Asian Hawk?
- Correct.
We're honored
with your presence.
Let's stop playing games
and get down to business, okay?
What business?
I already have everything I want.
You don't really think I'm going to leave
without the Armour of God, do you?
I don't really think
you'll be leaving at all.
I'm not going to let you
get away with this.
For centuries you've tried to secure
the power of the Armour of God.
And now that you have them,
you think the world is yours. Over my dead body.
Now, that shouldn't be a problem to achieve.
Stop wasting my time.
You know, if it's real power you're after,
perhaps I can...
interest you in some... money?
Money.
I live only for the thrill of destruction.
Kill him.
Now are you ready for death?
You think you're so smart,
getting girls to defend you?
Ah, you never cease to amaze me.
Such an honorable gentleman,
always thinking of the ladies.
But don't let their looks deceive you.
They are merciless killing machines.
You'll surely die.
It's not about honor.
It's about respect for your fellow man.
You think that killing
is a proper means to an end?
But I'd rather die
than follow those beliefs.
Your attempts to spread evil
will go no further, so help me, God.
Ooh!
Uh?
Sorry.
Aah...
I guess I'll take the Armour of God
and hit the road. What do you think?
No, no. Surely you don't think
our business is completed here, do you?
What else you got?
I've had enough of him!
Hold it!
- All right.
- All right?
Get him!
Ooh!
Excuse me.
Need a light?
Last chance.
This is it.
All right.
So, we will all die.
We won't die, men.
I promise you that he's bluffing.
Rise up and defeat him.
Time to call my bluff.
Haven't you had enough of this?
- I guess you must be...
- Oh, my God!
Get me some water!
Wait!
Ooh! God!
Whew!
Uh-oh. Oh!
Whoa!
Quick, hurry!
Hurry!
Whoa!
# Out of the east a dream comes #
# out from the sky #
# Setting me free #
- Are you all right?
- # Through the clouds #
# I will fly #
# The mountains must yield to me #
# Thunder will roar #
# The sound wakes the universe #
# Dragon will soar #
# High up, on high #
# I reach for high up, on high #
# Into the sky #
# I charge on into the sky #
# High up, on high #
# I reach for high up, on high #
# Into the sky #
# I charge on into the sky #
# Out of the east #
# A dream comes out from the sky #
# Setting me free #
# Through the clouds I will fly #
# The mountains must yield to me #
# Thunder will roar #
# The sound wakes the universe #
# Dragon will soar #
# High up, on high #
# I reach for high up, on high #
# Into the sky #
# I charge on into the sky #
# High up, on high #
# I reach for high up, on high #
# Into the sky #
# I charge on into the sky #
# We touch the clouds #
# The tiger with me will ride #
# Our hearts as one #
# Power right at my side #
# The future before us lies Magical door #
# Along with the tiger's way #
# Dragon will soar #
# High up, on high #
# I reach for high up, on high #
# Into the sky I charge on #
# Into the sky #
# High up, on high #
# I reach for high up, on high #
# Into the sky #
# I charge on into the sky #
# We touch the clouds #
# The tiger with me will ride #
# Our hearts as one #
# Power right at my side #
# The future before us lies #
# Magical door #
# Along with the tiger's way #
# Dragon will soar #
# High up, on high #
# I reach for high up, on high #
# Into the sky #
# I charge on into the sky #
# High up, on high #
# I reach for high up, on high #