Presented by IM Pictures
Produced by Popcorn Film
Producer
HAN Seong-gu
There once lived a mean
cuckoo guy named Young-Dal.
His wife died giving birth to
their daughter Il-mae.
Since then, it was my mother who
breast fed her and raised her.
From our birth on,
she was my destined partner
who stole half of my milk.
That's how
my first love began.
Crazy First Love
Teacher, can we stay closer?
You punks! Keep your distance!
You all are a bunch of animals
with too much testosterone.
Tes... what? What's that?
Joo, Young-dal must keep
his words with Sohn Tae-il!
My dear ladies!
You all know me, right?
Sophomore at Kang High School
Class 7, number 58
SOHN Tae-il!!
Promises are supposed to be kept.
Especially, words from a teacher
who is a role model!
How can he break his promise?
At this moment,
In the presence of Buddha, Jesus
and all other Gods in the world,
I accuse Mr. JOO Young-dal,
a teacher at Kang High,
of breaking his solemn promise!
10 years ago,
our teacher Mr. JOO promised me,
"Just wait till you have some
hairs on your balls!
When that happens, you can marry
my daughter Il-mae!"
Il-mae! My pubic hair started
growing when I was thirteen!
So, I ran to your dad
right away.
"Look! I have the pubic hair
Now, hand over Il-mae
like you promised!"
But, what did you say? Teacher?
"That's not it!
It's just hair attached to your body.
You wanna see my real ones?"
Fine. Let's just say it was just hair.
But now, tell me what
covers me down there.
You wanna call them a bunch
of black threads?
Teacher, do you wanna
check it out?
Show us! Show us!
Il-mae! Look!
Do they look like threads to you?
Testosterone is a type of
male hormone...
that can turn a normal kid like Tae-il
into a wild animal in a snap!
- Ready?
- Ready.
Let's go!
What the...?
- Boss!
- Kneel down!
Was it you that broke into
my territory and beat up
my boys in open daylight?
and beat up my boys?
What do you want?
I'm a righteous warrior!
You little shit.
You're from Kang High?
So am I. Is that why you're here?
Cut the bullshit.
Are you gonna take me in or not?
How's Mr. JOO?
Why the hell did you bring up
his name?
Stay still!
Teacher, what's happening to
our school?
I'm a gangster now, but
I graduated high school though.
Teach them a lesson!
Especially that curly hair!
48th year class
Byun, Kang-chul!
Yes, sir.
Get down!
What?
Because of little shits like you
these kids wanna be gangsters.
Listen! Urgent news!
- Tae-il from Kang High...
- What about him?
He went to the boss of the market
area and asked him to take him in.
- For real?
- But the boss told Il-mae's
dad on him
and now he's getting
his ass whipped.
Pants down!
On your stomach!
Do you guys hear my heart?
It's crying out in pain.
Ouch! Ouch!
If my heart hurts this much, then
how would your parents feel?
Right, Tae-il?
You haven't changed a bit, sir.
I'm so happy to see you again.
Your mother works so hard
selling fish at the marketplace to...
Feed me and to send me to school.
So what?
You little brat!
Are you giving me dirty look
during my admonition?
You wanna lose your eyes?
Sir, I apologize.
Even an animal like a crow
appreciates the love of its parents.
Then what bird are you, teacher?
You didn't keep your words.
What did you say?
You think I sold fish at the market
to make you a gang?
Il-mae! What did you eat to grow?
Milk.
What kind of milk? Cow milk?
No. Your breast milk.
After all I've done for you,
how could you seduce my son?
Ma'am, you got it wrong.
Il-mae didn't do anything.
She ruined my boy's life...
Go inside.
Teacher, why don't you just expel him
from school?
He's only causing more trouble
staying in school...
Look at me.
You can't even look at me.
Pretty embarrassing, huh?
Face is busted by a gang and
ass is whipped by my dad,
and your back is beaten
by your mother.
Let me see your back!
Why do you live like this?
I'm gonna show him...
how his unkept promise
brings me down.
You're crazy!
What am I supposed to do?
You rank in top 3,000 nationwide
but I'm not even in top 300,000.
And everyday, you get prettier
and I get uglier.
You're slipping away from me
and... Shit!
There's nothing I can do
What am I supposed to do with you?
Shut up! Stop whining!
...even when you're angry,
you look beautiful.
What?
When I think of your pretty face,
I can't control myself!
I can't sleep nor eat!
When I open a book,
the words turn into your face!
You're so goddamn pretty and my
body is boiling with hot blood.
What am I supposed to do?
I've never seen a student
as unruly as Sohn Tae-il.
And what's worse is that
our naive students worship him,
and it'll keep creating someone
just like him.
it's time to pull out our swords
and eliminate the bad wolf!
We agree with you, Mr. Principal.
Let's hear from his homeroom teacher.
Every teenager has a bit of wolf
within himself.
To achieve peace in our school,
we should take this chance
to emasculate them all!
Even the sheepish kids!
Testosterone!!
Teacher, you'll pick a husband
for Il-mae through open contest?
For real? Awesome!
Shit!
Teacher! Isn't she Tae-il's girl?
Since he entered high school,
suspended from school 3 times!
Disciplinary confinement 7 times!
Lewdness in public
Intoxication, unlawful entry
and attempted kidnapping
Plus, he's in the bottom
with an IQ of 148 and
preoccupied with joining a gangster.
If you were in my shoes, would
you give your daughter to him?
No way!
Teacher!
What are the requirements?
Requirements? It can be anyone
Just improve your scores
up to my daughter's.
The day you bring me
your report card,
you will marry my daughter.
Understood?
Yes, sir!
Yes? You got a question?
As a man to man! One on one!
Are you challenging me?
Why? You scared?
Where are you going?
You challenged me!
Here I come!
You little punk!
You're nothing!
You can't even swing one punch.
How dare you want my daughter?
- Teacher!
- I'm here.
- That's water.
I'd rather die with you
than lose her to someone.
You are unbelievable
You said you're gonna be a fisherman,
but can't even swim!
You're hopeless!
Teacher, what do I have to do?
Please tell me what I have to do.
to beat 300,000 kids in 2 years.
Please tell me!
Give it up!
I'll die if you ask me to die
Please tell me!
It won't happen to someone like you
Teacher, please tell me!
I said, it won't.
It's impossible! Impossible!
Ouch! What are you hitting me?
It stings!
Sleep only 3 hours a day.
Then, in 3 days, you will nosebleed.
If you nosebleed everyday
till you graduate,
Then my girl will be yours.
I guarantee!
Teacher, I'll nosebleed everyday.
Il-mae is mine.
You can't give her
to anybody else. Ok? Dad?
I got it.
Gees... You're so heavy.
You see the spot I'm on
Marked with white paint?
Yes, teacher!
This is the spot,
where you freshmen's proud 6 year
senior SOHN Tae-il fell down
bleeding from both nostrils with
college exam scores in his hand.
That's when I found out
a man can survive
way too much nosebleeding.
You all know the proud tradition
of our Kang High, right?
Yes, sir!
Say it!
One! We don't have
guidance department!
And?
One! We're the worst enemy
of the Red Cross!
That's how it happened!
When Tae-il made top 3,000,
and got early accepted to Seoul
National University,
our principal said to the
Department of Education,
"Our students study so hard and
nosebleed everyday,
they don't have any blood to
donate!
From now on, Kang High is the
worst enemy of the Red Cross!"
Goddamn persistent kid!
Worse than a leech!
Father in-law!
Let's set the wedding date...
dad?
First, go to college.
Welcome! Welcome!
This is Seoul National University!
My school!
I got into the law school,
like you told me to.
So, let me marry her now!
Il-mae's college expels students
who get married before graduating.
You're joking, right?
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Now I'm in a law school, he's gonna
ask me to pass the bar exam,
Then finish the judicial trainings
And after that,
who knows what excuse
he's gonna come up with.
SOHN Tae-il!! Stop right there!
Where are we going?
Let's do it! Let's make a baby!
Are you crazy?
What?
I can't betray my dad like that!
What about me, then?
Math workbook pg.216, #14-8!
What are all critical points,
if there are any, of a function
where k (t) equals to one divide by
the square root of "t" minus
squared positive one?
Answer!
its critical point is
(0, 1).
Buddha, the God of Mercy...
Name, SOHN Tae-il!
Il-mae!
Is he ok?
Exactly then, you know
what your father said to me?
"C'mon, Tae-il!
Just a bit more!"
What am I? His slave?
If I keep listening to your dad,
then I'm gonna die as a virgin!
Let's go in! What the...!
You kidnap my daughter
in open daylight?
You crazy punk!
We're gonna have a baby first.
Have what?
Dad! Tae-il!
Stop right there! You little shit.
You think you can run away?
Kneel down!
Release him.
We have laws in this country!
You think you can get away with
abduction and physical assault?
I've lived well without any laws.
You piece of shit didn't pass
the bar exam yet, so what the hell
do you know about the law?
This is your mother in law.
Give her a bow.
Mom! Look how bad he's treating
one and only son in law.
If she were alive,
she'd be in her early 40's
But I only remember her as
a high school girl who likes fast food.
You mean...
That's right.
We both were in high school
when she got pregnant.
I don't like you! No, I fear you!
You're just like how I used to be.
You don't know anything about her.
About her pain and suffering...
What you see is all you know.
Is that real love?
Bull shit!
You're just pleasing yourself.
Look at me!
I loved Il-mae's mom to death...
but she was gone at 18!
If you really love her, then you
have to know how to protect her!
Tae-il!
Yes, sir!
Il-mae isn't going anywhere.
I swear I'll keep her safe.
So, can she stay with me just
a little longer?
Can you please leave her with me
just a little longer?
Teacher...
I'll protect her!
Up until I graduate and
pass the bar exam,
I won't even touch her hair!
Thanks.
Kiss... I'll allow kissing.
Nonsense! If I kiss her, then
I'd wanna touch her boobs.
And if I touch her boobs, then I'll cross
the line that I must not cross.
Until the day you give Il-mae's hand
to me, I'll keep her intact, and virgin!
Tae-il!
What a lie!
She is a slut.
She slept with me a lot
when she's in high school.
She wasn't even a virgin
when we first had sex.
She already had abortions,
even five times!
And her tube got so damaged
that she can't even have a baby.
How do you know her so well?
How? She's my first love
and so am I to her.
Out my window, I can see
Il-mae's room well.
That's my room.
Well done, Tae-il.
I protect my girl, sir!
Il-mae, I had a really good time tonight.
I'm sorry about...
That's ok. Your friend Tae-il
always adds thrill to our date.
I don't see him.
Tae-il! You!!
Shit!
I'm gonna get wrinkled and die
as a virgin without kissing a man
Why don't you go for Tae-il?
Tae-il?
Do you really love me?
If you really love me,
if you can hear my heart,
then please look at me.
Stop that gibberish.
You really gonna be like this?
You're an animal with
too much testosterone!
Patience!
Other boys? I hooked up
Yonsei University boys
with girls from Sookmyung University.
Only Ewha girls here!
I'm the only one who stands up to pee.
So no need to worry, sir!
How do you manage to
prepare for the bar exam?
I brought everything with me.
I'm confident in memorizing
with my IQ, I gotta go, bye!
How do you say "Eat it while
it's warm" in local dialect?
Slurp it while it's hot.
Let's see, where is Il-mae's
cold medicine?
It's her shampoo, snacks.
Where is it? Oh, here it is.
Hello! It's time for my girl
to take her medicine!
Il-mae!
She went swimming with a boy
she met in the lobby.
I can't even leave her alone
for 2 seconds!
Don't you think it's way
too much sexy?
Not at all. I have to knock him.
out with one punch!
Il-mae! JOO Il-mae!
SOHN Tae-il! Let's see
who's gonna win this time!
Where is that bastard?
What... what are you doing?
Thanks, Tae-il.
For... for what?
For looking after me till now.
You don't have to do it anymore.
This is our last trip of
our college years.
I want to make a memorable moment
with you! Right now!
Here?
Tae-il.
Teacher, please forgive me!
Wake up!
Too much testosterone!
Cover up yourself well
before you come out.
Stop right there!
I can't move anyway.
Tae-il, if you walk out on me now
then it's over.
You might never see me again!
Do you hear me?
Calm down and come out!
After giving you your medication,
I've got a lot to study tonight!
You fool! What's so important
about that stupid promise?
I need you... right now...
There might not be next time...
Stupid...
- Are you telling the truth?
- Yes, sir!
You finally did it!
Everyone! Tae-il passed
the level 1 bar exam.
Sir, Il-mae is really mine, right?
Of course! She's all yours!
Where are you?
Are you with her?
My whereabouts is a top secret.
I'm preparing a present for her.
Ouch... Be careful, will you?
Alright. We're giving you a cool
finishing stitches.