Listen Hyuga.
Why don't you come to Tangou?
What?
It's my hometown.
We'll have Azumi come, too.
Tangou?
Sorry, Yae. I may not be
able to come to Tangou.
I thought this smell was familiar.
I guess my sense of smell
is as sharp as a dog's.
Who are you?
Me? I'm Bijomaru Mogami.
We just finished off three guys,
now a newcomer.
I hate to break up such a nice
romantic scene, but I want you to die.
She has nothing to do with us.
Let her go.
Sorry, no.
Being slashed before the girl you like
and exposing your misery
will increase your pain
and suffering all the more.
What did you say?
Have you ever thought of
yourself being slashed?
Blood comes gushing out.
No matter how much you endure,
it's useless, you know
you are going to die.
You want to die quickly, but you can't.
What will you think then?
One sword is broken.
That's no good.
Saru, loan your sword to him.
It's no fun slaying an enemy
who is not properly armed.
Don't worry.
We have no business with the girl.
I would be offended if you blame your
defeat on fighting with only one sword.
Do you know why this sword
does not have a hand guard?
I never defend. I will
immobilize you with one blow.
I was also taught to do as much.
I am totally thrilled!
You are quite quick.
But you failed to notice that
you are cut?
Don't come! Run!
Don't move! Stay and watch!
If you run, I will kil you.
It hurts, right?
Do you want to die quickly?
I won't let you die so easily.
Enough of that. The fight is over.
Monkey-face!
If you spoil my fun,
you will die, too.
Go ahead
Your bad taste creeps me out.
Hyuga!
Pity to leave her on her own.
Bijomaru!
What significance is there to kill
a girl who has nothing to do with this?
What significance is there to live,
anyway?
Shall we go?
The next one better be stronger!
If not, then I will fight against you!
You got that, Monkey-face?
He fought master fully.
We'll wait for Nagato here.
Yes.
He said you were sweet.
He wanted to stay with you
a bit longer.
Hyuga truly liked you.
What will you do now?
Will you seek revenge?
The friend of your enemy
will come to kill you.
A never-ending story. Will you
continue to kill each other forever?
There are many evil people in the world.
Someone has to kill them.
It doesn't have to be you.
Someone else can take care of it.
Frightenly good swordsman...
he's already killed one assassin.
But I can hardly like him.
In fact, I hate him.
Don't be so harsh. Saru,
I want you to do something.
The final showdown will be in Gamo.
- I wonder how they are doing.
- They are dead.
That's not true.
They will definitely come.
Master Gessai,
Kiyomasa is heading for Gamo.
Gamo?
It's a ship
He plans to leave Gamo by ship.
We must get him in Gamo, on land.
But the enemy is aware of our moves.
They won't sit still.
I know. We have no choice
but to start the attack.
Take these.
They might be of use at some point.
- Great!
- Be careful.
If they explode too close to you,
you'll be blown to bits.
Don't touch me!
Farewell.
I am counting on you.
You have a beautiful face.
How much is your ass?
You want to die that much?
Don't kill our allies recklessly.
Money!
Do you want more money?
We need your help.
You guys help us a little, and
more money and rewards will be yours.
Look, when we cross those mountains,
it'll only take 5 days to reach Tangou.
I see.
You will get to see your
mother soon, Yae.
Mother...
You don't know your mother?
Ever since I was little,
I've been with Master and everyone.
- Put this on.
- Girl's clothing.
I prefer this. This is more convenient
for hiding my swords.
You are a girl.
- I'm-
- Girls don't talk like that!
Stay still!
There we go.
You look beautiful.
Don't say that!
Azumi.
The swords don't suit you.
I don't want to see another person die.
Kiyomasa is in the mansion.
Let's go.
Master!
Okay, spread out!
I won't let you get away!
My nose is that of a dog's.
It's me, assholes!
That bastard.
I'll get him.
It's incredible you made it this far.
Why won't you finish him off?
If I kill him, he won't be of any
use to us as bait.
Did you say bait?
A few more assassins need
to be killed.
Master!
Ukiha!
Run, run away.
Wait for the next opportunity!
Run away, I want you to
complete your mission.
What are you doing? Run away quickly.
Don't worry about me. Go, go!
Run!
Smells nice.
Be quiet.
How fortunate we are on
a mountain like this.
Which one should I pick?
Stop it.
Stop it? Okay, I'll stop it. I pick you.
Taro, I'll give you this one.
No matter how much I try to escape...
...I can't avoid it.
Even if I don't want to kill...
...I am forced to kill.
You bitch!
I'm sorry, Yae...
I have no...
...choice but this.
If it weren't for Master,
I would never have lived.
He will protect you.
He always will.
I am going to wait for you.
I'll be waiting for you in Tangou.
If you hadn't been injured,
our fight would have been more fun.
It's a pity I can't stay and fight
your assassins.
Saru, I'll leave the rest to you.
Assassins are not going to show up
no matter how long we wait.
Such heavy security
for a few assassins.
General Kanbei is too cautious.
I'll be back.
Hey wait a minute.
You just took a break a while ago.
It's my turn now.
Let's decide with this.
- I'll bet on tails.
- Then I'll bet on heads.
I hear the strongest one
is still alive.
I can't wait.
Hey old man,
are you still alive?
Stop it.
You annoy me constantly.
Are you ready to die now?
Do you really think someone will come
and rescue a dying old man like you?
Huh, old man?
She's already here.
Azumi.
Don't come! Don't!
No, you must come.
Otherwise, he will die.
Damn you!
Wow! Incredible,
she is just incredible
Hey! Samurai bastards!
Who are you aiming at?
Damn it, who do you think we are?
Just because you're Samurai,
don't act so damned important.
This is bullshit!
This is our town!
Never mind about her, let's get them!
This is getting to be fun!
What the hell is your problem?
This fire ball will blow
everyone up into pieces.
Let's ignite this!
Oh, no...
I am delighted.
No one is left to disturb us.
How splendid!
I didn't even scratch you.
This is the first time I've had
to defend.
You are wonderful.
Why not die?
Master.
It's over. Everything is over.
Ukiha and Nagara are both dead.
But I'm still here.
There is no further mission
that you need to pursue.
From now on, live as you wish.
Survive and keep on living.
Master,
I don't know what to do without you.
You never used to cry.
It's so quiet.
Master.
No, don't.
Master!
Where do the stars go during the day?
Time to eat!
Let's go!
The stars are always there.
You can't see them during the day,
but the stars are always watching
over us from up above the sky.
Even if we get separated one day,
we will always be together.
I'll be watching over you at all times.
Kanbei.
It's been a stimulating journey.
Saru is not back yet.
We can't let our guard down.
I can't be scared of assassins!
When it's time to die, you die.
Don't worry.
Lord, you won't die so easily.
Your luck is too strong.
Kanbei,
the time has come for war.
That stupid old Ieyasu...
we will blow him up into pieces.
You have done well in protecting me.
Once we get home,
I'll take you to
a hot spring for some rest.
Masterful!
Lord!
Nagara.
What are you doing?
We are the only two left.
What shall we do now?
Nagamasa Asano, Kiyomasa Kato...
the next tar get is Masayuki Sanada.
This time, we'll probably be killed.
We are not going to die.
We will survive.
Everyone is with us.
Let's go.