Hey, baby, what's going on here?
Oh, hi.
Miss Gorightly!
Some day... Some day...!
You go to the powder room
and that's the last I see.
- Now, Harry...
- Harry was the other guy.
I'm Sid Arbuck.
You like me, remember?
Miss Gorightly! I protest!
Darling, I am sorry,
but I lost my key.
That was two weeks ago.
You cannot keep ringing my bell.
You disturb me!
You must have a key made!
But I just lose them all.
- Come on. You like me.
- I worship you, Mr Arbuck.
- Good night.
- Wait! What is this?
You like me. I'm a liked guy.
You like me. I picked up
the cheque for five people...
Your friends.
When you wanted change for
the powder room I gave you $50.
That gives me rights.
In 30 seconds I call the police!
All the time, disturbance!
I get no sleep!
I got to get my rest! I'm an artist!
I going to call vice squad on you!
Don't be angry. I won't do it again.
I might let you take those pictures.
When?
Some time.
Any time.
Good night.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I couldn't get the door open.
I guess they sent me
the upstairs key.
I couldn't get the
downstairs door open.
I said, I guess they sent me
the...upstairs key.
I couldn't get the downstairs
door open. Sorry to wake you.
That's all right.
It could happen to anyone...
frequently does. Good night.
I hate to...
I hate to bother you,
but could I use the phone?
Sure.
Why not?
Thank you.
Well, this is a...
nice little place you've got here.
You just moved in, too, huh?
I've been here about a year.
Phone's over there.
Well, it was.
Oh, I remember.
I stuck it in the suitcase
to muffle the sound.
I'm...sorry.
Is he all right?
Sure. He's OK, aren't you, cat?
Poor old cat.
Poor slob. Poor slob without a name.
I don't have the right
to give him one.
We don't own each other.
We just met one day.
I won't own anything
until I find a place where
me and things go together.
I'm not sure where that is,
but I know what it's like.
It's like Tiffany's.
Tiffany's?
You mean the jewellery store?
That's right.
I'm crazy about Tiffany's.
Listen.
You know those days
when you get the mean reds?
The mean reds? You mean the blues?
The blues are when you're fat
or it's raining, that's all.
The mean reds are horrible.
Suddenly, you're afraid
and don't know what of.
- Do you ever get that feeling?
- Sure.
When I get it, all that does any good
is to jump in a cab to Tiffany's.
Calms me down right away.
The quietness and proudness of it.
Nothing bad could happen there.
If I could find a real place
that made me feel
like Tiffany's, then...
I'd buy some furniture
and give the cat a name.
I'm sorry. You wanted something.
The telephone.
I was supposed to meet somebody.
This is 10:00 Thursday morning?
I just got off a plane.
I'm not sure.
Thursday. Is this Thursday?
- I think so.
- It can't be!
It's too gruesome!
Well, what's so gruesome
about Thursday?
I never remember when it's coming up.
Wednesdays,
I generally don't go to bed
because I have to catch the 10:45.
They're so particular
about visiting hours.
Be a darling and look under the bed
for a pair of alligator shoes.
I've got to do something
about how I look.
I can't go to Sing Sing
with a green face.
Sing Sing?
It's a ridiculous name for a prison.
Sounds more like an opera house.
Black, alligator.
All the visitors make an effort
to look their best.
It's touching, the women wearing
their prettiest things.
I love them for it.
And I love the kids, too.
It should be sad seeing kids
there, but it isn't.
They have ribbons in their hair
and shine on their shoes.
As I understand it,
you're going to visit somebody
at Sing Sing.
You can tell what kind of person
a man thinks you are
by the earrings he gives you.
I must say, the mind reels.
- May I ask whom?
- Whom I'm going to visit?
I guess that's what I mean.
I don't know if I should say.
They never told me not to.
Cross your heart and kiss your elbow.
I'll try.
You probably read about him -
Sally Tomato.
Sally Tomato?
Don't look so shocked.
They couldn't prove
he was in the Mafia,
much less head of it.
They only proved
he cheated his income tax.
He's a darling old man.
He wasn't my lover or anything.
I never knew him until
after he was in prison.
I've seen him every Thursday
for seven months.
I'd go even if he didn't pay me.
- Shoes.
- I only found one.
- He pays you?
- That's right. His lawyer does.
If he is a lawyer, which I doubt.
He only has an answering service
and always wants to meet
at Hamburger Heaven.
There you are, you sneak. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Dress... Dress...
Here we are... Bag.
And a hat, too.
There we are.
Anyway, seven months ago,
this so-called lawyer
asked if I'd like
to cheer up an old man
and pick up 100 a week.
I told him, "You've got
the wrong Holly Golightly."
I do as well on trips
to the powder room.
Any chic gentleman will give
a girl $50 for the powder room.
And cab fare, that's another 50.
Then he said his client
was Sally Tomato.
Sally had seen me somewhere
and had admired me à la distance.
It would be a good deed to visit him.
How could I say no?
It was so wildly romantic.
How do I look?
Very good. I must say I'm amazed.
I could never have
done it without you.
Bag...
Call me any time.
I'm just upstairs,
as soon as I get moved in.
Bye, cat.
You mean he gives you $100
for an hour's conversation?
Mr O'Shaughnessy does when
I give him the weather report.
It's none of my business,
but you could get in trouble.
Hold this for me.
And what do you mean,
weather report?
Just a message
I give Mr O'Shaughnessy,
so he knows I've been there.
Sally tells me things to say like...
"There's a hurricane in Cuba",
"cloudy over Palermo",
things like that.
Don't worry. I've taken care
of myself for a long time.
Taxi!
- I never could do that.
- It's easy.
Paul.
I'm late. I know it.
Were you locked out?
Didn't you get the key?
Oh, darling. I'm so sorry.
No, I got the key.
Miss Golightly, my neighbour,
kindly let me in.
Miss Golightly's
on her way to Sing Sing.
Just visiting, of course.
Miss Golightly,
Mrs. Falenson, my...decorator.
- How do you do?
Darling. Let me look at you.
- Are you through?
- Was the flight ghastly?
Grand Central station,
and step on it, darling.
Is it only three weeks
since I left you in Rome?
Seems like years.
- You seen the apartment?
- Not yet.
It was wicked of me,
but I couldn't resist.
I fixed it up without you.
I think it's darling,
but if you absolutely hate it,
we can start from scratch.
Hey, baby! Where you going?
Come on, baby. Open the door.
Ah, be a pal!
You're breaking up a beautiful party.
Come on, baby. Open the door.
Hey, the band's swinging.
Aw, come on, baby.
Once again, I must protest!
If you don't stop
that phonograph now,
I'm going to call
the police department!
Yeah. That's more better.
What's the matter, baby?
Come on. You're a great kid.
Open the door.
Come on, baby. I'm waiting for you.
- It's only me.
- Wait a minute. Miss...
Golightly. Holly Golightly.
I live downstairs.
We met this morning, remember?
Yeah.
It's OK. She's gone.
She works late hours for a decorator.
There's the most
terrifying man downstairs.
He's sweet when he isn't drunk,
but some vino,
and, golly, quel beast.
It got so tiresome,
I went out the window.
You can throw me out if you want,
but you looked so cosy
and your friend had gone,
and it was getting cold out there.
And I'd heard people in New York
never get to know their neighbours.
Well, how was Sing Sing?
Fine. I made the train
and everything.
And what's the weather report?
Small-craft warnings,
Block Island to Hatteras...
whatever that means.
You know, you're sweet.
You really are.
And you look a little
like my brother Fred.
Do you mind if I call you Fred?
Not at all.
300. She's very generous.
Is it by the week, hour or what?
The party's over. Out.
Oh, Fred. Darling Fred, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt
your feelings. Don't be angry.
I was just saying I understand.
I understand completely.
Stick around. Make yourself a drink.
- Throw me my robe.
- Stay where you are.
You must be absolutely exhausted.
I mean, it's late,
and you were sound asleep
and everything.
I suppose you think
I'm très fou or something.
No fouer than anybody else.
Yes, you do. Everybody does.
I don't mind.
It's useful being top banana
in the shock department.
What do you do, anyway?
- I'm a writer, I guess.
- You guess? Don't you know?
OK. Positive statement.
Ringing affirmative.
I'm a writer.
The only writer I've ever been
out with is Benny Shacklett.
He's written a lot of TV stuff,
but quel rat.
Tell me, are you a real writer?
I mean, does anybody buy
what you write or anything?
They bought what's in that box.
Yours?
All these books?
There's just the one book,
12 copies of it.
"Nine Lives" by Paul Varjak.
They're stories.
Nine of them.
Tell me one.
They're not the kind you can tell.
Too dirty?
Yeah, I suppose they're dirty, too,
but only incidentally.
Mainly they're angry,
sensitive, intensely felt,
and that dirtiest
of all words - promising.
So said The Times Book Review,
October 1, 1956.
- 1956?
- That's right.
This a ratty question, but what
have you written lately?
Lately, I've been working on a novel.
- Lately, since 1956?
- It takes time.
- I want to get it right.
- So no more stories.
I'm supposed to not fritter
my talent on little things.
I'm saving it for the big one.
Do you write every day?
Sure.
- Today?
- Sure.
It's a beautiful typewriter.
Of course.
It writes nothing but sensitive,
intensely felt, promising prose.
There's no ribbon in it.
There isn't?
No.
Something you said this morning
has bothered me all day.
What's that?
Do they really give you $50
for the powder room?
Of course.
You must do very well.
I'm trying to save,
but I'm not very good at it.
You know, you do look
a lot like my brother Fred.
I haven't seen him since
I was 14, when I left home.
He was already 6'2".
It must have been
the peanut butter that did it.
Everybody thought he was dotty,
the way he ate peanut butter.
But he wasn't dotty,
just sweet and vague
and...terribly slow.
Poor Fred. He's in the army now.
It's best until I get enough money.
- And then?
- And then Fred and I...
I went to Mexico once.
It's a wonderful place
for raising horses.
I saw one place near the sea that...
Fred's very good with horses.
Even land in Mexico costs something.
Whatever I do, there's never
more than $200 in the bank.
It can't be 4:30.
It just can't.
Do you mind if I just
get in with you for a minute?
It's all right. Really, it is.
We're friends, that's all.
We are friends, aren't we?
Sure.
OK, let's don't say another word.
Let's just go to sleep.
Where are you, Fred?
It's cold.
There's snow and...wind.
What is it?
Why are you crying?
If we're going to be friends,
let's get one thing straight.
I hate snoops.
- Yeah.
- Lucille, darling?
I've been trying
desperately to reach you.
Bill just got back...
a day early, the beast...
so I'll have to beg off.
You'll explain
to the rest of the girls?
You're a darling.
Maybe we can have
a long lunch tomorrow.
- I'll phone you in the morning.
- Whatever you say.
You'll manage to survive
without me tonight?
Sure. I might even take a wild,
boyish fling at writing.
- Good night.
Got yourself stuffed,
huh, Polly, baby?
Serves you right, big mouth.
- Buon giorno.
- Huh?
Aren't you drinking?
You have pockets or something?
What do you go by?
What's your name?
What do you call yourself?
- Irving.
- Perfect, perfect.
That's wonderful, Irving.
I'll be right back, Irving, baby.
Yeah? Kid's still in the shower.
You expected?
I was invited. That what you mean?
Don't get all tense. Come on in.
It's a party - lot of characters
come who aren't expected.
I'll buy you a drink. You drink?
Then I'll buy you a drink.
Hey, honey, your skirt's split there.
- What do you drink?
- Bourbon.
- On the rocks?
- Yeah... No. With water.
- Want rocks first?
- Yeah. Not too much.
All right. That'll set you free.
- Know the kid long?
- Not very. I live upstairs.
Look at this place.
It's unbelievable. What a dump!
What do you think?
- About what?
- Is she or isn't she?
Wait a minute. Hold it.
- Harriet!
- Hi, JB.
"JB"? What's that?
- You know Gil.
- Yeah. How are you?
- How about a drink?
- In the kitchen.
So... Oh, honey, that is you.
Fred, darling,
I'm so glad you could come.
I brought you a present
for the bookcase.
You're sweet.
Doesn't that look nice?
Give me a cigarette, OJ.
OJ's a great agent.
He knows a lot of phone numbers.
What's Jerry Wald's phone number?
Come on, lay off.
Call him and tell him
Fred's a genius.
Stop blushing, Fred.
You didn't say it. I did.
Quit stalling. How will you make
Fred rich and famous?
Let Fred and me
settle that, huh, puppy?
OK, but remember, I'm the agent.
He's already got a decorator,
I'm the agent.
Hold it.
Hi, boys. Come on in.
Everything you need's
in the kitchen.
So, listen, Fred, baby...
- No, it's Paul, baby.
- I thought it was Fred, baby.
- Is she or isn't she?
- What?
A phoney.
I don't know. I don't think so.
Well, you're wrong - she is.
On the other hand, you're right,
because she's a real phoney.
She honestly believes
all this phoney junk.
Now, I sincerely
like the kid. I do.
I'm sensitive. That's why.
You got to be sensitive
to like the kid.
It's a streak of the poet.
You known her long?
I discovered her. I'm OJ Berman.
Couple of years ago...
She was just a kid.
Lot of style, class...
- Lot of what?
- Class.
But you didn't know whether
she was a hillbilly or an Okie.
Know how long it took
to smooth that accent?
One year. Know how?
We gave her French lessons.
Figured once
she could imitate French,
she could imitate English.
Finally, I arranged
for a little screen test.
The night before - I could've
killed myself- the phone rings.
I pick it up. She says, "It's
Holly. I'm in New York."
I say, "You got
a screen test tomorrow."
I say, "Get back here!"
She says, "I don't want to."
"What do you mean? What do you want?"
She says, "When I find out,
I'll let you know."
- Fred, baby...
- It's Paul, baby.
Sure. Don't tell me
she isn't a phoney.
Irving!
Honey, Irving, where you been?
Mike, darling, I tried
reaching you all day long.
Your answering service
doesn't answer.
That's the trouble
with answering services...
And after all that she said...
- Time, darling.
- What?
The time?
- You have a watch?
- No.
- Oh, let me see. 6:45.
- Thank you.
Really, was that necessary?
This is some party. Who are
all these people, anyhow?
Who knows? The word gets out.
You don't mind, do you, darling?
Reinforcements.
Right in there.
Holly, darling!
What's that?
Mag Wildwood.
She's a model, believe it
or not, and a thumping bore.
But look at the goodies with her.
He's all right,
if you like handsome,
rich-looking men
with passionate natures
and too many teeth.
I mean the other one.
- The other one?
- He's Rusty Trawler.
He's the ninth richest man
in America under 50.
That's remarkable information
to have at your fingertips.
I keep track of these things.
- Excuse me. You owe me 47...
- Hold this a minute, darling.
Mag, darling,
what are you doing here?
I was upstairs
working with Yunioshi...
Easter stuff for the Bazaar.
Then these two nice boys
came to pick me up.
It was a mistake, of course.
My wires got crossed somewhere.
They were both very sweet about it.
May I present Josè Silva Pereira?
He's from Brazil.
Miss Golightly.
Very kind of you to allow me
to attend your party.
I'm so interested
in North American culture.
I've been already
to the Statue of Liberty
and to the restaurant Automatique,
but this is the first time
I'm in a typical North American home.
Wouldn't he just melt in your mouth?
And this is Mr Rusty Trawler.
Miss Golightly.
You're not vexed at me
for bringing them?
- Of course not, darling.
- I'm glad.
Now, who's going
to bring me a bourbon?
- OJ.
- Yeah.
Would you get Miss Wildwood a drink?
Which one's Miss Wildwood?
Mr Berman, we haven't been
formally introduced,
but I'm Mag Wildwood
from Wildwood, Arkansaw.
That's...hill country.
Now, you just make yourself
right at home.
Don't trouble yourself.
I'm contented to observe
the customs of your country.
OK, you do that.
Now, come along, Mr Trawler.
Let's see what we
can find to amuse you.
I wasn't supposed to pick you up.
At the last minute, I had...
Look, I wasn't supposed
to pick you up.
Yes?
Miss Gorightly!
This time I'm warning you!
I am definitely this time
going to calling the police!
Good evening!
Is it something important?
No. Just the guy upstairs
complaining about the noise.
He's angry.
He did mention something
about calling the police.
Oh, the police... The police?
That I cannot have. I'd better
find Miss Wildwood and go.
To think I'd find a beau of mine
mousing after
some cheap Hollywood trash.
Mag, darling, you're being a bore.
Shut up!
You know what's going
to happen to you?
I'm going to march you to the
zoo and feed you to the yak.
Just as soon as I finish this drink.
Timber!
Sorry.
- Oh, good evening, Ed.
- It's Paul, baby.
You remember Irving, don't you?
- This is Josè.
- Nice to meet you.
Yes.
Jewel thieves.
Sally helps me with my accounts.
I have no head for figures at all.
I'm trying desperately
to save some money.
I just can't seem to.
He makes me write down everything.
What I get, what I spend.
I had an cheque account.
I got rid of that.
He feels it's better to operate
on a cash basis, taxwise.
Some day, take this book,
turn it into a novel.
Everything is there.
Just fill in the details.
Would be good for some laughs.
No. No, I don't think so.
This book would break the heart.
"Mr Fitzsimmons...powder room, $50.
"Less $18... Repair
one black satin dress.
"Cat food, 27 cents."
Sally, darling, please stop -
you're making me blush!
But you're right about Jack.
He's an absolute rat.
I guess, of course,
I don't know anybody but rats.
Except, of course, Fred here.
You do think Fred is nice, don't you?
For you... I hope he is.
Goodbye, Uncle Sally. Till next week.
Goodbye, Uncle Sally.
Goodbye and don't forget
to send that book.
I won't.
Oh, what about the weather report?
Oh, yes.
Snow flurries expected
this weekend in New Orleans.
this weekend in New Orleans?!
Isn't that just the weirdest?
I bet they haven't had
snow in New Orleans for years.
I don't know how he thinks them up.
* Moon River *
* Wider than a mile *
* I'm crossin' you in style *
* Some day *
* Old dream maker *
* You heartbreaker *
* Wherever you're goin' *
* I'm goin' your way *
* Two drifters *
* Off to see the world *
* There's such a lot of world *
* To see *
* We're after *
* The same *
* Rainbow's end *
* Waitin' 'round the bend *
* My huckleberry friend *
* Moon River *
* And me. *
- Hi.
- What you doin'?
- Writing.
Good.
Well, hello.
- What's wrong?
- I don't know.
It's probably nothing.
I want to see if he's still there.
See if who's still there?
What are you talking about?
Look.
See? I noticed him
yesterday afternoon.
I didn't want
to sound neurotic, but...
- when he's there again today...
- Who do you think he is?
It could be anybody, of course,
but what crossed my mind was...
suppose Bill's
having us watched, huh?
OK, I'll take care of this.
No. No, don't.
If that's it,
you'll only make it worse.
I'll be careful. You wait here.
Darling, please don't.
I don't think you should.
Take it easy.
I just want to find out
what this is about.
All right, what do you want?
Son, I need a friend.
That's me, that's her,
that's her brother Fred.
You're Holly's father?
Her name ain't Holly.
She was Lula Mae Barnes.
Was till she married me.
I'm her husband Doc Golightly.
Paul Varjak.
I'm a horse doctor... Animal man.
Do some farming, too,
near Tulip, Texas.
Her brother Fred's
getting out of the army soon.
Lula Mae belongs home with her
husband, brother and children.
Children?
Them's her children.
She's got four children?
Now, son, I didn't claim
they was her natural children.
Their own precious mother -
precious woman -
passed away July 4th, 1955,
the year of the drought.
When I married Lula Mae,
she was going on 14.
You might think a person of 14
wouldn't know their own mind.
But you take Lula Mae.
She was an exceptional person.
She just plumb broke our hearts
when she run off like she done.
Just plain had no reason.
All the housework
was done by her daughter.
Lula Mae could take it easy.
That woman got positively fat,
while her brother,
he growed up into a giant,
which is a sight different
from how they come to us.
A couple of wild young'uns, they was.
I caught 'em stealing milk
and turkey eggs.
They'd been living with
some mean, no-account people
about 100 mile east of Tulip.
She had cause to run from that house.
Never had none to leave mine.
What about her brother?
Didn't he leave?
No. We had Fred with us
till the army took him.
That's why I come.
I had a letter from him.
He's getting out in February.
That's why I come to get her.
Lula Mae's place is with her
husband, children and brother.
The prize from
a Cracker Jack box. Want it?
Never could understand
why that woman run off.
Don't tell me she weren't happy.
Talky as a jay bird she was,
with something to say
on every subject.
Better than the radio.
The night I proposed,
I cried like a baby.
She said, "Why are you crying?
We'll be married.
"I never been married before."
I laughed and hugged
and squeezed her.
"Never been married before."
Listen, son,
I advise you I need a friend,
'cause I don't want
to surprise or scare her none.
Let her know I'm here.
Will you do that, son?
Yeah, sure, Doc.
If that's what you want.
Come on.
All right.
Coming.
Oh, darling, I'm on my way out.
I'm half an hour late.
Maybe we can have a drink tomorrow.
Sure, Lula Mae...
if you're still here tomorrow.
Oh, please, where is he?
Gosh.
Gee, honey, don't they feed you
up here? You're so skinny.
- Hi, Doc.
- Gosh, Lula Mae...
Kingdom come!
What's the matter? You all right?
I guess so... No, I'm not.
Will you help me?
- If I can.
- Come to the bus station.
He still thinks I'm going back.
I can't play it alone.
He's your husband.
- No, he's not.
- He's not?
It was annulled ages ago.
He just won't accept it.
Please, Fred.
I'll say you're seeing us off.
Don't say anything.
Just meet us out front
in about an hour. Please?
You wait right here, honey.
I'll get the bag.
Why don't I get some magazines?
Please, Fred, don't leave me.
Attention, please.
Leaving from platform 5,
through coach to Dallas...
Philadelphia, Columbus,
Indianapolis, Terre Haute,
St Louis, Tulsa,
Oklahoma City, Denison, Dallas.
Come on, Lula Mae. That's us.
Doc, I'm not coming with you.
Come on. Let's walk quietly.
I'll try and help you
understand. Help me, Fred.
I appreciate your help, but
it's between Lula Mae and me.
Sure, Doc.
I love you, Lula Mae.
I know you do, and
that's just the trouble.
It's a mistake you always made,
trying to love a wild thing.
You were always
lugging home wild things -
a hawk with a broken wing,
a full-grown wildcat
with a broken leg...
Remember?
There's something...
You mustn't give your heart
to a wild thing.
The more you do,
the stronger they get,
until they're strong enough
to fly into a tree,
then to higher trees,
then to the sky.
There's something I got to tell you.
Excuse me.
Couple weeks ago,
I got a letter from Fred.
From Fred?
He's all right, isn't he?
Yeah, he's fine, I guess.
He's getting out of the army
in February.
In February?
Well, that's only four months.
So, you got to come back.
Your place is with us.
Doc, you've got to understand,
I can't come back.
You got to understand
what I'm saying.
I don't want to pressure you,
but I got to.
If you don't come,
I'll have to tell young Fred
he better sign up for another hitch.
Don't do that.
Don't write that to him.
I'll write him and say
I want him with me.
I'll take care of him.
You're talking crazy, Lula Mae.
Doc, stop calling me that.
I'm not Lula Mae any more.
All right, Lula Mae.
I guess you know what you're doing.
Keep an eye on her, will you, son?
At least see she eats
something once in a while.
Sure, Doc.
So skinny.
Please, Doc. Please understand.
I love you,
but I'm not Lula Mae any more.
I'm not.
You know the terrible thing,
darling?
I am still Lula Mae.
Fourteen, stealing turkey eggs
and running through a briar patch.
Except now I call it
having the mean reds.
Well, it's still too early
to go to Tiffany's.
I guess the next best thing
is a drink.
Yes, I very much need a drink.
Buy me one, Fred, darling?
Sure.
Only promise not to take me home
until I'm drunk.
Until I'm very drunk indeed.
Do you think she's talented?
Deeply and importantly talented?
No.
Amusingly and superficially
talented, yes,
but deeply and importantly, no.
Gracious.
Do you think she's handsomely paid?
Oh, indeed.
Well, let me tell you something.
If I had her money,
I'd be richer than she is.
- How do you figure that?
- I'd keep the candy store.
Old Sally Tomato -
that's my candy store.
I'd always keep Sally.
That's why I'd be richer than she is.
We'd better get a little more air.
..every Tom, Dick and Harry...
No. Correction.
Every Tom, Dick and Sid -
Harry was his friend.
Anyway, every Tom, Dick and Sid
thinks if he takes a girl to dinner,
she'll just curl up in a little
furry ball at his feet, right?
I have by actual count
been taken to dinner
by 26 different rats
in the last two months.
27, if you count Benny Shacklett,
who's in many ways a super rat.
- I forgot my key.
- Never mind. I buzzed Yunioshi.
Do you know something funny?
In spite of the fact these rats
fork up $50
for the powder room
like little dolls...
I find I have $9 less
in the bank account
than I had six months ago.
So, my darling Fred,
I have tonight made
a very serious decision.
And what is that?
No longer will I play the field.
- Congratulations.
- The field stinks...
both economically and socially,
and I'm giving it up.
This time I'm calling
the police, the fire department,
and the New York State
Housing Commission,
and, if necessary,
the Board of Health!
Quiet, up there. You want
to wake the whole house?
As Miss Golightly was saying
before she was so rudely interrupted,
Miss Golightly
further announces her intention
to devote her
not inconsiderable talents
to the immediate capture,
for the purpose of matrimony,
of Mr Rutherford...
Rusty to his friends, of whom
I'm sure he has many, Trawler.
- Who?
- Rusty Trawler.
You met him at my party.
He came with Mag Wildwood.
Not the beautiful Latin type,
the other one - the one
that looks like a pig.
Remember?
The ninth richest man
in America under 50?
Ah...
Do I detect a look
of disapproval in your eye?
Tough beans, buddy,
cos that's the way it's gonna be.
Hi, cat.
- Holly, you're drunk.
- True.
Absolutely true.
True, but irrevelant.
What are you doing?
So I think we should have a drink
to the new
Mrs. Rusty Trawler...me!
Hey, take it easy.
What's up,
don't you think I can do it?
Tell me. I'm interested.
Don't you think I can?
You heard the Doc.
My brother gets out in February.
The Doc won't take him back.
It's all up to me.
I don't know why
you don't understand.
I need money, and I'll do
whatever I have to do to get it.
So this time next month,
I'll be the new Mrs. Rusty Trawler.
I think we should have
a little drink to that.
It's all gone. Isn't that too bad?
Got any whisky upstairs?
But you've had enough.
Go ahead. Get the whisky.
I'll pay you for it.
Holly, please.
No, no, you disapprove of me,
and I do not accept drinks
from gentlemen who disapprove of me.
I'll pay for my own whisky
and don't forget it.
I do not accept drinks
from disapproving gentlemen.
Especially not
disapproving gentlemen
who are kept by other ladies.
So take it.
You should be used
to taking money from ladies.
If I were you, I'd be more
careful with my money.
Rusty Trawler is too hard
a way of earning it.
It should take you
exactly four seconds
to cross from here to that door.
I'll give you two.
Hi. I wanted to talk
about the other night,
then I saw the paper, and...
Well, actually, I'm kind
of embarrassed about it,
but since it concerns you,
I thought I should
talk about it in person.
- What?
Oh, the earplugs.
I can't go through
the whole thing again.
It's sufficient to say,
I've come to make up.
As an added inducement,
I have all kinds of news.
Can I come in?
I guess so.
Just a minute.
Do I have a nightgown on?
No, I don't. Would you turn
around for a second?
Never mind. That's corny anyway.
I'll turn around myself.
Come in.
Have...you seen the paper?
Rusty, you mean?
Yes. I know all about it.
Certainly had him
pegged wrong, didn't I?
I thought he was just a rat,
but he was a super rat all along.
A super rat in rat's clothing.
You don't even know the best part.
Not only was he a super rat,
he was also broke.
Broke! I mean, but not a farthing.
His family has money,
but he personally is broke.
It turns out he owes $700,000.
Can you imagine
anyone owing $700,000?
$43, yes.
Anyway, that's why he decided
to marry the queen
of the pig people.
I'll tell you one thing,
Fred, darling,
I'd marry you
for your money in a minute.
- Would you marry me for mine?
- In a minute.
I guess it's lucky
neither of us is rich.
Yeah.
Oh, Fred, darling,
I'm so glad to see you.
What have you been doing?
Writing, mostly.
I sold a story.
Just got word this morning.
Oh, that's marvellous!
It really is, but...
Only how does your decorator
friend feel about it?
Aren't you supposed
to be saving yourself?
You know something?
I haven't got around
to telling her yet.
Look, why don't we go have a drink
or take a walk to celebrate?
All right. There's some
champagne in the icebox.
Why don't you open it
while I get dressed?
I haven't drunk champagne
before breakfast before.
With breakfast on several occasions,
but never before, before.
I've got a wonderful idea.
We'll spend the day
doing things we've never done.
We'll take turns.
First you, then me.
Of course, I can't think
of anything I've never done.
I've never been
for a walk in the morning.
Not in New York.
I've walked here at six,
but I consider that night.
- Do you think it counts?
- Sure. Now we're even.
- Don't you just love it?
- Love what?
Tiffany's.
Isn't it wonderful?
Nothing bad could happen to you
in a place like this?
I don't give a hoot about
jewellery, except diamonds.
Like that.
What do you think?
Well...
Personally, I think it's tacky
to wear diamonds before 40.
You're right, but meantime,
you should have something.
I'll wait.
No. I'm buying you a present.
You bought me a typewriter
ribbon, and it brought luck.
But Tiffany's can be expensive.
I've got my cheque and $10.
I wouldn't let you cash your cheque,
but a present for $10 or under,
that I'll accept.
Of course, I don't know
what we'll find here for $10.
May I help you?
Perhaps. We're looking
for a present for the lady.
Certainly, sir. Is there
something you had in mind?
Well, we had considered diamonds.
No offence, but the lady feels
diamonds are tacky for her.
Oh, I think they're
divine on older women,
but they're not right for me,
you understand.
- Certainly.
- In fairness, I should explain
there's also
the problem of finance.
We can only afford
to spend...a limited amount.
May I ask how limited?
- $10.
- $10?
That was the outside figure, yes.
- I see.
- Do you have anything for $10?
Frankly, madam,
within that price range,
the variety of merchandise
is rather limited.
However, I do think
we might have, let's see...
Strictly a novelty,
you understand...
For the lady and gentleman
who has everything,
a sterling silver telephone dialler.
That's $6.75, including tax.
A sterling silver telephone dialler.
Yes, sir. That's $6.75,
including federal tax.
Well, the price is right,
but I must say,
I'd hoped for something more,
how shall I say it,
romantic in feeling.
- What do you think?
- A silver telephone dialler?
I certainly think it's handsome,
but, well, you do understand.
Well, we tried, but...
We could have
something engraved, couldn't we?
Yes, I suppose so.
Yes, indeed.
The problem is, you'd have
to buy something first
in order to have some object
on which to place the engraving.
You see the difficulty?
Well, we could
have this engraved, couldn't we?
I think it would be very smart.
This, I take it,
was not purchased at Tiffany's?
No. Actually, it was purchased
concurrent with...
well, actually, it came inside a...
- a box of Cracker Jack.
- I see.
Do they still really have prizes
in Cracker Jack boxes?
Oh, yes.
That's nice to know.
It gives one a feeling
of solidarity,
almost of continuity with
the past, that sort of thing.
Would Tiffany's really
engrave it for us?
They wouldn't feel it
beneath them or anything?
Well, it is rather unusual, madam,
but you'll find that Tiffany's
is very understanding.
If you would tell me the initials,
I think we could have something
ready for you in the morning.
Didn't I tell you
this was a lovely place?
What is this place, anyway?
You wanted to sit down.
It's the public library.
- You've never been here?
- No. That makes two for me.
I don't see any books.
They're in there.
See?
Each one of these drawers
is stuffed with little cards.
Each little card
is a book or an author.
I think that's fascinating.
V-A-R-J-A-K.
Really?
Look. Isn't it marvellous?
There you are, right
in the public library.
Varjak, Paul. Nine Lives.
Then a lot of numbers.
Do they really have
the book itself, live?
Sure. Follow me.
Number 57. That's us.
57, please.
Nine Lives by Varjak, Paul.
Have you read it?
It's marvellous.
- I'm afraid I haven't.
- You should. He wrote it.
He's Varjak, Paul, in person.
She doesn't believe me.
Show her your driver's licence
or Diner's Club Card or something.
He is the author. Cross my heart
and kiss my elbow.
Would you kindly lower your voice?
Autograph it.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Make it more personal?
Really, Miss...
Go ahead. Don't be so stuck up,
autograph it.
What shall I say?
Something sentimental, I think.
What are you doing? Stop that!
You're defacing public property.
Well, if that's how you feel.
Come on. Let's get out of here.
I don't think this place
is half as nice as Tiffany's.
Did you ever steal anything
from a 5-and-10
when you were a kid?
No. I'm the sensitive,
bookish type. Did you?
I used to. I still do now
and then, to keep my hand in.
Come on.
You've never done it,
and it's your turn.
I can't see.
Hi, cat.
Lady of the house at home?
Trick or treat?
You're crazy.
You know that, don't you?
But I love you anyway.
- Tooley.
- Yeah?
I've...got to talk to you.
All right.
You want a drink?
If this is a serious discussion,
and suddenly
I'm terribly afraid it is,
you'll have to take off
that ridiculous mask,
or I'll have to wear one, too.
Tooley, look, please.
What's the matter?
Girl trouble?
Is that it?
Oh, I see.
Well, that's not so serious.
As a matter of fact,
I've been expecting it.
I can't say I like it,
but I've been expecting it.
Who is she?
Hasn't got anything to do with her.
This is between you and me.
Then it is serious.
Well, now.
Tooley, you're a very stylish girl.
Can't we end this stylishly?
End it?
Yes.
Well...
I do believe love
has found Andy Hardy.
Let's see...a waitress?
A salesgirl?
No. She'd have to be rich,
wouldn't she, Paul?
Someone who could help you.
Curiously enough...
She's a girl who can't
help anyone, not even herself.
But I can help her, and it's
a nice feeling for a change.
All right.
I understand.
I'll tell you what, Paul.
I am a very stylish girl.
- What are you doing?
- Writing a cheque.
Don't look so bewildered.
Surely you've noticed me
writing cheques before.
Pay to the order
of Paul Varjak, $1,000.
Take her away somewhere
for a week.
You're entitled
to a vacation with pay.
Simply a matter of fair
labour practice, darling.
If you were really smart,
you'd get the boys together
and organise a union.
That way you'd get
all the fringe benefits -
hospitalisation, a pension plan
and unemployment insurance
when you're...
how shall I put it...
between engagements?
Thanks for making it easier for me.
Don't be ridiculous, darling.
Take the cheque.
And call your girl.
No, thanks.
I've got a cheque of my own.
When you get yourself
a new writer to help,
try and find one my size.
That way you won't have
to even shorten the sleeves.
- Oh! What are you doing?
- Excuse me... I'm sorry.
You look just like
a girl I know named Holly.
Really!
I'm sorry.
Hi.
What do you want?
I want to talk to you.
I'm busy.
What are you doing?
Reading.
"South America:
Land of Wealth and Promise"?
It's very interesting.
Let's get out of here.
I said let's get out of here.
I want to talk to you.
What's the matter with you?
What's happened?
Fred, will you please
just leave me alone?
I love you.
- Where are you going?
- To the ladies' room.
- What's the matter with you?
- Let me go.
- No.
- Fred, let me go.
Let's get something straight.
I am not Fred,
nor am I Benny Shacklett.
My name is Paul, Paul Varjak,
and I love you.
- Let me go.
- No. What about South America?
If I'm marrying
a South American,
I'd better find out
about the country.
- Marry? What South American?
- Josè.
- Who's Josè?
- Josè de Silva Pereira.
Who's Josè de Silva Pereira?
You met him -
Mag Wildwood's friend.
The good-looking one
who came with Rusty.
Well, you won't believe this -
not only is he handsome and rich,
he's absolutely cuckoo for me.
- You're crazy.
- You think you own me?
That's it exactly.
That's what everybody always
thinks, but they're wrong.
Look, I am not everybody.
Or am I?
Is that what you really think?
That I'm no different from
all your rats and super rats?
Wait a minute.
If that's it...
If that's what you really think...
there's something I want to give you.
What's that?
$50 for the powder room.
The place is in such a mess,
I couldn't face it alone.
- Ah, you have a message.
- No.
Olè.
Good evening, Mr Yunioshi.
Oh, good evening, Paul.
Good evening.
Please, you must help me.
Let me go. No!
Oh, Fred.
Fred.
No! No!
- What did you do to her?
- Nothing.
There was a telegram,
and then this...
crashing everything,
and acting crazy.
It's appalling.
I can't have a public scandal.
It's too delicate.
My name, my position, my family.
Will there be the police again?
I don't see why. There's no law
against wrecking your apartment.
- Where is the telegram?
- There it is.
"Received notice
young Fred killed...
"in jeep accident,
Fort Riley, Kansas.
"Your husband and children
join in the sorrow
"of our mutual loss.
"Letter following. Love, Doc."
Her brother Fred.
This brother,
was she very close to him?
Yeah.
What can one do?
Try to help her.
I tried. It didn't do much good.
You got a ranch
or something in Brazil?
Yes.
That's good. She'll like that.
Well, you better get in there.
- Hi.
- Hello. Got your wire.
How did you know where to reach me?
I tried everything -
called people, asked around,
then suddenly thought of the
phone book. I'm glad you came.
You look fine.
I'm fat as a pig,
and I haven't had my hair done,
but I'm happy, really happy -
it probably shows.
You look très distinguè
yourself.
I've got a job.
I've been writing a little.
I've read three of your stories -
two in the New Yorker and one
in that funny little magazine.
- Won't you sit down?
- Thank you.
- I've taken up knitting.
- So I see.
It'll probably look very nice
once it's finished.
I'm nervous about it.
Josè brought up the blueprints
for a ranch house.
Maybe those and my knitting
instructions got switched.
It's possible
I'm knitting a ranch house!
Really, I can't tell you
how divinely happy I am.
What is that, anyhow?
Portuguese -
a very complicated language.
4,000 irregular verbs.
Very impressive.
What's it mean?
I believe you are in league
with the butcher.
Holly, what's this about?
Why did you want to see me?
Josè's in Washington tonight,
so I thought I'd ask you over.
Well, I've said goodbye
to everyone else I care about.
- You're going somewhere?
- Rio, tomorrow.
I've got the plane ticket, and
I've even said goodbye to Sally.
- Josè's flying with you?
- We're on separate planes.
He thinks it's wrong
to travel together.
His family's important, so he
worries about things like that.
I thought I'd show off
and cook dinner for us.
Did I tell you
how utterly happy I am?
Yes.
You are getting married, then?
Well, he hasn't really asked me,
not in so many words.
Four, you mean?
Well, that's how many
words it takes.
"Will you marry me?"
We'll get married, all right.
In church and with his family there,
and that's why he's waiting
till we get to Rio...probably.
Do you think it's trying
to tell us something?
I hope you like chicken
and rice with chocolate sauce.
It's an Indian classic, dear.
Three months ago,
I couldn't scramble eggs.
Are you all right?
Golly, darling. I did so want
to impress you.
Look, I'm not much
for chicken with sauce, anyway.
Why don't we go out somewhere
for a farewell dinner?
That would be fun,
as long as I can go like this.
Years from now,
years and years,
I'll be back...
me and my nine Brazilian brats.
They'll be dark like Josè, of course,
but they'll have bright green,
beautiful eyes.
I'll bring them back, all right,
because they must see this.
Oh, I love New York.
Then why are you leaving?
What's in it for you, anyway?
I know what you're thinking.
I don't blame you.
I've always thrown out
such a jazzy line,
but except for Doc and yourself,
Josè's my first non-rat romance.
Not that he's my idea
of the absolute finito.
He's too prim and cautious
to be my absolute ideal.
If I could choose from anybody,
I wouldn't pick Josè.
Nero, maybe, or Albert Schweitzer.
Or Leonard Bernstein.
But I am mad about Josè.
I'd give up smoking if he asked me.
Come on, darling, let's eat.
It's getting late.
I'm leaving tomorrow
and I haven't begun to pack.
Didn't want Josè to think
I'm a girl who loses her key,
so I had 26 of them made.
Wait. I got a better idea.
Kind of a farewell gesture.
Somebody must have tripped the lock.
Ah, crafty devil, that Yunioshi.
Wake up, wake up!
The British are coming!
Or, in this case, the Brazilians.
Exactly.
I've still got to clean up that rice.
Hey, you know...
There she are who did it!
The wanted woman! There!
Groenburger. Narcotics squad.
What do you mean?
What's going on?
- Why don't you ask your boss?
- What boss?
Sally Tomato. Ask him. Come on.
Look around for narcotic!
They got plenty in there.
- What's your name?
- Varjak.
Hold it down over there!
Paul Varjak. V-A-R-J-A-K. Get lost!
Get out!
I'm a writer. W-R-l-T-E-R.
I can't answer all your questions.
One at a time. One, please. Good.
One at a time.
Knock it off!
Now, why don't you start?
Did you carry messages in code?
Of course not.
I'd just give Mr O'Shaughnessy
the weather report.
Simply do not ask me
what this is all about.
- You did visit Tomato?
- Every week. What's wrong?
Tomato's part
of the narcotics syndicate.
He never mentioned narcotics.
These wretched people
keep persecuting him.
He's a deeply sensitive person,
a darling old man.
- Then you're innocent.
- Of course.
What are you going to do
about it? Who's your lawyer?
I don't know.
Mr O'Shaughnessy, I guess.
Mr O'Shaughnessy!
Hey! Get out of here!
All right, come on! OK, move.
Shut up!
Get in there!
- Yeah.
- Mr Paul Varjak?
Yeah.
Ready with Mr Berman
in Hollywood.
Kindly deposit $3
for the first 3 minutes.
Hello? Hello?
OJ Berman here. Who's calling?
- This is Paul Varjak.
- Nice to talk to you, kid.
Varjak. V-A-R-J-A-K.
I'm a friend of Holly's.
We met at a party.
- Who?
- Paul. Paul Varjak.
V-A-R...
Mr Berman, this is Fred.
Oh, Fred, baby, huh?
You're calling about the kid, huh?
Everything's under control.
You can just relax.
I spoke to my lawyer in New York.
I told him to take care of it,
but keep my name anonymous.
- What?
- I want no part of it. Hear me?
You sound like you're in a tunnel.
It's this executive phone I have.
- What?
- Executive phone!
They only got her on 10,000 bail.
My lawyer can get her out at 10am.
I tell you what you do.
You bust into that dump she lives in,
collect all her junk,
go get her, take her to a hotel
under a phoney name.
Keep her away from the reporters.
Will you do that?
Sure, Mr Berman.
I can't tell you
how much I appreciate...
Forget it.
I mean, I owe her something.
Not that I owe her anything,
if you get right down to it,
but...she's a crazy.
She's a phoney.
But she's a real phoney.
Know what I mean, kid?
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Thanks, Mr Berman. Thanks a lot.
Right!
Why don't you behave?
Quel night.
I did a little housebreaking
while you were away.
Clayton Hotel, driver.
84th and Madison.
OJ thinks you should
stay out of sight for a while.
I got your stuff here, including cat.
Hope he's all right.
Hello, cat...
Poor no-name slob.
Listen, darling,
did you find that plane ticket?
- Here. We can cash it in.
- Are you kidding?
- What time is it?
- A little after 10.
Idlewild Airport, driver.
- Never mind. You can't do that.
- Why not?
You don't understand.
You're under indictment.
You jump bail,
they'll throw away the key.
Don't be ridiculous.
Soon I'll be married
to the future president of Brazil.
That'll give me diplomatic
immunity or something.
I wouldn't bet on it.
What is it, darling?
I have a message for you.
Oh, yes, I see.
Did he bring it in person,
or was it shoved under the door?
A cousin.
Hand me my purse, will you, darling?
A girl can't read
that sort of thing...
without her lipstick.
You read it to me, darling.
I don't think I can quite...bear...
Are you sure you want me to?
"My dearest little girl,
"I have loved you
knowing you were not as others,
"but conceive of my despair
"upon discovering in such
a brutal and public style
"how very different you are
from the manner of woman
"a man of my position
could hope to make his wife.
"I grieve for the disgrace
of your present circumstances,
"and I do not find it in my heart
"to add my condemn...
"to the condemn that surrounds you.
"so I hope you find it
in your heart not to condemn me.
"I have my family
to protect, and my name.
"I am a coward where
these institutions enter.
"Forget me, beautiful child,
"and may God be with you.
"Josè."
Well...
Well, at least he's honest.
It's kind of touching.
Touching! That square-ball jazz.
He says he's a coward.
All right! So he's not a regular rat
or even a super rat.
He's just a scared little mouse,
that's all.
But, oh, golly... Gee, damn!
Well, so much for South America.
You're not cut out
for queen of the Pampas, anyway.
- Clayton Hotel.
- Idlewild.
What?
The plane leaves at 12.
On it I plan to be.
- Holly, you can't.
- Et pourquoi pas?
I'm not hotfooting it
after Josè,
if that's what you think. Oh, no.
As far as I'm concerned, he's
the future president of nowhere.
Only why waste a plane ticket?
Besides, I've never been to Brazil.
Please, darling, don't sit there
looking at me like that.
I'm going and that's that.
All they want are my services
as a witness against Sally.
Nobody has any intention
of prosecuting me.
To begin with, they don't have
a ghost of a chance.
This town's finished for me...
at least for a while.
There are certain shades of limelight
that can wreck a girl's complexion.
They'll have the rope up
at every saloon in town.
I'll tell you what.
When you get back to town,
call the New York Times
or whoever you call.
Mail me a list of the 50 richest
men in Brazil. The 50 richest!
Holly.
I won't let you do this.
- You won't?
- Holly, I'm in love with you.
- So what?
- So what? So plenty!
I love you. You belong to me.
No. People don't belong to people.
Of course they do.
- Nobody's putting me in a cage.
- I want to love you.
It's the same thing.
No, it's not! Holly!
I'm not Holly.
I'm not Lula Mae, either.
I don't know who I am!
I'm like cat, a no-name slob.
We belong to nobody.
We don't even belong to each other.
Stop the cab.
What do you think?
This ought to be the right place
for a tough guy like you -
garbage cans, rats galore.
Scram! I said take off! Beat it!
Let's go.
Driver...
Pull over here.
You know what's wrong with you,
Miss Whoever-You-Are?
You're chicken.
You've got no guts.
You're afraid to say,
"OK, life's a fact."
People do fall in love.
People do belong to each other,
because that's the only chance
anybody's got for happiness.
You call yourself a free spirit,
a wild thing.
You're terrified somebody's
going to stick you in a cage.
Well, baby,
you're already in that cage.
You built it yourself.
And it's not bounded
by Tulip, Texas, or Somaliland.
It's wherever you go.
Because no matter where you run,
you end up running into yourself.
Here. I've been carrying
this thing around for months.
I don't want it any more.
Here, cat!
Cat!
Where's the cat?
I don't know.
* Two drifters *
* Off to see the world *
* There's such a lot of world *
* To see *
* We're after *
* The same *
* Rainbow's end *
* Waitin' 'round the bend *
* My huckleberry friend *
* Moon River *
* And me. *