What are you doing, kid?
You use RMB in Hong Kong? Are you crazy?
I have no HK dollars
my friend, it's nothing I can do
I am not your friend
Can't you see I am in uniform?
Call me sir
Sir, I've been standing for an hour
I'm so thirsty
how about you borrow me a few dollars
When my uncle arrive, he'll pay you back
Everybody in Hong Kong needs help
who bothers to help you
You better beg the machine Can I?
Sir, please buy me a drink
This vending machine is not sir
You have to call him Mr. Machine
Mr. Machine, please buy me a drink
Thank you, Mr. Machine
What take my uncle so long?
Hurry up, after this
we would have played 200 rounds
I haven't slept for 3 days already
What? Want to leave with the money?
Oh, shit
What's it? What?
My nephew is coming from Guangzhou today
I have to pick him up at the station
see you
Black Tat, wanna run away?
You better clear the bills first
I didn't say I quit
But I have to pick my nephew up first
Clear the bills?
You think you will win for sure
You'll know it when we finish... Ping
OK, let me Say a prayer first
Oh, let me say some prayers too
God of Dogs bless me
Ping, be careful
Fishy Shing, you want to pick up Ping
you better go to the club
You don't have to leave your business
and play mahjong here
what's so good about her?
You like her big ass
Say it to yourself
it has been so many years
At least you'll have a happy ending
if you get married
I haven't met the right one
The right one?
You must be waiting for Blackie Tat
Who said I like him?
Everybody knows!
You better think about it
Gamblers usually
won't have a good ending
After my prayers, I will surely win
I will beat Blackie Tat
Touch wood
The God of Dogs? You worship a dog?
Damn you
Come on
let's worry about win or lose later
Where is Ping?
She went to the toilet
are you in a hurry to lose?
Damn you
Blackie Tat, you are not young anymore
He is only teasing you
and you put your nephew aside
Go pick him up now
You really think
I leave my nephew alone?
Honestly I'm afraid to see him
Why?
Have you heard a disease
called Natural-born losing control?
What is that?
It is a disease that
a man will lose control anytime
anywhere
He'll have no idea what he's done
I don't understand
This is a hereditary disease
from my family
My grandmother used to be like this
Whenever her sister called her
she'd gone crazy
My uncles said that
It is because the brain is affected by
certain sound waves
If my nephew calls me Uncle
I'm OK but if
He formally calls me Uncle Tat
I'll lose control
What will happen when you lose control?
Don't stay too long then
I might rape you
That's good, I've been waiting for this
Can you still control
your droppings then?
If I can't, I will do it in your mouth
It's 7 o'clock already
how comes you people are still sleeping?
I really worked all night last night
I don't want your explanation
I really don't have another man
Here it is
It's been scratched
1th or 7th floor?
I don't trust you
If you don't believe it
you can call him
It's better to call him here
Rather than looking for him each floor
Uncle Tat
What's the noise?
Danny, just open up
What do you want me to do then?
You say I love you' 10 times
then I'll open the door
All right, I love you...
I love you...
Wait. Thanks
So selfish
I love you...
Is this a swordplay from North China?
Chung, open up
Old Lady
why did you attack me with your sword?
Or it is from South China?
You don't have to sting me
even I guess it wrong
Bad-tempered
Uncle Tat, Uncle Tat
Good morning. Excuse me...
Why are you so noisy
early in the morning?
Uncle is not here
Let see check upstairs
Tat...
Tat your ass
Fine, I'll wait here
You have to go out someday
But if he doesn't, I'll be damned
The massacre in Shum Cheng
you can't run, uncle
Comrade
Is it evacuation?
Do you know
the murderer of the massacre?
Of course, that's a big news
I know he's hiding in this building
But I don't know which unit
This is his picture
If I get the right one
you'll be in deep shit, Ping
I'll take care of Ping, right?
You're in trouble
What's the matter?
Freeze, this is the police
I have a sure-win hand
What's the problem, sir?
This murderer of Shum Cheng just raped
and killed a family of seven last night
You're a beast
It was me!
Don't you remember
he was with us last night?
Oh yes, I was with you last night
Sir, maybe you've made a mistake
We have witness
Who's it?
That's him
Do you recognize me? I'm Sing
You son of a bitch
Let me go Police
Uncle Tat
Please help me
Don't worry. He'll be OK soon
I said don't worry
What have I done?
That's the same old cop, Uncle Tat
Help me
He loses control of himself
Help me, partner
My uncle is not a rapist
Help me...
Stop
Don't do that
Hereditary lost of control
It's my turn finally
What are you doing?
Why are you using the cutting board?
I'm sorry. I was a bit emotional
Sorry, I was a bit emotional
Sorry...
Nuts
Look at yourself
You look like monster, look at your hair
I thought it's popular in Hong Kong
Popular your ass
Again? Take it off
I've told you the kids from China
is cold-blooded
No sense of belonging
Call the cop?
I am the murderer of Shum Cheng?
What are you then?
The rapist of Guangzhou?
You son of a bitch
This is such a stupid old trick
There's a lighter inside the can
In the past. It was so obvious that
You were the one who informed the police
Otherwise how could you dad
Be the first person to be executed
during the Cultural Revolution
The little girl is falling, watch out!
She's falling
Lost of control
Chee?
You can see through the walls?
Yes, if I want to
What's the color of my underwear?
You haven't wore any
Wait a moment
What are these?
Birds
What kind of bird?
Those that can't fly
What are the hidden ones?
3 green in the middle
4 red on right and 4 white on the left
That's all
Fuck you
What you see in front of you
is not concrete. It's money
Money is everywhere in Hong Kong
Remember this
Be hygienic, pick it up
Sing
did you say after your sickness at 9
You realized
you have a supernatural power
Did the head of your unit know?
Oh yes Oh yes
Did they ask you to work for them?
Of course they did What then?
I was asked to patrol the city
the 1st year
To see if the underground pipes were OK
If yes, I had to ask for repair
I was doing good the 2nd year
I was promoted to be a customs officer
But after
they installed an X-ray machine
I lost myjob at once
I am lucky this time
Why?
All you have to do is to use
your supernatural power in gambling
Then we'll be rich
I don't know how to gamble
I just played mahjong a few times
Count on me. There're a lot of things
that you don't know
If you don't understand, ask
This is the Paradise of the rich
You can be like them if you have money
Good food, good house, good cloths
beautiful cars and women
What if I don't have money?
No money?
It will be like the two of us
give up everything
Watch out kids
In Hong Kong
you must say the right things
When you have the chance, don't miss it
Do you wanna do it?
Are you doing it?
Yes, of course yes
I'll do everything
Which one are you good at?
How are you doing, Uncle Tat
this's my fiancee
Really?
This is my nephew Sing, Say hello
Hello
Miss, I'll do it
Not this one
My nephewjust arrived from China
I'll get marry soon
I didn't work in the club already
Congratulations
Thank you Say congratulation
Say it
I'll come to your wedding
On your wedding day, I will surely come
Come, come your ass
Everybody likes to gamble in Hong Kong
It can roughly be divided into...
Mahjong, Tin Kau, Pai Kau
Poker, Dice etc
How about insect fighting?
Insect
You think this is China?
How about horse?
Horseracing is popular here
I can't put a horse
on the table to show you
After the training of these few days
Although you are not an expert
at least you are getting familiar
How about this hand?
I'll rearrange them like this
Are you sure?
I'm just making it fun, Uncle
Don't you like it?
Bet...
Please put down your bet
Last call, bet please...
4, 5 and 6. Big
Big
What happened?
I heard that the nephew of Blackie Tat
Hejust arrived from China
and won 10 games in a row
The house almost goes broken
Open, 4, 5, 6, 15 points. Big
That's weird
I'll take a leak. You'd better watch
Put down your bet
This is 13 points. Big
Don't push the house too far
Or we won't get much out of it
What does it mean?
We'll have to lose this time
together with others
OK, small this time
Small...
Last call please
13 points
Open, 2, 5, 6, 13 points. Big
You're crazy
You bit on small and 13 together
You're setting me up
I win while you lose. I like it
So what
You son of a bitch
Nothing I can do if you're so courageous
Then that's fine
Why don't you hit the other side also?
Uncle...
Old man
don't get yourself killed for the money
You're not having much luck
I like it. What can you do?
Nothing I can do if you're so courageous
Then that's fine
Do you know who I am?
I don't give a shit
Old man, you're talking too much
I'll fix you up
Don't go. Let me do it
Uncle, trust me
I can do it now You?
Do I look like I can't?
That's exactly what you look
Don't let my appearance fool you
My friend...
You can't beat old man
I'll beat you too, kid. Get him
Don't, don't hurt his head
Don't hurt his head
Go away
Are you OK?
I'm fine
Hold on
This one hurts. Oh it hurts
You think you're a good fighter?
If your brain is hurt
what do I do then?
You'll be dead now
if I didn't give a hand
This kind of things happened to me
every week
I like it. What can you do?
Nothing I can do if you're so courageous
Then that's fine
It's my duty to protect my nephew
Go first if this happens again
Get it?
Sorry
Do me a favour, comrade
I'll remember you
Hold tight
Thank you
I will marry you later
You don't have to drive so fast actually
My danger is over
Yours is over, how about mine?
This's the fastest
Why do you stop?
No gasoline
Don't worry, Miss, I'll be around
Why are there so many people
going after you?
I killed their boss
I'll kill you if you run
Brother
We're all friends and brothers
Maybe we'll be one family
in our next life
We should not attack each other
for such a small thing
I do understand your feeling now
Because my brother died when I was three
Not only that
my younger brother died when I was four
You talk too much, where are you from?
I'm from Guangzhou
Let's kill the bloody Chinese gangsters
Stand aside
Billy
Step aside, brother
You, stand aside please
Let me do it
It's my turn now. Hey, look over there
See you later, kid
Why are you calling me kid?
What's your name comrade?
My name is Yee Mong
Yee Mong
Bye-bye
Her mole is so tempting
Yee Mong, I am actually a good fighter
I really am, don't you trust me?
Yes, I do
I don't think you do
Believe me, I do
You only want me to show you my skills
Don't.... I don't believe then
If you don't believe, I'll have to prove
I know you will say this
Then it OK now
Don't fight
Where is Mr. Hung?
Mr. Hung is having a game
with Mr. Chan from Taiwan
Wait until he finishes his game
If we both have a flash, I'm bigger
OK, 5 million
But don't forget
I might have a royal flush
If so, you won't look so nervous
I don't believe you have a royal flush
I'll add 5 million
Why don't you simply show your hand?
How much have you got?
Around 8 million
OK, I will add 8 million
Mr. Hung
you have misjudged me this time
I really have a royal flush
What a coincidence
Mr. Hung, this is exactly the situation
in which big money is lost, isn't it?
Wait a minute
You are right
Damn coincidence makes one lose
Damn it
Chung, I'm sorry
You're lucky this time
You'll not be so lucky next time
It's not luck that I have, it's ability
You'd better watch out in next month's
World Gamblers Championship
You're too arrogant
I will definitely be the Champion
Let's go
Mr. Hung, Yee Mong has fixed Keung
Well done
It's nothing
By the way, in the casinojust now
There's an interesting man
Doctor said
Chee's operation will cost $100,000
Now the money we've got is not enough
Why don't we go to the race course
tomorrow?
I have some exclusive tips
Do your tips work?
I know the horse's owner
So you little bastard finally come back
Uncle always... Yee Mong
This is too early for dreaming
Let plan our bets tomorrow
in the race course
How about this round?
No. 3 looks a little depressed
No. 4 has some respiratory problem
No. 5 and 6 keep talking
I think No. 7 is most aggressive
Let's bet on No. 7
Are you serious? No. 7 will not win
Damn you. Trying to fool me
You can even see that
No. 7 is aggressive?
All the experts are saying that
it will fail
If the experts are so good
they should all be rich then
Let's go
Oh yes, you're the best
I'm not blaming you
Horses are different from Mahjong
You can't be totally out of line
This No. 7 is ridiculous
Stay here. I'll place my bet
Don't you trust my anymore, Uncle?
It's done
Do the tips work?
Iwill bet my life on it
No. 6 with No. 2, 3 or 4, Quenelle
$100 each bet
Thanks
Hurry...
No. 6...
Go faster, I've bet my life on it
No. 7! I should have trusted you!
That's great
Uncle
We've made it. Did you bet on No. 7?
The damage is already done
Only a little bit
I saw a friend there. Let me go over
Wait... What should I bet on this time?
I think...
Don't speak up
Write it here
Don't look
0k
No. 6, we'll be rich
That's not necessary, Shing
Luk. Shing
What a coincidence
Did anything happen to Luk?
I want to take a bet for Chee...
to get the operation fee
But she lost it all
Is Chee sick?
She's got a heart-disease
and need money for operation
But she lost all her money. Poor Chee
Luk
Can you show me your ticket?
Here! It's useless now
Not really! Let see if I can help
The only thing you can help is
to give me some money
I'll do my best, ok?
No. 7 has won just now
That's great
I'll bet on No. 6 next Of course
You win because of me
You'd better buy me dinner
Of course
No. 6, No. 6...
I see smoke coming out from his head
No. 9?
Don't...
Don't look at me like that
I'm the victim too
We trust the wrong person
Luk
the bastard asked me to bet on No. 6
Luk, look
He turned it into No. 7
That means we've made it
You can change the number?
That's right, he can do it
Luk, go and get the money now
Don't gamble anymore
I know, Sing
I want to thank you for Chee
That's enough. Go get the money first
Hey, kid, you really know how to do it?
Please turn my No. 6 into No. 9 then
Ijust wrote No. 9
But I put my bet on No. 6.
Stop the crap, come on
I can't
Every time I use my supernatural power
I need to rest for 1 or 2 months
Can't change anymore
1 or 2 months?
That means we don't have to gamble
anymore after today
Soccer? Can you do that?
How's that? The doctor said that
this is an excellent medicine
You'll recover soon. Getting better?
Guess what have I got?
Fingers
I've told you
the western medicine doesn't work
Let me give you a special recipe
Sing
Shing, just stay where you are
Chee wants to see you
That's right
Good girl. Chee
What happened to Ping's mouth?
It's nothing
Look said
you can change anything you want
What can I do for you?
I just want you to change here for me
It want them to be bigger
But I'm afraid I'll make it even smaller
All right with me too
Then you can reduce the size of my ass
Tat. Blackie Tat
Coming... There's a letter
What is it? A letter
Give it to me
Look What's that?
What letter is that?
An invitation
Hung Kong is the most prominent man
among the gangsters
His nickname is King of Gamblers
He is paying some attention
on both of us
It's an opportunity for us
Only can we become his right hands
We'll have endless money
Even we do not stay with him
we can still make money
I know
They've made it clear already
if you don't help him this time
We will be dead-men soon
But I've lost my power now
He will also kill us if he knows it
That's why we can't let him know
Don't gamble with him
just show your power to scare him
Don't be too serious
Did you see that Ace?
No
One
Two
Three
And four
There are only 3
This is called rumour
When you become famous
you have to watch your posture
After that, you have to package yourself
Put it on
This is perfect
And this one too, put it on
Overcoat, I've seen it in China
Be serious
Every one on the gambling table
has his own style
This is the scare armour
for the Gambling Saint
That's right
From now on
your nickname will be the Gambling Saint
You'll have your own style
The Gambling Saint
May I know how to spell your nickname?
Bull shit
Shit
Stop playing with the dirty stuff
Put on the sunglasses
so that none can see your eyes
Also
put some gel on your hair to look tougher
I can't do this Why not?
Really not Why not?
I hate styling gel
Don't push me. Uncle Tat
Where's the little bastard
Come here, put on some gel
Gel on the moustache
how about my armpit?
Don't kid, come on
I'm serious
I don't want to gel the whole body
Uncle Tat, I want to tell you
It is all useless if I don't Iooktough
That's why you need this gel
on your hair. Then you look tough
Please don't, it stinks
Stink your ass, I have it
all over my face and can't smell it
Come here, smell Together
Oh, shit
Your appearance is OK
but you need to watch your posture
This I can't teach you
you better watch the video
The God of Gambler
He looks great, I admire him so much
Iwill never look like him
That's why you need to learn
What is he walking so slowly?
Is that a wig?
What? I've washed it many time
and it still smells
What time shall we meet him?
7 o'clock
Mr. Hung, he's here
Please
Bring it
You should be proud of yourself
you even walk differently
Are you Mr. Hung?
Right
What can I do for you, Mr. Hung?
I always like to gamble
with the youngsters
Why don't we forget about gambling?
I can show you some of my tricks
And that's it for today
Show your tricks
This is a good one
I haven't seen before
Wrong
This means prosperity for everyone
Full of fortune for the whole family
Can you see the Aces?
Don't screw up this one
This is called vanishing
Everything's gone
Are you OK? I hope I haven't hurt you
I knew these tricks when I was a kid
We'd better talk about gambling
I hope that's not necessary
Why can't let me in? You can't go in
Icant?
lam his uncle as well as his manager
What are you doing inside?
It's none of your business
Leave him alone then. Can I sit down?
This $500,000 is your capital
We'll play around of dice. You don't
have to pay me back if you lose
If you win, the money is all yours
That's nice
Then you don't have to worry
I'll play it slowly then. Good luck
Ready the dices
0k
Mr. Hung
You first
Thanks. Give me new dices
I have to use ivory dices
Those three were made by ivory
I mean ivory from North Pole Elephant
North Pole?
Forget it
I'll live with Indian elephant
You can start
Come on
$50,000 for big
Big or small
Please give me some change
I'll bet $50 small
No, minimum bet is $50,000
Open 3, 5 and 5, big
Mr. Hung, I think this guy is a fool
OK, let me show his hand, small
I don't believe
you can see through the cup
Who do you think you are?
I don't believe it, too bad
That's not bad
you must have practiced a lot
Great. What's the matter?
Great. Terrific, Good
Yee Mong Mr. Hung
Give him another $500,000
All right Mr. Hung
It's time for dinner
Can I invite both of you to dinner?
Mr. Hung asked me to give you $500,000
He wishes you can win
No problem, just tell me, I will win
Let's start
Please put down your bets
4, 5 and 6, big
Open
3, 2 and 2, small
So the kid likes Yee Mong
3, 6 and 5, big
3, 4 and 1, small
That's great, 3 sixes, 3-of-a-kind
Cheer up
I hope you can work for me All right
No need to explain
I've been waiting so long
Don't worry, he will call us back
Mr. Hung, shall I call him back?
No, don't push him too much
Better set him up slowly
They didn't ask for us
Is it? We better go back ourselves
My Yee Mong
Stop dreaming
why does Mr. Hung invite you?
Because I could see through things
Really?
Do I wear underpants?
You've worn Luk's
Did you win then?
Just afew million
Over a million
its good enough for a house
I've given the money away as tips
You gave out a million as tips?
You told me to have style
and treat money as shit
You're not young anymore, don't pretend
Someone can see through things
in this world
You are now with Hung Kwong
Don't let him know who you really are
Are you kidding, boss?
You just give us $700,000 each month
I didn't say I want you
I just want your nephew
If you want my nephew
you have to sign me too
There are some conditions
We need body guards
for cars we want Rolls Royce
For flying, we want first class, and
Stop for now
I'll leave this condition open for you
You can add this later
Is it okay with you?
More or less
My conditions are much simpler
I need your nephew to represent Taiwan
To win the World Gambler Championship
Then you'll have everything you want
If not, you are breaking the contract
I'll do my best, it's difficult to say
Remember
breaking contract means death for you
Is there such term in the contract?
It's just been added
Mr. Hung, we'vejust checked
The kid is going to sign with Chung
tomorrow
As soon as
he signs the contract with them
Even if we get him
According to the regulations
We can't send him for the Championship
But we cannot let him
represent Taiwan too
Betray me? Take him to the dogs
I didn't do it, I didn't do it
Better sign
everything according to your conditions
Yes, except the condition you just said
In this World Gambler Championship
the reward is ten million
Do I have to explain to you? No
English? Let me do it. A, B, C, OK
Sign here? It's your turn
Why did the Taiwanese don't look at you
when he speaks
I don't know
Never mind
rich people have peculiar temper
But I have something to ask him
face to face
Hey Boss
my nephew has something to ask you
I had something to ask you
It's about...
Don't ask...
Better ask now
if you had something in mind. Ask then
Oh, I just want to know
why you always look up
Done
Follow me, let's hide in the room
Run faster
Oh, no
The exit...
Up-stairs... Quick
Let's go up-stair
Yee Mong
Watch out
Be careful
Go downstairs
Bon, are you all right?
You just arrive at the right time
let's go
I can't believe you would do this
If I kill Hung Kwong. You would do
the same thing if you were me
Good for you, Yee Mong
At last you're doing the right thing
Nonsense. The right thing?
She is always been mine
Get rid of him
Let's forget it. Spare him
He saved me once
Good, you do have my style
Let's go
Yee Mong is not suitable for you
Boss, this way please
there's too many people
Yee Mong, are you all right?
Don't leave me...
Boss, jump
Jump quickly
Are you crazy? It's too high
God, they're crazy
I'll jump first, follow me
Do we have another choice?
I am not young anymore
Don't be afraid, I'll go first
And I'll get you, okay?
Make sure you can
All right, I'll catch you, come on
This signal is so confusing
Run away quickly
Don't chase me, here I come
So you're still alive
Run, run quickly
You bastard
you said you're gonna to catch me
be quick shut up
You bastard
Come on...
It hurts
Come on, be quick. The ship is leaving
Yee Mong, are you all right?
Yeah, thank you
But I cannot be Mr. Hung's undercover
anymore
No more undercover
we have to fight man to man
Hey, be serious
Are you all right?
Yeah, and you? I'm ok
I'm hurt
It's a small scratch, no big deal
No, I want ice-cream
My God, after meeting Yee Mong
that bastard...
doesn't think anything else but her
The tournament is going to start
tomorrow
Please bless him to win. Thank you
He only sends some to protect us
but not help us to do the housework
Be a good boy Sing, what card it is?
Somebody is coming back
Luk, what's wrong with your waist?
Rheumatism. Sing
I'll prepare some soup for you
You guess
Yee Mong
Right... guess again
The tournament is going to start tomorrow
You'll get yourself killed
if you keep being like this
Yee Mong doesn't have moustache
Don't move your hand
what have you been doing?
I've told you that Yee Mong would not
fall for a country boy like you
Oh, Yee Mong
If you have money
Don't move
You are a pain in the ass
Yee Mong, pick one first
I'll revenge
Where are you? Yee Mong
BOSS
Sing I've found you Yee Mong
I've found Yee Mong for you
It's lucky that you speak up
The same for you
Sit down, time, place, where
Of course I can tell you
but I have a deal
For mine & Yee Mong's sake
I'll do anything
If you win tomorrow's tournament
I will bring you to Yee Mong
No problem
What's this card?
Ace. Diamond Ace
You can't go inside
King and Three two pairs
for Canada Representative
Six full-house
for Hong Kong Representative
Hong Kong representative win
We Win
Thank you, thank you
Thank you
A covered Ace Great
This round doesn't count
Boss The contract has been signed
I don't think we've got the deposit
Uncle, did we win?
Yes Where's Yee Mong?
Boss, we'll go first
We finally did it
What is it? You look
Very pretty
Do you like it?
What are they doing?
Protect you
Protect? Wait a minute
Why are you following me?
This is my duty
I am having a romantic time
with Yee Mong, leave us alone
Go away or I'll lose temper
Lose temper?
I got five men here, you better watch out
Now you are the bad buy
Yes, so what?
You got it, there's nothing I can do
That's enough
I don't believe
they would dare fighting back
Boss
if Sing doesn't want to be followed
Let's fix them up
I'm glad that I am his relative
I should be safe
Don't follow him if Sing doesn't like it
The best body-guard is already
next to him
That is Yee Mong
Sometimes you have to trust the women
Ying
Tat
why are you so urgently looking for me?
Nothing, I know you are a good fighter
I need you and your girls' help
Tat, so you are in business again
But I and my girls haven't done this
for a while
It's been a while
since I last did it too
The thing is, my nephew is in trouble
I need some girls with good Kung Fu
to protect him
If I can't get it, no one can get it
Yes
I have worked for Mr. Chan
for many years
Very few people knows that
Mr. Chan treats me good
I lost my parents when I was small
He's been taking care of me since then
What are you laughing at?
I just want to go to toilet
What I mean is
I'll laugh when I want to go to toilet
Excuse me
Kneel down
Mr. Hung wants him, not you
It's not worth to sacrifice for him
come with me
Let's go
Yee Mong
Don't go
Jesus Christ?
No, it's uncle
Don't go out
Don't stop me
Uncle Tat
You can't fool me anymore
You think I'm stupid?
Is you? Right
Are you all right?
Yeah, what's this? How about you?
I'm ok
Bubbles coming out Yes
How come?
I don't know, Let's go
Royal Flush
Hong Kong Representative wins
Taiwan Representative Mr. C.S. Cho
is absent due to sickness
I haven't won Hung for 10 years
I am going to win this time
Since you are getting old and stupid
to let him absent
Boss
what Yee Mong did has torn him apart
This is forgivable
I don't give a shit
if he absents for one more round
Sing will definitely be knocked out
I'll bet my life on it
Your life? That's too much
I said yours, not mine
Boss, do you think we can find Yee Mong?
I don't know, maybe she is dead already
Sing
Falling in love again
I love her but she doesn't love me
Nephew
Uncle, you better leave me alone here
You will never understand love
Of course I understand!
When I was young
I also experienced a lot of
life-torturing romances
It's not life-torturing
if you have more than one relationships
Open your eyes
I don't want to see anything
but Yee Mong
Open up your bloody eyes
Don't touch It's all illusion
you can see it but can't feel it
Home come you have her picture?
I got it from my boss to comfort you
Give it to me, give it to me please
Ok, let me tell you then
appearances change
Today Yee Mong is so fine
but after some time
Because of the magic of your love
She'll gain weight gradually
I will try my very best to nourish her
Because she always look at you
with half open eyes
She'll gradually become... like this
These'll be Yee Mong's eyes?
Yes, Can't you see yourself in her eyes?
Yes, I can
This is, living in a world of love
she'll always smile
I'll make her happy every day
That's why her mouth will grow bigger
Will her mouth grow
if she kisses too much
Yes. That's why after a few years
Her mouth will become. Like this
Can this be her mouth?
Don't you see her lips
are opening for you?
Yes, I can feel it
She will be so proud to have your love
I will do my very best
to make her feel proud
She will be proud of me
When she's proud, her nose will grow
When her nose grows
she will be like this
Jesus...
Don't
this is Yee Mong after a few years
It wont be
Nephew, look at yourself now
You won't love her
you wanna change your mind
You won't love Yee Mong anymore
Only because
she gains a little bit of weight
She changes because she loves you
But now you wanna dump her?
No, my love for her will never change
Ok, from now on
You'll have to get used
to her future look
A pretty woman will change
Especially when a woman falls in love
who will change even faster
If you think you should give her up
I'll destroy this for you
No, uncle, no, give me back, don't
Don't do it, give it back to me
There you go
I will not give you this picture
I will give her to you in person
Where is it?
Yee Mong, come on in
Fix him up
Yee Mong Sing
Fix me up, come fix me up
No
Why not?
I have tried hard to get involved
but I can't, he smells fishy
Making fun on my girl? I will kill you
You go out, go out, go out first
Bastard, what do you want?
It looks bad
When we split the money with Tat
it looks better
With Sing
we will be rich for the rest of our lives
We?
I do itjust for you
I didn't spend too much time
with your dad
But in my memory
That's why even you're not my son
But in my heart
I have always treated you as my own son
I am sorry, uncle
I don't know my supernatural power
can cause all these troubles
Your supernatural power
has nothing to do with it
But it is Yee Mong
Your love for her
has affected your power
From now on you have to forget about her
Build up your confidence
recover your power
I am deeply in love
I have no one to depend on
You do, you can depend on Ping
You can change your target
No, I can't, Ping is not Yee Mong
Yee Mong is my Goddess, not Ping
That's right
you can even call me your Goddess, right?
No, Yee Mong is a Goddess with make-up
Ping can be one too
Can she?
Can I?
Sing, be ready for your Goddess
Ping is coming
The Democratic Goddess
This doesn't count
What're you looking at?
It's you
Sing, what are you doing?
I found Yee Mong
This mole on the armpit...
What do you want?
We can talk
Fishy Sing
don't stare at sing like this
It looks weird on the street
For money's sake, raise her arm, go
Luckily her scar is not on her butt
Going out, Sing?
Need any drinks?
Yee Mong, what do you want?
Give me a lemon squash
Yee Mong likes iced coffee
I don't drink coffee
Whoa are you? I am talking to Yee Mong
shut up
OK, one coffee for her, one for Yee Mong
I want a lemon squash with a mixed grill
Please give me a pig's knuckle
It's finished, thank you
Nuts
So he knows you like mixed grill
Are you hot? You are sweating
Of course I am
I have to raise my hands all the time
I am talking to Yee Mong, shut up
I will clean up your sweat
Stop fooling around. I will do it
I thought I will never see you again
They are both freaks
Actually
I am a fighter, do you believe?
I am the boxing champion of Guangdong
two years in a row
Overall champion, before I came here
I just won the match
Against Fukian's champion
do you know that?
Yee Mong, are you listening? That's true
Actually I, really want you to know that
After you left
I beaten up the guys, I want you to know
Peter is looking for you
I am busy
I want to tell you I care about you
Yee Mong wants to sleep
she is getting tired now
She is talking to me right now
how can it be?
I really need to take a leak
it cannot be controlled, let her go
You are lying, give me back my Yee Mong
I don't believe it
How would you have the need
if you haven't had anything?
Eat something first
Eat
Take this rib-eye, it's tender
It's useless, Yee Mong has no teeth
how can she eat?
It seems better with some ketchup
Shit, I will have allergy
Put some mustard it's even better
It's notjust allergy
I will be in deep trouble
It is perfect now
Yee Mong likes sausage
Are you crazy?
You said you have lost your teeth
and can't eat
We'd better eat something good, waiter
Two lobsters, one baked crab shell
That's not necessary
Yee Mong is full already
You don't have to eat, right?
What are you doing?
Yee Mong is sick
Doctor...
You are crazy!
I really don't want that kind of money
How can an armpit eat lobsters?
It hurts so much
You really have a great arm-pit
it even eats the shell
You wanna see Yee Mong? Forget it
Are you OK, Yee Mong?
It's OK
Call the ambulance, quick
The doctor said
my hand will take a week to recover
Are you happy now?
I'll bring you to a place you like
Where's that?
It's nice, isn't it?
Yee Mong, is it nice? Yee Mong
Yee Mong, are you all right?
Yee Mong, you've knocked out!
Oh, you're here again
You steal Luk's underwear again
Tat
She knows I've stolen her underwear
Shit
Ah Ping, what?
What's wrong with your armpit?
I want to go sun bathing with Yee Mong
You better go & put sun tan oil first
What are you looking at
haven't seen an arm-pit before?
What's wrong?
Look at your mother's if you want
2 million
Do you need anything, sir?
Thanks
2 million for 4 of a kind?
You really know how to play
Sir, please do not
pick your teeth with the card
Sorry
You can't use this one either
But I have covered Ace
I'm lucky all my life
I'll see
if I could have 4 aces of a kind
2 million, 5 million more
I'll see if you are really lucky or not
I'll follow
Please deal
It's really unbelievable
I'm calling the shot
Show your hands
It's not the last hand, I'll come again
Loss to 4 twos
Right, save it for the next game
Uncle How about the matter?
Don't take chance, it's too dangerous
It's impossible, I can hear
his heart beat, it's bursting
Don't do it next time
Yes. Time to start
Please sit, we take photographs later
Ladies & gentlemen, this is
to introduce Taiwan champion gambler
Mr. Chan Chung together
with Wong Hung Kwong from Hong Kong
Signing the gambler Championship
Apart from the money
Both sides agree to place bet
for the amount of US$100,000,000 each
To be formal, I would like each of you
to act as witness
Now, both parties will sign the contract
Well, are you winning?
Of course
Good night
Let's say thank you to the God
Where is Shing?
Maybe in the room
Luk, where are the incenses?
It's under the table
Why are you cleaning up?
I used to live happily here before
It's because of Luk
Chee and Blackie Tat
We arejust like a family
Though we've fought over mahjong bills
And always have quarrels
but there's no hard feeling
But since Sing arrived from China
I have been hiding
and let you go out with him
It's all Blackie Tat's fault
look at him
He's Tat's uncle, but he never
teach his nephew to work hard
And treat him as his golden egg
he sees Sing like his father
He beg him, pledge him, look at yourself
I loved you
because you were respectable in the past
There's a lot of rich guy
offer you their hands
But you turn them down, money is nothing
It's important to be happy
You don't need to keep him company
I feel so bad
to see you doing this kind of thing
You talk like a man of honour
I like it
Really?
Shing, don't blame Ping
it's all my fault
Sure it is
you betray your friends, your family
Forgive me, God
It's none of God's business
God gives you special power
you should make good use out of it
and help the poor
But you just use it for girls and money
I am not treating you as my golden egg
It's because
I've been poor for a long time
I Just want us to have some good days
in future
I know this is tough
If we haven't signed the contract
I won t let you do it
I'm sorry, Uncle
Sorry to make you all so sad
I gotta go now
If you go to Guangzhou someday
I'll show you around
Hey, uncle, I think we've made a mistake
I'll never gamble again
and you better quit it too
Shit, I wonder if they are OK
It's all your fault
Let's try to find him
OK, let's go
They can go, but not you
My friend, have you seen this guy?
No
Look again
Tat
Find someone when you're still young
get married
But never marry a gambler
Give me 'play boy' please
Where's it?
I've seen him in the casino before
Really?
Seems like Hung's man
You think they have Sing?
I don't know Follow him
Taxi
How are you? Long time no see
How are you? Very good
Come get your food
The girl looks familiar
That's Yee Mong
the girl on the picture Tat showed us
If we save her
Chung from Taiwan will surely release Tat
You are smart
Hong Kong representative Hung Kwong
is here
Taiwan Representative Chan Chung
is here also
Give away
Your 100 million US dollars, I will win
Over there
The Gamblers Championship lasts from
within two hours
Whoever wins all the chips
from the other side is the winner
If that can't be done
whoever has more chips
at the end of 2 hours wins
You wanna kill someone with that spanner
It's still moves
Move? You son of a bitch
Let's go, you wanna kill him?
I'll kill yOu
Don't rape me, please don't rape me
don't you rape?
I'll send you back
What happened? Why does C.S. Cho
from Taiwan still not arrive?
I want to talk to thejudge
I want to postpone the game
for 10 minutes
OK, let's do this
The Taiwan representative
doesn't feel good
The doctor is on the way
Ladies and gentlemen, we have decided
To postpone the game for 10 minutes
You will replace him, can you?
Let me do it
this isn't breaking any rules
You look at me
don't you both like looking at me?
All of you are useless
how can you let him runaway?
If he doesn't come back later
I will castrate you
Brother, do me a favour
when you castrate
Use a sharp knife
or the wound will get inflamed
We don't use knife, we use hammer
Hammer?
We like to knock it down
The game has been postponed
for 10 minutes
Taiwan's Mr. Cho still hasn't shown up
According to the regulations
if one side is absent
And can't participate, he is giving up
So the champion of the game is...
Wait a minute
Taiwan's representative is here
Damn it, I thought he won't come
He really scared the shit out of me
that's ridiculous
He put on hair gel, He really did!
Now both sides are here, the game...
Wait a minute
A friend of yours sends his regards
I will be the winner of this game
It's Yee Mong's earring
I think your power is gone, isn't it?
Please be ready
Shit, I can't see the cards
What is he doing?
Does he fake it out?
I wanna quit
What's he doing, wanna quit now?
What the hell is going on?
He fakes it out?
He wanna make fun of me?
Please be quiet, ladies and gentlemen
He hasn't got the right to quit
let me tell you
If he loses the game, I'll kill you both
Boss, Sing is kid
if you want to kill somebody, kill me
My skill is definitely
not as good as his
All right, I'll have to take the chance
Sorry, I think I'll play again
That's right
be a gentlemen like a Taiwanese should
Please start
Mr. Hung, yourturn
$500,000
Mr. Cho, your turn
I'll follow, add another $100,000,000
What kind of strategy is this?
I've never seen it
Young man, this is only the 1st round
I'll quit
What is he doing?
This is only the 1st round
I don't know either, that crazy folk
Mr. Cho, your turn
I'll bet everything
let's not waste our time
Are you kidding?
Betting all you have again?
What's the matter?
Mr. Hung, be calm, you may quit
Please do not interface
your opponent's mood
Mr. Hung looks a little emotional
I'll quit
What's the little bastard doing?
What are you looking at? Show your cards
Again?
One more time
What's wrong with him?
Each game is the same
What do you know
he knows his skill is not as good
He is forcing Mr. Hung to bet on chance
Chance?
Mr. Hung, yourturn
$2 millions
Mr. Cho, your turn
Show hand, show hand
I'm listening to the crowd
Be slow, we still have time
There's only 15 minutes left
I cannot go on like this or I will lose
Can I be beaten by his beginner's luck?
Have you heard of beginning's luck?
Be quiet, everybody quiet please
I don't believe
you use such a poor trick
This is the best trick, idiot
Why don't we forget about skill
just bet our luck, start dealing
You'll lose if you don't have a flush
If I have a flush
your 3-aces will have to go
3-of-a-kind, can't I have 4-of-a-kind?
Then can't I have a royal flush? Deal
What about now? Can you hit 4 aces?
If you can, then you'll beat my flush
What's it?
Don't dare show us your cards?
What is he doing?
Shifting the cards
This is the state-of-the-art
Have you finished?
I have the right to think, haven't I?
You're playing with me, aren't you?
What is going on?
It takes so long to open his cards
Tat... Tat...
What are you waiting for?
I don't care who's coming, open up
Open your cards
Look at Sing
He is getting the Ace
Ace...
Ladies and gentlemen, 4 Aces
You wanna beat my flush with 3 Aces?
stop dreaming, oh, spade Ace?
I win, so I shifted it over there
I got it, Uncle Tat
He won
The covered card should be Heart K
what about now?
Nothing, the biggest you have is an Ace
He has 3-Aces, therefore he wins
He's cheating
That's right, so what
where's the evidence?
You changed my card
Security, get him
I object
Cheating in front of me?
You think I'm stupid? Take him out
Ladies and gentlemen, I announce that
The Champion of today's competition is
Mr. C.S. Cho representing Taiwan
I didn't expect the kid to be so good
Thanks for bringing Yee Mong here
so that I can use my power
Shing, you were right about me yesterday
I should use my power to help those
who really need help
Congratulations
Thanks for giving me the chance
to be with you
I know you did all these for business
I know we are from two different worlds
Yes
I have spent all my life in the US.
I could get my PhD degree
at the age of 18
But later
my father gave me his whole business
Then I didn't need the PhD degree
I have a wish, I wish that...
Uncle
What a coincidence, let me introduce
This is my nephew Sing
you just met before
Sing, this is my new girlfriend Pheonia
Not this one
I know...
Pheonia, how are you?
I'll leave you then All right
Tonight, we...
Congratulations, Uncle Tat