Presented by Cinema Service
Produced by Hanmac Films
57 B.C.
As the tribal age of darkness
and incantation was coming to its end
with the birth of new kingdoms
the kingdom of Shilla, founded by
PARK Hyokkose began to annex
nearby tribes with its military
power Auta The Leader of Moon
Tribe PARK Hyokkose
The First Emperor of Shilla
Why do you bear such hatred
to kill my people?
How can I forgive those who disgrace
my land with wicked spells
Your land?
We have resided here as long as
that Great Tree had been!
How dare you to claim
this land as yours?
I had given you a chance to
become a servant of my kingdom
but you've refused!
I'll grind your skin and
bones into ashes!
As long as this sword is here, you
will not trouble the world again!
THE LEGEND OF THE EVIL LAKE
896 A.D. - The 9th year under the
reign of Queen Chinsong of Shilla
The rebels are everywhere and our
people are crossing the border...
Our country is in distress
They say a hero is born
in troubled times
If you could help us to...
CHUNG Jun-ho
I never heard of a subject choosing
it's own monarch KIM Hyo-jin
Do not misunderstand
KIM Hae-ri CHOI Won-seok
I meant people suffer because of
monarch's wrongdoing
Then, you must faithfully
serve Her Majesty
One only sees
what he wishes to see
I'm helpless to protect Shilla
alone from all the rebels
The Great Emperor of Shilla
please grant me the strength to defend
the 1000 year sovereignty of Shilla.
Attack!
Executive Producer
KANG Woo-suk Thomas LEONG
Screenplay HONG Joo-ri
Adaptation
LEE Seung-moo LEE Kwang-hoon
Cinematography
KIM Yoon-soo LU Yue
Lighting LEE Seung-ku HAO Feng
I have alerted the rear guards
Sound KIM Bum-su JIANG Biao
Martial Arts Director YUEN Tak
Talwi!
Editing LEE Hyun-mi
Music LEE Dong-joon
Sound Supervisor LEE Kyu-seok
Even after a victory, they look
like bunch of stragglers
Hold your tongue.
You haven't even engaged in a
decent battle, General BANG.
Your Majesty, my duty is to guard you. So no chance
was ever given to me. Assistant Director LEE Jin-gu
Co-producers
CHOI Hee-il DOH Seong-hee
Producer Jonathan KIM
Director LEE Kwang-hoon
How will we control the overwhelming
power of the rebels?
We have to make sure our people
do not sympathize with them
Your Majesty, we should send an envoy
to China and await for their reply.
I'm afraid China will attack Shilla
under the pretext of reinforcements.
You must abolish the aristocratic
system and find men of ability.
I believe your duty is in National
Defense, not in domestic affairs.
You should mind your own duties.
Quiet.
The country is filled with thieves and
the palace is filled with conspiracies
to over throw the throne.
Biharang!
Will you stay and protect
me till the end?
Your Majesty, I'll do my best
as your royal servant.
Biharang.
Your Majesty.
Jaunbie was the name?
Don't get caught up with
a peasant like her.
Master, how have you been?
Your wound seems severe. It
must've been a fierce battle.
I'll be ok. Please don't be
worried about me.
General!
Will you marry me?
About Biharang's girl...
Her father was executed
for helping the rebels.
Your Majesty, how can you trust a
man who refuses marriage proposals
from royal families for
a peasant girl?
I have killed too many to
save my country.
That is your fate.
If you hold on to a passing fate,
it becomes yours.
Your Majesty! The rebels have
invaded Mujinju.
Their force is too strong. We
must send Gen. Biharang.
The Capital was recently attacked
by the revolting peasants.
Send Gen. KIM instead to
Mujinju for the back up!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, the rebels have
captured Mujinju!
What happened to
the governor of Mujinju?
He was killed mercilessly.
Your Majesty, only Gen. Biharang
can save us from the rebels.
Your Majesty, losing Daeya Fortress
will put Shilla in a great danger.
Allow me to defend Shilla
from the rebels.
I've put you back out in the
battlefield, again.
That is my duty.
Already 9 years have passed.
If there weren't so many battles,
you and I could've been together.
Back then...
I needed Prime Minister Wihong to
protect the throne.
However,
the only one I ever cherished in
my heart was...
Your Majesty.
I heard he was concerned about you
even on his death bed.
Yes, he was.
Biharang,
if the battle becomes too critical,
spare yourself and return to me.
General!
It will protect you.
You must be strong. Love turns
into hatred when it's broken.
- General BANG,
- Yes, sir.
Her Majesty shows too much
affection to Gen. Biharang...
General has been seriously
wounded. Come with me now.
Don't blame me for killing you.
I'm only carrying out an order.
Talwi!
Let's get a little taste
before we kill her.
I must be off. Take care of
the rest thoroughly.
There might be an ambush.
You shouldn't go alone.
The sword has vanished.
This place gives me creeps.
Let's get out of here quick.
Jaunbie!
Let's split up and look for her.
Be careful!
Jaunbie!
- Jaunbie!
- General!
Jaunbie!
General!
Get off me!
- General! It's no use!
- Jaunbie! Jaunbie!
Though she wanted to be my wife...
she never asked me of anything.
And she never said anything
for she feared she might
hinder my future.
The seal set by Emperor Hyokkose
1000 years ago has been broken.
And, now the evil spirit
of Auta is free again.
Auta! Who is he?
Before the time of Shilla, there were
many tribes who shared this land.
Auta was a leader
of one of the tribes.
My ancestors were commissioned by
Emperor Hyokkose to guard the seal.
The duty was passed down
to me for thousand years.
And Jaunbie was to succeed me...
General,
on my way home, I saw
officers dressed in black.
One of them had a large
scar on his face.
Aren't they the Royal Guards?
Who dare stops us?
Kill them!
General!