Nowadays, drug traffickers use every...
conceivable method to ship drugs
They put the drugs into condoms...
then into the stomach, anus, even corpses
Including babies' corpses
Last year alone, there were over...
150 deaths by poison when...
broken condoms leak drugs into the...
internal organs
But drug traffickers who die this way...
are in the minority
Most pass through customs successfully
Fighting narcotics has always
been a very important mission to us...
at the Royal Hong Kong Police
We know this data well
Can you get to the point?
Most of the drugs coming through...
South-east Asia come from...
a drug lord named Chaibat
If we arrest him, the drugs on the...
market would be reduced by half
In what aspect can the Royal
Hong Kong Police help you?
What we need is a super cop
Well, let me think about it
I'll let you know tomorrow
Fix it for me, tell me tomorrow
Yes, sir
That's a senior officer for you...
delegate, then disappear
How true
Fix it for me
I knew it
Call Ka-kui for me
Yes, sir
Thank you
Good morning, sir Morning
They're in a meeting
You can't ask Ka-kui to do this
Why not? Is he irresponsible?
He's very responsible
Does he disobey his seniors?
Whoever he disobeys must be bad
All you do is talk; you complain that...
I don't give him a promotion...
Here's a chance, but you stop me
You call this a chance?
A China labour camp is no joke!
Are you afraid he can't handle it?
If he can't, then no one can
I know; asking him to walk the beat...
is a waste of his talent, I know that
Now Interpol needs a super cop
Ka-kui is a super cop
But you won't let him do it
I know, but it's very dangerous
He's been with me for so long
How can I ask him to risk his life?
If you can't ask him, then I'll go back...
to Interpol and tell them...
no one in the Royal Hong Kong Police...
can so this, okay?
They should ask James Bond
Correct
Hello, sir
Uncle Bill
Come in, Ka-kui
I need you
Please, sit
What's so urgent?
I found you a great position
Duty desk at Sha Tau Kok precinct
Just sign here
Uncle Bill, let me do it
Isn't that what I'm doing?
Sha Tau Kok is great,
all that fresh air...
no need to walk the beat
I meant the Interpol job
You heard?
Let me do it
It's very dangerous
Uncle Bill, it be more dangerous...
to do a job every day...
that you feel nothing for...
and wait for the end of your shift
Do you need to discuss it with May?
No, I've already decided
Go home and pack
Yes, sir
Ka-kui
Yes?
Chief will be very happy
Aren't you happy?
I'd be happy if Chief will do this job
Are we too devious?
Yes, but you more so than I
Why?
You're my senior officer
Why do you have to go to camp?
You're not allowed to make phone calls
It's a special training camp
After this training, I may get a raise
You're not happy?
No, I hate it when you have those
special missions
Camp is best; it's safest
You won't be risking your life
This is my life insurance policy
This is my bank passbook
Why are you giving them to me?
You're the beneficiary; come
What's wrong?
My safety deposit box key
I have some foreign currency in there
Why are you giving me these things?
Aren't you coming back soon?
I'm worried it might take longer
Don't forget to pay my insurance fee...
and extend my banking services
What are you doing?
I'll be gone a whole month!
You'll be late
I won't get shot for it
Remember, no dating boys
No dating boys for you
May
Uncle Bill
One month will be over soon
I'll watch him for you
I must go, bye
Bye!
Goodbye, Uncle Bill
Your ID and air ticket to Guangzhou
Yes, sir
Be careful
Don't worry
China's Public Security Department
will give its full support
Then I'd worry more
Uncle Bill, say something nice
The best thing to say is "Good luck"
With this mission...
the Royal Hong Kong Police...
releases Ka-kui like a kite
The thread may break in the wind
Don't make these dangerous metaphors
Don't worry
If the thread breaks, I'll fly back
I told you he's smart
Good luck
Thank you, sir
Uncle Bill, I must go
Then, really "good luck"
Yes, sir Ka-kui
Stop nagging, will you?
In an emergency, call this number
Remember this number
Tear up the paper afterwards
I remember it
I'm going
I'll tear it up for you
Thank you
I'm making phone calls, don't disturb me
My phone number again
Great, I'll let the world know
Come in, please
Please sit
You're the super cop sent by Hong Kong?
The file from Hong Kong says:
Chan ka-kui parenthesis super cop
Super cops in Hong Kong...
are like goods in a supermarket:
Plentiful, and cheap
This young man is modest
We are one big family
We will do our best to assist you
Thank you all
Because your mission is very dangerous,
and we feel you do not understand
the situation inside China...
we have arranged for some lessons
To learn what?
Superintendent Yang from Interpol
will make arrangements for you
This is Superintendent Yang
How are you, Superintendent Yang?
Study hard
Yes, sir
You two talk together
Yes, Party Secretary
I didn't think Superintendent Yang...
would be such a pretty girl
You may speak Cantonese with me
Great, I feel much better
We start now Sure
From now on, you're Lin Fu-seng
Age 32, a buyer for the...
Foshan Fifth National Machine Factory
Are you clear?
Yes
Your uniform is very stylish
Can civilians wear it, too?
You were with the Foshan Martial Art Team,
Single,
Living at 17 Juanyao Village in Foshan...
with your mother and younger sister
Your father passed away in 1978
Poor thing, his father died so young
Are you clear?
Yes
Then repeat it for me
I'm Lin Fu-seng, age 32...
born in Foshan, I'm a Mushu...
Machine Factory buyer
Mushu Pork fryer
Foshan Wushu Team
I live at 17 something village?
Juanyao Village
That's a tongue-twister
And they call you super cop
You have no memory
Lady, it's my first try
Let's see you try it
I just tell you once:
I am Chan Ka-kui
Born on April 7, 1958...
Joined the Royal Hong Kong Police in 1981
In 19...
In 1984, promoted to Inspector Intern
Height, 5 foot 10; weight 73 kg...
Blood type: AB
I'm not clever
I just studied your data
You do the same, learn it well
Let's get your pictures taken
Take pictures?
I hear the Pearl River Bridge
is really beautiful
Now what?
Your hand here
Smile, look ahead
Now what?
Wushu Team, not opera troupe
Re-do the makeup
You could have said so sooner
Your turn
Spread your legs more
Look ahead, he's ready
Film is "Plastic Roll,
Walkman is Ready Music"
Soda can is...
"Easy-pull can"
Police is "No. 2", militia is "No. 1"
Gun is "Fire Cannon"
Are they all your subordinates?
Grandpa's
What does that mean?
The country's; but under my command
Chan Ka-kui Yes?
You're dead! You're Lin Fu-seng
You trapped me; you're evil
The men you'll be dealing with are worse
So I want you to be very careful
When do we leave?
According to reliable sources,
Chaibat has bribed mercenaries...
to spring Pao from the labour camp
We're just waiting for the right time
Those pictures will suffice?
The powers of modern technology
I know, but I don't know Wushu
Your file says you're a wrestling champion
That's just street-fighting
At the academy, we learned karate,
Taekwondo,
Boxing; Chinese kung-fu...
was not a part of it
This is "Hard Qigung"?
You didn't learn this?
Of course not; you're just standing
and getting hit; how stupid
Superintendent Yang
Comrade Wang; let me introduce...
our Head Coach of the Militia
The super cop from Hong Kong
"Super"? The you must be great
She's too kind
Not at all
He is 7th degree Taekwondo,
8th degree Hopkido...
9th degree Karate, 10th degree Judo...
and twice South-east Asian Wresting
champion, isn't that right?
What can I say?
Then I must learn from you
Of course
Stop training
Gather
Sit
Please
Must you do this to me?
We welcome the super cop from Hong Kong
Come
Is this some kind of a joke?
You'll be fine
Will he really hit me?
No
Stop the match if something happens
Of course not
Just for fun, right?
Sorry
You're great, I salute you
Your reputation is justified
Let's go again
Thank you
Please, play a little longer
How does this work?
Simple; hold here...
step on these
I'll push
How do I stop it?
Next time, you must say I'm
world champion in somersault
No more playing; our mission starts now
Do I look like I'm playing?
They have 3 vehicles, 6 men
Do you remember the coal mine's layout?
Yes
I may not be good at anything...
but my memory is my strong point
Really? I hope you remember where
the high passage is
Don't worry, my life depends on it
Tell your men not to shoot
Some of the guards have no bullets
You two, get ready below
My life depends on you; look out for me
Be careful
Why did you stop! Get to work!
Brother Pao, we go as planned
You hit me!
The prisoners are fighting
Freeze
Pao
Officer
No need
Thank you
Turn off the engine
This is a random check
Hurry
Go look around the back
Get ready to move
What's up there?
Nothing, just coal
Coal?
Officer
There's nothing here
Hua, get going!
Hurry, Hua
Quickly, Hua
Hua
Pao, get up
Let's go, Pao
Stop
Pao
Run
Pao... wait, I don't know him
Chicken Hung!
Hung
You're crazy, let's go
What did Hung say he didn't know?
He didn't know the way
Do you?
Yes, up there
It's so high; how do you get up there?
Jump off
Go up
Run, Pao
Over here
Don't move
There is a high passage up there
Jump down, I'll turn on the switch
All right
Hurry
Turn off the switch Yes
Come with me
Hurry
Someone is after us; hurry
Don't shoot
Just chase them
Hurry
Why did it stop?
I don't know
What to do now?
Get off here
Let's go
Freeze, don't move
Go
No way
This is the high passage?
What are you looking for?
To see if there is an underground passage
Freeze, don't move
There's no time, go
Run and I'll shoot
Go
Some high passage
Are you all right?
Yes
Let's go
Over this hill...
you will see the road; take it into town
Goodbye
Where are you going?
I took $2000 from Hung...
just to take you here
I don't do anything else
You have good moves
Take me into town
I'll take you to Hong Kong to do
big business
Hong Kong is too far
I'll take you into town for $500
I don't have $500
When we get to Hong Kong I can
give you $50,000, not just $500
I don't know you
I don't blame you; trust me
All right, it's a deal
Give me $50,000 in Hong Kong
See? You trust me
Hurry, it will rain soon
How did you know Hung?
I follow whoever has money
Where are you from?
Foshan
Don't you raise pigs in your hometown?
Our pigs eat vegetables
These pigs eat feed, so they stink
Pao
He's one of us
Pao has returned; come out
You're back!
Pao
Bring a towel, quickly
You've lost weight
It's so good you're out,
it must have been hard
What so hard about it?
Labour camp is like vacation
Pao is a big shot wherever he goes
That's right
How did I get in?
Fishball?
I don't know anything
Shar-pei, what happened to our goods?
Confiscated
Pao, it's not my fault, it's not me
No, Pao, I'm sorry
It's my fault, I'm sorry
Give me one more chance
No, Pao
Give me a chance
This here is Fu-seng
He's one of us
Where are the goods from Yunnan?
They arrive in two days
Pao, we must get out of here
Aren't you from Foshan?
Since we have time...
We'll go visit your family
All right
Fishball, Shar-pei, come with me
We'll meet at our old place with the goods
Yes, Pao
Let's go
Fu-seng
Fu-seng, Pao wants you
Yes?
Where is your home?
We're not there yet
This is Foshan
Yes, but we haven't arrived at my village
There's fork ahead, which way?
A fork? The we must stop
Where is it?
The police are behind us, hurry
Fu-seng, are the police
following us?
Don't worry; where do you live?
I live at...
You haven't forgotten where
you live, have you?
I've been gone 3 years
Everything has changed
You must remember something
Yes, but there are so many buildings
Come, Pao
Uncle Fu-seng
Grandma misses you, come home quickly
My nephew
Come home, come!
Third Aunt, Brother Fu-seng is back!
Fu-seng, you have returned!
Great, I'll take you to Mother
My Third Aunt
This way
Not this way, that way
I know, I was helping you with these
No need; follow us, please
Pao, this way
You haven't been back in years
Mother will be so happy to see you
You're home! I've missed you
Brother Fu-seng
You must have done well
Of course he has
See Mother first; she's missed you
Hurry, Fu-seng
Fu-seng's Mom!
Where is she?
Show your friends some hospitality
She may be sleeping
Pao, make yourself at home
Please sit
I have to go
Fu-seng, where is the washroom?
Outside, around the corner
Wherever no one can see you
It's the country-side; go anywhere
Who is that girl?
What girl?
That one
Which one?
The one in the picture of you
Your wife?
She is...
Elder Brother, you're home!
My younger sister
Your sister? Yes
When did you come back?
You've grown so much
You're prettier, too, and fatter
Don't pinch me so hard
You two have a great relationship
Yes, we do
Greet Pao
Hello, Pao
What's your name?
I'm Hua-nui
She's Hua-nui
Hurry, serve Pao some tea
We've always liked to fight
Take off your jacket, it's more comfortable
Fu-seng
How mighty you are
You rascal, haven't been home in ages
You've even grown a beard!
That's fine, Granny
That's "Auntie" to you
Auntie, he is your son
Fu-seng
Yes, Mother, I'm home
You've been away so long...
and you're leaving again so soon
You have squandered the family fortune
Did you bring money home?
Look, you glow at the mention of money
He will, please sit
Please sit
Have some tea, Pao
Please have some tea
Let me do it It's me
Bill, you...
You brought dollar bills?
No
Did you bring money?
Also no
No money and no dollar bills?
He did
He did?
Granny... I mean, Auntie
This is a gift from Fu-seng
For me? What money is it?
Hong Kong dollars
They're valuable
Hua-nui, go buy two boiled chickens
Let me treat you to boiled chickens
The way the world is...
Tai
My sister, that's Tai and Jiang
Hello, Tai, Jiang
Let me introduce you to my Mother
Mother
They're calling you
Calling me?
Let me introduce...
No need
Where are you going? It's dinner time
I'm taking Fu-seng to dinner in town
Rascal, leaving before dinner
I'm taking Fu-seng to make a fortune
Take Hua-nui with you
Great! I'll go change
Take Hua-nui?
Take me with you
Eat here first, we'll be back soon
It's boiled chicken!
Goodbye, Mother
This place is famous for wild game
Whether it's endangered or extinct...
you can eat it here
Hua-nui, eat what you like
All right
Pao, they're here
It's so cruel; your police don't care?
Here's Pao
Pao
Sit; Hua-nui sit here
Have some tea, Pao
They are...
My team, Fu-seng, Hua-nui
Sit over there
Go
Don't look
I think I see Bear
Thanks
Those guys at the entrance are police
Are they yours?
Of course not
He looks like the criminal who escaped
from labour camp
Pao cannot be taken by the police
I know
This is your turf, you find a way
All right
Simple, I'll find out
You two watch them
I'll get backup
What will you have?
Civet braised with Turtle testicles
What did you order?
Get me one, too
Get one more
This is Sergeant Chan Xiang-dong
calling dispatch
Please go ahead
I have found...
Comrade, I'm Interpol Superintendent
Yang Jian-hua
You can't arrest those men
Your identification?
I don't have them on me
Really? Turn, raise your hands
Let's go examine the goods now
They're leaving
We can't wait; we'll check them
Interpol Superintendent Yang calling
Please go ahead
Men...
Stop, we're the police
Don't move, we're the police
Careful
Do you know how to throw these?
At least I scared him
Out of my way
What are you doing? I'm a policeman
What are you doing?
Hua-nui is still there
Run now, save her later
Freeze
Bring them in
Superintendent Yang
Run and I'll shoot
Freeze
You're clear, go ahead
Lin Fu-seng, we've found you
You robbed the vegetable depot...
and People's Bank
You're a daring bastard
And you took on a new guy?
I'll arrest you
Go, quickly
Let's go, hurry
Thank you, sir
Pao, Hua-nui is still there
Never mind, come now
Do you want to go to jail again?
Hurry, Hua-nui
Stupid Bear, so careless
Hua-nui, you are really great
What's wrong?
I killed a policeman
That's normal, killing them
You can't let them kill you
I'll be executed!
I know, so what now?
Come to Hong Kong with me
All right
You're really bringing her to Hong Kong?
I can take you
Of course I can take her, too
We can't let her get caught here
Thank you, Pao
You are both excellent
Let's go
Damn stun gun;
I must bring one to Hong Kong
You really killed a policeman?
Oh, yes
May I come in?
You're so rude; come in
I'm your brother
What is it?
Why are you suddenly coming along?
Orders from above
Do they know I can't protect you...
if you came along?
They want me to protect you
You'll just get in my way
You're too macho
The Commander...
What is it, Fu-seng?
This wench dares talk back to me
and won't obey when I teach her
I'm teaching her a lesson now
What wench?
Mao said, "Women hold up half the sky"
He did?
You two stop fighting
We're near the observation tower
turn off the lights
Come out and help
You hit me so hard when I'm your brother
Would it be better if I'm your husband?
You should have said so sooner
We are the Royal Hong Kong Police
Stop the boat for inspection
Stop the boat
Fu-seng
A trap door
Hurry to the back
Fei, go look; I'll take over
Pao, two motors are destroyed
I'm not that easy to catch
Don't
Get away, don't stop me
Pao
Get away or I'll beat you up
The speedboat is coming
You dare play tricks on me?
Pao
Pao is coming up
Pierre
Pao, you're finally here
It's been a long time
How are you? About the same
That's good
Where is Boss?
Waiting for you
I'll go see him
Yes
Hi, sweethearts; can I join you girls?
Sure, sit down
I have some new stuff for you
Who wants to try it first?
Come on, give me your hand
Fu-seng, come
Relax, you will have a wonderful time
Okay
Close your eyes; you enjoy
Boss
Pao
Sit down
Let me finish this game
You look well, you must have
lived the high life in camp
Thankfully I left quickly
You said you wanted me to meet
two new members of your team
Yes
I can be here thanks only to
the two of them
Game Over
Who are they?
Fu-seng, and Hua-nui
Throw them into the ocean
What?
Boss
Jail made you lose your
awareness?
You brought two police here to see me?
Throw them into the ocean
Wait
Fu-seng
Hua-nui
I was going to do big business with you
But your boss treats us like this
I give you face
Let's go
Such a good chance
The gun is empty
How would you know?
People in my business must be careful
I like you both
Welcome to me team
Thank the Boss
Thank you, Boss
Boss, that woman died after her shot
That's fine
Johnny is an expert in putting drugs
into corpses
See if he'll find it useful Yes
Reuse and recycle
What is your name?
I'm Hua-nui
Have her try on the bullet-proof vest
Sure, follow me
Tomorrow, Hua-nui will go with me
Let me break the record now
Pao
What are we doing tomorrow that
requires a bullet-proof vest?
I'll tell you tomorrow
Come, watch Boss play his video game
Boss, Qiang betrayed Kunchat
Shall we have him dive?
Do the usual
Boss
Lawyer Chan is calling long distance
He needs to speak to you
Chan? Yes
Out of the way
Throw him in
He betrayed Boss
He deserves it
Come up
The phone, Boss
I don't care of we win or lose the lawsuit
But you must ask her to return the
bank code
Don't try your best, you must do it
I know how to reward good work
General
Welcome, Khun Chaibat
Too much rainfall in the Golden Triangle...
caused a bad harvest
I'm afraid I don't have goods for you
Where are your goods?
I can only get 30%, that's not enough
I don't care what you guys want,
I want 3 tons
You heard it, the two of them already...
took half of my stock
Give me the rest
Sorry, I reserved the rest long ago
Don't give anything to others
Do you set the rules now?
You think you're Bush?
I just to tell you today
I won't have any goods for you this year
So the purpose of today's meeting...
is to divide up my share
Is mine not business?
Does my money stink?
Who dares say that
But I've heard...
who hasn't paid for the previous delivery?
I haven't
I have a lot of money in a Swiss bank
If someone had not notified the
Malaysian police...
and had my wife arrested...
I would not owe you
You wife was arrested in Malaysia?
She may tell them about us
Control yourself
Chaibat, you cannot take action
He betrayed me
Talk is cheap
You intend to threaten us? With what?
With what?
General, this is good stuff
What is the matter?
It's a signal from Boss
Let me see
Don't move
No one shoot
These vests are packed with dynamite
I just fire one shot
We will all die together
Boss
Is my sister all right
Don't worry
She'll be fine with Boss
When you hear the explosion...
deal with those two guys for me
Can you do it?
Yes
Good
Put down your gun
Don't think you can take advantage...
of me, and betray me...
because you speak the same language
Chaibat, please understand
I am a businessman
If you have so many private matters...
solve it before you talk to me
Let's go out
General!
I did it, so what?
No one may leave this hut
Surround the hut
I've put up with you long enough
Don't even think about leaving here today
Shoot if you dare, fire!