That should hurt
Bring him back in 3 days
Yoo Oh-sung
Okay
No bath in the meantime
Okay thanks
Bye
Park Jin-hee
Hi, there
Hi
I'd like to buy some food
for Alphonse
- You bought some the other day
- No, No
Seems that he's lost his appetite
So I'd like to try...
Try this
It's new on the market
Special Appearance by
Kong Hyung-jin
Produced by Park Hyung-jun
Still here?
Oh, I had to stop by that store
Why don't you get a hook?
This is the only workout I get
Alphonse...
- Isn't that a writer's name?
- Yeah
I thought so
So many stars tonight
Cause it rained earlier
- You know a lot about stars?
- A little bit
What about constellations?
A little bit
Directed by Jang Hyung-ik
I'm a Capricorn
You know where that is?
It's not too clear tonight
There
To the right of the polestar
BYUL
How was your day?
The 74th time I saw her
She's a Capricorn
Alphonse!
Why don't you get sick?
You're way too healthy
So-ha
Mommy yelled at you again?
- You're a liar, Young-woo
- Why?
She says stars don't talk
and sing to one another
It's all a lie
That's not true
Let me show you
Come on, sit on my lap.
Stop crying
Now look
I don't see anything
No? Let me adjust it.
Try again
Where are the stars?
Liar!
Alphonse
Hey, Young-woo
I'm asking her out today.
How do I look?
Looking good... like a player
You've got no taste whatsoever.
Stay single forever
Young-woo, congratulations!
Going to the Equipment Fair abroad
as the employee of the year
- For real?
- Congratulations
Thank you.
Thanks
- Congratulations
- Thank you
Don't give it away this time
I won't
[Purun Animal Clinic]
Need more dog food?
- No
- I got it, you came for the doctor
No
No, really, I was just
looking at that puppy
Lie, and misfortune finds you
God, what have I done?
So sorry
I didn't see you there
Feels cool, though.
Oh boy
Come on, sit over there and
dry yourself off
Let me get you a towel
Sit here
Alphonse, how are you?
Hey there
Oh... hi
My mother sent me
these sweet potatoes
Move over, mutt
Try some
- Help yourself
- Alphonse
Come on, Miss. Vet
These are good for your system
Far better than ice cream.
Here you go
Boy, he licked it.
You want some, too?
Mr.
Miss. Vet
A beautiful Saturday afternoon
and you all don't have dates?
- How pathetic is that?
- Hello?
Hi there
Yeah, I'm coming
Excuse me
What a good picture!
Go out on a date or something
I don't date customers
What happened to your hand?
Got scratched by a dog
Too bad
Run over by a car...
he was writhing in pain
- Got a girl friend?
- What?
No, I don't
Really, no girlfriend
Him
I was talking about him
Stop smirking, the air's really
thick around here
Now if...
A girl asked if I had a girlfriend.
How should I interpret that?
- Who, Miss. Doggy?
- A veterinarian!
Keep it down
Why don't you go?
I did my tour of duty last year, sir
Wow, a dimwit remembers
Hey... hey! Come here
Alphonse,
when will you get sick?
You got all your vaccinations
You wouldn't mind one more,
would you?
Alphonse?
Alphon... Hey!
Alphonse, hang in there.
We're almost there
We're almost there, don't worry
Alphonse... Alphonse
- I put him under
- Poor boy
The wounds are pretty bad
Got a problem?
Thanks
Don't mention it,
Alphonse is my favorite customer
I wouldn't worry
He'll be up and and running soon
Alphonse, when you get better
go get him good, okay?
They'd send a single guy, right?
Not a man with a family?
What's up with you guys?
It's beautiful out there
You volunteer then
Hell no, I'd rather quit
Hey, employee of the year
- We should celebrate tonight
- Not tonight
Alphonse is sick at the hospital
You blow us off over that mutt?
Let's go guys, it's on me
Alphonse, does it hurt a lot?
He's bad, isn't he?
He told you to get sick everyday
Poor Alphonse...
It's all his fault
- Hi
- How's Alphonse?
- A lot better
Hey, So-ha
Shame on you!
He's sick because of you
- What?
- You told him to get sick!
Your mom's looking for you
I'll be back
You can take him home now
- What?
- Take Alphonse home
No, he's still seems in pain
But he...
And the wounds haven't healed yet
Well... I guess he's all right
Let's go home, Alphonse
You are all better now
Alphonse
Consider it an honor
You'll get a private vet...
And I'll get a wife
Are you up for a stroll?
Concert, movie, play...
Got everything planned out, huh?
Good luck.
Let me see you get married
Yes, Sir
What a thorough plan
If this doesn't work, give up
Why?
You think she hits on you
to sell some dog food?
She might be a gold-digger
Hi there
Hi
What do you want?
I was wondering...
- Are you an art lover?
- What?
Concerts, plays, movies...
You like them?
- I do
- What's your favorite?
All of them
If you have to choose one?
Plays...
Concerts...
movies...
Been a while since I saw a play
There!
That's good
I happen to have tickets for a play
Are you asking me out?
I'll think about it
Okay... that's the way it is
Wait!
Are you her next of kin?
- What?
- You reek of liquor
Anything wrong, officer?
She's in a coma.
Better for you if she dies
What are you talking about?
You drove drunk, bastard!
Sorry
But it wasn't me
It was the car ahead of me
Is that right?
Give me its plate number
Don't know?
You've got to believe me
Can't you see?
By the way...
I'm starving
What do you feel like?
Stop being a pig, man.
Let's go
Now!
Alphonse
Eat, he'll be home soon.
Come on, eat
Aren't you gonna eat?
You might die
Let me out of here, pig!
My father won't tolerate this
- Shut up punk!
- Fuck you
I am going to tell
everything to my pop
My father will kill you!
Young-woo
Hey
I can't believe you did it, man
I didn't
Suits at work are freaking out
over this whole thing...
swearing to have
you shipped off to the boondocks
But don't worry, I won't let them
What will you get for this?
I didn't do it!
Of course, I believe you
Did that vet show up?
What'd I say?
She's been toying with you
Forget that broad
When'd you become an orphan?
When I was little
Must've been tough
No, it was okay
You got some money saved up?
Strike a deal with the victim's family
I didn't do it!
Still!
- Was it you?
- You son of a bitch!
- Cool it, guys
- Hey!
I didn't do it!
It wasn't me!
I simply took her to the hospital!
I didn't do it!
Let go!
Let go of me!
What happened to him?
They just radioed in
they'd busted the real guy
Yeah?
I'd like to go to the Fair
on behalf of Young-woo
I'll wait for your approval.
It's for only a few months
No volunteers?
You want me to go?
I'll go
You've been with us
for only 3 months
3 months and 3 days
Poke your nose where it belongs.
Sit down
Yes, sir
Who's going?
What are you worried about?
A black sheep...
You know who that is
We've all agreed on it
Unbelievable!
He messes up once
and you try to get rid of him?
Why don't you go then?
Stay out of this, okay?
Keep quiet
Justice never loses
Put it all behind you
Life has weird twists
Sorry I've created a fuss
Words won't do
Easy on him, guys
Young-woo,
don't let them twist your arm
You didn't do anything wrong
Shut up and sit!
Quiet!
You've got nothing but big mouths
I will go
Nobody on earth is your friend
It's rough out there
and you give in so easily
Just for a few months
I'll send you a replacement soon
No
You don't have to
Let's go
Damn!
I look worse than a grandpa
Who'd think of my as my age
How's it going?
You're finally here
So glad to see a human up here
And a dog!
Is this my day or what!
Let's drink
To console you on your life
in these boonies
No, congratulate me
- Congratulate you?
- Right
Want me to congratulate you
on coming to hell?
Well then...
- Whatever... Cheers
- Cheers
Congratulate you... well alright
Feels like you're out here
on a picnic, doesn't it?
I felt the same at first
Give it a week, dude
You'll be talking to the walls
I might live here forever
What? Didn't you just hear me?
This is hell
Have you been to hell?
Look at what we're eating, dude
You think this is human food?
This is considered a feast here.
Egg roll I made for you!
What are you,
the god of the mountains?
Let me tell you
I no longer remember
what chicks look like
- It's getting cold
- Eat then
This is cold?
I almost burnt my tongue off!
Shake a leg
That's GukMang Peak
It's breath-taking, isn't it?
So freaking beautiful!
Come on, Young woo
It's the same machine
we have at headquarters
This one's ok
Don't ask me why they don't
make it auto-controlled
This is a troublemaker
A pain in the ass
This one's good
Alphonse!
Here comes Jin-soo!
- How much?
- 5 bucks
- Great hairdo, babe
- You like it?
- I'll drop by later
- I'll be waiting for you
Okay, Ok
[Hambaek Clinic]
Hey there
Where's nurse Kim?
Missed me?
Where does it hurt this time?
I'll be sick in 10 minutes.
Give me some medicine
This is no pharmacy
What are you, blind?
I know, but I am patient
What kind of nurse are you,
treating patients like dirt?
You don't look sick
Doc, stop this Nightingale!
- Eat well
- Okay
- You can go now
- Thanks, doctor
How are you, Doc?
Good, you?
Been good too. It's getting quite
cold up there, though
- It feels like winter in the mornings
- Always eat 3 meals a day
With good food
Hold on, let me say goodbye to him.
She hates me
Take care, Doc.
See you
Time for your medicine, doctor
I take it all the time.
One miss won't kill me
Doctor
Here...
I've brought this for your wife
Awfully nice of you.
Thank you
You saved my son's life.
This is nothing
Try this
A mother of my former patient
Brought this for you
You're so blessed
Not loved by her husband
I'm the least blessed
You save everyone's life
- But not mine
- Stop it
It's true, though
Lately, I keep seeing his face
You're at it again
I don't wanna hear it
Why can't you let it go?
Stop talking about him
Pretty good
Who taught you to cook?
Your mom?
Why couldn't God give me
a mom like yours?
Maybe it's a blessing in disguise
He'll give me a good wife
I wonder if my angel in white
is a good cook
Are you listening to me?
There's this doctor in the village
who's like a god-sent man
A living legend...
Hippocrates!
That's what they call him
Hi
- Just got off of work?
- Right
- How's Alphonse?
- Couldn't be better
God, it's all mildewed
You like it here, don't you?
I do
"I do"
Don't you miss anybody?
Family, friends, or a girlfriend?