Why'd she come here?
Her dying mom gave her a note to find
her aunt here
But her aunt has gone to Canada
She has no one there
What could she do?
Fucked up so she decided to earn money here
Her writing is a total mess unlike her
pretty face
To Lee Kangjae?
It looks like she really took you for
her husband
Dear Mr. Kangjae
Thank you for marrying me
Thank you
Because you married me, I am able to work here
Everyone's kind to me
I want to keep working here
Everybody's kind but you're the kindest of all
Because you married me
I sincerely thank you
Where should we go first?
To the job agency
We need some information about her
Pull over, please
Why?
Even though it's all fake,
I can't go there like this
What?
Why, am I wrong?
Oh, my god!
Thanks to you two, now I can be rest assured
Let's have a drink
Because of that bitch, I'm in this trouble now
I should've helped her then
Have some more
No, thanks
Well, that bitch came to me a month
before she died
Do you know what she said?
She said that she was sick
She looked all right to me
As you know, I'm not doctor
And besides, she owes me lots of money
How could she be sick without my permission?
It's cold
lsn't he a fucking bastard?
If it was his own daughter,
could he still talk that way?
There are so many bastards in the world
Hey, he looks exactly like you,
you know that?
You're like brothers
Shit, stop it!
Born in 1978... Let's see
She's only 23, 24 years old
What a pity at such a young age!
Thank you for marrying me
You're the kindest of all
Good night
You're really making this hard for me
It's warm in here
The cell is so damn cold
Husband, Lee Kangjae,
Occupation, a real hoodlum
A kind idiot who goes to prison for his friend
Wife is a dead bitch who died so pitifully...
You are pathetic and I am, too!
What a perfect match we are...
Why are you hassling her?
I'm just checking if she's legally married or
not, that's all.
Your husband's name?
Lee Kangjae... Lee Kangjae
What's his occupation?
He's in lnchon
He's a sailor
So he's busy
Even if he's that busy,
what kind of a husband never visits his wife?
They're all bastards who make life hard
for their wives
She is a hard-working girl
Just leave her alone
Go on, now!
Husband LEE Kangjae
Wife KANG Failan
The mountain is beautiful
The sea is beautiful, too
I want to see
Dear Mr. Kangjae
Failan!
It's me, don't you remember me?
Hello
Now you can speak Korean well
Failan, aren't you sick any more?
You've got a bit thin
She's really making you work hard, huh?
She's kind, everyone's kind
I thank Mr. Kangjae
Why should you thank Kangjae? For marrying you?
Well, he thanks you, too
He wants to see you
He wants to see me?
Yeah, he fucking misses you a lot
Fu...?
Fucking means... It means...
Anyway, he fucking misses you
Oh, shit! That bastard...
Hey, I'll come back later
Let's do some art together at the beach!
One sheep, two sheep, three sheep...
Why do we get off here?
Let's get some air here
Shit! Fucking crazy... It's freezing cold, fuck!
Now what?
Hey, isn't it good? Wow!
Don't go in there! It's dangerous!
The ice will break
Come on, you chicken!
What did I tell you? Hey, man! Hey!
That's not how you skate
You don't know a thing
Watch me, now!
Ready! Go!
Oh, home, sweet home!
Hurry up! Will you?
There won't be any problem, right?
When your wife's dead,
why would they look you up let alone
consoling you?
Are you a criminal?
You always feel uncomfortable
with cops, right?
Hey... You go in alone
Am I Failan's husband? Why should l?
Do I have to cry?
That's a bit exaggerating but
you should look sad
Hurry up!
All right! Wait!
I'm freezing!
Let's go in!
Who's the husband?
I am
Do you have your lD?
I forgot to bring it in such a hurry
But I brought this instead
Her social security number is...
781 01 1 245431 1
You even memorize your wife's number?
Husband LEE Kangjae
Wife KANG Failan
She died the day before yesterday, right?
Yes...
Since we were apart for a long time
I didn't know she was ill so...
If she had told me, I could...
That'll be all.
That's all? Can we go now?
What do you mean?
Let's go
What do you mean by that?
Hey, let's go
I meant that the process is over
so you can go now
Okay, I see
But wait!
Why is it that simple when
a person had just died?
lsn't it strange?
What do you think you're doing?
I'm not doing anything, but...
What the hell is he doing? Hey!
We're sorry
Yes, sir!
What did you say? Is she your wife or what?
It's over, just get out of here!
I don't want to stay here either
He's just very upset, sorry, sir
Ah, am I a criminal or what?
Hey, who the hell do you think you are, huh?
Why are you so pissed off?
Is she really your wife?
Legally, yes
Jesus, you're really losing your mind
Anyway, I don't know what the
hell's got into Yongsik
He asked me to say hello to you
Anything else?
Just give him a call
Take this!
You should move this
Don't touch
How may I help you?
Sir!
What is it?
I can tell who's the loser
Right
Do it quickly
I'm sick
What?
I'm very sick
What? You're sick?
I will work very hard
I can recover, I'll try hard
You don't look sick to me!
If I don't get your money in time,
my toes are sick, too
I can't wait even a month
Checkmate
You can put it here
Leave it there
Great
You're always smiling
Do you know how scared I am right now?
I might die
To lnchon
Funeral
It's so funny!
I'll take this
Only that?
Yes
Get it back quickly
You're going to High School next year, right?
Yes
Grow up, kid! Want to see something really cool?
It's cheaper there
Then go rent it there!
Bye
Well, it's spooky to see a dead body, isn't it?
Do you know who I am? I'm KANG Failan
Stay away!
Search high and low!
Hey, Officer, give me a break
You hopeless bum, let's go!
Get in
Wait, wait
Get in, bastard
Is she really dead?
It's okay now
Hey! If you overdo it...
What is the matter?
Fuck!
You fucking bastard!
Who? Me?
Of course, it's you, you fucking bastard
Who else is here besides you?
What about me?
You're such shit!
Why are you eating that?
Are you hungry? Or is it for your health?
Fuck! What is the matter with you?
Eat all you want, you bastard
Even your kinds need to stuff his
stomach to live
But I hate that!
Hey, what do you live for?
What bullshit!
Yours is more fucked up than mine
Shut up!
I can see your whole life
You're exactly Kangjae Jr.
That's enough!
I hate to tell you this
But if my life were like yours, I'd rather die
Yeah, you're right
I'm always fucked up
I'm the most fucked up in the world
But did you see her?
That bitch lying dead in the hospital said
I'm the kindest person in the world
Bullshit! So what?
What shall I do now that she's dead?
Do I have to live with the dead body, huh?
Okay, I got it, stand up please
Do I have to live with the dead body?
Lee Kangjae! Okay, okay, seat down, fuck!
Watch your mouth, you shithead!
Are you my father?
You little piece of shit
Shut up and just drink, Mister!
Yeah, okay, you motherfucker!
You are an actor!
Everyone would take you for her real husband!
It's all over now, let's go
Whom do I get her debt from?
Are you crazy?
What's wrong? Hey!
What are you going to do with the remains?
I don't know
Let's scatter them in the sea here
I think that would be best
Hello! Ah, yes, sir!
Wait a second
Yes, right
Everything's done
I'll go back soon
See you then
What did he say?
Nothing much
Who's there?
Are you the husband?
How could you show up now?
How could you!
You don't know how much Failan had
waited for you
How could you...How could you...
She'd waited so long
She worked so hard waiting for you
Poor girl, I feel so sorry for her
Hey! Wait!
Failan told me to give you this
when you come here
I almost forgot
She must've had lots to tell you
Aren't you going to read it?
Dear Mr. Kangjae
I didn't mail this
because I wasn't sure that you'd receive it
If you see this, the you've come to see me
Thank you
But I am dying
Thank you for your kindness though for
a short while
I know a lot about you
While I saw your picture not to forget you,
I came to like you
And after that, it became even harder for me
Being alone made it so difficult to bear
I'm sorry
You're always smiling in the picture
Everyone here is kind but
you are the kindest of all
Because you've married me
I have a favor to ask you
Would you come to see me when I am dead?
Would it be all right to die as your wife?
Sorry for asking this
But it is the only favor I have to ask of you
I am sorry I have nothing to give you
I love you more than anyone else in the world
Mr. Kangjae, good bye
The police is investigating gangsters over
the dead body
which was found at the harbor on the 18th
Inchon Bus Terminal
It's cold!
Now, you are back!
What a gambling! Look at the bet!
I'm happy to see you!
You idiots! Don't eat Chinese food
in the office!
Have a seat
The investigation is narrowing down
Let's finish our deal now
I kept my promise
Now it's your turn
Sorry
Don't be, it's me who should be sorry
I'm not going in
I'm going back home
Thank you for everything
Are you really going back?
I don't know whether it's better for you or not
Hey, how about a last wrestle?
You never beat me!
Why are you standing there like that?
Did you say that I never beat you?
Come on, for the last time, huh?
Wear it! You'll get a bruise
Whatever!
Let's do it!
Are you ready? Go!
Idiot, I was joking
Don't go before I come back
Where are you going?
Just wait! Okay?
Failan at the spring beach
Hello? Yeah? Yes, sir
Fucking Yongsik always send me
on errands when I'm busy!
Wonderful sea, what an art!
Say something to your husband
Mr. Kangjae, thank you
No, say something else
Say you love him
Okay, how about some singing?
I can't sing
Just try
Hey, once again
No!
Just once
Hey, come here, will you?
I'm gonna show it to your husband
Ready, go!
Hey Failan! You sing great!
Your husband will love it