Make sure to drop in.
Here's a discount ticket
with lots of cute girls.
We're all college girls.
A perfect place for
your taste...
You're not students!
If you are, go home and study.
Good evening!
Sorry.
Oh, that's right!
You work here.
Don't bother.
You'll get dirty hands.
Kajikawa, what are you doing?
Sorry.
Hurry up!
Broken.
It's all right. Don't worry.
hello, it's me.
I had a club meeting.
I'll be late. Sorry.
I'm home.
Hi! I'll fix supper.
Take a bath with me.
Ah, hey! Stop it!
Heisuke...
Heisuke.
It's hot. Be careful.
How about some dessert?
I've got to study.
Hello. This is Sugita.
Sorry to call so late.
My name is Soma.
Can I talk to Monami?
Which Soma are you?
From the sailboat club.
Hold on.
Naoko, telephone.
All right.
Hello.
It's me. Soma.
Oh, Mr. Soma, good evening.
Can we talk?
Yes, it's all right.
Second place Chunichi
will play hiroshima...
The Yokohama - Yakult
game was exciting...
A runner was on first base...
You're pulling my leg.
No. I mean it.
You have natural aptitude.
But a race? No way.
I guarantee you can do it.
Sorry, I've got to go.
Okay, catch you later.
Good night.
Ouch!
What are you doing?
Eavesdropping?
So what? Is it wrong?
I'm your husband.
Don't you trust me?
This Soma, what is he?
My senior. We talked
about the sailboat club.
For 30 minutes?
He must have something
else in mind.
Mr. Soma isn't that
sort of man.
Mr. Soma? You call a kid
half your age, Mr. Soma?
Heisuke, why are you
so uptight?
Young men are like beasts.
Just waiting for a chance.
Don't worry.
He's just a kid. Trust me.
Don't be so conceited.
What's that mean?
You're my old lady...
And don't forget it.
Sugita.
Yes?
Let's go for a run
next Saturday.
Can't do it.
Why not? You got
something to do?
I need time to study.
I see.
"Soma, haruki"
Look, Sugita.
On Saturday, you really can't?
Sorry.
Okay.
See you.
Yeah, thank you.
I'm home.
Sorry to be late.
I'll make supper.
You're late. The sailboat club
drive you home? Pretty ritzy.
I didn't want to take a taxi.
More.
Some more.
Naoko.
Naoko!
I want to concentrate
on studying.
Sugita. You know
how I feel about you...
Give me your cell-phone number.
I don't have a cell-phone.
You don't like me?
It's not that...
I'll pick you up
at noon tomorrow.
No. Not at my house.
Then, the usual place,
Cafe da Vinci.
Ah, but...
I'll wait there
until you show up.
Ah, hello! Hello!
Naoko.
How about going
out for lunch today.
Got other plans?
No...
Hello, Kuniko?
How're you doing?
Fine. It's been a while.
I'm fine, too.
So, your dad is strict.
Yeah, will you cover for me?
Okay, I'll do it.
You saved my life.
Just call me on the phone,
10 minutes from now.
Okay!
Right.
So, bye for now.
Thank you.
Heisuke, telephone.
Hello. Sugita here.
I've got to meet Kuniko.
I'll be back by evening.
See you later.
Sugita!
Heisuke... Why...?
So, you are Soma?
Yes.
I'm Monami's father, and
she can't see you any more.
Why do you say that?
We live in a different
world from you.
I don't get it.
What do you mean?
We're from outer space.
We came from outer space.
Aren't you ashamed?
Naoko.
Why did you go there today?
I wanted to tell him to
leave me alone.
Oh, no! You could ignore him
but you wanted to see him.
See. I'm right.
Don't I have any privacy?
No right to enjoy myself?
No! You don't!
I have never played around!
And I turn down every
marriage offer.
How noble.
Miss Hashimoto attracted me,
but I gave up because of you.
I think Miss Kameda at the office
loves me, and she's very nice.
But there's nothing between
us because you are here.
There's no bright future
or fun for me.
But I'm here.
I'm not good enough?
Are you happy with me?
What's that mean?
Are you? I've got to know.
Stop tormenting me like this.
Am I tormenting you?
Have I lost my
Naoko forever?
I have no choice
but to live as Monami.
Monami was a good child.
She wasn't a liar or
a cheat like you.
That's true...
I should have died properly.
Thank you.
What'll it be.
I'll leave it up to you.
Hi, there.
I'm home.
I'll make supper.
Sorry. I already ate.
Say...
That... How about it?
I think you realize...
That this is my first...
So, be gentle.
What?
Contraceptive?
Do we need it?
I think it's safe today.
Are you sure we are
doing the right thing?
Should I hide my face?
I think...
We shouldn't do this.
Ah! Sorry.
Can I have a beer?
A bottle?
Cleaning up alone?
I'm the sub-manager.
I'll be the manager of a
new shop soon.
You're working hard.
Your father would be happy.
He wasn't my real father.
I'm the son of a guy my ma
knew before she met dad.
I didn't know till a while ago.
But it doesn't matter now.
If you don't mind.
Will you tell me about it?
My dad mistook me for his
kid and married my ma.
Stupid, isn't it?
When I was five,
ma told him about it.
Dad left us and ma went wild.
I missed dad so much
I went to see him alone.
When he saw me, he called
ma and said he'd keep me.
I was living with dad
until the accident happened.
A little while ago,
ma told me...
Since her health failed
two years ago...
Dad had been sending her
money all the time.
I see... That's why he
overworked himself.
I thought he was spending
it on gambling.
When I found out the truth,
I decided to shape up.
I want to work hard to go
independent and live with ma.
And open a nice place for
families to dine.
Why did your father
keep you with him?
Well, I don't know.
Dad! Don't let go!
No, I won't! I won't!
There you go!
I did it! Yes, I can do it.
You did it, Fumiya!
My wife...
No... My daughter...
She heard the last words
of your father.
My family's happiness
is my happiness, he said.
He said that...?
Want some noodles?
Yes, but don't overcook them.
Right.
Naoko.
Hi, there.
I'll make you something.
Monami...
You have...
The right to live your life
the way you want.
Heisuke.
All this time...
I've made you suffer.
Monami.
Daddy...
I'm so confused.
I know I was on
a bus with mama...
Why am I here?
Monami?
Something wrong, daddy?
What are you saying?
Monami...
You don't remember anything?
Mama...
Keep calm and listen.
Your mother's not with us.
The bus you were on
had an accident.
Ahh, no, no...
Your mother is still alive.
I don't get it.
Your mother has...
lived 2 years as Monami.
And entered medical school.
Wait...!
Wait a minute.
It's a lie. I can't believe that.
After two years...
The girl's true
personality returned.
It hurts.
My head hurts.
Monami.
Heisuke.
What's wrong with me?
I feel weird.
Naoko...?
Monami returned just now.
I'm sure she'll return again.
Oh, I'm so glad.
It'll be hard for Monami
to understand all this.
I can write down the details
and tell her everything.
We don't know when
she'll return.
Just after I wake up.
That's when...
I can't doze off
in class. Right?
Daddy...
Monami?
I must have been
sound asleep.
Yeah.
With love, Mama
So, lots of things happened.
Ah... a lot.
I'll write to mama, too.
Monami?
Too bad, it's Naoko.
Today, you didn't miss any.
Look, Monami's letter.
Let's see.
Monami wants to study medicine.
Really?
But can she keep up in class?
Sure, the lectures are all
easy to follow.
Monami can catch-up.
I guess.
And I know it's time
for me to vanish.
Silly.
Three of us can live together.
Heisuke.
Stay by me until the time
Monami takes over.
Didn't you say,
We came from outer space?
We came from outer space.
Heisuke.
I think I'll let Monami
go to college pretty soon.
You think so?
She'll get used to it, and her
awake time is getting longer.
Not bad at all.
Now, I've got to go.
What's he happy about?
Good morning, mama.
Rather, good evening.
I never saw those words
in the textbooks.
But somehow I understand them.
I can solve ordinary math problems.
Your mama hammered it all
into the brain. That's why.
Thank you mama!
I'm counting on you. Thank you!
Silly girl, Monami.
I cooked your borsch recipe.
It's in the pot. Try some.
All right, I'll have some.
What do you think?
Delicious
It wasn't easy.
It's good.
It's really good.
Don't you think I'm pretty good.
I just have one complaint
What?
She's careless with money.
The wallet quickly gets empty
She needs a scolding.
All right, I'll scold her.
We sure bought a lot of stuff.
Don't tell your mother.
Hello! It's been a long time.
Hi! How are you?
Welcome!
Great!
Thank you.
Hello.
How are you?
Careful, it's hot.
It's good.
What kind of broth?
It's a secret.
This is really good.
Will you come again?
I sure will.
Let's bring mama here next time.
I'm home
Welcome back.
Naoko?
How about going out
tonight?
Not today.
It's not easy to stay
up lately.
It isn't?
I'm sorry.
I need more time to look
at you while I still can.
Silly. What are you saying?
Will I never be able to
see you again?
Stop that.
Anyway, let's go out.
If you eat something good,
your mood will change.
What do you say, Naoko?
Naoko!
I'm Monami.
Mama doesn't take over
too much lately.
So, I've got to take
care of the flowers.
Tomorrow, take me to
the Cape Lighthouse.
Is that mama's message?
Yes.
It was in her letter this morning.
Mama, really loved this place.
Daddy...
Is it all right for me to return?
Of course it is.
I'm sure mama is delighted.
Heisuke.
This ice cream is so good.
Heisuke, what's funny?
On our first date you ate three.
Your appetite amazed me.
That's not true.
I ate two, not three.
And you ate mine
down to here.
Only the cup was left.
You, in a "Darth Vader" T-shirt
and beach sandals.
It's still in fashion.
Heisuke.
Thanks for taking me here
on my last day.
So, this is the last day?
I can feel it myself.
This is the last of Naoko.
Can't you do something
about it?
Good-bye. Heisuke.
Naoko!
Thank you.
Please remember me.
Is she gone?
I'll do my best.
I'll live for
mama's share, too.
A FEW YEARS LATER
I'm glad I lived to see this day.
Where is Heisuke?
I bet he's crying in the toilet.
Just like our dad did?
Don't start that again.
Daddy.
All these years...
Thank you for everything.
Are you taking it to
the reception?
You are...
Was it you all this time?
Taking it with you?
This is the way you want...
So, here you are.
Fumiya.
Yes
I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Something a bride's father
wants to do at any cost.
Let me hit you.
Well... All right.
I can stand one blow.
Two blows.
One for taking my
daughter away...
And one for someone else.
It hurts.
You really meant it.
Congratulations!