He is wearing bullet proof vest!
Shoot his head only!
Although you saved me from the jail
It doesn't imply that
I'm out of danger now
From the day
we joined the Green Dragon Society
We two seemed
to be having life imprisonment
But this jail of Green Dragon Society,
is too big for us to escape
In these 20 years,
I've done many successful cases
But the failure
of the assassination of Princess Yuki
is caused by my wrong judgement
I know pretty well
about the rules of our society
Even I've made many contributions
No matter how many contributions
I have had
It can't compensate my fault
You've been tailing me for 3 months,
what do you want?
We are working
for our master respectively
I work for my client
Remember, I'm a city soldier
I'm May Yiu
Release the princess now
I won't remember
the name of a dead person
My fate and my eyes...
is ruined by this woman
I've never begged you, right?
Kill her for my sake!
Then, I can die at ease
I'll do it!
My good student!
A good master will not treat
his fellows badly
My life, is my deposit
Silver Fox,
I'll pay the rest in my next life
See you!
Master,
this grave is specially prepared for you
Die in peace
Sorry, I'm late
May I know...
May I know what are you looking?
Be patient!
You'll see the greatest invention
of the world soon
Siu Chuen, what're you talking?
May's sister is testing
her new invention now
This is called "Suffocate bullets"
A bullet can be suffocated
I'm successful now!
The gas tube exploded!
How are you, sister
May I know, is it dangerous?
Stay back!
Let me use my "dagger bomb"
Stand behind the yellow line
Successful!
Is it a prize?
Sister!
Don't look at me
From my experience
This is a natural retreat
This is not related to my new invention
Do you agree?
Softer please!
I'm hurt by a grenade,
not a needle
This is the information sent
by the police
Who do you think is the one
who murdered Old Eagle?
The only one...
is the best friend of him
Called Silver Fox
Silver Fox?
May, please don't take this case!
Since you're still young,
quit your job and get marry
Once upon a time...
someone told me these too
When I worked in the office
I dreamt of exciting life
Later, I met you and May
Then started my life as city soldier
After these years...
Suddenly, I hope to have ordinary life
You won't understand!
If I ask, from the sun and the moon,
which one will you choose?
I'll choose cake
What?
Don't you understand? Is it too abstruse
Both of us can't understand
what we are talking
One is attentive
One is active
Both of them can't stay together
Sister, Siu Chuen gave me a ring
He asked me to consider our marriage
Maybe, I'm only the secret admirer
Actually, Ching hasn't mentioned...
his love to me
Maybe, he doesn't like me
Do you love the concubine?
Damn it!
It's time to propose to May
I think she'll like this ring
Hi
Why are you so happy?
I won't tell you
But it'll be useless for you to know it
Ask May to tell you then
Do you know the murderer of Old Eagle?
Wrong!
Guess again
I can foresee something
The case of Old Eagle will be a trouble!
If any of us die
The one left should take care of May
My God! What a big mouth?
You are like a nosy bitch!
I'm serious
Although they are not involved
in that case
Take my advice,
don't let them stay with you so oftenly
Why?
You've killed Old Eagle indirectly
If Silver Fox knows that
they are so close to you
They'll be in deep shit!
Also...
What a horrible scream?
We've to pick Siu Chuen's sister up now
Where is your sister?
Behind the door
Kidding?
She'll be the wall paper definitely!
I'm leaving
Tonight is the right time
Some experts said it's the best time
to propose in a full moon night
If May receive my ring,
she'll be very happy
She must be eager to know
where our marriage would be held
St. John or Po Lin Temple?
Brother Ching, you're too selfish!
After your marriage with May,
Siu Chuen will become lonely!
How poor is he!
It doesn't matter!
We'll treat him some nutrious soup
What'd you like to drink?
I want something to drink
Daily soup is the best
You want daily soup now?
Would you want herbal tea too?
Why not buy some snacks too?
Palms, cakes, etc
OK, I'll buy if any
Thank you
Do you think
tonight is specially romantic?
Really? I don't think so
We've been here for many times
No!
I think tonight is specially romantic!
Thank you,
you finally show your affection to me
What are you doing?
Have you discovered...
the wooden chair we are sitting
is rather special?
What? Nothing special!
No, there is some black mark
Who made it?
This is a box!
Who left this here?
Is...
is...
Ching!
May, it's yours
Thank you
Soft drink
Why do you have red face?
Because I haven't eaten daily soup...
and cakes
Do you understand?
One'll have red face
if lack of daily soup and cake
But I want to cook
some soup for you in future!
Ching is so difficult to understand!
You'll have red face
if you don't eat cakes
How is your consideration?
Give me some more time please
I'll go to the toilet
It's mine, the ring is mine
Marry me
That's it! You needn't speak in English
You can talk in English too
"You are the one that I want
Oh! Oh! Oh!"
Marry me, OK?"
Can you understand what I'm talking?
You needn't understand
This is one method of proposing
Maybe, use the 2nd method
You want me to marry you?
Not that easy! Can you wait?
What? 3 to 7 years?
It doesn't matter,
the most important thing is to marry me
I'll do what you want
What?
Are you brother Ching?
Are you the sister of Siu Chuen?
Why are you so short?
Don't lie to me!
May
May, wake up!
Wake up!
Siu Chuen...
Follow me
I'll send you to hospital
We've no time
Ask Ching to take care of Wai Heung
Take care
Siu Chuen!
Brother!
Brother
If you don't want them to be in danger,
leave them
The target of Silver Fox is you only
When will I stop hiding?
He can't defeat us
if we join together, right?
If you don't listen to me, you'll regret
Sorry, I can't promise you
Only this way...
can make Ching stay out of danger
No! May won't love Siu Chuen
Let us send you to Macau
No!
Why do you want to stay in HK alone?
Shut up! I won't go back to Macau
My brother had promised me,
after this semester,
If I have good report,
he'd take me to HK
Can't you listen? He promised me
After the case of your brother,
I'll take you back to HK
Why should I listen to you?
You've no right to control me
Who do you think you are?
If your brother was still alive,
I'd have been your sister-in-law
My brother didn't mention you before
He didn't mention any sister-in-law
My brother won't marry you
You idiot!
I'd marry your brother
You liar!
You are jealous
I know you love your brother
He belonged to you,
he should not love the other one
But there are many kinds of love
Yours love is between brother and sister
The love between your brother and me
is the love of romance
No!
The love between Ching and me...
is a kind of friendship
Liar! Ours is beyond friendship!
You can cheat her,
but don't drag me down
Tell her!
Tell her we are not just friends
Don't you want to tell the truth?
Tell her!
We are not just friends!
I don't know!
Since she doesn't know, just tell her!
We're not just friends!
Why don't you face the world?
This...
is not true!
We are friends since childhood
I know everything of you
When you smoke,
I'll light the cigarette for you
You get marry...
why didn't Chuen tell me either?
Hadn't he told you?
No!
If he told me, I'd have killed me
Silver Fox could have no chance!
What are you talking about?
Where are you going?
I don't want to listen your bull shit!
Siu Chuen was my fiance
He was the man I loved most
The tear is for myself
I can't help!
Well, let me forget Siu Chuen first
I'll meet you later
Hope I'll still remember you
Sorry
Only this way can make you safe
If you are upset now,
I'll be more upset
What are you murmuring?
Don't cry!
Brother said you'd take care of me
OK
You want to live with me?
You'd learn how to take care of yourself
I'm a city soldier
I don't want any burden
This is the 1st time...
I've seen a man's eyes with sorrow
From that day,
the lives of Wai Heung and me
changed a lot
She is no longer a simple pupil
She is an assistant of a city soldier
In this year,
I've learnt how to take care of myself
Also I've experienced...
Many first times with Ching
Our 1st time of hand in hand
Our first embrace...
Get up!
How can you be my assistant?
I can do it!
Damn you! Watch me!
I'll teach you a lesson!
From that day onwards,
every time I go with him
My heart beats very fast
Isn't it called first love?
I wonder
what kind of 1st love Ching is having
In this year, everytime thinking of May,
he'll play his sword for 45 mins
He's so good in playing sword!
If he was born in the past,
he'd have been a romantic swordsman
When will he play the sword for me?
What is called love,
what is righteousness?
It's you again!
Why do you call so many times a day?
You call at least 3 times per day!
Is it funny to do so?
I don't know May's address!
You are devil!
You'll bring bad luck to me!
I wonder what's my bad luck this time
Oh my dress!
Am I your enemy?
Do you want a revenge now?
You always give me trouble!
If it was burnt a little bit lower,
I could make it as trousers
Now it's just a waste!
You want to know where is May?
Let me trap him!
Who is calling?
Oh my face!
Can it be trust?
Tomorrow is my 12th birthday,
will Ching celebrate with me?
Tomorrow is a very impressive day of you
Your lover will leave a kiss
on your face
Happy Birthday!
Why there is $5000 left here?
Wai Heung, tonight is a very important
moment for us
I'll bring you to a very decent place
Take the money on the table and dress up
I'll pick you up at six
Wai Heung
I'm coming
Are you ready?
Oh, you?
What's wrong?
I don't want you to disturb me anymore
You really want to know where May is?
What do you mean?
I'm going to tell you
You'll tell me?
I'm a lady
Don't touch me
I'm sorry
Please tell me now
Today is an important day of May
Being her sister, I'm so glad
Is she going to marry?
She wants to cover her identity,
she is called Madam of Pets
Tonight, she'd choose her husband
from kung-fu competition
Take her address
If you have that guts,
go and take her yourself
No! She won't marry
with the other one except me! You liar!
I won't cheat you
Don't you believe?
Just stay here and have some snack
I tell you, you've no choice
Trust it or not,
you've to find out yourself
Moreover, it's the truth
You are in my trap now
Where is brother Ching?
He is going to marry,
he won't dine with you tonight
What are you talking about?
Oh! Thank God!
My sister will be in peace from now on
I don't believe
Trust it or not,
it's not up to you
The maids are beautiful
Yeah!
The maids are pretty,
I think the Madam is much more beautiful
Don't you know that...
all competitors tonight must be under 40
What? My face is older than my age
I'm 28 only
How can you talk to Mr. Ford in this way
Disappear now!
Wait...
Grannie, before the competition
Ford has kicked over 20 people away
He is quite good for our Madam
Invitation please
Sorry, I haven't
So you can't get in
I have it, but I've forgot to bring it
No invitation, no entry
Why there are...
so many competitors?
Sure! If anyone marries Madam of Pets
He is marrying
the greatest doctor of the world
You know, she is the best doctor
If you can't marry her
You can still drink the Tin-chi water
Which is good for health
I've got so many VIP cards, so I'm VIP
Save it
No invitation card, no entry
You have principle, haven't you?
I'm leaving!
I'm the friend of Madam
May! I'm Ching...
Grannie
Hey
Watch out...
If you keep on fooling around
I'll kill you!
I'm a friend of Madam!
We are friends since childhood
Look at you, I can tell you are lying
Is Madam...
called May?
Isn't it?
We can't tell her name so easily
Heung
Yes
The competition will start soon,
guard here
If anyone wants to mess up
Kill!
Got it!
Get lost
Get lost!
Madam is here!
I'm Ford,
it's my pleasure to meet you Madam
How are you?
To express my sincerity to you
I'd be the 1st one to take the challenge
Who'd come and fight with me?
Madam,
among the competitors,
Ford is the best one
I see
1, 2, 3, Magic!
Disappear!
Is it great?
Can I go in?
No!
Don't you know you're in great danger?
I think you are guest,
so I give you some face
But Grannie gave an order that,
I won't give you face anymore
So what does that mean?
Just try, I'll show you
Don't look down
upon the women of our Palace
We are...
specially trained!
I've to teach you a good lesson
Mr. Ford's defeated all competitors
Who else would like to challenge?
I've come on time!
I've defeated all the useless men
According to the rules,
who is the winner,
who'll get marry with Madam
No way!
Buddy!
Why?
I'm thinking of your own good
What?
Sure! You'd check the woman before!
How can you risk your life...
without having a glance of her face?
What kind of bullshit is it? Who are you
You?
OK!
I'll tell you the truth!
Madam is cohabiting with me
When?
It's a long story!
What are you talking?
We've 2 daughters
Now, she is pregnant again,
for 24 months!
Bull shit!
I recognize the dagger! May, it's you!
Although you use different dagger,
I can tell it's you by the smell
A strange smell!
This dagger is for cutting
my tough skin of my feet
So, is the smell strong?
What?
Grannie should not laugh!
Don't mess up here!
Do you know who am I?
My enemy of course!
Don't you think you are my lover instead
May is my women
Can't you see...
her looking at me with love?
Catch him!
Again?
How smart is he!
Madam!
I'll do it!
Attack!
How is it?
I pretended being attacked!
This is a useful strategy!
Am I smart?
May,
do you know...
it's hard for me to find you?
What's wrong I have done?
Why don't you come to see me?
I know!
The death of Siu Chuen impressed you
But you'd not choose your husband
in such cheap way
If the pirate won
you'd have lived in the ship!
I think you've mistaken
I'm not May
If you want me to trust you,
leave your gauze to let me see your face
If you want me to leave my gauze
you'd defeat all the competitors
This is our rule!
Madam!
I won't change anything I set
He can come in this hall,
I'd give him this chance
OK,
you've your own reason
Do you want to marry May?
I'll make a dead set at you!
I'll chop your fingers off!
I've warned you
I'll make a dead set at you!
Go back!
Yeah!
Hey!
Your beard!
Go!
He is the Romeo of this century!
I've tried so hard to defeat Ford
I think our marriage...
Grab his woman!
Get lost!
Do you know...
the result of removing my gauze
To marry you!
Your sister has told me!
I can't guess...
we'll be so romantic here
You are more beautiful than before!
I can't match you, sorry
I'm leaving!
Wait! How can you leave?
Don't force me!
Well, I won't push you if you don't
want to take the responsibility
I won't beg anyone
Why do you want to do that?
I think you were my woman
If you want to suicide
Kill me first
Go!
I'm sorry!
You liar!
I'll take all your cards,
so you can't cheat anymore
Sorry,
I'm late for some personal business
Sorry!
Brother Ching!
Don't cry!
Happy birthday!
Although he kissed my forehead,
I'm so happy
Now, I'm 16 years old,
when I become taller,
he can't kiss my forehead
But my lips
I remember May used to come to our home
at this time annually
She'll plant the Jasmin for us
Because she knows that
Siu Chuen loved Jasmin most
Give me the pot
Don't you know,
my brother loved this flower most
Every Summer,
he used to bring me one
Actually, I love Jasmin
I don't know why,
everyone will think of Siu Chuen
when seeing Jasmin
Instead of thinking of me
Look! There are more Jasmin over there
How beautiful!
Miracle!
My jinx!
Don't go
Tell me where May is!
Find it from the Yellow Page Directory
Jinx...
I can't tell you are here!
Don't go!
Jinx!
I'll kill you!
Go to hell!
Suffocate Bullets?
Where is May! Tell me!
If you don't tell me, I'll kill you
Retreat!
The Suffocate Bullet?
So why do you ask me?
It's me!
Drunken again!
Have a look please!
Wake up!
Are you concious now?
I'm leaving, thank you
Wai Heung,
leaving without any notice is my style
Hope you'll not blame me
Cause I've finally traced out May
I've to find her
I've go to a very very long way
So, it's not convenient
to bring you along
I know...
you are a strong girl
You can take care of yourself
I'll come back, take care
What is love,
what is righteousness?
Or...
what is liar?
La...
It's me!
We are successful!
Ching is going to New York now
Just a phone no. Can...
drive him away
How can he dream that
the real May is just next to him
So, you don't have to worry now
Even Silver Fox comes back,
he can't find Ching
Hello...
Come out!
Silver Fox!
Thank you for your call
I know where she is now!
You bitch, you always disclose my place
Do you know it's dangerous?
What sort of danger?
Try my Thunder Bomb!
You're hurt!
Why you're still here?
Jinx!
I beg you
I've said you are my jinx!
Don't come close to me!
May is so stupid to set such trap!
How can you be trapped! Jinx?
Leave me alone
Or I'll teach you good lesson
Tell me where she is! Hurry up
Please... Don't come to me
OK! Then you come out
Tell me where she is
OK... OK...!
But you must leave me alone
after I tell you
You've got it, right?
Not very clear
Bastard! You'd call the ambulance for me
I'm so poor
Where are you, Brother Ching?
Listen, Silver Fox has been back
It's very dangerous for you
to stay alone
You'd go to May, I'll come back at once
May? Where is she?
Opposite?
You mean over the Jasmin?
Ask me to stay with her?
Why don't you phone to her by yourself?
Don't ask too much
The line is busy!
Go and tell her for me
That's all
It'll be faster by taking short cut
Sister May...
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
Where is May?
Silver Fox, I've waited you for one year
Now, we'll take a revenge for Siu Chuen
I'll use your life to pay for my eye
A metal tailing machine
Super dagger!
Let you try my Horrible Angel
May!
Are you OK?
How are you?
Don't go!
Hey!
What are you doing? It's a gun!
May, why there is smoke coming
from his body?
Brother Ching, be careful!
Don't let him stick to your body!
Don't worry, he is under control now
No, I am under his control!
You like it? Go ahead!
Watch out!
I want to make your bones broken
Let me go! I feel painful
Faint! Please let me down!
Wai Heung!
Go!
She is shot twice by my "Horrible Angel"
She has 24 hours left
After that, she'll lose control
And becomes my slave, forever
May Yiu, I have to find you
Hey, this is a hospital!
You can't go in!
Call the doctor for me!
Brother Ching?
Brother Ching!
You have waken up!
Why don't you go in?
May has told me
When she forgets Siu Chuen,
she'll come to me
If she wants to see me
She'll find me
May doesn't love brother at all
When she was unconcious
She has been calling your name
Calling me?
Do you know?
Everytime I look at your window
I'll think, what will the people
inside think about...
if they see...
those jasmin
Now, I know
In this year
Everytime I see you through the window
I hope to be with you
I see Wai preparing your dinner
I hope I were the one who cooked
But it was too late!
Will you remember me?
I will...
You have to remember,
what does May look like
If I become a Horrible Angel
you'd destroy me
Remember!
May
It's useless for you to point at me
She is a plant now
I can extend her life only
I can make her recover
Stop talking that to me
or I'll kill you
Don't you believe?
It's you
Why you are here?
Oh my ass!
Jinx! What do you want?
Follow me!
How to save her? Tell me!
Go ahead!
I beg you
Please let me die in peace
You shot me, you know?
Everyone knows that
you are an Encyclopedia
Tell me! How to save May?
Lock the door!
But you'd save me first
I'm a human being
My blood is flooding out
What do you want?
OK, I'll stop the blood flooding
How?
By my finger
No, I'll tell you
Go ahead!
Or I'll help you again
OK, I'll tell you
To make her concious, why one would do
What?
The frozen water of Tin Chi
in the Pet Palace
Frozen water of Tin Chi?
Can I buy one in the store?
Get lost!
It can only make her concious
To save her from Horrible Angel,
only one doctor...
can do it!
Who is it?
Hey...
She is Madam of Pets
Where are you going?
Oh my Suffocate Bullets! Where are they?
He stole it, for sure
What shall I do now?
Shit! May and Ching have gone
They must have gone to Pet Palace
I've to call the police
Madam of Pets?
Madam, Madam...
How dare you enter our palace
without permission?
I want to see you, Madam
Please call her out!
Madam will not see you!
Please ask her out!
You want to see her? Defeat me first!
So big!
Poor eye sight!
Suffocate Bullets! Let's go!
You'd blame yourself!
How are you?
I...
You give me up because of this woman?
I've found my woman
Please save her!
Save her!
Don't you think I'll save her?
You abandon our Madam
We won't save you two
Get lost!
I want to beg for mercy
So, I'll not leave even you scold me
I just want you to save my woman
Your woman
Kick her out!
Yes!
Stop!
Madam!
Please don't angry with her
I...
I can't think any other way
So I have to beg you
Please save her
You want me to save her?
OK, I'll give you a chance
Kneel down in front of me and beg me
Maybe, I'll consider your proposal
Come on
Kneel down!
Don't
Even you promise to save me
I haven't promised to let you save me
He is my man, I won't let him kneel
in front of me
So he won't kneel down
in front of other woman
Don't!
If you don't do it, she'll die
I'll give you 6 hours for consideration
After that,
the Horrible Angel will be effective
Then, it'll be useless for you
to do anything
Please remind me
I've to see Ching lossing his woman
I won't let you see it!
I'll make you blind first!
Leave her alone!
Leave her alone?
OK! Beg me
Beg me, I'll let her go,
and I may save her
Come and beg for mercy
No! Don't do that!
Brother Ching!
Now you can save her now
I won't
Have you ever being rejected?
I'll let you taste...
the bitter fruit of being rejected
I know it now...
It's bitter of being rejected
I won't blame her
Because I've done something wrong first
Now,
it's just fair to her
I asked her
not to push me some day before
I don't want to push her now
Since she doesn't want to save you
Let it be!
Let's go
I've no way to save May
But I can...
stay with May forever...
I can see through the window
in this house
Excellent smell of the Jasmin
Yeah!
The Jasmin is most beautiful tonight
Really?
Can't you feel that,
here is specially romantic
Don't you feel it?
The moon specially full tonight
Why there is a ring?
A wedding ring
Who left this here?
It's...
It's me!
I want to propose
Marry me!
Why do you cry?
I miss this! Time is so short
I'll leave you soon
I won't let you leave me
I've open all the gas pipe
When you start to become Horrible Angel
I'll explode the house
Ching!
We'll be burnt together
In my dictionary
There is no perfect ending
Wai Heung!
How are you?
Are you OK?
I'm worrying no one'd attend our wedding
You've come the right time
Your corpse is my wedding gift
What a big mouth!
I'll kill you
Same!
I've good preparation
Let me eat this nutrition food first,
come on
My God!
Every injection will...
increase the effect
Come again!
I see how much you can stand?
But all will be effective...
after 24 hours
So it doesn't matter how much I was shot
Come on!
OK, I'll attack
I'll catch you
Why do you hide inside?
I'm locked
Locked? OK! Attack!
You love chasing people? Watch me!
Fainting?
Shacking?
Hey...
Go to hell!
Come again?
Hey, you'd not bump your head
on the wall even you've lost
You want to come out
by breaking through the mirror?
Stop dreaming!
Hold it!
Don't go
I can't stand it
I can't stand anymore
Come and help me! Brother Ching!
I'm coming!
Pull tightly!
I'm pulling!
Hey!
I've got it!
4 Horrible Angels! Go to hell now!
My God! Superman!
Why do you fly so slowly?
Punch in!
Again!
I'm faster!
May!
Finally will become my slave
May...
Wake up, May!
Counter attack! She is not May!
Brother Ching
Attack him, now!
Go through May,
then she'll be your slave!
May!
May...
Let's go
Go! Forget about me!
Madam Pet?
Go!
I'll go to hell with you
Brother Ching!
Go! Forget about me!
Pull her out!
Don't pull me out!
Brother Ching...
Save him! Save him now!
Brother Ching!
Don't go!
What do you want?
Why do you do that to us?
You'll never be hurt
by the Horrible Angel...
after taking this
Why do you have to save me?
I want you to be miserable
after lossing Ching!
I won't...
let you die together
Brother Ching
Brother Ching!
Thank you for saving May
How dare you cheat Madam! Arrest him
Let's go
Stop! Let them go!
Madam isn't that stupid
But she wants
the perfect couple flee away
Perfect couple?
But Ching is injured
by the Horrible Angel!
Madam's put the solution...
on May already
Brother Ching won't be dead
That was the last time...
I saw them
They've never come back to me
Many years later, someone told me
They appeared once in Tibet
We'll remember you forever, Siu Chuen