With spring,
Flowers,
Colors,
Questions arise
Peaceful
$20, next?
Life
Peaceful, $20
Next?
Marriage
Marriage, the real question
Not so loud
Everyone can hear
You have
A classic rich look
Girls need love
Don't be shy
Your hand
Parents are apart
You only have Mother
It's right or it's free
No, only Father
Mom died
So I'm right: single parent
And 2 sisters
It's right or it's free
No, only child
So I'm right, no boys
Forget it
No, I'm getting to the
Good part
A forked love line
Excuse me?
It means you'll
Marry a rich man
You're joking
Me, marry rich?
Why not?
If I say you will
You will marry rich
I hope so; how much?
Up to you, $200 or more
$200 for that?
Here's $60
$61 total
Wait
Free advice:
You're too thin
Exercise more
Exercise?
With my job?
Yes, I deliver propane
But I'm the Boss's daughter
So it's part-time
I grew up in Harmony Village
It's old
And so are its people
But to me it's the best
Our Head of Security
Told me he killed a lion with
His bare hands
But I didn't know
There were lions in Hong Kong
Our Head of Agriculture
Has the best fruit
But bad hygiene
Our Head of Culture
Only reads English books
But only the pictures
His daughter MT, my best friend
She reads the papers
And magazines she sells
So she knows it all
Except whether
She prefers men or women
It's a mystery to all of us
Dad is Head of Energy
They call him Uncle D
Hobbies: Popsicles and comics
Everyone respects him
Dad, I quit
I'm your bookkeeper
All right
Modem youth are so spoiled
They give up too easily
It's too heavy
You expect this
On my salary?
All right
You cost more than my maid
And she works all day
But I'm a girl
This work
Scares off the boys
I'll never marry
You are my daughter
In olden days, a princess
You must marry a celebrity
I refuse to make deliveries
I'll do it myself
Stop acting
Last time it was the other hand
Both of my hands are trembling
Where is Monam now?
Level 73
Great!
Will he continue?
Yes
Surely he'll go for Level 74
And when he succeeds
Of course he'll try Level 75
I must wear a glove
On my left hand, too
Marry rich?
No
It would be nice
Fry 10 more eggs, we need more food
Uncle D!
Very punctual
All alone?
I couldn't sell these
It's my gift to you
Thanks
Stay for dinner
I'll go now
Stop acting
You came when you smelled food
I couldn't sell these
It's my gift to you
What do I do with them?
And you brought...?
Uncle D...
Bring it out
Then I will
Come out!
Uncle D!
So many?
Fine
Sit
Good girl
Eat
Here
Mi!
Great fried eggs
She cooks well
Open another can of fish
I'm glad you came
Together
How great to have a good daughter
He has MT
But is it a boy or a girl?
Whoever marries Mi
Is so lucky
Don't even think about it
Uncle D's daughter
Must marry a rich man
The richest!
Rich men may not be good
That's true
But poor men are no good at all
Uncle D is so wise
Sure
So how is the land deal?
It's almost done
No one wants to buy
Relax
Uncle D is king!
They were really hungry!
They came for free dinner again?
You look like a prisoner
I want dessert
Prisoner?
- So!
- What?
A fortune-teller
Said I'll marry a rich man
You're going crazy
Thinking of marriage
I want to marry
I over 20
It would be nice
Let him take
Care of me
Since you'll be marrying a rich man
Focus on that
Where would I
Find one?
I don't know
What is a rich man?
A millionaire?
How is that different from a rich man?
And...
What?
Don't touch me!
Tell me you don't like it
Or how would I know?
Just say so
I don't like it!
Try this
Disgusting!
I'll try
This way
Rich Man!
Is this 2 Shek O Road?
Where is the kitchen?
It's not for the kitchen
It's for the garden barbecue
Hurry, they're waiting
I'm busy, don't bother me
No time
I'm not so ugly
The rich are so rude
Is this a church?
No wonder people want to marry rich
Mi!
Cici Chan?
Yes, how are you?
It's been so long
Fine, and you?
Okay
You're delivering pr
Family business
Come, see who's here
Mi brought the propane!
Come see!
Mi?
Hurry!
Mi!
Teresa?
Loomi?
I've changed my name
I'm Sonreysia now
Son...
Why are you here?
Cici's wedding is in 2 days
We're having a party for her
This is her husband's home
Mi...
Remember when we were kids
We sat together in school
You were the smartest
And I, the dumbest
Cici, what is 1+1?
Mi?
2!
Name some famous people
Einstein, Beethoven, Sun Yat Sen,
Picasso...
And Cici?
Wilson
Who?
We are the same age
He has short hair, wears glasses
Best of all, he's a banker's son
I will marry him
I wasn't stupid
I knew my priorities
Marrying rich is a must
You're marrying Wilson?
I'm not so lucky
You're doing well
She's marrying the son of a famous lawyer
And you
She married the 2nd richest doctor
Dr. Chan, the heart specialist
Of course
Sunreysia married the grandson of the Kwoks
I'm heir to the family propane empire
So, Mi
Are you married yet?
It's late
I must go
Stay
Talk to us
I must go
I'm too ashamed
Mi
Everyone said you were smarter
Don't you feel I'm smarter now?
That's smart?
Of course
I must go
Bye, then
She delivered the propane
And I forgot the tip
No need
I must
It's hard labor
Thanks
We'll visit you soon
It's killing me!
I'm so unlucky
What's so great about marrying rich?
I've been told I will
I won't marry anyone
But the richest man!
I will marry a rich man!
Sir, Satellite 2 must shift
Mr. Law booked it for a teleconference
Tell him to delay the meeting
She's interesting
But he booked this slot
We'll make less money, I don't care
This makes me happy
I will marry a rich man!
Lock Satellite 2 to the target
"Marry A Rich Man" ready?
Yes
I will marry a rich man!
What's the use?
Can't wish without a shooting star
I can't be that lucky
Make a wish
"The Glass Slipper"?
Welcome to "The Glass Slipper"
This story appeals to all
Because of the exciting villains
And the star, Cinderella
Marries a rich prince
Oh, come here, please
If the evil stepmother
Or stepsisters married well
We may feel cheated
But for kind Cinderella
Not only is it fine
That she marries a rich tale
It's a beautiful fairy tale
Not only is it okay to marry rich
If you are kind
It is an enterprising idea
Glass slippers don't pinch
What a good book
I've never seen anything like it
It tells the truth simply
Every point hits the spot
It's great
I'm getting excited
It says
Marrying a rich man is like a job
It takes effort, resources, and money
That's the same as a CEO
Right
If you're fated to marry rich
Where is he?
Help me find him
I don't know what sex I want
I can't help
But I'll sponsor you
With all my savings
No need, thanks
Stop it
It's my investment on you
When you do marry a rich man
Repay me, with interest
And if I fail?
Pay with your flesh
Relax, Hong Kong girl
All right
Relax
- Like this?
- Right
Don't fear crudeness
It's the same old moves
First, a smile
Don't worry about beauty
A beautiful smile
Is all you need
Let's practice
This is most elegant
Most kind
Most innocent
Most sexy
How's this?
Most toad-like
Grooming and self-confidence
Go to the most expensive shops
Don't worry about money
Be gracious
There's nothing they can do
May I help you?
I want to try this
Establish self-confidence
Pose outside the fitting room
As flamboyantly as possible
Keep going
Until you feel beautiful
Confidence rules in fashion
Let your clothes know who's boss
I don't like them
Buy something
Don't make it hard on the sales staff
Actually, there is something
Yes
Here
$12, right?
Next, practical experience
Go where the rich gather
Some private hospitals
Are good choices
Dress sexier
Little girl
What's your name?
I'm HG
For Horny Goat!
I'm rich
And dying
When? It's up to you
Interested?
Let's do it here
Marry me!
We'll go to my villa in A-nus
We'll enter A-nus in the morning
Have fun in A-nus
And come out from the back at night
Come with me
Marry me
In 3 months
We'll trap my stepmother
And put my brother in prison
Then we'll split the fortune
I'll run for president
Then rule the world!
You think you're Ultraman?
Even if I were
I'd be Ultraman in furs!
Where did she go?
Crazy!
I'm too busy for a press conference
I'll go back to the office
I hate cameras in my face
Welcome, friends of the press
Today, I...
Are you all right?
I'll help you up
No need
Were you molested? I'll call the police
Leave me alone
I'll call the police
- Leave me alone
- I'll call the police
Stop it with the police!
Relax! Relax!
Wait outside
You think I'm a thief?
Sorry, Miss
Wilson?
You know me?
You're so famous
All my classmates want to marry you
Really?
Yes
Will you give me the film?
Which paper are you with?
Do I look like the paparazzi?
I am a CEO!
Mimi Cheng... propane?
Hello!
I'm Wilson, a pleasure
What happened just now
Can it remain between us?
Please?
No need to look all pale
I'm pale?
- Very
- Really?
Fix your makeup for your meeting
This part is grey
Okay
Oh, no!
I don't have powder
I wonder who does?
I have a compact
Yes
I don't know how to apply makeup
I wonder who does?
Let me help you
Just a bit
Thick brows make you
Look heroic
Blot off the oil
Go on
We're done!
So soon?
TV lighting is harsh
I look fat on screen
- A slimmer look?
- Yes
Deeper shadows here
Straighten your nose?
- Straighter
- Yes
What's taking Boss so long?
Lip balm?
Sure
Thanks
Smooth as fresh tofu
I want to lick it
Am I okay?
For camera, yes!
Really?
Thank you
Any time
The lip balm?
Keep it
- Thanks
- Bye
Mimi?
Just "Mi"
Mi, may we discuss
Propane digitalization?
I don't understand that stuff
It's very commercial
Mi...
Or may we discuss other topics
Like
Propane-lip balm-digitalization?
3 in 1
Call me, bye
Bye
This Wilson?
Yes
Really?
- You don't believe me
- No
He gave me his number
It's going through!
This is a Planned Parenthood
Survey, what safety
Precautions do you take during sex?
All right, thanks
It's him!
No sparks, though
You're joking!
All this work to find a rich man
You found Wilson, but "no sparks"?
No, we don't have that...
Magic
Magic?
The goal is a rich man
What magic?
What's wrong with you?
It's that
Feeling you get
When you spin and lose
Balance and direction
Understand?
Drink tequila
Touch an electrical outlet
It's the same feeling
Don't set a bad example
Okay, sorry
Deep truths simply
Let's use the deepest one
I may meet someone
I like, who is rich and handsome
How deep?
The book says, many qualified ones
Are in first-class cabins on planes
Plus after a long flight
Boredom breeds romance
Where do you want to fly to?
Somewhere
Romantic, artistic
With lots of cute guys
And that is
Milan!
First Class is this way
Coach is over there
Would you like a drink?
No. Thank you
Sir, this is your seat
Incredible!
Will you marry me?
Are you all right?
Fine
You're the one
- Hi!
Damn you! Stop that!
Where is your seat?
Here
This is my wife's seat
She's been standing one minute!
Let's see your ticket!
It's up front
Look before you sit! Get up!
She's still standing
Must she wait?
Ridiculous!
Sitting by me!
Wrong seat again?
No, it's right
How rude
Yes, boors are everywhere
You alone?
Going to Milan?
You, too?
Yes
Something to drink?
Would you like a drink?
A drink.
Iced Ovaltine, please
We don't have that
A Grape Fruit Juice
It's canned, how about
Some freshornjuice?
Oh, my God!
This is ridiculous!
I can't stand it!
It's "fresh orange juice"
Not much difference
It's a huge difference
What horrible service
It hurts my ears!
For example, say
Beef jerky
Beefjerky
No...
Can't make jerky with bees
It's "beef...
...Sherky
For example, again
Dried Mangoes
Dy...
I'll get your drink
Sorry, was I too insistent?
But I...
No, I don't like
Slurred words, either
Your accent is interesting
I'm from Hubei
But educated at Oxford
So my accent is... different
And you?
Stanford
- Really?
- Yes
Oxford, Stanford, both "ford"s!
What coincidence!
I'm Chris
Christopher?
No
It's Christmas
I want every day to be happy
as Christmas
So I changed my name
Or you can call me Mas
Not Mars, Mas
Mi
Hello
What a sweet smile
Excuse me, Mi
I want to go the toilet.
Bingo!
Rich and cute
And sleeping together already
What?
I said, why are you going to Milan?
On business?
I don't have to work for a living
I enjoy my life
I travel all over to visit churches
Europe's 3rd biggest church is in Milan
Called Duomo
You know it, I'm sure
Yes, the Duomo
Why do you visit churches?
It's beautiful!
Mi!
Why do you visit churches?
Because I want to choose
The perfect one for
My wedding
You're engaged?
No
Girlfriend?
How strange
Don't men fear marriage?
I can't wait
But I want it to be
Alaise and forever
That's "always"
Always!
I want to go shopping
Good idea
Then a great meal
Where's my wallet?
Stolen
Can't be!
Mine's gone, too
That man bumped into us
Should we report this?
Yes, let's call Hong Kong
My assistant will handle it
Let's go
Hi, Dad?
Yes, I'm in Italy
It's beautiful but cold
This is a collect call
So talk for at least 3 minutes
All right
Before I left
I put some veggies in the fridge
CEO? Yes, those stocks...
Hold 2 lots, sell 2 lots
What?
What do you talking about?
Keep the cash flow at
At $246 million
Are you all right?
You were talking about veggies
Right!
Fire them all, tomorrow
Just do as I say
That's all, then
Done
Should we get replacement cards?
What's the rush?
Let's play a game
What game?
A penniless life
That's not fun
We're both rich
We've been here many times
Yes, but...
And everywhere nearby
Yes
So
All right
If I hadn't met you on the plane
I wouldn't have known where to go
Let's play
Let's go
Stand there
Gorgeous!
Let me see
Here
A kaleidoscope!
Use this
This?
Too bad our wallets are gone
Never mind
This is the fam ous
Panino
With ham, cheese, lettuce...
Delicious!
You sound like a documentary
Of course
I'm hungry
Let's get the replacement card
No
We're having so much fun!
But I'll starve
In an alien land
You won't
Look!
Don't tell me
You're using that old movie device
You play guitar?
So crude?
Watch me!
How crude!
Let's go to have a coffee
Over there? Okay
I'll be here, okay?
Okay
Mi
I'll play, you dance
We'll make a fortune
You go ahead
Me?
No one wants to watch me
You do it
I can't
Flamenco is easy
Like this
Try it
1, 2, 3, 4!
Like this?
Be serious
No one is paying
I said I can't dance
Try again
1, 2, 3, 4!
Someone paid?
Forget it
You must be desperate
I'll help a fellow Chinese
Thank you
That's not enough for a panino
Miss Designer Clothes wants a panino?
Sorry
Quiet
It's not enough for 2
You're worse!
This is all I have
Thank you
We'll take it
Food!
Well?
Great!
We had enough for 2
Where's yours?
For you!
You bought a gift instead?
I never said I like it
I like it
I want to give you what I like
How cute of you
It's a happier world through this
Even I look better
Handsome!
Aren't you hungry?
I'm full from watching you
Here
Thanks
You okay?
Fine
Let's sit on the bench
Okay
I'll massage you
Thanks
I've observed that
Your spine is maligned
With the lifting I do
What?
Weights, at the gym
Right here!
Hard enough?
Harder
Okay!
Use your elbow
You're tough
Cry out if you like
It excites me
It feels great!
Do my head, too
Sure
Relax
Clear you mind
I wish I could
Do me a favor
Think for me from now on
I must think about that
I don't want to be casual
It's fine, we're not that close
Then...
Okay!
I'll think for you
I feel so loved
Like a princess
If so, am I your...
Imperial Eunuch?
What do you think?
Do you like this?
It's great!
Good morning
Let's go
What's wrong?
My legs are asleep
Let's go
I'll pound them for you
Better?
Great
I'll help you
Okay
Let's go
Slow down
Okay
It's beautiful!
Glass slippers are impractical
You can't use or eat them
But everyone wants them
Just like love
You feel that way, too?
You like them? They're yours
They're very expensive
How beautiful they will be
On you at your wedding
The most important part of a wedding
Is who stands next to you
You are disgusting
Yes, I am
No kissing allowed?
So conservative?
What's up?
Sorry...
Me... mine...
Thank you!
Is anything missing?
No
You?
Let's celebrate
My treat
No, mine
Let's go
- Yes
- My treat
I'm so full!
It was great!
Now we need a place to sleep
Let's go
Hundred, thousand...
The bill is over 20 million
That's over HK$70,000
You can't get that in Hong Kong
Of course
What?
I only have small change
The rest must be stolen
Mi, can you?
I don't have the cash
Use your credit card
I just reported the loss
I need to talk
Yes?
I'm not rich
I read this book
On how to catch a rich man
You may be angry
But no matter what
I really like you
It's okay
I'm glad you're so honest
I like you, too
And hope to be with you
But I don't understand
Why I have the same book?
The men's version?
What do you do?
I'm a mechanic
I deliver propane
At this point
We must resolve this bill
I promised I would think for you
Wait here
No matter how
I'll be back with the money
You won't abandon me?
Leave the thinking to me
Okay
Come back soon
Wait here
He won't be back
Telephone?
Hello, credit card center?
I need your help
Sorry, Miss
You're over your limit
But I'm alone in Italy
Can't you help?
But our company policy...
In your ads you say
You'd help in accidents abroad
In accidents
We will, but
Our ads say
Accidents are skiing mishaps,
Emergency illness,
Lost luggage, but not
Inability to pay a restaurant bill
And such a high one
You don't know what happened!
I met a man I liked on a plane
We're happy together
I thought he was rich
But he isn't
But it doesn't matter
I lied to him, too
Just as I felt like a princess, he left
I'm deeply sorry about that
But our company policy...
I'll loan it to you personally
Thank you
Pay me back at 2% over prime
Make sure you do!
It's quite fair.
He brings me joy
He makes me cry
Love's live a fairy tale
Moves me and fills me
I'd die for love
Give it all I have
I'll play my part
Reality's sad
The poor princess
Deluded by the glass slippers
She never meets the prince
The slippers don't exist
Love's an illusion
For fairy tale chasers
Fresh orange juice?
I've just been shorn
I had to run!
How cruel!
We were poor and poorer
What else could I do?
True
We put our money together
To help you find a rich woman
But you found her instead
Good thing you left in time
You must not have used
The English I taught you
I did, almost choked to death
Forget it
Such bad luck
Mas
You're desirable
Why go abroad?
You can get it here
I can't do that
Stick to your goal
In this economy
You need a rich backer
Since I've been with Jenny
My life is better
Since I've been with Jane
I have a new home
Fatty took me shopping
Look, a Praha wallet
I have a Perraer, look
It's Cartier
Right
With diamonds
Forget it
You can think for yourself
Youth fades
Find someone rich
To care for you
It's good
There's a "Dancing Queen" at Club 258
Incredible face and body
And she's rich, and fussy
We'll go with you soon
But you must be smart
Think of us, too
You must repay our loan
We have more cars to test
Hurry
Coming!
I miss Mi
She must hate me
Explaining would be useless
I'm not rich
Even dogs ignore me
Riding the wind purposely
Found a landing spot
There you are waiting
Waiting for me
I dash downward
Either toilsomely
Or lazily
Same target
From the air
Things look like poker cards
Should you vanish
I'd fall to pieces
Call her if you want
Go on
And kiss you dearly
Then I'd have lived
Forever
Should accidents prevail
And I'm ocean-bound
Your passionate eyes
Sleepless
Sceptical
Disturbed
I must buy her a "Strong Wife"
Does it work?
I don't know
But the ad says
"Face it quietly...
...and bravely"
You're like the sky
And I'm the wind
Drifting and drifting
Out of balance
I'm neither confident
Nor special
But with your love
I'm brave
From the air
Things look like poker cards
So much junk food
Mi has been jilted
She'll only eat these
- Really?
- Yes
You're big
You're not small
I head Mi has been jilted
And is like a junkie!
No
Hold the phone
Sure
You're dressed too warmly
Uncle D
What is it?
I hear Mi is a junkie, and suicidal
I'll suicide you!
You okay?
Daughter
What happened?
Mi!
I'm glad you're here
I'm out of propane at home
So I'll buy some
I might as well give
My business to my friend
Thanks
You look terrible
Where is your car?
I'll take it there
Are you all right?
Your boyfriend?
Your girlfriend?
Just friends
I'm carrying it for her, okay?
We're in no hurry
Haven't been to a village in a while
I want to walk around
Be careful in your
High heels
True
We'll just sit and chat
Hey, anything to drink?
They're so rude
I know!
Let's beat them up
We can't
They are guests
Get someone else to do it
Soda?
Help yourselves
I don't let her have soda
- Go ahead
- Thanks
Drink up
So you can go
No, my home has just been sprayed
You know, it takes the smell
A long time to go away
In a 4,000 square-foot home
4 of up, perfect for mah-jong
Great!
I don't know how
Just play
So slow
8 Bamboos
9 Coins?
I have 3 triples!
Be careful
Mi...
1 Coin? Mine!
3 triples, last tile!
I just dropped it
That's Taiwan rules
No going back
But we're playing Cantonese rules
It's the same
You must be quick
To claim your tiles
You must pay our losses
What were you doing?
You did this to yourself
You forced me to play
I'm paying your losses
So shut up
- You are stupid
- So dumb
I was waiting for a Character tile
Why did you discard a One Coin?
I almost won
Too dumb to play
Let's beat them up now
Calm down
Give them more soda
Yes
How's your phlegm?
Wilson?
Wilson? Wilson?
Wilson...
Are you Uncle?
He called me Uncle!
I want...
To buy propane?
- We have fresh cans
- Thanks
I came to see Mi
Mi
Please
Sit
My dad
Hello, Uncle
Wilson...
My old classmates
Hi!
You must be MT
Call me M
Playing mah-jong?
Yes
Join us
I don't play
Come on
- I don't play
- Come on
I don't play mah-jong
What's the bet?
3 Bamboo
I don't think so
Quiet, let Mi play
Leave this, or this
Or claim that
Mi has 3 triples, she's winning
Careful
Two Bamboos Open Kong
I picked a 3 Bamboos
Amazing
That's the wrong call
You're crazy
I need 2 Bamboos and you called
Open Kong
Don't you know how to play?
You just discarded 3 Bamboos
She's crazy!
She doesn't know how to play!
I quit!
Great
Uncle, I'm Wilson
Stay for dinner
Just a shitty little meal
Thanks
You should eat out
Come
Okay?
Sure
Let's go
Are you all right?
I didn't think Mi
Was so capable
Why brag about minor things?
Then, our land deal
Don't worry
We can have the whole city
Bye!
When did you get a nose ring?
Just now, in the bathroom
It hurts
Don't be shy
Go hunting, shopping
"Dancing Queen" will be here soon
At that time
Don't think of dignity
But of yourself, and our money
We'll watch out for you
Sorry, it's too crowded
Are you alone?
Nice legs
He's on his way
"Dancing Queen" is here
Not bad
Make your move
Hurry, before anyone else
Hurry
Help!
Let's go
So soon?
Mi!
Are you all right?
Fine
Don't go! Mi!
You know him?
No
No?
We'll eat these wings
Close up shop
And sleep
You're a good buddy
With me when I'm sad
Good thing I didn't explain
Mi's with Wilson now
He suits her
I'm old and poor
We'd make her life hard
She must be so happy
That's good
You said you don't like men dancing
What happened in Italy?
Why did you abandon me?
So what if I did?
Nothing wrong with that
What?
We like rich people
It's good you're with Wilson
Congratulations
In the mood for barbecue?
Why not?
Hungry? Have one
Yes, I did it to myself
Fine!
Your kaleidoscope; you liked it
Fine
Don't misunderstand
I didn't
Will you ask me in?
Why?
Very direct!
When my friend saw you
She was very unhappy
What the hell?
Very direct!
I like direct people
I don't want her to be unhappy
Take this cheque
Don't make her unhappy
I'm not buying love
When she's happy, I'm happy
Bye
Wait!
Yes?
Can you put my name on it?
My forgetful secretary
To the company, or to you?
My name
Which is?
Christmas Yan
Christmas Yan?
Mr. Yan, you're from...
Hubei
- Hubei?
- Yes
Hello. I'm Wilson
Mr.?
Yan
From?
Hubei!
Mi
Marry me
What are you doing?
Putting on the ring
Stand up
Asking for her hand in daylight?
How can she agree
In front of everyone?
Seal it with a kiss
Out village is peaceful
Blessed and beautiful
Does Wilson suit me?
He's not bad
But no sparks
Be patient
Overcome it
When's the banquet?
How many tables?
1st, I hope to fix my own company
4th, I'm concerned about our youth
About our village
- Yes
- Like this?
- Yes!
- Speak!
I hope we improve
Ourselves
Play badminton
- He's drunk
- Get the pen!
Can I have your
Autograph?
Sure
Here
Uncle
I can't sign a land sales contract
He's not drunk
Intoxicate him!
Drink!
Quiet!
Where's your car?
I need a life line
Tell me, you be quiet
Our youth should raise their competitiveness
Set their sights far
To compete in China
Come out!
Out of the way!
Hi!
What are you doing?
How dare you!
I fed you wings and you betrayed me?
You...
Why did you give me glass slippers?
You asked why
I gave you what I like
So I'm giving you what you like
Where did you get the money?
Your friend
Forced a cheque on me
I had to take it
But I'll repay him in installments
What does this mean?
Mi
Don't go
Listen to me
I've thought it out
I don't want you to be unhappy
There is a reason why
I didn't return for you
I was going to rob someone
But they're bigger than I
And I was afraid
So I decided to beg
But couldn't evoke pity
So I took off my clothes
To look more pathetic
But the police came
It's hot! It's hot!
And took me away
So I couldn't go back
Really?
Yes
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't want you to regret anything
I can't even afford
To fix my washing machine
If you're with me
You'd have to do laundry by hand
And I can't afford lotions
Soon you'll have "Housewife Hands"
Mi
You can't be a princess with me
I can't make you happy
Princesses can have "Housewife Hands"
Then can we be together
Alaise and forever?
It's "always"
Always and forever
Did you get naked?
Down to my underpants
How did you get to the police station?
Walked
How long?
15 minutes, I was freezing
Why didn't you pull up your pants?
I was handcuffed
I couldn't understand the policeman
So I didn't dare move
In case he shot me
Where's Mi?
What is it?
Nothing
It looks like her
It is her!
You're wrong!
- Let's drink
- It's really Mi!
Excuse me
- They're shooting TV
- What is it?
- Congratulations!
- Say something
Everyone wants to know about you
What's going on?
Looks good! Congratulations
To us?
Yes!
You had been selected by our company
We've filmed the whole process
Others have received this book
But never has anyone
Given up money for love
I admire you!
He means you
We've filmed your story
for a reality show
But I need to buy your rights
For $10 million
$10 million?
Excuse me
I'm Uncle D, their manager
Let's talk about this
$10 million is not enough
How much do you want?
Start with $500 million
Let's talk
We'll follow
I will marry a rich man!
And I, a rich woman!
We're both rich
Why don't we...
We should
Wife
How many kids do you want?
None
But you love kids
I do
I didn't say I'd have any
No
Then I'll force you to!
- No
- Will you have children?
- How many?
Welcome to "Marry a Rich Man"
Before we introduce Mas and Mi
It's starting
We spoke to some of their friends
My daughter married a rich man
Because she lives in Harmony Village
Temperate climate, great feng-shui
Suitable for all major developers
Even if you don't buy land
Take home some propane as a souvenir
My fortune was right
Do you want kids?
Let's watch the show
She did marry a rich man
If she can marry rich
So can I
I'm so excited
Do you want kids?
In a moment
Who are you?
Why are you here?
From which paper?
Are you paparazzi?
Turn it off!
It's not me, I love my wife
I love mine
I didn't...
I only visit proper massage parlors
Turn it off
Do you want kids?
Are you safe?
Yes
Boy or girl?
Whichever
How many times?
Up to you
You have a huge stomach!
No, this is muscle!
It's ugly.