Hey folks, I know the Mets are
down three zip in the best of seven.
I know no world series team has ever
come back from 3-0 down to win 4th straight.
I know they haven't played well,
I know the pitching's been bad.
I know no clutch hitting in '86 and '69,
seem a long, long time ago.
And there's no Ruth there's no Garett,
goodness gracious, no Donn Clendenon.
But, you are not out of it
until you lose 4 games,
in a best of 7.
That is all there is to it.
Back to the phones we go, Bruce is
in Bay Side. Bruce, how are you?
How you doin' Chris?
Good to have you aboard, what's up?
Listen, I'm writing off this season.
As far as I'm concerned, the Mets
are out of it. They're down 3...
Writing off?
If you look at great teams
of the past, the As in the '88,
the Indians in '54,
went over 100 games.
The following years these teams
weren't been anything. They're no good.
Forget it, they're gonna
be out of this year.
Question! Did the Indians in '54 say
after the loss of the third game:
"Stop the show at game 4, we've lost".
They won.
Did the As do it? The As won in '89.
It's not easy to win every single year.
This is a team that has
proven they cannot win.
- It's so obvious. Every year...
- They won in '86, did they?
They won in '86 because the guy...
Go! Go!
How many times
you've been late for school?
Your sister gets to school on time.
What's the problem with you guys?
You wanna be driven
around like the President.
I'm your goddamn chauffeur!
Dad, it wasn't our fault!
Yeah, whose fault was it, mine?
No.
Aunt Wendy told us
to take out the garbage.
And she hogged the bathroom.
All morning!
We couldn't get in there,
wash our teeth or do anything.
We had to wait till she got out.
By the time we got out the bus was gone.
So how're we supposed to be on time?
It's the only way we're gonna get there.
Hey, listen to me!
I'm the boss, not aunt Wendy!
When it's your turn to use the bathroom,
you tell aunt Wendy to get
the fuck out of the bathroom!
What are you, men or mice?
She's hogging the bathroom.
Call me, I'll throw her the fuck out!
They're gonna lose, 4-0!
No, they're not!
They're gonna win!
Strawberry is going to fucking kill them.
Knock it off!
Strawberry is killing them.
Knock it off, will you?
Giving me a goddamn headache.
Bye, dad!
Get some shots.
I want some shots over here.
From this point, in here.
Mikey, come here. I think we've
got some prints over here.
How you doin' Mikey?
I got two young girls,
shot in the head, twice each.
Kinda messy.
Over here, Mikey.
Get some pictures from the other side.
I don't know if they're still wearing
the rounds in their head or what.
Hey Mikey, get this back door over there.
There's something on the inside.
Thank you.
Anybody seen anybody?
We got this one Chinese guy over here.
Saw a couple of guys running over
these park benches, 1st Park Avenue.
We got a pretty good
description on the two guys.
The uniform guy put it on the air.
We'll see what happens.
Michael, on the inside of that door.
Let me have some shots on the eye level.
The Mets my ass.
Dodgers will smoke them.
What about tomorrow?
What are you thinking?
You like the Mets?
What do you think of that shit back there?
Terrible.
You guys got money coming,
what are you gonna do?
Dodgers all the way.
Save the money.
With Cone the pitcher?
That Cone-head motherfucker
got right for his game.
I wouldn't bury the Mets.
Even money with Cone the pitcher?
That's right.
You don't think they're
gonna beat him twice, do you?
They're right.
I'm putting my $300 on Mets even money.
Listen...
take the $500,
put it on the Mets.
You say it like it's a fucking
death sentence. It's a smart bet.
I think it is a fucking death sentence.
Strawberry...
No, man. He can't win 4 in a row.
Three, that's it, max.
What about Strawberry?
Gimme some for the phone, please.
- Mike, how are you?
- What's up man, how you doin'?
Here's what we're gonna do.
We took in $10,000 in action.
We got 6 on the Mets,
4 on the Dodgers.
Plus I want another $15,000
on my own, on LA.
15? But that's what you're up!
Why don't you just go ahead?
Don't give me that bullshit.
The Dodgers are a lock.
Are you sure?
Just put in the bet.
I wanna make some money.
You got it.
Gimme something cooked.
It's good shit. Cut it in half.
Shit's gonna kill you, man.
What the fuck, are you a drug counselor?
Or a drug dealer? You don't do your own
product, what kind of business you makin'?
Get back! Police activity!
Just something back for the road.
I'll see you in a couple of days,
and I'll have the money.
Easy! Easy!
Which one of you guys got the money?
Empty your pockets out, the two of you.
Empty your pockets, let me see them.
If I wasn't black you
wouldn't be doing this shit, man.
- He did it.
- I did what? You shut the hell up, man.
What's going on?
Lieutenant sir, the owner says
they stole cash from the register.
Shut the fuck up!
He was chasing them down
the block when I caught up with them.
Go get me a Bud. A High Boy.
Make sure it's fucking cold.
I'll straighten this out.
- That's bullshit.
- That's he!
- It's him! Arrest him!
- How much did they take?
How much did they take?
500 dollars.
Take this guy down to
the precinct and make a report.
You've got to come with me, sir.
- No, I don't want to go.
- Just relax, okay, just relax.
Gimme the fucking money now.
Get the fuck outta here.
Your daddy will be right back.
The door sticks, just a second.
Just on time.
I've some very,
very fine brown shit for you.
Same you loved last time you were here.
No, nobody there.
Where is your pipe?
You ready?
Let's see, where'd I put the lighter?
Here's the lighter.
You got a lighter.
I'll light my cigarette.
It's lit, oh my God.
Get you a little bit more right here.
A little more.
It's a big pile.
So with Brett Butler went on third
and Cow Daniel's on first.
Strawberry stands in
against David Coner.
Coner leading in for the side.
He goes to the stretch,
the pitcher on the way.
And it's a long, high blast,
right center field.
Over the fence, off
the score board of Shea Stadium.
Darryl Strawberry trots around the bases,
and he hits one of those shots
that have trademarked his career.
Play the crowd, but baby,
too little, too late.
The Mets 11-0 lead is now 11-3.
A three run homer for Strawberry,
his third home run of the series
and RBIs 10, 11, and 12.
It's 11-3 Mets.
No matter how far Strawberry hits a ball,
he cannot drive in enough runs,
to get the Dodgers back in this game.
Strawberry with the moon
shot getting congratulations...
in the Dodgers dugout.
That brings is Eric Davis to the plate
and right now all the Dodgers
wanna try and do,
is close the Mets out, gain some
momentum back going into game 5.
If they can make a little noise here,
get some offence going...
I'm going to the table, sit here.
Mom, you okay?
Have a little bit of cake, huh?
Strawberry, you wanna cup of coffee?
Why don't you come in
and have a cup of coffee?
You know, let's face it folks.
I know they got a ways to go yet.
I know they have ways to go,
with the Dodgers.
Possible man shot, 153 King Street.
First one to get is always
the hardest to get.
Confirmed man shot.
Hey Veronica baby, what's going on?
There's a key somewhere under the back seat.
- Over here is a black man
with his throat cut.
- They come in here?
- Yeah, probably.
- They search the car?
- I'll check car.
- All right, good.
- Hey Sarge, how you doin' boss?
- I got a black male with his throat slit.
- Any weapons?
- That needs checking.
- What's that?
- Coke.
Put it in evidence.
I want you two guys to go contact your
junkie friends over on 125th street.
See what you get up. And you
two guys go over to porn shops,
see what else we can get from that.
What's going on?
They raped a nun in Spanish Harlem.
Imagine have that happen to you.
I would have killed these motherfuckers.
They took the fucking chalice,
the Host was still in there.
What did they want with the Host?
What the fuck you think? What do
you think, they wanted to eat the Host?
They wanted to pawn
that fucking chalice off.
They put up a $50,000 reward.
Leave it to the Catholic Church.
Girls get raped every day,
and now we're putting up 50 Gs just
because these chicks wear penguin suits.
What is your fucking problem?
The church is a racket.
So what? Are you a catholic?
I'm a catholic.
Why don't you have
a little bit of fucking respect?
Hey, fuck that noise.
How about the Mets?
I bet you won a shitload on 'em.
More than you did.
I wanna get paid.
What about tomorrow?
Where do you guys wanna go?
You wanna make a bundle,
leave it all on the Mets.
What, you think they're gonna beat Martinez?
The series has got to last 7 games.
Do you know how much money
is riding for commercial time alone,
for the New York, L.A. team?
When is the last time
the series in New York,
did not last 7 games?
Revenue alone in TV commercials?
Endorsements for the players,
The income it's bringing to the city
in transportation, there are no
fucking jobs in New York, are there?
There's no way the series will end tomorrow.
There's too many people want
to milk it for all its worth.
Did I steer you wrong yesterday?
I make a small move.
Leave it on the Mets.
What you wanna do?
I'm in.
Are you a doubter?
I'll tell you what then.
Don't listen to the advice
I told you yesterday.
So you owe me money.
What you wanna do?
Can I help you with something?
I'm in charge of the investigation.
I'm just checking security.
Security...
You wouldn't want those
guys coming back, would you?
For the nun? Or for you?
Here at the soil
are the undergarments,
and the nun's habit.
They are to be taken
by you for evidence.
Now, black pubic hair,
other than the patient was found,
during colon inspection.
Here are the samples of that.
There was trauma to the vaginal mucosa
with multiple lacerations,
that appear to be made
with a sharp object,
in which the hymen
membrane is broken.
It was stated that
this object was a crucifix.
Trauma consistent with multiple penetration.
3cm laceration.
Let the Mets be uplifting.
Let the Mets have dinner at home.
One bullet has been lodged.
Just a couple of more to go.
And I tell you something right now:
The longer this series goes...
the longer this series goes...
the Dodgers will get awfully tight.
And if it somehow
gets two games seventh,
Do you girls know you're
driving with a tail light out?
- Really?
- Yeah.
No, we didn't know.
Thank you for telling us.
Let me see your license and registration.
Actually, I don't have my license with me.
- You don't?
- No.
- You have a driver's license?
You don't have it with you?
Whose car is this?
Listen, this is our father's car,
we don't have a license.
Does he know you got it?
Yeah.
He does?
Does he know you got the car?
Well, not exactly.
You've been bad girls, huh?
Where you're coming from?
New Jersey.
Any drugs in the car?
No.
- No drugs?
- No.
Where were you tonight?
We were at the Cat Club.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, we were at the Cat Club.
You know I should take you in for driving
without a license and registration?
That's a serious thing.
I'll have to call your father up.
How do you feel about that?
Don't, don't do that.
What were you girls doing at the...
what was? Kit Cat Club?
You get a little stoned there?
Come on. I'll do the right thing
if you do the right thing.
I know what it's like to get stoned
a little bit, to get high a little bit.
You gettin' stoned there?
Have any grass there, coke?
We smoked a little grass.
How would your father feel
if he knew that you were here now?
You won't tell him.
That depends.
What do you think about that?
Couple of very beautiful girls,
you know that?
Come on, give us a break.
Couldn't you just give us a warning
for not having... for the tail light,
...and let us go home?
Well you know something,
two just beautiful girls like you...
I could give you a warning.
You want a warning?
Here's the warning.
You do something for me, I'll do something
for you. What do you say about that?
You do something for me and your father
won't find out you took his car and
you're driving without a license.
You got a boyfriend?
- You got a boyfriend?
- No.
I'll tell you something right now.
Listen up to me, ok?
I'm gonna take you down to
the precinct house and call your father.
You hear me?
You can't do that.
What would you do for me if I don't do that?
Whatever you say.
- Yeah?
- You can't call our father.
You ever sucked a guy's cock?
Did you?
Look at me, you.
You ever sucked a guy's cock?
I'm talking to you.
Are you serious?
Did you?
Yeah, so?
Don't talk to me that way,
you hear me?
I'm gonna hold your ass right in,
Sorry.
Just let us go.
We're gonna fix it in the morning.
I'll let you go.
Turn around. I wanna see your ass.
You mind that?
Just one look at your ass.
What do you say?
You, come here.
Look at me. Look at me.
You ever sucked a guy's cock?
You ever sucked a guy's... look at me!
Let me see how you do it.
Show me your mouth
when you suck a guy's cock.
Come on.
Show me your mouth.
What's the big fucking deal, you've
sucked a guy's cock before, haven't you?
Come on, show me.
Show me how you suck
a guy's cock, you hear me?
Show me how you suck...
just turn around.
Show me how you suck
a guy's cock. I'm fucking serious!
The last time I'm gonna ask you.
I'm taking you in, you hear me?
Show me how you suck
a guy's cock.
Show me with your mouth.
Come on, spit the gum out.
Gimme the fucking gum.
Show me how you suck
a guy's cock.
Come on, show me. Show me.
Open your mouth.
Open your mouth and show me!
Show me. Open your mouth.
That's it, show me, like that.
Like that.
Come on, you little fuck.
Show me! That's it, close your eyes
and lick that fucking dick in your mouth.
Come on, that's it. You suck it.
You suck it up.
Show me that fucking mouth.
You like sucking dick?
You like sucking a fucking dick?
Open your mouth
and lick the fucking dick.
Cocksucker,
open your fucking mouth.
It's ok, he's leaving.
Go gently with her.
Sister, I can't imagine
how you feel right now.
But it's very important that we learn
as much about what happened as possible,
so we can get this information
out over the police radio.
What can you tell me
about what happened?
Can you tell me
how many of them were?
Can you tell me what color they were?
Were they black? Were they white?
Were they Hispanic?
Can you tell me how old they were?
Was one older than the other?
There were two of them.
Two young men.
What can you tell me
about the older of the two?
Were there any distinguishing marks?
Or tattoos? An earring?
Did he have a beard or a moustache?
Can you tell me how they were dressed?
Sister, I know this is difficult, but
I can't emphasize how important it is.
the sooner we can
get this information out over the...
Here it is, ball two from Franco,
and John Franco is struggling.
Daniel's in a game situation here
and if he can work his way aboard...
Strawberry has the chance
to play hero once again.
Strawberry on deck.
Strawberry already with 3 hits tonight.
And there's a strike.
3 to 1 and count.
Alright, move. Take the pitch.
Eyes! Eyes! Come on Daniel!
Left of second for one. Relay to first.
It's a double play!
You cocksucker!
You fucking miserable fucking...!
Cocksucker!
He's a fucking shit!
You fucking nigger fucking cocksucker!
You fucking piece of shit!
The body of Christ.
Congratulations... asshole.
Now you owe me 30,000.
Now what are you gonna do?
Double or nothing on the next game.
Double or nothing.
Are you out of your mind?
There's no way I'm gonna
let that bastard take my money.
Take your money? This guy will
blow up your house along with you,
and everybody else in it.
There's no way LA's gonna lose
this game, they're playing at home.
Strawberry is ready to break out.
Fuck Strawberry.
You're gonna end up
owing this maniac 60,000.
That's my business.
Just place the bet.
Those boys.
Those sad, raging boys...
They came to me as the needy do.
And like many of the needy,
they were rude.
Like all the needy, they took.
And like all the needy, they needed.
Father. I knew them.
They learn in our school.
And they play in our school yard.
And they are good boys.
You knew them?
Who were they, Sister?
Who are the boys?
What are the names of these...
good boys you knew?
I could tell you their names now.
And I know you'd be bound
by a sacred vow,
to keep my secret.
But I cannot tell you their names.
For I too am bound.
Jesus turned water to wine.
I ought to have turned bitter
semen to fertile sperm.
Hatred to love.
And maybe to have saved their souls.
They did not love me.
But I ought to have loved them.
For Jesus loved those
who reviled him.
And never again shall
I encounter two boys,
whose prayer was more poignant,
More legible.
More anguished.
Sid Fernandez and Darryl Strawberry,
a battle of wits and talent here.
In the bottom of the ninth in Los Angeles.
Strawberry readies himself.
Fernandez checks for the sign.
The pitch on the way, swinging.
Strike one.
1 and 1, on Strawberry as
Fernandez came in...
with that fast ball
and Darryl could not connect.
1 and 1, the count. Two outs.
Bottom of the night for L.A.,
men on second and third.
The Dodgers find themselves down by 3 and
in need of one of those Darryl moonshots.
One-one pitch from Fernandez.
Swinging foul ball,
off to the third base side.
1 and 2 the count to Strawberry now,
as he once again, walks around,
thinks about what he might see
on this next pitch from Sid Fernandez.
New York Mets, trying to do something
that no other team has ever done.
Come back from a 3-0
deficit in a best of 7 series.
Strawberry is ready,
so is Fernandez.
On the way...
High and outside, it's now 2-2.
So the string runs a little bit longer.
The tension builds here in L.A..
As Strawberry and Fernández battle.
Dodgers trying to eliminate the Mets.
The Mets trying hard...
to send this series
to a seventh and final game.
Fernandez wants
to change baseballs now.
He gets another one back
from the home plate umpire.
It's now a 2-2 count in a game situation.
Once again, no team has
ever come back from 3-0 deficit,
to come back and win a series.
That's what the Mets
are trying to accomplish here.
Strawberry with that big year
this year for the Dodgers.
Trying to continue his
hot hitting in this play-off.
So it's lefty against lefty,
old teammate against old teammate.
Strawberry steps in.
Fernandez to the stretch.
The pitch!
He goes around?
Yes! Darryl Strawberry!
On the check swing goes to the
far, he strikes out.
This game is over.
As Strawberry goes down looking.
The Dodgers are looking at a Mets team
that has tied this series to three.
What drama on a 3-2
pitch third base umpire said,
yes sir, he did go around.
And the expression in
Darryl Strawberry's face says it all.
We're tied 3 games a piece,
and the Mets win 8 to 5.
Hey! You alone, come here.
It's like the old days.
Knock yourself out, ok?
Do it man, come on.
How many drinks did you have?
Well, you got the money?
What money?
Stop fucking around.
Did you bring the money with you?
I don't got it. Not tonight.
You can't get blood from a stone.
Stop fucking around.
Did you bring the money with you?
This ain't no fucking
joke anymore, seriously.
Just put $120,000 on tomorrow's game.
You're a fucking joke, you know that?
- Sweetheart...
- You make me laugh.
Can we get a vodka on the rocks.
He's been waiting since the game ended.
You got me waiting
3 hours like a fucking moron.
What do you think? That you're
like a big game or something with you?
I'm gonna win.
Just make sure the fucking bet's in.
I told you once before that,
this guy will come by your house and
blow your house up with your wife and kids.
Good.
I'll give him an extra
10 grand for his trouble.
Hate that fucking house.
Ya? You think that maybe because
you're a cop he won't kill you?
You're this close already to death.
I've been dodging fucking bullets
since I was fourteen.
No one can kill me.
I'm blessed.
I'm a fucking Catholic.
How's the case going?
What case?
The case with the $50,000 reward?
Remember?
We're on it big time.
Lots of leads.
You can use that 50 to
get yourself out of this hole.
The Dodgers are going to win the series.
It's a fucking lock.
Get this, man.
I was at the game today.
Face to fucking face with Strawberry.
And... and...
And I knew...
that he struck out on purpose.
And that he's saving
it up for the Big One for tomorrow.
Today, for the first time, I understood...
That you're sick of the fucking head.
...that it never could
have gone any other way.
Never could have gone any other way.
So you'd just better
put in my fucking bet.
$120,000 on the last game.
The big one.
Come on! Are you a bookmaker,
or fucking what?
You know, I'll tell you the truth. To be
honest with you. I'm fed up with this.
Here, I'm going to give you this
guy's number. You call him yourself.
You tell him what
the fuck you want.
Put your own bets from now on.
You leaving the sinking ship?
I'll give you something.
That ain't no joke.
You couldn't pay 60.
You lose, you'll be in for 120.
For a fucking guy like you,
they'll kill you for nothing.
Yeah, keep laughing.
I was supposed to meet him
at midnight with the 60.
It's now 1:00.
Better be careful.
I mean it.
What's up man. Come on in.
How you feeling? Come on in.
Go on and help your
sister with the homework.
Make yourself at home.
Sit down.
The Dodgers are going to win tomorrow.
Yes, I know.
There's 30.000 there, so be careful.
Wanna give you a ride, man?
No.
You sure?
You take care, man.
Large?
I want my money.
It's still my money.
If you wanna have a chance
at any part of it shithead,
you will take my bet!
For $120.000,
on tomorrow's game.
What about the one you
owe me from yesterday's game?
Fuck yesterday's game!
The series is seven games not six!
Put in my bet.
I'll think about it.
There's nothing to think about.
Either you put in my bet,
or you get nothing.
- Really?
- Ya?
Really, I'm no fucking asshole.
I'm a fucking cop!
You meet me tomorrow.
In front of the Garden, 33rd and 8th.
You bring your cash, I'll bring mine.
Vampires are lucky,
they can feed on others.
We gotta eat away at ourselves.
We gotta eat our legs
to get the energy to walk.
We gotta come, so we can go.
We gotta suck ourselves off.
We gotta eat away at ourselves
till there's nothing left but appetite.
We give, and give and...
give crazy. 'Cause a gift that
makes sense ain't worth it.
Jesus said seventy times seven.
No one will ever understand
why, why you did it.
They'll just forget about you tomorrow,
but you gotta do it.
Hirscheiser leans in for the sign.
His pitched Benia... ball outside.
Hirscheiser does not have his good stuff,
he has struggled the entire forth inning.
Gooden leads off third.
Vince Coleman on first dancing back
and forth trying to distract Hirscheiser,
he's having enough trouble
concentrating on his pitches at this point.
Ease to the stretch.
Here's the 1-0 pitch to Benia.
And Benia rips it down third base line.
It's rolling toward the corner.
Gooden scores easily.
Now the ball is bouncing around the corner
and Coleman is tearing around third.
He'll score.
Benia rounds second holds up.
Goes back into second with a double.
The Mets lead 5 to nothing.
And you gotta wonder, if the Dodgers
could ever recover from these deficit.
That should be it for Hirscheiser.
Before he even reaches the mound,
he has motioned to the bull pen.
And in relief comes Ramon Martinez.
Listen to me, sister.
Listen to me good.
The other cops'll will just put these
guys through the system.
They're juveniles.
They'll walk.
Get it?
But I'll beat the system.
And do justice.
Real justice.
For you.
I have already forgiven them.
Come on lady! These guys
put out cigarettes on your tits.
Get with the program.
How could you...
How could you
forgive these motherf...
These guys. Excuse me.
How could you?
Deep down inside, don't you want
them to pay for what they did to you?
Don't you want this crime revenged?
I have forgiven them.
But do you have the right?
You're not the only woman in the world.
You're not even the only nun.
Your forgiveness...
will leave blood in its wake.
What if these guys
do this...
to other nuns?
Other virgins?
Old women who die from the shock?
Do you have the right to
let these boys go free?
Can you bear the burden, sister?
Talk to Jesus.
Pray.
You do believe in God, don't you?
That Jesus Christ died for your sins?
What? Got something
that you wanna say to me?
You fuck!
You rat fucker, you!
What?
Say something. I know,
you're just standing there.
You gotta say something!
Something!
You fuck! You fucking stand there!
And you want me
to do every fucking thing!
Where were you?
Where the fuck were you?
Where the hell were you?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
I did so many bad things!
I tried...
I tried to do...
the right thing, but I'm weak!
I'm too fucking weak!
I need you to help me!
Help me!
Forgive me.
Forgive me, please.
Forgive me, Father.
Quite a match up here.
Ramon Martinez against Johnson.
The power pitcher and the fast ball hitter.
I stole it from my husband's shop.
So I could return it
to where it ought to be.
It's a holy thing.
A holy thing.
- Which way is it?
- The boy's right across the street there.
Julio and Pablo.
It's a holy thing.
A holy thing.
Baila. Baila si quieres mas.
Freeze! Put your hands in front of you.
Keep your hands out in front of you.
Get outta here.
You, get out.
And the remaining Dodger fans,
have finally something to cheer about.
The Dodgers must have been wondering...
if they could do anything right today.
Put them on.
Lock them.
- What's your name?
- Julio.
- Pablo.
Put your hands where I can see them.
Gimme a light.
Now it's going to be Harris,
representing the Dodgers' final hope.
Hold it.
Want some good shit?
Harris, like many of these
Dodgers, came out on fire.
Mets are now all standing
on the steps for anticipation.
Pitch thrown his ball one.
The count's even, 1-1.
Put your hand up there,
where I can see them.
...and they're already celebrating.
Foul ball, coming back and out of play.
Now David Cone need one more strike.
to complete the most amazing
comeback in playoff history.
I'll never forget the '86 championship.
But this one, has to be the best.
Everyone, but everyone,
has counted the Mets out.
And now they're one strike
away from winning it all.
This whole thing is really unbelievable.
Here we go, 1 and 2 to count.
Strike three called!
The Mets win it...
Harris doesn't like it, but it's all over.
The Mets have won the championship.
And the Mets are the first team ever
to come back from a 3-0 deficit,
to win a playoff
or a world series.
You raped a holy thing.
You destroyed that young girl.
And she forgives you.
You hear that?
She forgives you.
You're fucking heroes.
You liked holding her down and
shoving your dick into her?
While she couldn't do nothing about it?
Did you like that?
Watch this, motherfucker.
Watch this, you cocksucker!
Look at that! You can't do
a thing about that, can you?
Can you? Look at me. Can you?
Move. Move, you cocksucker.
Move, I'd like to blow your
fucking face apart.
You fucking scumbags.
And she forgives you.
How could she forgive that?
How could she forgive
you slimy little bastards?
How could she forgive a thing like that.
All aboard.
You think you're not
getting on this bus...
you're dead wrong, man.
There's no fucking way
you're gonna miss this bus.
You get on this fucking bus!
'Cause your life ain't
worth shit in this town.
Hey! Cop!