Come on, T.
Come on, baby.
Wake up!
- He was hit... He was hit by a car!
- It's okay.
We need to get him
to the hospital.
Right now! Right now!
We'll need a gurney out here.
There's a kid. I think it's bad.
We'll need some help.
Are you the boy's mother?
Please, follow me.
Is that your boy?
No.
What happened?
I... I think he got hit by a car.
That was his mother.
- She said he was hit by a car.
- Hit and run?
Like I said. I don't know.
I picked them up...
I need you to file a police
report if it was a hit and run.
Shit, I don't even know them.
I wouldn't know what to write.
Just stay, tell the police
what you did. What you saw.
Take you five minutes. Promise.
Wait!
That's my baby!
I know you're not
supposed to move people,
but I didn't know
what else to do.
The boy was laying there...
and the woman was hysterical.
I did the best I could do.
I just lugged him in the car
to come here as quick as I could.
That's what I did.
You did a good job.
So you were
just passing by?
Yeah, just passing by.
I don't know the lady at all.
I'll give you my card.
We'll do a follow-up
if we get anything.
We might call you as well,
if we need to.
- That'd be all right?
- Whatever you need me to do.
I got your number right there.
Is that it?
Can I go?
Yeah. Thanks.
Will that boy
make it all right?
No, he died.
Mrs. Musgrove,
I'll give you my card
and you feel free
to call me anytime
that you can remember
anything about this. Ok?
I'm so sorry.
Can I get something
to clean that off?
That's mine.
- Here's your purse.
- He's gone.
- My baby.
- Yes, ma'am.
He's gone. He's gone.
Will you take her home, won't you?
I don't really know her.
- I'll take her home.
- That's a good idea.
Yeah,
I'll take her home.
Could you do me a favor
and throw that away for me?
- Yes, sir.
- I'd appreciate that.
Where do you live?
Ma'am, you'll have to tell me
where you live.
Now, I'll go
in your purse.
I'm letting you know
I'm going in your purse
to find
an address on you.
You should call
some of your kin people
or a friend or something.
I'm going to have to go.
You gonna be all right?
They told me to call
the Coroner's Office in the morning.
I'm sorry?
They told me to call
the Coroner's Office.
They said
they gonna do an autopsy.
I don't know why
they'll do an autopsy.
He was hit by a car.
I imagine that'll help them
find out who did it.
You really believe
they'll do that?
I believe they'll try their best.
I do.
He's a Black kid.
You think they'll do that?
Here's your bag.
I'll leave it on the floor.
I'm real sorry.
Mr. Grotowski?
Just want to say
sorry about Sonny.
- We liked him a lot.
- We feel bad, sir.
Which one of you is Willie
and which's one's Harry?
He's Willie.
He's Darryl.
I'll see ya.
I appreciate that.
I'm going over to the cafe.
Do you want me to give you a ride?
You sure
you don't mind?
I'm going
that way anyway.
Is this music
all right with you?
- 'Cause I can change it.
- No, it's cool.
You ain't got a car?
It's broke.
I'm saving
to get me another one.
$8.64. Thank you.
Thank you.
You have
a good shift, okay?
Thanks.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Hey, Pop?
- Look it here.
- What are those for?
I bought a gas station.
- That right?
- Mmm-hmm.
It's all bought and paid for.
We own it.
Don't say "we".
You own it.
I didn't buy it.
- Yeah, well...
- I wouldn't have bought no gas station.
Is that right?
I would have stuck
to what I knew best.
- What's that?
- Corrections Officer.
Right.
Well, I ain't
a Corrections Officer no more.
I'm a gas-station owner.
I already made the deal.
It's too late, Pop.
You want me
to fix you something?
No.
Hey.
Here you go.
How are you doing?
I'm doing all right.
Tired.
- You gonna eat something?
- Chocolate ice cream.
Plastic spoon.
You got it.
Thank you.
- You're all set?
- Mmm-hmm.
- About time for you to get off?
Did you want me
to give you a ride?
No...
I really couldn't ask you
to do that.
It's right on the way home.
- You sure you don't mind?
- No, I'd be happy to.
Okay.
- It's right on Prospect Street.
- Clement's?
- Yeah, Clement's.
- You bought Clement's?
Yeah.
I know Clement.
- I can't stand that man.
- He ain't going to be running it. I am.
Well, that's good.
Thanks for the ride.
Can I ask you a question?
Why did you help me?
- What do you mean?
- When you took me and my baby to the hospital.
Why did you do that?
I don't know. I guess...
I just...
doing the right thing,
I guess.
My son died.
And...
well, he...
he died and then...
I never was
a very good father.
He was a good kid.
I guess that somehow
I just...
when I see what you're going
through there
it made me think about something.
I don't know.
You know when you feel
like you can't breathe?
And you can't
get out to...
from inside yourself,
you know?
Really.
Do you want
to come inside?
I like these curtains.
I got these here curtains
on credit.
I never heard of anybody
getting curtains on credit before.
What do you think?
They cute? Ain't they cute?
I love these curtains.
They're good and red all right.
I got...
I got these curtains right here
on credit.
And the man told me...
that I really wasn't supposed
to get this deal.
But I think he liked me,
and he told me I could have
these curtains on credit.
I said, hey what the hell?
Red curtains
will be great for my place.
So I said, hey I'll take it.
- So I got me some red curtains.
- Damn straight, huh.
You sure suck
that whiskey down.
I mean,
Lord have mercy.
My husband used to love him
some Jack Daniel's.
Like I said,
it's a good drink.
- You wait right here. I'll show you something.
- Okay.
Sit right here.
What you got?
Some kind of a school annual?
No.
These pictures
right here...
these are my husband's
drawings right here.
Lawrence.
My husband,
he drew those.
He got himself electrocuted
over there in Jackson.
He got himself...
These right here,
these are my son Tyrell's.
He drew these.
He drew all of these
right here.
He got his talent
from the old man, I guess.
Didn't he?
That's the only thing
that negro ever gave that boy,
was some drawing.
Taught him how to draw.
- It runs in the family, sounds like it.
- Yeah
You know...
he was a good kid, you know.
He was a really good kid.
He was so good.
He was...
he really...
he loved me.
He really loved me.
I understand.
He was so fat.
You saw how fat he was.
I don't care what
I brought in this house,
he just ate it up!
I don't care
what it was I brought in here.
I bring
some Popeye's chicken,
that boy eat the whole thing
before I can get a bite!
He would eat his ass off!
You haven't seen
nobody eat like...
He would eat candy
and gumballs.
He'd make me take him over there
to the Super K-Mart
and he put them quarters
in that gumball machine.
He had to wait
till he get the red gumball.
He always had to get
the red gumball.
He sounds like a character,
I guess.
He'd get
that red gumball
and he'd just eat
on that red gumball.
Hey.
I was a good mother.
I did... every single thing
I can think to do...
I was really good.
- I was a good mother.
- I understand.
I didn't want him
to be fat like that.
I did not want my baby
to be fat like that,
'cause I know,
a Black man in America,
you can't be like that!
And I tried to...
I was trying
to tell him,
"You can't be like that,
you can't be like that
in America, and a Black man."
I was just...
I'm not sure... I'm not sure,
what you want me to do.
I want...
I want you
to make me feel better.
to make me feel good.
I want you
Can you make me
feel good?
Make me feel good.
I don't know
what to feel good's about.
Just make me feel good!
I felt it too.
I needed you.
I needed you so much.
I hadn't felt anything
in so long.
Thank you.
You okay?
Me getting sick back there, doesn't have
anything to do with you, alright?
Pop?
Hey, Pop?
I'm in the damn bathroom!
What the hell happened to you?
I twisted my ankle
trying to take a bath.
Damn it,
I told you to be careful.
Goddamn!
Wiggle your toes.
- You feel that?
- Yeah.
Yeah?
I'm sinking.
- What are you talking about?
- I ain't worth shit.
- You stop that.
- I can't clean myself.
Can't walk to the kitchen
without falling.
Can't get to the phone
before it stops ringing.
I don't feel
like a man anymore.
You're a man, Pop.
Can't even remember
what a woman smells like.
There's a man here.
Where?
Thank you.
- How are you doing?
- Hey, how are you doing?
All right.
What can I do for you?
I got this '89 Comanche
out there...
it needs a lube job,
new points and plugs.
I was wondering
if you'd work on it for me.
Yeah.
When do you need it by?
Just as quick
as you can, really.
Maggie!
Leave that alone, babe.
Put that down.
I can get that to you
about tomorrow afternoon,
late tomorrow then?
I'd appreciate it.
Maybe them boys of yours can...
if they're not doing anything...
wash it and wax it
and everything?
I'm selling it.
All right.
Yeah... I'll ask them.
I'll tell them about it.
I'm sure
they wouldn't mind.
I can't take this.
It was my son's.
It'd mean a lot to him. I'm sure
he'd want somebody to use it.
I ain't saying
I don't want it.
I just can't take it.
I want you to have it.
I really do.
It'd mean a lot to me.
Let's just take it
for a little spin.
Come on.
- I ain't even got my shoes on.
- We won't go far. Let's go. C'mon.
You see how it drives.
- What the hell is this?
- Stick shift.
Here's the insurance and title,
and all the papers you need.
It's all set.
- Okay.
- I'd like to see you tonight.
- We should do that.
- Is that all right?
- I'll see you later.
- See you.
Hank?
That's good.
Hello?
Hank!
It's Leticia.
I'm coming on in, Hank.
Hank?
Who are you?
You just walked in my house?
My bad.
- I...
- Hank?
- You're looking for Hank?
- Yes.
Is he here?
Who are you?
My name is Leticia Musgrove.
And...
me and Hank is...
friends.
Musgrove?
Please,
little darling...
have you got a cigarette?
Yeah.
But it look to me like
you don't need to be smoking.
Come on.
Have you got one?
Match?
So, is Hank here?
Yeah, Yeah.
He'll be back shortly.
I'm Buck, his father.
Is that for Hank?
Yeah.
It's a gift.
I'll see he gets it.
Woo!
Damn!
Hank must have done
something right
to deserve
a fine hat like this.
I guess he did.
In my prime, I had a thing
for nigger juice myself.
Hank's just
like his daddy.
He ain't a man
till he split dark oak.
Hey, Leticia?
Hang on.
Where are you going?
Hey!
- What happened?
- I met your daddy.
- Get off me!
- You can't do that.
Give me a chance.
Whatever he did...
It don't matter
a whole lot, do it?
- Give me a chance to talk to you.
- Get off me!
We're family.
I'm your father.
Remember that.
Hank?
What's your problem?
- I believe that's it.
- Thank you.
I didn't date
that thing at the bottom.
No problem.
Anything below that line,
I didn't do.
Now, you will take
good care of him, won't you?
- Oh, yes.
- 'Cause...
I want him
to go out in peace.
You must love him very much.
No, I don't.
But he's my father.
So, there it is.
They'll get you
a TV set tomorrow.
Finally getting rid
of me, huh?
They'll
take care of you.
There's a telephone at the end
of the hall. You can call me.
This is it.
I guess so.
I'm stuck.
Me too.
I don't want
to go out like this.
Me neither.
Goodbye, Pop.
What?
You want your car back?
No, I don't
want the car back.
I mean for you to keep that.
What?
I want you to know
I sent him away.
I ain't got time to talk.
I wish you would talk to me.
Y'all ready to order?
- How are you doing, Ryrus?
- All right. How are you?
- I'm all right.
- Who's Leticia?
My girlfriend.
Sheriff's Department.
Hello?
- Who's banging on my door?
- The Sheriff's Department.
- Time to go, lady.
- No, no wait.
- Time to go.
- No. Here.
No, I don't take anything.
You settle with your landlord,
then I go away.
No,
I got the money.
I suggest
you get fully dressed.
- I'm going to put you out.
- You ain't putting me out.
I 'bout got the money.
I'm still saving...
I painted
the ceiling and the wall
and fixed it up
a little bit.
I figured I ought to.
I'll move your stuff here
so you don't have to worry with it.
I'm going to the kitchen
to get a thing or two
so if you want to relax,
make yourself comfortable.
Whatever you want to do.
- This is Tyrell's.
- I thought I'd put it up there.
That's my boy's room.
All right. Here.
You can go up
if you want to.
Can I look at these?
Yeah, go ahead.
That's him right there.
He don't look like you.
He got his mother in him.
I don't mind sleeping
across the hall if you want me to.
- Maybe you should sleep by yourself.
- No...
I wouldn't feel good
if you left me in here
all by myself.
I just want you
to be comfortable here.
I want you
to be comfortable too.
I want to take care of you.
Good.
'Cause I really need
to be taken care of.
Can I touch you?
Yeah.
Did you feel that?
Oh yeah.
Did it feel good?
Yeah.
I didn't hurt you or anything?
Not in a bad way.
What?
Nothing, I just...
I want to go out
and buy some ice cream.
- Now?
- Yeah.
It just feels right.
- Okay.
- Well...
Can you buy me some?
Yeah.
What kind do you want?
Chocolate.
Hey.
I bought
some chocolate ice cream.
Are you okay?
You sure?
You look real pretty.
Let's go out on the steps.
You want to?
Let's go.
I went by our station
on the way home.
I like the sign.
I think
we'll be all right.