Oh!
Ooh.
Good God!
So, you had fun up there.
I was blending;
that's what agents do.
Would you please stop?
I'd like to get to Banning's
table before morning.
Whoa! Hey, slut, thanks.
I hate celebrities
who brush off their fans.
Banning's girlfriend
has been drinking.
Okay, she might be
able to tell... Clark!
Yes.
Stop.
Get on the scene, Sex Machine.
Great job, man.
Hi.
Hi. Good evening.
Hello.
Well, we're all
vaguely honored
you could join us, I suppose.
Singing is my favorite
type of music.
Oh, admirable.
Regrettably, this is
my vacuous fiancee.
I think her name is Cheryl
something.
Oh, charmed.
I could look at you all day.
Do you ever dance
unprofessionally...
Emperor?
Let's see what I can do.
Oh, excuse us.
Of course.
Do you know how to mambo?
I hope so.
Whoo!
Hmm... '92 Dasani.
Gentle bouquet with a hint
of vinyl polychloride.
Earthy yet... ethereal.
Cheers.
Oops.
I spilled.
You and Banning seem very close.
Tell me about his work.
I don't want
to talk about him.
I want to talk about you.
You're such a handsome devil.
So are you.
When I can't sleep at night,
which is quite often
I step into my
laboratory and I play.
It's not work, you see.
It's glorious
wet... play.
Well, maybe I can
come over and play.
That would be very nice.
The thing is, I, uh...
I have a small problem...
trusting people.
I don't know if I can trust
myself with you, Deitrich.
Well, maybe we can come up
with a way for you to pro...
Her name's Del Blaine.
She's CSA.
Oh, bloody hell.
He drives a BMW,
registered to Clark Devlin.
You told me you
dealt with Devlin
with the skateboard bomb.
Yeah, well, he looks
pretty alive to me.
Pretty good dancer.
He's all over Cheryl.
You want me to do
something about that?
No.
Maybe the rancid tart
might actually be
of some use for once.
Get the boys, would you?
Whoo! I am so bushed.
I'm sorry,
you'll have to excuse me.
Unfortunate interruptus.
So, my long streak of love,
here is the key
to the hospitality suite
should you feel the need
to spend the night.
Good-bye.
Well, I think I'll just go up
to room 7-2... excuse me... 6-8
and take a long, hot bath
in room 7-2-6-8.
Good night.
And once again,
we end up with nothing.
I can get her to talk.
And say what?
Oh, Emperor,
would you sign my bra?
Oops, I'm not wearing one.
What is it with you and bras?
She has information.
Oh, right, and that's why you
have to go up to her hotel room.
You have never seen my work.
This is what
Clark Devlin does best.
Can I go home?
No, you have to cover me.
With what, a shot of penicillin?
Huh?
Fine.
I'll be waiting by the pool.
Oh, wait.
What's her room number again?
7-2-6-8.
7-2-6-8. 7-2-6-8. 7-2-6-8.
Yoo-hoo!
Cheryl!
Hey, you little devil.
What kind of bubbles
do you like?
Little...
...or big?!
Hang it for me, will you?
So...
I know you can dance, but...
what else can you do?
Get on the bed.
I'll show you.
Oh!
Okay, Mr. Devlin,
let's see your magic.
Oh, my God, your hands
are like a machine.
Oh, I am never working
with him again.
So, tell me about Deitrich's
good friend, Walter Strider.
Oh! Never heard of him...
but I know Dry Martini.
Maybe someone should mix us
a couple.
Y-O-U spells "you."
Oh.
You're smart.
Really?
And a good speller.
Thanks. I graduated
top two-thirds
of my sixth grade class.
What a gentleman.
Look, it's Cocktail Barbie.
Take your clothes off
and stay a while.
L-I like my clothes on.
Kinky boy.
Wh-Wh...?
Where did you
get that pin?
Oh. Deitrich.
Want to have a closer look?
Huh?
I'm sorry.
Look at the time. I got to go.
Oh, Emperor.
Where are you going?
What are you doing?
Oh, Emperor.
Oh, where are you going
you naughty boy?
I adore romance when it's rough.
Whoo!
Get back here!
You're dead meat!
Come on!
Take a bath.
Oh, yes, because I've been
a dirty, dirty girl.
Go fill the tub.
Do you like it with bubbles?
Hot bubbles.
Oh, yippee!
Yippee!
Tiny bubbles in my wine...
Makes me feel fine
Come on, her voice reminds me
of my mother.
Is that room service?
What's happening?
What's going on under those
cute little boxers of yours?
Emperor, the bubbles
are perfect.
Come to mama, Emperor!
Coming!
Ow!
Help!
Say good night... agent!
Del Blaine. Del Blaine.
Sorry.
Emperor...
This is not what I signed up for!
I need my bathroom bud.
Shh. She's in there taking a bath.
What happened to your nose?
Sorry!
Honeymooners.
Yes, some things never change.
Emperor!
Emperor, come back!
Please!
Oh...
Go! Get going.
Ouch!
Can't you do anything?
Why are you so mad?
Gee, let me think.
Because big, ugly men
are trying to kill me?
Because I got stuck
with a millionaire playboy
dilettante for a partner?
You don't care
how you make people feel.
I happen to be
an extremely sensitive person.
Ow!
Okay, you think
you know feelings.
Look at me.
How do I feel?
Sick.
Sad.
What about now?
Constipated.
Creepy.
Horny.
Is funny.
Is angry.
Is crazy.
You know nothing.
This is why you don't have
a boyfriend.
No wonder you didn't get
anything from Banning.
Oh... right, I didn't
get anything from Banning
except where
his friggin' lab is.
Where?
Let's see if the great master
"agent" can figure it out.
Banning said he sometimes
has trouble sleeping.
Big secret.
All men have trouble sleeping.
Sometimes at night, he goes
down and works in his lab.
He sleeps in his lab?
He sleeps in his bedroom.
His lab's in his bedroom?
No.
Get your facts straight.
His lab is at his house...
his casa, where he lives...
get it?
Excellent.
You passed the test.
I put in a good word
with the boss.
Well, let's go
see Chalmers tonight.
No.
Keep him out of this.
Just you and me.
You know,
if you're so good at this
why-why don't you tell me
something about me?
Okay.
You have big crush on me
and I know your
name is Del Blaine.
First of all, you wish, and...
my real name is Delilah.
Delilah?
Suits you.
Hey...
Hmm?
Ooh!
Oh!
Oh... oh, Emperor!
Hey!
Oh, God, Clark,
isn't anything sacred?
Oh, rug burns are so sexy!
It's the driver.
Oh, my God.
Thank you.
Invitations?
Oh, yes.
Why don't you offer him
five bucks?
I have them somewhere.
Birds of a feather...
Nice party, huh?
So, you're the strong,
silent type, huh?
That's the whole
bouncer package.
I didn't mean your package.
Thank you...
Dr. Schwartz.
Shalom.
Come, darling.
Product launch, my ass.
Let's go find
Banning's lab.
Let's go.
Are you trying to get me alone?
Where'd they go?
Don't tell me
the great Clark Devlin
can't come up with an answer.
Although
he can walk on water.
It's a trick, right?
Come on.
Wow!
Mr. Devlin likes insects, too.
What?
Oh, uh, uh, I mean
sometime I speak of myself
in the third person.
Hmm, Del Blaine
thinks you're a freak.
Have you cleaned the tanks?
What are they doing down there?
I don't know.
When you're done here
you can go and sweep the tunnels.
Don't use the blower!
I can tell the difference.
And don't touch the tequila
for me and Mr. Banning.
Whatever you say there,
Dr. Simms.
Yes, Dr. Simms.
Louder!
- Yes, Dr. Simms.
We better hope the little
ones follow the queen.
Well, if they don't
the stock is going
to be worthless.
"Follow the queen"?
Huh? Have you seen Cheryl?
Maybe he's gay.
Cheryl? No.
Man, let's get out of here.
Let's go have a smoke.
It still stinks.
Hey.
How did you...?
Whatever.
Look at this.
He's pinpointed
the national reservoirs.
He's going to poison
the water?
Not with that stuff.
It's too detectable
and there's
government safeguards.
Let's check out the computer.
Now you're thinking.
Who are they?
They shouldn't be in the lab.
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
Oh, your God what?
DNA recombinant microbes
carrying a T-4 genome.
English.
Genetically induced
hydrogen-oxygen barrier.
Normal person's English.
Dehydrating water.
Drink it,
you'll shrivel up and die
but the big question is,
how is he possibly
going to introduce it
into the water supply?
I think we better go.
Huh?
Go.
Quick, over there by the wall.
Nobody here.
Let's check the hatchery.
You're on my foot.
What was that about?
Shh! Go!
How did they miss us?
What, are they blind?
Don't look up my skirt.
Banning's got the bacteria
but he has to transport it
from his lab to the water.
There's no way he can.
Maybe with airplanes.
Not possible.
Besides, even if he could get it
to a reservoir undetected
an alarm would trigger
the second the surface
of the water's broken.
You're really smart.
It's an act.
I'm an inexperienced girl
who's trying to bluff
her way through.
You are?
Come on, stop humoring me.
Just be honest.
Honest?
All right.
You think
I'm the great Clark Devlin.
Yeah, hello?
Steena, I can't talk right now.
Yeah.
Yeah, I can handle it.
Bad news?
Can we go somewhere
and be... alone?
Sure.
I didn't know
you were so strong.
Take off your clothes.
Let's not do anything
we'll regret.
Take off your clothes.
What's happening?
Look, I knew
the second I met you
you weren't Clark Devlin.
Now take off the tuxedo.
It doesn't belong to you.
I wanted to tell you,
but I just didn't know how.
Take off your clothes.
What is that?
Hey!
Whoa!
You, out here!
Okay.
Take the clothes.
Slow down.
My name is Jimmy Tong.
I'm Mr. Devlin's driver.
He asked me to find
Walter Strider.
I don't want to hear
any more of your lies.
Now, give me the watch
and the shoes.
Now, where's Clark Devlin
and how did you think
you were going
to get away with this?
Things happened.
I decided to go with the flow.
What about the underwear?
They're mine.
L-I mean, my roommate.
Jimmy.
Suits you.
These are my roommate's, too.
Go finish your business.
Have you seen the Emperor?
No.
Impolite to leave
without saying good-bye
to the host.
I was just looking for Deitrich.
I'll take you to him, then.
Like a big terrier
with a little rat.
I think she was
down in the lab.
Well, at least your interest
in water was genuine.
Look, I'm here because of you.
You wanted to know
if I could be trusted?
I bet this tux
is just your size.
Thank you.
We got a positive location
on Blaine, sir.
How long till we get to her?
20 minutes.
I've transmitted
the coordinates.
Dear Mr. Devlin
I did the best I could,
but it wasn't good enough.
I did not find Walter Strider
for you.
I also lost your tuxedo.
I'm sure you will get it back.
I guess I will go back to being
what I was before I met you.
Oh!
Water Strider.
Water strider.
Water strider!
Stupid!
My beautiful little darlings.
Gerris maginatus.
Species native
to Southeast Asia.
Commonly known
as the water strider.
Walter Strider.
Yes, the water strider.
Very good. Very good.
Well, it's brilliant.
They touch down
on the reservoirs.
Their little feet transfer
a deadly bacteria
without breaking
the surface of the water
so no alarms sound,
and it looks like
a nasty little trick of nature.
Fortunately
there is one drinkable
water source.
Yours.
Deitrich,
you're a genius.
Too bad it won't work.
Oh... you so wrong.
Wrong! Wrong! Wrong.
It will work because
my plan is perfect.
Sorry, Mr. Banning,
it's your plan... and mine.
Um... it's ours.
Shut up. Explain.
Oh, all righty.
The life cycle
of the Gerris maginatus
begins with mating...
something Dr. Simms
is not personally familiar with.
Anyhoo, the insects swarm
to freshwater
where fertilized eggs are then
deposited on the underside
of lotus leaves
and hatch into larvae.
Spare me
the Discovery Channel blather.
Tell me why it won't work.
Yes, tell us.
Why it won't work?
This is the northern
hemisphere, correct?
You incubated insects native
to the southern hemisphere.
So, simply, it is too cold
for them to mature sexually...
much like Simms here.
Therefore...
they won't mate.
Therefore,
they won't seek out water.
Is this true?
No, I knew a girl once,
in college, quite well.
Very well.
And then you remember
cousin Doris?
No, Simms, the bugs.
The bugs.
Oh, you're not going
to believe this hootchie
are you, Mr. Banning?
Oh, yeah?
Ask him if I lied
about the tuxedo.
This tuxedo is...
it's all right. It's...
"All right"?
That is the most incredible
piece of technology
on the planet.
And I am laying it
in your big, hot hands.
Mr. Banning, release the bugs.
Go ahead.
Do what he tells you.
You might have a chance
at second prize
at a junior high school
science fair
but you can forget your dreams
of world domination.
Slip into it, Deitrich.
See how it feels.
The other ten percent's
in there.
You've got plenty of it.
Hey, Dr. Schwartz.
Tell your boss
Clark Devlin is back.
Drapes nicely.
Well, it certainly puts
a spring in one's step.
Happy to have lightened
your loafers, Deitrich.
One question.
Why are you doing this?
Hey, what the hell is this?
This is the moment where
50 CSA commandos storm in
take you,
your pretentious accent
your jackass sideburns
to the Federal pen where,
guess what?
All they serve is highly
chlorinated tap water.
Presenting Clark Devlin.
Have I told you how amazing
you look in this tuxedo?
Simms, prepare for release.
With pleasure, sir.
Hatchery doors opening.
Water sources targeted.
Pods will begin releasing
striders in five minutes.
Maturation level: 85%.
Why are you here?
I've come to save you.
That's great.
What about the big guys
with the big guns?
For years, I've heard about you.
Now we finally meet, I find
that the great Clark Devlin
is nothing more
than an ordinary man
who's about to die
an extraordinary death.
You're right
except for one thing.
My name's Tong.
James Tong.
You okay?
Uh, Jimmy, is there
something you want to tell me?
Later.
Oh, you've got
a good suit as well.
All right!
Let go!
X-4 genome bacteria-induced
water striders: 100% mature.
Bacteria drop sites identified.
Pods now opening.
What are you doing?! No! No!
She's ruining everything.
Electrical malfunction.
Hatchery door is disengaged.
Ah, I knew girls like you
in high school.
Yeah? Did they do this?
Uh-huh, they did.
Mr. Banning, you must
open the hatch manually.
Sod off.
Manual hatch release required.
Rotate valve counterclockwise
to open hatch.
Get off.
Bloody open!
Manual procedure complete.
Hatchery doors opening.
Airborne striders
awaiting queen release.
Hatchery doors opening.
Clark!
I mean, Jimmy, help me!
I'm busy.
All mature striders
ready for release.
Bacteria-laced microbes
fully activated.
His head's about to explode.
Look at him.
Look at him!
You might know a few tricks
but you're just
a sad, pathetic man.
Smoking is bad for your health.
You okay?
Yeah, duh.
By the way, nice going.
Now millions of people are going
to die of dehydration.
You left the hatch open.
They're not flying away.
Yeah, what are they waiting for?
They are waiting...
to follow the queen.
Airborne striders
awaiting queen release.
Oh, my God.
For once, you're right.
The queen is going
to lead the striders
to freshwater sites
all over North America.
Quick, grab it
before it's released.
Queen strider disengaged.
Alert!
Let's go.
He's got the queen!
Wait!
You dropped it.
Don't move!
Oh!
Ow.
Sir, excuse me,
I deserve to see this.
Ugh.
Trouble.
Okay, okay, make hustle, ladies.
Let's go. Let's go.
Watch out, Aqua-Lung.
Hey, pal, nice suit.
It's okay, kitten.
Everything's going
to be all right.
It is not okay.
You just decked the hero.
L-I'm a genius and I can testify
for a piece of immunity.
Also, I'm from
a neutral country...
Shut it.
Well, looks like we
got here just in time.
Oh, to what? Take credit?
Oh, you're hilarious, Blaine.
Winton Chalmers, CSA.
I spearheaded the operation
that took down Deitrich Banning.
I bet you're Jimmy Tong.
Here's your tuxedo.
You happy now?
Well, I will be when I get it
safely back to headquarters.
By the way, Blaine,
not a bad job
for your first time
in the field.
Well, I didn't do it alone.
She always says
nice things about me.
When you finally
do something right,
you deserve the credit.
Well, sir
it's an honor to help
the United States of America.
I feel exactly
the same way, soldier.
You don't think you're going
to be able to get away
with a bureaucratic pat
on the butt, do you?
Well, I'm hoping to.
Ooh, man down, people.
Well... there is one thing
you can do for me.
And that would be?
All right, tracking
systems locked on.
Anybody screws up
and your ass is mine.
Block off this end
of the street.
Roger that.
All right, we're at
T minus 30 and counting.
Is everyone in position?
Manhole agent up.
Flower lady, hot dog vendor, go.
Replace the hot dog vendor.
Come on, hustle.
Let's go.
This is Bird Three,
the street is secure.
Uh-oh, bike messenger.
Hostile forces moving in.
Go on, Randall, take him out.
Roger. T-14 descending.
Advance the lead
operation vehicle.
Bring in the package
as soon as I cross.
Roger that.
Hustle, people.
The package is on the move.
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
it's show time.
How's our package?
I forget what to say.
But you can do this.
Focus. Go.
Huh?
Go.
Package dropped.
Roger. Target locked.
Jimmy, what do you say?
The name's Tong. James Tong.
I'm the man. I'm the man.
Del, did you tell him
to say that?
No. Well, sort of.
Oh, God.
Come on, ladies, relax.
He's just pumping out
pheromones.
Clark, shut up.
I do believe I'm in charge
of this operation.
Package is locked on target.
Why did you wear those pants?
He's stopping.
- What's he stopping for?
- Why is he stopping?
Use the door, Jimmy.
He's really
breathing heavy now.
Have you seen her?
He's out of his league,
if you know what I mean.
Shh!
- He's like a hunter.
- It's the gallery owner.
Randall, quiet.
Nice.
Clark, please,
would you focus?
He's about to speak.
Open your mouth.
Hi.
- He said, "Hi."
- Hi.
That's the girl?
He came up with that on his own.
She's not that pretty.
Jimmy, smile, come on.
Move on to something else...
quick.
He doesn't look so good.
- Jimmy? Jimmy?
- He doesn't look so good.
Clark, give him a line.
Steena, shut up.
- Just look deep into her eyes...
- Clark, no.
That crap doesn't work...
Looks like
he's hyperventilating.
If I remember rightly,
it worked...
Don't listen to them.
Listen to me.
I can't think with you
screaming in my ear.
Everybody calm down, all right?
Not you, her.
No, no, her, her.
Look deep into her eyes...
It's me.
...and tell her you had a dream
about her last night.
Clark, be quiet.
Del, will you shut up?
Uh...
I hate to say this, Jimmy
but don't take advice
from women about women.
Shut up.
Clark, you've been reassigned.
The voices are screaming in my ear.
Hey, if you can hear me
wipe that look off your face.
Remember me?
Hooters.
Soul patch.
Okay, I'm going to have
to ask you to leave.
I'm the love of my life...
No, no! No, no!
You're the love of my life.
No, you never tell them
you love them, Jimmy.
Can you have... dinner with me?
Get out.
Pretty sure he craps
his pants, people.
I just want to have dinner.
Get out now.
- Lunch?
- Now!
Oh!
All right, we're
terminating this mission.
Pack it up and roll home.
I think I blew it, Mr. Devlin.
Jimmy, I wrote the book
on this stuff.
Trust me, you didn't blow it.
You outgrew her.
Maybe.
Tell you what.
Take the weekend off.
First thing Monday morning
we'll head for somewhere with
more interesting prospects.
How about Monte Carlo?
Sounds good.
Thanks, Mr. Devlin.
Thanks, everybody.
It's okay, Jimmy.
Hang in there.
Next time.
Well, if you were trying
to get her to notice you
mission accomplished.
What are you planning
for the second date?
Running at her with a knife?
It's difficult for me.
What is so hard?
You just have to say
something like...
"Excuse me, you want
to go get some coffee?"
When I around beautiful
women, I can't talk.
Sure. Beautiful women.
You know, a real knockout.
Like the beautiful lady
in the gallery.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
What?
You can't tell how I feel?
You look sad.
No.
Sick?
Constipated?
No.
A little.
Tell me, what's wrong?
It's just no guy would ever
do anything for me
like what you did for her.
Or tried to do.
You know why?
Because you are
a pain in the butt.
Yeah, nice working
with you, too.
Hello.
Delilah, excuse me.
You want to have a coffee?
I only drink organic green tea.
Wrong answer.
You're never going
to have a boyfriend.
Fine.
Coffee. I love coffee.
You learn quick.
Is that your happy face
or your horny face?
I tell you later.
James. James...
Tong...
Cut.
Oh...
Couldn't tell you
what I'm about to say.
Purse!
Cut.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
The bird hit the guy.
Is this a bunch of crap.
Is this a bunch crap?
Bunch of crap.
Okay.
You think I'm speak
very good English, huh?
What's in your head,
flies out your mouth.
fly from your mouth.
What's in your mouth...
That's okay. Cut.
No wonder.
This is why
you don't have a boyfriend.
That's...
That's... thought...
Frog?
Fraud.
Look at...
Look at her ugly face.
Every time I look...
Every time, she just like this.
How can I act?
- Can we do a single on me?
- No.
Action!
Aah...
No, no, no.
Cut! Cut!
Let's follow 'em.
They'll take us to the lab.
Who?
Let's...
Cut.
I got the happy partner
over here.
Jimmy.
What do you...?
She smile the whole movie.
Waste of film, waste of time.
What is she doing?
Hit me!
Oh, no!
You're fast.
But I'm faster.
Captioning sponsored by
DREAMWORKS PICTURES
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org