Frost fills the sky over
Ten Mile Lake
Silken threads anxicus of youth.
Looking at the moon and feeling lonely.
Envious of love, not of imortality.
This pointing will remind you of me.
Sian's grave?!
Sian died long ago.
She's ghost?!
Yes!
I'm a ghost but I bring mortals no harm.
I died far away from my home
An evil spirit took by corpse
and won't let me rest in peace.
If you want to save me,
move my bones away from here.
Then it will be possible for
me to be reincarnated.
Sian!
I will save you.
Ning!
Let them go, please.
The Diamond Sutra!
We've escaped!
Sian, we're safe!
Dawn is breaking.
Sian, hide in the tower of ashes.
If the sun's rays shine on you,
you'll never be reincarnated.
Ning, good-bye forever!
I hope that Sian will be reincarnated.
I must return
to the Orchid Buddhist Monastery.
If you need me, you can find me there.
Take care!
Looking for the way,
the way of freedom.
Sea and mountains,
I have traversed countless times.
A thousand paths,
all leading to my homeland.
The endless verdent mountains,
The mountains everywhere,
in howling wind and driving rain.
The path of the ancient garden.
Why does it never end?
The way of the Tao,
the way of freedom.
Devils and demons always
pronounce themselves good.
The anger of youth
Weeping ghosts and angry spritis,
Times gone-by,
Why was there such a sea of blood?
The path of the ancient garden
Why can one never return on it?
Who is that young man?
He's the poor schoolar who
lived 2 blocks away.
Things have changed since he
was last here.
Wasn't he that shop's bill collector?
He doesn't even know it went
out of business long ago!
Welcome! Welcome!
The bill collector's here.
How much money did you collect?
We're here to catch escaped convicts.
It's the police! Run!
Pursue them!
You're Bing Chow?!
You've made a mistake.
He has a beard and I don't!
You shaved it off!
Take him back and collect the reward.
Get in!
I haven't committed any crime!
Let me go.
I've been wrongly accused!
You're made a mistake.
I'm not Bing Chow!
I am wrongly accused!
My name is Ning,
not Bing Chow.
Old man may I ask who...
A man just like you,
fated to being imprisoned.
So pessimistic!
It's all my elders' fault,
insisting I get an education
When I grew up,
I was learned and wrote books.
But when I write of my travels,
I'm accused of revealting state secrets.
When I write of history,
they say I'm satirizing the present.
If I analyse milltary strategy,
they say I'm planning arebellion.
I can't even write fairy tales,
for they accuse me of promoting superstition.
Finally,
I wrote the biography of a powerful man.
Then he was arrested,
accused of being a rebel.
We here both sentenced to life imprisonment.
Wouldn't you say that prison is my fate?
A cockroach!
Where?
Cockroach?!
You're really wasteful!
The cockroaches here are of the best quality.
There are no delicacies here
After you're been here a while,
you'll even salivate ever a housefly.
Old man, how long have you been here?
I was your age when I first arrived.
Look how I've changed!
Full of character!
You've been here a long time
Help! I am innocent!
I'm not Bing Chow!
I am innocent!
You've made a mistake.
I'm not Bing Chow!
Another nightmare.
What did you dream this time?
I dreamt you were haggard and exhausted.
Exhausted?!
True, you will soon be totally exhausted.
You have nightmares every night.
Look at the calendar.
You've been here so long and
still can't adjust.
Soon you'll even forget
that your last name is Chow.
Old man, my last name isn't Chow!
Bing Chow!
Supper!
OK.
A chicken leg?!
Happy days are here again!
Old man!
There's only one bowl. You eat first.
No, it's for you.
I'd rather eat cockroaches.
I'll tell you something
when you've finished.
I haven't had chicken in a long time.
Old man, why are you carving my name?
All these men ate chicken legs.
We call that chicken a headless chicken.
After you've eaten it,
they chop off your head!
Chop off your head?!
Bing Chow, we have no personel quarrel.
Don't come back from the
greve and seek revenge on me
They behead people at noon.
It's now the middle of the night.
Some official's son got in trouble,
and they're looking for a substitute.
At night, the executioner
can't tell one from another.
Is there no justice in the world?
Is there no reward for being a good man?
It is of no concern to me.
I was always an honest man.
I'll give you whatever I can
This painting was a gift
from my dearest one.
I don't want to part with it even in death.
Young man, you have a good heart.
Let me give you a present.
You are so learned.
It is fortunate that I die
rather than you.
You're a good man.
Such a pity you have to die.
It would be a pity if you died, not me.
Anybody's death is a pity.
You're a rare speciman.
If you die, your type will be extinct.
It's been a long time
since I set somebody free.
This tunnel leads to the outside.
Go out and start anew.
Don't give me such false hopes.
If this is an escape route,
why didn't you escape long ago?
It's less troublesome for me
to write my book here.
When I finish,
then I'll escape and get it printed.
Don't worry about me.
Always keep this bundle with you.
Once you're out of here,
never come back!
Get going!
What will happen to you
after I've gone?
They like hearing my stories
So long as I don't get to the story's end,
they'll never harm me.
But they'll accuse you
of helping me escape.
I'll say you were put to
death for somebody else 2 days ago.
They won't dare make a fuse.
- Go!
- Take care!
Bing Chow! The time has come
Bing Chow!
He's dead.
I've escaped!
There's even a horse here waiting for me!
That old man is really remarkable!
I must repay his kindness someday.
Hey! That's my horse!
What a stupid horse!
Letting a stranger ride him!
I don't even have time
to wash my hands!
You think you're fast over land...
I'll go underground!
Open sesame!
I must find a place
to get out of this downpour!
Good! A house!
Open the door!
"Righteous Villa"...
Anybody home?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
8 coffins!
Must be the whole family.
I won't disturb you.
I just want to stay the night.
Don't bother to get up.
I'll take care of myself.
I told you not to go any trouble.
Please go back!
The way you rush about
in no fixed direction!
I had a hard time following you underground.
Don't you have any idea
where you're going?
Your face looks so horrible,
you must have suffered a painful death.
If you'd rushed around underground
all day like me,
you wouldn't have the energy
to come back to the surface.
I don't know you.
Why are ou following me?
I don't know you either,
so why did you take my horse?
That's your horse?
I thought it was the old man's.
Still you should have asked before taking it.
You're alive! Sorry!
It's all a misunderstanding.
If there's anything I can do to help,
just let me know.
Enough of your tricks!
A good thing my reactions are so fast.
Friend, you need a place to stay the night.
Here there's a roof over your head.
Might as well stay here.
How do I know what you'd do
after I fell asleep?
I knew it!
Let's draw up some boundaries.
I'm staying next door.
If you have something to say shout it!
Don't come over.
I haven't bathed in a long time.
The way
The spoken "way" is not "way"
Of haven and earth,
Of humang and swards
Of evil and good,
This way, that way, every which way
Say that their way,
is the only way
Bah. Tehah, hah!
All bullshit,
This way, that way,
is still not the way
Ha! Ha!
The way of flowers and tea, Ha!
Of life and death,
Of density and intensity,
Of light and heat,
Of evil spirits
Of people committing crimes
Of bed ones in power! Ha!
I find my own way
I seek
My way!
Who is it?
Are you a mortal?
Hey, friend next door!
Get up! There's ghosts!
Get up! Do you hear me?
Hurry and get up!
Not a sound.
Maybe he left already.
What a nuisance!
Friend, there are fierce ghosts here!
Ghosts?
I'll use my magic to banish them!
Ghosts and goblins,
I order you to leave!
Oh, you understand the occult!
My nose is sensitive to
other worldly spirits...
So why do I smell nothing now?
Get out of the way!
Abracadabra!
Strange!
Not even a hint of ghostly odour!
Abracadabra!
Hocus-pocus flash!
- Don't come here!
- Leave!
You're not even real ghosts!
Wasting my occult talents.
Phonies?
Want to trick me?
A good thing you have a waistband.
Stay away from me!
I'm falling...
Stop hugging me!
Let go!
If I let go, I'll fall!
If you don't let go, I'll...
Sian?!
Sian!
Hocus-pocus heebie-jeebie!
I order you to freeze!
Freeze!
Sian, is that you?
What kind of black magic is that?
Let them go!
Otherwise I'll kill him.
Oh... Freeze!
Kill him!
He's no friend of mine!
Elder Chu!
Are you Elder Chu, travelling incognito?
Elder who?
Your disciple is deeply sorry.
Disciple?!
Elder Chu?!
Sian, it's me!
Don't you recognize me?
We come from a good family.
My name is Windy.
This is my younger sister, Moon.
Elder Chu.
Elder, you can save us.
My father is Lord Fu,
the ex-Minister of Rites.
He was framed.
They're now transporting him to be executed.
We want to attack the transport wagon
and rescue him.
You are the learned and brilliant Chu.
You two are loyal imperial warriors.
Everyone is an eminent personnage.
Now it's my turn to introduce myself,
I am... Spell!
My name is Autumn,
from the Kunlun sect.
I've read everything that
the Elder has written.
I only use my magic to battle demons.
I never get involved in affairs of state.
We pay our respects to Elder Chu.
My name is Ning, not Chu.
I can tell you are clever.
Clever people do not always
reveal their identities.
Anyway, in our hearts
we know who you really are.
How can I make you believe me?
No need for you to say anything.
Everybody remember
From now on,
Elder Chu will be known as Ning.
Chu is Ning.
Yes!
We will now take an oath.
Whoever reveal their identities
will be chopped up into 10,000 pieces.
Yes!
Such an honour that you rode my horse!
Sian,
do you remember this painting and poem?
Sian?
Poem?
He's reciting poetry.
Quickly, pen and paper.
We must record what he says.
Elder is giving us a hint.
Hurry!
Frost fills the sky over 10 Mile Lake;
Silken threads anxious of youth.
Looking at the moon and feeling lonely;
Envious of lovers, not of immortality.
Very profound!
What does "10 mile" mean?
10 mile!
It is all very deep.
His words are too profound!
10 Mile?
That must mean 10 Mile Pavilion.
There's a 10 Mile Pavilion near hear.
That's right!
Sister, "10 miles" refers to 10 Mile Pavilion.
It's nearby.
I understand.
10 Mile Pavilion is not far from here.
"Frost" refers to Frost's Descent.
Each year has 24 climatic periods...
After the autumnal equinox comes the frost...
and today is the day of Frost's Descent.
Elder is telling us that father will be
transported past 10 Mile Pavilion.
He's telling us to rescue him there.
Elder is truly perceptive.
We can save father.
We had it right!
Good.
It hurts!
What's the matter?
Get up!
Reporting!
Miss Windy! Your father will pass
the 10 Mile Pavilion tonight.
We already know that.
Elder is truly brilliant!
But what about the rest of the poem?
What do those 2 stanzas mean
3 stanzas.
The meaning doesn't matter now.
Interpret it in any way you desire.
He means that we should have our own views...
not just listen
to what other people say, right?
So, should we still listen to
what Elder says?
Not only listen,
but take notes and ponder his meaning
We must pass his wisdom
on to future generations.
Right!
Time to leave!
Good-bye.
We're off to 10 Mile Pavilion.
Yes. We're off to 10 Mile Pavilion.
Miss Windy,
please return Sian's painting to me.
Yes, Elder.
When you call me Sian,
is that a hint that I need a pseudonym?
From now on, my name is Sian
If Sian were reincarnated,
she would now be a babe in arms.
She's not Sian!
What are you spying on?
Me?
Nothing.
What are you spying on?
I wanted to see what you were spying on.
Time to go!
Do you think your fiance, Prince Ma...
is as handsome as Elder?
We were betrothed before birth.
How do I know what he looks like?
Is that what people mean by fate?
Who are you referring to?
Oh, nobody.
It's just that I feel so fortunate.
Fortunate?
You're frothing at the mouth!
Evil spirits!
Is this a foot print or a hand print?
We'll know when we find the monster.
Right!
It even harmed a man.
What a pity to leave it here.
Better show it to Elder.
OK!
There really are ghosts in this place!
What is that?
A corpse!
It's all that ghost's fault.
Don't hug it.
Put it down.
How did this person die so pitifully?
I'd say this an evil ghost.
The odour is very strong.
It's back!
Is it looking for us?
Use your "freeze" magic.
Right!
I command you to freeze!
Heebie-jeebie! Freeze!
That'll stop him!
How do you do it?
When you see a ghost, shout "freeze".
Like this? Freeze!
Is that right?
Oh, no!
How do you lift the spell?
I have to think of a way
to communicate with him.
What can I do?
Let's try this...
If I'm right,
move your eyes up and down.
That's right! Fantastic!
If I'm wrong,
move them from left to right.
Great!
Will a hand gesture lift the spell?
What?
Not up and down or left to right.
Don't joke with me.
If we wait too long,
that monster will get us.
Does lifting the spell
have to do with an acupuncture point?
Your eyes are moving faster
than a revolving lantern!
I understand!
You're provoking me into hitting you.
OK.
I'm going to hit you now
Ready or not, here it comes!
Let's get out of here!
Come on!
You're too heavy.
I can't carry you.
Drag it!
Dragging you isn't fast enough either.
Better hide upstairs.
I told you
not to fool around at a time like this.
That monster is so tall,
it'll see us if he stand up straight.
How can I undo the spell?
It's safer inside.
Better hide yourself quick.
I told you to hide inside.
Why did you go down there,
where it's so dangerous?
Try the "freeze" curse!
Freeze!
Let's continue without guessing game.
You're getting heavier and heavier.
Can't carry you much longer.
Since that monster isn't here...
let's try to lift the spell.
Does it have anything to do with this amulet?
Yes?!
What then?
Point at me.
Point at me and the curse will be lifted.
Point!
How do I undo the spell?
Freeze!
Don't move!
Move! Move!
Why does he "unfreeze" so quickly,
but you haven't moved for so long?
Do you mean...
I pointed to this amulet...
Then I asked you how to lift the spell...
And he moved!
Freeze!
I'll take care of it.
Get out of here fast!
Finally lifted the spell!
Get out of here!
Abracadabra!
Open up a way out!
Out of the way!
I'll take care of it!
Abracadabra!
Hocus pocus!
I order all ghosts to be expelled!
Wow!
It doesn't fear my incantations!
It's still moving!
I order all ghosts to be expelled!
Even when it's chopped up
he can still run away!
It could still come back at any time.
Elder, get out of here.
I'll pursue it!
Be careful!
Earth, open up!
Dawn is breaking
Heebie-jeebie!
Freeze!
Earth, open up!
Want to leave!
Wow!
My magical powers are no good at all
Earth, open up!
A magician?!
Take this!
Hey!
Stop! Stop!
Are you stupid?
I told you to stop!
We don't even know each other.
Why are we fighting?
I learned magic to deal with evil spirits.
If you don't stop,
I'll use my magic to "freeze" you.
Why are you blocking my way?
I was just taking a rest
after battling some ghosts,
and you say I'm blocking your way.
When that monster makes a run for it tonight,
you'll be in deep trouble.
Brother!
Call me Master.
Master, your skill is extraordinary.
If you worked for the imperial court,
your future would be boundless.
You know that I'm a Taoist monk.
Seeking wealth and position
is for the likes of you mere mortals.
I don't want to end up like you...
Earth, open up!
What a pity.
Hu, our horses' hoofs are rigid.
They won't move!
It must be that monk's magic at work!
He said there are evil spirits.
Be careful!
Yes!
Lord Fu!
There's nothing I can do
about squabbles in the imperial court.
It's hard to tell right from wrong.
I'm just following orders.
But don't worry.
I'll make sure your journey is safe.
After we get to the capital,
whatever the emperor does to you
is not my responsibility
Let's go!
Where can I get something to eat?
Please give me a bowl of your cheapest food.
What?
The cheapest?
Sit down!
If you're starving don't waste your money.
Show me your face.
Go!
Stand up.
Don't lower your head.
Go!
Don't run away!
Don't move!
Monks?
Stand still!
Out of the way!
Get out of the way!
What kind of magic is this?
It's Windy...
Come back!
Hey!
The soldiers never come to
10 Mile Pavilion last night.
Rush back to Righteous Villa
and lie in ambush for them.
Hey!
Back to Righteous Villa?
It's haunted!
Come back!
Elder! Elder!
I wonder if Elder has already gone?
Better search for him.
Yes!
Do you think father's transport
has already passed by here?
No. They're not supposed
to reach here until after dark.
Miss Windy, the villa has been ransacked.
I'm sure Elder did it
to remove any traces of our presence.
Set everything up.
Prepare to attack.
Yes!
Hurry up! Over there!
Who is it?
- I'm Ning.
- Ning?
Oh, it's Elder!
This villa is haunted.
Haunted?
Where is Miss Windy?
Inside.
Ghosts?
Real ghosts?
Miss Windy!
My clothes!
Elder, they said you came.
Miss Moon!
Who are you?
Oh, it's Elder.
I recognize your back.
Elder...
I...
With your beard shaved off,
you're so, so...
Yes.
When my sister sees you,
she'll be so happy for me.
Happy?!
When you came in,
did you see my sister?
Your sister?
No. No!
Sister! Sister! Sister!
What are you grinning about?
It is improper to look.
There are some things you shouldn't look at.
You're all right!
I didn't recognize Elder
with his beard shaved off.
Really?
I must see for myself.
Elder,
if you have something to say, just say it.
It scares me when you hint at things.
I'm cold.
Your face is so hot,
how can you be cold?
Wouldn't this be faster?
Not fast enough.
Faster would be better.
- Faster?!
- OK.
Elder...
Elder said he was cold.
Cold?
Elder,
you're overly exerting yourself.
Have you seen Miss Windy?
No, I'm looking for her too.
Where did she go?
There's noise coming from upstairs.
Let's go up for a look.
Don't go up there.
Strange!
Nobody up here.
Maybe it's next door.
Let's go over and look.
What are you doing?
Sister,
Elder came back to find me... us.
Why are your clothes so dishevelled?
Don't be so impolite in the future.
Miss Windy, this villa is haunted.
Do we still have to pretend to be ghosts?
No matter what,
we must wait here for father.
We mustn't leave.
In this moment of danger,
we must thrust out
our chests and be fearless.
We must be utterly devoted to our cause.
Elder, let's go in.
Elder!
Your clothes are torn in the back.