Room 1954
- Certainly, sir
- Thank you
Who Am I, Christine,
South African Tribune. Remember me?
Here, take one of my cards
I finally found you!
It's amazing
how hard it is to track you down
My editor's been asking...
Excuse me. Could you do me a favor?
My taxi's waiting outside.
Can you pay for it?
Then the interview. Okay?
OK, no problem. But remember the deal
The interview as soon as I get back.
I trust you
Check her out
Thank you
Police, step aside, please
Police? I didn't even see your I.D.!
He's gone that way!
What did you give him?
My card. I told you I'm a reporter
I'm doing a story on him
Sure. Story. Right
Come in, come in
What's going on?
What?
Go! Go! Go!
Stop!
Start the car!
How?
I'll shift the gears!
What?
What's going on?
Come in!
Wait! Are you crazy?
Slow down, come on! I'm not in yet!
Come on, move it, get on!
Third, fourth gear
Which gear you run?
I don't know
Look out!
Watch out!
Be careful!
You stop messing the gear!
Find a better road!
Let me
Go! Go! Go!
Oh, no! We can't move!
Do you know how to drive?
What do you expect? I only have one arm
Move, I drive
We're stuck!
Don't worry, I can figure out
Do something. They're right behind!
Back to the car
Car 54, in pursuit
Hey! Watch out!
I'm driving
The police! We're saved!
Good!
No! Even the police are after me!
Why? What have you done?
Just keep going!
You're great!
Piece of cake
They're back there!
It's a dead end!
Not again!
What was that?
Nothing, just sit tight!
Next time warn us about seat belts!
Sorry!
Sorry? Christine, are you okay?
I'm all right, but they're
right behind us! Get us out of here!
Push me up
Let me show you what I'v got
They're behind us!
Come on, let's go, that way!
We're gonna go over! Lean to the right!
We gotta help them!
OK
Come out! Hurry up!
Thank you
Don't thank him! Grab him!
Sorry
You've gotta trust me
Will this work?
Yes. Good!
So why are those guys after you?
Everybody's after me
C.I.A., Secret Police, even you
You must be hiding something
Hiding what?
You must have stolen
something from them.
Where is it?
Where is what?
I don't know! Try to remember
How did you do that so quick?
All I remember is I've got 6 passports
6 passports? No fingerprints? Amazing!
But this is not you. Who is this?
I got it from the dead body
Dead body? What a great story! Christine
It's not a story!
Eleven done one too many.
What does this mean?
- It's a puzzle.
- Eleven done one too many
You remember something, don't you?
Tell me!
I used to be good at that
Someone bring my memory back
What are you doing?
I'm trying to help him!
Don't you remember?
The doctor said it would help
I told you! Never do that again!
OK
Who am I?
We ran into a slight snag. We lost him
I suggest you find him. Quickly!
He's lost his memory.
What harm can he do us?
You ever heard of short term amnesia,
you idiot?
What do you want me to do?
What you were supposed to do
in the first place. Kill him!
Right
Africa's a bit bigger than Washington
Are you sure you want a piece?
Very juicy
Guys! I've broken the code!
It's a phone number.
A company in Rotterdam!
Rotterdam?
Yeah!
How do you know?
Eleven done one too many
The letters stand for
numbers on a phone key pad
The first number
is the international code, zero eleven
then the country and city codes.
Don't you see?
Done is d-one, right?
So look, d is three and one is one
31, the Netherlands!
Okay
The company's name is Heinex Holdings
But all I got
was their answering machine
Sounds great! But I still don't get it
Where did you learn
to break codes like that?
Spy novels. I'm addicted to them
They could know my past.
I have to go there
You mean we have to go there?
You promised me a story, remember?
Besides,
the newspaper will pay our expenses
Okay. But you go at your own risk
It sounds so exciting.
I wish I could come with you
Hey, let's take a picture
for my African scrapbook
No!
What's wrong?
Something wrong?
I tried to scare him, just like you did
That was a good one!
I got you
Did it work?
Anyway, this one's out of film.
Let's try the other one
Forget it. Yuki, thank you very much.
We'll keep in touch
Say goodbye to your brother
Let's go
Where are you headed?
Airport
You're going to walk?
I'll drive!
Good idea
What's wrong with my driving?
"Rotterdam, Holland"
This is the place
The encoded phone number belongs to
that building over there
Did you talk to anybody?
- Yes
- Who?
The operator
Then what?
I just hung up
You hung up?
Who am I supposed to talk to? There must
be over a hundred companies in there
The number is right
The matches from the dead body
are also from this restaurant
He must have been here
That's obvious. So what do we do now?
Shall we just walk in and take a look?
I don't think so.
The place is heavily guarded
Even the police would have a hard time
getting in there
Where are you going?
I've got to make a phone call
Here. Use mine
No. I'll use the pay phone.
Reception's better
Mr. Morgan
Hello? Who's that?
It's Who Am I. Remember me?
Yes, of course. How could I forget?
I found out something very important
Yeah? What's that?
Are you there?
A building. Maybe their headquarters
Whose headquarters?
The people trying to kill me
I'm at the coffee shop across the street
And whereabouts in South Africa
is this building?
No. I'm in Rotterdam!
He's across the road
What?
Hello? Are you there?
Yeah. I'm here
OK, don't do anything
Give me 30 minutes to arrange
back up for you, then call me
I need more information
OK
And remember, don't trust anyone.
Got it?
Hey, are you listening?
Yes
What's going on?
Our native friend's in the coffee shop
across the street
Take your men and finish him off
Who?
Our African friend
What do you mean? The coffee sho...
And don't blow it this time
OK! Go!
Peter, wait!
Don't kill him! Bring him back here
Yes, sir
I need to find out what he knows
Yeah, I'm here. Okay, don't do anything
Give me 30 minutes to arrange
back up for you, then call me
I need more information
And remember. Don't trust anyone
Listen to me!
Why are you tapping my phone calls?
I'm a reporter, remember?
What kind of reporter uses this?
The best!
I'll do anything to get the story!
Anything?
Yes. Anything
Quick!
Look, I'm sorry. I shouldn't have
done that. I crossed the line
But I'm not the one
you should be worrying about
Maybe your friend on the phone
is lying to you
No. He's C.I.A.
Every organization
has people on the take
Look, I didn't mean to offend you
Here. You can have the tape
Let me explain!
This is a gun! You're not a reporter!
Now I know
how you broke the code so easily
And opened the handcuffs!
Who are you? What do you want?
Listen to me!
Who are you?
All right
I haven't been totally honest with you,
but it was for your own protection
I'm with the C.I.A.
Now you're C.I.A.
Yes, but I'm on your side!
Nobody's on my side!
You call anybody in the bathroom?
Who were you calling?
What are you talking about?
You set me up!
You, round the back!
I've got him! Come here to help!
Think you can get away?
Excuse me
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
What's going on here?
Mind your own business!
Hey, you can't do that!
Feels good?
Get him!
Stop! Don't move!
Don't shoot!
Here, Sweetie
Donation, Save The Children Fund
Mr. Morgan?
Who Am I?
You're right. Someone's after me
My men couldn't find you
at the coffee shop
What happened?
I had to leave. Where are you?
I'm on my way to Rotterdam
You stay put. Where are you?
How long till you get here?
3 to 4 hours.
I'll commandeer a military jet
Where are you?
I'll call you then
So why don't we just kill him?
Because we still don't know
what he's found out
The buyer's coming this afternoon
When the transaction's complete,
we'll have nothing to fear from him
You take care of
the three Einsteins upstairs
When the deal's history, so are they
I want that lab pristine
And no evidence left in the building
It's being dealt with
Hey, Mr. Armano
Hey, nice joint you got here
I'm getting to like Rotterdam
I see the General's got security
nice and tight
Yeah. And he's been expecting you
Oh, sorry!
Over here. This entry point. And here
I want 24 hours surveillance.
Effective immediately
Yes, madam
What are you doing?
So that happened to the power station
That rock is really something
Now that's what
I call quality advertising
Can you imagine the amount of energy
produced by these fragments?
My client prefers reality to imagination
That's why we're not giving you
all the money up front
But I would say that half a billion
dollars is more than enough motivation
for you to deliver a quality product
Mr. Nelson is not giving charity
Believe me, he's getting a bargain
He's only paid one third of the cost
of the research project in South Africa
and he's getting a complete product
They're bringing the scientists
and the merchandise right up
Bring in another pot of hot coffee
So you take 20% on the deal, Armano?
Frank, I'm just a poor boy
trying to make a living
This disc contains the only
remaining information about the formula
The rest of the research files
have been completely deleted
And keep in mind that
we still do not have all the knowledge
to control the energy
expansion completely
Yes, sir. That's a problem
We need more time to solve this problem
Once we solve it
the energy could be used for
a positive purpose
He's right
That's very considerate, gentlemen
but we had something
a little bit different in mind
Can you imagine, an ordinary machine gun
with the destructive force
of a ballistic missile?
You promise us that you should not
use the formula for destruction
We've already spoken about
your daughter, Manfred!
Wait a minute!
And now, you sell it to arms dealers.
Yes. That's it!
Take these gentlemen away
Seems they've overexerted themselves
This Mr. Nelson of yours
is not only a very astute man
but he's also going to be very rich
because everybody's going top
want this weaponry
Can you believe this little piece
of plastic costs billions of dollars?
Champagne is ready outside, sir
Why don't you take our friend here
with you and show him our hospitality
Yes, sir
It's so hard to find a good help
you can trust these days
Yes
Six, seven, eight zeros
Don't make a mistake. One zero makes
a hell of a lot of difference
I don't play around
when it comes to money
You know when I press this enter,
all that money's going to be yours
Let me
"Your request is being processed.
Please wait."
Look at this.
They call this swift banking
and I still got to wait
Come on!
Calm down!
You waited this long,
what's a few minutes?
I need a drink
I'm the one
who should be worried about this
General
I still think there's too many people
that know about this
What do you think?
Relax!
The commandos involved in the mission
all met with a tragic accident
Oh yeah? Well according to my sources,
there was one survivor
He doesn't even know who he is
And by tomorrow, he won't exist
And our three learned gentlemen
will be disposed of along with their lab
Well, why wait? We got the disc.
Why not do it right now?
Yung, take care of the three gentlemen
Yes, sir
Your statement worries me a little
What? Am I going to be the next to go?
That's right. You did send me the five
hundred million dollars, didn't you?
I'm joking. I was kidding.
We're friends, Armano
Now look! Friendship!
Friendship!
"Save The Children Fund"
Coffee?
Yes, coffee
Coffee, coffee
How's it going?
We have a dress code. Tidy up
Congratulations, General
All in good time
"Transaction aborted."
What's the matter? Not enough zeros?
That's funny. It's not on my screen
What are you talking about?
I just fonNarded it from our account
Here, take a look
The name of my account
is Heinex Holdings
So what?
It's not in Heinex Holdings
It's in Save The Children Fund!
"Donation received. Thank you very much."
No!
Somebody's been messing
with my computer!
Someone sneaked in!
Knocked out one of our guys!
It's him! Seal off the building!
Floor to floor search!
Find him! Kill him!
He's in the building!
Who's in the building?
What? He's in the building?
That's it! This is a set up
You guys are trying to set me up,
aren't you?
Yes, sir
That's the man! Right there!
That's the man!
When you were pouring the coffee
you were messing with my computer,
weren't you?
No! It was your own man!
My man?
Shut up! Where is he?
Just outside!
Go down. Search the kitchen!
Dont worry
Don't worry
I'll find him
The scientists! We can't kill them now!
Stop them!
Save the children. I hate children
I want this building secure from top to
bottom. Seal off all the escape routes
And check the ventilation system
Groups of three
Stay alert. He's a special operative
A million dollars to the team
that kills him
Now get going
Yes, sir
I'm depending on you two
Right. Before this goes any further,
I want my disc back
Are you still trying to
pull something on me?
You think I'm some little punk,
you can just push around?
What's the matter?
Are you getting senile before your time?
Don't you remember? I gave you the disc.
Like this
You gave me the disc?
Well, I gave you the disc back.
Just like this
You have it on you. Don't you?
Get your greasy hands off me!
That's the guy
who was pouring me coffee!
It's him!
Him who?
Get out of my way!
Get the men here!
You missed! What an idiot!
And you shortstuff. You got my disc!
Is this what you want?
You got a fraction of a second to give
that disc back to it's rightful owner
or I'm going to break your little...
Don't talk! Kill him!
You shut up! I got it under control
What's the matter with your mind?
Because of this?
You stole and kidnapped,
and killed nine good men! All for this?
Why do you want to destroy life?
When you can make it better?
What do you want?
Nothing
I want my life back!
He's over here!
Get the disc and kill him!
The children thank you
General, are you okay?
Call an ambulance!
Get that disc!
Come on. Yes, sir
He's down there!
Don't move!
Who Am I?
Morgan! It's you!
Of course, it's me!
I've been trying to find you!
You've come to kill me!
You're one of them!
What are you talking about?
I've come to get you out
You're lying. What are you doing here?
I'm working undercover
It's taken me two years to get into
Sharman's organization
I'm this close to nailing him!
Yeah. I guess you saw me
in the conference room
Once the money goes through, he's mine
I sent the money to the children's fund
You what?
You know what you've done?
You've blown a two year investigation!
The disc!
You must have had access to the disc
Have you got it?
Yes
Good. It's crucial evidence.
You keep it
Now, let's get you out of here
Wait a minute.
Your men found me at the coffee shop
I never told you where I was
Of course they found you.
Remember the calling card I gave you?
It's got a microchip in it
It gives your location
every time you use it
They tried to kill me!
They weren't my men
By the time my men got there,
you were gone
Sharman must be tapping my phone!
Look, if I'd wanted to kill you
I could have done that in South Africa
Sharman must have sent the hit men
after you in Johannesburg
But don't worry, we'll take care of them
Look, I know you're confused
You don't know who to trust
Like I said before, don't trust anyone
You've got the disc. You keep it
Now, let's get you out of here
I might not get out. You keep it
Let's go
You'll never know who you are
I might have an amnesia.
But I'm not stupid!
Don't trust anyone! Remember?
Get your hands off me! Go get him!
The disc!
He's got the disc!
You've got two choices
Give us the disc, and jump off
Or no. 2, we take the disc
and throw you off
I like the third choice
I keep the disc
and I throw you both off!
Good!
How long?
30 seconds
29 seconds. Not bad!
Go and again
Behind you!
Take it easy, we've got plenty of time
20 seconds
Come on
Time's up!
Shut up!
Good!
Game's over!
Let's finish him!
What are you fighting for?
Where is the disc?
It fell at the carpark!
Finish up, quickly!
The black bag in the carpark,
pick it up
You want more fight?
Don't hit me!
He's up there!
Which side he's going off?
I don't know
You bunch of burns!
I can't believe
you're still in one piece!
You've got no choice, come on
They gotta be kidding!
We won't catch him in this!
It's under control
Execute Plan B
That's Plan B?
No! Plan A!
What's plan B?
You'll see!
Go!
Think you can trust me now?
Sorry. You're just so young to be C.I.A.
Young?
We've got people who are eighteen!
What is this? I'm one of you!
NS1 Special Ops!
We know who you are
Then you know I'm undercover!
Yes. I know
You're a disgrace to the C.I.A.
Get him out of my sight!
All units! Search for the disc
Nice kick!
Thank you.
We couldn't have done this without you
Anybody would do it
One thing I never forget
my father told me
Always do the right thing
and stop the people who don't
I wish everyone taught
their children that
And don't worry,
Thank you
One last thing. Have you got the disc?
He also told me, respect nature
I dropped it somewhere
I know
Where are you going?
Africa