I am Korean.
I was born in Seoul
but many people
mistake me for Chinese.
I am definitely Korean
and my home town is Seoul.
Looking back now,
it seems a long time ago.
I think it was about
when I was 8 years old.
At that time I was small for my age.
My father sent me to Taekwondo
lessons with my older brother.
I remember I had very tough training
at those Taekwondo classes.
Because I was small,
my father was worried that I would be
bullied by other kids.
Ever since I have participated
in martial arts.
When I was about 18 years old,
Bruce Lee became
very popular worldwide.
After I saw one of his movies,
I fell in love with his style.
Because of Bruce Lee,
I entered the action movie industry.
From that moment,
I exercised hard.
And I was ambitious
to be an action star like Bruce Lee,
I managed to get myself
into the movie industry.
I started out in martial arts...
by taking up Taekwondo.
Then gymnastics, to pursue
my career in the film industry.
After that I took up Hapkido,
Kung Fu
and all sorts of other martial arts.
Even now, Bruce Lee remains
my biggest hero and inspiration.
After I watched Bruce Lee's movie,
I decided to be an action star like him.
Back then, the audience cheered
Bruce Lee really loudly in the cinema.
I was very impressed.
I wanted to be a martial arts movie star,
so I got into the movie industry.
Now, I am working in
the Korean movie industry.
In Korea, there are not as many
martial arts action movies
as there are in Hong Kong.
I don't think there is a lot of space for
Korean martial arts actors in Korea.
So I had a lot of difficulties building
my career in this field in Korea.
I think things are a bit different
these days.
Things are looking up for
the Korean action movie industry.
Right now, I am also working as
a fight coordinator.
I seldom get the chance to work
as an actor in Korea.
My friends and directors
in Hong Kong
sometimes call me
to offer me roles.
Acting and fight coordinating
are both very appealing to me.
As long as my ability continues,
I won't give up these two roles,
and I'd like to do them
for the rest of my life.
For some time, there has been
a trend of changing Hong Kong movies
from martial arts to
Chow Yun-Fat's gun-fighting movies.
The trend continued
for about five years,
and hardly any martial arts
movies were made.
So Golden Harvest Productions
wanted to bring back
traditional martial arts action movies,
and I had heard that they were
looking for someone
who specialises in side-kicks
and who comes from Korea.
As soon as I heard that,
I made a demo tape and sent it
to Golden Harvest Productions.
David Lai and his team from
Golden Harvest Productions
watched my demo tape
and happily gave the role to me.
David Lai and the writer flew over
to Korea and met me for an interview.
In the original script,
the character was a well-built
and handsome guy,
obviously not like me.
After watching my demo tape,
they changed the script so that
it was tailor-made for me.
I think David and I have
some kind of strong connection
which you can't really explain.
And even he describes
the same thing to me.
When he met me for the first time,
he felt he'd met me before,
as if in a previous life.
That's what he said and
we both believe this.
In "The Scorpion King" my character
is not an entirely bad person.
Of course, my character's father
is a gangster pimp.
When his adversaries
come to rescue the girls,
my character fights against the men
who try to attack his father.
Personally speaking,
I think my character is a guy
who loves his father
and likes to try and protect him.
I think he's a good man.
Of course, my character's father
is a bad man
and my character doesn't like
what his father does.
Character-wise, I like him 100%.
His hairstyle covers one side of
his face and reaches down to here,
and the idea for this appearance
mainly came from David Lai.
The character's appearance,
the movie concept
and my style of martial arts
all fit together very well.
That is...
because the movie's concept
was so good,
it became extremely successful.
The martial arts coordination in
"The Scorpion King"
wasn't done by just one person.
At first, the fight coordinator
was Yuen Biao
and then it changed to Yuen Tak.
And my martial arts action
was modified by monitoring
my demo tapes
scene-by-scene whenever needed
with input from the director
and fight coordinators.
We'd be like: "Let's do it
this way for this scene",
because certain sidekicks were more
suitable for certain scenes, and so on.
My action is entirely my idea
and the fight coordinating was done
by Yuen Tak, Lau Kar-Leung
and David Lai - all of us directed
the fight scenes.
In the movie, all special sidekicks
which I hadn't performed before,
were developed by me in Korea.
The demo tape
which was made in Korea
was actually very useful when
making the film in Hong Kong.
Talking about Lau Kar-Leung,
even before I went to Hong Kong
I watched his movies
and I was curious about him
and wondered who he was.
When I saw him in person
at Golden Harvest Productions
I was...
rather disappointed.
He's about my height,
and looks, in some way, a bit like
someone from the countryside.
But I was very impressed with him
when we were on location
due to his spirit and professionalism.
When he appeared on location,
he would bring a flask of coffee
and he seemed to drink about
20 cups of coffee
until shooting
was finished for the day.
This was to keep himself alert...
so he could show his action style
as much as possible,
and set good examples for younger
actors in the action movie field.
I really respect
his professional attitude.
He is a well-known Kung Fu master
in Hong Kong.
He's about 60 years old
but his muscle tone and
general fitness level
seem to be like that of...
a 20 or 30 year-old man.
Compared with any other man
younger than him,
he has excellent fighting ability.
I like to call him my "master". He's a
role model for many people in this field.
Watch it! Right foot!
Kar Lok, Chin Kar Lok...
or Chung Ka Rak in Korean,
is a very special friend.
Recently, he was directing a movie
and asked me to be a special guest
in his movie
which was being made
in Hong Kong.
Just thinking about Chung Ka Rak
makes me smile.
He's very funny,
and is a very close friend of mine.
Recently, Chung Ka Rak made
a movie called "No Problem 2".
He offered me a role in the movie
so I went to Hong Kong to do it.
"The Scorpion King" was the beginning
of my life in Hong Kong.
In his own way,
he gave me a lot of advice.
He has been a good friend
ever since.
He has excellent ability in this field,
and used to be an action double for
Jackie Chan's action sequences.
He has good skills
and is easy to work with.
He's always smiling,
and I think he's a very happy person
and enjoys his life.
In "The Scorpion King",
there are mostly action scenes.
I feel that the movie reflects
a lot about myself.
Regarding the action sequences,
even when I went back to Korea
after shooting,
there was hardly any editing done,
just a few scenes added.
So I'm very satisfied with the movie.
One of the episodes at the time...
Almost every time I finished
my action scene,
having pulled it off successfully,
the guy who was my character's
father took me out to nice restaurants
almost every day and bought me
delicious meals.
And David Lai...
took me to fancy bars after shooting
one scene after the other.
They showed me around the town
and gave me a good time.
At the beginning in Hong Kong,
the difficult thing was that
because it was my first time,
I didn't have any translation support.
I only had translation support
at the beginning
and after that,
I had to manage on my own.
Their instructions and my intentions
went totally the opposite way
from each other.
My instruction was to do one thing
but what I did was something else,
and this made everybody laugh.
After completing the movie, I feel...
there were a lot of difficulties.
At the time of shooting,
I wanted to run back to Korea,
because it was that difficult.
But after the shooting,
when I watched the movie,
I felt this was a Hong Kong movie,
different from Korean action movies.
This is a Hong Kong movie
which can survive worldwide
due to all the hard work
that went into it.
I can never forget
"The Scorpion King".
Even in the future,
personally I don't think I could do
a movie as good as this.
I think it is only possible
in Hong Kong.
From the very beginning of pursuing
a career in the film industry,
Jackie Chan, Yuen Biao and Sammo
Hung Kam-bo were my favourites.
The first time I met Yuen Biao,
I felt very excited and tense.
In action scenes with him...
I was very impressed
with his excellent skills.
That's why he is a very popular guy.
He's a team player,
he's very strong,
and is also a really good actor.
Starting with "The Scorpion King",
I lived in Hong Kong for five years.
I felt very rewarded
and have few regrets left.
When shooting movies, the most
important thing is one's health.
When I wasn't filming,
I spent most of my time
training alone.
While I was doing that...
because the food in Hong Kong
was so oily,
I felt the food wasn't right for me
and my health suffered a little bit.
At the end of that year,
I finished "Saviour of the Soul"
with Andy Lau.
And then I went back to Korea
to get married.
I got married and settled in Korea
and after that I didn't have a chance
to go back to Hong Kong.
Based on my Hong Kong experience,
I made up my mind
to build my career in Korea.
Right now...
in Seoul...
I'm working in the Korean
movie business.
In the future,
if there are any good offers as a fight
coordinator or martial arts actor,
I would like to show
something different
that hasn't been shown before
by a fight coordinator,
combining Hong Kong
and Korean action movie styles.
Furthermore...
I'd like to encourage
many junior actors.
I'd also like to get into
the Hollywood market with them.
I also have the desire to be famous
as a Korean action star.
Please wish me well with it.
Thank you for watching me.