Frost fills the sky over Ten Mile Lake
Silken threads anxious of youth
Looking at the moon and feeling lonely
Envious of love, not of immortality
This pointing
will remind you of me
Hsiao-tsing's grave?!
Hsiao-tsing died long ago
She's ghost?!
Yes! I'm a ghost but I bring
mortals no harm
I died far away from my home
An evil spirit took by corpse
and won't let me rest in peace
If you want to save me
move my bones away from here
Then it will be possible
for me to be reincarnated
Hsiao-tsing!
I will save you
Ning!
You dare oppose me?! I will
never excuse you from death!
Let them go, please
The Diamond Sutra!
We've escaped!
Hsiao-tsing, we're safe!
Dawn is breaking
Hsiao-tsing, hide in the tower of ashes
If the sun's rays shine on you
you'll never be reincarnated
Ning, good-bye forever!
I hope that Hsiao-tsing will be reincarnated
I must return to the
Orchid Temple
If you need me, you can find me there
Take care!
Who is that young man!
He's the poor scholar
who lived two blocks away
Things have changed since he was last here
Wasn't he that shop's bill collector?
He doesn't even know it
went out of business long ago!
Welcome! Welcome!
The bill collector's here
How much money did you collect?
We're here to catch escaped convicts
It's the police! Run!
Pursue them!
You're Bing Chow?!
You made a mistake
He has a beard and I don't!
You shaved it off!
Take him back and collect the reward
Get in!
I haven't committed any crime!
Let me go
I've been wrongly accused!
You made a mistake
I'm not Bing Chow!
I am wrongly accused!
My name is Ning, not Bing Chow
Old man may I ask who...
A man, just like you, fated to
being imprisoned
So pessimistic!
It's all me elders' fault, insisting
I get an education
When I grew up, I was learned
and wrote backs
But when I write of my travels
I'm accused of
revealing state secrets
When I write of history, they say
I'm satirizing the present
If I analyze military strategy, they
say I'm planning a rebellion
I can't even write fairy tales
Finally, I wrote the
biography of a powerful man
Then he was arrested, accused
of being a rebel
We were both sentenced
to life imprisonment
Wouldn't you say
that prison is my fate?
A cockroach!
Where?
Cockroach?!
You're really wasteful! The cockroaches
here are of the best quality
There are no delicacies here
After you're been here a while
you'll even salivate ever a housefly
Old man, how long have your been here?
I was your age when I first arrived
Look how I've changed!
Full of character!
You've been here a long time!
Help! I am innocent!
I'm not Bing Chow!
I am innocent!
You've made a mistake
I'm not Bing Chow!
Another nightmare
What did you dream this time?
I dreamt you were
haggard and exhausted
Exhausted?!
True, you will soon be totally exhausted
You have nightmares every night
Look at the calendar
You've been here so long
and still can't adjust
Soon you'll even forget that
your last name is Chow
Old man, my last name isn't Chow!
Bing Chow!
Supper!
OK
A chicken leg?!
Happy days are here again!
Old man! There's only one bowl
You eat first
No, it's for you
I'd rather eat cockroaches
I'll tell you something
when you've finished
I haven't had chicken
in a long time
Old man, why are you
carving my name?
All these men
ate chicken legs
We call that chicken
a headless chicken
After you've eaten it, they
chop off your head!
Chop off your head?!
Bing Chow, we have
no personal quarrel
Don't come back from the grave
and seek revenge on me!
They behead people at noon
It's now the middle of the night
Some official's son got in trouble
and they're looking for a substitute
At night
the executioner can't tell one from another
Is there no justice in the world?
Is there no reward for being a good man?
It is of no concern to me
I was always an honest man
I'll give you whatever I can
This painting was a gift
from my dearest one
I don't want to part
with it even in death
Young man, you have a good heart
Let me give you a present
You are so learned
It is fortunate that
I die rather than you
You're a good man
Such a pity you have to die
It would be a pity if you died, not me
Anybody's death is a pity
You're a rare specimen
If you die, your type will be extinct
It's been a long time
since I set somebody free
This tunnel leads to the outside
Go out and start anew
Don't give me such false hopes
If this is an escape route, why
didn't you escape long ago?
It's less troublesome for me
to write my book here
When I finish, then I'll escape
and get it printed
Don't worry about me
Always keep this bundle with you
Once you're out of here
never come back!
Get going!
What will happen to you
after I've gone?
They like hearing my stories
So long as I don't get
to the story's end
They'll never harm me
But they'll accuse you
of helping me escape
I'll say you were put to death
for somebody else two days ago
They won't dare make a fuse
Go!
Take care!
Bing Chow! The time has come!
Hurry up!
Bing Chow!
He's dead
I've escaped!
There's even a horse
here waiting for me!
That old man
is really remarkable!
I must reply his kindness someday
Hey! That's my horse!
What a stupid horse! Letting
a stranger ride him!
I don't even have time
to wash my hands!
You think you're fast over land
I'll go underground!
Open sesame!
I must find a place to
get out of this downpour!
Good! A House!
Open the door!
"Righteous Villa"
Anybody home?
1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8
Eight Coffins!
Must be the whole family
I won't disturb you
I just want to stay the night
Don't bother to get up
I'll take care of myself
I told you not to go to
any trouble. Please go back!
The way you rush about
in no fixed direction!
I had a hard time
following you underground
Don't you have any idea
where you're going?
Your face looks so horrible, you must
have suffered a painful death
If you'd rushed around
underground all day like me
you wouldn't have the energy
to come back to the surface
I don't know you
Why are you following me?
I don't know you either
so why did you take my horse?
That's your horse?
I thought it was the old man's
Still you should have asked
before taking it
You're alive! Sorry!
It's all a misunderstanding
If there's anything I can do
to help, just let me know
Enough of your tricks! A good thing
my reactions are so fast
Friend, you need a place
to stay the night
Here there's a roof over your head
Might as well stay here
How do I know
what you'd do after I fell asleep?
I knew it!
Let's draw up some boundaries
I'm staying next door
If you have something to say, shout it!
Don't come over
I haven't bathed in a long time
Who is it?
Are you a mortal?
Hey, friend next door!
Get up! There's ghosts!
Get up! Do you hear me?
Hurry and get up!
Not a sound
Maybe he left already
What a nuisance!
Friend, there are fierce ghosts here!
Ghosts?
I'll use my magic to banish them!
Ghosts and goblins
I order you to leave!
Oh, you understand the occult!
My nose is sensitive
to other worldly spirits...
So why do I smell nothing now?
Get out of the way!
Abracadabra!
Strange!
Not even a hint of ghostly odor!
Abracadabra! Hocus-pocus flash!
They're coming
Leave!
You're not even real ghosts!
Wasting my occult talents!
Phonies?
Want to trick me?
A good thing you have a waistband
Stay away from me!
I'm falling...
Stop hugging me!
Let go!
If I let go, I'll fall!
If you don't let go, I'll...
Hsiao-tsing?!
Hocus-pocus heebie-jeebie!
I order you to freeze!
Freeze!
Hsiao-tsing, is that you?
What kind of black magic is that?
Let them go!
Otherwise I'll kill him
Oh... Freeze!
Kill him! He's no friend of mine!
Elder Chu Kot!
Chu Kot?! Are you Elder Chu Kot
traveling incognito?
Elder who?
Your disciple is deeply sorry
Disciple?!
Elder Chu Kot?!
Hsiao-tsing, it's me!
Don't you recognize me?
We come from a good family
My name is Windy
This is my younger sister, Moon
Elder Chu Kot
Elder, you can save us
My father is Lord Fu
the ex-Minister of Rites
He was framed. They're now
transporting him to be executed
We want to attack the transport
wagon and rescue him
You are the learned
and brilliant Chu Kot
You two are loyal imperial warriors
Everyone is an eminent personage
Now it's my turn to introduce myself
I am...
Spell!
My name is Autumn
from the Kunlun sect
I've read everything that
the Elder has written
I only use my magic
to battle demons
I never get involved
in affairs of state
We pay our respects to Elder Chu Kot
My name is Ning, not Chu Kot
I can tell you are clever
Clever people do not always
reveal their identities
Anyway, in our hearts
we know who you really are
How can I make you believe me?
No need for you to say anything
Everybody remember...
From now on
Elder Chu Kot will be known as Ning
Chu Kot is Ning
Yes!
We will now take an oath
Whoever reveal their identities
will be chopped up
into 10,000 pieces
Yes!
Such an honour that
you rode my horse!
Hsiao-tsing, do you remember
this painting and poem?
Hsiao-tsing? Poem?
He's reciting poetry
Quickly, pen and paper
We must record what he says
Elder is giving us a hint
Hurry!
Frost fills the sky
over Ten Mile Lake;
Silken threads anxious of youth
Looking at the moon
and feeling lonely
Envious of lovers,
not of immortality
Very profound!
What does "ten mile" mean?
Ten mile!
It is all very deep
His words are too profound
Ten Mile?
That must mean Ten Mile Pavilion
What do you mean?
There's a Ten Mile Pavilion near hear
That's right! Sister, "ten mile'
refers to Ten Mile Pavilion
It's nearby
I understand
Ten Mile Pavilion is not far from here
"Frost" refers to Frost's Descent
Each year has 24 climatic periods...
After the autumnal equinox
comes the frost...
and today is the day
of Frost's Descent
Elder is telling us that
father will be transported
past Ten Mile Pavilion
He's telling us to rescue him there
Elder is truly perceptive
We can save father
We had it right!
Good
It hurts!
What's the matter? Get up!
Reporting!
Miss Windy!
Your father will pass the
Ten Mile Pavilion tonight
We already know that
Elder is truly brilliant!
But what about the rest of the poem?
What do those two stanzas mean?
Three stanzas
The meaning doesn't matter now
Interpret it in any way you desire
He means that we should
have our own views...
notjust listen to what
other people say, right?
So, should we still
listen to what Elder says?
Not only listen
but take notes and
ponder his meaning
We must pass his wisdom
on to future generations
Right!
Time to leave!
Good-bye
We're off to Ten Mile Pavilion
Yes. We're off to Ten Mile Pavilion
Miss Windy, please return
Hsiao-tsing's painting to me
Yes, Elder
When you call me Hsiao-tsing, is that a
hint that I need a pseudonym?
From now on, my name is Hsiao-tsing
If Hsiao-tsing were reincarnated
she would now be a babe in arms
She's not Hsiao-tsing!
What are you spying on?
Me?...
Nothing
What are you spying on?
I wanted to see what you were spying on
Time to go!
Do you think your fiance, Prince Ma...
is as handsome as Elder?
We were betrothed before birth
How do I know what he looks like?
Is that what people mean by fate?
Who are you referring to?
Oh, nobody
It's just that I fell so fortunate
Fortunate?
You're frothing at the mouth!
Evil spirits!
Is this a foot print or a hand print?
We'll know when we find the monster
Right!
It even harmed a man
What a pity to leave it here
Better show it to Elder
OK!
There really are ghosts in this place!
What is that?
A corpse!
It's all that ghost's fault
Don't hug it. Put it down
How did this person
die so pitifully?
I'd say this an evil ghost
The odor is very strong
It's back!
Is it looking for us?
Use your "freeze" magic
Right!
I command you to freeze!
Heebie-jeebie! Freeze!
That'll stop him!
How do you do it?
When you see a ghost
shout "freeze"
Like this? Freeze! Is that right?
Hey!
Oh, no!
How do you lift the spell?
I have to think of a way
to communicate with him
What can I do?
Let's try this...
If I'm right
move your eyes up and down
That's right! Fantastic!
If I'm wrong, move them
from left to right
Great!
Will a hand gesture lift the spell?
What?
Not up and down or left to right
Don'tjoke with me
If we wait too long, that
monster will get us
Does lifting the spell
have to do with an
acupuncture point?
Your eyes are moving faster
than a revolving lantern!
I understand!
You're provoking me into hitting you
OK. I'm going to hit you now
Ready or not, here it comes!
Let's get out of here!
Come on!
You're too heavy
I can't carry you
Drag it!
Dragging you isn't fast enough either
Better hide upstairs
I told you not to fool around
at a time like this
That monster is so tall, it'll see
us if he stands up straight
How can I undo the spell?
How do I lift the spell?
It's safer inside
Better hide yourself quick
I told you to hide inside
Why did you go down there, where
it's so dangerous?
Try the "freeze" curse! Freeze!
Let's continue with out guessing game
You're getting heavier and heavier
Can't carry you much longer
Since that monster isn't here...
Let's try to lift the spell
Does it have anything
to do with this amulet?
Yes?! What then?
Point at me. Point at me and
the curse will be lifted
Point!
How do I undo the spell?
No good asking you!
I must figure it out for myself
Freeze!
Don't move!... Move! Move!
Don't move!
Why does he
"unfreeze" so quickly
but you haven't moved for so long?
Do you mean
I pointed to this amulet...
Then I asked you how
to lift the spell...
And he moved! Freeze!
I'll take care of it
Get out of here fast!
Finally lifted the spell!
Get out of here!
Abracadabra! Open up a way out!
Out of the way!
I'll take care of it!
Abracadabra!
Hocus pocus!
I order all ghosts to be expelled!
Wow!
It doesn't fear my incantations!
Take this!
It's still moving!
I order all ghosts to be expelled!
Hocus pocus!
Even when it's chopped up
he can still run away!
It could still
come back at any time
Elder, get out of here
I'll pursue it!
Be careful!
Earth, open up!
Dawn is breaking
Heebie-jeebie! Freeze!
Freeze!
Earth, open up!
Want to leave!
Wow!
My magical powers are
no good at all
Earth, open up!
A magician?!
Take this!
Hey! Stop! Stop!
Are you stupid?
I told you to stop!
We don't even know each other
Why are we fighting?
I learned magic to deal
with evil spirits
If you don't stop, I'll use my
magic to "freeze" you
Why are you blocking my way?
I was just taking a rest
after battling some ghosts
and you say I'm blocking your way
When that monster makes a run for it
tonight, you'll be in deep trouble
Brother!
Call me Master
Master, your skill is extraordinary
If you worked for the imperial court
your future would be boundless
You know that I'm a Taoist monk
Seeking wealth and position is
for the likes of you mere mortals
I don't want to end up like you...
Earth, open up!
Well done, young man!
Hu, our hourses' hoofs-are rigid
They won't move!
It must be that monk's magic at work!
He said there are evil spirits
Be careful!
Yes!
Lord Fu!
There's nothing I can do about
squabbles in the imperial court
It's hard to tell right from wrong
I'm just following orders
But don't worry
I'll make sure yourjourney is safe
After we get to the capital
whatever the emperor does to
you is not me responsibility
Let's go!
Where can I get something to eat?
Please give me a bowl
of your cheapest food
What? The cheapest?
Sit down!
If you're starving
don't waste your money
Show me your face
Go!
Stand up
Don't lower your head
Go!
Don't run away!
Don't move!
Monks?
Stand still!
Out of the way!
Get out of the way!
What kind of magic is this?
It's Windy...
Wait!
Come back!
Hey!
The soldiers never come to
Ten Mile Pavilion last night
Rush back to Righteous Villa
and lie in ambush for them
Hey!
Back to Righteous Villa?
It's haunted!
Come back!
Elder! Elder!
I wonder if Elder has already gone?
Better search for him
Yes!
Do you think father's transport
has already passed by here?
No. They're not supposed to
reach here until after dark
Miss Windy, the villa
has been ransacked
I'm sure Elder did it to
remove any traces of our presence
Set everything up
Prepare to attack
Yes!
Hurry up! Over there!
Who is it?
I'm Ning
Ning?
Oh, it's Elder!
This villa is haunted
Haunted?
Where is Miss Windy?
Inside
Ghosts?
Real ghosts?
Miss Windy!
My clothes!
Elder, they said you came
Miss Moon!
Who are you?
Oh, it's Elder
I recognize your back
Elder...
With your beard shaved off
you're so, so...
Yes
When my sister sees you
she'll be so happy for me
Happy?!
When you came in, did you
see my sister?
Your sister? No, No!
Sister! Sister!
Sister!
What are you grinning about?
It is improper to look
Ms. Moon
There are some things
you shouldn't look at
You're all right!
I didn't recognize Elder
with his beard shaved off
Really? I must see for myself
Elder, if you have something to
say, just say it
It scares me when
you hint at things
I'm cold
Your face is so hot
how can you be cold?
Wouldn't this be faster?
Not fast enough
Faster would be better
Faster?!... OK
Elder...
Elder said he was cold
Cold?
Elder, you're overly exerting yourself
Have you seen Miss Windy?
No, I'm looking for her, too
Where did she go?
There's noise coming from upstairs
Let's go up for a look
Don't go up there
Strange! Nobody up here
Maybe it's next door
Let's go over and look
What are you doing?
Sister, Elder came back
to find me... us
Why are your clothes
so disheveled?
Don't be so impolite in the future
Miss Windy, this villa is haunted
Do we still have to
pretend to be ghosts?
No matter what, we must
wait here for father
We mustn't leave
In this moment of danger
we must thrust out our
chests and be fearless
We must be utterly
devoted to our cause
Elder, let's go in
Elder!
Thrust out our chests
Your clothes are torn in the back
How do you write the
"freeze" incantation?
I didn't spy on him
I didn't even know he was outside
Better tie your heart down
Otherwise, it might fly away!
If I could lie it down, I would!
This is how you do it... Freeze!
It works!
This is the "freeze" incantation
If you see that monster
do this and he'll freeze in his tracks
Like this?
Don't do it haphazardly
This spell is hard to reverse
Give me your hand. Yes!