Watch out for the devil!
Yin!
Prajna paramita!
She is here!
I'll take care of her, come on
Watch out!
I saw it
This Tree Devil is very powerful
Now its energy is gone!
Let me freeze it
with the power from my palm
But it will resurrect
in a hundred year's time
Hocus pocus!
Prajna paramita!
Master,
we've finally found Kwan Bo County...
It's just over...
There?
Over there?
Look at your map
Hey... it's flown away
Where's it gone?
We'll get to Kwan Bo County
if we head west
Master
There's rain clouds coming,
let's find shelter
Alright
Let's go...
There's a place to hide
Buddha,
please make the rain go...
so we can get on our way
Master, I'm not thirsty,
you drink it
It's bad luck!
Go!
Gentlemen!
I didn't even recognize the skull
Give me my money back!
He's a master swordsman!
The man with the money
should go on ahead!
Run, run!
It's a tragedy, tragedy!
Master,
there's a killer outside, he's...
...here?
Thank god I got my money back,
I've been saving!
If those thieves took it...
It's a bit cold, isn't it?
Money is illusion,
why kill for it?
Be merciful,
or you will pay for your deeds
Merciful?
You don't have to make a living...
I worked hard for this money!
You want to fight?
Master!
It's only a hoe...
Fong,
dust to dust, ashes to ashes...
Go and bury the bodies
This guy's really shifty.
The gold...
Stop talking and start working
I'm soaked!
Don't mind if I light a fire?
Master, the bodies are in pieces...
So I bury hands with hands,
and legs with legs?
No, be sure to bury whole corpses
I'm not sure that's possible
Alcohol keeps out the cold.
Want some?
Let's all get warmer...
You stupid fool!
Fire! Fire!
Master,
is this how you punish him?
Rubbish,
I'm not an arsonist!
I'm sorry,
we all make mistakes...
I've made you lose your shelter...
The market is just ahead!
We're all wanderers...
We don't bear grudges.
See you later
I've put the bodies back together again...
But there's one finger left
With my expertise,
I don't bother with fingers...
Maybe someone else did it
Are there other chopped up bodies?
This is common fighting ground,
may die...
Enjoy putting them back together
Oh! It's getting dark
Ghost Festival sword and weapons for sale
Help! Murder!
You hit me! Stay there!
This sword is the latest style!
Do you think I'm buying jewelry?
Who hit me?
Show yourself and fight!
Who hit someone?
What's happening?
Make way!
Police passing through, make way!
Police passing, make way!
What's going on here?
I don't know
Forget it then
Hey, stop staring at me!
It's nothing, nothing's wrong!
Come look at our swords, sir
It's Ghost Festival!
The human race has stooped to new lows...
How can we Buddhists redeem their souls?
I really don't know
With my wisdom, I can save them...
But my body's feeling very weak...
Let's find an inn,
get some food and sleep
Buddha meditated facing
a wall for 3 years...
and you complain after
no food for one day...
For penance, chant 5,000 times,
to purity the mind...
Right! Look, food, let's eat,
then purity my mind
His brain's in his stomach!
That cretin,
I'll kill him for 15 dollars
It was only 10 dollars last time,
why more?
Because I'm a better swordsman now
So you say-but how good?
Beef brisket and noodles!
Hey, I never ordered that
Are you saying I made a mistake?
Orders returned are charged double!
- What do you want?
- I told you I didn't order it!
More of them than us,
okay, take it away...
It's just a misunderstanding
As I improve,
my price will rise again...
If you don't like it,
find someone else
For that price,
I need some sort of sample
- You want me to show off? No problem!
- You want to see sample?
Sir, spare us some food?
I bet you my head
No, get lost!
Fong
My sword's a bit long, I'm sorry!
We shouldn't stay here, let's go!
Every time I see you there's trouble
Brother
and more trouble now
with that lump of gold!
Master, there's shelter ahead
It's a Temple
Orchid Temple
The entrance is over there
They've gone inside...
But Orchid Temple's haunted,
wait till dawn
Yes, let's wait!
Dawn?
What if someone else gets it?
Hey, you lead!
Me?
A ghost got my foot, run!
Run!
It's a bit draughty in here, Master
Don't be afraid, let me tell you...
Orchid Temple is haunted
What?
Haunted...
Master, Master!
Fong, stop stepping on my heels
I just want you to know I'm behind you
If you're so scared,
sleep outside the door
It's pouring outside
Master,
if it's really haunted...
I don't mind if we carry on walking
Fong, we have Gold Buddha to protect us...
No one will dare come in...
So we won't have to worry
about it being stolen...
We'll just stay overnight
Shall we satisfy the God of Hunger?
You beg the ghosts
to spare you some food
Funny,
I've forgotten what I've just said!
Who said a ghost got his foot?
Was it you?
- No
- Was it you?
- He did!
If it got you,
how come you could run so fast?
There's a woman singing, up there
Sister,
it's raining so hard outside...
I wonder how long
before they come inside
We're here!
So many men!
Women! They're beautiful!
Smells so good
Don't go, so beautiful!
Come on
There are more!
They're so ugly!
The one in the middle's the prettiest
She's so old!
The one next to her's beautiful
Priestress, there are so many,
I'll help Lotus
Alright,
that way I won't have to wait so long
These men're already trapped,
who needs your help?
I thought you'd be quicker,
it took you ages
They're already ours,
so what's the rush?
Take your clothes off, she's coming.
I'm taking the prettiest one. Hands off!
Your skin's so soft.
Give me a kiss!
Go to hell
There're all kinds of games,
want to try?
Something in the water bit me,
what is it?
What is it? Let's go!
What's happening?
Let's go, they're demons
What's that sound, Master?
The ghosts are out
What shall I do?
Master!
Watch the Gold Buddha,
and stay put...
I'm going to catch the demons!
Don't come near me,
I have a Gold Buddha
You're powerful,
you hide even from me!
Show your true selves!
Stars scatter!
Still able to hide,
it's powerful!
Priestess, what about that monk?
Don't worry!
He maybe powerful,
but he's no match for me
We'll play with them awhile.
You seduce the little monk
Priestess, let me go,
I can handle him
You're not experienced enough,
when it comes to men
Priestess, I know exactly what you mean...
You don't want her wasting your time
Let me bring him back to you quickly
Sorry,
I forgot your cover was damaged...
You got all wet
I'll say some prayers as penance later
I know you have great powers...
If we really meet a - ghost...
Please help me destroy whatever it is
Buddha!
Oh no!
Help, there's a ghost!
A ghost chasing her?
That means she's not a ghost
Help!
Ghost!
Lady!
There's a ghost! Ghosts!
I'm so afraid!
I'm so scared, please help me!
I can see flesh!
Where is the ghost?
Let me hide behind you!
Look,
there's something moving over there...
Hold me tight!
Your leg
Feel my heart,
it's beating so rapidly!
Come on!
I break my vows,
if I'm near a woman!
Let's pray together,
it'll keep the ghosts away
Don't pray now,
let's do something else!
Let me go, or I'll break my vows!
Did you know, you're my first man?
Let me help you undress
What? Undress?
Hey wait, my shoe!
If Master sees me like this...
he'll never believe I was saving your life!
No! I must pray
Where're my prayer books?
Fire! Come and save me!
How did it catch fire?
My clothes are on fire!
Take your clothes off!
Fire, help!
Stop undressing,
they're not burning now!
I must, I'm afraid of fire!
But I'll see everything
Lady
Hey, monk... has the fire gone out?
It was so dangerous!
My clothes are all burnt, what to do?
Cover yourself with my robe
You're so kind!
Put it on quickly, I won't watch
I tripped on your clothes
Stop,
or I won't be able to control myself!
I'm a bad girl,
are you as bad as me?
I thought,
you were being chased by a ghost?
Ghost? Here's your ghost!
Come and get me...
This is fun!
But it didn't last long!
Lucky I prayed in time...
or I would've done that
"stuff" with you
Hey, monk...
What would you have done?
Tell me
I said means I want...
I want means I desire...
I desire means I'll do...
If I do, I'll never stay a monk!
No, I must pray
Stop praying, help me up...
Quickly!
I'll help you up...
But you promise not to come too close...
Darn I saw it!
Aren't you interested in me at all?
Interested? In what way?
All men are interested in this!
Don't take off my pants...
It's strange!
Your head aches when I pray...
You weren't being chased by a ghost!
You are a ghost!
I'm going to get you!
It's really haunted,
I'm scared!
I better run!
Come over here!
Reveal your true form!
You're mine
Reveal yourself!
Stupid monk,
why've you stopped praying?
Go,
if Master returns you'll never escape!
Why are you letting me go?
I'm giving you a chance to reform...
So you can reincarnate as a good person
I'm evil! I'll never change
Hey, my robe!
If you want it, get it yourself!
It serves you right!
Help me, quick help me!
Go on, scram!
Waiting for me to hit you?
Hey, my robe!
Still playing games with me!
Master!
You appeared so suddenly!
Fong,
what're you doing here half naked?
It's too hot,
I came outside to cool down
Hot? Where's the Gold Buddha?
- It's inside, it's just fine!
- Well.
Did you see anything untoward?
No way,
not with the Gold Buddha here...
No ghost would dare come near...
Even if it did,
it wouldn't get away!
And did you find anything?
That demon is quite something
Anyway, we're staying only one night...
and leaving tomorrow with the Gold Buddha...
So we'd better get some rest...
or we'll be tired tomorrow
Okay...
I'll capture them sooner or later
Your senses are impure,
that's why you're hot...
Take the Gold Buddha out and pray
Take the Gold Buddha out?
Pray all night in front of it
On my own?
Why,
you want me to keep you company?
No, no!
Okay, let's go inside!
Will you stop that.
If Master sees it, I've had it!
Fong
Good morning Master
Bring the Buddha, we're leaving
Okay
Darn,
he'll find out sooner or later
Please help me find the Gold Buddha!
- What did you say?
- Nothing, just saying my prayers
- Fong
- Yes
I'm glad the Buddha's safe...
or there's no point
in going to imperial Temple
That's right!
Master, if we leave like this now...
it's not quite right...
Since you know Orchid Temple is haunted...
shouldn't we stay and get rid of the demons?
I remember a certain old monk...
sort of say in some manuscript...
"If no one goes to hell,
and we don't go to hell...
who will go to hell?"
You're a monk,
and you don't know which manuscript!
I've always had a bad memory...
but leaving like this is irresponsible
You're right!
I'll stay and catch the demons...
You take the Buddha to imperial Temple
Right, I'll go
Fong, are you alright?
Yes,
after praying all night my mind is pure...
but my stomach is even purer...
and now in the sun, I feel faint
Are you saying that...
you're sick?
I'll be fine Master,
I'll overcome it...
I'll make it...
I'm getting there,
it's getting better...
No it's not working...
I'm going to faint
I think you're hungry,
I'll beg for food...
My student does not behave like a monk
Buddha be merciful!
Gold Buddha,
I'd better find you today!
Haven't slept all night,
I feel faint...
I'll find the Buddha,
and get Master to leave...
or when he's out,
she'll come for me again...
and it'll be another sleepless night!
Snake!
What now? Oh no!
I only have a day left...
Buddha, have mercy, help Fong
Buddha!
Look this blade cuts heads off
like slicing melons
Really?
Let's try it on your head
Please be merciful,
put down your knives
- Get lost
- Give me something
Shove off!
You monks,
always lecturing people...
You're ruining our business...
Get lost!
Give me the money you owe me
- I don't have any money
- Give my money back!
- No money? What's all that on the ground?
- That's my money!
It's mine now
Since when did I owe you money?
When you asked me to do the job
What job?
I don't know you
Exactly, he doesn't know you!
The money's mine
- I don't know him
- Go to hell
Sir,
how do you know the money's yours?
He's right, prove it's yours,
and you can have it!
Right, you said it,
you better mean it
Abracadabra...
Rise...
Money, money, are you mine?
Ah! It's black magic!
Let's go!
You also follow Buddha,
you should do good...
not concern yourself with money
How else would you get any alms?
I wouldn't accept that sort of money
No? Then leave...
At least I earn my money...
You wander around begging for food...
You're just a beggar in disguise!
Money is only illusion...
You can't get what's not yours
Monk, is this your doing?
Mercy, Buddha is merciful
You're a fake, monk!
Admit your pranks!
There must be a way to break his spell!
Hey, don't go! Don't go!
My money!
Another fruitless job...
Damn monk!
It's getting dark!
What shall I tell Master?
I'll say the snakes took it...
How could the snakes take it?
Right,
I'll say the ghosts took it...
The Gold Buddha repels ghosts.
Impossible!
I'll tell him the truth
That'll be Master...
I didn't mean it Master,
I just dropped it!
Master, actually...
It's you?
It's you again?
What are you doing here?
If you don't go, how'll I make a living?
Darn!
Let me rest for one night okay?
The way you live,
don't you feel like a whore?
Perhaps if you were human,
making a living...
But you're a ghost,
why a slut too?
Am I a slut?
Anyone who strips a guy's pants off is a slut!
What are you looking for?
The Gold Buddha...
- I don't know where it...
- The Gold Buddha?
Why're you getting so close?
I had enough fun last night!
It's only down there
Don't come so close to me!
You think I don't want to?
I can't leave till the Gold Buddha's found
I'll help you
The Gold Buddha's very powerful...
Aren't you afraid?
There's no other way...
If you don't leave,
I'll have to move!
That's a point!
Let's go together!
Last night you surprised me and I fell...
I dropped the Gold Buddha somewhere here
Don't step on my clothes...
If they fall off,
you'll say I was stripping
Where is it?
- Snakes! I forgot to say there're snakes here
- Where?
- Over there!
Stop it, my head aches!
I'm only praying very softly
Go upstairs,
you're getting in the way...
With you here, I'll never find it!
Go on!
You're right
Mind the snakes
Snakes! Lots of snakes!
The Gold Buddha!
I found it!
Where is it?
Over there, help me, there're many snakes
I didn't tell you to kill them...
How did this happen?
What will I say?
How can I put it back together?
I've been bitten by a snake,
it hurts!
Help!
I don't want to kill you, go!
Are you alright?
I've been poisoned
What shall we do?
Suck the venom out with your mouth...
Please, quickly
I can feel the venom...
I feel faint
Is that alright?
That's fine, thank you...
It's okay,
anyway your wound isn't real
Then why did you swallow the blood?
To keep you happy
The wound isn't real,
but the venom is!
You're right, that means...
I'll help you suck it out
No, that means mouth to mouth
You'll die once the venom takes effect...
Pretend I'm not a woman
Then who are you?
Pretend I'm your Master
He would never do this
Pretend I'm your mother
I've never met my mother.
Try someone I've seen
How about him?
Him?
Okay
Whatever
What are you doing?
Sucking the venom
What did you stick in my stomach?
My tongue
Why stick your tongue in my stomach?
To suck out the venom!
There's still some left in you
Really?
Is your heart beating rapidly?
Yes!
Does your whole body feel hot?
Yes
Do you feel sweaty,
your head ache?
Yes
That's the effect of the venom...
We have to carry on
I'd rather die
Don't die here...
or you'll become one of us
Okay, come on
Hang on
Are you ready?
Yes,...
why didn't you stick your tongue inside?
No! There's no venom.
I was lying
How dare you deceive an honest man...
It's because of you.
I dropped the Buddha...
Look how I treat you,
is this my thanks?
I'm a monk!
I have rules to follow...
You keep seducing me,
you're trouble!
Really?
From what you say,
isn't it a bore being a monk?
You can't do what every man wants to do...
Don't you feel deprived being a monk?
Deprived?
I never had anything to lose...
The priority is to fix the Buddha...
So when Master comes back,
we can leave
Don't set your clothes on fire again!
Why're you a monk,
if it's such hard work?
The first person I set eyes on, was Master...
My first clothes were monk's robes...
What else can I be except a monk...
Do I have a choice?
You're grown up now,
you can choose
I've been with Master for years,
he's family...
Why'd my parents leave me in a monastery?
I'd like to know what my parents look like...
So that if I ever met them...
I could avoid them
Don't fall off!
Your life is better than mine was...
At least you have a Master!
Were you an orphan, too?
No...
I was sold as soon as I was born...
Whoever bought me became my parents...
Finally a rich man
took me as his 2nd wife...
I was murdered by his mistress,
and buried here
That's the first time
I've told this story
I was lying
I'm glad it's a lie...
If it were true,
it would be tragic
So in comparison, you're free now...
Not being sold again and again...
Pity you're a ghost,
we could've been friends
Aren't we friends now?
Little monk,
could you get close to anyone else?
I don't know
Do you think I'm beautiful?
Oh no, Master's returned, run away!
Fong, what are you doing?
Master, I'm just repairing the stairs...
Wait outside, it's almost done
The feeling of evil is stronger today
Master, you can't go inside
Why?
There are snakes inside
Snakes?
My powers protect
and make me immune to venom...
Snakes don't come near me
She must be gone by now!
The demons are close by
Fong
Why're you holding a comb?
I bought it, to...
comb my eyebrows,
it looks great...
You want to try it?
Shave your eyebrows
and you won't need a comb
Where's the Gold Buddha?
It's over there Master, see it?
Fong, close all the windows
Why close them?
To stop the demons entering
Very clever, Master!
Thank God, Master didn't run into her!
Fong, bring me the gold paint
Okay
Oh, it was on the table
Your gold paint
Oh no, it's finished, Master
I haven't written on
all the windows yet...
Bring out all our holy objects
Seal all the entrances
Oh no!
Fong, what is it?
Did you see something?
It's just that I haven't eaten all day...
I'm feeling a big faint...
Master, let me help you
I found you some food.
Get it from my bag
The ghosts will come from this direction...
But we've run out of holy objects
There's a gap over there...
Why don't you hang it up there?
This is where the evil's the strongest.
I'll repel it
Master, some ghost took your beads!
Strange,
how could a ghost take my beads?
I'll get rid of all of them!
Help!
Fong is in trouble!
Little monk!
You shameless demon!
Help! Help
Help me! Master!
Help! Master!
Mercy shrouds the world!
Help me!
The stars will scatter!
Fong, listen to me...
Go back and bring me my holy objects
Right!
Mercy is boundless!
I warned you not to play with that staff
Help!
Are you alright?
Get it away from me!
How come you are... so cold?
Ghosts get cold before they fade away!
Leave me alone, I have to rest...
Otherwise I won't survive as a ghost
Right, I'll go and save Master then
It doesn't look like you can move
Have you recovered?
I must go and save Master
Hush!
It feels cold!
What's happening?
One of my sisters is here
Good. I'll ask her to help you!
No, we hate each other
If you bring her here,
we'll both be in trouble
So what can we do?
I can smell a human
Let's have a look
Don't worry I have the staff
There's no time
Oh, it's you!
Are you surprised?
Fooling around behind the Priestess's back?
How dare you disobey her orders?
Why do you look so ill?
Maybe you're the one fooling around!
Are you bitching because you feel guilty?
I helped the Priestess fight the two monks...
and I got wounded...
Come over and help me...
Why should I help you?
Just because you're her pet,
you put on these airs...
I'm sorry, I have no time
What was that?
Someone's hiding behind me
Who?
The little monk
Really?
Trying to trick me into helping you?
No chance!
I'd never help you!
Why don't you stay,
and wait for the Priestess
You're so cunning...
Trying to delay me
from helping the Priestess...
I won't fall for your tricks...
Let's go