I'm voting for Dukakis.
Hm ...
Well ...
Maybe when you have children
who need braces ...
and half of your husband's pay
cheque goes to the federal government,
- you'll regret that.
- My husband's pay cheque?
I'm not squeezing
one out till I'm 30.
Will you still be at the Yarn Barn?
That's a great place
to raise children.
- That's really funny.
- I think a year of partyings enough.
- She's going to Harvard next fall.
- I haven't gotten in yet.
You think Dukakis will provide for
America till you squeeze one out?
Yeah, I do.
- When can I squeeze one out?
- Eighth grade.
Excuse me.
Donnie, you're such a dick.
Whoa, Elizabeth!
A little hostile there.
Maybe you should be in therapy,
then Mom and Dad can pay someone
to listen to your thoughts ...
so we don't have to.
Ok. Tell us why you stopped
taking your medication.
You're such a fuck-ass!
- Please.
- Did you just call me a fuck-ass?
- That's enough.
- Go suck a fuck!
- How does one suck a fuck?
- Shall I tell you?
- Please.
- Not at the dinner table.
- Stop.
- Fuck ...
What's a fuck-ass?
I took a year off to be with you.
- What?
- How did you know?
- I didn't know it was a big deal.
- It is a big deal.
I'm reading. Get out.
Where do you go at night?
- just get out.
- Did you toilet-paper the Johnson's house?
- Is that why you're here?
- No.
I stopped rolling houses
in the sixth grade.
Where's my son?
I don't recognise you.
Then you take the goddamn pills.
Bitch.
Our son just called me a bitch.
You're not a bitch.
You're bitching,
but you're not a bitch.
I want to be a president
who makes sure that we ...
never again do business with a
drug-running Panamanian dictator ...
or funnel aid to the Contras
through drug dealers,
Values begin at the top,
Dukakis ... Son of a bitch.
Those are the values I want
to bring to the presidency ...
and to the White House,
- Panama is a friendly country.
- Tell him, George.
I talked to the president of Panama
about their money laundering,
Mr. Noriega was there,
but there was no evidence,
When the evidence was there,
we indicted him,
I've been watching you,
Come closer,
closer,
28 days,
six hours,
42 minutes,
12 seconds,
That is when the world will end.
Why?
Son? Donnie Darko?
Donnie Darko?
What the heck's going on here?
- Who is it?
- It's Eddie Darko's kid.
He's just a neighbourhood kid.
Guess he was sleep-golfing?
Watch out for that drool spot!
Are you all right, son?
So let's stay off
the links at night, Ok?
I'm sorry, Dr Fisher.
It ... It won't happen again.
- Kids ...
- Let's golf.
- No one's allowed.
- This is my house.
- I said ...
- This is my house!
Wait a minute.
- Here's your brother.
- It fell in your room.
Ms Darko? I'm Bob Garland.
I'm with the FAA.
- The what?
- I'm with the FAA. May we speak privately?
- In private?
- Please.
- And here ...
- Ok.
All right, we have arranged a hotel.
Get some sleep
and we'll take care of this.
- Great.
- Thank you.
Kids, come on.
We're going to a hotel.
They don't know where it came from.
- Where's Pop?
- He's still at work,
If it fell from the plane ...
what happened to the plane?
They don't know, Samantha.
Can't we make money from this?
Can't we sue the airline?
Shut up, Sam.
Why do I have to sleep with Donnie?
He stinks.
When you fall asleep tonight,
- I'm gonna fart in your face.
- I'm telling Mom!
Samantha, don't go over there.
Frankie Feedler.
You remember. From high school.
He died. Remember?
On his way to the prom.
They said he was doomed.
Jesus.
They could be saying
the same thing about Donnie.
Our Donnie.
But he dodged it.
He dodged his photograph.
Somebody was watching over him.
Mrs Farmer will bring you home
after practice. Bye, honey.
Donnie ... good luck.
- Oh, my God! Tell me everything.
- I'm not allowed to talk about it.
- Oh, my God!
- Hi, Cherita.
- Shut up!
- Darko cheats death! Huh?
You're a celebrity! I called you
a jillion times. Where you been?
- At a hotel.
- Dad saw you at the golf course.
- You sleep-walking again, buddy?
- I don't want to talk about it.
Now that you're famous,
have a smoke.
What happens
if you tell Mom and Dad, Sam?
- You'll put Ariel in the garbage disposal.
- Goddamn right, I will.
- So grody.
- Hey, Cherita, you want a cigarette?
- Shut up!
- "Shut up!"
Go back to China, bitch!
Just leave her alone.
- That's some good shit, huh?
- It's a fucking cigarette.
"There would be headlines
in the papers.
The grown-up gangs who ran
the betting at the wrestling ...
and the barrow-boys
would hear with respect ...
of how Old Misery's house
had been destroyed.
It was as though this plan had
been with him all his life,
pondered through the seasons,
now, in his 15th year,
crystallised with the
pain of puberty."
What is Graham Greene trying
to communicate with this passage?
Why did the children
break into Old Misery's house?
- Joanie?
- They wanted to rob him.
If you had actually
read the short story,
which was a whopping 13 pages,
you'd know that the children ...
find a great deal of money
in the mattress, but burn it.
Donnie Darko, perhaps with your
recent brush with mass destruction,
you can give us your opinion.
They say it when they flood the
house, when they tear it to shreds,
that destruction
is a form of creation,
so burning the money is ironic.
They just want to see what happens
when they tear the world apart.
They want to change things.
- May we help you?
- Yeah, I just registered.
- They put me in the wrong class.
- You look like you belong here.
Um ... Where do I sit?
Sit next to the boy
you think is the cutest.
Quiet!
Let her choose.
Joanie, get up.
What people don't understand
is that Dukakis ...
does not have
the financial infrastructure,
Well, the construction guys ...
say it will take about a week
to fix the roof.
Airline better not fuck us
on the shingle match.
- They still don't know?
- Know what?
- Where it came from?
- Oh, no. They can't tell us.
Something about a matching
serial number that got burned.
I had to sign a form saying I
wouldn't talk to anyone about it.
So we can't tell anyone
what nobody knows?
Yeah. But you tell ...
What's your doctor's name?
- Dr. Thurman, Dad.
- Yes. Tell Dr. Thurman whatever you want.
- Dad.
- What?
- Dad!
- Oh ...!
What's that woman doing
in the middle of the damn road?!
No mail today. Maybe tomorrow.
What did she say to you?
- I made a new friend.
- Real or imaginary?
- Imaginary.
- Would you like to talk about this friend?
- Frank.
- What did he say?
- He said to follow him.
- Follow him? Where?
- Into the future.
And then what happens?
And then he said ...
then he said that the world
was coming to an end.
Do you think
the world is coming to an end?
No.
That's stupid.
For my entire life
I was a victim of my own fear.
Love,
I was feeding fear with food.
Fear,
Finally, I looked in the mirror.
Not just in the mirror,
I looked THROUGH the mirror,
In that image,
I saw my ego reflection,
For two years,
I thought it was normal ...
for a 10-year-old to wet the bed,
Shh! Quiet!
But the solution
was there all the time,
I'm not afraid any more!
All over America, people have
come together to join hands,
People who believe that human life
is absolutely too important,
too valuable and too precious
to be controlled by fear.
Pay close attention,
You could miss something.
Hello, My name is Jim Cunningham
And welcome to "Controlling Fear".
"... and the prince
was led into a world ...
of strange and beautiful magic."
Wow.
"The Last Unicorn"
by Samantha Darko.
- Give it back!
- "There was once a unicorn named Ariel ..."
- You wrinkled it.
- It's not wrinkled, Sam.
It's 7:45. The bus should've
been here 20 minutes ago.
Maybe Martha finally went nuts
and hijacked it.
There's this rule ―
at 7:45, we get to go home.
There's no rule.
Cherita, you should ... go home.
Yeah, if you're here when the bus
comes, we'll get in trouble.
- Shut up!
- "Shut up!"
Hey, Porky Pig ...
I hope you get molested.
Hey! Hey! I can't believe this!
School's closed
today because it's flooded.
- No way!
- Yeah.
Holy shit!
That's the best news ever!
My God, is this ever going to stop?
Eventually, yes. But right now,
I got 12 classrooms full of water.
All coming
from a busted water main.
- What else?
Principal Cole,
I'll show you what else.
That's unbelievable.
That's solid bronze, isn't it?
- Yep.
- How did this happen?
I heard a cat burglar
trashed everything ...
and the Mongrel
got his head cut off.
- Hah!
- True!
Beth's mom said the boys' locker
room flooded ...
and they found faeces everywhere.
- What are faeces?
- Baby mice.
Hey.
Has anyone ever told you
that you're sexy?
I like your boobs.
Hey.
School's cancelled.
Do you want to walk me home?
Sure.
- Don't look so freaked.
- I'm not.
Check your backpack.
Those guys steal shit.
Fuck 'em!
- So, why'd you move here?
- My parents got a divorce.
My mom got a restraining order
against my stepdad.
He has emotional problems.
I have those, too.
What kind does he have?
He stabbed my mom
four times in the chest.
Oh. Did he go to jail?
No, he fled.
They still can't find him.
Mom and I had to change our names.
I thought Gretchen Ross
was pretty cool.
I was in jail once. I mean ...
I burned down this house.
It was abandoned,
but I got held back in school ...
and I can't drive till I'm 21.
But I'm over all of that.
I'm ... painting and stuff.
Writing. I want to be a writer.
Maybe a painter. Maybe both ...
I'll write a book
and draw the pictures.
Then maybe people will understand
me. I don't know, change things.
Donnie Darko ― what the hell kind
of name is that?
It's like a superhero or something.
What makes you think I'm not?
I should go. For physics, Monnitoff
is having me write this essay ―
the greatest invention
ever to benefit mankind.
It's Monnitoff.
But that's easy. Anti-septics.
Like, the whole sanitation thing.
Joseph Lister, 1895.
Before anti-septics, there was no
sanitation, especially in medicine.
You mean soap?
Well, I'm really glad
school was flooded today.
Why is that?
We'd never have had
this conversation.
You're weird.
Sorry.
No, that was a compliment.
Well, look, uh ...
You want to go with me?
- Where do you want to go?
- No, I mean, like, "go" with me.
- You know, like "going together".
- Sure.
Ok. Where are you going?
I'm going home.
Stupid ... "Where are you going?"
I'd like to try something new.
Have you ever been hypnotised?
No.
When I clap twice, you will
wake up. Do you understand?
- Yes.
- So, tell me about your week.
I met a girl.
What is her name?
Gretchen.
We're going together now.
Do you still think
about girls a lot?
Yeah.
- How are things going at school?
- I think about girls a lot.
I asked you about school, Donnie.
I think about fucking
a lot during school.
What else do you think about
during school?
"Married With Children".
- You think about your family?
- I just turn down the volume ...
and think about fucking
Christina Applegate.
I asked you about your family.
No.
I don't think about fucking
my family. That's gross.
I'd like to hear
about your friend Frank.
Sam Bylan.
Cherita Chen.
Donald Darko.
Daye Dennis.
Hey, you fuck!
Did you say I flooded the school?
- I didn't say shit.
- Yeah, well, they think I did it.
If you're innocent, then you have
nothing to worry about, right?
Fuck you! You know what I think?
I think you did it.
Beer and pussy ― that's all I need.
- We gotta find ourselves a Smurfette.
- Smurfette?
Mm-hm.
Not some tight-ass Middlesex chick.
Like, this cute little blonde ...
that'll get down with the guys
like Smurfette does.
Smurfette doesn't fuck.
That's bullshit. Why do you think
Papa Smurf made her?
Because the other Smurfs
were getting too horny.
Not vanity.
I heard he was a homosexual.
Then she fucks them
while vanity watches.
What about Papa Smurf?
He must get some action?
What he does,
he films the gang-bang.
Later on, he beats off to the tape.
First of all, Papa Smurf didn't
create Smurfette. Gargamel did.
She was sent as Gargamel's evil spy
to destroy the Smurf village,
but the overwhelming goodness
of the Smurfs transformed her.
And as for the whole gang-bang
scenario, it just couldn't happen!
Smurfs are asexual.
They don't even have ...
reproductive organs
under those little white pants.
That's what's so illogical
about being a Smurf.
What's the point of living
if you don't have a dick?
Donnie, why you gotta get
smart on us?
Grandma Death.
Excuse me! Excuse me!
Stay off the road, Miss Sparrow,
or I will call Social Services.
I hate that Miss Farmer.
She's such a fucking bitch!
Yeah.
- How old is Grandma Death?
- 101.
She does the same thing every day.
Just walks back and forth
and back and forth to the mailbox.
Nothing ever in there.
Oh, wait, wait, wait ...
She's going back to the box.
We may still have mail.
- Mail, mail, mail.
- Here it is.
This could be it. Oh ...?
Oh, no dice, Grandma. Sorry.
Someone ought to write that bitch.
Authorities continued
their search ...
for a suspect in the Middlesex
Ridge School vandalism.
The private school
has asked for donations ...
to restore its beloved mascot,
known only as the Mongrel ...
It's very helpful.
There's a good turnout tonight.
What are you trying
to accomplish here?
There was urine and faeces
flooded in my office.
Whatever fits.
"Whatever fits"?
In cooperation
with the county police,
we have begun
an active investigation ...
into the cause of the flooding.
And our suspects include
several of our own students ...
I want to know why this filth
is being taught to our children.
Kitty, I would appreciate
if you would wait ...
Dr Cole, not only am I a teacher,
but I am also a parent
of a Middlesex child.
Therefore I am the
only person here ...
who transcends
the parent-teacher bridge.
Don't worry, you got away with it.
I have in my hand Graham Greene's
"The Destructors".
This short story is part of my
daughter's English assignment.
In this story,
several children destroy ...
an elderly man's house
from inside out.
How can you do that?
And how do they do this?
They flood the house
by breaking through a water main.
I can do anything I want.
And so can you.
And I think that this garbage
should be removed!
Excuse me.
What is the real issue here?
The PTA doesn't ban books.
The PTA must acknowledge
that pornography ...
is being taught in our curriculum!
- It's meant to be ironic.
- Excuse me. Go back to grad school.
Why did you make me
flood the school?
They are in great danger.
Do you even know
who Graham Greene is?
I think we have all seen "Bonanza".
Well, um ... while we are
on other topics ...
Where do you come from?
Do you believe in time travel?
Who are you talking to?
I was just taking my pills, Sam.
A storm is coming, Frank says.
A storm that will swallow
the children,
and I will deliver them
from the kingdom of pain.
I'll deliver them
back to their doorsteps,
send the monsters
back to the underground.
I'll send them back to a place
where no one else can see them.
Except for me.
Because I am Donnie Darko.
Who is Frank?
A six-foot-tall bunny rabbit.
In these modern times,
our attitude and beliefs
are so delicate, so fragile.
I have had a "Cunning Vision",
This vision has released me.
It's important that
our lifeline be rejuvenated,
so that we can breathe again.
It's time to breathe.
It is time to breathe.
Thank you, Jim Cunningham.
So now let us begin Lifeline
Exercise Number One,
Please press stop now.
As you can see, the lifeline is
divided into two polar extremes.
Fear and love.
Fear is in the negative
energy spectrum.
- Love is in the positive energy spectrum.
- No, duh (!)
Excuse me?
"No, duh" is a product of fear.
Now, on each card
is a character dilemma ...
which applies to the lifeline.
Please ... Take this. Thank you.
Please read each character
dilemma aloud ...
and place an "X" on the lifeline
in the appropriate place.
Cherita?
"Juanita has an important
math test today.
She's known about the test for
several weeks, but has not studied.
In order to keep from failing,
Juanita decides
to cheat on the math test."
Good. Good. Very good.
Mr. Darko.
"Ling-Ling finds a wallet
filled with money.
"She takes it to the address
on the driver's licence ...
but keeps the money."
I'm sorry, Miss Farmer.
I don't get this.
Just place an "X"
in the appropriate place.
I know what to do, but you can't
lump things into two categories.
The lifeline is divided that way.
Well, life isn't that simple.
I mean ...
Who cares if Ling-Ling
keeps the money?
It has nothing to do
with fear or love.
They are the deepest
human emotions.
Ok. But you're not listening to me.
There are other things
to take into account,
the whole spectrum
of human emotion.
You can't just lump everything ...
into two categories
and deny everything else!
If you don't complete the
assignment, you'll get a zero.
Donald, let me preface
this by saying ...
that your Iowa Test scores
are ... intimidating.
So ...
Let's go over this again.
What exactly
did you say to Miss Farmer?
I'll tell you. He asked me ...
to forcibly insert the lifeline
exercise card into my anus!
Nobody cares about responsibility,
morality, family values ...
Kitty ... Excuse us, please.
They've suspended him from
"after school" activities for 6 months.
Since this jet engine fiasco,
I don't know what's gotten into ...
I'll say this because our daughters
are on the dance team together ...
and I respect you,
but after witnessing
your son's behaviour,
I have significant doubts
about your ...
Our paths through life
must be righteous.
Go home and look in the mirror ...
and pray that your son doesn't
succumb to the path of fear.
Do you remember
that weird gym teacher, Mrs. Farmer?
Yeah. Ok, well, my brother told her
to shove a book up her ass today.
And then my parents
just bought him all this new shit.
Yeah, I know. I wish a jet engine
would fall on my room.
- Dr Monnitoff.
- Donnie.
I know this is gonna
sound kind of weird,
but do you know anything
about ... time travel?
A wormhole with an
Einstein-Rosen bridge,
which is theoretically a wormhole
in space controlled by man.
So, according to Hawking,
a wormhole may be able
to provide a short cut ...
for jumping between two distant
regions of space-time.
So to travel back in time,
you have to have a spaceship ...
faster than the speed of light.
- Theoretically.
- And be able to find a wormhole.
The basic principles of
time travel are there.
Your vessel and portal.
Your vessel can be anything.
- Like a DeLorean?
- Metal craft of any kind.
You know, I love that movie. It's
so ... like, futuristic, you know?
Listen, um ... don't tell anybody
that I gave you this.
Woman who wrote this
used to teach here.
She was a nun long before that.
Then overnight she became
this entirely different person.
She up and left the church,
wrote this book ...
She started teaching science,
right here at Middlesex.
"The Philosophy of Time Travel".
Roberta Sparrow?
That's right.
Roberta Sparrow.
Grandma Death.
It's called
"The Philosophy of Time Travel".
- What does philosophy have to do with it?
- Guess who wrote it.
Who?
Roberta Sparrow.
Huh! She wrote a book.
- Grandma Death wrote a book.
- That's a terrible nickname.
We almost ran her down
the other day.
She lives in that piece of crap
house, and you know she's loaded.
- You're right.
- She was known for her gem collection.
Kids used to go up there
all the time ...
and try to steal stuff from her.
She became a total recluse.
I didn't know she was alive
till we damn near knocked her down.
She was just standing
in the road, frozen.
I walked over to see if she was OK.
And she whispered in my ear.
- What did she say?
- I think Frank wants me to talk to her.
He asked if I knew
about time travel.
She wrote a book about it,
so that can't be
a coincidence, right?
What did she say to you?
She said that every living creature
on earth dies alone.
How did that make you feel?
It reminded me of my dog Callie.
She died when I was eight and she
crawled underneath the ... the porch.
To die.
To be alone.
Do you feel alone right now?
I don't know ...
I'd like to believe I'm not,
but I just ...
I've just never seen any proof,
so I just don't debate it any more.
I could spend my whole life
debating it over and over ...
and still wouldn't have proof,
so I just don't debate it any more.
It's absurd.
The search for God is absurd?
It is if everyone dies alone.
Does that scare you?
I don't want to be alone.
And his tapes have
made me realise ...
that for the last 39 years, I have
been a prisoner of my own fear.
Fear.
You have got to meet
this Jim Cunningham.
I can't believe he's single.
It has been a disappointing night
for these Super Bowl champions.
You're right, Dan, Coach Joe Gibbs
is on the sidelines.
He's gotta be thinking, "What
happened? What went wrong tonight?"
- And here's the kick,
- Oh!
It's no good ...
- Shit, we need a quarterback.
- We need a miracle.
We need to go for a safety.
What the future holds for this MVP,
we'll have to wait and see.
You guys want anything?
This week on "Who's The Boss?"
Samantha borrows Tony's van ...
and gets caught without a licence.
Better make sure
we don't miss that one.
Here we are again,
Fourth down now ...
Tomorrow, we meet our partners ...
for the Young Inventors' Fair.
What if you could go back in time
and take those hours of pain ...
and replace them
with something better?
- Like images?
- Yeah, a Hawaiian sunset ...
or the Grand Canyon.
Things that remind you
how beautiful ...
We've been going together
for two weeks.
Yeah?
Well, I er ... I ...
You want to kiss me?
- I'm sorry, I ...
- Look, Donnie, wait. I just ...
- Well, I like you a lot.
- I just want it to be ...
at a time when ... it ...
- When what?
- When it reminds me just ...
When it reminds you
how beautiful the world can be?
Yeah.
And there's some fat guy
staring at us.
I don't think telling any woman ...
to forcibly insert
an object up her anus ...
is something that should
go without consequence.
I think we should buy him a moped.
I think we should get a divorce.
- You won't tell Mom, will you?
- Why would I?
- You tell Mom everything.
- No, I don't.
- Let me see it.
- No, it's not finished. It's ...
Ok. It's cool.
That's scary.
You think?
Thank you for seeing us
at such late notice.
We both felt
we should come and discuss ...
What I think is going on
with your son.
Yes.
Um ... Well, he's er ...
You know about his past, and he
was suspended from school ...
for insulting his gym teacher.
I'm not sure that's a good example.
I think he had just cause.
Rose, let me lay out
what I believe is happening here.
Donnie's aggressive behaviour ...
his increased detachment
from reality,
seem to stem from his inability to
cope with the forces in the world ...
that he perceives
to be threatening.
Has he ever told you about Frank?
Frank?
Yes, the giant bunny rabbit.
The what?
I don't recall
him ever having mentioned a rabbit.
Donnie is experiencing ...
what is commonly called
a daylight hallucination.
This is a common occurrence
among paranoid schizophrenics.
- What can we do?
- I would like to do more hypnotherapy ...
... and increase his medication.
Whatever will help him, really,
is ... That's why we're here.
We just would like him
to experience some relief.
So if you think that more
medication will do that,
then I think
we should give it a try.
It's complicated.
Yeah?
There's like a force in your brain
that just sends you someplace.
Do you go someplace familiar?
No, but each time I keep waking up
farther from my house.
Scary.
Donnie Darko.
I know.
- Good morning, you mongrels!
- Good morning.
Is that all you can muster?
Good morning!
- Good morning!
- Now, that's a tiny, tiny bit better.
But I still sense some students ...
who are actually afraid
to say "good morning".
Good morning!
Yeah, that's what I like to hear!
Too many young men and women today ...
are completely paralysed
by their fears.
They surrender their bodies to the
temptation and destruction ...
of drugs, alcohol
and premarital sex.
Now, I'm going to tell you
a little story today.
It's a heartbreakingly sad story
about a young man ...
whose life was completely destroyed
by these instruments of fear,
a young man searching for love
in all the wrong places.
His name was Frank.
- We're moving through time.
- What?
Hi. My stepsister, like,
I sometimes worry
that she eats too much.
- Shut up, Kim!
- I'm just trying to help.
Oh, sweetheart, please!
There's no reason
to be embarrassed here.
Many times we eat because we are
afraid to face our ego reflection.
We find ourselves
looking at the mirror,
rather than into
and through the mirror.
When we do that, we can finally
see how beautiful we are.
- Thanks!
- Sure. Come up here. Don't be afraid.
Er, how can I find out what
I wanna be when I grow up?
Oh! That's a hard one.
Well, look deep inside of yourself,
deep within your heart,
and find what makes you feel love,
pure, unconditional love ...
and go to that. In your studies,
in your athletics,
in your relationships,
go towards love.
- Thank you.
- Come on up.
Next.
- How do I learn how to fight?
- "How do I learn how to fight?"
Son, violence is a product of fear.
Learn to truly love yourself ―
TRULY love yourself ―
and the world will be yours.
- Ok.
- Get yourself up here!
All right!
- Good morning.
- Good morning!
Um ... How much are they
paying you to be here?
Er ... Excuse me?
- What's your name, son?
- Gerald.
Well, Gerald,
I think you're afraid.
Do you want us to buy your book?
Because that was
the worst advice ever.
See how sad this is?
Want your sister to lose weight?
Tell her to stop eating Twinkies
and play field hockey.
No one knows what they want to be.
It takes time to find that out.
Right, Jim?
And you ...
Yeah, you.
Sick of some jerk shoving
your head down the toilet?
Well, lift some weights ...
or take a karate lesson, and next
time kick him in the balls.
Son ... See this? This is an anger
prisoner, a textbook example.
- Prisoner.
- Do you see the fear, people?
This boy is scared to death.
Son, it breaks my heart
to say this,
but I believe you're a very
troubled and confused young man.
You are searching
in all the wrong places.
You're right, actually.
I am pretty troubled
and pretty confused.
And I'm afraid, really, really
afraid. Really afraid, but I ... I ...
I think you're
the fucking Antichrist.
It's amazing.
He thinks he's telling the truth.
Everything he says
is a fucking lie.
Everything he says!
Everyone thinks he's so rad.
He's such a fucking chud ...
Are you ok?
Sit down. Calm down.
You ever hear of Grandma Death?
Who?
"The Philosophy of Time Travel".
What is this?
She wrote it.
I'm ... I'm seeing stuff ...
Like really messed-up stuff.
That book describes
stuff I've been seeing,
and it can't just be a coincidence.
She must be in.
She never leaves this house.
Maybe she's asleep.
Donnie, look.
Send her a letter.
Each vessel travel along a
vector through space-time ...
along its centre of gravity.
Like a spear.
- Pardon?
- Like a spear coming out of your chest.
Um ... Sure. Yeah.
In order for the vessel
to travel through time,
it's got to find a portal,
a wormhole or ...
Could these portals ...?
Could these portals
just appear anywhere, any time?
I think that's highly unlikely.
No, you're talking about
an act of God.
If God controls time,
time is pre-decided.
I'm not following you.
Every living thing
follows a set path.
And if you could see your path,
then you could see the future?
That's a form of time travel.
Well, you're contradicting
yourself.
If we were able
to see our destinies ...
manifest themselves visually,
then we would be given a choice
to betray our destinies.
The mere fact
that this choice exists ...
would make all preformed destiny
come to an end.
Not if you travel
within God's channel.
I'm not going to be able
to continue this conversation.
- Why?
- I could lose my job.
Ok.
It gives me no pleasure
to deny you ...
one of the great writers
of the 20th century.
Alas, I have not yet been elected
queen of the universe,
so I must obey the rules.
So, anyone seen in this school
reading this book ...
will be suspended.
Not to worry.
Someone pre-ordered a dozen copies
at the Sarasota Mall bookstore.
In Mr. Greene's absence,
we will now be reading another
classic ― "Watership Down".
Here, Donnie.
Pass these back.
Maybe you and Frank
can read this one together.
Now you know where he lives.
And they grow
out of our ... chest, solar plexus?
Just like she described, the way
they moved and they smelled.
It's like they're workers.
Assigned to each one of us.
They just ... They're like liquid.
I followed it
into my parents' bedroom.
What did you find?
Nothing.
- So we call them IMGs.
- Infant Memory Generators.
You buy these glasses
for your infant,
and they wear them
at night when they sleep.
But inside the glasses
are these slide photographs.
Each photograph is of something
peaceful or beautiful,
whatever the parents want.
What effect would it have
on an infant?
Well, nobody remembers
their infancy.
Anybody who says they do is lying.
So, this will help develop
memory earlier in life.
Yeah.
Did you consider
that infants need darkness ...
as part of their natural
development?
No.
Yeah.
What if the parents put in pictures
of Satan or dead people?
Is that what you'd show your kids?
Er, well, I mean, didn't your dad,
like, stab your mom?
Get out.
Gretchen!
Gretchen! Gretchen.
I'm sorry about those guys.
- Two for "Evil Dead", please.
- That'll be $2.
Why do you wear
that stupid bunny suit?
Why are you wearing
that stupid man suit?
Take it off.
What happened to your eye?
Why do they call you Frank?
It is the name of my father.
And his father before me.
Frank ...
where's this going to stop?
You should already know that.
Watch the movie screen.
There's something
I want to show you.
Have you ever seen a portal?
Burn it to the ground.
Ok. Now, girls,
I want you to concentrate.
Failure is not an option.
And, Bethany, if you feel the need
to vomit up there, just swallow it.
- Ok, Mom.
- Hey, you guys, good luck out there.
Now, that was really something.
Thank you, Cherita Chen,
with "Autumn Angel".
Now the moment
we've all been waiting for.
It is my pleasure to introduce
to you Emily Bates, Suzy Bailey,
Samantha Darko, Beth Farmer
and Joanie James.
They are Sparkle Motion.
How long was I asleep for?
Whole movie.
Well, look what the cat dragged in!
How you doing, Donnie?
Your little sister
was broken-hearted ...
that you missed
her big show last night.
- Dad?
- Hm?
I'm crazy.
You're not crazy.
I used to be crazy.
But you're not crazy.
- Look, you're my only son ...
- I know ...
No, hold it. I know I'm not
the best communicator, but ...
whatever happens to you,
be honest, tell the truth,
even if they do look at you
funny ― they will.
But what you gotta understand, son,
is that almost all of those
people are full of shit.
They're all part of this great
big conspiracy of bullshit.
And they're scared
of people like you.
Because those bullshitters know ...
that you're smarter
than all of them.
You know what you say
to people like that? Hm?
"Fuck you."
The blaze was extinguished
sometime after 8:00 last night.
Firefighters discovered
what has been referred to ...
as a kiddie porn dungeon,
Cunningham, who has become a recent
celebrity, was arrested ...
- Oh, my God! ...
while at Sarasota Heights Country Club.
Arson has not been ruled out
as the cause of the fire,
Now a group of
Cunning Vision employees ...
Dad played golf with that guy.
... vehemently denied
the alleged link ...
to a child pornography
publishing circuit.
In a vicious statement, Connie
attacked fire department officials,
claiming a mass conspiracy.
I'm sorry, Karen.
This is a progressive school,
but we don't feel
your methods are appropriate.
What exactly about my methods
are inappropriate?
I am sorry that you have failed.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have another appointment.
You can finish out the week.
Fuck!
Good afternoon. It's a great
pleasure to announce ...
that the Middlesex Ridge School
dance team ...
has been invited to perform on
"Star Search '88" in Los Angeles.
- I know now a terrible thing is coming.
- What do you mean?
The field, the field,
it's covered with blood,
Blood? Don't be silly.
All right, it's getting dark,
We should get back to the burrow.
Back to the burrow? It'll come
there, it's all around us!
- Stop it, Fiver,
- We've got to leave here.
When the other rabbits
hear of Fiver's vision,
do they believe him?
Why should we care?
Because the rabbits are us, Donnie.
Why should I mourn for a rabbit?
Is the death of one species
less tragic than another?
Of course. A rabbit's not like us.
It has no history books,
no photographs,
no knowledge of sorrow or regret.
I'm sorry. Don't get me wrong,
I like rabbits.
They're cute and horny.
If you're cute and horny,
you're happy.
You don't know why you're alive.
You just want to have sex as many
times as possible before you die.
I just don't see the point
in crying over a dead rabbit ...
who never even feared death
to begin with.
You're wrong.
These rabbits are the product
of the author's imagination.
He cares for them,
so we care for them,
otherwise we've just
missed the point.
Aren't we forgetting
about the miracle of storytelling?
The deus ex machina?
The god machine?
That's what saved the rabbits.
No, it was ridiculous.
I'll call you back.
- Rose.
- Kitty.
I'm sure you've heard the horrible
allegations against Jim Cunningham.
I know. Something about
a kiddie porn dungeon ...
Oh, please, please!
Don't use those words!
It's obviously a conspiracy
to destroy an innocent man.
I'm spearheading the Jim Cunningham
defence campaign.
Rose, I have to appear at his
arraignment tomorrow morning.
The girls have to leave
for Los Angeles.
As their coach, I was the obvious
choice to chaperone them.
- But now you can't go.
- Yes.
Now, believe me,
of all the other mothers,
I would never dream of asking you.
But none of the others
are available.
I don't know, Kitty. It's a bad
weekend. Eddie's in New York.
Rose, I don't know
if you realise ...
what an opportunity
this is for our daughters!
This has been a dream of Samantha's
and all of ours for a long time.
I made her lead dancer!
Sometimes I doubt your commitment
to Sparkle Motion!
Elizabeth will be in charge.
She'll drive you to therapy.
And if you need anything,
you promise me
that you will call Dr. Thurman?
How does it feel
to have a wacko for a son?
It feels wonderful.
Here ... Sorry! Here you are!
- You guys are gonna win. I know it.
- So do I.
Here's the keys. There's food
in the fridge and do not ...
Mom, go.
You're gonna miss your plane.
Mom, I need ...
There's nothing broken in my brain.
- I know.
- Bye, Donnie.
Ok, go. Go!
Hello, Donnie.
It's Friday.
Shouldn't you be off with
your friends, scaring old people?
- What's going on?
- I don't know. That's a good question.
I'm no longer your English teacher.
They fired me.
That's bullshit!
You're the only good teacher here.
Thank you.
What's "cellar door"?
This famous linguist once said ...
that of all the phrases
in the English language,
of all the endless combinations
of words in all of history,
"cellar door"
is the most beautiful.
"Cellar door."
I promise that one day everything's
gonna be better for you.
Shut up!
- I want to talk about your past.
- No ―
I want to talk
about you and your parents.
They didn't buy me
what I wanted for Christmas.
What did you want for Christmas
that year?
Hungry Hungry Hippos.
How did you feel, being denied
these Hungry Hungry Hippos?
- Regret.
- What else makes you feel regret?
- That I did it again.
- You did it again?
I flooded my school and I burned
down that pervert's house.
I only have a few days left
before they catch me.
Did Frank tell you
to do these things?
I have to obey him.
He saved my life.
I have to obey him
or I'll be left all alone.
And then ...
And then I won't be able to figure
out what this is all about.
I won't know his master plan.
Do you mean God's master plan?
Do you now believe in God?
I have the power
to build a time machine.
How is that possible?
How is time travel possible,
Donnie?
Time's up, Frank said.
- When is this going to happen?
- Soon.
What is going to happen?
- Frank is gonna kill.
- Who is he going to kill?
- I can see him!
The sky's gonna open up.
If the sky suddenly opened up,
there would be no law, no rule.
There would only be you
and your memories,
the choices you've made
and the people you've touched.
If this world were to end,
there would only be you and him ...
and no one else.
You can stop
taking your medication.
They're placebos.
Just pills made out of water.
Thank you.
Donnie ...
An atheist is someone who denies
altogether the existence of God.
You're an agnostic.
An agnostic is someone ...
who believes that there is
no proof of the existence of God,
but does not deny
a possibility that God exists.
Goodbye, Dr. Thurman.
Hey.
I got in.
I'm going to Harvard.
Hey, we should totally throw
a party. Mom and Dad are gone.
It's Halloween.
We could get away with it.
Ok. But it has to be small.
We got eggs, water balloons
and a dozen rolls of toilet paper.
I stole four beers from my dad.
- We got a keg.
- Keg beer is for pussies.
Rose, this is Lilian Thurman.
It is important that you call me
as soon as you get this message.
Thank you.
You ok?
Yeah. My mom's gone.
You want to come in?
I don't know.
She didn't leave a note
and the house was all messed up.
But you're ok.
Did you call the cops?
Yeah, they said
I should leave the house ...
and that I should go
to a safe place.
I'm just so scared. I keep thinking
something awful is happening and ...
It's my fucking stepdad, I know it.
I guess some people are just born
with tragedy in their blood.
- Hey, have you seen Frank?
- No, they went on a beer run.
If you're there, please pick up.
Oh, well, Good news,
The girls got
three and a half stars ...
and are in the quarter-finals.
Samantha was amazing, Anyway ...
We're taking the red-eye back
tonight and ...
- Mom, we've got to leave.
- Yeah. Ok.
We should arrive
8:30 in the morning.
Um ... I hope everything's ...
I hope everything's all right.
I love you. Bye.
- Come with me.
- Where are we going?
- Donnie?
- Look, we gotta go.
- We've got to see Grandma Death.
- Why? About the book?
- No, it's Frank.
- Donnie ...
Time is running out! We gotta go.
Donnie, nobody's here.
Let's just forget about it.
"Cellar door."
What?
Donnie! Donnie!
Donnie!
- Why the fuck are you here?
- Oh, my God!
- You're dead!
- What do we do?
- Shit!
- Leave them alone!
Don't fucking move!
There's a car!
- Get the hell out of here!
- Come on!
Seth, a car's coming. Let's go!
I have a bigger knife now.
Fuck!
Did you call the fucking cops?
- Deus ex machina.
- What did you just say?
- What the fuck did you say?
- Our saviour.
Donnie!
Frank ...
Is she dead?
What were you guys doing
in the middle of the road?!
Go home!
Go and tell your parents
everything will be ok.
Go!
The storm is coming.
You must hurry.
I'm going home.
Dear Roberta Sparrow, I've reached
the end of your book ...
and there's so many things
I need to ask you.
Sometimes I'm afraid
of what you might tell me.
that you'll tell me ...
this is not a work of fiction.
I can only hope that the answer
will come to me in my sleep.
I hope that when
the world ends ...
I can breathe a sigh of relief ...
because there will be
so much to look forward to.
Hey. What's going on?
Horrible accident.
My neighbour ... got killed.
- What happened?
- Got smushed by a jet engine.
What was his name?
Donnie. Donnie Darko.
I feel bad for his family.
Yeah.
Did you know him?
No.