What's the meaning of this check?
You trying to get me to cheat?
No...
I'm just the middleman.
You trying to play fast and loose
with me, or get me in trouble?
Do you think you're going
to get ahead of me...
...if I take a fall?
Look at this!
I'm the only Golden Leg!
You can't even dream about that.
No... I don't.
I just want a little kick-back.
Please don't tell anybody.
You're trash!
I'm sorry. I'll see you later.
Golden Leg! Golden Leg...
Golden Leg...
Hung, you've been a star player
for twenty years.
Since Fung missed the penalty kick
and lost his golden leg,
you've never have any rivals.
Now how do you feel about...
Oh, no! Don't talk to
me about that!
Hung, your Evil Team
has already won the gold
for five straight years.
What's the secret?
Secret? The secret is having
the greatest coach in soccer.
So you're confident
you'll win the gold again?
What are you, a rookie reporter? I don't
think that question even needs asking.
Excuse me...
Good morning, Hung!
Golden Leg!
Good morning!
Hung, your shoe is dirty.
I'll help you clean it up.
It's fine. I can take care of it.
Hung, I'll take your car over.
Hung, you promised to offer
a coaching job to me.
I'm ready.
I've got the confidence to train
a team as good as the Evil Team.
Do you think you can
still be a coach?
Forget it.
But you said...
Get real.
Don't you see?
You're a cripple now.
Do you think you can
still depend on this tattoo?
Hung...
I've served you for twenty years.
How can you say something like that?
I'm not in the mood for this today.
Things change.
You looked great when you were young.
You see, now you just look like a dog.
Forget it. Get lost.
I've already taken care
of you for twenty years.
You know, that's a lot of money.
Hung!
You're so vain!
If you hadn't given me...
...that bribery payoff twenty years ago,
I wouldn't be crippled now.
What? Are you losing your temper?
Why don't you shout louder?
Hey! Did all you guys hear that?
There're thousands of reporters outside.
Would you like me to let them come in?
You know,
I kept you here to keep your mouth shut.
But do you think anyone would believe...
...a handicapped beggar like you now?
- You!
- Don't be angry.
If you want to blame somebody,
blame yourself.
You should blame your greediness.
Forget it.
I'll tell you one more thing.
I was the one who arranged
that "accident" with your leg.
Damn it!
That's no way to kick.
Pardon?
I said...
...that's no way to kick.
So how would you do it then?
There has to be a fusion of
strength from the waist to the foot.
What do you mean?
My idol, Bruce Lee,
has already elaborated on it.
If you want to learn more,
you can take two
Kung Fu lessons from me.
Learn Kung Fu from you?
You just look like a cleaner.
Cleaning is just my job.
I'm really a post-graduate student.
Post-graduate student?
Focusing on how to
effectively teach Shaolin Kung Fu.
This is my name card.
Shaolin Orthodox School
Mighty Steel Leg.
Look! It's really strong.
Fighting is not my style.
I'm a well-educated man.
You're wrong.
Look at that girl.
I know she's sexy, so what?
- I'm an educated...
- No...
Watch this!
If she had learned Shaolin Kung Fu,
Weight Vest,
she would not have fallen like that.
You see!
So Shaolin Kung Fu is great!
Hey! Do you want to learn Kung Fu?
You're crazy!
Look at the woman over there.
If she had studied Shaolin Kung Fu,
Iron Hand,
parking would be much easier.
So Kung Fu is wonderful!
Excuse me! Do you want to learn...
No... Here, get lost!
This coin isn't just yours.
I should get a share.
Don't try to ruin our relationship!
Look at that!
What's wrong?
You've already spent a whole week
trying to trim this tree.
You're fired. Get lost!
- I'm sorry...
- Go away!
If he had studied Shaolin Kung Fu,
Nine Fences of the Recluse,
he would not be in trouble!
Nine Fences of the Recluse
sounds like it came from Hua Shan.
Don't you know every kind of Kung Fu
originally came from Shaolin?
Kung Fu is absolutely great
for people of all ages.
Brutality is just the wrong
impression of Kung Fu.
Kung Fu is an art,
a kind of indomitable spirit.
I'm looking for a good method...
...to package Shaolin Kung Fu...
...to help people understand...
...the true meaning of it.
Enough, already!
I'm not finished yet.
You're already finished.
I still have to make an appointment
with you as my client.
You're done!
Please seize this opportunity!
The lame can also learn Kung Fu.
What are you talking about?
Who's lame?
You're not qualified
to even talk soccer with me.
I'm sorry!
Yes, I'm lame.
It's none of your business.
What? Being lame?
Why you stinking...!
What the...?
Moron! Did you think
that would scare me?
Hey, do you still want the garbage?
If you don't, I'll call the other one.
I'm coming over.
Hurry up!
Did you think that would
scare me? Huh? Idiot...
Hey, hey, hey, get out of here!
Ah, excuse me! Could you give me a hand
putting this over there?
No problem!
Wow! What a leg!
- Twenty cents!
- You're kidding! Just twenty cents?
There are some cups and plates inside.
Won't you give me ten cents more?
No more!
Go on, move it over there.
Mui, would you please give me
ten steamed bread!
Using Tai Chi Kung Fu to make
steamed bread is a striking idea.
The steamed bread looks
sweet and tasty.
I'm so impressed...
...by her strong arms.
You...
What are you doing?
Singing is the perfect way...
for me to express
my true feelings about you.
You're so beautiful!
I'm not beautiful. Don't laugh at me!
Look at this! This steamed bread is incredible!
Tastes wonderful!
Your Tai Chi Kung Fu, Shifting Bodies
and Transposing Shadows...
It's a firm but gentle Kung Fu,
Shove a Thousand Cattle with Four Tales.
So!
That's why the steamed bread
is so tender yet firm.
They're fifty cents each.
Two steamed bread, that's one dollar.
- That much!
- Yes, that much.
It may be expensive,
but it's worth it.
I only have fifty cents right now.
Would you mind if I paid
you back two days later?
No...
Well! You're a typical Kung Fu master,
speaking with grace and ease.
You know, we have something in
common. I'm also a Shaolin master.
Would you allow me
a face-saving proposition?
No.
Okay!
This is a pair of precious sneakers.
The original price was two dollars.
Now, I'll give you a discount on the price...
One dollar and fifty cents,
and I'll take one more steamed bread.
- I'm going to call the police!
- Okay!
Why won't you give me a break?
Ah, you are so beautiful...
Shut up!
Stop singing, please.
Put your money down
and go away right now.
If you want to sing,
you ought to go climb up that mountain.
Only a loony would be singing over here.
I don't agree with this girl.
It's not crazy for someone to be singing here.
This is breaking out.
I've never given up my dream...
...of being a composer.
This gentleman's song is...
...so creative and enthusiastic.
Thank you!
You're welcome.
His song has touched me deeply
and draws out my enthusiasm.
Right now, I feel like I'm going to...
Explode!
Even though I'm just a butcher,
I also dream of being a dancer.
Do it!
Haven't you got anything
better to do right now?
Stand up straight! Put your hands down!
Stop scrunching your neck up!
You're all nuts!
This is no place to be dancing!
Are you out of your mind?
All I do is go out to get a facial.
I can't leave for a minute and you
turn this place upside down!
What are you screwballs doing here?
Why are you so ferocious,
shouting at everybody like that.
I came here to buy steamed bread.
Is my steamed bread ready?
Coming! Just a minute!
Did that guy pay
for the steamed bread?
He did.
What's this dirty stuff?
Throw it away!
First Big Brother!
It's okay!
Keep working. Clean it up, please!
Are you sick, First Big Brother?
I've got a headache.
I got drunk last night.
Anyway, what do you want?
I wanted to let you know
I've been awakened.
- Really? You've been awakened?
- I've been awakened.
I finally understand.
If I want to teach
Shaolin Kung Fu to the world,
I need to package it
into a new and modern form.
What kind of packaging?
Singing!
You won't believe what I saw today.
- I saw a steamed bread shop...
- Stop bothering me!
But, what would you think
if I combined Shaolin Kung Fu...
...with singing and dancing?
Don't even think about it!
How can you dismiss it like that
if you never even try it?
Stop thinking about it!
I've already told you you need to
make a living in the real world.
There's a vacancy for a toilet cleaner.
It would be good for you...
...to take it rather than
to keep living in a dream.
If we don't have any dreams in life,
we're no better than salted fish.
Yeah, well look at you, you're a real
salted fish, not even a pair of shoes!
How can you talk about dreams?
Now just hold on a minute!
The fire in my heart
isn't put out that easily!
Why not? Just blow it out!
But it'll just be lit up again!
Enough, already!
We both have our own lives.
Please don't bother me!
I need to work to support my family.
You mean you are willing
to give up your Iron Head?
Are you forgetting how much
effort you put into it?
You're wrong!
I've never given it up...
...not even for a day!
Fei!
Boss!
Dammit!
The dancers quit the show already.
What are you doing hanging around
here doing nothing about it?
I'm not! I have a great idea.
What's that?
Uh, combining Shaolin Kung Fu
with singing and dancing.
What kind of Shaolin Kung Fu?
Look at this!
There's no way that's gonna sell.
He's good enough.
No way! And what about you?
Me?
Dammit!
What about your Iron Head?
If you don't do a good job,
I'll kill you tomorrow.
OK.
First Big Brother, thank you!
Shaolin Kung Fu is great!
Really great!
Shaolin Kung Fu is wonderful!
Wonderful!
I'm Iron Head.
Iron Head.
You're Mighty Steel Leg.
I'm Mighty Steel Leg.
Be serious!
Shaolin Kung Fu is great!
Really great!
Shaolin Kung Fu is wonderful!
Wonderful!
I'm Mighty Steel Leg!
Mighty Steel Leg!
He's Iron Head!
Ahh, I'm gonna die!
What are you singing about?
You sound like you're howling.
The lyrics are pathetic.
I can't understand
a thing you're saying.
That's right. Who wrote this garbage?
- Yeah, who did it?
- Who did it?
Creative work is highly subjective,
but I must respond to your criticism.
The singing is just
the beginning of the show,
the climax is the performance of
Mighty Steel Leg and Iron Head!
Iron Head?
I told you already
that you wrote awful lyrics.
I'm not Iron Head. He's...
Iron Head?
- I said...
- Iron Head?
Mighty Steel Leg!
He's Mighty Steel Leg!
You're still saying
Mighty Steel Leg?
I oughta kill you!
Mighty Steel Leg!
I'm the real Mighty Steel Leg!
Iron Head?
Don't you understand
Chinese? He's the real...
Iron Head?
You're so stubborn!
Iron...
Do you want to start a fight?
Thank you so much!
Happy hour is going fast.
It's time for us
to say goodbye right now.
Let's listen to some music!
You guys are crazy!
Let's see if you can take some more!
Thank you!
Why you stinking...!
What on earth?
Let's go! There's nothing interesting here!
Do you still want to fight with us?
I promised my Shaolin master I wouldn't
use Kung Fu to fight with anyone.
This guy is crazy.
But all you guys should apologize!
Apologize?
It's not our problem.
This was all your fault!
Don't move! You said you wouldn't
use Kung Fu to hit anyone!
I didn't come here to fight.
I came to play soccer.
That's it, I'm gonna kick your...
Hey, get up, quit goofing around!
What's he...?
Stop, please! I'm so sorry!
Do you have any money on you?
Yeah.
Thirty cents.
Hey, are you taking my money?
Yes, I am.
Did you study Tong Long Fist?
I did.
Don't be an embarrassment to
Shaolin Kung Fu anymore!
Would you let me
take a look at your leg?
I'm not really in the mood.
But go ahead.
Amazing! It's the real thing,
pure Kung Fu.
A great killer slim leg.
It's Shaolin Mighty Steel Leg!
Could it be possible to use
Kung Fu to play soccer?
Are you serious?
Yes, of course!
That's it!
That's a great idea,
use Kung Fu to play soccer.
Why didn't I ever think of that?
Aren't you that cripple?
I'm not just a cripple,
I'm the ex-soccer player, Golden Leg.
Now, I'm a soccer coach.
That's great!
You can teach me how to play soccer.
Now, hold on.
No! You told me I could use
Kung Fu to play soccer.
But I need some time to think this over!
I don't have time to think anymore!
It's afternoon already!
Time doesn't wait for anyone!
But we have so much to prepare!
I'm ready! What do I need?
At least a pair of shoes!
Do you have any money
to get your sneakers back?
No. But...
I threw them away.
Threw them away!?!
Your sneakers were broken.
They're well worn.
- Yes, they were broken. But I...
- Go home!
My boss will shout at you
if she comes back and sees you.
Wait!
You can't have the broken ones back.
Those have been fixed.
Do you want to have them?
First Big Brother, what are you doing?
First Big Brother, are you okay?
I'm fine.
What do you want?
I finally got a great idea
for sharing Shaolin Kung Fu.
It's playing soccer!
Please let me go!
You've already gotten me into trouble.
I got fired.
Now, I have to clean rest rooms
to pay for my boss's loss.
I've come here to help you.
No! Absolutely not!
If you bother me anymore,
my whole family will commit suicide
in front of you.
Committing suicide isn't a good way
to solve any problems.
Be brave!
Don't be stupid!
I'm just a loser!
Please don't come here anymore!
If you still want to form a soccer team,
you can ask the other Brothers.
Please, don't bother me!
I beg you!
Iron Head.
Good morning, Fourth Big Brother!
Good morning, Sing!
How are you?
Let me introduce a great guy to you! He's...
Nice to meet you!
This is Fung.
I know, Fung is famous
in the stock exchange market.
You see!
He has that great I.T. Look.
Fung is a soccer coach.
Soccer coach!
Of course, everyone knows
that Fung is the most...
...famous figure in the soccer world.
Do you use your legs to play soccer?
You see! I'm right.
Actually, do you have any jobs?
I want you to join my soccer team.
Play soccer?
I haven't had a job for six months.
How can you ask me to play soccer?
If you can use your Empty Hand...
...to be the goalkeeper...
What's Empty Hand?
That was years ago.
You know,
I even forgot when our Master died.
Please listen to me!
We're going to sign up for
the National Soccer Tournament.
The prize is one million dollars.
Really?
So, I see you're the sharp one.
Look at that!
All dressed up and everything.
Many years ago, our Master
ordered us to share Shaolin Kung Fu.
Now, you guys get this great idea
of using Shaolin Kung Fu...
...to play soccer!?!
Look here!
This is a group picture
of our Master and Brothers.
I always keep it UNDER my pillow.
You should know what I mean.
Great! Let's sit down
to talk about what you mean.
I'll call you if I've got time.
Oh, and remember to find a job for me.
I really don't have time to talk to you.
Some clients are waiting for me, I need
to keep my eyes on the stock market.
You know, each of my trades are
hundreds of thousands of dollars apiece.
Hello! What's the price right now?
My driver is on leave today.
And I just loaned my car to my friend,
and I left my wallet in my office.
I'm sorry! I don't have time
to have lunch with you guys.
I'm really busy!
Go away!
Third Big Brother, think about it!
If you can use Iron Shirt...
...to be the back...
What's Iron Shirt?
Look around! The sky
is full of planes.
The streets are full of computers.
It's the 21st century.
Stop living in your dream world!
Well, I think it's a good idea,
combining Kung Fu with soccer.
He's right! And the prize
is a huge amount of money.
For heaven's sake! You think I'm...
I'm trading hundreds of
thousands of dollars a day.
There's absolutely no way I'm giving up
my trading to play soccer with you guys.
I'm sorry for being
so direct, you know...
But it'd be impossible to give up
my trading and sign up to play
soccer with you lame-o's.
Forgive me. I'm just an honest guy.
Finally, it's also impossible for me
to win any damn soccer game.
Truly, the probability of winning is 0%.
Probabi...
Probability!
Okay...
See this? It's always heads or tails.
You'll never get the middle.
So the probability is 0%.
Let me try!
Get lost!
I've got an appointment
with my client at the coffee shop.
I'm very busy!
We could take you out for
noodles at the same shop.
Morons! I'm dealing with
hundreds of thousands of dollars!
How can I go have noodles
with you guys?
He's my Sixth Small Brother, Weight Vest.
This is the famous soccer coach, Fung.
Fung, how are you?
Uh, what Vest?
Weight Vest.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Vest.
Fifth Big Brother, are you thinking
about playing soccer?
Yes.
If you can use Shaolin Kung Fu
Weight Vest to be the forward with me,
Our attack should be flawless.
- Do you have confidence in this?
- Of course.
Great! Are there any
diet pills around here?
It's useless.
Since this virus got into my head,
there's no way for me to lose any weight.
Since becoming like this,
I can't even walk quickly,
let alone be able to use
Shaolin Kung Fu Weight Vest.
Yeah, you're a little overweight,
but that's not so important.
Forget it!
See, this is a picture
of how I used to look!
Since becoming like this,
I can't even get a date with a girl.
You don't understand how it is.
I do. I can't date girls either!
Really?
Why? Too much gossip about
your girls in newspapers and magazines?
What kind of newspapers and magazines?
Oh! I'm sorry!
Since I've had this disease,
I can't control myself.
I'm sorry. Please leave me alone!
Small Brother!
You should have confidence!
You can do it!
Everyone calls me Lazy Pig now...
You know, you're the only one
who calls me Small Brother.
Thank you!
Lazy Pig, help me get that
package of red tissue rolls.
The red one!
Playing soccer?
Yes, Second Big Brother!
If you can use
Hooking Leg to be the back,
I believe...
Your defense will be flawless!
Absolutely!
So you think I can
still use Hooking Leg?
Sure, you just need some practice.
If you trust yourself,
you will get your Hooking Leg back.
Really?
I just saw you
cleaning sewers recently.
Why did you get a second
job washing dishes?
Why?
Why are you asking me that?
I don't understand, either.
Why didn't I have a rich father,
Lee Ka Sing?
Why am I going bald,
even though I'm so handsome?
You guys aren't going bald,
but you're so ugly.
Why did the other guys get to
go to school when they were young?
While I was forced
to study Shaolin Kung Fu,
and then become a cleaner,
washing dishes,
and cleaning out sewers?
Calm down! Second Big Brother.
If you're brave enough,
you can control your fate.
Calm down? If I wasn't so calm,
I'd kill you guys!
Calm down?
Why are you just sitting here?
Can't you see how bad
it smells in here?
If it still stinks when I come back,
you'll be cleaning up with your tongue!
Your apartment is great!
It's well furnished.
I can't believe you work
as the cleaner downstairs,
but live in the Penthouse
on the 59th floor.
You've got good taste!
This kind of apartment is so popular
I can't even get one.
The exhaust is okay.
Just a little bit noisy.
Would you mind if I move in here?
Forget it!
Your Brothers aren't that great.
We can find others to join our team.
It was all my fault.
I couldn't persuade them.
It's okay.
You know, I'm so glad that you trust me.
Thank you.
I'm going to train you guys
in the shortest time possible
...to be professional soccer players.
So you need to be serious
and mutually support each other.
I understand!
Let's go!
Please listen to me!
What would you do if
you were in my position?
Yes, of course.
I've got to call.
Hold on a second.
The ball is coming back!
So! Finally willing
to come back, are you?
- You made us wait for an hour
- Wait for an hour!
What are you doing?
Playing soccer!
The ball is over there!
You, come here!
Let me see you kick the ball from here.
But the ball is over there.
Yes, the ball is over there!
You can't even get the ball.
How are you going to kick it from here?
Listen up, there are four
basic skills to playing soccer:
Pass, stop, hold and kick.
- I understand!
- Don't move!
Okay. Let's start from the beginning.
Yours.
Hold it!
Watch out!
Concentrate!
Come on! Move!
That's it... do more fakes.
That's better.
That looks like a good fake.
Do more fakes.
Fung, why can't I
participate in the training?
Look, even though your
leg's so strong,
you haven't got any control.
What happens if you...
kick the ball up into the sky...
and it hits a plane?
Could you pay for it?
- No.
- So...
Sixth Small Brother!
I'm borrowing your eggs!
What?
If you can control the egg freely
in the air, you can play soccer.
- No problem!
- Okay!
You see? It's not that easy.
Sixth Small Brother,
what are you doing!
Oh, no! My egg!
Look, I'll get you another one later!
No way!
Give it back to me!
Concentrate...
My egg!
OK! Yes!
Yes! OK!
Yours!
Right...
Good...
Yes! Go!
Keep your eye on the ball!
Watch out!
How can you let him
kick it like that?
Kick it!
Come on!
That's incredible!
He could play all by himself.
No! It's about teamwork.
You can't play soccer with just yourself.
The game will be 30 minutes.
There are no breaks.
We'll follow the international rules.
I'm the referee.
Do you have any questions?
Of course not. You know how grateful
we are that Golden Leg is the referee
and is leading a young soccer
team to play against us.
We're just happy to be here!
Say hi to Master Fung!
- Hello Master Fung!
Okay...
Well, this guy has some issues
with your team's players.
Now, this game is a demonstration
of our soccer playing skills.
We'll use it to resolve this conflict.
Ah, we see! They look very intent.
From their tidy uniforms
and friendly faces,
I can feel deeply their sincerity
and the strength of their spirit.
Thank you!
It's okay, nothing to worry about.
I'm an auto mechanic.
I use this crescent wrench
to screw things down.
You understand, don't you?
Yes, of course.
Ah, as I already explained,
the reason I have a hammer,
is because I'm an auto mechanic.
Okay, okay. Your team's style...
...is infamous in
the amateur soccer world.
I understand.
Well, it's just an undeserved reputation.
Looks like the sky's getting cloudy...
Okay. Anyway, take care of yourselves.
Shake hands, please!
Pass it!
Help!
Third Big Brother!
Calling military headquarters, we
just suffered an overwhelming attack.
Send for reinforcements!
Stand up.
Stand up!
Get up quickly!
Come on, get up!
What are you doing?
Coach, they're lawless.
Why don't you stop them?
I'm the referee.
I'm not supposed to stop them.
What's the meaning of this?
Do you want us to sacrifice ourselves?
Alright, you! Out!
Are you nuts?
This is a test.
If you guys can't pass it,
there's no way you're
playing soccer again!
We're just playing soccer.
We're not fighting a battle.
Real soccer games are battles.
I surrender!
If you had the guts
to ask us to play,
why do you want to surrender?
Are you trying to mess with me?
I can't take it anymore.
My bones feel broken.
I'm a pitiful creature!
Please let me go see a doctor!
Put it on your head!
Look at you. You look like a dog.
Don't you have any self-respect?
I don't want to see your face again.
Put it on your head quickly
and go see your doctor.
Yes, I'm a dog.
I don't have any self-respect.
First Big Brother is coming back.
What are you talking about?
I can feel their Kung Fu coming back.
- Do we have any weapons left?
- Not anymore!
Okay then, Final Attack!
Oh, for crying out loud! I missed it!
Help!
Thank you, Brother! You made
us get our Kung Fu back.
Thank you for coming back!
Thank you!