Stop, you are not capable
to defeat them.
Brother Koo, are we going to
take her along with us?
Cut the crap.
Those who are hurt by
Asia the Invincible,
Are all our friends.
We can't defeat them by kung-fu,
let's use the cannon.
If you do so, we will die together.
A part of this ship has been...
destroyed by Asia the Invincible.
If we try to attack each other
by the cannon...
the ship will be sunned,
all of us will die.
Brother Koo,
the cannon has no blast wire.
Save your crocodile tears,
this ship can't stay any longer.
As we just want to survive.
Give us Snow, then we'll let you go.
Right, Highlanders are Highlanders,
Hans are Hans.
We're of different world.
Give us Snow, then we'll let you go.
Have you forgotten...
how Snow treated you?
For this sinner.
Don't you think
it's worth dying with us?
Ching, don't let the wind
extinguish the fire.
Sir, this ship has run aground,
if we delay anymore,
we will be sunk with this ship.
Ling, in such as emergency,
how can you talk like this?
What do you mean?
No, I don't want to die like this.
You have internal conflicts
among yourselves.
You are not as united as us.
Sir, I don't want to rescuer her.
Please let me go!
To betray us at such critical moment?
You are not my subordinate.
Go now.
Thank you, Sir!
Come and join us.
He knew our drawbacks.
So I have to do so,
please forgive me.
Ching, in order to save an enemy.
We have to kill our man,
What's that are we going
to rescue or kill?
Brother Koo, what's the matter?
Brother Koo. You...
I think, your valves are closed
by a supreme kung-fu master.
The blood is flowing backward.
You are seriously hurt,
you are dying!
Yes, I am hurt by
Asia the Invincible.
We are dying too.
Since you cannot protect yourself,
why should you save me?
It's me who leaded him here.
I have to bear all responsibilities.
When the sun rises from the East.
That'll be the end of your life.
That's why...
I time the time left.
The noise.
Shit, it's the Spanish warship.
The Spanish warship is approaching.
Where is it?
They come for...
Asia the Invincible.
We hand the flag
of our Sun Moon Sect.
They will shoot us
once they see the flag!
Don't listen to him,
don't listen to him.
What are you waiting?
Lower the sail.
Face them with the cannon.
You are the courtier of the gov't,
don't cheat me with such trick.
Why should I cheat you?
- Ching, lower the sail.
- Don't move!
Or I will fire you!
Ching, go now.
Ching, it's peaceful around.
Luckily we haven't met
another warship.
Brother Koo,
when will this woman leave us?
Just throw me into the sea.
Brother Koo.
Stop helping me.
Will you call me dog again?
Unless you take off this dog's clothe,
or you'll be dog forever.
Go on insulting me if you feel great.
Hold it.
Stop thinking anything nonsense,
Asia the Invincible will not come back.
I know you must hate him.
I am just worrying about him.
He is fooled by fate,
he can't escape.
If I were Asia the Invincible.
I won't leave you.
Ching, when will we reach the camps?
According to the speed
of the current.
We can reach the camps after 6 hours.
Wear it, I am Asia the Invincible.
Boss, she sings better than you.
Give way!
Damn you, where do you come from?
Do you want to take
the bread out of our mouths?
Are you the one
who gives order here?
You want to challenge me?
Not necessary, tonight,
I will listen to you.
Where are the pretty girls?
Stop bothering me.
Are your boss looking for me?
I do want it, so what?
You are not qualified to touch me.
Damn it!
Do you think that you are protected,
so you don't even respect me!
I tell you, we wanderers are nasty.
Today, you are the boss,
tomorrow I will be the boss.
She is sick, let me serve your boss.
Get up.
Breathless? He is breathless.
Kidding?
Gut up, wake up.
How are you, Master?
Mo Yan Lu Choung.
If you want to take them away,
gamble with me.
If you win, you may take them away.
I think you two
are great kung-fu masters.
But, this is such a small bet.
Why not make it bigger?
What?
The winner can take us away,
The bet is too simple.
Why not cut the legs
off from the loser?
You want to add
a pair of legs for gambling?
What? Are you scared?
Okay. I won't give it a damn.
Just go ahead.
it depends on fate.
What do you want to bet?
Big or small?
Small!
How about you?
Big!
Fine!
No need to open it. I am the winner.
I have to open it.
The dead won't argue with me.
I am still here.
The loser should pay his legs.
Open, 4,5,6. Big.
You lost.
Don't offend him.
Cut your legs off.
How dare you!
General Mo Yan Lu Chong,
we will follow you.
Please let her go.
She doesn't know the rules.
All of you go back,
take her to see me tonight.
Yes.
General...
Mo Yan Lu Chong.
Don't think that
it's an ordinary bet.
Some one will come to take your legs.
Go.
I haven't known your name yet.
I am the same as you,
we have no names.
The people are heartless
and they claimed me heartless.
I am sorry to drag you down.
I should have to thank you.
It's you who let me know that.
It's painful to be
an ordinary people.
Who are you?
Me?
About the answer of it...
I do want to know too
Help yourself!
Mo Yan Lu Chong, long time no see.
Asia the Invincible, here you are.
After you had visited
the Black Cliff 3 years ago.
I wrote to Japan
to check which generation...
you are of the
Mo Yan Lu Chong Family.
Asia the Invincible,
you are very smart.
Oh! How come?
I had told you...
that someone would
come for your legs.
You've known my background already.
Right! Because all the troops of the
real Mo Yan Lu Chong were destroyed.
Since the 4th generation of...
Mo Yan Lu Chong Family has been
taken over by Liu Seng already.
Watch my Mo Yan Sword.
Cut!
Ninja Disappearance!
- It's your real face.
- Thunder Bomb!
Ninjas come out!
Poison liquid.
You're also a great Kung-fu master.
Why do you pretend
to be Mo Yan Lu Chong?
What a pity! Actually,
you are a miserable as I do.
You dare not show others
your real face.
Sir, are you alright?
I'm fine, go out.
Yes.
"Commander of Ming Dynasty Navy"
Why there isn't any guard?
Go in and take a look!
I've caught it, I've caught it!
it is still yelling!
Here comes Officer Koo.
Where is Officer Tin?
Officer Tin? He hasn't waken up yet.
Still haven't got up
to inspect the military affairs yet.
Being navy officers of Ming Dynasty,
all of you are badly disciplined.
You come here to settle the riot.
You are such a mess.
How can you fight with the enemas?
Keep on insulting.
I don't mind giving a lecture
to your damn soldiers.
How would you tackle
your foes when they come?
Yes Sir.
Greet. It's great!
- Brother Koo.
- Brother Kai Wan.
Brother Koo.
Your camp is loosely guarded,
don't you afraid of
any attack from the foes?
How come! There are so many foes.
All of us just want to live.
Not many people like fighting.
Brother Kai Wan.
May I know your good name?
Get us 2 jars of Kaoliang, hurry up.
Coming, don't be in such a hurry.
Making you drunk.
Get us the main course.
Get me some more wine.
There are many advantages
of being a soldier.
When you hunt, you will get
supply of guns from the Court.
There are chefs from the Court
who take care of our meals.
I treasure my fortune,
so I enjoy sharing nice things
with my bosom friends.
come, have a cup of wine with us.
Brother Kai Wan.
You bastard.
How adore you scold me?
General...
There is something wrong
in the Western yard.
- What's happening?
- No information right now.
- Assembly!
- General!
General.
Here comes Asia the Invincible.
All our soldiers have been injured.
General, Asia the Invincible
is so cruel that,
the soldiers of our two battalions
were seriously injured.
So powerful? Let me handle him.
- The force of Battalion 7 follow me.
- Yes, Sir.
it is the one in red.
I want to compete with you.
Move faster. Protect His Excellency.
Protect His Excellency.
Brother Koo.
Chin, if something
happened unexpectedly,.
You would have to leave here at once.
Brother Kai wan.
Officer Koo,
which part you've got hurt?
Brother Kai Wan, cheer up...
Brother Kai Wan...
It's funny. It's really very funny.
Our camp is the happiest one.
We haven't enjoyed
such a game for a long time.
It's rare for us having visitors.
Brother Koo, it's a funny game.
I'm afraid that you have never
got such a chance to play.
Brother Koo, don't you believe
there is Asia the Invincible?
Of course, there is an
Asia the Invincible.
Call our Asia the Invincible out.
Asia the Invincible...
Asia the Invincible?
See, our Asia the Invincible
is not so bad.
Officer Tin and all officers!
Asia the Invincible,
the most prominent among
the brothels of the 13 provinces.
They're all bought by me.
Asia the Invincible is just a name.
I can call myself
Asia the Invincible too.
Come on, call one.
Versatility, a full unity
of the world of martial arts.
Hurrah, General Tin!
Sing a song, with bureaucratic tone
"Versatility, a full unity
of the world of martial arts,"
"Asia the Invincible."
"Hurrah! Hurrah, General Tin!"
Sing like this, then I will leave
a good reputation for generations
I also know the Kung-fu of
Asia the Invincible's flying needles.
Let me show you.
Bingo!
Good! I'm great!
- Snow!
- What?
Tin.
I just want to check her wound.
She is my woman.
I won't let anyone touch her.
Yes, it's not decent
to fool other's wife.
She is seriously hurt.
Here is not a good place,
you had better
take a rest in my camp.
It's not convenient for us
to stay in the camp with you.
Not easy?
Let me go out,
so you can sleep with her.
- Man!
- Yes.
- Take these two guests for a rest.
it seems to me that
I can only sleep...
with my Asia the invincible tonight.
Am I your woman?
Light more!
It's funny!
How wonderful is it.
Give me the wine.
Oh shit! Asia the Invincible?
Versatility, a full unity
of the world of Martial Arts!
Unbeaten! General Tin!
Brother Koo.
Brother Kai Wan, something a
gentleman should do but something not.
We should not argue for a woman!
We can do nothing
once get involved in a war.
Koo, you said I was your woman.
Now, how can you settle it?
Well... Take care of yourself.
He asked me to take care of myself.
We'll, let's take care.
Go to the camp now.
Okay.
But I've to dress up as
Asia the Invincible first.
You want to be Asia the Invincible?
Good!
I've stop your valve remotely.
I don't want you to pretend
to Asia the invincible anymore,
so I must take you away.
You lie down so quickly!
My dear Asia the Invincible!
Bingo!
Dismiss!
- Bingo!
- Dismiss.
Bingo!
Shit! You're touched
my laughing valve!
Watch out!
Go away!
Can't you see that I am
playing games with General Tin?
Help me.
Dismiss!
Bingo!
Your laughing valve
is attacked again.
Brother Tin, Brother Tin, hold on.
It's nonsense,
let's play something else.
You listen,
we'll play something else.
We'll rehearse the declaration of
war on Asia the Invincible tomorrow.
But you'd better call me
Asia the Invincible now.
Versatility, a full unity of
the world of Martial Arts! Come on!
the world of Martial Arts!
Unbeaten! Asia the Invincible!
Officer Koo, Hurrah! Hurrah!
Versatility, a full unity of
the world of Martial Arts.
Unbeaten! Asia the Invincible!
Officer Koo, Hurrah! Hurrah! Hurrah!
We can't escape from the war.
Even we're going to die. I want to
die by the side of Asia the Invincible.
Thank you for let me go.
Snow, you go and look for
Asia the Invincible now.
But, I don't want to
see you again in the battlefield.
What's the matter?
Chin, are you crazy?
I don't want you to become
another Asia the invincible.
When I am lonely.
I hope a fried to accompany me.
We can get him back to Black Cliff.
Then we should
find ways to defeat her.
The Spanish, are you still
looking for the Sacred Scroll?
Who are you?
Do you know
where's the Sacred Scroll?
You've asked the correct person!
I am Asia the Invincible.
Asia the Invincible?
You are powerful because of this?
Your science. Is shit.
Armour?
What power did your God give you?
This is our holy cup.
Your God is useless!
Kneel down!
Your Bible should be re-written.
From now on.
The God mentioned
in your western Bible...
Should be re-written
as Asia the Invincible.
Come on, let's in prayer.
Holy Asia the Invincible,
Holy Asia the Invincible.
Hand the flag of the
Sun Moon Sect at the bow.
- Keep on temping Asia the Invincible.
- Yes, Sir!
Anything special?
Nothing.
General Mo Yan Lu Chong, Liu Seng
And all other Japanese ninjas.
We are get ready to fight.
Let's go!
Today, I want to show you something,
which you've never seen before,
that's my real face.
Look!
Are you surprised?
Can you imagine the
invincible General Mo Yan Lu Chong,
is a hooker in the camp
of the wanderers?
You must be having some bad feeling.
Since you have been
deceived for a long time.
You don't know...
who is the master behind.
Let me tell you.
The real name of Mo Yan Lu Chong
is Asia the Invincible.
I have got the military order.
Who goes against me should be killed.
Attention.
Let's go ahead.
We'll join with the Spanish warship...
to unite the world.
Since the people can't forget me.
I'll lead the troops
to declare war again.
I will change my name to
"Asia and Europe the Invincible".
- Raise the banner.
- Yes!
"Asia and Europe the invincible"
Sir, a warship is found ahead.
This is the Mo Yan
warship of the Japanese.
Sir,
the Japanese and the Spanish warship
raised their banners.
They declare war on us.
What?
It's strange, why do the
Japanese and the Spanish...
declare war on us?
Raise our flag and declare war.
"Koo"
Fire.
Report, Koo's banner is hanging on
the warship of Ming Dynasty.
Fire to them to show our trench!
Declare war now.
Koo's banner.
It's Koo!
Instruct the Spanish warship
to attack the warship of Ming Dynasty.
- Check the ship!
- Yes!
Koo, you are great!
Fine, let's sink into the water.
Sir,
the Japanese ship
disappears suddenly.
It's a submarine.
Bet there is much undercurrent here.
If they sail below the sea,
their route will be hindered.
That's what I want.
Pour the paint into the water
to disturb their view.
Yes. Execute now!
Sir, our route is hindered
by the submerged rocks.
The Ming Dynasty Navy
poured the paints into the sea.
Visibility is poor, we can't move.
You want to trap us
at the bottom of the sea?
Fine, bomb the submerged rocks
with the mine.
Yes.
Report, the Spanish warship
is approaching us in full speed.
it seems that they want to crash
against us, please give instruction.
- Lower the sail.
- Lower the sail in full speed.
Yes!
Lower the sail.
Get ready the war.
Koo, you have been
exhausted in the fighting.
Asia the Invincible
hasn't shown up yet.
Chin, I tell you.
The wish of everybody,
is to meet the strongest enemy
before his death.
If he were the leader of the enemy.
It's too early to say
who'll be the winner.
Report,
the body of the ship is damaged.
We'd emerge from the sea at once.
Koo must be waiting for me.
Well, let's go up.
Asia the Invincible!
Focus the top of their sail.
Asia the Invincible,
you show up eventually.
Get ready the cannon!
Asia the Invincible?
But you are not better than me
at leading the troops.
You've got the magic power
from "Sacred Scroll".
Although this is
your personal achievement,
it can't make you
achieve great success.
That's why your troops didn't attack,
but were destroyed
at the Black Cliff.
Bull shit!
My failure was caused
by my foe whom I admired.
I didn't want to hurt him,
thus I pretended that
I was kill Dundee the cliff.
Last time, you could escape
because of the "Sacred Scroll".
Now, the history is repeated.
If you had not had the luck
to adopt the "Sacred Scroll",
you'd not have escaped
from my attack.
You're qualified to be
a great martial arts master only.
But being a king or a great general,
You are not qualified
to be named a sassier the Invincible.
I want to be king, I have to recruit
a great general first.
I want you to be my general,
so I will show you my power.
If I had practiced the Sacred Scroll.
You'd not have defeated me.
Anyway, our fight
should have been over.
You're wrong!
Our fight has not been over yet.
Give it to me.
It's too easy to defeat you.
Your 14 valves
are both live and dead.
Let me open your closed valves.
Your Kung fu will be improved greatly,
so you are able to fight with me.
Koo, watch it.
Snow, I said...
I didn't hope to see you
in the battlefield again.
I want to see Asia the Invincible.
Snow!
Snow, I will save you.
Only Asia the invincible can save me.
Snow, come back to me now.
Holy Master.
Do you think it's worth doing it?
I have waited for this moment.
I know you come for me.
Koo, get lost.
Koo, return Snow to me.
I won't return her to you.
Come to get her yourself.
Asia the Invincible,
you are always alone.
Why do you follow me?
Don't go!
Snow, no matter how,
I have to take you back.
But what a pity that,
you could never hear what he said.
Otherwise, you'd be very happy.
Hand her to me.
Asia the Invincible,
it's useless for anything you said.
She could never hear you.
You are lying!
You have never trusted anybody.
You've made it.
But you have got no one
to stay with you.
Asia the Invincible, you always
want to search for yourself.
Actually, what you have done,
either good or bad, that's you.
I don't need you to tell me.
What a pity that, you are always
making remedy to what you've lost.
But, you never treasure
the things you've gained.
I want you to lose
what you have gained.
Well, but I want her back now.
Snow. Let's start
from the very beginning.
Asia the Invincible.