Let me introduce you.
My assistant, Lakeisha.
How are you?
You speak Mandarin? Great!
She only speaks a little.
Let's go.
I am so happy!
Let's get out of here!
Miki, get up here!
They're coming after us!
Hurry!
They're directly behind us!
Hold it!
Jackie, help me!
Forget the luggage.
At least we're safe.
You are shaking.
I thought we were going to die.
What have you done to them?
I didn't do anything!
Really nothing!
She didn't mean it.
Does this happen often here?
Only today!
Now wait a minute!
I promise we won't see her again!
That's the way out?
Yes!
Don't be scared!
Are you alright?
Miki, are you ok?
What have I done to deserve this?
I should cheer up for Jackie.
What are you doing?
Washing dishes.
I need to buy something.
Now?
It's been all crazy since I arrived.
I need at least some underwear.
Sorry, but all shops are closed now.
She said...
I know!
That mine are small!
No, she said she has clothes that fit your size.
I heard the word "small"!
My English is poor but I understand the word "small".
Hers are not very big either.
She did use the word small,
but not referring to yours!
It's allright now.
Sorry for all the trouble.
Forgive me.
It was really an unforgettable day.
Let's have some fun tomorrow.
Thanks,
but I've had enough "fun" today.
I came here for one thing.
I know.
Really?
Yes.
The clothes here are beautiful.
What?
Aren't you here to buy clothes?
Shut up!
Jackie, help me!
Jackie, get out!