Distributor
Leonard K. C. Ho
Producer
Chan Pui Wah
Production & Art Direction
Chan Che Wei
Action Consultants
Lau Kar Leung, Corey Yuen
Action Director
Yuen Tak
Screenplay
Chan Che Wei, Barry Wong, Lui Sau Pung
Photography
Wong Bo Man, Tsang Che Chung
Original Music
Ms Lam
Leading roles
Chin Kar Lok, Liu Chia Liang, May Lo
Special Guest
Yuen Jung
Cast
Woo Fung, Victor Hon, David Lo,
Frankie Chan, Yuen Shun-Yi,
Lau Yuk Ting, Lau Sek Yin
Director
David Lai
Sell your daughter
if you can't pay.
"DEBT"
Take her away.
Don't!
Go!
You're free now.
Go.
Fai Yuk-Su... Stand up.
That slap was a
present from Lincoln.
And this is from Shakespeare!
We're discussing famous quotations.
And what are you doing?
Drawing cartoons.
"Windblown Grass"? "Cloudy Skies"?
"Seeking A Failure Strategy"?
Can you afford to fail?
You think you're a genius
so you don't have to study.
Mozart was a genius. At six years old,
he performed in front of the emperor.
But you?
You're so slow!
You! Next time I catch you
doing this, I'll expel you.
Give them back!
Hey,
give them back.
- Give me back my drawings.
- Here you go.
I don't even know what you drew.
Only one fist and one foot?
A comic book is supposed to be
like this, crazy!
Wow, great.
Fantastic.
Really great.
Yeah? I think he's going to kill me.
I made him so angry.
No. I mean the whirlwind kick you
drew. Nothing could beat that.
No more bullying the weak!
Catch!
I've warned you before
about using the basketball court.
You know the school team
needs to practise,
but you're still using our space.
Haven't you been beaten enough?
You're just a bully!
Get off.
Come on.
If we don't leave now,
we're going to die.
Let's go!
Stop! Stop!
Master, come home now
or your father will scold me.
You go on ahead. Don't follow me.
Go home.
I asked Mui to make you soup.
If it gets cold it won't taste as good.
Please come home
and do your homework.
- Why do you still keep a maid?
- I discussed it with my dad.
He says it's inappropriate for
a gentleman not to have one.
You have her follow you all day.
- Don't you have a conscience?
- No, you're wrong.
Even though she's my maid,
she's more of a nag than my mother.
- Go and do your homework.
- Okay.
- Dad, I'm home from school.
- Uncle.
Yuk-Su. You didn't burn incense
for your late mother.
- I'll go and do it now.
- You're so forgetful!
What happened to you?
Been in a fight again?
You've got a black eye.
If your father...
- You can rinse now.
- Thanks, Uncle.
Yuk-Su, bring water
to wash his hair.
Won't be a minute...
Uncle Chai,
I'll do it myself.
What are you up to?
You...
Fai Yuk-Su!
You bad boy.
Had another fight?
- You should be studying!
- Uncle...
It wasn't his fault.
I was being bullied.
He stood up for me.
If you don't get in
to medical school,
your dear mother
will turn in her grave.
Does it hurt?
- It's okay.
- Let me see.
You call that okay?!
- Master, so you are here!
- Put on my blazer.
Are you giving it to him?
Your father will be angry with me...
Mind your own business!
Master, please come home now.
Your father will hit me if you don't.
Come on,
please.
Yuk-Su, I'm off.
See you, Uncle.
- Take this off first.
- Come on.
Let me wipe the hair off your clothes.
Wait for me!
- You two want to earn extra cash?
- Yes.
It's getting dark.
Quickly, follow me.
Okay.
Inspector Wa, today we'll be
working on your diction.
Repeat after me.
Listen:
And again...
- Trying to kill me?
- Inspector Wa.
Are you all right?
Little bitch. You do this every time!
No food for you.
- It won't happen again.
- No food for three days.
What have you done again?
Hey, move on,
you.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Apologies.
Hey, Siu-Yu, you haven't poured
the Master's tea yet.
Coming.
Inspector Wa,
this is for you.
The Sandakan matter
has not been settled yet, has it?
What do you think?
It's not settled?
No.
Master,
your Ginseng tea.
Your tea, sir.
Out!
You've been keeping
that one from me.
You like her?
Tin, give her to
Mr Wong tomorrow.
Good evening, Mr Sandakan.
This way, please.
Inspector Wa's been
waiting for you a long time.
Please come in.
Merry Christmas.
A local gift for you.
Mmm...
how fragrant.
Are you scared?
Done something wrong?
This gun is very old
but won't misfire.
This is especially for you.
Here's to working well together.
But if I see this bastard again,
I won't be so polite.
I asked for 40 girls from you
in our last deal
and only 20 showed up on board.
That's not possible. The paperwork
showed 40 fingerprints.
We even watched them embark.
Perhaps that bastard
stole them from me.
You stole them?
You come to me
because you lost some goods?
Would you come to me
if you lost your wife?
Scum!
Why are you being
so rude to my dad?
I don't need my hands. One kick
and I'll tear your head off.
You touch one hair on my father's
head, you'll pay with one of your legs.
Very good.
- Men!
- Yes?
Take them outside.
Good!
Come with me.
You've got to leave. Your master's
going to give you away to Mr Wong.
Go on home.
Hey,
where are you going?
Believe me.
I'm telling you the truth.
- Let go of me.
- Siu-Yu! Siu-Yu!
Coming,
coming...
Ah, Siu-Yu! Come,
come, come...
You don't have to work any more.
Pack your things.
Tomorrow we're sending you
to Mr Wong.
What for?
To enjoy the good life.
How's about a kiss?
Come on...
Come on!
Quickly!
Stop them!
They're getting away.
Hurry up so you can catch them!
Where are they?
They're there!
It's them!
Stop! Stop!
Want to elope?
- Yuk-Su, what are you doing here?
- Huh?
Little punk!
Hey, guys...
Hey, hey...
- Headmaster, you know him?
- He's one of my students.
- What's going on?
- He tried to steal our maid.
- And he's one of his students.
- From now on, he's expelled.
Yuk-Su! Yuk-Su!
Why are you beating my son?
That's enough.
He's the headmaster's student.
Don't stop on my behalf. Our school
doesn't have students like this.
Fai Yuk-Su, as from tomorrow,
do not come back to school.
You've insulted our school.
Headmaster.
Give him a chance?
It's okay.
Siu-Yu can't have gone far.
Get her back.
And let them go.
- Give him a chance. Please.
- Go! Go!
- Headmaster!
Father.
Let's go!
Follow them!
Father,
I'll carry you.
- Help!
- Use strength! Use strength!
Help! Help!
Please open the gate!
Quickly, open the gate!
Help! Help!
People are chasing us.
I'm going in to get them.
- You want in? We can't allow that.
- Don't stand in our way.
Let's rush them!
They ran inside,
but they won't let us pass.
Don't move!
Hey, stop, stop.
Oh, it's you,
Soh-Bo (SILL Y).
My teacher's name is Jean-Paul,
not Soh-Bo.
A misunderstanding.
You know how my English is.
A terrible misunderstanding,
but then...
I'm trying to apprehend
two fugitives.
Did you see them
enter your place?
- They definitely went in.
- I saw them go in.
No-one's been in here but us.
Move aside.
Move aside!
- If you don't believe me, go search.
- Damn!
If you say no-one's gone in there,
how can I not believe you?
Okay. If you do see them,
please notify me.
Let's go!
- It's all right now. Don't be afraid.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Thank you for saving our lives.
- Not at all.
- Father.
- Bring medicine.
- Did those creeps beat you up?
- Yes, sir.
Help him up.
She fell in herself.
It wasn't me.
Hey!
What are you doing here?
Why haven't you gone home?
Master, my home is in Dong Guan.
Let me follow you. I'll be your maid.
Father.
Good deeds are not done
when you want to do them.
There is a time
and there is a place.
The poor can't fight the rich and
the rich can't fight the government.
You believe
you've helped this girl.
In fact,
your help has made it worse for her.
Master,
I don't want to cause you any trouble.
I'd better... I'd better
just go back to Master Wa.
I can't allow you to be fed to the lions
and not do anything.
It's too dangerous
to let you go right now.
Where does Mr. Faat live?
Take these kids away!
I don't know!
I'm going to smack you!
Where does Mr Faat live?
- You're hurting me!
- Do you know or not?
Let me go!
- Let's leave!
- Where can you go?
I have a friend
you can stay with for now.
"NO.1 BEEF NOODLES"
So that's what happened.
I'm sorry to trouble you.
I really am.
That's all right.
In today's world
people have to help each other.
Don't worry. Stay here for now.
Wait till your leg's healed.
If your son has no school to go to,
he can help out around here.
- Thank you so much.
- That's okay.
- Master, time to get up.
- Don't bother me.
- Hey!
Give them back.
- What?
- Master, your father says to get up.
What did you call me?
Master?
Master?!
Master!
What are you doing?
Dr Sun Yat-Sen wants equality,
so no pigtails.
I don't want there to be servants
and masters in the world.
"Master"?!
"Master"!
Why do you believe
you're lower than anybody else?
I won't next time,
Mast...
- What do I call you?
- Yuk-Su.
Master Yuk-Su?
It's Yuk-Su.
Not Master Yuk-Su.
Do you understand?
- Yuk-Su?
- That's it.
- I'll get you water to wash your face.
- Okay.
Hey!
She loves to serve!
Honourable Sir, I've decided
you're my teacher. I'll be just like you.
You'll teach me kung fu so I can help
the weak and serve the people.
- What are you saying?
- Father!
Go and help Master Yat. Remember
to burn incense for your late mother.
Okay.
- Good morning, Master Yat.
- Morning. So, you've been expelled?
That's true.
No more school.
Uncle Wing told me all about it.
If you've really been expelled,
stay here and help me cook.
Start by collecting
the water from over the hill.
It's so heavy!
Let me do it for you.
I'm used to this kind of heavy work.
Okay. I'll let you help me.
I'm going out.
- Hey, where are you going?
- To J.P.'s place.
- "J" what?
- J.P.'s place. You don't know him.
That big French guy
that helped us last night.
- Are you sure you can?
- Why not?
- Because I'll get into trouble.
- Look...
Say nothing and no-one will know.
Get the water, then hide the bucket.
And if anybody asks you where I am,
what do you say?
You say I've gone
to get the water.
I'm gone.
"Ba..."?
What "Ba"?
Students, the lesson that I want to
teach you today is...
...the relationship between muscle
and strength. Now...
This is called muscle.
What's this muscle called?
- The "Mouse".
- Yeah, the "Mouse".
Wrong.
It's called a "bicep".
Bicep.
What's going on?
What's happening?
- You again?
- Yeah, Honourable French Man.
I really look up to you.
Take me as a student.
I've only 2 dollars.
Take it as a deposit.
That's not enough.
It won't do.
These students paid 100 dollars.
And you pay only 2 dollars?
It's not fair to them,
is it?
I'll pay my way
to make up for it.
I can wash towels.
I'll mop the floor. Anything.
Take me in.
I'll take you in
so you can work as you study.
- You're in. Okay?
- Thank you, Honourable Sir.
Oh, yes.
Take this first.
Now, students,
you know about the biceps.
Yes.
Hey, come here.
Students, these two
are quite similar in size, right?
Right.
But do you know their respective
muscles are quite different.
- What's the difference, Sir?
- Look.
This here is the
abdominal muscle.
Now,
this is blubber.
Fat and flabby.
Soft as blubber.
These are fat cells.
- He's got no strength!
- That's it?
Are you okay?
Students...
This is muscle against fat.
When faced with strength,
the most obvious difference is...
Strength!
It's very important!
If I can pack 500lb
in one punch...
- Bravo!
- That's great!
Students.
If each of you can pack 100lb
and punch five times,
that's 100 x 1 x 1 x 1 x 1
and once more,
- how much is that?
- 100.
Right. So my 500lb punch
can beat all of you.
One punch of yours, even five
punches, may not knock me down.
So how can we get you to do
a 500lb punch?
One or two muscles won't do it.
You have to use all your muscles.
Wow!
That's great!
The Chinese are called the sick men
of East Asia. Why?
Bad nutrition. Eating rice every day
which bloats the belly.
If you don't eat enough meat,
of course you're under-nourished.
You look at those foreigners.
They're all huge.
And the reason is,
with every meal they eat meat.
So, if you want to have good nutrition,
you must eat meat.
Also. The Chinese overcook
vegetables and lose all the vitamins.
Look what the foreigners eat.
- What is it?
- Salad?
- Yuk-Su, have you finished?
- Yeah. These are the last buckets.
Must have been hard for you,
working night and day.
- Hard work never killed anyone.
- You've fetched buckets all day.
How many do you think you did?
Huh?
How many?
- Maybe eight to ten.
- So that's one every hour.
No, no.
30 buckets.
30 buckets?
One bucket every 20 minutes.
That was quick!
Hey, tank...
Are you having me on?
Ordinarily you hold
eight to ten buckets.
Now someone's here,
you hold 30 to 40?
- Are you elastic?
- There's no need to berate me.
Today I went out to help a friend.
He was being bullied.
Yesterday you saved a maid
and today you helped a friend.
- You're a good lad.
- That's right.
To fight injustice and save people
is my goal in life.
- I really admire that.
- Thanks.
- Master Yat, it's dinner time.
- Let's go and eat, then.
Yuk-Su, what does
your friend look like?
Really fat, he's got small eyes,
a snout of a nose and talks a lot.
Fatty Hing is really fat,
huh?
- Father.
- Where have you been?
I've just explained
to Master Yat.
How Fatty Hing was being bullied
and I had to help him.
That's why I'm so late.
- Fatty Hing. When did you get here?
- Half a day ago.
Here's your meal.
Just look at yourself.
If you don't start behaving,
how are you going to
face your late mother?
Yuk-Su,
I'm going now.
About your drawings.
I'll get them tomorrow.
Goodbye, Uncle. Goodbye, Master
Yat. Goodbye, Uncle Lofty.
Hey,
not so fast.
- Stay for dinner. We've got enough.
- No, thanks. I'd better go home.
- Let's eat.
- Go on, eat.
- Father, let's eat.
- Wait.
Didn't Uncle Chai just say hard
workers have food to eat
and lazy people
will have nothing?
Right? I think you're already full,
so you'd better not have any more.
You'll mess up your stomach.
Why not do some exercise instead?
You can grind some rice for me.
Go on.
Who wants to eat? What's the point
of eating rice anyway?
Why should I be grinding rice?
I want to be a hero!
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
Eat your dinner.
I'll grind the rice.
Do you really like being a slave?
You're already free.
No need to be so grouchy.
You think you've got it tough?
There are people worse off than you.
You've never had it hard. Anyway,
you have a father and a best friend.
It's different for me.
When I was young,
I was sold off as a maid.
I don't even know
if my mother's alive.
Why were you sold off?
I lived in Dong Guan.
My father was a tenant farmer.
The crops kept on failing.
At first, we were able
to have two meals a day.
But my father got sick and died.
Mum sold me to pay for the funeral.
Once sold...
I had to work for eight years.
Don't cry.
Let me help you wipe your tears.
I'll help you with the rice.
It's dawn.
"It's the first suggestion of dawn,
Darkness still prevails"
"One tankful of water,
two people"
"Tolling away,
keeping ourselves strong"
"This long road
is getting shorter"
"Brimming with water,
the jars are full"
"Heart filled with
feelings of love"
"When you walk ahead,
I'll walk where you walk"
"Working together in harmony"
"When your heart is filled with sweetness,
so is mine"
"May the water be our witness"
Finished.
I'll get some water.
You take a rest.
I don't want to sleep.
I was wrong yesterday.
I'll do all my chores first.
"Fetching water,
romantic love still ongoing..."
Let me give you a hand...
"Facing a prisoner's fate
because of my feelings"
No, that's okay.
You'd better stay here.
Wait for me.
I want to help you.
Hey!
"...it turned out to be your kiss"
"Brimming with water,
connecting together"
"Heart filled with
feelings of love"
Now, as you can't read,
I'll read it once for you.
"In consideration of
the loan to my father,
and the fact that the loan of 20 Yuan
is unable to be paid,
I, Cheung A-Choi, agree to be sold
to the house of Yi-Hung as a maid,
without salary or benefits of any kind,
to work for no less than 20 years."
"This agreement is binding and I have
no recourse against said agreement,
which is also a
transferable document
which allows me to be bought and
sold at a price agreed by my master."
- Daddy!
- Behave!
Get to work!
Leave!
Greetings,
Inspector!
- Dad!
- Get to work!
Let's go!
There's plenty more
where that came from.
You haven't found that maid yet,
have you?
What have you been doing?
Send your men out to find her.
Don't worry.
She won't get away.
TRUE SWORD,
I BESEECH YOU...
- Get up.
- Just a little longer.
- No more sleeping!
- You little punk!
Don't! Don't!
It's eight o'clock.
- Come with me.
- You're useless.
I spent the night grinding rice.
I even fetched the water.
- What's wrong with sleeping a bit?
- You think you're overworked?
You think I'm mistreating you?
The work you did
you should have done yesterday -
never mind your
chores for today.
Wash the wok like I do.
- That's too hot.
- No, you're just too slow.
Do it faster.
That's better.
It's not dirty. Why clean it?
- Not dirty? Take a look.
- You're right.
- It's so dirty.
- Rub the stains harder.
If you don't,
we'll end up with black noodles.
Hey, you'll break up
all the noodles doing that.
- Then how should I do it?
- Noodles can't be turned. Toss them.
Toss! Toss!
Toss!
I toss!
- I succeeded!
- Add salt.
Add sauce...
that's it. See?
Wow! It smells great.
I'll take it out for them.
- Tell us which is better.
- Who cooked which?
I can't say.
You have to decide for yourselves.
You just try it.
He can't be better than the master.
Yeah, yeah.
Come on,
let's eat.
Let's taste before discussing.
- Come, come.
- Master Yat! Uncle Chai!
Wow!
Mmm... beef noodles.
Why didn't you wait for me?
Wow! Great stuff. Noodles.
Let me have a taste.
This one's fu yung noodles.
I wonder what this is.
Let me try it.
Well?
Master Yat,
you're really good!
Every time you cook something,
it's unique.
But this time it
tastes a bit weird.
But it's true.
- It does grow on you, though.
- Eat it all, then.
Fine. If I eat it all, I'll get fat.
So let's share it.
You... you...
get fat by yourself.
We'll eat Master Yat's
fu... fu... fu yung noodles.
Come,
let's eat.
It's obvious to you all.
I'm not good enough yet.
Yuk-Su.
Let me put in a fair word.
I tasted both dishes in the kitchen.
Yes, Master Yat's dish is better.
But Yuk-Su's isn't bad.
It tastes funny, but it's good.
Granddad, have some.
- Try some?
- Yeah, let's have a taste.
The flavour's been sealed well.
I can tell from the oil colour.
There's a man in Guangzhou City
who makes seven-colour noodles.
- Really?
- Yeah.
And I'm going to check him out.
Yuk-Su,
hold the fort while I'm gone.
Me?
I can't do that.
- Just stay calm.
- Yuk-Su, try your best then.
He's put all his trust in you.
You'd better thank him.
- Thank you, Master.
- That's all right.
- Time for a drink, right?
- Yes!
Let's fill the glasses.
Want a ride?
Now, do your best
to look after the business.
I understand,
Master.
Have a good trip.
It's here!
- It smells so good!
- It's unbeatable!
- Let's have a taste!
- It's so tasty!
Siu-Yu, I've prepared
more than 30 plates here.
Now...
You heat them up in here
and if there's not enough
you split them into two.
I can't.
I'll get into trouble for that.
If father hadn't got hurt
we wouldn't be here.
Frankly, I, Fai Yuk-Su,
am not meant to cook noodles.
I've got to go and learn
kung fu so I can help the weak.
That's what I really want to do.
- I know. You're a free man.
- I'm glad you understand.
I'm off.
Hit it higher.
Now watch me.
Get up.
And where have you been?
Here for a day then gone for a month.
Sir, even though I wasn't here,
I've been practising kung fu.
Based on what you taught me
on the first day,
I've been pushing myself. I haven't
forgotten a single thing you've said.
I'll try you out.
- Ricky!
- Yes?
- A demonstration.
- Okay.
- Come! Come!
- Let's get a good seat!
I wonder who'll win?
Go on.
- Great!
- Bravo!
- That was great!
- Back to practise! Practise!
He's completely different!
Sir, I really remembered all you said.
I ate raw meat at every meal.
Hey, let's see how many pounds
you can hit now.
200lb.
That was good!
Don't throw wild punches!
Not like that.
Aim well.
If you're too impulsive,
you waste energy.
Come on.
Don't duck.
Let it hit you.
You've got to be able to take it.
Watch it carefully. Go with the flow.
Hit hard!
You're stronger than it.
Now, come on.
"You think I'll feel pain,
you think I'll be tired"
"How to hate,
how to practise."
"How to love,
how to say goodbye"
"Using hands and
feet to be healthy"
"With a dream I fight reality"
"I'm already very,
very exhausted"
"Dreaming about how
to hold up the sky"
"I can only focus and go forward"
"Strong body, so as to be forthright
and strike one more time"
"Strong heart, it's for each fight
that you need to be replenished"
"A youth, with strong body and mind
that will never change"
"Rushing ahead,
within reality you challenge yourself"
"A youth, with strong body and mind
that will never change"
"Rushing ahead,
within reality you challenge yourself"
I can be a hero now!
Quickly...
quickly!
Sister!
Give me back my sister.
Be quiet!
Want to riot?
It's good that you've come here.
Keep quiet.
What is it?
Inspector Wa,
I've come to buy back my sister.
We sold her to them
to work as a maid, not a whore.
- I have the contract.
- Can't you read?
"As a slave or a prostitute."
That's what it says.
I don't care.
He said she'd be a maid.
Being a whore's much better.
It's not as tough as being a maid.
He should try being a whore!
Here's the money.
I want her back.
I've had someone
calculate it for me.
For two years that's 27.30.
The principal and interest is all here.
Means 2 dollars a day.
And that works out
to be 1, 460 dollars.
Do you have that much money?
Leave!
This contract is legal.
If you don't leave I'll arrest you all.
Go!
Inspector, arrest them all
for trespassing. Quickly!
- Give me back my sister!
- Arrest them all!
Master Wong!
Master Wong, give her back.
I beg you.
Evil bastard.
Sonny!
Father?
Whoever touches one hair on
my father's head pays with a leg.
Let's go now!
Let's go!
Go! Go!
Out! Go!
- What?
- Piss off.
Let me go!
It's not her!
Piss off!
Waiter,
what's taking so long?
Hurry up!
All right, all right.
Just a minute, the rest is coming.
What's going on here?
There's too many people
and we can't cook fast enough.
I'll go and take a look.
What's taking so long?
It's still not here.
What are you doing?
Who is your boss?
I belong to Mr Chan.
Go to hell!
Where's Yuk-Su?
Huh?
- Where is Yuk-Su?
- Oh, he's...
Where's he got to?
- That little punk!
- It's not ready. You must add sauce.
Okay.
It'll do.
Quick!
Beef noodles are here!
- That's disgusting! How's yours?
- It's horrible.
Shorty,
come here.
What? My name's Lofty.
Not Shorty.
- Shorty, eat it.
- Eat! Eat!
What was that for?
- What are you doing?
- Tell your boss to come out.
My... my... boss has gone
to Guangzhou.
Oh, no.
Mr Wong's men.
Tell Yat to come out!
Let's go.
- It's like sticky goo.
- How can they serve this stuff?
Let's go.
Siu-Yu. Come on out,
quickly.
Stop!
Mister, what did we do
that made you tear down the sign?
What's it to you? Get lost.
Who are you?
Well,
I'm the boss here.
The boss?
"No.1 Beef noodles"?
More like the worst.
Calm down,
mister.
I opened this shop
to make a living.
Smash the board
and we'll be out of business.
What is this?
- They're beef noodles.
- Beef noodles?
- Yes.
- It's manure.
Maybe this one's not good.
I'll go and make you some more.
Stay right there.
- I make good ones.
- You said "good", huh?
Yes.
So eat it all.
Eat it.
Lick it off the floor.
You don't have the right to say
you're number one.
You are a dog so
crawl like a dog.
Crawl.
- Lofty, clean this up.
- Yes.
Hey, Siu-Yu.
Doesn't that look great?
What happened?
What's the matter?
Father, I told you not to work.
What about your leg?
You little punk!
I'll kill you!
You're useless.
I'll kill you.
- Don't hit him.
- Don't try to stop me. I'll kill him.
- Why are you hitting me?
- How can you face your Uncle?
Uncle Chai! Uncle Chai!
Calm down. It wasn't his fault.
Will you listen to me?
- Master Yat, I'm so sorry.
- Don't be like this. Get up.
Your poor mother.
She'd turn in her grave.
He doesn't know himself.
He's unfit and weak,
yet he's always picking fights
and even wants to be a hero.
The poor
can't fight the rich
and the rich
can't fight the government.
I work my guts out
to get him into the very best school
just so he'll be able to
rise above all this
and become a good
medical student.
And now it's all over.
It's lucky you took him in, but he
can't even learn to cook noodles
and now he's brought you
all this trouble.
- I'm so very sorry.
- Don't be like that.
As soon as everything's cleared up
we can start again.
If Yuk-Su doesn't like cooking
he can always continue drawing.
Everybody's good at something,
you know.
He actually can draw well.
Drawing?
What good is drawing?
When I was 20,
I won an award at
the Salone in Paris.
You have a great talent.
What good was this talent
when my wife starved to death?
That was just money problems.
What's so good
about drawing well?
When I was in Beijing,
I was so poor I had to sell my quilt.
And when my wife was in labour,
I couldn't send her to the hospital.
As a result,
she died giving birth to Yuk-Su.
I vowed that day I would never
draw again for the rest of my life.
Don't, Chai.
Please don't.
That little punk -
of all the things he learns,
why does he learn the worst
from me?
Look. This is what he draws.
They're worthless. Throw them away.
It's all right.
He's still very young.
He'll change as he grows up.
Don't let it get to you.
- Try and get some rest.
- Dear mother of Yuk-Su...
I'm so sorry.
Yuk-Su!
Why are you burning
your drawings?
Siu-Yu tells me you sneak off
to practise kung fu.
Do you think you can solve
all problems with force?
Yes, I can.
If I'd known kung fu
they couldn't have hurt my father.
And those men today wouldn't have
smashed your restaurant.
That is true.
With a personality like yours,
if you don't learn kung fu
somebody's going to kill you.
But why do you go out to learn?
Don't you know
I've already been teaching you?
Yeah. Washing the wok
and tossing the noodles.
Washing and tossing
are the basics of kung fu.
"One - guts. Two - strength.
Three - kung fu." Yours is kung fu?
Try it if you dare.
- Easy if you've done it for years.
- What about your strength?
Can cooking noodles
give you a 500lb punch?
Come here.
Use your new 500lb punch.
Punch.
Come on.
Yuk-Su, controlled strength -
that's what you need to learn.
Chinese kung fu is being able to
have control when you want.
I put my strength into my four fingers.
Therefore the egg didn't break.
Still not convinced?
Let's try it again.
- Wow! Washing the wok!
- Tossing the wok!
Want to learn my kind of
beef noodle kung fu?
Yes.
- Serious?
- Yes.
Then remember, if you learn my kung fu,
you can only use it in defence.
- Yes.
- No attacking.
I understand.
There'll be time for that later.
Go and take a bath.
Yes, Teacher.
Dice the tomatoes.
Slice the onion.
Slice the tomatoes.
Dice the onion.
Catch it.
Keep up with me.
Slice the pepper.
Slice the onion.
Flatten the ginger.
Dice this.
Catch this tomato.
Your hands are quick
but your eyes are far too slow.
To learn kung fu
your reflexes must be fast.
How would you stop this?
By hand?
- By ducking?
- Of course! Now, remember.
Teacher. Why do we only use
our hands and not our feet as well?
- Using feet is hard.
- That's not so.
I know a man who can kick birds
right out of the sky.
Show me your kick.
I'll try.
Left foot.
You knew which one
before I even started.
Now,
kick again.
One...!
Now, before you moved your foot
your shoulder moved.
How could you move your foot without
your shoulder moving?
Use your foot
without casting a shadow.
Now, there's one more
type of shadowless kick.
Hold on, Teacher.
Wait. Let me draw it first.
I'll be quick.
Great.
Got it.
Hold on tight.
You moved your left shoulder.
Got hold of it?
That's great!
It didn't move.
I need to draw it.
Be my model.
What?
You want to draw me?
More or less.
Now, copy the kicking pose I was in.
- Come on. Lift up your foot.
- I can't.
Yes, you can.
I'll get some paper.
Don't move.
- I'm falling.
- Good, good.
That's great.
This is great.
Wash the wok.
Wash them with both hands.
Wash, wash...
- Teacher.
- Watch it! What are you doing?
- The shadowless kick.
- The shadowless kick?
- Practising it all night?
- Yeah.
You're overdoing it. You're bruising
yourself even before you perfect it.
- You use this to practise with?
- Yeah.
But this doesn't move. When you're
fighting, your opponent will move.
Why are you hanging these woks up
at this hour of the morning?
- Washing the wok in the air.
- Think your opponent will stay still?
Left.
Right.
Left...
right...
- Don't starve me. I won't do it again.
- Go back to sleep.
Remember, while fighting you must
be agile while using your feet.
Once you lift your feet he'll kick your
other one, so you must be balanced.
- Balanced.
- Remember what I say. Balance.
Balance. My centre of balance
must be lower.
Look at you.
Are you trying to be an eel?
Yuk-Su, those eels...
I need them to make my noodles with.
- What's all this?
- You said to keep low. I'm practising.
Have you gone mad?
I want those eels dead. Cut them up.
- Okay.
- You've made him angry.
- Yuk-Su, are those eels ready?
- Yes, nearly.
Teacher, I've made seven-colour
noodles for your birthday.
Really?
Master, you've got to make a wish
before you blow out the candles.
Don't be daft - the wish shouldn't just
be mine. We should all share in it.
- Blow!
- Now, let's all blow together.
- One, two, three!
- Happy birthday.
- Yuk-Su.
- Fatty Hing, what a coincidence.
Turn on the lights.
Come on in.
Happy birthday.
No, just carry on.
- You're tense. Why are you here?
- Siu-Laan's in trouble. Come on.
- What's the matter?
- Siu-Laan's been sold as a prostitute.
How could you do that to her?
- You sold her as a whore?
- It wasn't me.
- Was it your father?
- It wasn't him either.
- Her mother did it.
- Why'd she do that?
It's all your fault.
You told me not to keep a maid,
so I persuaded my dad.
And he agreed -
and set all the maids free.
But Siu-Laan's mother sold her again,
seeing as she's still young.
- What do we do?
- Isn't your kung fu good now?
Why don't you and Master Yat
go and save her?
- No way. My father will kill me.
- So what do we do?
Siu-Laan's in real trouble. It's your
fault. You told me not to have a maid.
One more drink...
Now he's getting drunk.
Master. Here's some more wine.
It's from France. Good stuff.
- Have another one.
- Don't mind if I do...
Thank you...
Need to sleep...
- Come back soon.
- Okay.
"NO.1 BEEF NOODLES"
That's the girl.
I supply girls for the Chinatowns in
London, Korea and San Francisco.
I supply them all.
You've come to the right man.
- Have you considered the price?
- Oh, the price is no problem.
We just need to see the samples.
Not here.
These ones aren't suitable for France.
Do you have any more?
Move it.
Come on.
- Go in.
- Walk!
I'm not going.
Let go of me. No!
- I'm not going!
- Move!
Master.
- Master!
- Siu-Laan!
Let me go!
Master,
please take me home!
Don't come any closer!
- Don't! Don't!
- Get out of here.
Let's go.
Stay back!
Sonny...!
Look at that.
He didn't have to duck.
Wow! 500lb.
Keep away.
Wasn't that something,
Fatty Hing?
- He even broke the door.
- Even the wall's dented.
The "Scorpion Tactic".
The "Windblown Grass".
The meat isn't working.
- Honourable Sir!
- Get away!
- "Two Dragons At Sea".
- That's 1,000lb.
"Seeking A Failure Strategy".
"Crouching Dragon".
Honourable Sir!
Come on!
"Heaven's Knife
Whirlwind Kick".
Come on, let's go.
Let's go, quick!
Quick, quick,
let's go!
Siu-Yu!
They set fire to the restaurant.
Go save your father.
- We've got to go now!
- Siu-Yu!
Quickly! Go back and save them.
Don't worry about me.
Here...
Take him to hospital.
Quick!
Father!
Teacher!
Fire! Fire!
How tragic!
- Father!
- Pour water!
- Don't go in!
- Where's my teacher?
- He's gone to help your dad.
Teacher!
Come back out!
Father!
Teacher!
I'm going to save Siu-Yu.
Don't go in there.
Teacher...
I dragged you into this.
You're right.
Forbearance is useless.
For more than ten years
I've been concealing myself here.
Hoping to forget the underworld,
all the hate.
In the past, I was knifed and suffered
humiliation in silence.
I hoped that grinning and bearing it
would bring peace.
Teacher!
Do you know who I really am?
I'm the assassin from
the Green Dragon Triad,
called the Dragon Severer, the most
feared killer in the underworld.
You punk!
You dare to come back?
Get the weapons.
No need.
- Teacher, why did you throw it away?
- Together.
You stupid old fool,
let's see if you can beat nine of us.
Give me the stick.
- Quick.
- Yes.
Teacher, catch!
This is the real
three-section stick.
You've hit me,
Yuk-Su!
- Come bathe with me.
- No!
Don't!
- Don't? Then you'll have to starve!
- Let me go!
Help!
Catch!
Let me go.
Siu-Yu!
Sonny!
- Sonny.
- Teacher!
Sonny!
- Free the maids first.
- Okay.
You stupid old man.
Have you forgotten your humiliation?
Strange. How does he know
which foot I use before I use it?
I see.
He's watching my shoulders.
Okay, I won't move.
Let's see what he does.
"Southern shadowless kick".
Watch.
Watch, watch!
Watch!
Even if you can predict my moves,
I can still kick you to death, old man.
Don't just lie there!
Get up.
Fatty.
Let's get out of here.
Come on.
- Quick, quick, quick!
- Quickly, let's go!
Quick! Quick!
- Siu-Yu, I have to go. Fatty!
- What?
Take Siu-Yu home.
I must help my Teacher.
- Be careful.
- Go now.
Wow! Teacher,
you're the best.
Watch out,
"Crouching Dragon"!
Teacher!
How are you?
- Father?
- Sonny. Slaughter them!
You hit my father.
I'm going to take your life.
Sonny!
You hit my Teacher,
I'll hit your father.
Watch his shoulders.
Right foot.
Left foot.
Watch it!
Right foot.
- Watch carefully.
- I did, but he was too quick.
Do the "Shadowless Kick".
You want me?
Come and get me.
How can you do it on a table?
Grab his foot.
Wash the Wok.
- Teacher, I did it.
- Watch out.
Wash, wash.
Yuk-Su!
Wash.
The "Scorpion Tactic".
That hurts!
Yuk-Su,
what are you doing?
The "Eel Tactic",
Teacher.
The boy's mad. I've fought
everywhere and never seen this.
100 eels going up the beach.
I'll flatten you! I'll flatten you!
I'll flatten you!
"Heaven's Knife
Whirlwind Kick"!
Watch.
Toss the wok!
Wash the wok,
Yuk-Su!
Stand firm,
extend all limbs!
"Southern Shadowless Kick".
I did it, Teacher!
I beat him!
"To be or not to be"
is from William Shakespeare.
This is an important speech in Hamlet
when the prince takes his revenge.
Hamlet was alone in the castle,
and his feelings...
Well,
you could say...
Get up.
That slap came from Lincoln.
This one's from Shakespeare.
Drawing comics in
the classroom...!
Fai Yuk-Su used
to draw in class.
You compare yourself to him?
He is a genius. He's got an MBE.
Think you can get one?