The Legend of Ginkgo Tree
Kim Seok-hoon
Seol Kyung-koo
Choi Jin-sil
Kim Yoon-jin
Lee Mi-sook
Executive Producer
Kang Je-kyu
Written by
Kim Seon-mi, Park Je-hyun
Directed by
Park Je-hyun
Once upon a time...
In the Mt. Holy lived
Mae and Hwasan tribes.
Mae made war on Hwasan
to rule the world...
...and, worshiped by Hwasan,
Mt. Holy punished Mae.
Years later...
Having been exiled to the barren land...
...Mae made the holy sword with
blood and bones of 1,000 people...
..in an attempt to destroy
Hwasan tribe and Mt. Holy.
Now, the descendant of the Hwasan Royal Family...
...needs to be given as a sacrifice
to complete the holy sword.
No regrets?
We'll be lonely.
With you and our baby,
I couldn't be happier.
Why?
Do you really think
I loved you?
Wake up!
I only needed your sperm.
You did your job!
Forever, Mae tribe!
The baby will die anyway.
You want to kill it yourself?
What are you waiting for?
Go head!
I'll never forgive you!
Brothers and sisters of Mae!
Having ruled the world
for thousands of years...
...owning everything on earth...
...the curse of Mt. Holy
put an end to our prosperity.
In years to come, if there's to be
our descendants, our own flesh...
...they'll rule the world again,
and Mt. Holy won't stop them.
With the holy sword
made from blood and bones...
...let fight the curse of Mt. Holy!
Descendants of Mae!
Regain the honor we enjoyed
and prosper forever!
500 years from now,
when the black moon is up...
...a girl will be born
and named Vee.
Only her spirit can
wake up the holy sword!
Your holiness will shine the world...
...saving our tribe
from the everlasting nightmare.
Witness the eternity of Mae!
With a 500-year-old promise,
when the darkness falls...
...the spirit of Vee
will complete the holy sword...
...that will free us
from the chains of Mt. Holy!
The spirit of Vee!
Open the world of darkness!
I'm taking her with me.
She was born to be a sacrifice.
You can't change her fate!
It's also her fate
that I'm to protect her!
Don't be dirty her fate
with the name of tribe Mae.
I won't tolerate it!
Bring her back to me.
By all means!
Years later...
Where's Dahn?
- Nowhere in sight! Where?
- The valley of clouds!
- Who are they?
- Beats me.
We shouldn't let them
enter the village.
A backward grip!
He's from our tribe!
Wait for Dahn.
If we do, the village will be
in danger. Come on!
Are you okay?
It's time to go home.
It's all over.
I had a dream last night.The golden
leaves covered the whole village.
I guess it tried to tell me
you were coming.
I gave it a lot of thoughts.
It's not easy coming home
after deserting your family.
What happened today was
Hwasan against Mae tribe.
We couldn't care less
about who's after you.
Long ago,
you deserted us and left Mt. Holy.
Nether can you come back,
nor stay here. Leave!
Vee... is that your name?
I heard Han call you that.
Yes, Ma'am.
- How old are you?
- 15.
It hasn't been easy for me.
Right before you came,
Mt. Holy cried.
I guess we'll find out later
what it meant.
Han wants you to stay here.
He believes that
Mt. Holy will protect you.
I won't ask you
Whatever my dad wishes.
You can stay,
but Han is leaving tonight.
This pendant of warrior
symbolizes courage before death.
It also symbolizes hope.
Courage is the only hope
that saves you from death.
Someday,
it'll clear your eyes out of fear.
We've lived a life of hardships.
But I know that
daddy isn't a bad man.
Don't worry about me.
I won't.
Though I won't be with you,
I'll keep praying for you.
Be well.
It's from Vee.
Take a good care of her.
She needs friends.
I haven't seen anybody
making paper for ages.
I would do it with my mom
when she was alive.
She said I was better
at it than Juk.
It's been already 5 years.
I remember her.
She was such a sweet lady.
It's just
an old memory now.
You care so much about Juk.
Because he's my best friend.
What were you talking about?
- Who?
- You and Vee.
I taught her how to make paper.
You saw, didn't you?
- Nothing else?
- No, that was about it.
- What are you getting at?
- Nothing.
You like her, don't you?
Silly goose!
I will be fine.
I know I will!
Come on!
- Dahn! Dahn! Dahn!
Today, sons of Mt. Holy
became adults.
Congratulations!
You'll be off to Mt. Sunghwa
in the morning.
It's Mt. Holy that decides
who survives...
...but those who make it back
will be warriors of the tribe.
We'll light the night for you.
This is for you.
I made it myself.
It will protect you.
I always take things from you.
Haven't I told you?
I'm your shadow.
Thanks, man!
I'm so lucky to know you.
I'm happy that I can help you.
It's the painting of prophecy.
They say our future lies in it,
but I don't buy it.
Do you know
that it's only Haeah
and me who are allowed in here.
In the morning,
you'll be off to Mt. Sunghwa.
When you come back,
you'll be the patriarch.
And, by the rules of the tribe,
I'll be your wife.
That's not...
What are you doing?
Have a safe trip.
I don't want anybody else
to become the patriarch.
Let's get out of here.
They're waiting for me.
Who?
Who's waiting for you?
I've been looking
all over for you.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
You're leaving in the morning.
- And?
- Have a safe trip.
- What am I supposed to say?
- No presents?
Oh, I completely forgot.
Sorry about that.
No, I've got one for you.
There you go. Take it.
My late father gave it to me.
Play it when you feel down.
It'll cheer you up.
It worked for me. Goodnight.
You look gorgeous tonight.
Wait! Thanks.
Tell me about it.
About what?
- I don't have your heart.
- That's not true.
It's Vee, isn't it?
Does she know?
What are you talking about?
You've changed a lot
since she came here.
She's just a friend.
Can you swear on it?
Stop being silly.
You're evading my question!
I'm afraid you might give up
on your goal because of her.
Nothing's going to change.
Vee needs friends.
You can never be sure!
All I want is to become a king
and rule the world.
I hope you mean it.
Keep in mind what you want
and who can help you.
This pendant of warrior
symbolizes courage before death.
It also symbolizes hope.
Courage is the only hope
that saves you from death.
Someday, it'll clear your eyes
out of fear.
Bye.
Make it back!
Our ancestors' fury was
buried here 500 years ago.
As the descendants,
if we wreck vengeance...
...we won't be breathe as alive
and close our eyes as dead.
The day of fate is coming!
We've got to destroy Mt. Holy
and Hwasan tribe!
Go bring back Vee,
the key to the holy sword!
Forever, Mae!
The fire of Mt. Sunghwa
will be waiting for you.
By all means,
bring it back to Mt. Holy.
The tribe will be waiting
for the new patriarch.
Out of the woods is Mt. Sunghwa.
Whoever stays alive,
bring the fire back home.
At any cost,
we have to pull this off!
- The leader...
- I will!
Dahn, take the lead.
Help!
Let's go!
Pull!
Are you okay?
Dahn!
The village!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine. Go help others!
It's okay.
Warriors are back!
Welcome home!
Congratulations!
Don't be sad.
He's just being late.
Maybe he's lost,
or has a place to stop by.
Wait for him.
He's coming back.
It's a mess in here.
It'll take a while to clean it up.
I thought I had to tell you
what happened in person.
We tried to save him
but only to fail.
It's all my fault.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay. Don't say anything. Don't
Dahn always supported you.
He'd wanted to see you
sit in the throne.
I'm so happy you're back,
but I just can't believe it.
I can't believe he's gone.
Feels like he's coming in here
anytime soon.
Yeah, he's coming back.
Maybe he's already here.
Dahn is not coming back!
Dahn's dead.
- Mom made them for you.
- Thanks.
They're pretty good.
Try some.
Delicious, isn't it?
I know why you're sad.
It's Dahn, isn't it?
Is he dead?
No... he's coming back.
I'm sure he's coming back
for you.
He's here!
Long time, no see.
- Who is it?
- Get back inside!
Time to go home, girl.
They're waiting for you.
I'm not going anywhere.
This is my home. No way!
I wish I could tear you apart
right now!
But I won't
You have a job to finish.
It's shame that
your daddy isn't here.
You're late.
It feels as if I was dreaming.
A tree broke my fall,
and I was in a strange place.
- Somebody saved me.
- Who could it be?
Don't you leave me again.
You hear me?
I won't.
I knew you'd make it back.
The patriarch should be selected
through the competition.
But all the warriors
and elders are in favor of Juk.
Dahn?
I'll accept their decision.
Good. By the unanimous decision,
Juk will be the patriarch.
No! The position is only given
to the best warrior.
The tradition should be valued.
Therefore, I ask for a duel
with Dahn.
I ask for your permission.
The winner will marry Yun...
...and carry down the blood
of the Hwasan Royal Family.
For the honor of Hwasan,
do your best.
Why are you doing this?
The best warrior
should be the patriarch.
Don't worry.
You'll be the one.
Let's call it quits
before one of us gets hurt!
What do you mean?
You're willing to lose?
- It's you that Yun wants.
- And Vee wants you?
Don' t be mistaken.
You can't deceive the tribe.
If you don't do your best,
you'll end up dead.
Why are you doing this?
I want Vee.
How about that?
What do you say?
- What's wrong?
- Mt. Holy...
It's over.
Pay respect to Juk,
the new patriarch!
Juk, where were you?
- Congratulations!
- Thanks.
Sorry I've lost a friend, though.
I'll see you later.
She said she was going
to Mt. Holy?
By the precept of Mt. Holy...
...Juk, you'll marry Yun
and become the new king.
The wedding will be held
7 days from today.
Dad would tell me about Mt. Holy.
He said that l'd end up there,
and it'd make me suffer.
- I think the time has come.
- I don't understand it.
Forget about it.
You're confusing me.
The day you came back...
What happened today
...it's not coincidental, is it?
Didn't you see?
Mt. Holy tried to kill me!
Please, leave.
I want to be alone.
We broke the rule!
People of Hwasan aren't
allowed to go to Mt. Holy.
Those who did in the past
never made it back alive.
We should be happy
we're still alive.
That's what frightens me.
I came back alive, didn't I?