There's enough to blow up
the Empire State Building.
I just met him!
I've never seen him before!
Do you think you can get away?
Would you like a coffee?
A cigarette?
Two spoons of sugar?
Yes.
The temperature ok?
Ok.
This will offend the law. I won't do it.
You seem comfortable.
Then should you cooperate with us now?
Cooperation?
You want me die?
If you cooperate, you will walk out of here.
We will keep everything secret.
If needed, we will keep you under protection.
If you three could protect me
for my whole life,
then I would consider it.
Don't talk that way.
Even if we release you now,
after you get out of here,
we will find drugs on you.
Well...
we could also find you guilty
for raping young girl.
Have you had good results this way?
Sure. It never fails.
What's the charge?
I've seen a lot worse than this
before going to jail, I'll play along.
You all seem like nice young ladies...
Have you not seen anything like this before?
No! Stop! I've had enough.
No, please!
Nice young ladies, huh?
Aren't you going to play along?
I'll sue you!
Say that again. Guns have a habit of
going off when you least expect it.
We'll just say it was an accident.
Yeah. Escaped prisoner!
Good. Get my gun!
No! I'll talk.
Why didn't you say so?
Come on, sit down.
Cigarette?
No.
There are men in here.
Show's over.
I have sold some explosives lately.
One buyer was a fisherman.
I've known him for long.
After buying, he sold it to someone
who used to blast reef fish.
The other one buys my stuff
to refill empty bullet shell cases
and then he sells them as bullets.
Yet he had only sold a few.
The third guy's name was Polar Bear.
He's a big-time dealer.
He often hangs out at the Yaumatei Pool Hall.
Taxi
Target on a taxi.
It's BP5608.
Big mouth, got it?
Taxi number BP5608.
Heading north to Kok Road.
Big mouth copied.
I see target BP5608.
It changes to TST metro station.
All copy.
Renew info.
Get to TST metro station.
Target on metro heading Kung Tong.
Copied.
Stay there.
Yes.
Target off metro.
Target on a taxi.
It's CW721,
heading Industrial area.
Target off the car.
Heading Yat Sing Street.
Copied. Over.
Sum, your team leave first.
Car to Yat Sing Street.
Start supervision. Wait for orders.
Yes.
I'll take a look.
Pal, where is Pak Lok Street?
Don't know.
Thanks.
Someone carrying two bags heading your way.
Polar Bear.
You went shopping?
Were you followed?
No. Don't worry.
Come on. Open up.
There are three of them.
Detective Chan, it's them.
Must be them.
Three persons' voices.
Louder, let me hear it.
Brother, stop waiting...
All things prepared?
Of course.
Then, I have to make a call.
Not here.
Make sure no one bugging.
Find a place in TST.
Make sure everything is fine.
No wasting time. Get going.
Three persons.
They're coming out.
Copied.
You don't deserve this.
It's you who doesn't deserve it.
Check the number plate
and follow the van.
You stay here, I'll go and take a look.
Right.
Let's go.
We now start the car.
Yes.
Where are you going?
To take a look.
Be careful.
I will.
I see.
Detective Chan,
they've shaken off our unit.
They'll come back.
Call them off.
Come back here.
Don't shoot! It's me!
Be quiet.
You scared me.
I fell over.
Someone's up there.
Hold it!
Turn around.
Police! Who are you?
The guy must be deaf and dumb.
Did you see three men
come through here a few hours ago?
You ask him.
Do you work here?
Do you sleep here?
Right. I got an answer
but I have no idea what it means.
You ask him.
Take him to the station.
It's OK. You're coming with me,
just for questions.
Come, it won't cost anything.
No need to lock.
You don't need those.
He's deaf.
Are all these toys in here yours?
Stop!
He can't hear you.
Help me find my gun.
Sir! Are you all right?
There's a deaf-mute running around,
find him.
Right!
I didn't know he could fight.
Neither did l. Go and find my gun.
Ok.
If we can find the backing to finance
the buyout of Indian Ocean Bank,
it'll be a welcome addition
to our portfolio.
Mr Fung, telephone.
I said no calls.
I know, but it's that man again.
Jimmy.
Excuse me.
You called the cops.
No, you must be mistaken.
We haven't...
Cut the crap.
We knew you'd go to the cops.
But we won't change our minds at all.
After 12 p.m. tomorrow,
if you still agree to pay
the $20 million,
publish an ad for your company in one
of the newspapers tomorrow morning.
Again.
Where was the call from?
It was a modified mobile
so we couldn't trace it.
We knew you'd go the cops.
But it doesn't change things.
We'll show what we can do
with our explosives at 12 tomorrow.
We won't waste time
bargaining with you again.
Don't worry, they're bluffing.
We've sent extra officers
to protect your buildings.
You'll be fine.
Listen,
this blackmail has gone on
long enough. It's time to act.
Fey,
long time no see.
Polar Bear.
This is Ken.
I didn't grass you up!
Really?
Why did they turn up after you got caught?
Why did they let you go so easily?
Because they couldn't keep me
with no evidence.
I didn't grass you up, I swear!
It makes no difference,
we've made other arrangements.
Where are we going?!
You'll find out.
Miss Wong. What is it?
We've checked the mail.
Thanks.
And these are for you.
Who sent that?
Don't know. Someone special?
If you don't know, who would?
Thanks.
Plant this bomb
and we're even.
Do the job or you're finished.
Where shall I put it?
I'll tell you later.
Let's go.
Roger. Thanks a lot.
Ready.
I'm a cop. What's this?
I'm a cop.
I.D. card
What?
Nothing.
CID. Your case.
Well?
Nothing.
Ok.
What's that?
Excuse me, CID. May I see your bag?
The red bag.
Excuse me, CID.
Make it quick.
It should be fine.
Here's the mail, sir.
Roger.
Do you think it's a bluff?
I hope so, but we can't be sure.
Talk to you later. Yes?
Tell her he's coming.
Roger.
Ka-kui, May's downstairs.
She wants to talk to you urgently.
Thanks.
May. What's the matter?
I've written a letter for you. Bye.
May. You came all this way
to give me this?
It's important so keep it safe. Bye.
Oh, yeah, where's the scooter?
We didn't get along so I sold it.
I'll follow her.
I have my backup units in position.
Yes. I think they're bluffing.
Then we should depend on the police.
All right.
What is going on?
Get an ambulance.
Get the fire extinguisher.
Call Mr. Lam.
Why this happened?
Go investigate.
Stay calm.
Don't panic.
Ka-kui, come with me.
Call the fire department. Come on!
Bring a fire extinguisher.
Come on. Put the fire out first.
Come on, get moving.
Ambulance here?
No.
Go make calls.
We need more help.
Phone, sir.
Bill, you take the phone call.
Ka-kui, meet me upstairs.
I thought you were supposed to protect me.
What's up?
Parcel bomb. Miss Wong lost an arm.
How's Miss Wong?
She's doing well.
The doctor said her arm would recover.
They'll do a skin graft
on her face later.
So we'll wait and see.
Wong's decided to pay up.
What am I going to tell Raymond?
Uncle Bill, that's the way it goes.
We said it'd be a tough case.
We're dealing with
an organised bunch of criminals here.
I wish they'd blown me up instead.
I don't like putting lives at risk.
Don't worry.
If they come and collect the money,
I'm sure we'll get them.
If I pass on what you said to Raymond,
he'll not be happy at all.
What we need is real action.
Sir
I guess you've seen the papers.
Now what do I tell the chief?
That's the way it goes.
We said it'd be a tough case.
We're dealing with
an organised bunch of criminals here.
I wish they'd blown me up instead.
I don't like putting lives at risk.
Don't worry.
If they come and collect the money,
I'm sure we'll get them.
All this is talk,
what we need is some real action.
Something's up. Raymond's in trouble.
That's the way it goes.
We said it'd be a tough case.
We're dealing with
an organised bunch of criminals here.
I wish they'd blown me up instead.
I don't like putting lives at risk.
Don't worry.
If they come and collect
I'm sure we'll get them.
I understand your situation
and I'll note it in the report.
Good luck with the case.
You come, too.
Why the long face?
Did you two have a fight?
Right! But it's the last one.
Yes? I'll get him.
Hold this.
Ka-kui, phone.
Put it through.
Right. Put it through.
Hello. Ka-kui.
May's been kidnapped!
When?
We'd just left the shop
and someone lifted her into a van.
Who did it?
I don't know. But it must be
something to do with you.
Could it be those thugs again?
Chu Tu.
Ka-kui... Hello?
Ka-kui! What's up?
An old score.
Ka-kui!
What happened?
May is caught.
What's the matter?
Sign this cheque before you're dead.
Our brothers...
Please stop.
He's a patient.
Let me finish.
We did what you asked.
That's why we deserve something.
You won't need
any money when you're dead.
Chu Tu!
Chu Tu! Hey, you!
Chu Tu! Chu Tu!
Where is May?
I don't know.
I didn't do anything. It's him.
Where the hell's May?
Stop it! He's sick.
Put him down.
Where did you take her?
I didn't take her.
Who did then?
I was very nasty to you before.
But now I'm sick and penniless.
Why would I take her?
He's got no money now.
It has nothing to do with us.
He made your life miserable.
We did it because of money.
Then who could it be?
There's a phone over there.
Don't die before you sign this!
Sign this cheque before you're dead.
You...
He's nearly dead, so I won't care.
If not, maybe I will.
Hello?
Ka-kui!
May!
You recognise her voice.
We're at the Hung Fung Industrial Building.
Who is this? What do you want?
Come alone or she's dead.
Wait!
I know where it is.
May! Are you all right?
Be quiet.
Are you all right?
I'm OK.
Why have you kidnapped her?
Ka-kui, by the time you read
this letter...
Stop!
...I've decided we should be apart.
No.
I don't think I'll see you again.
It's a love letter!
Just like they say,
Unlucky in love, lucky in money.
There's more.
Bastard!
When we met,
I thought you liked your job very much
and you'd be my Mr Right.
Now I realise the only thing
that matters in your life is your work.
I tell myself that what
made me fall in love with you
is also what
made me want to leave you.
Yeah, why? Why did you break up?
You told me that
you didn't want me involved with your work,
but I didn't mind.
You never spent
enough time with me.
Being with you was
the happiest time in my life.
But when you weren't there,
it was the worst time of my life.
That's not right.
If I didn't leave you,
I'd spend my life waiting
for you to come home...
Can't you stop it?!
She's crying!
So is he.
Keep reading, go on.
..because you can never stop
being a policeman.
a policeman who never stops.
We're in trouble.
I think it's the right decision.
Please forgive me for making
such a selfish choice, May.
What do you want?
We want you to help us get rich.
Our speciality is blackmail
and the hardest part of it is the pick up.
You'll collect the ransom for us.
No way!
You don't have a choice.
He said no.
I think you'll enjoy this.
Stop!
Don't!
Stop it! Please!
Stop it!
Please stop it!
Ka-kui, are you hurt?
Don't worry.
So you want to play the hero?
Now it's your turn.
Please don't!
You rotten swine!
Nice one!
Kill me if you have the guts.
So tough!
Really? Let's see if his girl
is tough, too.
What do you want?
How's that?! How's that?
Enough! You've made your point.
Does that mean you'll do it?
Just let her go. I'll do anything.
We won't let her go
unless you help us.
What do you want me to do?
Collect the money for us.
You don't have any choice.
I'll do it.
Good man.
I wouldn't advise you to remove it.
Break one wire and the whole thing blows.
The same thing happens
if I press this button.
You'd better be careful.
Ka-kui.
Be careful.
I'll come back for you.
Ready?
He's on the line.
Trace the call.
I'll get Uncle Bill.
Is the money ready?
We'll collect it in 10 minutes.
It's ready.
Did you call the cops?
No.
Where's Ka-kui?
I can't find him.
How could he be so irresponsible?
I can't wait.
Don't take any risks.
Let's go.
You'll have 10 minutes
to get back here again.
No tricks.
If we don't get our money,
your vest will go bang!
We'll be waiting.
Get going.
Good luck.
Yes?
Police officers.
Mr. Fung Chairman
You will pay me.
How you know?
Please sit.
You promised to bug
We could check it.
It's bad that you aren't that effective
when handling the bomb case.
We have everything ready.
Once they pay the money,
we will have our action.
Hope you won't do anything
to make anything worse.
Because this will encourage the bombers.
So they police couldn't help.
We could only depend on ourselves.
Ka-kui, the boss was looking...
Ka-kui! It's Ka-kui.
Ka-kui!
Ka-kui! Out of my way.
Let me go!
Get out of my way!
Ka-kui!
Excuse me.
Ka-kui.
Ka-kui, where have you been?
Never mind. I'm here to collect the money.
What?!
Is he your man?
Yes, he is.
Ka-kui, what's going on?
We don't have much time. The money!
What are you doing?
Ka-kui!
Move and I'll shoot you.
Don't pull the trigger.
No!
Don't push me.
If you shoot me, everybody here...
will be blown sky high.
If one wire breaks,
the whole thing will explode.
Ka-kui, what's going on?
Can't we work this out?
If I don't leave here in 10 minutes,
it will go off.
I don't have time!
Let him go. Please leave us.
Attention all units,
don't stop Ka-kui.
Ka-kui...
Don't follow me.
Get out of my way!
I think he did it.
Great.
Looks like he was followed.
Let's go.
Tell him to move up.
Give me the money.
I'm being followed.
Let me shake them off first.
Believe me.
Are the cops behind us?
Stay back! Don't come near.
Why did you stop here?
What are you doing?
What's going on?
A bomb's about to blow. Run!
A bomb! Run!
There's no cops!
I'll blow him to bits.
Wait! What about the money?
And you can't get a radio signal
in the tunnel.
What now?
We've got the girl. Don't worry.
Let's go.
Maybe we should split up.
Kill her if it goes wrong.
May.
Where is she?
Look, he's back.
I told you he wouldn't play tricks.
May!
Quiet.
Freeze! You're under arrest.
Really?
Come on then, arrest us.
Don't move.
Move and I'll shoot you.
You think so? You'd have to shoot fast.
There are three of us.
Think about it.
If I don't shoot you,
you'll only spend years in jail.
And then you'll be a reformed person.
That's better than dying in this condition.
We are ready.
We want to be rich.
Yes.
But you are way too cruel.
What is cruel?
Fortune Maker
In this society,
only if you do something good to the society,
everyone will help you.
You will be repaid.
Then you will be rich.
And you will have new outlook.
That's what you could do.
Yet, now what you have done,
has harmed the society.
This is against everyone's benefit.
What does that mean?
Look.
Beside you guys,
who will think you are doing the right thing?
Who would think of your purpose?
You are right.
Yes.
That doesn't sound too bad,
we might take your advice.
But we're still young.
After we did our time, we'd all be old men.
Don't push me!
Run! This is a fireworks factory.
May!
I'm over here!
Are you all right?
Ka-kui, be careful!
Good work!
Ka-kui! Come here!
There's the rubbish chute.
There's an exit.
May, you go first.
It looks too high.
Just jump.
Ka-kui, are you all right?
I'm fine. Get out of here, May.
As far as you can.
Be careful.
Dad.
Do you want to try this yourself?
You want some more? Take this.
And more, bastard.
Want some more?
You want some more? Here!
Bastard!
More?
Shit. Not enough...
Ka-kui!
Stop crying, OK?
Look, the fireworks are beautiful.