Let's go!
Sir, the helicopter's
crashed in China.
The Chinese have
found the pilot's body..
..but, there's no
trace of Karanveer Dogra.
Maybe the Chinese military
have arrested him.
lnform the Chinese
side that it's a crash.
Sir, the problem is..
..that the helicopter's
crashed into the river.
And, due to strong
rains and current..
..the entire wreckage
was washed away.
They didn't find anything.
- Oh my God!
ln that case,
it'll be hard for them to believe us.
And they'll think we
sent Karan in as a spy.
And if, they're think that..
..it's hard to imagine
how they'll treat Karan.
We've no interest in torturing you.
l'm not interested
in getting tortured either.
So, what was the real motive
behind your infiltration?
Our helicopter crashed
during a routine training...
We didn't find any wreckage...
Nor did we spot any helicopter
on our radars that day.
l've told you before.
Our helicopter crashed
after a routine training.
Chinese government
agency has claimed, that..
..they've caught an
lndian spy infiltrating..
..at the Lapcha border.
Calling it a serious matter..
..China is going to take this
matter up at the international level.
Sir, Capt. Karan Veer Dogra..
..will be tried in a Chinese
court on spying charges.
l admit.
They didn't find the wreckage.
We don't have any evidence.
But, sir. We've internal logs
and records, that clearly prove..
..that during a routine operation,
our chopper..
lt's not about records.
lt's about politics.
China wants to humiliate us.
They won't consider
any records as authentic.
But, sir. Their action is against
the military code of conduct..
Codes and conducts
have no place in politics.
Just deny that officer's existence.
And erase all records.
This should be our stand,
there was no such
man in our country..
..or officer in our army.
Do you know what Karan is, sir?
Karan's a commando.
The best amongst Para-commando's.
Do you know what a commando is?
How a common man is
turned into a commando?
Have you everjumped
from 20,500 feet..
..carrying 65 kilos?
A para-commando has
to do five such jumps..
..in his initial training.
And one, of them is
in the dead of the night.
And one, armed with the
weight of an entire battle-gear.
60 kilometers hike carrying
50 kilos of weight,
Trekking to height of 20 kilometers with the same weight.
handling 22 types of gun,
diving deep into the ocean,
this is just a routine
for a commando.
Fighting armed
men without weapons,
infiltrating enemy regions,
and eliminating them..
..in his own area.
ls just a day's job for a Commando.
A commando explores
those remote areas where...
...even the sunrays
find it difficult to reach.
Poisonous snakes who are responsible for multiple
deaths...
..are part of a commando's diet.
A commando re-captures those
isolated areas for the country...
...where even you would
be scared to go with z+ security.
A commando is equivalent not to
thousand but ten thousand, because...
...out of ten thousand applicants only one qualifies as a
commando.
Only one.
And, it's not just his hard work,
the taxpayer's money,
the sweat and blood..
..of the Army's
training officers, and..
..their passion to die for their
country, all this makes a commando
Without even thinking for a second,
you're abandoning
a commando like Karan..
..who without even
thinking for a second..
..sacrifices his
life for his country,
..you're giving him up to Chinese army.
Colonel Sinha, what's more important..
..the country or a soldier?
Our officers are giving
you one last chance..
..before trying you
in the Military court.
Confess that you're an lndian spy.
Why protect a country..
..that denies you're a soldier?
The government does exactly
what politics demands,
But the army doesn't teach
us politics, nor betrayal.
Let's not waste each other's time,
Let's finish what you have started.
Happy Diwali, son.
Should l fire?
Should l?
Go play!
What the.. (playing game)
Hello, Mr. Sarabjeet.
Can he show some respect?
What a shot!!
Killing the enemy in his
own territory is so much fun.
l was talking about 'Angry Bird'.
Bro..
Look, uncle.
Until yesterday, you were in power.
But today,
the five administrators of Dilerkot..
..are under my control.
l'll have no problem in getting
Elected to Parliament.
Before we start campaigning..
..l want you to get
Simrit and me married.
That will put an end to
this family feud, bloodshed..
Get out of here.
Or it will start all over again.
SP sir..
- Kairon Sir.
Your men will die in this bloodshed.
You know it well.
And, l won't lodge a police report either.
Taking action
is out of the question.
Father.
When l saw the cars outside..
..l knew l was in
for a free horror show.
See. The devil in 3D.
Father, who allowed his cars inside?
No one dare stop me.
Right!
And, as far as the
cars are concerned.
Consider them yours.
Hello.
He's crossed all limits, right?
Who wouldn't fall in
love with this attitude MP!
You had an objection to me staring at you.
So, with due respect..
..l've proposed to
your father to marry you.
Simrit. Go inside.
Father. You know l
won't sacrifice my life..
..like dutiful daughters-in-law.
Right, sister Simrit we're..
- Shut up!
You weigh just 20 kilos,
with the clothes.
l wouldn't mind shooting you.
The bullet will pierce
through your body.
l can wipe it and use it again.
Father, ask him to shut up
else my shoe will do the talking
Simrit. Go inside.
You'll do as l say.
Fine, uncle.
l'll take your leave.
l can abduct Simrit as well.
But l respect you.
So, l expect the same in return.
What now, Simrit?
What do you think your
father's answer will be?
Father will have to
think about everyone, Priti.
l think l'll have to
take matters in my hand now.
But, Simrit, everyone
in my family's scared of him.
They say he's always
true to his words.
lf he's dangerous, l'm Simrit Kaur.
l'm no scapegoat
to take it lying down.
l'll go call father.
What do you think?
Won't AK know that you're
planning to run away?
l can't spend my entire life
as a vote-bank for AK.
l am not an animal
who can be tied to a hook.
l will break away.
l will runaway.
Come on! Come. Let's go back.
Come on. Follow her.
That way.
Hey! You go that way.
Come.
There she is.
We've found our sister-in-law.
lt's her.
Greet her.
Hello, sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law,
do you need a lift back home?
What are you doing?
Don't be stubborn.
She's already playing
games with her brother-in-law.
Come on, let's play hide and seek!
There she is.
Where are you going, sister-in-law?.
Stop.
Where are you going?
- You'll get tired.
Stop. Sister-in-law. Stop.
Sister-in-law. Stop.
You'll get tired.
At least hand us your bag.
Where are you going?
Sister-in-law.
Save me please.
Sister-in-law, l'm no villain.
Hey, silent Hero!
You bumped into her by accident.
Apologise and leave.
Get lost.
l don't know you.
Neither her.
l've no interest in saving her.
And, l've nothing to
lose in breaking your bones.
We're warning you only
because you don't know us.
We rule Dilerkot.
We're the most powerful
politician here.
Politicians!
Then you'll certainly
end up with broken bones.
Now, you've made this my war.
l see. How?.
A year's anger.
You gave me a chance to express it.
We won't run.
We'll fight.
Beat him!
Charge!
Come on. Let's go!
Hey, stop!
l'll show you!
(Crowd in background murmuring.)
We won't spare you!
Don't even try.
You'll live longer.
Wait and watch.
Hey! Hello. Hello.
You just made a mess.
Added to my troubles.
You're welcome. - Welcome?
O Bruce Lee's relative!
Don't think you're a
hero by beating up 20 men.
There'll be another
200 here in 20 minutes.
l would've begged,
pleaded and slipped away.
But you messed up my entire plan.
Come on. Come with me.
Come.
You think l need to run.
Not someone as stupid as you,
but l do. Ok!
All because of you, now..
..ln no time there will
be 200 men here to stop me.
And it's all your fault.
As long as l don't
get rid of these goons..
..and cross the border of Dilerkot..
..l won't let you go either!
Come on.
Stop! Listen to this joke.
lt's a nice one.
Pat to Mike..
''Your dog looks just like a lion.''
''What do you feed him?''
Mike replies,
''He's actually a lion.''
''But looks like a dog because..''
''..he has been screwing
a lot of bitches nowadays.''
Please, God. Please.
We're already in deep trouble.
Please don't test us anymore.
Please let us cross Dilerkot.
Please!
Please let me escape the
clutches of that AK.
Please!
Say something, MP. Or you'll burst.
He shouldn't cross
the border of Dilerkot.
lf you're so angry, you should've
Stopped him then and there.
Why come running home to me?
''Bro! Bro!''
Please, please, Lord. Please.
MP. See, another good joke.
Listen to this.
Bro, this is no time
for cracking jokes.
Time!
You aren't dead
yet why can't l crack jokes?
When and where we
need to catch them..
..the time and place
is all decided, here.
Don't worry, listen to this joke.
We've crossed Dilerkot.
Finally!!
God!
Sorry. l dragged you
along at the bus stand..
..because l was scared.
By the way, where are you headed?
Pathankot.
Pathankot!
This bus is headed that way.
By the way, l'm heading for Simla.
Thank you.
l was seriously scared
back at the bus stand..
..that's why l said those
things instead of thanking you.
Want to know a secret?
Actually, l'm still a bit scared.
That's why l'm blabbering.
Otherwise,
l don't talk so much normally.
Like they say,
conversation helps divert your mind.
You should try.
Silent man.
Tell me something about yourself.
Why?
l am no fool to
blabber like this.
Don't you talk without a reason?
And you talk only without a reason.
Wow! You knock people
out with that blunt face.
People iron their clothes.
But you've an ironed face!
Brother! We've found our sister-in-law.
Come on.
l told them... that
he can't be a local.
The problem is, after this
you'll be good-for-nothing.
So...if you've any jokes,
or one-liners..
..you'd like tell us,
you can do that now.
Afterwards,
the bullets will do the talking...
Your men, your weapons, your place.
So, you can crack
all the jokes you want.
See, Simrit.
Your bodyguard has
already surrendered.
Now, l'm your only hope.
You can't be anyone's hope.
You can only make people hate you,
not love.
God must have replaced you..
..with 100 bastards on earth.
When you'll step out after our wedding night..
..you'll be swearing
on my name in entire Dilerkot.
l swear on AK....
l swear on AK... l swear on AK...
AK... AK...
Don't let him go!
No.. no..no!!
Why were you laughing?
- No. no.
Come out.
No, brother, l didn't..
No.. - He was laughing..
- No, brother.
You think it's funny. - No. Not me..
l wasn't laughing.
Tell me.
What was funny?
He just ran away after hitting me..
He didn't face me.
..that does not make him brave.
He's invited his
death by provoking me.
Shut up!
Stop wailing like a woman!
Everyone who's heading
out of Dilerkot..
..be back in a day and watch the fun.
l'll tie a belt around his neck..
..and drag him to Dilerkot square.
And kill him there.
Just one day.
Who was that man on the bridge?
lt's difficult to defeat
the enemy without knowing him.
Amrit Kawal Singh.
He was born on a no-moon-night.
His father was a tyrant.
And so, people called him a devil's..
..born to a devil.
He has no eyeballs.
Yet, he can see.
He was born in 1974.
So he calls himself AK 74.
lf some unfortunate
soul tries to challenge..
..he can't stand
up to him for too long.
Just a week ago,
the District Forest Officer..
DFO sir, l just received
a nice one on the jungle.
Listen to it before you go.
An elephant was
bathing in the jungle.
A mouse came along
and said ''Come out''.
The elephant replied ''What is it?''
''Come out!''
The elephant came
out in a fit of rage.
He said ''What is it?''
The mouse said ''Nothing, go back in''.
''Tell me what's wrong?''
''l said go inside!''
''l just wanted to
see if you are wearing..''
''..my underwear.''
Oh ho DFO sir.
You should've heard the last line.
Would've gone with a smile.
His family knew that it's a murder,
not an accident.
But, no one dares to
face that bastard.
Those who could..
..are now addicted
to drugs sold by him.
Get them addicted
while they're in school..
..and they fall prey to
it by the time they're young.
That was his master-plan
to rule over Dilerkot.
Anti-allergic medicines, cough syrup.
These boys get high
on animal medicines as well.
This guy owns all retail
and distribution of medicines.
Whenever a drug
license is cancelled..
..the next day, he gets it out.
He controls the entire system,
so no one challenges him. .
But you did.
His strength is not his money,
but the fear in people.
He didn't scare you, nor me.
He and his men will come after us..
..to maintain his
fear amongst people.
After us?
My family's used
to challenging these guys.
But, what's your story?
l was locked away for a year.
The jail l was in, was really filthy.
They wouldn't let me clean it.
That day l realized,
that the filth in my country
has landed me in this mess.
lf scum like AK aren't cleaned up..
..then someday he'll
be in the same position as a politician..
..that back then led me in that mess.
That's when l decided in that jail,
The war outside comes later, first l
need to clean-up the mess inside.
l'll start here, and finish there.
We're here,
and the bridge is back there.
We'll walk through the jungle,
parallel to the bridge.
They won't dare to
come on the highway.
They'll walk through the jungle.
We'll walk through the jungle..
..2-3 kilometers
parallel to the highway..
We'll go on the highway
only when it'll look safe.
They've two options MP,
both are dangerous.
One leads to me, the other
leads them inside the jungle.
Right now,
that bastard AK..
..seems more dangerous
than this jungle.
There's no point in
choosing the jungle route.
ln fact, it'll give
us the feeling of a hunt.
You could've just shown
your muscles if you wanted to.
Why tear your clothes
as an excuse?
Shoes leave a track.
And those who leave a track behind..
..often end up dead.
Sir!
The hunt's on.
Yes, sir. - But don't kill him.
l want him alive. - Yes.
Then, l want to tie him up,
drag him to Dilerkot square..
..and kill him there.
Right sir!
ln everyone's presence.
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
l'm just holding your hands,
don't expect me
to grow wings and fly.
Let's go right.
Right?
Do you have eyes or compass?
How do you know where to go?
Can you hear a voice from above?
Rises from the east,
sets in the west.
See your position..
..match with the sun's position.
You'll know where you are,
and where you're headed.
Wow!
Thank God! We didn't
jump off at night.
Otherwise we would've
been in trouble.
The stars lead the way at night.
- Nonsense.
Liar.
Do the stars speak?
This isn't the time to explain.
Let's go!
He can be headed in any direction.
We came that way.
That leaves three.
Let's divide in three
groups and catch him.
But don't shoot him!
l've told everybody that l will catch him alive.
Get that.
Right, sir.
Let's go.
Just a minute.
lt's a nice one.
Listen before you go. - Yes.
lt will help boost your morale.
Mike's wife was kidnapped.
The kidnapper cut-off
his wife's finger..
..and sent it to Mike's
home as evidence..
..along with a letter for ransom.
Mike said ''This can
be anybody's finger''.
''Send me her head,
so l can recognize her.''
Let's go.
Sir, few people have
sited him at Nurpur.
There's just one place left between..
..Pathankot and Nurpur.
Dilerkot.
Don't scream!
- Snake bit me. - Quiet. Quiet!
You screamed for no reason.
l'm dying here,
and you're yelling at me.
Suck my blood out, quickly.
lt's a trinket snake.
lt's commonly found in these areas.
They are not poisonous.
There they are. Let's go this way.
Don't kill him.
We've to catch him alive.
Let's go quickly. Come on.
No. Let me go.
lt's the law of the jungle..
Kill or get killed.
Say something Balvinder.
Did you find him?
Where are you?
Balvinder,
we're taking the mountain route.
Meet us at the post
and riverjunction.
Let me speak to AK 74.
Look, handover the girl..
- Just do as l say.
Let me speak to AK 74.
l think it's him..
Look. You don't..
Know me! The smallest of idiots in
lndia keep saying this dialogue.
But, l know you.
Because l can guess one's type..
..and one's stature from
their speech and actions.
You're just a local thug..
..but, people like you gather
votes and become a lion in..
..a herd of cowards.
You really don't know me.
Actually, you are not in front of me.
You couldn't say
a word on the bridge.
Because, l know the difference..
..between bravery and foolishness.
You don't.
Follow me,
and your people will end up dead..
..and an illiterate like
you won't even know how to count.
What do you think?
We cannot find you.
Didn't you hear what l said?
lf you don't go back,
l will find you and kill you.
You really crack me up.
The more stubborn a person...
.. is the more l enjoy killing you.
l warn only once.
Listen carefully.
Stop following this girl.
Take these corpses home.
lf you want more,
you can come after me in the jungle.
Which way did they go?
l don't know.
We cannot handle him alone.
Doesn't seem like a human being.
He's trained.
And his biggest advantage is,
he knows the jungle.
We'll need more men.
We'll return in the morning
with proper preparations.
Let's head back with
the corpses for now.
l've made a promise
catching that rascal alive.
Atleast one l have to..
Get up!
Where were you when
he was abusing me?
l was lying unconscious.
lf you are living on my money,
You listen to someone abuse me,
only when dead.
Not while lying unconscious.
Don't go back to Dilerkot.
Let's wait at Atla Forest post.
l'll inform the other team
over the wireless to come there.
More men,
poachers, trackers and hunter dogs.
Let's gather all of them around.
And, at the break of dawn..
..we will hunt the guy down.
We'll halt here at night.
A little further.
Animals come here
to drink water at dawn.
You won't find a
better insect repellent.
This will keep you warm.
Who are you?
Commando..
l mean... l was..
Or still am..
Don't know.
So, bodyguard.
Go on.
Last evening you threatened me.
This morning l'm in the mood.
Better surrender wherever you are.
Otherwise, you will be hanging
at Dilerkot square in the evening.
Stay wherever you are.
lf you try to follow me,
l'll bury you alive.
l'm scared.
Listen. Listen.
This is a nice one. Hear it.
What did Mike say in Pat's ear,
that he died after hearing?
l'll give you the answer before..
..beheading you this evening.
You're so lucky.
You'll die with a smile.
You make me laugh.
Listen.
No more talk, the game begins.
The game's already begun.
l'm coming after
you with hunter dogs.
You either step out with men or dogs,
step out alone sometime..
..to get the feeling of being a man.
Wait until evening.
You'll know who the real man is.
Fine. This evening l'll
clear your misconception..
..that you're a man.
These many men are enough.
Yes.
l'll beat him unconscious..
..and bring him
back tied on a bamboo.
Politician?
Then, l'll surely beat you up.
Look.
This is my last warning.
Stop following this girl.
What?
You didn't think that was funny?
Oh, l forgot.
You never laugh.
You just carry this
stone face all the time.
Right.
There's nothing funny about it.
lt's a good thing.
You have taken up the responsibility
of defending yourself.
Good.
Let's go. They're coming after us.
'They're coming after us.'
As long as you're with me,
l don't have to worry.
You get so eager when
you see those thugs.
You clean their clock.
There won't be any left for me.
l just thought it's a good habit..
..to exercise in the morning.
Really, who am l trying
to educate about exercising.
You're a live example
of benefits of exercising.
l meant example in a good sense, okay.
Wow! Till yesterday you were scared.
But this morning,
you've turned brave.
With you around, fear's mother or
sister will not dare come near me!
What's that?
lt's a knife.
How about l teach you how to use it?
- No.
lt can be useful.
Like this. Drive it in the stomach.
And, if you can't lift it..
..then, just place it
on this nerve on the neck.
On the jugular.
After that, no one can get up!
Nonsense.
Do l look like a fool?
l've no interest in
acting like a warrior?
lf you can't use a knife..
..then, just twist
the finger like this.
That pain's as bad
as breaking the neck.
He won't be able to fight you.
Or these two fingers.
Thrust them in the nose
and just pull hard.
The pain's unbearable.
Yuck! l don't want to do all this.
Don't just carry it.
Use it if needed.
l met so many guys who
wanted to look after me.
But you're the first
one who believed..
..l can take care of myself.
Come on, l'm hungry.
Anyway, there's not much difference..
..between you and the
animals on Discovery Channel.
Both can live on air and termites!
Your man Karanveer Dogra..
..is behaving like a Chinese agent.
He injured a few men
at Dilerkot bus stand.
Killed a man at Andheria bridge,
kidnapped a girl and
fled into the jungle.
Before he does anything else..
penetrate the jungle, and kill him.
Without a military
court inquiry, sir?
l've made all the inquiries.
Carry out my orders immediately.
Otherwise, l can send any army unit.
Colonel Sinha, capture and kill him.
Hello.
Where are you going?
- l've some work to do.
l'm going to miss you.
- No. l promise you won't.
Yes.
The man you ran into trouble
with yesterday is a soldier.
And his unit's looking for him.
So, show them around Dilerkot.
Pretend you're searching for him.
And, bring them to Dilerkot
square in the evening.
They'll find his dead body.
Wow! Not bad Silent Man!
One thing is for sure,
with brawns you even have brains!
One more thing.
Give me your address..
..before you leave for Pathankot.
l'll have girls drooling over you.
What happened?
Nothing.
There's something.
Otherwise,
you wouldn't have noticed me..
..even if l was undressing
under the waterfall.
So, come on. What is it?
That's how wild
cats eat fish as well.
You know a lot about wild cats.
Do you like wild cats?
Tell me.
Hello.
Stop!
That soldier doesn't make a mistake..
..or leave tracks.
But Simrit has left
a trail for me MP.
That's Love!
Just a minute.
Where did this shirt tear?
Don't know.
He knows the game.
The dogs are going around in circles.
And, the water has
washed away the tracks.
They aren't going to
settle down in the jungle.
lf they're headed for the highway..
..then, they must be going west.
The girl's with him..
..so, he won't take
the mountain route.
He'll take the jungle route.
What if we take that
route and surround them?
Come, sir.
Yes.
How can l help you?
Him! He's an astonishing man.
He beat up people at the bus stand.
Careful.
Or, they'll get alerted.
Stay here.
Now you are with in my reach,
soldier!
(Cursing)
(Cheering sound)
(wailing)
Who wouldn't fall in
love with this attitude!
Now, l'll drag you
tied to a bamboo, soldier
Just look at your stride!
Left-right.. Left-right..
Hunters don't dare
to catch the lion..
..even when he's wounded.
And, you are not even a hunter dog.
Yourjokes really hurt me, soldier..
..then l get angry.
But when l really hurt..
..you will not get
angry but get killed.
You like jumping in the river,
don't you?
Die!!
MP. We forgot to complete
that joke in the morning.
Oh no.
- He would've died with a smile.
No need to be formal with kin.
But, who will we hang at the square?
Oh no.
Why beat him up so badly?
You guys are ruthless.
He doesn't look like a duplicate now.
Sorry. l got carried away.
How can you get carried away?
Couldn't you control yourself?
ls he dead?
Bro.
Don't die before we reach the square.
You have to die there.
Hold it.
Good.
Bless you!
Let's go.
- Come on.
Hello, sister-in-law.
Congratulations on your marriage.
Me too.
So, finally l am
going to tie the knot!.
Hello.
- Hello, uncle.
Daljeet here from Canada.
What happened?
You said Simrit will reach
Simla in a day and call me.
l had to get her visa.
The entire plan went haywire, son.
That thug AK, was keeping a watch.
He found out about Simrit's escape.
''l don't care''
Yes, Kuki.
News for AK sir.
Go ahead.
Simrit's father helped
her run from Dilerkot
He was trying to send her to Canada.
His nephew Daljeet
called from Canada.
l overheard their conversation.
Fine.
Come over tonight for your drug dose.
Who was that?
Brother, just a minute.
That was Kuki on the phone.
Sister-in-law ran
with the help of her father.
He was planning
to send her to Canada.
You did a really good job today.
- Thank you.
After winning the elections,
l'll give you a promotion.
Make her watch everything.
She should realize her mistake.
Go ahead, gulp it down.
After that, run over them.
Don't worry.
Here you go behind the bars,
and there your family
becomes as rich as her family!
Come on.
Stop! Wait.
Hear this before you go tojail.
Teacher told Raju
''Son, never say you don't know''.
Always say ''l know everything''
Raju goes home.
''Papa, l know everything.''
''Son, here take this 50,
aunty only comes over to meet me.''
''Mom, l know everything.''
''Son, here take this 100.
Don't tell anyone.''
''Uncle only comes to clean the room.''
''Uncle. l know everything.''
''You know it, then won't
you give your father a hug?''
Go on.
Stop.
MP. Kuki's left.
Won't people suspect
that he's the only survivor?
Yes, brother.
- No, brother.
Yes, Kuki.
We should have atleast
one real accident.
No, brother.
Please let me go, brother.
Bless you Kuki.
- But l have helped you.
Forgive me. Let me go.
Let me go. Forgive me.
- Sister-in-law.
Watch closely.
Let me go.
Forgive me.
Pardon me.
Brother!
Pardon me..
- We want a home run.
Pardon me.
Pardon me..
- We want a home run.
Sir.. sir...
Home run!
Let's settle the scores.
l killed them, you forget that.
You humiliated me, l'll forget that.
The choice is yours.
Either we have a wedding
night few days later..
..or you spend tonight
with all of my men here!
l've kept my word.
You can see him hanging
here... after l leave.
l've brought Simrit back.
So, let the celebrations continue
Until my marriage.
l'm going to have fun tonight.
l've called for a
new lass from Mumbai.
You tried running away, Simrit.
What did you gain?
Lost everything.
You better compromise now.
l might have back then.
But not anymore.
lt wasn't easy watching
father and the others die.
Now, l'm waiting
for the moment when..
What's the point in waiting, Simrit?
Don't you understand?
No one's going to come, Simrit.
He never leaves any job incomplete.
l started this, but he'll end it.
Karan will be here.
He'll come.
Come on, let's go. Quickly.
MP!
l'll get the police force.
Brother.
l think it's another good one.
But, you won't laugh this time.
We'll meet again.
(cursing)
Hey soldier.
Down here.
What happened?
Couldn't find her?
You haven't crossed that level yet..
..after which you get the princess.
He has killed everyone.
He has killed everyone!
She's praising me.
To come down here,
you need to cross another level.
After you cross this level,
we can play the final.
We couldn't find your body.
Since then he's been wanting to..
..kill you before me.
He's been after me.
''l'll kill him. l'll kill him.''
So, you can finish playing.
l'm off to the next level.
Come on.
What? Let's go.
He will not die easily.
Come on!
You..
Let me speak to the minister.
And tell him that the terrorist
has come back to Dilerkot.
Yes.
Are you waiting for
Dilerkot to be obliterated?
Send a team to Dilerkot,
and kill him. Get it!
l haven't reached there yet, sir.
l'll take the force from
Police Lines and go to Dilerkot.
Okay.
And listen,
the press is reaching as well.
Tell them, that he's the
enemy's brain-washed soldier..
..and a terrorist,
not one of our commandos.
Shoot him.
(Crowd running)
(AK cursing)
Oh, God!
Don't worry, AK.
A commando's always fair.
A few thousand thugs like him..
..are suppressing a billion
people like you.
Because people have forgotten..
..that no one can be more
dangerous than a mob.
One!
Hit just one of them.
And you'll know that..
..they thrive on your fear.
They scare you with 20.
So, you come in a group of 200.
And watch, who scares whom?
l made a big mistake.
l should've put you in
the car along with your father..
Your expiry date has come.
Better die quietly.
Otherwise, l'll clobber you to death.
Come on.
Those whojust watch,
become the next victim.
What good can we do at the border..
..if you let them
weaken us from inside.
You'll pay for it.
Hey, stop.
Stop or l'll shoot.
Stop soldier.
(Reporters murmuring)
Kill him. Kill him.
Shoot him, SP.
Kill him.
Stop it.
Your masters think..
..every guy in a
uniform is their pet,
but, people still have faith in us.
And Karan has
strengthened that belief.
Colonel Sinha, this is our case.
lt is our case, our man,
and, our country.
Karan, finish what you have started.
SP. SP.
SP, shoot him.
Shoot him, SP.
l'll handle everything.
SP. Shoot him.
(Curse word)
SP. SP.
What are you looking at?
l'll turn over a new leaf. l will.
Simrit. Simrit. Tell him.
No, no, no.
There's no enmity between us.
Listen to me.
- Let's complete that joke of yours,
you'll die with a smile
What did Mike say in Pat's ear,
that he died?
Bang!
- No!
He lied about his
eyes and scared you,
don't be scared of such stories.
Make up your own
stories and scare them.
Now?.
l've killed him in front of my unit,
so, l'm bound to be court-marshaled.
l'll be discharged,
with honors or without,
don't know.
You could ask about me too,
it won't hurt you, Hero.
You're the real hero, for them.
Do what your father
used to do for them.
Thought about everyone.
But you didn't think about us.
That's what l have
to do after l leave.
What?
Think about you.
You're going, so saying this
only to make me feel better?
l'm coming back.
Just asking you to wait.
By the way,
l am Captain Karanveer Singh Dogra.
9, para-Commando.
Some people lovingly call me,
The Silent Man.....
Nice to meet you, Captain.
Simrit Sarabjeet Kaur.
People lovingly call me..
- Blabbering queen.
No! But you can.