[ People Chattering ]
HELLO TO YOU.
I HOPE YOU'RE FINE.
WHO KNOWS
THE ELECTRON WAVE FUNCTIONS...
FOR KRYPTONIAN
CONVALENT BONDING ?
SORRY.
LEYA ?
THE CUBE ROOT
OF THE WAVELENGTH
OVER THE NATURAL LOG...
HELLO, KARA.
HELLO TO YOU.
OH, IT IS BEAUTIFUL.
WHAT'S THAT GOING
TO BE, ZALTAR ?
I THINK... A TREE.
A TREE.
WHAT IS A TREE ?
A LOVELY THING
WHICH GROWS ON EARTH.
EARTH ?  YOU MEAN
WHERE MY COUSIN WENT ?
AND TO WHERE ONE DAY SOON
PERHAPS I MIGHT VENTURE
AS WELL.
I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
HOW ?
IN THAT.
THROUGH THERE.
THE BINARY CHUTE ?
BUT YOU COULD NEVER
SURVIVE THE PRESSURE.  IT--
THAT I CAN,
ZIP ZAP, AND I'M GONE.
BUT YOU'D NEVER
LEAVE US, ZALTAR.
YOU'D NEVER LEAVE ARGO CITY.
INDEED I MIGHT, KARA.
TOO MUCH OF A GOOD THING HERE.
PERHAPS I'LL TRY
SATURN INSTEAD.
- YES, I THINK I MIGHT.
- SATURN IS--
IS THAT FURTHER AWAY
THAN EARTH ?
SILLY QUESTION.  DID YOU
NOT STUDY SIX-DIMENSIONAL
GEOMETRY AT SCHOOL ?
DO THEY NOT TEACH YOU
ANYTHING ANYMORE ?
WELL, OF COURSE THEY DO.
UH, I KNOW THE EQUATIONS.
UH--
I JUST CAN'T SEE THEM
IN MY HEAD.
MOST GREAT ARTISTS
FIND MATHEMATICS
TROUBLESOME, KARA.
ONLY USE YOUR IMAGINATION.
MM-HMM.
SATURN AND EARTH
ARE IN OUTER SPACE,
BUT WE-- WE ARE
IN INNER SPACE.
OUR CITY HAS
TWO GREAT POWER SOURCES.
THIS IS ONE OF THEM.
LOOK.
AN OMEGAHEDRON.
THE GUARDIANS
LET YOU HAVE IT ?
NOT EXACTLY.
I BORROWED IT.
YOU STOLE IT.
OH, ZALTAR,
THEY'RE GOING TO--
NO.  BORROWED IT,
FOR THE AFTERNOON.
FOR INSPIRATION.
INSPIRATION.
BUT I THINK THAT I SHALL
NEVER SEE THE BRANCHES
OF A LIVING TREE.
WHY ?  AN OMEGAHEDRON
CAN CREATE LIFE, CAN'T IT ?
IT CAN'T, CHILD.  IT CAN'T.
JUST THE ILLUSION OF LIFE.
IT'S A FANCY SHADOW
OF THE REAL THING,
WHICH IS THE MOST
WE CAN HOPE FOR
ON THIS LONELY OLD ROCK.
[ Woman ]
KARA !
KARA, I'VE BEEN LOOKING
FOR YOU FOR AGES.
OH, I'M SORRY, MOTHER.
ZALTAR.
ALURA, JOIN US.
WE'RE JUST
INVENTING MIRACLES.
PUT YOUR FINGERS HERE,
KARA, AND PRESS HARD.
GOOD.  NOW, TRY IT.
LET YOUR
IMAGINATION EXPLODE AND
GIVE IT A TRY.  GO ON.
ZALTAR, MY HUSBAND TELLS ME
YOU TALK OF LEAVING
ARGO CITY.
FOR WHERE ?
PARTS UNKNOWN.
IT IS, ALAS, A FACT.
YOU AND ZOR-EL HAVE A LIFE HERE.
YOU HAVE EACH OTHER,
AND YOU HAVE KARA.
BUT, ZALTAR,
YOU FOUNDED THIS CITY.
IT'S YOURS.
AS FAR AS THE EYE CAN SEE,
RIGHT TO THE VEIL,
SMACK, AND THEN WHAT ?
WHAT IS BEYOND ?
ALURA, I CANNOT CONTAIN
MYSELF TO ARGO CITY ONLY.
MY HEAD IS BOILING WITH IDEAS.
MY IMAGINATION IS TOO VAST.
IT'S UNCONTROLLABLE.
IF YOU WANT MY OPINION, ZALTAR,
YOU'RE STARTING TO REPEAT
YOURSELF...
WITH ALL THIS
AIRY, GLITTERY STUFF.
EXACTLY.  THAT'S WHY
I'M GOING TO VENUS.
VENUS ?  WHEN ?
TOMORROW.
OR THE NEXT DAY,
AT THE LATEST.
ZALTAR, HAVE YOU
THOUGHT ABOUT THIS ?
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE TO ME.
I HAVE THOUGHT INTENSELY.
MY MIND IS MADE UP.
- KARA, THE POWER SOURCE !
- [ Screams ]
ZALTAR !  SAVE ME !
PLEASE, HELP !
- NO !
- KARA !
ZALTAR !  HELP !  NO !
- [ Alura ]
KARA, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT ?
- [ Man ]  CALM DOWN, EVERYBODY.
IT'S ALL OVER.
YOU'RE HERE WITH US.
YOU TOOK THE OMEGAHEDRON.
THAT'S NOT CORRECT.
I LOST THE OMEGAHEDRON.
OH, NO, FATHER.
I DID.
NO MATTER WHO.
WITHOUT IT,
THIS CITY CAN'T SURVIVE
MORE THAN A FEW DAYS.
OUR LIGHTS WILL GROW DIM,
AND THE VERY AIR
WE BREATHE SO THIN.
I KNOW.
SO I SHALL FIND IT.
I SHALL GO RIGHT
TO THE END OF INNER SPACE
AND I SHALL RETURN IT.
IMPOSSIBLE.  HOW ?
NO ONE CAN LEAVE ARGO CITY,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
THIS IS OUR UNIVERSE, AND
YOU'VE DESTROYED IT WITH
A GAME, A CHILDISH GAME.
I THINK
IT CAN BE DONE.
THROUGH THERE.
THE BINARY CHUTE,
IN THE TRAVELLER.
[ Man ]
LIKE A COWARD.
CHOOSE INSTANT DESTRUCTION WHILE
THE REST OF US ARE DOOMED TO
STAY HERE IN OUR BELOVED CITY...
AND SLOWLY PERISH.
KARA !
KARA, NO !
NO !
YOU LUNATIC !
SHE'LL BE KILLED.
OH, NO, SHE WON'T.
SHE WILL BE SAFE.
THROUGH THE BINARY.
THROUGH THE WARP.
- INTO ANOTHER REGISTER.
- ANOTHER WHAT ?
GRAVITATIONAL RADIATION.
A PATHWAY FROM
INNER SPACE TO OUTER SPACE.
THEN SHE'LL NEVER
BE THE SAME, EVER.
AT LEAST
SHE'LL BE ALIVE.
AND MY FATE IS SEALED.
I'VE LOST THE OMEGAHEDRON.
I MUST BE SENT
TO THE PHANTOM ZONE.
YOUR SUFFERING
WILL BE SHORT.
MINE... FOREVER.
SOME MORE CHAMPAGNE,
MY DEAR SELENA ?
WHAT ARE YOU
THINKING ABOUT ?
[ Sighs ]
SUCH A PRETTY WORLD.
I CAN'T WAIT
UNTIL IT'S ALL MINE.
THE ONLY WAY
YOU CAN RULE THE WORLD IS
TO BECOME INVISIBLE, MY PUMPKIN.
INVISIBLE ?
YOU'D ALMOST KNOW HOW
TO MAKE ME INVISIBLE.
OH, I DO KNOW.
TAKE FIVE BLACK BEANS
AND THE HEAD OF A DEAD MAN.
PLACE ONE BEAN IN HIS MOUTH,
TWO BEANS IN HIS EYES.
THEN--
NIGEL, ENOUGH.
BUT IT WORKS.
THEN YOU CAN GET ANYWHERE,
DO ANYTHING.
NIGEL, HOW LONG
HAVE WE BEEN TOGETHER ?
OOH.  MONTHS, DARLING.
THEN WHY DOES IT SEEM
LIKE YEARS ?
BECAUSE YOU'RE SO IMPATIENT.
YOU WANT EVERYTHING YESTERDAY.
IT TAKES A LIFETIME
TO DISCOVER THE SECRETS
OF BLACK MAGIC...
FROM THE ANCIENT
GRIMOIRES.
- [ Whooshing ]
- HOLY... COW.
I WONDER--
IMMORTALITY
BE UPON THIS ONE.
SHE IS A SHARER OF
THE SUN'S EVERLASTING LIFE.
THERE WILL NOW
BE NO DANGER OF DEATH.
THIS WORLD
WILL KEEP HER FOREVER.
WHAT IS IT ?
WHAT'S GOING ON ?
I'VE JUST
OUTGROWN YOU, NIGEL.
THESE THINGS HAPPEN.
YOU CAN'T TREAT ME
LIKE THIS, SELENA.
WITHOUT ME,
YOU'D STILL BE READING
TEA LEAVES AT LAKE TAHOE.
[ Whirring ]
[ Radio Squeals ]
???? [ Rockabilly
On Radio ]
YOU CAN'T RUN OUT
ON ME, SELENA.
I'VE GOT THE KEYS,
SWEETHEART.
THE PRESIDENT CONFIRMED REPORTS
THAT SUPERMAN HAS EMBARKED ON A
SPECIAL PEACE-SEEKING MISSION...
TO A GALAXY SCIENTISTS ESTIMATE
MAY BE SEVERAL HUNDRED TRILLION
LIGHT-YEARS FROM OUR OWN.
OH !
[ Gasps, Laughs ]
WHOO-WHOO !
[ Whinnying ]
[ Man On Radio ]
NOW HERE'S THE WEATHER
FOR THE GENERAL CHICAGO AREA.
INCREASING CLOUDINESS
WITH THE POSSIBILITY
OF SHOWERS.
BREEZY BUT WARM
WITH A HIGH OF 62.
BIANCA !  I'M HOME.
BIANCA !
WHAT ?
SHOW YOUR FACE.
I HAVE A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
THEY TURNED OFF
THE HOT WATER AGAIN.
I'M REALLY GONNA HAVE
TO KILL SOMEBODY
DOWN AT THE D.W.P.
I FIGURED THE ONLY WAY THAT
WE'RE GONNA PAY OUR BILLS
NEXT MONTH IN THIS DUMP...
IS TO JUST GO AHEAD
AND START OUR OWN COVEN.
NO LONGER NECESSARY.
I WAS READING IN THIS BOOK,
THE WITCHES GUIDE
TO HEAVEN AND HELL.
IF YOU START YOUR OWN COVEN,
ALL YOU DO IS CHARGE FIVE BUCKS
A HEAD, MINIMAL ADMISSION.
CHICKEN FEED.
THAT'S BETTER
THAN GOOSE EGG.
WHAT'S IN THE COFFER
OF SHADOW THERE ?
WHERE'S LITTLE NIGEL ?
NIGEL, MY DEAR BIANCA,
IS HISTORY.
OH, YEAH ?  HOW SO ?
THE WATER DEPARTMENT IS HISTORY.
THE CAR PAYMENTS ARE HISTORY.
THE MORTGAGE PAYMENTS
ARE HISTORY.
HOW ARE
THE PROPERTY TAXES ?
HISTORY.
THE WORLD IS AT LAST
MY OYSTER.
[ Beeping ]
[ Vehicle Approaching ]
[ Horn Honking ]
NOW, THIS I LIKE.
- HELLO.
- "HELLO," SHE SAYS.
WELL, HELLO TO YOU,
HONEY BUN.
HELLO.
I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU COULD TELL ME
WHERE I AM.
WHAT DO THEY CALL
THIS PLACE, EDDY ?
LOVERS LANE, ISN'T IT ?
YOU GOT IT IN ONE,
BILLY BOY.
LOVERS LANE.
OH, NO, YOU SEE,
WHAT I MEANT WAS--
WELL, THOSE
LIGHTS OVER THERE.
WHAT ARE THEY CALLED ?
CHECK OUT THE VIEW
FROM BACK HERE,
EDUARDO.
OH !
STOP THAT !
- HEY.
- YOU'RE SUPERMAN'S
BEST FRIEND, HUH ?
NO.  HIS COUSIN.
I'VE COME HERE TO SEARCH
FOR THE OMEGAHEDRON.
IT'S A POWER SOURCE
VITAL TO ARGO CITY.
- THAT'S WHERE I LIVE.
- NO KIDDING.
EDDY AND ME HERE,
WE'RE ON A SECRET
MISSION ALSO.
WE'RE OUT LOOKING
FOR A GOOD TIME.
AND YOU JUST WON
THE BRASS RING, BABY.
[ Groaning ]
- OH, SHE WORKS OUT, HUH ?
- WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS ?
IT'S JUST THE WAY WE ARE.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE
DONE THAT, BABY.
COME ON.
[ Gasps ]
OH, I SEE.
YOU REALLY WANNA PLAY GAMES,
EH, SWEETHEART ?
COME ON.  COME ON.
[ Groans ]
HUH ?
EDDY.
I THINK MAYBE WE SHOULD...
KIND OF KEEP THIS
TO OURSELVES.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ?
???? [ Pop ]
FREDDIE, YOU LITTLE
DEVIL, HOW ARE YOU ?
FRESH AMMUNITION,
EVERYBODY !
[ Guests Chattering ]
[ Man ]
WHO SAID THAT ?
IT'S TRADITION.
[ Laughing ]
TRY TELLING YOUR WIFE.
I NEED ANOTHER.
WHERE IS IT ?
WHERE'S THE LITTLE
MYSTERY BALL ?
LET ME HAVE A PEEK.
MAYBE I CAN SHED
SOME LIGHT.
I HATE LIGHT.
IS IT ELECTRICAL ?
IS IT HOT TO THE TOUCH ?
WHERE IS IT ?
SAFE AND SOUND.
GO MIX.
LEAVE ME TO MY THOUGHTS.
GO MIX ?
WITH THESE PEOPLE ?
YOU MUST BE MAD.  WHO ARE THEY ?
WRINKLY LITTLE WRETCHES.
THESE ARE
MY FOOT SOLDIERS, NIGEL.
MY ARMY OF THE NIGHT.
I'M CONSIDERING
NOTHING LESS
THAN WORLD DOMINATION.
AFTER YOU LEFT ME IN THE LURCH,
I SAW SOMETHING THAT SHOULD
WORRY YOU GREATLY...
IF YOU'RE SERIOUS
ABOUT TAKING OVER
THIS PLANET.
MY SECRET WAS BLUE AND RED,
AND IT KNEW HOW TO FLY.
I'VE A SECRET, TOO, NIGEL.
I HAVE THE POWER.
NOW, GET THAT
THROUGH YOUR HEAD.
OH, I BET THEY'RE
IN FOR IT NOW, EH ?
COUNT ON IT.
I HAVE IN MY TIME SEEN
A GREAT NUMBER OF THINGS...
EVEN MORE IMPRESSIVE THAN
A HUMAN CIGARETTE LIGHTER,
DEAR LADY.
TO WIT.
WHAT IS THAT ?
OVERREACHING AMBITION.
TAKE HEED.
TOUCHED A LITTLE NERVE,
DIDN'T I ?
HELLO.
THE RED TOAD THAT LURKS
IN THE BRIARS AND BRAMBLES
IS FULL OF SORCERIES.
THERE'S A LITTLE BONE
ON THE LEFT SIDE.
A LITTLE BONE ?
A LITTLE BONE
WHICH IF BOUND TO A MAN
STIRS UP THE GREATEST LUST.
- I WANNA BE RICH AND FAMOUS.
- THEN STICK WITH ME.
I WAS PUT ON THIS EARTH
TO THRILL MILLIONS.
MMM.
THIS IS SCRUMPTIOUS.
WHY DON'T WE
GO SOMEWHERE ELSE
AND DANCE CHEEK TO CHEEK ?
[ Screaming ]
STOP IT, SELENA !
THAT'S NOT FAIR !
PICK ON ME !
[ Moaning ]
OH !
THANKS.
HEY, NO SWEAT.
WHAT HAPPENED ?
OH, NOTHING MUCH.
GET OUT OF MY HOUSE,
NIGEL,
AND DON'T COME
SLITHERING BACK.
I'M WARNING YOU, SELENA.
DON'T BE SO SHORTSIGHTED.
GOOD MORNING.
[ Girl ]
HAVE YOU GOT IT, LUCY ?
IT MUST BE NEAR THAT OAK TREE.
FOUND IT, GUYS !
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN THERE ?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO FIND THE BALL.
[ Girls Shouting ]
COME ON !
DON'T TAKE ALL DAY.
YOU'RE HOLDING UP THE GAME.
HEY, IT'S
YOUR TURN TO BAT.
LET'S GO !  LET'S GO !
- OKAY, OKAY,
LET'S PLAY BALL.
- ALL RIGHT, BATTER.
[ Cheering ]
[ Girl ]
HEY, TOSS THE BALL BACK,
WILL YOU ?
- LOOK AT THAT.  OOH-WEE !
- THANK YOU.
COME ON !
MAKE IT TWO IN A ROW !
PLAY BALL.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN ?
WITH THE PRINCIPAL.
DANVERS IS DOING
HIS USUAL NUMBER.
GEEZ, ANOTHER BARFY NEW STUDENT.
THEY'RE REALLY SCRAPING THE
BOTTOM OF THE BARREL THESE DAYS.
HANG IN THERE,
DANVERS.
DON'T LET 'EM
GET TO YOU.
THIRTY DAYS.
SEMESTER'S JUST STARTED.
YOU'LL BE--
HELLO.  I--
DIDN'T KNOCK.
DON'T WE TEACH YOU
MANNERS AROUND HERE ?
DON'T WE TRY TO IMPRESS
ON ALL OUR YOUNG LADIES...
THAT ANIMALS
IN THE JUNGLE NEVER KNOCK,
BUT MIDVALE GIRLS ALWAYS DO ?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING ?
COME BACK HERE.
[ Knocking ]
- COME IN.
- I FORGOT.
I'M JUST NOT USED TO--
WAIT A MINUTE.
WAIT JUST ONE SECOND.
I HAVE NEVER BEFORE IN MY LIFE
LAID EYES ON YOU,
HAVE I, YOUNG LADY ?
NO, SIR.  I'M NEW HERE.
WELL, OBVIOUSLY YOU'RE NEW HERE
IF I'VE NEVER LAID EYES ON YOU.
JUST WHO ON EARTH
ARE YOU ?
UM--
[ Clears Throat ]
ON EARTH, I'M LEE.
LINDA LEE.
WHERE'S YOUR LETTER
OF RECOMMENDATION ?
LETTER ?
I MUST TALK TO YOU,
PRINCIPAL.
I AM BUSY NOW.
SO ARE THEY.  THEM.
ALL THE LITTLE MONSTERS
YOU ADMIT TO THE PLACE.
THEY HAVE NAILED
MY DESK DRAWERS SHUT.
NEVER IN ALL MY YEARS
AS A SCHOOLTEACHER--
COME, DANVERS.
I WILL NOT BE PROVOKED.
I WILL NOT LET HIM GET TO ME
THIS SEMESTER.
I'LL BE STRONG.
BE STRONG.
BE LIKE A ROCK.
NOW, WHAT DID YOU SAY
YOUR NAME WAS ?
OH, YES, YES.
LINDA LEE, HUH ?
YES, MY COUSIN
PROBABLY WROTE YOU.
UM, MAYBE YOU GOT HIS LETTER
UNDER "K" FOR "KENT"
IN YOUR FILES.
KENT ?  KENT ?
IT DOESN'T RING ANY BELLS.
DOESN'T EVEN RING A--
WELL, HERE IT IS,
BIG AS LIFE.
"MY DEAR MR. DANVERS,
I'M WRITING ON BEHALF
OF A VERY SPECIAL YOUNG LADY"--
AN ORPHAN ?  WELL, DON'T EXPECT
TO BE TREATED ANY DIFFERENTLY
ON THAT ACCOUNT, MISS LEE.
- OH, NO, SIR, I WON'T.
- ONE WAY OR ANOTHER,
WE'RE ALL ALONE ON THIS
MISERABLE LITTLE PLANET.
YES, SIR, I KNOW.
SINCE YOUR SCHOOL RECORDS
WERE OBVIOUSLY LOST IN THE MAIL,
YOU'LL HAVE TO START
AT THE BOTTOM.
IT'S ONLY FAIR TO
THE OTHER GIRLS.  YOU'LL
HAVE ENGLISH, LATIN, MATH,
BIOLOGY, COMPUTING...
AND CHEMISTRY.
ALL AT ONCE ?
IDLE HANDS ARE
THE DEVIL'S PLAYGROUND.
THIS WAY.
???? [ Music Playing ]
[ Girls Chatting ]
MAN ON THE FLOOR !
[ Girls Screaming ]
???? [ Stops ]
[ Knocking At Door ]
OPEN UP, LANE.
I KNOW YOU'RE IN THERE.
I'M NOT DECENT,
MR. DANVERS, SIR.
AND YOU NEVER
WILL BE EITHER,
YOU LITTLE LIAR.
COME ON.  COME ON IN.
I HAVEN'T GOT ALL YEAR.
NO.  I'M SUPPOSED
TO HAVE A SINGLE
THIS TERM.
WE DON'T ALWAYS GET
WHAT WE WANT, MISS LANE.
DISAPPOINTMENTS
THICKEN OUR SKINS.
WHO WANTS THICK SKIN ?
[ Clears Throat ]
I'M LINDA LEE.
HI.
OH.  HI.
- I'M LUCY LANE.
- LUCY LEE, THIS IS LINDA LANE.
NO, IT ISN'T.
SHE'S LINDA LEE, AND I'M--
LUCY LANE.
- YOU TWO KNOW EACH OTHER ?
- NO, WE JUST MET.
- WHEN ?
- JUST NOW.
THOUGH WE'VE KNOWN
EACH OTHER FOR YEARS,
HAVEN'T WE, LINDA ?
- OH, GEE, I DON'T THINK--
- OF COURSE.  THEDAILY PLANET.
OF COURSE.
LINDA'S COUSIN WORKS THERE
AND YOUR SISTER--
WHAT'S HER NAME ?
THE ONE THAT'S ALWAYS
CALLING ME AND BOTHERING ME.
LOIS.
AH, YES,
THAT'S THE ONE.
ANYWAY, UH, SHOW OUR
NEW MISS LEE AROUND,
MISS LANE.
BY THE WAY, SHE'S AN ORPHAN.
BUT DON'T LET HER PLAY
ON YOUR SYMPATHIES, HMM ?
- SO WHO'S YOUR COUSIN ?
- CLARK KENT.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
CLARK KENT'S YOUR COUSIN ?
YOU'RE PUTTING ME ON.
- DO YOU KNOW HIM ?
- DO I KNOW HIM ?
DOES MY SISTER KNOW HIM ?
NOW, THAT'S THE BIG QUESTION.
OH, I SEE.  I GUESS IF THEY WORK
AT THE SAME NEWSPAPER,
THEY MUST KNOW EACH OTHER.
- WELL--
- IS THIS WHERE I'LL SLEEP ?
WELL, THIS IS YOUR BED,
BUT WE DON'T SLEEP
AROUND HERE.
NONSTOP EXCITEMENT
IN THIS DORM.
ALL THE REAL DEMENTOES
ARE SENT HERE.
SO, WHEN'S THE REST
OF YOUR STUFF ARRIVING ?
I DON'T HAVE ANY OTHER STUFF.
WHAT, IT'S ALL
IN THAT LITTLE BAG ?
OH, WELL, YOU SEE,
I HAVE THE MEANS TO BUY MORE.
IT'S JUST--
WELL, I JUST HAVEN'T
HAD THE CHANCE SINCE--
- DO YOU KNOW HIM ?
- SUPERMAN ?  SURE.
MY SISTER'S GOT
SOMETHING GOING
WITH THE BIG GUY.
HEY, YOU CAN BORROW
ANY OF MY CLOTHES
ANY TIME YOU WANT.
JUST DIG IN
AND HELP YOURSELF.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE VERY KIND.
HE'S A REAL CHARACTER.
A REAL HUNK.
I'LL INTRODUCE YOU
TO HIM SOMEDAY
IF WE WIND UP GETTING ALONG.
NOW, THEN,
FOCUS YOUR TINY MINDS...
ON THE KIND OF PROBLEM
THAT USED TO TAKE WEEKS
OF THOUGHT BEFORE THE COMPUTER.
EVEN NOW IT CAN TAKE
A LONG TIME WITHOUT
CERTAIN ALGORITHMS...
WHICH, IF YOU BEHAVE
FOR TWO SECONDS,
I MIGHT REVEAL TO YOU.
LOVE.  HATE.
LOVE.
THE CARDS HAVE DECIDED.
PEOPLE WILL DO ANYTHING
FOR LOVE.
THEY'LL JUMP
OFF CLIFFS FOR LOVE.
THEY'LL DROWN THEMSELVES
LIKE LEMMINGS.
SO...
I'LL MAKE EVERYBODY
LOVE ME.
OH, NO CHANCE.
YOU'RE AN AWFUL PERSON,
HONEY, REMEMBER ?  FORGET IT.
USE YOUR IMAGINATION, PINHEAD.
THAT'S WHAT MAGIC IS ALL ABOUT.
- WHY ARE WE NOT MOVING ?
- OOH, BECAUSE I'M IN LOVE.
COME HERE,
YOU BEAUTIFUL THING.
HE'S CUTE.
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON ?
[ Nigel ]
HERE'S AN EXERCISE IN BIG
NUMBERS I WANT YOU TO TRY.
[ Selena ]
IT'S TRYING
TO TELL ME SOMETHING.
WELL, WHAT ?
THAT WE'RE NEAR DANGER ?
I DON'T KNOW.
HOW DO I KNOW ?
- I KNOW.
- WELL, TELL ME.
MY PRINCE HAS COME.
[ Bianca ]
OH, NO.
I SAW HIM FIRST, SELENA.
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
I COPIED HIS NUMBER FIRST.
WELL DONE.
NOW, LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
[ Beeping ]
YOU'LL BE GIVEN THE AVERAGE
SIZE OF A CHINESE FAMILY,
AVERAGE AGE OF DEATH,
AVERAGE AGE OF MARRIAGE,
AVERAGE AGE OF PREGNANCY.
USE THIS EQUATION
TO COMPUTE THE POPULATION
OF CHINA IN THE YEAR 2040.
LINDA, ARE YOU WITH US ?
[ Scattered Laughter ]
UM--
YES, SIR, I AM.
OH, ARE YOU ?
WHERE, MIGHT I ASK ?
WELL, HERE, SIR,
ON EARTH.
[ Girls Laughing ]
HOW FORTUNATE
FOR THE REST OF US.
MAY I PRESUME THAT WHILST
YOU WERE STARING AT THE WALL
AND NOT AT YOUR TERMINAL...
LIKE YOUR OTHER
LITTLE FRIENDS HERE,
YOU WERE HARD AT WORK
SOLVING THIS LITTLE
EQUATION ?
OH, YES, SIR, I WAS.
I MEAN, I WAS--
EXCELLENT.
THE ANSWER, PLEASE.
PAY ATTENTION, CLASS.
MISS LEE IS ABOUT
TO ENLIGHTEN US.
5,271,009,010.
[ Girls Laughing ]
[ Bell Ringing ]
COME ON.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE HE MAKES YOU STAY.
COME ON.  HURRY.
- MISS LEE ?
- OH, SHIT.
- YES, SIR ?
- HAVE YOU BEEN GOING
THROUGH MY PAPERS ?
- OF COURSE NOT, SIR.
- THEN HOW DO YOU KNOW
THE CORRECT ANSWER ?
HOW ?
I GUESS I JUST--
IT'S THIS CRAZY WEATHER
WE'VE BEEN HAVING, SIR.
ALL THE STORMS.
SHOCK WAVES,
ELECTROMAGNETISM.
IT MAKES PEOPLE SMARTER
THAN THEY ARE FOR A SECOND.
WE GOTTA GO, SIR.
OH, BOY.  THANKS.
HOW DID YOU KNOW
THE ANSWER ?
I DON'T KNOW.
SIX-DIMENSIONAL GEOMETRY.
I NEVER COULD DO IT BEFORE.
YEAH.  WELL, YOU WANT
SOME FRIENDLY ADVICE ?
DON'T GO SHOWING IT OFF,
'CAUSE NOBODY'S
GONNA LIKE YOU.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
[ All Shouting,
Cheering ]
Nice going.
- You know she tripped you on purpose?
- Absolutely.
She's retarded.
There's not much time left.
Come on, let's go.
You take it, Myra.
Hey, Myra, see if you can
put Lane out for good.
Come on, team.
Come on.
You guys all right?
- Oh, my God. What happened?
- You all right?
- Yes, I'm fine.
- How did she do that? It hit her shoulder.
Hey, you guys. Did you see
that cute guy in the softball field?
Oh, yes.
With the black hair
and the big muscles?
He was something else.
- Did you talk to him?
- No, but I'm gonna.
- Talk? Who wants to waste time talking?
- He's working on the trees.
He could be around for a while.
- Are they in?
- Yes.
Are you sure you wanna
go through with this?
Hey, what's with you?
Chicken shit?
Oh, boy, I'm really gonna enjoy this.
I can't wait to hear them scream.
But, Myra, why don't you shut off
the hot and give them an ice bath?
Are you kidding me?
That's nowheresville.
If you shut off the cold
you might scald them.
So they lose a little skin.
Serves them right.
I want to see them suffer.
I'm wet!
- Come on!
- Don't leave me. Don't leave me!
I hate you!
You never looked better!
We'll get you all!
- What do you think?
- It looks the same to me.
It's kind of dull.
All you need is a couple of streaks
and your ears pierced.
I can do it for you free of charge.
- My ears what?
- Pierced. Like, I take a needle...
...and then I heat it up, and then
I dab it with some alcohol and zap.
All the guys go crazy.
Because I have holes in my ears?
What are you, putting me on?
Sometimes I can't
figure you out, Linda.
- So where are you going this weekend?
- Nowhere.
Nowhere? Well, you can't stay
around here. This place is depressing.
- I mean, like the tombs.
- Why?
Why? What, were you born yesterday?
This is a three-day weekend.
A three-day weekend.
So listen. Why don't you
come home with me.
I live about five miles from here and I got
this guy coming up from Metropolis.
I think he knows your cousin,
Clark.
His name's Jimmy Olsen.
I think he's real stuck on me.
Anyways, I could ask him
to bring a friend along.
What are you doing?
Oh, nothing. Nothing.
No. I think I'm gonna stay here
and study. Get things organized.
Just a sec.
Hey, Linda. I'll see you later
at Popeye's then, okay?
- All right, I'll try. I promise.
- You better. It's gonna be fun.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye. Have a good time.
Come along now, Lucy.
Mom, how are you doing?
Mom, I've had a terrible week.
Get the dog in the car.
"Take a spider off his web...
...and shut him up inside...
...two shells of a nut.
Now boil the nut in oil...
...into which has been added
some of the web.
With a silver spoon,
put two drops of the oil...
...into some water. "
Right.
"He who drinks the water shall be in love
with the first person he sees...
...so long as the spider
is shut up in the nutshell...
...or one day goes by,
whichever comes first. "
Big deal, one day.
Why don't you just use, you know:
I'm saving it for bigger things.
Hi, folks, you're missing the big sale.
Country and western boys
from the Chicago area.
Now to start off the hour...
Bianca, get the door.
Bianca!
You rang? Hey, you!
I said, you rang?
Oh, yeah. How you doing?
I'm looking for some person
called Mrs. Selena?
Madame Selena.
And you've found her, lucky boy.
You must be very popular
in the neighborhood.
I always see your truck parked around.
Oh, yeah. I get a lot of repeat business.
People like my work.
Yes, I'm sure they do.
Wet your whistle?
Oh, yeah. As a matter of fact,
don't mind if I do.
So, where's the one at?
- It dropped dead.
- Where at exactly? Out back?
You know, I thought we might get
to know each other a little more...
...before we dig in
and talk real turkey.
Well, see, I'm kind of
a private person, you know.
- I mean, I do my work, I go home.
- To your wife?
No. At the present moment in time
I'm enjoying a single status in my life.
Cheers.
- Bottoms up, huh?
- Bottoms up.
I noticed you got a pretty
alkaline-looking soil out there.
What I want are some
houseplants inside here.
Something that goes well
with the house.
- This is a house?
- Of course it's a house.
There's the bedroom over there.
I think it's getting dark in here.
You know, what kind of plant
is gonna wanna grow in this dump?
I don't know.
Shade plants.
To us.
And to the seeds we'll plant together.
Yeah, I'll drink to that.
You probably killed him, you know.
Sleep well.
And when you wake,
drown in my eyes and be all mine.
If that's the goddamn
Jehovah's Witnesses again...
I'll get it.
Oh, hello, Nigel. It's you.
Nice suit.
- Subtle.
- I want to see Selena.
She's indisposed at the moment.
Whoever it is, we don't want any.
It's Nigel, and he's not going away
until he talks to you.
- What the devil do you want?
- I want to make a very serious proposal.
In that outfit?
This is a leisure suit.
I've got three days off...
...from those little beasts at Midvale
and I intend to let my hair down.
That ball will not operate at its fullest
until you internalize your power, Selena.
Some mosaic invocations.
- Some what?
- Come again?
Exactly. That's my point.
You girls are rank amateurs
playing with fire.
Because we own the matches.
I, of all people, know a hustle
when I hear one. Goodbye, Nigel.
- It was nice talking to you, Nigel.
- No, it wasn't.
- I hate to seem pushy, my fairest-
- A word of advice, Nigel.
If I had your skin problems,
I'd stop bothering people...
...put a bag over my head,
and go live under a bridge!
There's nothing wrong with my skin.
That bitch.
You know, some people.
Where is he?
Where is he?!
Whoever he sees first
he'll love with all his heart.
What? For a day tops, right? He was
too young for you anyway, you know.
No, I do not know. Where is he?
Hey, I know that guy.
- Oh, the cable's out.
- Oh, what cable?
This is a mirror.
So, how come
we could ever see him in it?
That was magic, damn it. The power.
Oh, so make it happen again,
you know?
I can't make it happen again.
I don't know how I did it the first time.
Maybe you should let that thing
out of its box, you know.
Maybe it's more powerful
if you let it out of its box.
- The box.
- Where is it?
- The box?
It's underneath the rug
where you left it. Go ahead.
It's stuck.
This is not my day.
It's stuck? How could it be stuck?
It's growing.
How could it be growing?
It's made out of lead.
Too bad there's no sound.
How come there's no sound?
Get off the road, turkey!
Hey, dummy, you wanna die?
Stupid. You wanna kill yourself?
Anyway, she saw a lawyer,
and now she's gonna file.
I told her to take him for every cent.
Clean him out.
- Thank you very much.
- You're welcome.
Here you go, everybody.
- Who wants onion rings?
- Yeah. Here.
- Thanks.
- Some french fries?
- French fries are mine.
- Chicken for myself. Thank you.
- Thanks.
- Side order of tomatoes?
- Thanks for inviting me, Lucy.
- I'm glad you could come, Jimmy.
- Who wanted root beer?
- Yeah, thanks.
Oh, there's Linda.
Hey, Linda!
- Hi.
- Oh, hello.
- That's Clark Kent's cousin?
- Who's Clark Kent?
Is that Linda?
- Guess what.
- What?
There's this all-night party tonight
at Eddie's. He's the guy with the tattoo.
His folks are out of town.
And the guy with the bow tie,
that's Jimmy.
So you wanna come?
I don't know.
I'm not signed out for an overnight.
So what? Go back, sign in
and climb out the window.
Mrs. Murphy's drunk as a skunk by now,
totally on another planet.
Oh, I don't know.
It just doesn't seem right.
But that's why it'll be fun. Okay?
Okay.
Get off the road, buddy.
Hey, stupid.
- Look at that dingleberry.
- What's a dingleberry?
Hey, you, space cadet!
Get out of the street!
- What is wrong with him?
- I don't know.
He's probably on drugs. And he's gonna
get creamed if he's not too careful.
- Hi. Jimmy Olsen, photographer.
- I'm Kara.
- Who?
I'm concerned, well, that if
we don't do something-
Yeah. You go out there and
try to help a guy like that...
...and he's probably got a gun or a knife,
you know. It's not too safe.
Hey, I'm starving. Let's eat.
Come on, Linda.
Power of Shadow
Bring him to me
Look at that.
- You've never seen a tattoo, Linda?
- Look!
- What's that?
- There's somebody hanging out of it.
Doesn't look like
there's anybody driving.
Oh, my God. It's a runaway.
- Somebody's gotta do something.
- What's she doing?
Lucy, be careful. Lucy!
- Come on.
- Lucy!
God, where's the pump?
- Oh, excuse me. I'm in a rush.
- I know the feeling.
Are you okay?
It's gasoline! It's gasoline!
A storm dragon?
A supergirl.
Oh, my God.
Don't. Don't look at her.
You're gonna be all right.
There's no broken bones.
I love you.
What did he say? What did he say?
Looked like "I love you" to me.
No! No!
You love me?
With all my heart forever.
A bird of free and careless wing
Was I through many a smiling spring.
The cold repulse, the look askance,
The lightning of love's angry glance.
Let me behold you.
I have to go.
- Everything's under control.
- Lucy?
Just go on back to your homes.
Lucy.
Thank God.
- You all right?
- I think so.
I hit my head.
Nigel must know her.
She must be one of his students.
He must have put her up to it.
No. I don't think that at all.
She just happened to be in the wrong
place at the wrong time, right?
Materializing in a bulldozer, huh?
She's a wimpy little thing. I don't even
know why you care what she does.
Because nobody gets in my way.
Why don't you just leave this kid alone
and worry about the other one that flies.
I worry about everything.
It's my job. Stand back.
Oh, come on now.
She's just a teenager.
What good is a sword
if it's not unleashed?
But she's a total zero.
You don't even know her name.
The naming of names
is not necessary.
Let us concentrate on her face...
...and my Shadow will do the rest.
Your what?
Power of Shadow, take shape
Look like a vicious dark star
Seek out
That wretched young creature
And destroy her wherever she
Are
Oh, God, that's awful.
That's never gonna work.
Oh, my God.
Next time...
...remind me to do this outside.
Leave this place and do no harm.
There she is again.
What did she say?
No, this is not possible.
This is not right.
Where's the wimp?
I think he can take care of her.
See? What did I tell you?
She quit, right?
Wrong.
Every time! Every time!
Send a man to do a woman's job
and that's what you get.
Damn her eyes.
Who is she?
- Are you asking me?
- I'm telling you. Find out.
Well, sure. But, you know,
I think I recognize the costume.
Where have you been?
- Outside-
- Look at you.
Look at those clothes.
I'll go change. I'm sorry.
And you'll put on your
proper school uniform.
- And get out of that ridiculous costume.
- Yes, ma'am.
- And cover your legs.
- Don't you "yes, ma'am" me.
- No, ma'am.
I think you're blowing this thing out
of proportion, if you want my opinion.
This box is definitely getting
bigger and uglier.
All I'm saying is you can't go nuts...
...over a landscape guy
and a teenager in a blue suit.
She flies.
Can you get that through your thick skull
and into your tiny brain, Bianca?
The girl can fly.
Okay. Now, let's get serious.
Come to mama.
- Selena, cut it out.
- I'm not doing it.
I think we're venturing where, you know,
fools rush in and angels fear to tread.
I'm no angel.
It's the wimp again.
And she's trespassing.
Hello.
Oh, no. Not now.
'Tis only but me, my love.
- Please, you'll let everyone know.
- What? That I love you?
- I'd shout it from the highest hill.
- Please don't.
I know you think me the fool,
but at least tell me your name.
Linda. Linda Lee.
Linda. Lovely Linda Lee.
These roses pale beside thee.
- Well, thank you, but I'm-
- Sweet chocolates for my sweet Linda.
What are you doing?
Please?
- Oh, no, I-
- Please?
Well, all right. But just for a minute.
You hate me, don't you?
Hate you? I don't even know you.
- I don't even know your name.
- Ethan.
Say my name aloud but once
and I shall die the happy fool.
Look, Ethan-
Ethan.
Your soft caress did at once renew
the beating of this broken heart.
Are you crazy?
Marry me?
Marry you?
- I don't-
- Don't say it. Don't, please. I know.
- What?
- We're from different worlds.
- You mean, you know where I'm-?
- Just give me a chance, Linda.
Love makes everything possible.
A poor uneducated gardener
can indeed worship a rich debutante...
...and make her happy if she'd just-
Oh, Ethan.
I'm not rich. I'm just-
Well, then I'll support us both.
You're nuts, you know that? You're
so sweet, but you're out of your mind.
Over you.
What a touching scene.
Round and round they go
Where they stop
Boy, you're really getting
the hang of this.
Where is she?
Jesus.
Who are you?
I am Selena.
Diadanus of Catania,
priestess of Sechnid.
I am the ultimate Siren of Endor...
...and you, little lady, are trespassing
on private property.
She means him.
I am Kara of Argo City...
...daughter of Alura and Zor-El.
And I don't scare easily.
- No?
- No.
Try...
...this.
This lady is improving by
leaps and bounds, I gotta tell you.
You okay?
No.
You want a hacksaw or something?
Now I am really upset.
What's going on?
Put me down.
- Where am I?
- You're safe.
Safe? Where's Linda?
Put me down.
- Where's my Linda?
- Take it easy.
Ethan.
Very clever. That ought to keep her
out of your hair for a few hours.
"Clever"? A cheap trick.
Power of Shadow
Bring him to me
Didn't work, huh?
Maybe they're too far away.
I can make the sky rain coconuts
with pinpoint accuracy...
...but I still can't control men's minds.
Not with her around.
So maybe-
Now, don't go through the roof.
But maybe we ought to back down
and give old you-know-who a call.
You know. "Who. "
- Spit it out.
- Nigel.
- I shall pretend you didn't say that.
- But I did.
All I'm thinking, and forgive me
for thinking of out of turn here...
...is that he's been around.
He knows things we don't.
Plus, the way you wrap him around
your little finger, I'm always amazed.
- What's in it for me?
- Me.
My dear Nigel...
...the way to a woman's heart
is through the elimination of her rivals.
- Murder. Are you proposing that-?
- Certainly not.
Leave that to me.
You deliver the goods.
- Her.
- Her? How?
By getting me him.
- She'll follow.
- Well, I don't.
- Follow any of this, I mean.
- Put that down.
Nigel, I want one thing:
Time to master my new toy.
So we can rule the world?
And you want him here,
Johnny Appleseed, in your living room?
Yes, in the flesh.
So she'll follow? No other reason?
- None.
- You're sure of that?
I'm sorry. The little spider got out.
What?
Where am I?
- Who are you?
- Kara.
Kara?
- What happened?
- You got hit on the head by a coconut.
What's with the Halloween costume?
This is not a costume.
These are my clothes.
- What do you mean?
- Look, I have to go now.
I will come back for you later, I promise.
I've gotta get to the amusement park.
Amusement park?
Linda.
I gotta find Linda. She was in trouble.
Oh, Linda's all right.
She can take care of herself.
No, no, no, she can't. Something's
wrong. She's in big trouble and I love her.
I love her.
Yeah, I do love her.
- I have to go, Ethan. Goodbye.
- Yes, so do I.
Hey.
I told you Linda
can take care of herself.
You just flew over my head.
I saw you.
- I'll go back and take care of everything.
- You just flew over my head, true?
True.
- Like Superman.
- He's my cousin.
- He's your cousin?
- Yes. I shouldn't be telling you this. I'm-
Wait. You can do the whole number?
Leap tall buildings in a single bound?
- And look right through things?
- Yes.
- Bend steel bars?
Oh, Selena. I have to go.
Selena has the omegahedron.
Wait, take me with you.
I have to find Linda.
- What is it?
- The Burundi Wand.
Pure unadulterated evil.
Ready?
But how can you love her?
You don't even know her.
Oh, yeah, I do.
If she's in trouble then I got no
business standing here talking with you.
- Even if you are what you say you are.
- Linda is not in trouble.
Look, don't make me get rough, okay?
You wouldn't stand a chance.
Please trust me.
Linda is all right.
How do you know?
I just-
Know.
Linda.
Oh, my God.
How did you do that?
Ethan.
Nigel, you are wonderful.
Pure genius.
You deserve me.
Something else.
Now, let's get out of this dump.
Hey, what's the matter?
Catching flies?
Lucy, look.
One minute that,
and the next minute this.
What is it?
It's a mountain, Lucy. Isn't it?
- Tell me I'm not seeing things.
- How did it get there, Jimmy?
I don't know.
It just appeared.
How can a mountain just appear?
Hey, there's something at the top.
- Looks like a castle.
- It's more like a fortress.
Ethan?
Ethan.
Enjoy your prison, Supergirl.
Forever and ever.
No, Ethan! Don't do it!
Ethan!
Where am I?
You can't arrest me
without a warrant.
Slow down.
We want Selena out!
Smile, lunkhead. You're not a gardener
anymore. You're Prince Ethan now.
- Are we gonna stand up to her or not?
- Yeah!
Selena must go!
Who's this little twerpette?
She's someone who believes in freedom.
Lucy, it's not a good time
to express yourself.
I don't know who you think you are,
or what evil force you represent.
But if you think you can just get rid
of anybody who stands up to you...
...just make them disappear,
like my friend Linda...
- Who?
- Linda, my roommate.
She disappeared the day
that mountain showed up.
- The wimp.
Seize them.
Drive off.
- Let me go!
- Nobody messes with Jimmy Olsen!
Now, let go of me. I'm with the press!
- Zaltar.
- Squirt?
- Zaltar?
- Squirt.
- Zaltar, it's me. It's Kara.
- I know.
Squirt?
What is that?
- Where are we?
- Nowhere.
- The Phantom Zone?
- It's lonely here, my Kara.
So sad.
I've been here forever
and I shall stay here forever.
- Ethan?
- Yes, my darling.
Don't call me your "darling. "
You despise me.
- Get me the Coffer of Shadow.
- Yes, my darling.
I think we need something...
...there.
Oh, Jimmy.
Oh, terrific.
The old dangling-in-a-cage routine.
Pathetic, Selena.
- Who is that guy?
- He's my math teacher, I think.
What are they for?
Insurance.
But you can't just give up.
- You founded a whole city.
- I did.
And then I doomed it to destruction.
That was an error. A tragic one.
When you're my age and you make
as many tragic errors as I do...
...it is a different tune
that you will sing.
I will not. I will never give up.
I will never spend my entire life
in a place like this. I would die first!
Strong words. There are worse things
than dying and I deserve every one.
- What is this?
- A horse.
I think.
On Earth, I think it's called a horse.
And you made this here?
- Then you haven't given up.
- Don't be ridiculous.
Earth, Zaltar, Earth. A tree, a horse.
You keep making things from Earth.
- The place intrigues me.
- Then let's go there.
Certainly. When is the next train?
What is a train?
What's so funny?
Don't laugh at me, Zaltar.
I'm only laughing at myself.
For you, I weep.
- Is this train a way out of here?
- There is no way out of here.
That is the point of the Phantom Zone.
My neighbors now: The criminals,
the corrupt, the evil.
They're here, over the hill there,
with no way out.
But there's always a way out.
If there's a way in,
there's a way out.
There is a way.
- But it's impossible.
- Why?
No. It wouldn't work.
You'll be swept into a singularity
if it didn't work. No.
Forget I mentioned it.
Have a squirt instead.
I could do it.
- Then please, at least teach me how.
- There's nothing to teach.
You can't, as they say, practice
at the rift. You get one chance.
- The rift.
- Sure you won't have a squirt?
Once you get used to it,
I think it's delicious.
You're right.
You are absolutely right.
There is enough doom and gloom
in the air already.
And it is better to accept defeat
than to take a chance...
...and try like fools to redeem ourselves,
save our city and those we love there...
...plus all the people on Earth
that this wicked sorceress...
...is going to make suffer
just because of us. Cheers.
We could die trying.
We won't.
We won't. Come on.
Tomorrow...
...Thursday, Friday.
Just like here,
we go for the cops first, right?
And the Army.
By Saturday, we have the continental
United States, Mexico, Canada.
Oh, my God, Selena. It's the box.
- Hush it up.
- No.
What the box wants, the box gets.
What is it?
Fascinating.
I don't know.
Is this it? Is this the way out?
Not yet. This is the Quantum Vortex.
We must risk our destruction in it.
To move mountains,
you must make sacrifices.
Zaltar, I'm scared.
Accept your fears.
Confront your demons.
Find your destiny in the maelstrom.
Zaltar, I can't. I can't.
You...
...can.
Two specks. Look.
What do I do?
How do you murder someone
in the Phantom Zone?
- She's with some old guy, it looks like.
- Move, huh?
- Come on.
- Calm down, okay?
This is what I want.
The Salian Fireballs.
Page 321, chapter six.
What's that?
"Power of rainmaking. " No!
"How to separate husband and wife. "
No. Not now, not now.
Well, you better find something fast,
like an atom bomb.
I found it.
Summoning the Demon storm.
We go higher, girl!
- Higher!
- Come with me.
I am with you. On, girl!
I am with you.
Zaltar!
Oh, thank God.
You've had your fun, Selena.
The game is finished.
Hardly.
One false step, bluebird,
and even if you don't...
...your friends will get the point.
Hey, no!
I don't like this.
Don't worry, Lucy. Don't worry.
- I wouldn't, if I were you.
- Well, you're not me.
Quick, get out of the way!
Into the alcove over there.
- Come on.
- Hurry, Jimmy. Hurry.
The omegahedron, Selena. I want it.
Well, then, Supergirl,
you shall have it.
Supergirl, above you. Look out!
I think I'll be going,
if you'll excuse me.
That's what I said.
I'm staying, I'm staying.
You have no friends, Selena.
You treat everyone as if
they were put on this earth to serve you.
More or less, I think they were.
You included.
Power of Shadow
Appear
Destroy her
I can't.
You can.
On, girl.
Confront her with it.
It's the only way!
I have to go. I have to return this
to where it belongs.
And I must ask you all something.
It's all right, Supergirl.
We never saw you.
- We never even heard of you.
- Thank you.
Ethan. Linda, she-
She had to leave in a hurry but she-
You don't have to say a word.
I know.
I'll explain about Linda.
Thank you, Ethan.
Take care of yourself, kiddo.
That was some kiss.
Goodbye, Linda.