- [Bird Screeching]
- [Vehicle Approaching]
Not a good start.
[Rapid Beeping]
[Wind Echoing]
Huh?
Just looking.
I'll put it back.
[Speaking Native Tongue]
- For me?
- [Speaking Native Tongue]
- This for me?
- [Grunts]
- You sure?
- [Speaking Native Tongue]
- I keep?
Ah, thank you.
[Grunts]
- This one too? Okay.
- [Assenting Grunt]
- Hmm?
- Mm-hmm.
- [Speaking Native Tongue]
- See that? For water.
[Chuckles]
Cheers.
For emergency.
[Men Shout Word]
[Chanting]
[People Chanting]
- [Chanting Stops]
- [Grunts]
Why, when you already got the jewels,
did you go and drink the holy water?
- "Holy water"?
- A dreadful fate befalls
he who drinks the water.
- You mean I've been poisoned?
- No, though you might wish you had.
You've been chosen
to marry her.
- [Kissing Sound, Giggling]
- Eww.
- [People Gasping]
- What? Where are you going?
[Yelling]
- [Crackling, Hissing]
- [People Gasping]
- Happy New Year!
- [Men Growling]
[Men Yelling]
- Bye.
- [Men Yelling]
[Yells]
You dropped the jewels!
[Air Hissing]
[Woman Yells]
All that for nothing.
- Hello, Duke.
- [Man] Welcome, Condor.
- I heard you had some
trouble in the Amazon.
- It was okay.
Sometimes you have
to roll with it.
We wouldn't want to lose
our best agent, now, would we?
Come and sit down.
We'll have a cup of tea.
I don’t think you brought
me here for a cup of tea.
- Did you?
- Uh, you're right, Jackie.
How much do you know
about the Second World War?
- Enough to know
we must never have a third.
- [Chuckles]
In the latter part
of the Second World War,
the German forces
were retreating out of Africa.
An officer was ordered
to bury gold...
in a secret base
in the African desert.
The gold was looted
from all over Europe.
The captain in charge
of the mission is now dead.
Only he and his men
knew of the base.
This officer in charge,
with 18 men, hid the gold,
but immediately after
the mission was completed,
the officer, along with
his 18 guards, disappeared.
- Where do I fit in?
- Well, the United Nations have
ordered me to find the gold.
And because
the bullion was taken...
from many different countries
during the war,
it's more than possible
they will begin a dispute...
over the right
of possession.
So I felt if you
found it first, well,
it would be a little
less embarrassing.
This way, we can avoid an incident.
That's why you're here.
Now, let me introduce you
to Colonel Bartok.
- Pleased to meet you.
- Lieutenant Colonel Bernard.
- Nice to meet you.
- It's quite an honor, Condor.
- And this is Ada.
- Hello.
Ada's an attaché
to the U.N.
She's an expert
on African desert environment.
Under her guidance, I'm confident
you will find your destination.
She's gonna be
my guide?
- Sounds as though you have
no confidence in me.
- Don't get me wrong.
I expect the worst
and always hope for the best.
lf you work out the details before hand
and stick to your plan...
naturally you have
to be flexible...
you don’t need
to stand around hoping.
It's a pleasure working with
someone with so much confidence.
I can see you'll both
get along just fine. [Chuckles]
Colonel Bartok, show the Condor
the key which he will need...
for the special mission.
Ah. Certainly.
A most unusual key.
It's the key to open
the door to the base.
Will the gold still be there
after 40 years?
Once the base was sealed,
the government kept the key.
[Ada] That's right.
- Now, I have another question.
- What?
For the period of this mission, Condor
and I are supposed to be partners,
but just in case of a misunderstanding,
who has the final word?
- [Duke] Who do you suggest?
- No problem I can see.
So I make
the decisions, then.
- I'll see you tomorrow morning,
Royal Library at 10:00.
- But tomorrow...
- Hey. I thought it was my decision.
- Tomorrow morning.
I have a few details to discuss
with the Colonel. Good-bye, Duke.
- Use the library.
- All right. See you in the morning.
Good day.
- I have all the research materials...
- [Chuckles]
Who said "Expect the worst
and hope for the best," huh?
- [Chuckling]
- She's quite a girl.
[Ada] What do you know
about the desert?
- [Jackie] It's all sand.
- Wrong. Only 25% of the Sahara
is covered by sand.
Temperatures can reach
up to 130 degrees by day,
and at night, they fall
below freezing.
It rains only once
every few years.
Man can survive
seven days without food...
but will die after only
two days without water.
- Are you listening, Jackie?
- Yeah. Who are these guys?
The circled one was the officer
in command of the mission
- and some of his men.
- According to this.
He could
still have family around here.
What are you doing?
- I want to look for them.
- That's useless.
The German government has searched
everywhere with no luck.
Geography lesson is over for the day.
I got to go.
W-Wait! Jackie!
There's still
work to do!
We haven’t solved
the water problem yet.
Hmm. "For sale."
[Door Opening]
- [Door Closing]
- [Woman Panting]
- [Urinating]
- [Sighing]
- [Sighs]
- [Toilet Flushes]
[Water Running]
[Water Stops]
[Sneezes]
[Woman Screams]
What are you doing here?
Get out!
[Panting, Screams]
Oh! Let me go! Stop it!
[Whimpers]
Keep quiet. You don’t scream.
We won't hurt you if you shut up.
What do you want?
You can take my money.
- I don't want money. Relax.
All I want is for you to...
- [Yells]
- [Gasps]
- [Muffled Yelling]
It's okay.
Don’t be scared.
- Who are you?
- I'm asking you.
- Me? I'm here to help you.
- Yeah, but who are you?
- Let me ask him first. Who are you?
- [Gun Cocking]
- [Man] Freeze!
Don't move, or I'll shoot.
- Who are you?
- Who we are is not your business.
We want the gold.
You follow her here
for gold? What gold?
Ask her.
Oh. So you've been the ones who’ve
followed me and annoyed me on the phone.
And you're the granddaughter
of that German who hid it.
You tell me where the gold
is hidden, or I'll shoot.
- [Gasps]
- No, no. I said we were
not to use violence.
Quiet! We must not
fight in front of people.
Tell us where the gold is,
or I'll shoot
your boyfriend dead.
[Sighs]
He's not my boyfriend.
That's right.
I'm not her boyfriend.
So, it's none
of my business, is it? Bye-bye!
Hold it!
Then why
are you here?
Uh... I saw a for sale sign,
and came up to take a look around.
Someone was taking a shower upstairs,
so I got curious. Pretty nice view.
- [Gasps]
- I'm sorry. Like to see what I saw?
- Oh!
- [Men Grunting]
Don’t move!
Okay.
Your organization.
It's time to talk.
- We won’t talk. Ever!
- Soldiers of the faith will
never give up the holy battle,
and you will not
make us talk!
[Together] Let death overcome all!
Save them
for next time.
Don’t mess up
the lady's house.
Now, get out of here!
- You better not bother her again.
- We will never give up the gold.
Justice is on our side!
- Why did you pull my towel off
in front of those pigs?
- [Choking]
- Wasn’t there another way?
- [Gasps] It worked, didn’t it?
Hey, Mack. How you been?
Jackie, is that you?
- Yeah, it's me.
- [Metal Wind Chime Clattering]
- I need you to take a look at this key.
- Let me see it.
The key is in three parts.
Some of these knobs
are insulators,
which means that
when you turn the key,
you could set off
an electrical system.
The design of the handle
also has some purpose.
- It could be a trap, do you think?
- Yes. It could easily be that,
unless you know the combination number
that was used to open the door.
So whoever locked it
is the only one who knows.
- I'm afraid that's right.
- Okay, Mack. Thanks.
Good luck.
Okay, what's the deal?
I got a piece too.
Hand it over, quick.
Empty your pockets.
- [Coins Jangling]
- Come on. The other one.
Where's the key?
- He's got the gun!
- Hold it!
- Hey, you there.
- [Yelling]
- Hold it.
- [Sirens Wailing In Distance]
[Tires Screeching]
There! Get him!
- [Man] Don't let him get away!
- [Man Grunts]
- [Woman Screams]
- Sorry.
Come on!
This way!
After him!
- Did you see that?
- That's my car!
- Look out!
- [Men Yelling]
- [Yells]
- [Mover] Hey! What are you doing?
No!
My painting!
[Groaning]
Hey! What are you
doing with my paint?
One more shot, please.
[Crowd Screaming]
[Woman Screaming] Grab my baby!
My baby!
Help me! My baby!
- [Truck Horn Blowing]
- No!
- Bumpy ride, huh?
- [Cars Approaching]
Oh! My baby.
- Hold on!
- What the hell are you doing in here?
- Hey, look out!
- [Men Yelling]
There!
Watch it, you idiot!
Get him!
[Sighs]
[Duke] There's 240 tons of gold
in the secret base.
[Jackie] lf l live long enough
to see it.
These guys really
want to get me.
Could they be old enemies
who are after you?
They don't want me.
They want the key to the base.
Well, you don’t think I invited you here
to enjoy an African safari, huh?
[Horn Honking]
Wait a second.
Hey. What are you
doing here?
- I've decided I'm going with you.
- Who's the lady?
- She's the German officer's
granddaughter.
- Ah. It's a pleasure.
- How do you do?
- It's not some happy vacation
we're going on.
And anyway, you're related to one of
the officers in charge of the mission.
- I really...
- Why does everyone
treat him like a criminal?
I want to prove his innocence
once and for all.
- Take me with you.
- I'll be responsible for her.
I thought we already agreed
that it’s me who has the final word.
Ada, perhaps she can
help you on this mission.
This time, I'll make the decision.
You will all go together.
Of course.
Thank you.
I'm most grateful.
- Thank you, sir.
- Surely.
Thank you, sir.
- Be careful. Best of luck.
- See ya.
[Chuckles]
- Good hunting.
- Bye-bye.
- [Background Chattering]
- [Men Yelling]
Oh, my friends!
I thank the gods that smile on you!
Thank them for us too.
- [Spits]
- Whoever you are, good evening.
How's the food?
- Not too bad.
- More precious than gold.
Gold? Sounds interesting. Tell me
more about it. Sit down. Please.
[Innkeeper] Oh, it's only a rumor.
I'll tell you someday.
- It seems as though everyone's
heard about the gold here.
- Mm-hmm.
- Where do you think the real map is?
- Why are you so curious?
The soldiers who were to bury the gold
could have hidden it here.
But they’ve been missing for so long,
they're probably all dead.
So? To disappear
doesn’t mean they're dead.
Well, then why didn't
any of them show up?
Maybe they decided
to keep the gold for themselves.
Are you saying they may have
conspired to dig up the gold?
Let's say, together.
Or even on their own.
And then, of course, they could
have asked their relatives
to help them secretly.
Are you suggesting my grandfather
got me to spy on the two of you?
Oh, no. You don’t suppose?
You don’t like me. It was quite obvious
from the moment you saw me.
lf that's the way
you feel, I'm truly sorry.
Hey, come on.
Cut it out, both of you.
You shouldn’t argue
in front of strangers.
Does the meal
not please you, eh?
My cooking is not so bad.
You must eat.
- It's my specialty.
- I'm not hungry. I'm going upstairs.
- What...
- Please bring the check.
You can take these away.
- You eat nothing, eh?
- No. Not tonight.
lf you really don't want it, sir.
Table three.
Look here, we work
as a team, don’t we?
Hey, it was you who agreed to bring
her along. I was against it.
- Jackie?
- Hmm? What's up?
- Come and see.
- Have a good night.
- Is anything missing?
- I don't know yet.
- Look at this whole mess.
- Jackie!
- What is it?
- It's awful. All of my luggage.
It's... It's everywhere.
You see?
They've gone through everything.
Good thing I hid the key
somewhere safe.
- Why isn't this hidden somewhere safe?
- [Gasps]
Oh, my back!
Use your head! Keep listening!
Listen!
[Yells]
- Who do you think did it?
- You know, that's a good question.
You came upstairs first.
Didn’t you see anyone?
Do you mean to say
that you’re accusing me?
Of course not.
But if the shoe fits...
You saw my room.
It's been searched.
Hmm. You could easily
have done it yourself.
It's what you call
"covering your tracks."
- She's crazy.
- Elsa.
- One minute, Jackie.
- What is it?
Your room is
pretty small, isn’t it?
Sleep in here, if you like.
On the sofa, of course.
The room isn’t large,
but the bed is comfortable.
- Uh, wait!
- Don’t be afraid.
African vampires
don’t like Chinese blood.
Hmm.
[Hisses]
[Grunts]
[Shrieks]
Don't let her upset you.
I'll go try to straighten things out.
- Is the coast clear?
- How should I know?
- You're breaking my back!
- Quiet, you idiot!
It's fine.
l just don't get her.
Oh.
Harder work than
pumping water on a farm.
Hey, take it easy.
Just be nice.
- Lock your door.
I'll be back soon, okay?
- Yeah, okay.
[Door Creaks Open]
[Grunts]
Don’t play games with me.
- Stop it!
- I'll kill you!
- It's me!
- You Peeping Tom!
- It's me, you idiot!
- You?
[Groans]
It's me!
I knew you wanted to hit me,
but did you have to hit so hard?
Oh, yes. I knew
it was you, all right.
That’s why I hit you so hard.
[Gasps]
- Are these friends of yours?
- Check their bags.
Oh, not again.
l just finished packing.
- Oh, ho, ho. Thank you.
- Uh, may I?
- Thank you very much.
One more chocolate.
- Yes. Bye-bye.
- Thank you. Thank you very much.
- Bye-bye.
Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
Room service.
Room service. Huh?
[Chuckles Nervously]
What's that?
Chocolate.
Good sleep, eh?
Eh, no. No chocolate.
No good sleep.
- "No good sleep"?
- Go away. We are not sleeping.
Ah!
[Chuckles]
- Condom?
Good sleep. Very good sleep.
[Chuckles]
Oh, condom! Good.
- Huh?
- Magic.
Ah! Magic.
Good magic! The very best!
Strawberry flavored.
- Good night.
- [Groans] Strawberry?
Good night,
and good luck, eh?
[Chuckling] Condom?
- Good night.
Ada?
Don’t come in here! I'm busy!
Go away! I don't want you in my room.
- Why are you treating me like this?
- Because I don't want you here. Go away!
- Jackie, what's...
- Uh, some business has come up.
It won't take long.
Go back to your room.
"Business"?
What kind of business?
[Sighs]
This business.
I don't usually wear
a towel to do business.
- What's going on?
- Hey!
Go away! I'm busy!
Can’t you see us getting smelly
in here? [Sniffing]
- Get it?
- Eww. You're crazy.
[Sighs]
Get out!
- [Gasps]
- Hand them over!
- Huh?
- Cut the funny talk.
- Where are the goods?
- I'm sorry... Hey!
[Grunts, Groans]
Don't hurt him! Please!
- Just tell us what you’re looking for!
- Where is the map and the key?
I don't know where they are.
[Grunting, Groaning]
- Oh! Please!
- You better talk, or we’ll kill him.
I can’t tell you.
I don’t know!
Stop! Stop!
Stop hitting me!
Try hitting her, okay?
No.
Well, okay. Talk,
or I'll take it off.
[Gasps] Jackie, if he takes
my towel, I'll be naked!
Good. That's something
I've been waiting to see.
- [Grunts]
- [Cries Out]
- Jackie, help me!
- Huh?
- Don’t move!
- He said not to move!
- Open wide! Bite!
- [Yelling]
- Oh, Jackie! Oh! Oh!
- Ah. Good sleep.
Freeze!
- Room service. Room service.
- Get in.
Watch her!
What have you got?
I have roast chicken.
Roast chicken, you see?
You like very much?
You see? Roast chicken?
You see? Yes!
[Chuckles]
Have a nice dinner. Bye-bye.
- Oh, no.
- You can't fool me, lady.
- Don’t move!
- Huh?
- Drop the gun, or he’s dead.
- [Elsa] Great! I knew you’d do it!
I knew you’d see the gun!
Good idea, huh?
Yeah! That's for
pulling off my towel.
- You're going to get a big kiss.
- I'd like to kiss him too.
He's so sweet.
- [Women Laughing]
- Yeah, go on. Get rid of them. Huh?
Jackie?
What are you doing?
- Why is there so much tape on the gun?
- I was afraid it would fall out.
Oh, I'm sorry.
- I told you not to come in.
- We don’t want to hurt anyone.
We mean what we say. We want
what we came for... the key and the map.
Oh, but I am telling you
I don’t have it!
You searched my luggage.
I'm not the type to lie.
I know nothing. I am sorry if you don't
believe me, but what can I do?
- I don’t know where it is. Huh?
- Don't fool around with me.
- Oh! [Shrieks]
- Hmm? Hmm.
Why were you just
standing there staring?
- Why did you pull my towel off?
- She meant well. Don’t start.
- Why'd you hit me?
- Serves you right for looking!
- They looked. Why don’t you hit them?
- What?
Cut it out. We're wasting time.
Start with her.
Me?
- One,
- I think you better talk.
- two,
- He can’t mean it.
three!
- No!
- Hold it. I'll talk.
- Are you really going to talk?
- You told me to.
But it won't help them.
You're completely surrounded
by my men out there.
[Ada] Are they really out there?
I'm not kidding.
Hey, guys, you can come in.
[Yelling]
- The gun! Oh!
- You take it.
- I got it!
- Don't let him get it.
- Give it to me!
- [Yells]
- Don't... Don’t move!
Put your hands up!
- I've got the cartridge.
Huh? Back to you!
- I can't take it.
- Ada, back to you!
Look out!
There's still one shot in it!
- Ada, where are you going?
- I've got to get this out of here.
- Help, Jackie!
- Jackie, wait!
- Help! Thief! Help!
- Give me that!
That man, he took my things!
Help! Stop him!
Over there!
That man!
- Somebody!
- Excuse me!
Go away!
I got it.
Move it! Go away!
- [Man] Look at this!
- Come here!
- Someone, help! Help me!
- Ada! I'm up here!
- Here! Catch!
- Got it!
- What's going on?
- [Both Women Scream]
- Let go of me! You're hurting me!
- Gimme that key!
It's gone!
[Groans]
They key is down here.
I see it!
- Another condom?
- Please help. Robbers!
- Robbers? [Gasps, Yells]
- [Man] You!
Ada, did you pick up
the key? Did you?
- [Man] I can't sleep.
- Jackie, hurry! It's there!
- I see it.
- [Women Chattering]
- I can't move my leg!
- I'll get it.
- [Elsa] Oh, careful.
- Wait! Don’t you come down here!
I can see it from here.
I'll pick it up. Stay there.
- The roof might collapse.
- [Yelling]
Ada! Do you want
your towel? Ada?
- Are you okay?
- I'm all right.
It's just my towel is gone.
- Where's the key?
- Over there.
[Innkeeper] It's all right.
I'm coming!
- Where are these robbers?
- They're over here!
Hurry!
Those two down there.
- Shoot them! Hurry!
- Pay me.
- What?
- No money, no shoot.
- Oh, wait a minute. There.
Ahh! That's good.
Take the gun.
- You shoot.
- Why?
Good deal.
Gun is yours.
- [Shrieking]
- [People Screaming]
Don’t leave me!
Powerful gun...
[Gasps]
- Let's go back to my room.
- Okay.
- I cannot walk backwards.
- So turn around. My arms are stuck.
Left foot first.
[Men Chanting Prayers]
Get a move on!
Ah, welcome. The gods have smiled
on you. How many rooms would you like?
There's a German girl here
with two of her Chinese friends.
Where are they?
I like papers.
No money, I no talk.
- [Sputtering]
- You will talk.
Uh, yes, yes.
I remember now.
Uh, they left
early this morning.
- Where'd they go?
- The desert pass.
To the desert!
Forget about him.
May the gods punish you.
That smell.
[Groans]
[Jackie] Hmm. Look at that.
[Ada] Jackie, maybe she needs help.
- Hey, can we give you a ride?
- Oh, thank you. I'm so lucky.
Momoko, you say you’ve come to do
some soul-searching here?
Well, we are born and we die,
and we don't know why.
- The desert holds the key.
- Is it the key to life or death, huh?
What kind of desert
philosophy is this?
Jackie, do you understand
what they are talking about?
What are you doing?
[Screams] A scorpion!
- Where is it?
- It's okay. It's gone.
- Just a scorpion.
- On your back!
Help me! Help!
- Will someone come and help me?
- Momoko, look out!
- It's poisonous!
- It's my pet. The little darling.
Oh, where! [Crying]
- [Both Laughing]
- It's all right.
It's my pet, Ding Ding.
He's a darling. He doesn’t sting
unless someone provokes him.
I'm sorry
he scared you.
[Chuckling]
It's a lovely moon tonight.
It looks beautiful, doesn’t it?
I must get some rest.
- [Birds Twittering]
- [Camels Braying]
[Footsteps Approaching]
- Attack!
- [Men Yelling]
Stop! You dare to strike a chief?
Bring me my gun.
[Ada] Jackie!
Stop with the noise,
or I'll beat you to death!
Give it to me.
[Groaning, Yelling]
- What kind of scorpion is that?
- A King Scorpion.
[Sputtering]
- Hurry, Chief! We got the car
and women. Let's go!
- Forget him!
- [Men Chattering]
- Let's go!
- Are you all right?
- I'm okay.
They're gone.
Oh! My poor Ding Ding.
My little Ding Ding!
Okay, now.
- You guys okay?
- I'm okay, but John is badly wounded.
- Who are those people?
- They are desert bandits.
- At sunrise, we must follow them.
- They will kill us if we follow.
I'll go with you, Jackie.
- But first of all, I want
to bury little Ding Ding.
- Of course.
[Distant Chatter]
Where did all those people
come from?
From the desert.
It's a market.
- They're holding an auction.
- Let's wait until dark.
- Get down.
- Uh-huh.
All right. Any advance on 20, there?
Going for 20, once.
Going for 20, twice.
Going for 20, sold to the goat herder!
- [Elsa Shouting]
- [Catcalls]
- Jackie, I've got the rope.
- Good. Keep a lookout.
Okay.
A young and gorgeous
Aryan blonde.
And here's an Oriental sex
kitten whose eyes are filled
with fire that you can buy.
Rarely seen in the desert.
The blonde has a big behind.
One you can really
sink your teeth into.
The kitten is as soft as silk.
Who can ask for a better bargain?
Starting price, ten camels
for the two of them.
- [Man] Twenty!
- [Auctioneer] Twenty!
Any advance on twenty?
Momoko, do you know
how to drive?
Jackie, someone's coming!
[Moaning, Groaning]
What are you doing, huh?
Sorry.
- Anyone for 65?
- Sixty-five beasts.
I have 65 from the sheik
in the sunglasses.
Going once... 65.
Going twice... 65.
- [Cracks Whip] Sixty-five
for two beauties.
- [Man] Seventy.
Seventy! The chief over there
bids seventy camels. Anymore?
- Seventy-five!
- Eighty.
- Eighty-five!
- Eighty-five.
- Ninety!
- Ninety-five!
- Ninety-five.
- One hundred.
- One hundred and five.
- One hundred and ten. One-twenty!
- [Sheik] One-fifty!
- Oh!
- [Laughing]
- Who is that sheik?
- The man who has made us rich!
Sold! Once, twice,
three times... 150! Sold!
In. Now, step on...
- [Grinds Gears]
- Try again.
[Chuckling]
Oh, such beautiful skin.
- Get off!
- I like it. I like it. I like you.
[Whispers] It's me.
It's me, Jackie.
I've come to save you.
Don’t worry.
[Chuckles]
Oh, the sheik is the one!
I will go with him!
- Don’t you come near me!
- [Grunts]
[Men Laughing]
Someone has stolen
my clothes!
- [Laughter Continues]
- He knocked me out!
- That's him! He’s wearing my clothes!
- Get him, men! Now!
[Yelling]
Come! I'll catch you!
- [Women Yell]
- I'm sorry! Come on!
Switch on the ignition
and steer.
Step on it. Oh! Oh!
I forgot the hand brake!
[Yelling]
- That way! Get them now!
- [Crowd Yelling]
Hurry! Hurry!
- Come on! Ah!
- Help! Jackie, I can't get out!
[Screams]
Shut up!
Great! Get Momoko!
Go! Go! Go!
- There you are! Where do we go?
- Hurry up!
Over here, Momoko!
Stop!
Hey, Momoko!
[Men Yelling]
Hang on!
Wait! Come back!
[Leader] After them!
- Our Jeep!
- My girls!
- [Jackie] Where are we going?
- I don't know! The Jeep’s taking us.
- [Jackie] It's not
a rollercoaster! Steer!
- You’re sitting on the wheel!
[All Yelling]
- [Women Panting]
- Take a rest.
[All Groaning]
I help you.
- [Gunshot]
- [Women Scream]
[Laughing] Praise Allah
for delivering you to us again.
- Now you will lead us to the base.
- Hmph.
[Panting]
Here, Amon.
lf this map is correct,
we should be near the place.
Nothing but sand.
It could take years to shovel that up.
- You sure you got it right?
- Read it for yourself, you idiot!
- [Sighing] Here. Let me see the map.
- Let her have a look.
Let's see.
- You got your compass?
- Yeah, sure.
Ahh! Turn the compass,
not my arm.
You see.
We're near the spot.
There are so many
sand dunes out here.
After 40 years, the base could be
completely buried.
- Are you sure it's supposed to be here?
- It should be right here.
The map could have
been wrong.
Military maps are always accurate
within approximately three miles.
"Three mile"? No problem. Let's call
a cab. Be there in half hour.
Allah! Have mercy!
- [Muttering]
- Don’t move!
[Yelling]
Amon!
Throw them some water.
- Here.
- We don't ever want to see you again!
- Thank you! Thank you!
- Why are you thanking them?
It is our water!
- Let's go.
- Bye-bye.
The fates will punish you!
You will burn in the fire of eternity!
- Keep away!
- [Gasping]
This is the worst
failure of my life.
Gotta be a first.
Who's this?
- My grandfather.
- Oh. I stayed there
with one of my friends.
- The natives who live there
worship this idol.
- [Gasps]
See? I bought this figurine
because it resembled the idol.
Jackie, look!
- This picture was taken near the base.
- Could you take us there?
- Mm-hmm.
- Maybe we'll be lucky after all.
That's the place
in my photograph.
Don't go down there. The natives
that live there are very vicious.
- We know all about vicious people.
- Thank you, Momoko.
- Take care.
- Thank you for bringing
us here. Bye-bye.
- Good luck, Momoko. Bye-bye.
- Be careful! Bye!
- Hey. Are you praying?
- Checking if it's hollow below us.
[Chuckles]
Jackie! The entrance
is over here!
- Jackie, wait for us.
- Follow me.
[Moans] Ahead!
Don’t panic. It's an animal head,
not a human one. Come on.
- [Shrieking]
- Did you see that?
- What are you talking about?
- [Women Screaming]
- What is it?
- Keep moving!
- [Women Shrieking]
- Hurry! Hurry!
- Hurry!
- This way!
This way. This way!
- What are we gonna do?
- Out of my way!
Your hands!
Get off! One at a time!
- He's coming!
- [Elsa] Take that!
- [Beeping]
- Ow!
- Uh, we're tourists.
- Smile!
Take another picture.
Get going!
- Dead end.
- Hey! Where do we go?
- Here. Take one.
- What is it for?
Go! Go!
- [Grunting]
- He won't go down!
Hit him higher! Agh!
[Men Yelling]
- Ever seen that?
- Chinese kung fu. Hmm.
- [Whispering]
- [Grunts]
[Chanting Together]
Oh, look.
I don’t suppose they're...
dancing to be
friendly towards us?
I think it's
an old tribal custom.
Come on. Let's try.
[Chanting Continues]
Right foot first.
[Crowd Chanting]
You may as well stop.
Reinforcements just arrived.
- [Crowd Hooting]
- What do we do now?
[Quietly]
Improvise.
- Look at all those ox heads!
- Just go! Jump!
Quick! Quick!
Hurry!
- They are not following us.
- Who cares? Come on. Let's go!
- Are they waiting for more men?
- [Jackie] I don't think so.
- There's too many already.
- Help! Help!
- Ada!
[Chanting]
- Where is she?
- What are you doing down there?
- Hurry! I'm sinking!
- Hold on!
[Chanting Continues]
- Take hold.
- [Fabric Tearing]
[All Yelling]
[Chanting Continues]
[Cheering]
- Look. Someone there.
- Yeah, come on!
Give us that water!
Come on!
Give it here!
- That's mine.
- It’s yours?
Hey, boss!
Here!
- Strange.
- Ugh!
Looks like we found
the base, all right.
- [Blowing]
- [Snorting]
[Gasping]
It's my grandfather!
[Jackie] How do you know?
- His name's on the cross.
- He's been murdered.
- How do you know that?
- Look at this.
- [Gasping] A knife?
- I'm sorry.
- Are you sure it's him?
- It is him.
- What is that?
- It's a book.
No, don't! Jackie,
how could you do that?
- What kind of book is it?
- It's my grandfather's diary.
What does it say in it?
Does he mention his killer?
"We pushed ahead 12 miles.
Four men..."
Go on
to a later page.
"The war has gone badly today,
but I believe our general...
will lead to final victory.
Our Field Marshal Rommel
is unsurpassed in military maneuvers."
On the base.
Does he mention that?
"They trucked over a load
of heavy metal.
The captain ordered me
to move it into Lab One.
- What is so heavy? Could it be gold?
- It is the gold base.
He gave me 18 pills and ordered me
to give them to my men.
I've been asked to work out
a code forth combination.
I will use Eliza's birth date."
- Who is Eliza?
- That was my mother.
- Her birthday. That's it!
- l just wonder how
all of this fits together.
- Go on reading.
- [Jackie] I think
I know what happened.
lf I’m not mistaken, your grandfather's
guards are down here.
When they completed the mission,
he made them take the poison pills.
No wonder he was so unhappy.
He was ordered to kill his men.
Strange.
He had 18 men.
Fifteen down here, two upstairs.
That's only 17.
- Where's the last one?
- [Man] Don't move!
- Get in there!
- Oh!
I'm the 18th guard. I was clever
not to obey your grandfather.
- Are you all right?
- Who is this man?
I'm pretty sure
you are Adolf.
How do you know my name?
You forgot it’s on this.
The last man didn't swallow the pill.
So he killed.
- You killed my grandfather!
- Your grandfather was not a good man.
In fact, he had
his own men poisoned,
and when I refused to take it,
he broke both my legs!
I've been waiting
for this day many years.
The gold belongs
to the United Nations by right.
Since it's here,
the gold is mine.
No one is going
to take it away.
[Henchman] Right.
You guys go first.
- Gold always attracts the scum.
- Get going!
I have an idea. Maybe if we offered
to pay more, they'd work for us.
They might decide
to take your share as well.
Shut up
and get a move on!
Get going!
Move it! Move!
[Shouting]
This way! Follow me!
This way! This way!
Quick, quick, quick!
- [Henchman] Up ahead!
- [Ada] Oh, I can't see!
[Grunting, Panting]
- [Henchman] Come on! This way!
- Go on! Careful!
- [Henchman] Let's go!
- Mark! Mark!
- Yeah?
- That generator. Get it started.
- Now!
- You guys, start the generator.
- We'll go after 'em!
- Ammunition's down there.
[Adolf] Don't shoot
unless you have to.
There's a whole arsenal
down there!
- Hold your fire!
- Right.
- [Mark] Check it out down there!
- They're coming!
- Go! Hide over there!
- Okay. - Quick.
- Where are they?
- I can’t see them anywhere!
[Mark] Spread out!
Search every level!
[Hinge Creaking]
[Door Slamming Shut]
Hey! Did you guys
hear that?
- [Automatic Weapon Firing]
- Don't shoot! You can't break
through that door, idiot!
Try again.
Don’t turn the lights on.
It won’t take long.
Here we go.
Ahh! Jackie,
they found us!
- There's one missing.
- Jackie!
Don’t switch 'em on.
Do not let them get away!
Almost there. Faster, man!
Okay, switch 'em on!
Don’t move!
Hold it!
Drop your guns!
- [Jackie] Get in line.
- Jackie, you were great.
- You are amazing.
- Ada, pick up the guns.
- I'm gonna find a rope to tie them up.
- Okay.
I'll shoot.
Better believe her, boys.
She shoots like a maniac.
Not a move. Whoa!
- Where are you from?
- Keep your hands... Oh!
- Oh, Jackie, save me!
- No hope of that now.
Get them!
Jackie!
- Look out!
- [Gasps]
[Clanging]
- [Sighing]
- [Screaming]
- Jackie!
- Save us!
[Grunting]
I'm busy.
Take him down!
Come on!
[Shouting]
- There he is!
- Get him!
Get up there!
Go on!
Head him off!
Block the stairs!
This way, guys!
- It's a dead end!
- There's nowhere to go. We're trapped!
- You wanna fight, you bully?
- Ha!
[Knuckles Cracking]
[Growling]
Get him!
From the other side! Hurry!
[Electricity Crackling]
Pull me up!
- [Groaning]
- [Together] Ole!
- [Together] Charge!
[Together] Yea! Charge!
One more!
[Grunting]
Yeah, he's out.
Let's go help Jackie.
- Pig!
- [Grunting]
- Take that!
- [Shouting]
[All Laughing]
We did it!
Ole!
- [Laughing]
- [Gunshot]
Go!
Get that gate open!
- Got it!
- I think my hand is broke!
It's fine.
[Grunting]
- [Women Whimpering]
- You bitch!
Serves you right!
All right.
Where is it?
Where's the key?
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
Wait!
Before you shoot.
I'm the only one who knows
how to use the key.
It was my grandfather who used
my mother’s birth date for a code,
and I'm the only one
who knows it.
And I alone know
the procedure to unlock it.
Is it that complicated?
Yes, it could be,
but it’s the only way to go.
- Where is it?
- There should be a corridor over there.
Let's get moving.
You, boy.
- You go first.
- Wait.
You open it.
What's the combo?
There are three steps.
First you need the number.
- My mother’s birth date
is on the 16th of September.
- Nine, one, six.
Right.
I have waited over 40 years
for this day to come. Now it’s here.
[Gasps]
[Screaming]
You lying scum!
You're trying to kill us!
- I swear I wasn’t lying.
- I told you all I know
about the procedure.
And my mother’s birthday
is the 16th.
- Are you sure there isn't
something you forgot?
- Let them go. Go on.
- [Gasping]
- No.
- Let's go.
- Are you sure you got
her birthday right?
Of course.
It's on September 16.
What is it on
the Chinese calendar?
- They don’t use the Chinese calendar.
- See? It’s written here.
"I will use
Eliza's birthday, probably."
Then he wasn’t sure he'd use it.
Could he have used yours instead?
- I wasn’t born yet.
- Oh, but of course not.
- What is it?
- It's my grandfather's tag.
- Could it be?
- There are two.
But which side is it?
- Six, nine, eight?
- [Together] Could that be it?
[Whimpering]
Those bullets can go
through ten people.
The first number
is six. Go.
[Tumblers Clattering]
- [Tumblers Clicking]
- Nine. Nine.
Quit poking me.
Move your hand.
[Tumblers Clattering, Clicking]
Eight.
- Please? Number eight?
- [Tumblers Clicking]
- [Loud Creaking]
- It hasn't opened. Why not?
- [Gasps]
- [Clicking, Creaking]
[Gasps] What is that, Jackie?
- [Women Whining]
- [Clicking]
[Ada] What's going on?
- [Loud Slam]
- [Screaming]
[Electricity Crackling]
[Exhaling]
[Creaking]
Get the other one.
[Grunting]
Gosh. How come
it's so small?
- Well, where's the gold?
- This is only the elevator, imbecile.
Come on. Let's go.
Hurry up.
Over here.
[Man] Look at that.
Remove the canvas.
Up there. Go on!
Don’t stand there.
At the top of the stairs.
- Leon, go quickly!
- Sure.
- Oh, man.
- Look at that.
Oh, my God.
- That's incredible.
- Look at all that gold.
- We're rich! We're rich, boys!
- [Shouting, Cheering]
[Shouting, Laughing]
Push me in!
Push me inside!
They won't listen
to you anymore.
- [Leon] Beautiful!
- [Adolf] Push me inside.
Do you hear? I order you!
- Yes!
- All right!
Wow! Rich at last!
Hey!
- [Women Gasp]
- Don’t move!
Tell them to drop their guns,
or you’re dead.
You must do as he says,
and quickly. Do you hear?
- Put down your guns. - No.
- Put them down!
Imbecile, you had better
listen to him!
Don’t you call me
an imbecile!
Then you had better
find a way to rescue me!
Now I'm the boss.
Don’t talk like that to me.
You're what?
This is rebellion!
With 240 tons of gold,
we can afford to rebel against you.
Okay, if you want it,
go ahead and kill him.
- [Gasps]
- You calling my bluff?
I'll count to three.
Drop your guns, or he’s dead. One.
- [Ada Whimpering]
- Two.
- Three
- Ahhh!
Well, he wins.
lf you won't kill him,
then I will.
There's more gold to come,
and only I know where it is.
I would be willing to share it
with you all equally if you
will just not kill me.
I don’t think
you've many tricks left.
Keep an eye on 'em, Joe.
You come with me.
Let's move the gold.
[Mark] You heard me.
Move it!
- I got this one over here.
- All right. Okay.
- Let's get the gold out of here.
- All right!
- That's it.
- Whoo!
- Gimme a hand.
- [Mark] Get this stuff loaded up.
Yes, sir.
[Men Chattering]
- I got this one.
- Incredible!
- [Chattering Continues]
- [Motor Whirring]
[Shouting]
- Damn it!
- Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
- Let's get him!
- Now what, huh?
There's a control room upstairs.
Go up and see how Jackie’s
doing. You, push me up.
[Elsa] Ada, down there!
Look!
Where's the light?
It's impossible to see. Over there.
- Nothing works.
- [Grunting]
- Damn it! Which is the light switch?
- There are switches everywhere.
- Don’t let go!
- Oh, my!
[Screaming]
It's even worse!
- Let's see. Um...
- [Engine Winds Down]
- We've got to help!
- [Ada] Why is Adolf
taking so long to get here?
It's a suction!
Damn strong!
Oh!
It started again!
Turn it off yourself.
Oh, what now?
We could try the panel there!
Break it!
Quickly!
[Screaming]
[Jackie Screaming]
- Don't touch that button!
- I already pressed it!
- It stopped!
- They've all stopped!
- You stop them.
Don’t you understand?
It's a military base.
It's a self-destruct button.
The whole place will blowups.
In 30 minutes, we'll all be killed.
Why didn't you wait for me to get here?
[Sighing]
- [Snarling]
- [Adolf On P.A.] Jackie!
Jackie! Hurry!
We have no time!
Get the door!
- I won't let him escape me.
- Open the door, you idiot!
[Screaming]
Superman!
Bumpy ride.
Fun, though.
Now see Superman's footwork!
- Warn him! Where's the mike?
- Ohhh!
Quickly! The whole place
is going to explode, Jackie!
Explode?
What?
We only have 20 minutes?
We were trying to help you get out,
and then Elsa pressed that button.
There is no way out of here.
There could still be a chance
if we can blast through the air vent.
- The air vent? Are you sure?
- That's right.
The weakest section of this facility
is the ventilation shaft.
Yeah. Wind power!
- Oh, help me, Momoko.
- Okay.
Jackie, here's the switch you wanted.
Adolf refuses to come with us.
I am not coming with you.
I should have died 40 years ago.
I want to be with my friends.
This is where I belong, you know. Bye.
He's staying, but if we want out,
we better start.
Okay. You three
get ready.
Starting... now.
You're running out of time.
I will turn the fans to maximum
power gradually. Good luck.
Here, Jackie.
You've got to push the switch.
[Whimpering]
- You're not bringing all that!
- It's my share!
- [Grunting] No!
- Too bad for you!
- Ahhh!
- What a waste!
[Warning Siren Blaring]
Now!
[Groaning]
[All Screaming]
[Screaming]
You're safe now.
Let's go.
Run! It's gonna cave in!
- Oh, the gold!
- So what?
At least
we're still alive.
Come on. Go.
[All Yelling]
A consolation prize?
[Gunshot]
Oh, the fates be thanked!
They've led you back to us.
Here. Here's the gold you wanted.
Might bring you luck.
Who wants gold?
We want water!
Here. You can
finish it.
[Shouting, Grunting]
It goes to show
we never really know what we need...
or want.
I never thought
I'd see people fighting over water.
Uh! Water! Water!
I suggest we get together
and look for it.
- Well, you are the expert here.
- I don’t know.
I think we should go that way.
There should be an oasis to the north.
- You sure?
- No.
- I think we should go over this way.
- It's that way.
No. We've got to listen
to our desert expert.
We've walked over a million sand dunes.
Where's the water?
I am sure it is
just over the next one.
Are you sure?
- [Jackie Muttering]
- [Ada] As I was saying,
only a quarter of the desert
is covered in sand.
[Amon] The gods must be
angry with us!