Father,
do you have a name for this sword?
It's called "The Ultimate Sword,"
the best sword I've made in my life!
Which is better -
martial arts or a good sword?
A good sword can...
help a novice
And make an expert really powerful
But most important is
who is using the sword
Cloud, remember:
Kindness is invincible!
Lord Conquer has led Conquer's Clan
to the strong position it is today
Mud Buddha, you are praising yourself
You are in charge of the geomancy here,
and if we do well, so will you
I hope so
Jester,
you are Lord Conquer's right hand
Truly a servant of one,
master of thousands
It's a dangerous way of living
We always envy each other
His Lordship has been waiting all day
Greetings, Lord! Greetings, my Lord!
You've come
You know me well
How will I do in my duel
with Sword Saint?
My Lord's martial arts skill will find
no match in the world
Neither No Name in the south nor...
Sword Saint in the north
are worthy opponents
Mud Buddha,
you talk like Jester
Lord, I didn't teach him to sweet talk
If I can defeat Sword Saint,
Conquer's Clan will rule the world
But I can tell you, my Lord...
You may have to wait ten years
for the duel with Sword Saint
Why do you say that?
The time has not yet come
My Lord, a gift for you
What is it?
"When the Wind and Cloud combine,
the Fish with Golden Scales
becomes a Dragon"
These two birth charts
are of the two disciples you will have
One is named Wind
The other is named Cloud
Wind and Cloud?
The wind is formless
The cloud is unpredictable
As to...
how to find them,
that depends on your fate
And after I find them?
You will be invincible
for the first half of your life
And the last half?
Find Wind and Cloud first
Jester
Yes, my Lord
Use whatever means necessary
I must find Wind and Cloud
Yes, my Lord
This is a Persian treasure,
it is called the Ying Yang Magic Box
It has 108 Celestial Stems
and Terrestrial Branches
My Lord is so intelligent,
if you can find...
the correct combination
the box will open
It holds the answer to
the second half of your life;
I will
then be able to give you an explanation
Do not use force to open this box
If you do...
the box will explode
and all will be destroyed
Good!
I, Conquer, can certainly open this box
Out of my way! Go away!
"By order of Conquer's Clan,
all boys with the listed birth chart
must become disciples of Conquer's Clan"
Master!
Master...
Conquer's Clan seeks boys with
young master's birth chart
Do not let them know of Cloud
Yes, sir
Cloud
Come here
Wind, did you memorize
the Blizzard Rhyme I taught you?
Don't worry father, I remember
"When river reaches Buddha's knee,
Burning then will Cirrus Cave be"
Father, what does this mean?
This river floods all the time
Legend says,
when the Buddha's knees are flooded,
Cirrus Cave up in the mountains will
catch fire,
and the villages will be flooded too
Wind, I have carried you a long time
Why don't you get down and walk with me
I like the feeling of
being carried by you
Father, will we see mother on this trip?
Who told you, Wind?
I am already ten, no longer a child
Promise never to mention
your mother again
All women are trouble
Conquer, I have retired for many years
Why must you force me?
Fire Unicorn in the south,
lce Blizzard in the north
My goal in life is to gather
the World's Ten Greatest Weapons
For you to posses the Blizzard Blade is
a crime punishable by death
I have already buried it in the hills
If you want to fight, we'll use bamboo
But if I win...
I'll choose between Blizzard Blade,
or your wife
If I loose today's duel...
You can have the Fire Unicorn Sword
You must pay for your madness!
Whispering Prince,
you're using bamboo today
It is only the first round
I'll give you two years
Bring Blizzard Blade to me then
at the Cirrus Cave
I'll take your wife for now
Wind, wait here for Father
Father, I hope you'll bring Mother
Its been sometime...
You're alone?
Ying
Husband
How have you been?
Very happy
Whispering Prince, don't you understand?
Ying wanted to come with me,
I never forced her
Ying!
Didn't you notice?
Ever since your retirement
to the countryside...
I have never smiled
I want a man to be celebrated hero
I want your humble visitors...
to adore me
Now I understand...
Only by robbing you of your love
I can make you fight back
I shall force you to use
the Blizzard Blade
I'll tell you a secret
I only used her
to vent my desires
I never loved her
Conquer, you are despicable!
Mother!
Wind! Mother, I miss you
We will fight to the death,
but I have one request from you
Speak
I have only one son, Whispering Wind
If I die, please let him live
Yes, I promise you
I have dishonoured you and your father
Mother!
Mother! Don't!
Mother...
Father!
Father...
Wind, run! Don't worry about me!
No, I won't run away!
Run! Hurry! Father...
What have we Stridings done to you?
Why do you destroy my homestead?
It is our Lord's order
Hand over your son
and the Ultimate Sword
Give it to Conquer's Clan
and we will spare you
I'd rather die than surrender!
We'll find the sword
after we kill you all
I have hidden it
Even if you find it,
you cannot use it without it touching
my blood or that of my son's
There's a child
Is he Striding Sky's son?
Perhaps not, he isn't crying at all
Take the child and all the swords
Yes
Where is Father? Where is my father?
Calm down!
My father brought you here
or you would've been eaten by wolves
Curious? This is Conquer's Clan
I'm Charity, daughter of Lord Conquer
He's Frost
You've fainted for two days
Have some tea
I'll take you to eat later
Isn't it too hot?
My Lord's brilliance will
unite Heaven and Earth...
These three years,
the Clan has gone far
We are the greatest Clan now
I am naming heirs to
further strengthen us
Frost,
Cloud and Wind will be
my closest disciples
With their Frost Fists,
Cloud Palms and Wind Kicks
Conquer's Clan shall dominate
the martial arts world
My Lord's brilliance will
unite Heaven and Earth
"Unable to meet in battle
Duel to death in ten years. Sword Saint"
Mud Buddha, you are a true prophet
Why didn't you attack with
your full force?
Master's body is invaluable, I dare not
If I cannot handle your attacks,
then I deserve to die
Master Cloud,
His Lordship wishes to see you
and Master Wind
Bring the coloured stones to Charity
Yes
Come in
Charity, this is forbidden ground
We are not allowed to go in
To outsiders only,
but I'm Lord Conquer's daughter
This is the Sword Grave,
our sword storage
If not forbidden,
it may still be dangerous
That's why I asked you to go with me
I'll go in myself, cowards
You two go, I'll stand guard
See, you cherish me more
Let's go, Wind
Women are trouble
Look! Magic fire!
No, these are just firebugs
I'll take some home
Someone's coming. Let's go
Let's go
"With the unique powers of
Wind and Cloud,
Lord Conquer has obtained supremacy
and expanded his empire
With the strength of his martial arts,
Conquer has overcome all
but one of his rivals - Sword Saint"
This prophecy is a gift from Mud Buddha
Together with another verse
I'll be able to find out my fate
That other verse is still locked
in this magic box
I have been unable to find
the right combination for ten years,
and Mud Buddha has disappeared
for ten years
Frost, Wind, I have lost my patience
Go and find Mud Buddha
Legend says...
in order to find Mud Buddha,
one must first seek the Fire Monkey"
Use this clue in your search
Aren't you coming with us?
I am only a watchdog
Once I step outside these gates
I'll be doomed. Very fragile,
I can't take hardships
Jester!
Wind, your Wind Kick
lacks practical experience
Therefore, on this journey
be careful and obey Frost
I understand
Cloud,
You have a different mission
I await your orders
Fong in Unchallenged City wishes
to become our ally
I told him
I wanted his Unchallenged Sword
as a token
It's his birthday,
so go to Unchallenged City
I will bring back the Unchallenged Sword
I want more than that...
Bring back Fong's head
Can you do it?
Yes, Master
You have achieved 70% of your power
with your Cloud Palms
You can succeed,
with Hawk's and Bat's help
Father, I want to go, too
Charity, what is it?
If they can go, why can't I?
I see...
Would you like to go with Wind,
or Cloud?
You are going to kill, leave me out
Wind, I'll go with you
We're not going to play
Neither am I
We'll help out the weak and be heroes
These are not the teachings of the Clan
Jester, be quiet
Prepare to leave tomorrow
Yes Yes, Master
Charity, stay
Cloud
Have you been to the forbidden
Sword Grave with Charity?
Yes, but please don't tell Master
Chase me, Grandfather!
Little Pigtails, don't run!
Old Man, we'll be fighting here
Leave quickly
Surround him!
I respect you as a Shaolin monk
Give me the Fire Monkey!
What a pity
No one can turn down
an order from the Unchallenged City
"To find Mud Buddha,
first seek the Fire Monkey"
Why do you want to find Mud Buddha?
It is my father's 60th birthday
I want Mud Buddha to wish him well
and tell him he will live
for a hundred years
Life is determined by fate
If Mud Buddha were to tell him
he will die on his birthday,
then what?
Nonsense!
Unchallenged City is at its strongest
Together with Conquer's Clan,
Father will rule the martial arts world
Soon, even you Shaolin monks will have
to let us have our way
Fire Monkey belongs to
the Shaolin Temple
Mud Buddha stole it,
so he must return it
If you refuse to hand it over,
you might not return to Shaolin!
I am Whispering Wind
Pardon my interference
Let's go
They're about to fight. Let's go
Old Man, stay and watch what happens
You don't know what is out there
It may be more dangerous
Who dares to be so arrogant?
What a pity
Wind Kick, Frost Fist
Don't you recognise
the Masters of Conquer's Clan?
I thought you are all one family
Sometimes,
quantity doesn't mean anything
We'll soon...
be one family
Why fight among yourselves?
Don't talk nonsense
Don't associate yourself with us
All of you against one monk?
You can't possibly be good men
You're saying
we take advantage of our numbers?
Frost, have we gone too far?
I don't think so
I've only disabled their powers
Buddha have pity!
Your Holiness, this is my first quest
Please make it easy on me
and lend me Fire Monkey
I promise to return it in a month
I told you it belongs to
the Shaolin Temple
If you must take it,
then how are you
any different from those people?
Without Fire Monkey,
we can't find Mud Buddha
What shall I tell my Master?
You too are looking for Mud Buddha?
You have no respect for me!
That's right!
Shut up!
Your Holiness, please help us
We need Fire Monkey
I'm sorry but I cannot oblige
Then, excuse us
Excuse us
Firey!
You can insult me some more if you want
Now that I have Fire Monkey. I'm leaving
Wind!
Forget him
Why?
We only needed the Fire Monkey
in order to find Mud Buddha
Now that he is already here,
why bother?
Sir, please do not disguise anymore
So you recognise me
I know
you're a famous master of disguise
To keep calm
in the face of such chaos...
you're no ordinary man,
and when the innocent girl
cried out to the monkey,
we knew
Grandpa, where are they taking Firey?
Don't worry, they won't hurt him
I revealed too many secrets
about the future
and was punished by heaven with boils
all over my body
Only Fire Monkey can suck out the poison
and ease my pain
Please bring it back to me
Don't worry, sir. We'll try our best
That's good to know
Let's go
Lord Conquer must be anxious to see me
After you
Master Fong, you are a great man
3,000 advisors
Loyal subjects everywhere
You have all good things one can desire
On this birthday
your only son Ming has given you
a 3-day banquet,
but why is he not here celebrating?
He's out...
looking for Mud Buddha
Has Conquer's Clan sent anyone?
Not yet, Master
Young Master, mission complete
Master Fong looks very happy
Everyone
from Unchallenged City is there,
except his only son Ming
We'll strike at 4 a.m.
Yes, sir!
Who is it?
Forgive my intrusion
Oh, it's Young Master Striding Cloud!
My master orders me to bring back
the Unchallenged Sword
People from Conquer's Clan are so vile!
Master, someone is still alive
Please don't kill me!
Finish the job
How did this happen?
Why? Why?
Who murdered our whole clan?
What good are you?
What good is Mud Buddha?
Fire Monkey is innocent. Don't punish it
Your Holiness
I beg Shaolin to seek justice...
Help me seek revenge, and justice
To kill all of Unchallenged City
in one night...
Only Conquer's Clan is powerful
enough to do this
Buddha have pity on us
Wind, what are you thinking about?
My father died here
Master rescued me
Legend says...
Blood Bodhi fruits grow in Cirrus Cave
They heal all diseases
and increase powers
But no one has successfully gone in...
and returned
They say a Fire Beast guards the fruit
Master Wind,
do you know anything about
your father's duel?
So you've heard about this?
Master said,
it was swordsman Southern Unicorn
He also died in the cave
Promise me one thing
Please tell us
Little Pigtails has lost her parents
I'm her only family
I want to help her find a foster home
Do you sense something wrong
about this journey?
When a buddha of mud crosses the river,
he cannot guarantee safety for himself
Father has been murdered
most brutally...
we are all
that's left of Unchallenged City
You must help us!
We have to avenge Unchallenged City
and my father
You must help me seek revenge. Revenge!
That couple agreed to adopt
Little Pigtails
Master Wind is a kind person
If everyone in Conquer's Clan
were like you,
the martial arts world would be at peace
How is Conquer's other disciple, Cloud?
Cloud is an unpredictable, moody loner
But his martial arts is
the best among us all
Exactly as destined
Grandpa!
Come back, Grandpa!
"The Dragon is powerful
but will be stranded
when Wind and Cloud become a storm"
Years ago, you left without a word
Leaving me with this piece of junk
Now that the puzzle is revealed
Explain what it means!
"Wind and Cloud will make you,
and break you as well"
What does that mean?
One cannot fight against his destiny
My Lord's ten years of good fortune
has passed
It is now the turning point of your life
"Wind and Cloud will make you,
and break you as well"
Obviously, it means that my life is now
under the control of wind and cloud
But does that wind and cloud...
mean my disciples
Whispering Wind and Striding Cloud?
It is inevitable that
the servant will usurp the master
This is destiny. Mortals cannot fight it
Destiny?
I don't believe in destiny or fate
My Lord was a great believer until now
Mortals are like that
Believing in good fortunes,
but not believing in bad ones
Deceiving themselves!
We are the masters of our own destiny!
I hold my destiny in my own hands
I will change my fate!
"Cloud"
"Wind"
Four famous weapons
of the martial arts world...
One blade. Three swords
All priceless treasures
Blizzard Blade is buried in Cirrus Cave
The Ultimate Sword has never been found
Fire Unicorn Sword
and the Unchallenged Sword
are both mine. I am pleased
Cloud, you didn't disappoint me
You taught me well
Good!
Father!
Behave like a lady
I heard Cloud had returned
I just wanted to see him
Thank you for your concern
Who's concerned about you?
I'm concerned about what you owe me
Did you bring them?
What does Cloud owe you?
Father,
your passion is to collect famous swords
I'm a collector, too
I am fond of interesting stones
Cloud owes me 19 colourful stones
Ridiculous!
My Lord! My Lord!
Masters Frost and Wind have returned
Where are they?
They are outside, and dare not enter
Get up!
You lost Mud Buddha due to inexperience
Thank you, Master
But Cloud succeeded,
and brought back the Unchallenged Sword
I'm going back to my chambers
Striding Cloud's mood is
like a wild horse... unpredictable
It's been ten years,
with Fong's death...
I'll hear from Sword Saint soon
We'll finish our duel from ten years ago
I must intensively train
my Trinity Strength
Come here
Before I go into seclusion,
I must settle something
Among my three disciples,
you have the kindest heart
Wind, it is my wish that
you marry my daughter
I will arrange for a date
Charity, don't you like Wind?
Don't ask me
Look after her
Master, let's discuss marriage later
Your father and I had betrothed you
to each other
I didn't tell you earlier
because it wasn't the right time
You and Charity have grown up together
What a perfect match
If you do not consent
I will be greatly disappointed
Congratulations, Wind
Skinny, Girlie, let me tell you...
father wants me to marry Wind
Well, I do like Wind...
but I also like Cloud
Charity, it's me, Wind
Wind
I want to talk to you
Come in
This is not Sword Grave
You won't be punished
I will be brief
Go ahead
I remember when Master brought me here,
you were the first to offer me some tea
I felt very warm
Father said if he hadn't rescued you,
you would've been eaten by wolves
I remember
So when he mentioned about
marriage today,
I was very happy
But I know love must
come from both sides
I don't know
whether this is Master's wish,
Or if it is your own wish?
But if this is not what you want,
I won't force you
Does Charity know about this?
I'm the one to decide
She has to accept it
Your eyes,
they're the same as
when I took you in ten years ago
If you're unhappy about this
you may be excused from attending
the wedding banquet
Doctor Yu
You're the most respected person
in our village,
You must help us
You heal us when we are ill
You mediate our fights for us
We respect you the most
We have had bad harvests,
and Conquer's Clan taxes are high
We can barely survive
Please help us
I will go and speak with Conquer and
explain your hardship
Thank you, Doctor Yu
Thank you Please get up...
Go home
Muse and I will go within these few days
Let's go home
Muse
Father, your arm is burning again
It does not seem to belong to me,
sometimes it hurts so much
They say I can heal all diseases
But I cannot heal myself
Father,
are we really going to Conquer's Clan?
Wonderful! I can go see the world
I can learn to mingle, and explore
What did you say?
Just babbling
Welcome!
Master Frost! Master Frost!
Here, try it on
Jester, what are you doing?
The groom will have to tie this on
Do me a favor, see how it looks
You look pale and sick
Not as pale as you!
Charity is getting married
Are you depressed?
No. Who said so?
I watched you all grow up
I can see through everything
If you love someone,
you only wish her to be happy
Wind has a kind heart
It is good that Charity is marrying him
Congratulations!
Such a tremendous event
I wouldn't miss it for the world
It's the groom! Congratulations!
I hear
your fiancee is pretty as a flower
I'm not the groom
I am...
I'm Frost of Conquer's Clan
Welcome, on behalf of my Master
So you're the famous Frost
Lord Conquer has three disciples
Fists, Palms, Kicks
Each has a speciality
Too bad they don't use swords
You are so crazy about swords
You must be the one known as Seedy Sword
That's right!
Father, look over there
I am Doctor Yu from the Lake region,
representing 320 villages of 16 towns
I seek a meeting with Lord Conquer
Your invitation?
Is there a celebration?
Oh, good!
I have never been to a banquet!
Please tell me,
is it a birthday, marriage,
or a birth?
Muse
There're so many people anyway
One more
or one less wouldn't even matter
Please let us go in to take a look
What is it?
Jester I am Doctor Yu...
Mr. White Face, can you let us in?
What a smell! It stinks!
It's the scent of a woman
Women?
We pick herbal medicines
in the mountains
These are the smells of herbs
You pick medicinal herbs?
Then you must be Heal-all Doctor Yu
with the Fire Beast Arm?
That's right
I thank you on behalf of Lord Conquer
Come in, we'll talk after the banquet
Look after yourself
Leave us
Yes, my Lord
Father
It's your wedding day today
It makes me miss your mother
You look a lot like her
Do I really?
She died giving birth to you
All these years,
though I've had other women,
the one I love the most...
is your mother
I always thought
you had a heart of stone
Charity...
Do you know what I wish?
Not for the best martial art
Not to be ruler of the world
But to see...
my daughter live a happy life
I wish you to marry well
Father