Haul in that line or it'll foul us.
Start the engine.
- Where are you goin'?
- I'm gonna make a phone call.
Hello, mayday, Orca. Coast Guard?
Coast Guard, this is the Orca.
Do you read me?
Coast Guard, this is the Orca. Do you...
Excuse me, Chief.
That's great. That's just great.
Now, where the hell are we?
You're certifiable, Quint.
You know that? You're certifiable.
- You're certifiable, but I'll tell you this!
- Boys.
I think he's come back for his noon feeding.
Hook me up another barrel.
Bring her around after him.
Full throttle.
Get me right up alongside of him.
I can't rev it up that high,
it's not gonna take it.
Five degrees port.
All right, hold your course.
Five degrees port now.
Hold your course.
- Fast fish.
- Watch my hand.
Be sure you watch my hand.
Follow me. Follow me.
Lad, you watch him now.
Starboard. Starboard.
Run him down.
Hard apart.
Watch him.
Starboard.
I can't believe it.
Two barrels and he's going down again.
It's incredible.
- They're up again!
- Now what?
Why don't we lead the shark into shore
instead of him leading us out to sea?
Grab a couple of poles.
Hang on now, we're going around.
Into starboard. Easy.
I'm gonna back her off now.
Keep a watch on it, boys. Watch him.
All right, gentlemen, snag them.
Now then tie them to the stern cleats.
Brody, bring your end around the cleat.
That's right, it'll lock itself off.
Give him room, Brody.
Stay clear of the line.
Watch it. Stand clear.
Stand away from those stern cleats.
Back home we got a taxidermy man.
He gonna have a heart attack
when he sees what I brought him.
Throttle back. You're losing the cleats.
My God, this one, too. They're both going.
- He's eating his way through that line.
- He's working his way right up to us.
Come on, Quint. Hurry!
Out of my way.
Watch it.
Untie this. He'll pull out the transom.
Make it fast.
I can't. It's trying to run.
Pull, you son of a bitch!
Go ahead. Pull your bloody heart out.
It's impossible!
We're breaking up! Cut it!
Watch your hands!
Cut it quick. I can't hold it!
He can't stay down
with three barrels on him.
Not with three barrels, he can't.
What about us?
Get the pump out of the locker
in front of you, will you?
We're gonna sink, aren't we?
Keep an eye on the barrels.
Pump it out, Chief.
Starting to go under.
He can't with three barrels on him.
Not with three he can't.
You ever have one do this before?
No.
He's chasin' us. I don't believe it.
I'm gonna draw him into the shallows.
Draw him into the shallow water.
I'm gonna draw him in and drown him.
- We're headin' in, Brody.
- Thank Christ!
- You ever had a great white do that?
- No.
How far do we have to go?
Don't put that much pressure on it.
- Goddamn it.
- Shut up. Get back there.
Hold on.
"Farewell and adieu to you,
fair Spanish ladies
"Farewell and adieu, you ladies of Spain
"For we received order
for to sail back to Boston"
You idiot, you burned out the bearings.
All right stop the boat. Stop the boat.
Stop it.
What exactly can you do
with these things of yours?
I think I can pump 20 ccm
of strychnine nitrate into him.
If I can get close enough.
Get this little needle through his skin?
No, I can't do that.
If I can get him close to the cage,
I can get him in the mouth.
- That shark'll rip that cage to pieces.
- You got any better suggestions?
Easy.
Up she goes.
Ain't got no spit.
Try and keep him off me until I'm lower.
Okay, okay, I'm ready.
Bring him up, goddamn it.
Bring him up now!
Pull it up. Pull it.
Come on, Quint, bring him in.
It's giving way.
Rig something!
Got it?
It's comin'.
Slower.
Show me the tank.
Blow up!
Smile, you son of a bitch!
Quint?
No.
Can we get in on those?
What day is this?
It's Wednesday. It's Tuesday, I think.
I think the tide's with us.
Keep kicking.
I used to hate the water.
I can't imagine why.