Look over there!
Is this all?
It's what the boss gave me.
It should be more.
Let's go, it's late!
Osvaldo, let's go hunting?
Sure.
He dreamed.
Yes, he dreamed again.
Never leave him on his own,
be watchful.
Let's go.
Bring us something to eat.
Okay!
Going hunting again?
We'll have success today!
You're incapable!
Indians!
Get out of here!
Sooner or later |'|| shoot you!
Look, a macaw!
Don't miss him.
He ran off.
I'll go tell the others.
Now you'll go
where you can feel good.
Let's go back.
Put her in face-down.
Angué is here, I feel him.
| return your things to you.
Your bracelet,
telephone, clothes, shoes.
I don't want your things around,
that's the end of it.
You wouldn't listen to me.
You were always stubborn,
but now you're alone.
I don't want your things anymore.
Now get out of here,
you'll be left alone.
I don't want to live here anymore.
Get moving, burn everything!
Hurry!
NATIVE RESERVE
PROTECTED AREA
Osvaldo dreamed about Elma,
he knew she'd hang herself.
Who's Osvaldo?
Lia's son.
Then I have to teach him
to be a shaman.
We can't keep living on the Reserve.
We must return to our land,
to our tekohé.
Or else we'll all die.
FORBIDDEN TO SELL ALCOHOL
TO NATIVES
Another two cases of suicide
on the Dourados Native Reserve.
The bodies of two adolescent
natives were found in the forest.
Steves, turn that shit down!
I'm no Indian!
Chew your change.
Nadio, how's it goin'?
Hello, Dimas.
Hello.
What do you need today?
I brought a list.
I'm not extending credit
to you anymore,
you already owe me,
you're fooling with me.
You don't have all that money.
I'll leave you
the horse and carriage.
What are they worth?
Two thousand.
Two thousand? They're worth
one thousand at most.
That's not even a horse.
One thousand, okay?
Let's make it one thousand.
And I'll offer you a drink.
Dimas,
I need a ride.
A ride to where?
Steves!
Two sacks of flour, three of rice...
Oil, yerba mate...
Let's go,
I'm not waiting any more.
Let's stop here.
Here?
Yes.
But this is Moreira's land.
This is Moreira's land,
come on, I'll take you back.
We're staying here.
I'll take you back.
It's here.
This is our tekohé,
our ancestors are buried here.
We're staying here.
We'll starve here.
No one will starve, we'll hunt,
you'll have to learn.
I'm not going in the forest,
Angué is there.
It used to be all forest here.
All forest.
What are those people doing there?
I don't know.
Give them an inch
and they take a whole yard.
It starts like this and then
becomes a never-ending problem.
Tie it.
Someone‘s coming.
How are you doing?
Fine.
Who's Nadio?
I am.
You?
My name's Tito.
I'm very tired.
So?
I heard you were setting up camp,
I've come to stay.
To stay?
Yeah.
Think we'll be here long?
I don't know.
The sun's setting.
It'll be dark soon.
That's him.
Is it true
you dream what happens later?
Yes.
Then you can be a shaman like me,
but you have to start now
on the right path.
You have to learn
to recognize the good voices
and defend yourself
from Angué, the evil spirit.
You must take the maraca now,
always caress and play it,
it'll defend you.
Give me the maraca.
This is your maraca.
You have to sing and pray.
You have to play it all the time.
Louder!
Nadio, he's dreaming again.
Wake him up.
Osvaldo...
Go get some water.
Go away!
Neo!
It's full of shit here.
I clean,
but the birds keep shitting.
If they keep shitting,
you keep cleaning.
Have you got any left?
Yes.
The lighter too?
I have everything.
Let's go.
What are you doing here?
What are you doing here yourself?
What's that?
This?
It's a cell phone
to talk with Nhanderu.
A cell phone...
Go talk to your god somewhere else,
we want to swim.
Did you come to the river to pray
or to screw that little girl
with the crooked legs?
Let's go.
Let's go!
Look at that.
They're already bringing water in.
We can't let that happen.
You have to be a scarecrow,
you gotta scare them.
My bag!
You bastard!
You'll starve here.
They're coming!
Here they are, it's them!
Sit down here.
Look at this bottle, you must
be as transparent as this.
As you prepare to become a shaman,
you mustn't touch any woman.
|'|| teach you secret prayers,
very powerful prayers that can kill.
Tuiuiu.
Blue Arara.
Gaviéo de penacho.
Did you tell them
the Indians here eat people?
They cut them in little pieces
and roast them on the fire.
Maria, must I call your father?
Can't we have
a moment's peace here?
What's going on?
Cut this foolishness.
Get out.
Lia!
Talk to the white man,
he has something in his belt.
Let him come,
he won't hurt us,
it's just a gun,
don't be afraid.
Hi.
What are you doing here?
I don't have any water.
Go to the river.
I can't leave my post.
I'm not giving you any.
Come here.
What do you do with that gun?
Jerk-offs?
Do you shoot jerk-offs
with your gun?
You jerk-off!
Nadio!
Tito, where's Nadio?
Are things okay?
Things are okay.
There's work at Fazenda Santa Rita,
I'll take you there free.
How many days?
Ten.
Too many.
Just ten days, come on.
No one's going,
the women can't be left alone.
I'll go.
Go, take your things
and don't come back.
Let's go, Tito.
Mami!
There's a woman in Dourados
looking for a housemaid, how about it?
Have it your way.
But stop coming to me
asking for credit
and telling me
you've no money for food!
Want work?
Don't show up at the store!
Help me!
Grab hold!
Where did this meat come from?
It's payment for work.
Show me the brand.
Show it to me!
What are you doing here?
You can't camp out here.
Your place is in the Reserve!
Why don't you go back
to the Reserve? That's your place.
What are you doing here?
You'll just cause problems,
why are you here?
Give it to her.
Here, Lia.
You're learning,
you can't eat that meat!
You mustn't eat it!
It can hurt you,
you must sing, you must pray.
What do | eat then?
Go hunting!
Kill other animals.
There's nothing left to hunt.
The jaguar attacks us,
but he's our brother.
The cobra attacks us,
but he too is our brother.
The cow occupies our land,
he's our enemy.
You mustn't eat it!
I don't know, you find a way.
I'm not a lawyer, you are.
They're camping right outside
my property and I can't do anything?
I'll wait for news.
Continue, it's very nice.
No.
Why not?
You can't watch.
Now you can continue.
You killed the cow, didn't you?
Don't worry,
my father has lots of them.
What's your name?
Maria.
Where are you going?
To the man with the long nose.
His dick is long, not his nose!
The man with the long dick!
Would you like some water?
Do you have any cookies
for the children?
Yes, I do.
Want a piece?
Yes.
Do you eat people?
Don't you ever wash?
You stink of cheese!
Lovely Indian!
Put it there in the earth.
Get out of here!
You can't stay here.
Leave.
Out!
Come on, out.
Be careful, stay away from that.
You'll get sick.
There are no marks
of either jaguar or cobra.
But it can't be hoof-and-mouth.
So what is it?
The curse of the Indians.
I saw arrows stuck in the ground.
It's the shaman.
Look at him.
I told him to wash,
his dick is full of lice.
What are you doing here?
We're getting water.
Go away!
Here comes butt beautiful!
He's coming to you!
No, to you!
Careful, he's always straight up.
Everything straight up
comes down sooner or later.
He'll get here with his dick out.
You have to get out of here now!
Listen to him, the grouch.
You're always asking for water,
now help me carry it.
Now sing for us.
I'm not going to sing.
Come on, sing!
No!
If you leave, |'|| sing.
You scared the animal off.
What was it?
It was my lunch.
A macaw.
What do you pray at the river?
I pray...
I pray to Nhanderu
to be able to see people's future.
If I pray a lot,
I can also break your scooter.
Why break my scooter?
If I want to, I can.
Is it hard to ride a scooter?
Will you teach me?
Get on.
Behave yourself!
This is how you accelerate,
push this and change gear
and then let up slowly, understand?
Want to try?
Okay.
Slowly.
Neo!
Listen to me,
take them this money
and tell them there's work
with tourists next week.
But on one condition,
that they go back to the Reserve.
It won't do, even for transport.
How much is that?
Three hundred.
What did you bring today?
Rice and beans.
No meat, right?
What more could you want?
You're not staying with me tonight?
Too bad!
You can't even screw, you fag!
Ask your sister!
How's it going?
Fine.
The boss sends this money
and says she'll give you more.
There's more work for you.
But you have to leave here
and go back to the Reserve.
What does she say?
She brought us money,
but we have to leave.
Why don't you come live with us?
What do | tell the boss?
Did she give you the money?
Yes.
Give it to me, I have to buy
many things, more people are coming.
I won't, we have to buy food.
There is a lot to eat in the forest.
That's not true,
there's nothing there, just Angué.
Don't think about Angué, the dead
are dead, think of the living.
I won't give it to you, go hunting,
we need the money for food!
I won't give it to you.
Mami, I came to help you.
Here.
Why did you come?
To help you!
Why did you stop?
Put the water down.
Why?
Put it down.
Take my hand.
Why 7
I want to be with you.
You're too young for me.
But I want you.
You're too young.
Mami, I love you.
Me too,
but you're too young for me.
We can't.
Papa, Mami doesn't want
to stay with me.
You're too young for her.
But I'll grow.
I'm going to marry her.
Come here everybody!
Tito!
Come, I have to talk to you.
Osvaldo, come on.
Nadio!
There's good work
at the Fazenda Irajé.
Twenty reais a day, plus meals.
And I'll take you for free.
No one's coming, this is
the center of the movement.
How many days of work?
Five, one hundred reais,
plus meals, let's go!
Let's go to work,
there's nothing left to eat.
No one's leaving.
I'm going to break your truck.
Let's go to work.
Get in, come on.
You go too.
Let's go!
Off to work!
I'm not going to work, the shaman
ordered me to pray and sing.
Let's go!
Don't go!
Come on!
Come on.
Think I'm an idiot?
What the fuck were you thinking
sending money to the Indians?
Do you think by giving them money
they'll leave?
I'm working.
You have to understand...
You have to understand that...
You know nothing
about how things work here.
You're a foreigner
who just got here.
The next time you speak to me
like that, I'm leaving, clear?
Don't butt into my affairs,
I know how to resolve things.
She went and got an Indian woman
to work here...
Who's making all this ruckus?
I don't want to hear
those shit songs.
Shut your mouths.
What are those?
We're making braids for children.
What's your name?
Jessica.
What did you bring?
This.
Is this all you brought?
So many days of work
and this is all you bring?
You didn't say you were going.
You were very drunk that day.
The center of the movement is here,
you know that.
You did what you wanted and
sold yourself to the fazendeiro.
Ireneu, aren't you ashamed?
You have obligations
and you don't obey.
Now I want you to leave.
Take this and eat it.
You're too hard on your son.
Speak to him more kindly,
he'll take your place someday.
Lia...
I want to say something.
What?
I want to be with you.
No, I don't want you.
Why not?
I don't like you.
I'm alone and so are you...
But I don't want you.
Why not?
I want you.
Come on.
You'll die old and alone!
Ireneu... You used to go hunting
and now you won't anymore.
You followed your friends,
you worked in the fields
and you sold out
to the fazendeiro.
You did this to yourself
because you wanted to.
No one made you do it.
But that's enough now!
|'|| forget you and leave you.
You were my son, my family,
but now I want
nothing more to do with you.
I leave you alone, I'm going.
Don't cry, let's leave
or Angué will enter you.
Haven't you ever seen a woman?
Man of the beautiful click!
Lovely Indian!
Long click!
Big click man!
Tasty man.
Beautiful man.
Tasty click...
You really have a big one!
Tasty man.
Come out!
Out!
This way!
Come this way!
They're talking about
the land in Brasilia,
the courts have
to resolve the problem.
As for you, Nadio,
don't let your people
enter in other cultivated fields.
And particularly
not in the residences.
Moreira will commit himself
to keeping his people
from entering this occupied area.
If any one of you
does anything foolish,
I'll be forced
to call the federal police.
I don't want justice violated,
okay?
With all due respect,
Mr. Attorney,
I don't see
how you can talk of justice
when this land has been invaded,
a land duly recorded
at the land office.
We don't need papers,
I don't understand them
and I don't even care.
We are here.
The land is ours.
We no longer have the forest,
we no longer have
anything to survive on.
We're here
and we're staying here.
This land...
My father arrived here
more than sixty years ago.
That's three generations.
I was born here.
My daughter grew up here.
| work this land
from dawn to dusk,
so that it gives fruit.
| sow nourishment
so that people can eat.
Stay here until Moreira leaves.
Look here...
This story pains me deeply.
The only way
to eliminate this anthill
is to find the queen and kill her.
If anything happens
to any of those Indians,
the suspicion of everyone
would fall on me.
Moreira,
if you don't uproot this evil,
what's happening in your fazenda
will happen in all the others.
Third hut, he's sleeping.
Is that you, Nadio?
No! They'll kill me!
Why so many suitcases?
Please...
I'll be gone a while,
three or four months.
Until things get straightened out.
You're the ones who killed Nadio!
You're the ones responsible!
You too, Maria, you're cursed,
you're a whore!
A bitch!
Cowards!
And now you run off!
You bastard!
You killed him!
You wretches!
Get out, fast.
I'm not afraid of you!
Or you either!
Put that gun down!
Get out or I'll kill you.
Shoot me in the face then!
Big ears man!
Get out!
You have to do something,
when your boss comes back,
tell him I'll take him
and cut his head off!
I won, you lost.