Its body is armored
in iron and concrete.
Its mind is wrapped in
computers and high technology.
This is the city and
the time we're living in.
But most people ignore
the unexplainable or mysterious.
Those things that we can't
figure out through ordinary logic.
Around these ordinary people,
following common rules...
all the while seeking out
strong desires and pleasures...
and hanging on to
a little happiness...
there exists a vast and fearful world
of darkness beyond our time and space.
I'm afraid I know all about it.
Taki, here you go.
I lost the bet, so I have to pay.
You just guessed wrong.
Yeah, but I've been a
bartender for a long time.
I've never seen a girl whose kept
her guard up as much as Kanako.
How could I have imagined
that she'd accept your offer.
Tough Luck! I'll keep this.
Well, she's sure taking her time.
Thanks for waiting.
Here she comes. 10,000 yen.
What do you mean 10,000 yen?
Well, it's none of your business.
Is it Taki?
Right.
Oh, don't be so secretive.
Alright, I'll find out tomorrow!
Let's go!
So long Ken. Get back to work!
Got it.
See you.
Hey Taki, why don't we bet on
the Giants and Tigers game, next?
A re-match?
I accept!
That night, I was happy.
Like I fell into rapture.
She was the girl that I liked, at the
bar I frequently visited for 3 months.
Finally, she asked me
to come to her place.
This was a surprise.
What made you change your mind?
Well...
You live in this luxurious place?
Isn't that a little too bold?
Don't you like impatient girls?
Yeah, but I am more of
a romantic than I look.
You're so strong.
I'm so attracted to it.
This woman has a devil inside.
She completely changed
from how she was at the bar.
It was very different than what I'd
expected, but I'm not complaining.
You...
You realized a little too late.
You're of no use to me anymore.
Don't worry.
I'll relieve you right now.
It's OK.
I already got what I wanted.
What did you do to Kanako?
You're so worried about the girl?
I didn't kill her.
I just made her sleep in
the restroom, at the bar.
See you soon.
What is going on?
There's not much time before
the signing of the peace treaty.
WlCKED ClTY
Yes, you're right... yes...
Oh, of course I do.
Yes sir, I will do it.
Yes, thank you very much.
I'll talk to you later.
Mr. Taki, the President
wants to see you.
Sure.
Oh, I guess your playboy lifestyle
has caught up with you.
Take care of yourself.
Thanks for your concern.
It pierced my heart.
Hey Taki, you want to join us today?
Mah-jong? Sounds good!
But I'm completely broke.
You better look for another sucker.
There's no bigger sucker than you.
See ya!
You guys are all the suckers.
I'm Renzaburo Taki.
I work at the sales department of an
electronics company in Shibuya, Tokyo.
This is my official job.
Mr. Taki from the
sales department is here.
Let him in.
It's a MacGreggor, isn't it?
Yes. I finally got it.
The grip and hit are really nice.
It's perfect, just what I expected.
I like it.
By the way, I heard you
had a strange experience.
I guess we can't trust
the peace treaty.
Is it those extremists?
It seems so... but for now, I filed
a complaint with their leaders...
through the Vatican.
Well, you better be careful
which women you date.
Your biggest weakness is women.
Any reason for them to
be taking action now?
The signing ceremony date for the next
peace treaty has been moved up.
It will be held tomorrow, in Tokyo.
That's very sudden.
Investigations has discovered that
people from the other side...
have illegally infiltrated this side
by using a shield breaker.
We must take care of this quietly.
As you know...
I have no doubt, that when this
peace treaty is signed...
it will start a new era in the
relationship between both sides.
The terms of this treaty will continue
the peace for another 500 years.
Anyway, a V.I.P. is arriving at
Narita airport, 7 p.m. tonight.
He's attending the signing ceremony.
So I want you to guard him
until tomorrow.
For the Black Guard,
Mr. Renzaburo Taki.
The Black Guard,
that's my other face.
Your life is always
in danger with that job.
Who is he?
Giuseppi Mayart.
You must have heard of him.
He's finally coming here?
We can't close the
peace treaty without him.
Please guard him closely.
He' II be the main target of the
extremists who are against this treaty.
Thank you for giving me
such a thoughtful assignment.
I'll do my best.
Oh, one more thing.
They want to assign you a partner.
Her skills are the very best and
I hear she's good looking, too.
Well.
She' II be waiting for
you at the airport.
Look for the best
looking woman there.
One more thing.
She's from the other side.
A Black Guard from
the other side?
Yes, so don't get any
strange ideas.
Don't worry. I know,
more than anybody...
how scary the women are
from the demon world.
There is the world where humans live,
and then there's another world...
...the demon world.
We've been in contact with
each other throughout our histories.
The two worlds have sought interaction,
harmony, and coexistence...
Still, there have been
fierce and bitter battles...
fought between our worlds,
again and again.
Finally, the heads of our two worlds
made a treaty for coexistence.
It was a kind of a secret deal.
The truce is renewed
every couple of hundred years.
And now, as we approach
the end of the twentieth century...
these two worlds are trying
to close the new peace treaty.
I guess we can't resolve this
with friendly conversation.
Do you think that toy
will work on us?
Don't worry, this toy
isn't what you think it is.
That sounds good.
I'll get you this time.
Shit.
You're very cute.
But you don't look
good in this world.
Good bye.
I guess you're my partner.
You saved my life.
For a skilled guard of this side,
you're still quite a wimp.
I'm much obliged by
your honest opinion.
I'm...
Renzaburo Taki, 25 years old.
Height 180 cm, weight 65 kg,
blood type AB.
Official job is a salesman of
an electronics company.
Monthly salary is 230,000 yen.
Single.
Bingo!
And you? Don't forget to include
your measurements, too.
I'm Makie, no last name.
My job on this side is as a model.
But I've got no reputation in that job.
The sponsors don't like me because
I scared off all the other models.
I see. Your beauty is too perfect.
It's almost unreal.
Thank you for the compliment.
Now we have to hurry.
He will be arriving soon.
Your dedication to the job
is such a sad thing.
But it's nice too meet you.
What kind of person
will we be guarding?
Giuseppi Mayart.
A traditional demon emissary
and a great medium...
I believe he had retired and was
living in the ruins of Pompeii...
or at the heart of the Apollonian Mountains,
after he attended the signing ceremony...
of the last treaty in 1851.
I heard he's the key person
for the signing ceremony.
Anyway, I hope everything goes smoothly.
But why did they choose
you as my partner?
I guess you must have great skill.
You mean you don't trust
women from the demon world?
Almost never.
I've had a very bad experience.
You probably deserved it.
I guess so.
This partnership is not
what I wanted either.
But I just follow my
superior's orders.
It doesn't matter. We have to stick
together until this assignment ends.
I agree.
Shit! They really did it.
This is too much to do,
just to kill one person.
It's terrible.
Indeed.
I had sensed danger,
so I moved up to an earlier flight.
I guess I was right.
Who are you?
I'm Giuseppi Mayart.
Nice to be with the
two of you tonight.
Well, I was told that a woman from
the other side would be guarding me.
But you're much more
beautiful than I had expected.
Don't be rude!
What did you just do to me?!
You're the rude one.
What do you mean?!
This is a greeting in the human world!
Mr. Mayart, I think it's good
that you're so lively...
but you have to be a little discreet.
Even though it's
just for tonight...
she and I have been
assigned to protect your life.
You can do anything you want after
the treaty is signed tomorrow...
but until then, I want you
to follow our rules.
What's the big deal? She's just a
woman of the demon world.
Who knows what kind of real form
she has under that beauty.
You already must know what happens
to the people who sleep with them.
They all became zombies after their
life energies were sucked out.
Do you know why so many people
still want to have sex with them?
Because of how it feels.
People feel such incredible ecstasy,
it can't even compare with human sex.
You should be careful too, because...
You should watch your tongue, sir.
I don't feel confident
protecting you by myself.
You don't have to worry about that.
A job is a job.
I will protect anyone,
even at the risk of my own life.
Oh, those words make me feel
really secure.
Then I leave the matter
to both of you.
Please make sure that
no danger comes to me.
But, I still want to taste this
special ecstasy at least once.
Anyway, where are you taking me?
A special hotel built
with an energy barrier...
to shield us from the demon world.
It was made for the safety
of special V.I.P. like yourself.
This place seems boring.
I came all the way to Tokyo.
Can't I visit some hostess club
or a massage parlor?
I was looking forward to going there.
I want you to stay in this room.
What a musty smell in here.
I've been waiting for you.
I'm the owner of this hotel.
You must be exhausted after
such a long trip to come here.
As you can see, our hotel
is not luxurious, but...
...please hold out for a while.
We will provide the
best service we can...
Long time no see.
Are you doing well?
Yeah. I've heard you
are doing well too.
How are the guest
arrangements today?
Don't worry,
it's just you guys.
It seems like a big terrorist group on
the other side wants to destroy this.
We should be careful, even if this
area is protected from invasion.
The barrier's resistance level has
been increased by three times.
Don't be so nervous!
How's he doing?
He's pushing me to take him out
and have some fun.
Mr. Mayart.
Oh, Taki.
This woman is so stubborn!
Look at this.
Massage Parlor Playboy.
They provide so many good
looking women. Let's go there!
You can't go anywhere.
Oh... you don't like that place?
How about this one?
Cabaret Club Queen Mate!
This must be the place for us!
Let's go to this place!
I will go with you wherever
you want, after this assignment.
Damn you. You're so picky.
How about this!?
And don't complain anymore!
Fashion Massage Love.
Mr. Mayart!
I can not give you permission
to go outside of this room.
This is an order!
Damn it. You're stubborn, too.
You will sleep with us
in this room tonight.
No way. I certainly object.
I'll sleep with that woman,
but never with you.
I can't sleep with a
man being next to me.
Then you don't have to sleep.
Wh...wh-wh-what?!
Who do you think I am?
This peace treaty doesn't
conclude without me.
In spite of this, you still trap
me in such a crappy hotel.
This is outrageous!
This hotel is located above the
point where the most powerful...
spiritual energy can
be transmitted in Tokyo.
There is no way for them to enter.
They can't even come close.
Then, why is that woman here?
She is a member of the
Black Guard from the other side.
She has been trained
for this situation.
All right, if I can be alone with her,
I'll stay here.
Why don't you sleep in the hallway?
OK, I'll stay with you Mr. Mayart.
This is my chance to try a
woman of the demon world.
Keep your eye on him.
If he does something strange,
just tie him to the bed.
D...don't be rude!
What the hell are you telling her?
You fool!
You nincompoop!
Idiot!
The guest upstairs is a
truly important person.
Do you know him?
Giuseppi Mayart...
He came to Japan,
incognito, 20 years ago.
He hasn't changed much
since then, but...
What's wrong?
I wonder a little,
if he's for real or not?
It's just my intuition,
but in my humble opinion....
he might be a decoy.
That might be possible.
They use a decoy freely, to attract
the enemy's attention on us?
Oh, well.
Anyway, are you still single?
What kind of question is that?
Can't you tell by
just looking at me?
How about the lady
you came with?
Don't joke. She's a woman
from the other side.
You can't have children,
but I hear the sex is incredible.
Well, I've never thought I would hear
such words coming from your mouth.
Is that so?
It's just what I hear.
Do you like your job?
I don't know.
You must be proud of your work.
It's very honorable to have such an
important job, protecting both worlds.
Is it? I don't know if it's worth
protecting human or demon society...
by risking my own life.
It's because you still don't
have anything to truly protect.
You better find something fast,
then you'll understand its meaning.
Something to protect?
Is it that simple?
It is.
Checkmate.
Here, let's have one more game.
Old man, you never give up.
Don't complain!
I'm helping you kill time.
It's them!
Bastards! They're trying
to break the spiritual shield.
It can't be... there's no way
for them to enter here!
Here they come!
Mr. Mayart, don't leave there.
G...get them.
Makie, it's me.
Jin?
You look nice, wearing
the clothes of this side.
Very attractive.
I guess you've joined hand
in hand with the humans.
Traitor!
Why did you betray us?
Tell me!
Humans are such lowly
creatures compared to us.
They will just have to serve us.
There's no reason to be equal or fair.
I don't even want you
to understand.
You're as stubborn
as you used to be.
I should have made you
sleep with me back then.
Do you think you can take
my heart, if you take my body?
That's just the way you think.
Would you like to try?
I'II make you crazy.
Master.
Don't worry, they only got my
fake hand. You should go upstairs.
How's this? Your body is
more honest than you are.
Y...you!
Don't bother.
You can't use that trick.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Where is Mr. Mayart?
He's hiding in the bathroom.
What kind of emissary is he?
Sorry Taki. I relied on this
spiritual barrier wall too much.
Can you find Mr. Mayart?
Don't worry, I have an
idea where he's going.
This is paradise. I could never
imagine such a great place.
I'm glad I've lived long
enough to experience this.
I'm getting so full of energy,
because you are so pleased.
I'll give you the full treatment.
Here, why don't you lie
down on your back.
Here you are.
Oh, Sir, you have so much vitality!
I can even outlast young men.
Sir, how old are you?
I've been living so long,
I don't remember anymore.
But I am well past 200.
No way! Nobody your age
can keep it up like that.
We both have had a very long life.
Anyhow, you have marvelous breasts.
They're like art that God created.
Oh, you look like a baby doing that.
You don't look 200 years old at all.
Huh?
I swallowed something.
What was that?
What are you talking about?
I haven't had a baby yet.
There's no milk.
Here, let's continue.
Paradise, paradise!
Wha...
What the hell is this?
I'm going to take you to the
real Paradise, Giuseppi Mayart!
Y...you're a terrorist from
the demon world?
Mayart...!?
If you kill me, the old man dies too.
Do you want that?
Taki, rescue Mr. Mayart.
Both of your lives will end tonight,
no matter how far you escape.
You're the one
whose life will end.
This isn't good.
His life force is almost drained.
We have to give him
spiritual treatment.
Where are we going?
A spiritual treatment hospital.
It will take one hour
no matter how fast I drive.
I hope he can hold out until then.
There's no reaction to
my psychic powers.
He may not last
more than 30 mutinies.
He's caused a lot of trouble.
What's the matter?
They are trying to take us
into demon space.
Now what?
We've been transported
into demon space.
We're completely trapped.
Stop the car.
It's no use driving anymore.
What are you going to do?
Stay here with Mr. Mayart.
I will break the barrier.
That's too dangerous.
I told you. I'm willing to risk
my life for this assignment.
But I haven't heard your
measurements yet.
Mr. Mayart!
What's wrong?
Shit! That soap girl was a parasite.
What's going on?
Makie!
Taki... run away, hurry!
Please protect Mr. Mayart.
The demon space barrier
is about to open.
Hurry... hurry up and run...
Makie.
We're in Motoakasaka...
Still far away from the hospital.
Makie is gone...
She used up all her energy and power to
break through the demon space barrier.
She might have been blown up
when the barrier was broken.
She helped us by sacrificing herself.
A woman from the demon world.
I hope she's still alive.
SPIRITUAL TREATMENT CENTER
How is his condition?
His life force is incredible. I think
he'll recover in less than 30 minutes.
I want to make sure this place
has enough protection.
The spiritual barrier here is
20 times stronger than usual.
It's totally different from
the Teito Hotel in Hibiya.
We've been fighting with them for
5,000 years. We've learned a lot.
That sounds good.
Doctor!
What's the matter?
They're here! We're completely
surrounded by a demon space barrier...
within a radius of 5 kilometers!
Increase the barrier's strength.
Send a request for help to
India, Tibet, and Mt. Koya...
to strengthen the spiritual wave.
Mr. Mayart, you still
have a lot to go through.
Can you hear me,
Renzaburo Taki?
I have something interesting
to show you.
Makie!
How do you like it?
Look at this well.
This is the end of a traitor.
She is a resident of the demon world.
Despite that, she assisted
this deceptive peace treaty.
In addition, she's killed her ex-lover.
There is no way to forgive her.
I will let her serve the
desires of these men.
After that, I will torture her slowly.
Mr. Taki, don't you want
to rescue her?
You may be able to do it.
What do you think of that?
Why don't you come here?
Where are you?
Wait!
Don't go! This is a trick!
But they have clearly
challenged me!
Are you serious?
What do you think
will happen to me?
As a Black Guard,
you're supposed to protect me.
As long as you stay here,
they can't even touch you.
Is she that important to you?
Important enough to go and
save her by leaving me here?
Don't forget! She's a woman
of the demon world!
She's not human.
She sacrificed herself to save you.
Of course she should!
I'm an irreplaceable
Demon Emissary in this world.
The peace treaty of the two worlds
can't be signed without me.
Don't even compare me
with that monster bitch!
She deserves to be raped and
tortured by her fellow monsters.
She might even be enjoying herself.
I accept your challenge.
Let me go there.
My pleasure.
I will guide you.
Wha...what did you say?!
Y...you would leave me here?
I haven't given you permission!
Do you think you know
what you're doing?!
As a professional Black Guard,
you're acting ridiculous!
You fool!
Damn you!
Black Guard, Renzaburo Taki.
My sworn enemy has
fallen into our hands.
Don't even think that
I'll let you die so easily.
The woman... let Makie go.
Are you in love with her?
Do you want to sleep with her?
Don't express your
own dirty thoughts.
It doesn't matter.
I will test your ability
as a man, right now.
I will ask your body how
much you're involved...
with this disgusting
conspiracy that's going on.
What are you talking about?
Come to me. Inside my body...
No man can resist this.
Come on...
I will suck everything from you.
Hurry...
Come on! Hurry.
How's this?
Incredible, isn't it?
You will do anything I want.
Tell me about the
conspiracy on your side.
That woman... Makie.
Did you sleep with her?
Kill him.
Makie.
Taki...
Is he the prince who came
here to save the princess?
Your fantasy ends here.
The assimilation seems
like it's finished.
Do you understand...
what has just happened
to the men you beat?
Shoot!
Shoot as much as you want!
Renzaburo Taki,
this is your end.
Bastard!
How come you have so much power?
Are you all right?
You have a deep wound.
Thank you. I'm so happy.
I never thought that you would
have come here to save me.
You're my partner.
Of course I'll save you.
I became the enemy's hostage.
You abandoned your post,
right in the middle of an assignment.
We' II both be fired
from the Black Guard.
There's something
that worries me more.
What's this conspiracy they
were asking me about?
Why did they want to know
if I slept with Makie?
Is there a secret
conspiracy going on...
behind the peace treaty
being signed tomorrow?
Was the man who came to
the hotel, your ex-boyfriend?
That's history.
He completely changed after being
brainwashed by the terrorists.
He was a nice person before.
I had no choice but to kill him.
Don't worry.
That's the way our job goes.
Why did you become a Black Guard?
There are so many people
who want peace in both worlds.
Both worlds need to coexist
with each other.
For that to happen,
somebody has to do this job.
Is Mr. Mayart well?
He's being protected at
the spiritual hospital.
Do you want to pick him up?
Can you move?
Your psychic powers have
healed me well. I'm already cured.
But, you' II get cold
dressed like that.
What do you think?
You look great.
Now I can imagine that you
were working as a model.
You told me before,
I have unreal beauty.
I don't feel that way anymore.
You just have perfect beauty.
Really?
Sure, perfect.
Oh, I'm glad.
Already acting like
boyfriend and girlfriend.
You guys must've had
lots of fun, didn't you?
Your job is supposed to
be guarding Mr. Mayart!
How could you walk away from it,
just to do the things you want?!
You have disgraced me!
You guys are so happy-go-lucky.
You must've went to a love hotel
and made out. You rat!
Both of you are already dismissed.
Please leave here.
I will send you
a formal notice, later.
Go! Go! I'II have nothing to do with
incompetent people like you two.
Bye-bye.
Mr. Taki.
You have disappointed me.
You had a lot of potential to
become a great Black Guard...
but you're too much of a romantic.
That is your biggest flaw.
Is that you?
I've made a mess.
I underestimated him a little.
I'm sorry. I should have
finished him off, that last time.
We're the only survivors.
There's no time to call for backup.
Go and finish him, no matter what.
Yes. I got the result of his
body fluid analysis.
We were right.
He has the DNA?
Yes.
It will take a while for me
to regenerate. You take over.
I will take care of it.
Taki.
Don't say anything.
It's not your fault.
I did everything on my own.
I guess a romantic
isn't right for this job.
That's true.
Especially not me.
Well, I am quite a romantic myself.
Mr. Mayart!
Why did you follow us?!
Well, there are no sexy nurses
in that hospital.
All of them are rough men.
It felt so stuffy being there.
That isn't a good excuse!
Hey, hey. Can we go to a place
called "Cabaret Club" next?
Don't joke!
We got fired from being
your babysitter!
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Let's just do what I want to do,
and I'll take all the blame for it.
Mr. Mayart, don't you realize,
you have a very important job?
I know, I know!
I certainly know that!!
But I still have a
little time until then.
I refuse!
I will take you back
to the Teito Hotel.
It's much closer than taking
you back to the hospital.
Fine! Do that!
I can escape from there anytime.
Taki!
Makie, are you all right?
Yes.
She's coming.
Nice to see you again.
Taki!
Makie.
Traitor!
How could you fall
in love with a human?
People who love each other
can die together.
What an envious ending!
I'll chop up both of
your cursed bodies.
Who the hell are you?!
Taki.
Is this a dream?
If this is a dream,
I don't want it to end.
Tears...
This is strange...
We, who live in the demon world,
shouldn't have tears.
Why do I have
tears inside of me?
Whatever happened...
I guess we're still alive.
I wonder who brought us here?
Maybe God.
I'd love to think that.
Be careful.
They're very close.
Giuseppi Mayart!
What are you doing?
The enemy is behind you!
Perfect! I've finally encountered
my real enemy!
You guys have to hurry and go.
Go? Where should we go to?
To the signing ceremony of
the peace treaty, of course.
That's where you should go!
Both of you are the ones who must go.
Us?
You still don't realize it?
It wasn't you two
who were guarding me.
I was called here
to guard you two.
Then it was you who carried
us here and healed us?
Yes. I used my psychic powers
to heal both of you.
What's this all about?
I'll explain.
To insure a lasting peace...
we felt that some kind of
spiritual exchange was needed.
Something representing
the spiritual wave...
between the human world
and the demon world.
But the biggest barrier that kept
our two worlds from interacting...
is that there's no way to mix
the blood of each other's race.
However, after a few thousand
years of our effort...
some spiritual mutation had occurred.
There are still very few, but...
...we've produced some subjects whose
DNA can be mixed with each other.
And the scientists of both worlds
selected the best couple.
You and Makie are the first couple.
You two can have a child who bears
the gifts from both worlds.
And it's that child who will
become the leader of a new world.
Our...
...child?
Indeed.
These terrorists are afraid of that,
and have tried to kill you.
You doddering old fool!
How much more
will you interfere with us?
Oh, it's you. Still alive?
What are you made of?
We both should have taken
each other more seriously.
Let's bring this to an end.
Go and eat him up
until he's just bones!
Our power is far beyond
any humans' ability.
Y...you bastard!
Bastard!!!
Taki, are you all right?
I used too much power.
Are you still trying to regenerate?
I guess rapidly regenerating in his
condition must have some side effects.
Don't shoot!
The piece of meat will
just keep on regenerating.
Well, here we go!
Come on and fight me!
I'll turn you into a puff of smoke.
Makie.
Is she...?
What a miracle!
This is the effect of the mutation.
She has definitely conceived.
This power is the best proof.
Makie is already pregnant
with your baby.
I've never imagined the symptoms
would come so quickly.
There was one condition needed in
order for Makie to conceive a baby.
The laboratory concluded that in order
to conceive and transfigure the DNA...
the couple had to have
a spiritual bond of love.
That's why I made you go
through all this effort.
In order to bring out
your love for each other.
I don't believe this.
There was no other way
under such a tight schedule.
Forgive me.
You're a big fool!
Everything was planned ahead?
I'm afraid so.
However, nobody could predict if the
two of you could love each other.
I feel like beating you up.
Weren't you serious when
you made love to Makie?
Unfortunately...
Is it?
I thought so...
...at first.
Taki.
Do you believe a woman
of the demon world?
Those tears you had.
I believe they were real.
My, my...the results have
exceeded our expectations.
Maybe, Taki won't beat me up.
Well, shall we go?
A new treaty, the start of
a new life and a new world.
He's quite a character.
The long night ends.
A bright day breaks.
Just like the man at
the hotel told me...
Someone whom I should protect
is in my arms, right now.
And there is my child...
who doesn't even have shape,
but is inside of her.
This child may create a new future
for both worlds someday.
But...
my job...
as a Black Guard won't end
until that day comes.
Subtitles by Kentai Films