If he makes the wrong decision,
then we have no choice
but to decide for him.
I'll raise my average above 50
on the next mid-term.
What did you say?
Ji-hoon!
I'll get above a 50, okay?
Wait a minute, sir!
From an expert's perspective,
this is an abnormal act of...
Shut the fuck up!
It's none of your business!
Do you know me?
I know what I'm doing.
Have you really gone crazy?
Speak Korean
so I can understand.
I'll get above a 50, okay?
If I don't, do as you like.
Fuck! Fuck!
Just tell him
you'll go abroad.
Make some sense. Pack!
And I'll reserve your ticket.
Do you think raising your grades
is as easy as fighting?
If you don't wanna help,
then leave!
Yeah, you won't need my help
since you speak English well!
Why do you need tutoring?
I can speak English,
but I can't read it!
It's different on tests!
This is insane.
Then why did you
make that promise?
How do you expect to raise
your average from 8 to 50?
God can't even help you.
Feel bad? I'm sorry,
but I have to say it.
It's better than
a promise you can't keep.
There's no use in having
an I-can-do-it attitude.
Stop speaking nonsense,
and tell me what to study.
Peasants' Uprising of 1895.
Are you feeling okay? Did you hurt
your head when you fought Jong-soo?
He's a cruel bastard
for hitting your head.
Do you know about
the Peasants' Uprising?
What?
It was caused by a death
in the Ulmi Year.
Do you know what death it was?
What?
Queen Myungsung was killed
by the yakuzas.
Know who Queen Myungsung is?
Come on.
Think I'm that dumb?
It's Actress Lee Mi-yeon.
You idiot.
It wasn't her in that TV series?
It was Kang Soo-yeon, idiot.
Fuck, why does he have
to study all of a sudden?
I should've just picked randomly.
That's what I'm saying.
Here's some solid advice.
Do as your father says.
Wanna die?
Go become a mafia gangster,
and form a global gang.
Yeah, becoming a national hero
will be easier.
You call yourself a tutor?
Then you think
a tutor can do magic?
What will you do
if I get above a 50, huh?
From here to there are the
questions I taught you before.
So you could've
gotten a 60 score.
But the result? Only 18.
Anyway, so what'll you do
if I get above a 50?
You get above a 50?
Then I'll dance on stage
at our school festival.
That would be fun.
You made a promise, okay?
Sorry to call all of you here.
I have a problem,
so you'll have to help me.
I'll assign you a subject,
So make 100 questions each.
At least half of them
must be on the test.
It's mine.
Ji-hoon, you can smoke
two cartons during class.
Ji-hoon, please.
Let's talk about it.
Let's be reasonable!
You can't do this to me!
I helped you with the test!
The next entry is
a Junior majoring in English.
Let's welcome Choi Su-wan!
Hi, I'm Choi Su-wan,
a Junior majoring in English.
I hope you enjoy it.
Bye.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
Weren't you embarrassed
for a girl?
Why didn't you
just dance naked?
It looked like a strip show.
Who's the one
who told me to dance?
Have plans this sunday?
None of your business.
Just tell me. Although I know
you won't have any.
Our club is visiting
an orphanage. Why?
Is that bastard going?
Who? My honey, Si-kyung?
Honey, my ass.
Why else would I be going
if he wasn't?
Hey, is that a volunteer's attitude?
Think what you like. Bye.
How do you do?
I've been thinking a lot.
It's been on my mind constantly.
So I've had many sleepless nights.
Just say you want
to screw her, asshole
Si-kyung.
Su-wan, it's not a choice,
it's fate.
I'm fine with throwing
my everything away.
My family, friends, and future.
My mind and body
isn't mine anyway, Su-wan.
Si-kyung.
Si-kyung, are you okay?
Hey, Kim Ji-hoon!
What are you doing there?
What'll you do now?
They're not your friends anymore.
Look at my arm.
I can't bathe and wipe my ass.
And look how dirty my hair is, asshole.
Know how precious
the right arm is?
Shit, only if your big head
hadn't dodged him.
Fine, I saw you in action
at the pool hall,
so I'll make you Number 2,
okay?
Number 2?
Shit. Ji-hoon, you bastard.
What's taking you so long?
Are you drunken?
You're pathetic for a tutor.
You don't wanna get paid, huh?
What?
Hi.
How long have
you been drinking?
Sorry.
Let's have today's class here.
Today's subject
is broken hearts.
Did you get dumped?
Nope.
Yeah.
Wanna die? Stop screwing around.
Everyone, I've been dumped!
I've been dumped!
Everybody,
I've been dumped...
What the hell
was so good about him?
At first,
I liked his soft smile.
And then...
I liked his voice.
And since I liked liking him,
I liked him even more.
And then I loved him.
Since I loved him,
my heart became broken.
But I could only let him go.
There's nothing I can do.
I'm stupid, heart-broken,
hopeless, and down.
Hurry and get up!
You're too drunken.
Ji-hoon, what are
you two doing?
Now you're trying
to seduce him with tears?
Ji-hoon, don't trust her.
Since you're studying with her,
the guys are leaving you.
Hey, I'm really tired already,
so you better go, okay?
Ji-hoon!
It's you. The City Chick.
Nice to see you.
Wanna drink with me?
Have you gone nuts?
You're always mean.
Stop acting so drunk,
damn it.
Why'd you hit my pretty face?
Come here and
I'll give you a kiss. It's so soft.
You crazy bitch!
Ji-hoon!
Let go.
You're really overdoing it today.
What's gotten into you?
This is the place.
Why? Wanna throw up?
On a rainy night...
By a red telephone booth...
Under the streetlight...
I wanted my first kiss
at a place like this.
You're really overdoing it.
I even practiced a pose.
Like this.
Why? Why does God
have to be my rival?
Hey!
Who are you to make her cry?
Su-wan may be a Country Chick...
Man, I'm pissed.
She's not worth
getting hurt from you!
I think there's
been some mistake.
Mistake, my ass.
I don't know who she is,
but if I see that
she's worse than Su-wan,
you and her are dead.
Got it? So who is she?
Fine, the sweetheart
who's in your heart now.
This is making me sick.
Who is she? I said who?
You're making a mistake.
It's not a woman.
I'll be a father soon.
- What?
- A father.
You rotten son of a bitch.
You already have a kid?
Rotten bastard.
Thanks for the milk, asshole.
You bastard.
Why'd you hit him? Why?
Do you have to keep this up?
Okay, hit me. Hit me.
Are you really a girl?
Why does your punch sting?
Feel better now?
Was he your first love?
Has this happened to you?
Think I'm the type
to get dumped like you?
Have you ever
truly loved someone?
Probably not
with a temper like that.
Wanna fly into the sky?
I'm serious.
Like it?
I like it! Very much!
Tomorrow is our last lesson.
That's right.
Hey, Su-wan.
What?
I've been thinking.
You're a pretty cool chick.
Now you know?
This is the first time
I've told somebody this,
but I think I like you.
Hello?
Su-wan. Su-wan.
Can't you hear me?
Su-wan, can you hear me?
What? What? I can't hear you.
Su-wan, pull the left string!
Don't panic.
Su-wan, are you okay?
It hurts.
You have to study English consistently.
There's no other way.
Study the idioms and synonyms
I wrote down before your test.
You've done a good job.
Well, I...
I hope I was a
good teacher to you.
There's no need to emphasize
that you were a teacher.
I understand.
Wait a sec.
Oh boy, my legs hurt.
Su-wan!
Oh my gosh, it's my friend.
What are you doing here?
You bad girl, how'd you
catch me on a date?
This is my friend, Su-wan.
- Hello.
The guy I mentioned.
The med student.
Hello.
Yes, hello.
Who have you been
hiding from me?
No, he's the one
I've been tutoring.
The bad student?
So you two are dating now?
Think I'm crazy to
date a high school...
It looks fishy to me.
This doesn't seem like
a place to study.
It's our farewell party.
Wanna join us?
No way.
We're getting very intimate.
Have fun with your teacher.
I'll call you later.
Why? Envious?
Of course. He's handsome,
and has a good major.
Snobs. And being rich
would also be nice, Right?
All you care about is status.
That was mean.
Is that your standard
for guys, too?
Guys like that wouldn't be bad.
But it's crazy to date
someone in high school?
That's now what I meant.
I thought you were different.
But you're all the same.
You all think superficially.
What makes you so different from
Ho-gyung who's materialistic?
What is it?
This is yours.
Why should I accept this?
Then don't. I bought it for you,
so it's not even mine.
What is it?
Does Kim Ji-hoon's tutor
live here by any chance?
Su-wan? She went on a delivery.
Stop! Wait!
What do you want?
Are you Kim Ji-hoon's tutor
by any chance?
Not anymore.
Grab her!
Come with us for a moment.
What are you doing?
Hello?
Say something! Speak!
It hung up.
Damn it!
What bastard is prank calling?
Hold on for a sec, idiot!
What?
Choi Su-wan?
I have to make a delivery,
so stop this.
Hello? Hello?
Who? Lee Jong-soo? Hey!
My ear's gonna fall off,
you bastard!
Of course you have to come.
Here?
Catch her, you bastards!
Hello?
You're with Jong-soo, huh?
Where are you?
Damn it,
I'm running right now!
So you ordered the chicken?
I doubted it at first.
But I'd never think he'd like
a Country Chick like you.
Your job was to tutor him,
not seduce him.
Here's the chicken,
so pay me 216,000 won.
I wanna throw you like
that chicken and crush you.
Why'd you throw it?
Who are you to do that?
My dad raised them himself,
and my mom cooked it.
And you throw it away?
Stop it! Stop it!
I said stop it!
What do you want?
She's mine,
so you stay out of it!
No she's not, she's mine.
You bastards.
It's not your day to tutor,
so be quiet.
You're a hostage today.
Ji-hoon's bait.
Pay for the chicken.
Pay for the chicken!
Hello?
We're waiting too long
because of you, asshole.
Are you testing my patience?
- Shut up your mouth!
- Let me go, you bastard!
Are you okay?
Do I look okay to you?
Let's go.
Ji-hoon!
He's here. I said he's right here.
You can't leave now.
Jong-soo, you've gone insane.
Ji-hoon, I can't
take it anymore.
I wanna make sure today.
Is it that bitch or me?
Move, bitch.
If you listen to me,
I'll let her go, but if not...
No, you move!
Ji-hoon!
That's the bastard!
Who the hell are you?
They're the bosses
of the Makjubshi Gang.
This is fucking humiliating,
but I had to call them
because of you, asshole.
Damn it, who the hell
are you guys?
What do you want?
With that Country Chick,
no, with Ji-hoon...
No, I came to talk
to both of them.
Hey, what I want is that...
It's my turn. I brought her here,
so butt out.
Damn it, I'm the one
who went to the store.
You idiot, all you had to do
was have her deliver to you.
Stupid idiots.
Hey! Hey!
Are you okay?
What if I'm not?
I see you're still feisty.
Hey, I told you to stop smoking.
Out of breath already?
Very nice. Who gave it to you?
Stop it.
I thought you'd call me.
What's wrong with all your friends?
Get some new ones.
I sure do know
how to pick them right.
The necklace.
Looks good on you.
Wait for me!
Wait for me, asshole!
Like I told you before,
what I want is that...
Go home, you bastard.
But I have something to say!
Hurry and tell me who it is.
Is it me or this bitch? This bitch?
Yeah.
But I like you!
She's not the only one
who likes you!
I like you, too!
I can be a better
girlfriend than her!
Hey, stop crying, damn it.
Why do you bother people?
It's my hobby, why?
Go ahead first.
First, we'll take care of them,
then it's our turn.
Do as you like.
Stop crying like a baby.
I heard a lot about you,
so show me what you got.
Shit, I've been showing it,
so where were you? I'm exhausted.
Can I ask you something?
Asking questions
is a good habit.
Is this your skin?
Hey! Move those hands!
Ji-hoon, where are you going?
Please transfer to another school!
Stop staring, damn it.
Screw you.
Do what she says.
Starring
Kwon Sang-woo
as Kim Ji-hoon
Kim Ha-neul
as Choi Su-wan
Executive Producers
Lee Kang-bok & Lee Seo-yull
Produced by
Jang Jung-gwon
Original Story by
Choi Su-wan
Screenplay by
Park Yun-seon
Directed by
Kim Kyung-hyung