Executive Producer:
KANG Woo-suk
Producers:
LEE Kwan-soo KIM Sang-jin
KIM Seung-woo
KIM Jung-eun
BYUN Hee-bong KIM Hae-ok
JEONG In-han KIM Young-0k
JANG Hyun-seong KIM Kyung-beom
Special Guest SEONG Ji-ru
No Litter!
You bastard! That trash!!
You little shithead!
It said 'No Litter'!!
You human trash! Stop!
You're so dead.
What are you doing up there?
Me? I'm waiting for someone..
Written & Directed by JANG Hang-joon
He should be here soon..
After a good lap around my
neighborhood..
- I feel incredibly refreshed.
- I see.
Now, let's talk some more
about your work.
Your latest work
is a masterpiece.
I brought it with me and,
I must say the cover
is simply beautiful.
It's a photo of your late father
with your mother
They look lovely together.
How was your husband's funeral?
He broke my heart again and again,
but, none of that matters now.
My father? Well..
He was a child prodigy.
He finished '1000 Characters Text' by
age 5 and 7 Chinese Classics' by age 10.
His father was a scholar
of Chinese Classics.
Chinese Classics scholar my ass!
His father was a pimp.
And, even as a kid,
he had no interest in studying.
He only liked girls.
When he was 14..
he did it with a young maid
who worked at his house.
I was told he never had
any interest in women.
He was an unsusceptible man
towards women.
I guess I'm like
my father in that way.
He was a hard worker.
He studied all his life
to go to university.
When he was finally admitted
he only slept couple hours
a night to study even more.
He never studied!
His father's pimp money
was his entrance ticket.
And, of course,
he had no interest in education.
He was too busy getting laid.
When did you find out about
his other family?
When Seon-guk was 2
we went to
visit him in Seoul.
And there he was with his
4 other children.
- Bastard!
- He'll go to hell.
But, for some reason..
he really liked spring.
In the winter,
he'd never go outside.
But, when the warm spring breeze
starts to blow,
he'd go out and wander around
like a person under a spell.
SPRING BREEZE
Damn it!
- Teacher
- What?
Can we turn on the heater?
It's freezing today.
You didn't wear your thermals?
No.
Do you pay for the heating?
I told you to wear your thermals.
I'm sorry.
Oh, teacher
- Now what?
- You have to call the publisher.
Ok.
He said, if you don't submit the
manuscript by this month..
I heard you!
The new tenant is moving in today.
- New tenant?
- Yes.
I didn't rent out any rooms.
Is GOH Ki-nam your father?
Yes.
He signed a contract through
our real estate agency.
You see that registered seal?
The contract is legit.
I think the house is too big
for just one person.
You should hide your
registered seal somewhere safe.
So, who's moving in?
Here she comes.
This is your landlord.
Hi. I'm Hwa-jung.
It's very nice
to meet you.
Hello.
A respected man like myself
can't live with
a vulgar woman like her.
Tell her to look for another place.
- I can't.
- Why not?
Your father already
took the lease deposit.
Lease deposit?
How much?
30 million won.
30 million!
This is the room, right?
What the...
Excuse me. But, you didn't vacate
the 2nd floor room.
- The 2nd floor room?
- Yeah
That's the room I rented.
Please vacate it for me.
God damn it!
Wow!
This room can be rented out.
Dad, why are you doing this?
Male elephants start mating when
they're 10 years old.
For Asian elephants, the mating
season lasts for a month per year.
After only a few days with their
female partners, the mating ends.
Yes, she's got the contract
and the receipt.
No, he signed it when he was
alive and took the deposit.
I'm not talking about me.
- I'll get it.
- Why would I lie about that?
So, is there a way or not?
Can he kick her out?
What?
- Welcome!
- Nice house!
Bye.
What are those?
Oh! Come and
say hi to my landlord.
Mr. GOH,
am I interrupting you?
My friends are here for a housewarming
party and they want to say hi.
They don't have to..
Everyone! This is my landlord and
that's Hee-gu.
- Hello!
- Hi!
- Your landlord is very handsome.
- He's exactly my type!
- You're so lucky!
- The one with glasses is so cute!
Look at him smile!
Go and tell those dumb vulgar
species to be quiet.
- OthenNise, get out of my house!
- Yes, sir.
Who is that?
- Hee-gu!
- May I speak with you?
Sure. Come in
- Wait.. First, have a drink with us!
- C'mon. Just one drink.
No. I'mjust gonna..
What the hell happened to him?
Why is it getting louder?
"Clap your hands and sing"
"Everyone look this way!
Shake your body"
- "Champion"
- "Scream your head off"
- "Let the music take over you"
- "Champion"
- "You! You! You! You! Champion"
I'm sorry.
Can I talk to you for a sec?
Me? Ok
I'll be right back.
I'm coming.
- What's up?
- Let me ask you for a favor.
- Sure.
- I have to work. So, can you be quiet?
What do you do?
none of your business. If you
wanna drink, drink quietly or go out
Alright. We'll go out then.
Can Hee-gu come with us?
Go. Go
and get wasted with this
coffee shop girl. Ok?
How did you know I work
at a coffee shop?
Isn't that obvious?
- Wow! You really can drink!
- Thank you.
When I'm in my top condition,
I can easily finish 12 bottles.
Uhm..
What's Mr. GOH like?
- My teacher?
- Yes.
He's a bastard. Bastard!
A real mean bastard.
He's got no friend
and no cell phone.
He still uses a beeper.
He says his work is all that
matters in his life,
but I don't think so.
He likes money! Money!
Fuck you, GOH Seon-guk!
What does he do?
- He writes..
- Writes? He's a writer?
- How did you know?
- You just said he writes.
Wow. That's totally cool!
- What kind of stories?
- A novel.
Right now, he's writing a love story
but it's not going well.
A love story?
That's my specialty.
That's what I know the best.
Talking about love stories..
do you wanna hear
a killer love story?
Damn it's hot!
Shit!
Who turned on the heater?
Is she out of her mind?
Good morning.
- Did you turn this on?
- Yes. I did.
Who said you could
turn on the heater?
No one did. I just turned
it on because it was cold.
I get cold easily.
What's up there?
Uh.. nothing.
Just don't ever
turn it on again.
Why not?
Because it's broken. Broken!
- If you're cold, wear thermals.
- I think it works fine
You don't believe me?
Hello? Hi.
Our heating system broke
No, it doesn't work.
Yes. My address is..
This is broken, too.
I just got it fixed but..
Don't use the phone
or the heater!
ﬁCome and talk to meﬁ
ﬂ Take about anythingﬁ
ﬂ Let's have a drink tonightﬁ
E! can listen to anything you sayﬁ
Hi. I'm Hwa-jung,
the new girl at
Forget Me Not' coffee shop.
Stop by whenever
and I'll be your friend.
Just think of me as your
granddaughter. See you soon.
E I miss youﬁ
E! can fall in love with youﬁ
Hi!
- You're super pretty!
- Super thanks!
Bye.
Forget Me Not Coffee Shop
What's the next question?
Question #7, across..
- Author of "Gone with the Wind."
- I know this one.
What's her name..
Wait.. Maybe it's Clark Gable.
- Which one?
- I'm not sure..
It is her....
Ah! She's the one who tells
the story, so.. Vivien Leigh.
Wow. You are so smart!
Vivien.. Leigh..
How about this one?
Something-egg.
Type of cooked egg.
- 'Fried' egg?
- No. I don't think that's right.
It's gotta be
more difficult word.
How about 'sunny side up?'
- Isn't it 'scrambled?'
- 'Scrambled..?'
Right! Ithink
that's the right answer!
'Scrambled.'
Wait.. The ruler of Catholic Church
is 'Pope', right?
Then it has to start with 'P.'
P?’ Word that Starts with 'P'?
Po.. Pa.. Pu..
hey
Hi.
Are you also here to report
your new address?
- Rice
- Rice?
We came here to receive rice.
I see.
Is he your brother?
Did you eat?
Eat as much as you want.
Come by whenever
you're hungry. Ok?
Can we come
with our grandma?
Grandma?
Of course.
Hi, Mr. GOH!
Kids, say hello to Mr. GOH.
He's my housemate.
Hello.
Who are they?
They're my new friends.
Eat. I got plenty of food. Eat.
So, what's your problem?
I..
I met someone.
Again?
There's this new beauty salon.
I went there to get a hair cut..
and that's how I met her.
It must've been fate..
Teacher, he's ready.
Hello.
She started to gently caress my
hair with her long slender fingers.
Every living cell in my body was
being awakened from a long sleep
In my head, they were celebrating
their freedom from
the monotonous cycle of life!
Pow! Pow!
After the most ecstatic experience
of my life, as I was about to leave,
she said to me with
her sweet voice,
Come again.
And I said to her,
Yes. I'll be back.
You're pitiful.
My heart is still pounding..
- So, did you go back?
- Yup.
I dyed my hair black today.
Do you like it?
No
What did the publisher say?
He's really pissed
about the delay.
Why don't you return
the advance payment?
I already used it
to build my house.
The only source of income I have
is to finish this book.
Or a sudden rise in sale of
.
- Can I use your phone
- Still using a beeper?
You're so cheap. Get yourself
a cell phone, will you?
Give it.
Nobody uses a beeper anymore.
No, there are 180,000 beeper users
in this country.
180,000!!
Hello, sir?
No
I wasn't yelling at you.
I swear I wasn't yelling.. No, sir.
So why didn't you deliver
it on time?
What?
I said 'by 9 o'clock!'
You delivered it
at 10 o'clock!
Why did you do that? I didn't say
'by 10 o'clock!
What? What did you say to me?
I'm your customer, asshole!
I want to talk to your boss!
Put him on the phone, now!
Please may I speak to your boss?
I'll speak to him directly.
Hello?
If you keep doing business like this
I'm gonna kick your ass!
What?
You want a piece of me?!
UFO!
Look! UFO!
- Get him!
- Get him! Get him!
He's here!
- did you say you were in a track team?
- Shut up.
He was too fast.
- You lost him?
- Yes.
- Sir, going to see the publisher?
- Yeah.
Aren't you gonna take your car?
Are you gonna pay for the gasoline?
Did you wear your thermals?
- You're not cold, right?
- No, sir.
It's a story I heard.
I thought it was
quite interesting.
Please take a look at it.
Wasn't it supposed to be
finished by last October?
It's already February.
I'm sorry.
That's not what I want to hear.
How much of it is finished?
It's almost done.
I'm very sorry.
I said, that's not
what I want to hear.
You're really
pushing me this time.
I'm really sorry.
I said stop saying that.
I even gave you the advance
payment like you asked.
Don't you feel
guilty about that?
If I were you, I would finish the
book as quickly as I can.
I'm sorry.
- Damn it! I said stop saying that.
- Then, what should I say?
You made me feel like shit and I
can't even say I'm sorry?
- Should I say 'thank you' instead?
- You're crazy!
Yes, I'm crazy! I'm so fucking
sorry that I went crazy!
I'm crazy! So what! What!!
Crazy bastard!
You don't feel sorry at all!
Look at yourself!!
You said don't say 'I'm sorry!'
Finish it by this month or return
the advance, plus the penalty fee.
Or else, they'll sue me.
Why did you act like that to him?
You don't wanna mess with him.
- How much of it is finished?
- Let's talk about something else.
What's going on with
that beauty salon girl?
I was just there today.
I can't stop
thinking about her.
You know..
love is like hair.
Even though you cut it,
it keeps growing and growing.
Shut up.
Just out of my curiosity,
what happened with that stalker?
- Who? Yong-shik?
- No, not him. The one from Chunan.
- Soo-chun?
- No, not that crazy bastard.
Sang-won?
Last girlfriend I had was..
During '88 Seoul Olympic.
- 1988? During JEON administration?
- No. During ROH administration.
- Why?
- she nagged me to go to the closing day
Before that?
No.. The one who lived with you in
that house with blue front door.
The one with hair like this..
- Oh, Hyun-doo!
- Yes, him!
Are you serious?
While the political
power changed 4 times,
you've only had 1 girlfriend?
You gotta have at least one for
every new administration.
Tell me the truth. Have you ever had
a sleepless night because of a woman?
- No.
- And you're writing a love story?
Why not?
Love is all fiction.
- I told you to buy more beer.
- I didn't think we'd run out.
Is the heater really broken?
That's what he said.
Can I help you?
Isn't this the residence of Mr. GOH?
Yes. But he's not here.
I see.
May I ask who you are?
I'm Hwa-jung.
I moved into the 2nd floor.
- And she's my super close friend.
- I see.
We are writer buddies of
Mr. GOH.
We dropped by for a drink with him.
Would you ladies like to join us?
Of course!
What are you doing? We shouldn't..
Hello? Yes, sir.
How do you do?
Mr. GOH?
His beeper doesn't work
here in the basement.
He's right here with me
Hold on.
It's the publisher.
- Asshole...
- Hello, sir.
I apologize about
this afternoon.
No, I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
Yes. Sure..
Why didn't you tell me about that
amazing story when you came by?
Excuse me?
Passionate but
corrupted love!
It sucked me in
from the beginning.
So, what happens next?
Everyone wants to know.
What do you mean..
That synopsis you left in our office.
The synopsis?
It's a story I heard.
I thought it was quite interesting.
Please take a look at it.
Fine! Take it! Take it all!
This is going to be
the next bestseller!
Thank you. You're too kind.
I get behind schedule a bit,
but you know I deliver the goods.
Where are you now?
At the office?
Thank you!
Mr. GOH, you're home!
Have a seat.
- For our trip to Daeguanryung!
- Cheers!
Daeguanryung?
Oh, we forgot to tell you.
A week after next week, we're going
to the Daeguanryung farm. All of us.
- How about you?
- Sure. I guess..
Let's drink a toast, again!
- For Daeguanryung trip!
- Cheers!
Teacher, are you awake?
The story..
Did you come up with it?
It's Hwa-jung's story.
- What?
- Hwa-jung made it up.
Did you read it? Isn't it good?
She didn't tell me the whole story.
Should I ask her for the rest?
- No, don't.
- No?
Don't!
Yes, sir.
I'll get your breakfast ready.
That can't be.
She's only a dumb coffee shop girl.
This can't be! She's
stupid and vulgar and..
Then what am I? I'm a writer.
A writer!!
Impossible!!
I think your PR really worked.
- It's been full house since this morning.
- Really?
Our comrades from
last night are here, too.
- Hi!
- hi
- How are you this morning?
- Very well.
I came for a cup of coffee with
someone special..
Oh my....
- Get me a cup of coffee
- Yes, sir.
Did you put in sugar?
Why didn't you knock?
Get me green tea! Green tea!
Did you read it?
What do you think?
Congratulations.
Conventionality
and corruption.
Modern but classic!
Heartwarming! It's great!
You gotta tell me
what happens next.
So what happens?
What happens?
Well..
Is Hwa-jung home?
- No. Why?
- Then can you help us?
- Why should I?
- Our grandma..
She passed away.
Grandma..
She's alive!!
Grandma!
Call the ambulance!
What's wrong with your phone?
Our phone line is disconnected.
Can we use your cell phone?
I don't have a cell phone.
Please.. Help me..
She fainted due to
malnutrition.
Fortunately,
she doesn't have any major illnesses.
She'll recover by tonight.
Okay
Are you her guardian?
What? How much?
We're sorry but she doesn't
have a health insurance.
Wait
You heard, right?
That's a lot of money for me.
You have to pay me back. Ok?
Ok
You promised. And with interest
would be even better.
Alright
- Sir..
- What?
I'm hungry.
The worst kind of people are those
who never pay back what they owe.
You don't wanna be like those
people, right?
- Hey, guys
- Hwa-jung!
Hwa-jung!
I can't get pass this part.
What?
It was nice what you did today.
Me?
Oh, that. They'll pay me back.
I'm kinda busy. Do you mind?
Oh, sorry.
- Wait!
- Yes?
About that story you told Hee-gu..
- The one with a woman drowning..
- What about it?
I'm curious what happens next.
Can you tell me the rest?
Sure.
But, why?
Are you gonna write
that into a novel?
My story will get published?
For real?
You know my writer buddy Mr. SHIM?
Of course.
He wants to make it into a novel.
So he asked me to
get the rest of
the story and tell him.
Why didn't he ask me?
He's little shy.
I see.
So, can you tell me
the rest of the story?
- Completely.
- Completely?
Ok. I haven't thought
about the ending, yet
But I can try.
When she turns her head
she sees him sitting in a bus,
right across from her bus.
She's so happy to see him.
And as she's about to get off,
the bus leaves.
Why didn't I think of that?
The handkerchief that holds the
fragrance of his mother..
- Wait.
- of his mother.. And?
He starts to run.
And keeps running.
Crashing into every obstacle
that lies in front of him..
Then he sees the light.
How long has it been since he last
saw the light? His eyes glisten.
It's great.
I guess you'll really
finish it by this month.
Ithink so.
Hey, join me at Hwa-jung's coffee
shop. I'm going there right now.
- Why?
- Just to kill time.
No. I'll pass. I need to rest.
I pulled all nighter last night.
Ok. Bye.
Hey, join me at Hwa-jung's coffee
shop. I'm going there right now.
What? He used me to get
the story from you?
Yes! I can't believe he lied!
Liar! Liar! Liar!!
No!
Hello? Where are you?
- I'm almost there.
- No!
What's wrong?
- Just come to my place.
- Why?
- It's urgent!
- What's wrong with you?
You come out.
I'm almost there.
Just stay there and
don't talk to anybody!
Do I make you feel uncomfortable?
- What?
- It's just that
You could've asked me directly. You
didn't have to go through Mr. GOH.
Mr. GOH?
What about Mr. GOH?
Move, Move!
Get outta the way!
About the story.
You mean the one
Mr. GOH's writing?
- No, the one you're..
- No!
What's up with your hair?
Mousse.
I need to talk to you..
- Why don't we talk here?
- Yes. Stay.
What? Hwa-jung likes me?
She said that?
Her boyfriend is in prison.
In prison?
When he gets out next month,
he's gonna come after you.
Why me?
He's jealousy incarnate.
Imagine what he'd do when
he finds out
that the love of his life has
betrayed him?
Would he hurt her?
No. He'll kill you first.
Avoid being seen
with her anywhere.
That is the only way
you'll live!
Did I seem little strange
this afternoon?
Yes. You looked like a lunatic.
I couldn't tell you, but..
Yesterday, I told you Mr. SHIM is..
too shy to ask you for the story, right?
- Yes.
- I lied.
But I can't tell you the truth.
No, no. You should know.
Mr. SHIM..
He's sick in his head.
Really? No..
He doesn't seem like so.
You can't tell byjust looking at
him, but when he has his fits..
I shouldn't tell you this.
I promise I won't tell anybody.
- Shh!
- Okay
When he loses control of himself,
he grabs his head like this..
and smashes it like this.
- And his nose bursts out in blood!
- God..
Especially
when his pride is hurt.
He strangles himself
foaming in his mouth..
If people find out that he's writing
your story into into a novel..
That's why you rushed to come over
with all that mousse in your hair.
It was a close call. Very close.
Now that I think of it, it was weird
how he always changed his hairdos.
It's the worst when he has a perm.
I'm sorry, buddy
I had no choice.
Daeguanryung?
Why would I go there?
You said you'd go. That's what
you told everybody.
I didn't mean what I said.
I'm not going.
So, I'm not going, either?
Why would you go if I'm not going?
Isn't it obvious why they're going?
They're gonna have a barbecue
party and get drunk.
With coffee shop girls
in their arms,
their goal is to get laid.
So vulgar and stupid.
What? He said I'm mentally sick?
Yes! And he told you I have
a boyfriend who's in prison?
Yes! And the story is yours?
Yes, it's mine!
He has no conscience!
- Bastard!
- Asshole!
- Coward!
- Shit head!
Teacher, what's the matter?
Let's go to Daeguanryung.
Mr. GOH, have you ever
been to the Daeguanryung farm?
- No.
- They must have milking cows there.
The white ones with black spots.
- Probably.
- I wonder how many. A lot, right?
I love animals.
I never miss an episode
of 'Animal Kingdom' on TV.
I bet you like that show, too
Last week was about
desert animals..
I hate animals.
And, especially, that stupid show!
I can't believe she's been talking
about animals for last hour.
- Yes?
- I'm sorry to bother you, but
my friend is hurt.
Can you please give us a ride?
- We're kinda behind schedule..
- Poor kids.
We'll pay you.
Thank you so much.
We're very sorry.
Assholes!
Ungrateful punks!
- Poopy heads.
- Poop.. Poopy..Poopy heads!
Bastards!
Those who don't
give a ride
are as bad as those
who steal cars.
We gave rides to everyone. But,
how come no one's giving us a ride?
Car's coming!
He's a bastard, too.
- I'm freezing.
- I'm freezing, too.
I'm starving.
I'm starving, too.
Why the hell did I come?
Look! Light!
Wait for me!
TV is going crazy again.
I told you to buy a new one!
Nonsense! This will last us
for another 10 years!
Hello?
Who is it?
Yes?
Hi. Can I please use your phone?
We don't have one.
I'm sorry to bother you
but I don't have a place to stay
for the night. May I stay here tonight?
- Sure. Come in
- Thank you so much.
I'm sorry, but there's
one more person.
C'mon! Come!
Please help yourself.
- Thank you.
I can't believe
those bastards!
If it was me, I would've
taught them a good lesson!
What would you have done?
During the war, I captured 10
North Koreans with my bare hands.
Whatever.
You're the biggest coward
in the world!
What? How dare you to talk like
that to your mighty husband!
- Mighty husband? That's funny!
- What's wrong with you?
- Are you gonna hit me? Hit me!
- Shut up!
C'mon, hit me!
I'm really gonna hit you!
Are you thinking
about Soon-duk, again?
Why do you always
bring her up?
Why do you get so sensitive
whenever I talk about her?
- Stop talking about her!
- Soon-duk!
- Shut up!
- I said shut up!
- Soon-duk!
- Shut up!
- Shut up!!
- Soon-duk!
Cops are searching for their car.
We should hear something back soon.
- Please find the car
- we'll try
Don't worry. They'll be fine.
You don't have to.. Thank you.
The sky is like a garden of stars.
Oh, dear.
It's beautiful.
Mr. ROH, what do your children do?
My children?
This is kinda embarassing but...
I'm...
still a bachelor.
An innocent bachelor..
- Shut up!
- Soon-duk!
- Shut up!!
- I said shut up!
- Soon-duk!
Tell me. How far did
you go with her?
All the way!
And we did it anywhere
at anytime!
Some days, we did 3 times a day!
I can't sleep.
- You should be embrassed
- Shut up!
Mr. GOH, have you
ever been to a zoo?
- A zoo?
- Yes.
I can't forget that one time when
my mom took me to a zoo.
I begged her to take me there
I was so excited.
It was my first
visit to a zoo.
I saw tigers, elephants,
deer, monkeys, seal and..
What's that bird
with big eyes that
stares like this?
An eagle?
No. The one that sits
like this on a tree.
An owl.
No, it's..
- Korean wood owl.
- No, that that one
No, it's 'something-op' owl..
Something-op? 'Top?' 'Cop?'
No, not 'cop..' 'Hop.. Sop..'
Oh! Sop owl!
- Scops owl.
- No, sop owl.
It's scops owl. The one with sullen
face that sits on a tree like this.
It's scops owl?
Anyway, it was really cool
seeing a scops owl.
Among all the animals,
I liked leopards the best.
There was
a motherless baby leopard..
and he looked so sad.
After looking around for a while,
I told my mom
I wanted some ice cream.
She told me to stay where I was
and went to get some ice cream.
I waited..
for hours and hours..
But, even when it started to
get dark, she didn't come back.
I looked for her everywhere,
but I couldn't find her.
I was so scared, I wanted to cry.
But I didn't.
Finally, I realized
she wasn't coming back.
You don't know
how much I regretted
asking her to
buy me some ice cream.
I didn't really have to eat it.
I was 7 then.
Since that day, I've
forgotten what she looks like.
Maybe it's because I'm dumb.
I can't remember at all.
I wish I had a picture of her.
That's all we talked
about in orphanage.
We had some weird kids there.
There was one called Booger.
He picked his nose everyday and he
stuck his boogers everywhere.
Sometimes his nose bled, too.
One day, he started to collect
his boogers in a small jar.
And after 7 years, the jar filled.
He proudly carried it in his arms
as he walked out of the orphanage.
All his boogers in thatjar..
That's why we called him Booger.
Thank you for your hospitality.
Thank you, again.
- Were we too loud last night?
- Yes.
No. We slept very well.
Stay on that road and
it'll lead you to the village.
There, you can catch a bus to
Seoul or make a phone call.
And take this.
No, we can't accept..
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Bye.
From the back seat,
he took his bandage and..
- I'm worried.
- About what?
About Hwa-jung?
Don't worry about her.
- She doesn't like you anymore.
- Really? That's nice.
- But I'm not talking about her.
- Then, the beauty salon girl?
No. A new one
She's a bartender
and she's incredible.
she's...
I think you're incredible.
She lives like a nameless fish
at the bottom of the ocean
Then one day,
she receives a phone call.
No. I think 'a letter' works
better than 'a phone call.'
- 'A letter' is better!
- Right.
and it zooms in like this..
As she takes her last breath
in the midst of snowy mountain,
the dying woman
dreams a fading dream.
One fine summer day
a man is watering
his garden with a hose.
Children play gaily underneath
the cool water stream.
From the porch, she watches him
playing with the children,
with a gentle smile on her lips.
As her spirit prepares herself to
leave her cold body..
she smiles for the last time.
The smile of..
sweet dreams.
- How is it?
- Hot
- How does it taste
- Good
This is the only thing
I can cook really well.
You hold your chopsticks funny.
- I'm fine like this.
- But it looks too weird.
You gotta hold it like this..
Like this. You try it.
No. Don't cross them.
They gotta be parallel.
Forget it. I like my way better
I think it's weird if a writer
can't even hold his chopsticks right.
Don't worry about it. Just eat.
You wanna eat pizza tomorrow?
Do you like pizza?
No. Let's eat noodles.
Ok
Are you surprised to
see a card on your wall?
Today is my birthday.
I'm super excited since
it's my first birthday here.
Tonight, I'm throwing a birthday
party at the coffee shop
I hope you'll come.
Birthday party?
Good day, sir?
Nothing special.
You're gonna propose to
your girlfriend tonight?
Me? No.
It's obvious!
Look, you even got
champagne and flowers!
It's not what you think.
- C'mon. Don't lie.
- Are you embarrassed?
We can tell.
- It's ok.
- Shut up!
Pull up over there.
There?
7,900 won, please.
What?
You picked up 2 other customers
along the way and took a detour.
I'm gonna report you in.
What's your cab number?
Have some conscience!
How can you charge me
for the full price?
Take 6,000 won
I didn't take a long detour.
Wait!
The bouquet!
- I hope you like it.
- Thank you so much.
What is it?
- So pretty!
- It's so cute!
Mr. GOH, you didn't
bring a gift?
Gift?
I got something and..
Let me guess. A poem!
When I retired from teaching,
he recited a poem for me.
How romantic!
That's so cool!
gas 23,000 won
groceries 11,000 won
Title.. 'Zoo'.. by GOH Seon-guk.
Going to a zoo
on a warm spring day
The lion,
king of all animals..
and tigers..
and elephants..
and giraffes..
and donkeys..
and..
orangutans..
chimpanzees...
and panda bears..
and deer are..
locked up..
in a small cage..
with countless scratches.
In front of a Ieopard's cage,
a little girl waits for her mother
eating her ice cream.
A motherless leopard
steadily gazes at her.
Soon a leopard and
the girl become friends.
A leopard, who lost his mother
in a vast prairie of Africa,
consoles the little girl.
In the darkness of the night,
in an empty cage,
the two motherless souls
welcome the long sleep
of their mothers' wombs,
Then, her mother's
voice awakens them.
As the girl bids farewell
to her dear leopard, with her
hand in her mother's hand,
an escaped scops owl flies
over her head
towards a distance sky.
Thank you.
That was beautiful.
ﬂ Kiss me, kiss me much,ﬁ
E in the stillness of the night,
when the lilacs fade and fall.ﬁ
ﬂ Kiss me, kiss me muchﬁ
ﬂ Please bring me the sweet
smell of lilacﬁ
ﬂ Kiss me, kiss me much,
my sweet little girlﬁ
you're my lonely St. Mariaﬁ
ﬂ Kiss me, kiss me much,ﬁ
E in the stillness of the night,
when the lilacs fade and fall.ﬁ
ﬂ Kiss me, kiss me muchﬁ
ﬂ Please bring me the sweet
smell of lilacﬁ
Hwa-jung, it's me.
What are you two
doing in my house?
Mr. GOH, I wasjust giving Hee-gu
some advices on his troubles.
I thought you a decent boy, but..
- Teacher, it's not what you think.
- No. I understand.
It's natural for young kids like
you to like each other. But! why here?
Mr. GOH, it's not what you think.
Hee-gu likes someone else.
Not you?
How many girls?
You must be pretty good, huh?
Tell me. Who else?
- Do you really want to know?
- Yes.
Hee-gu likes..
you.
Done!
- It's finished!
- What's finished?
What? What?
- Where d'you come from?
- Sorry
- You scared me
- But, what's finished?
- Nothing. What do you want?
- Me?
I need you to come with me.
Hee-gu, you have to stay still.
Why do you think
they put this on you?
- You have to rest.
- Where is my teacher?
He said he'll come.
Give him a few minutes.
He's really angry, right?
No. He worried about you so much.
Don't worry.
Is this ok?
Teacher..
How are you?
I have to stay here for about 2
months, but I'll be fine.
You said you have
something to tell him.
Don't worry about me.
I'll be back at work in no time.
You know what?
I don't want to
coming back to work.
You love me?
You make me wanna puke!
You dirty bastard!
Mr. GOH..
- I'm going.
- But..
- What's wrong with you?
- Hee-gu...
You should feel grateful for
being loved. No matter what.
- You...
- Mr. GOH, say something.
Mr. GOH..
Wait! Can I talk to you?
I have nothing to say about him.
I feel gross.
- Please don't do this.
- Do what?
You're his teacher.
Can't you just embrace
your student as a teacher?
Just this once...
I'm not his teacher anymore.
Finished?
Mr. GOH!
Why do you have to be so cruel?
Go back and tell him you're sorry.
Why should I?
And stop telling me what to do.
Giving me a story doesn't give
you any right to butt into my life!
Besides, I don't need that crappy
story, anyway. I don't need..
You're writing that into a novel?
No.. I mean..
Did you lie about
Mr. SHIM's illness?
- No.. It's..
- Was it all lie?
How can you do this to me?
I really believed you
but you lied about everything!
Why?
Fine, I lied! I lived my whole
life lying to everyone!
But, you're no better than I am.
All you do is pour coffee and
seduce men. Dumb and vulgar..
Is that what you think of me?
Is that really
what you think of me?
I'm not as terrible
as you think I am.
Did you know next week is the
49th Day of your father's death?
No. And I don't
really care to know.
You should forgive you father.
He wasn't as a good father
or a good husband
as your portrayal of him
in your book.
But I still like him
as who he was.
After how he hurt you?
I lied to you
about something.
Do you want to know what?
What?
I told you
your grandpa was a pimp, right?
And I told you your father slept with
a girl who worked for grandpa.
I know. I don't wanna hear it again
Well, that girl was...
me.
When I was 13,
I was sold by my father
for his gambling debt.
When I first got there,
no one was nice to me.
Even the ornamental hairpin
which my mom gave me
was taken away from me.
I worked all daylong.
It was hard living but
I was grateful for not starving.
When everyone went to bed, I would
sit by the kitchen fireplace and
think about my mom and cry.
That's when I met your father.
He was very compassionate
and kind.
He was the only one
who was nice to me.
After a year, I was sold
to anotherhousehold.
Whenever life got too difficult,
I thought of your father.
Then in Masan,
I met your father again.
It was he
who finally freed me
from all the debt.
So, how can I ever forget him?
Oh, I have something for you
Before he passed away,
he gave that to me.
So I could live rest
of my life comfortably.
But, I don't need it.
I'm old and I have no use for
all that money. It's yours.
Think of it as your
father's last gift.
There's one more...
This..
Lately I've been seeing
your father in my dreams
and I think it's time
for me to go join him.
When you meet
a girl you love,
give this
ornamental hairpin to her
It's a present from me.
Mom,
stop talking non-sense.
You're not gonna die.
You know..
when I see your father again,
even if he has...
another new wife,
I'd very much like to
live with him again.
You want some pizza?
No, I gotta act more natural..
You like pizza, right?
- Pizza for you!
- Thank you!
- Thank you, Mr. GOH!
- You know how I think about you.
Mr. GOH, thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
Hwa-jung.
huh?
I'm sorry for
not saying 'goodbye'.
I appreciate
all your kindness.
Goodbye. Hwa-jung.
Hi. What brings
you here at this hour?
Where is Hwa-jung?
She's gone.
You didn't see her?
- To where?
- To Namwon. Why?
It's just...
She didn't clean up the room
before she left.
But, anyways..
Waiting at the Zoo
When the warm spring breeze starts
to blow in Serengeti Park,
all the wild animals
begin to emerge
from their winter hideouts.
Winter in Africa doesn't get too
cold. However, to all animals,
there's nothing more delightful than
a tickle of warm spring breeze.
With arrival of spring,
animals start their search for
their partners.
The mating season
starts in full swing.
This massive male hippopotamus
have found his female partner.
Giraffes, known as the gentlemen
of Serengeti, are not exceptions.
It's delightful to see greetings
from baby giraffes.
Even an orangutan, the lord of the
jungle, has found his female partner.
This is the season of love
for all animals.
However,
there are always exceptions.
Leopards don't have specific
mating season.
This lonely leopard is Amur
Leopard.
Unlike other African animals,
who travel and live in groups,
he takes pleasure in solitude.
He also wants a partner, but
he's not ready for one, yet.
What are you doing here?
- I can't go through with this.
- What?
You only got 30 min.
till the wedding!
Did you..?
I didn't know at first
but more I see her
I want to be with her.
You'll forget her
when you get married.
When you don't see her
you'll forget her.
But I can't not see her.
Who is she?
Jin-sook..
She's my wife's sister.
You understand me, right?
You're a piece of shit!
You don't deserve to love anyone!
Get your hands off me!
You don't deserve to be in love!
Do whatever you want!
Love may come easy to you,
but if you can't keep it,
it's meaningless.
What the hell do you
know about love?
You've never been
in love your self
I know.
I know the feeling
of not being able
to sleep at night and
spending the whole day
doing nothing because..
because I can't stop
thinking about her.
I know now.
You fell in love.
1, 2, 1, 2, Good! Good!
Hello.
How's your leg?
Good
This is my boyfriend.
How do you do?
You guys look good together.
How's Hwa-jung?
Good..
- Hi
- Hello
Waiting at the Zoo
- Hwa-jung
- Huh
- Another delivery.
- Again?
- Yeah
- To where?
Kwanghanroo, near the gazebo.
I don't know why anyone would
order coffee from there.
That's ok. I'll go.
- Bye
Pretty cool, huh?
Hundreds of years ago, on
a fine spring day like today,
Mongryong sees
Chunhyang on this swing
and fall in love with her.
They endure much
suffering and pain,
but they let it blossom.
My heart aches just thinking
about them.
Doesn't yours?
Blossom what?
Their love!
Mongryong sees Chunhyang
from that gazebo over there.
The gazebo is called Kwanghanroo.
Shall we go over there?
I'm here
but nobody ordered coffee.
Alright.
I'm going back.
You look
just like someone I know.
Except for the bear.
Hwa-jung, it's me. GOH Seon-guk.
I ordered the coffee.
Mr. GOH?
What are you doing here?
And what's up with your beard?
Well.. I got lazy
and didn't want to shave..
I was bored and
just came out to
get some fresh air..
What's that? Wasn't the mole on
the other side?
Huh?
I put it on this side,
today. It's removable.
Depending on my mood, I put
it on different spots.
I see.
Are you...
Still really mad at me?
No. It's ok now.
I'm thinking
about starting a new novel..
and can we write it together?
Like the last time?
Your name will be on the cover.
If you don't want to, then it's ok.
Oh...
This is for you.
What is it?
My mom got this from her mother and
she wants me to
give it to you.
Are.. you..
proposing to me?
Well..
It's not.. I mean..
I went to see my mom and..
since I don't have a girlfriend..
you know I don't have
women at all...
I don't know any women and..
We're close,
$0..
What are you watching?
That man
is about to propose to her.
That's so romantic!
That man is about to
propose to that woman.
Even a pizza is too big
to order when you're alone.
Should we go somewhere else?
Well..
You can do it!
He said, you can do it!
He said, you can do it.
To be honest with you,
well..
Honestly...
I didn't think much of you
when we first met.
But, more I got to know you..
I became...
Do your best!
Till the end!
He said, do your best
till the end!
You can do it!
You can do it!...
I like..
I like you.
What?
I can't hear you.
I really like you.
And I can't live without you.
Me, too.
I need you
And I can't live
without you, either.
Ah.. even after hundreds of years,
the spring breeze of Choson Dynasty
is still blowing.