MagnaVolt.
The final word in auto security.
No embarrassing alarm noise,
no need to trouble the police...
...and it won't even
run down your battery.
Magna Volt.
Lethal response.
On the international scene, the Amazon
nuclear power facility has blown its stack...
...irradiating the world's largest rain forest.
Environmentalists call it a disaster.
But don't they always?
In national news,
Attorney General Marcos today...
...approved the ED 209 combat unit
for deployment in five American cities...
...despite widespread complaints
of malfunction.
The surgeon general is dead.
Gunned down 20 minutes ago by a militant
addict of the deadly designer drug Nuke.
The greatest health threat
facing our nation.
Nuke.
The most addictive narcotic
in history.
A plague that...
Nuke! Nuke!
This station has just received
this transmission from Cain...
...convicted murderer
and leader of the Nuke cult.
The people want paradise.
And they will have it.
The assassination is the latest
act of terrorism by Cain...
... following the bombing
of a drug treatment clinic that left five dead.
After the latest breakdown in negotiations,
Detroit's police returned to the picket line...
...demanding better terms from
Omni Consumer Products, OCP...
...the corporation contracted by the city
to run the police department.
OCP cut our salaries 40 percent
and canceled our pensions.
Now they refuse to even talk to us.
God knows why,
but they want this strike.
What happened?
Get up!
- Hold him!
- You put my eye out, you bitches!
Shut up, you fuckhead!
- You're breaking my fucking arm!
- Hurry!
Look at this. What a nasty man.
Night's made. Let's pay Papa
and get us what we need.
Nuke me, baby!
- I'll kill you bitches!
- He's up! Come on!
- You're shit with a timer, man!
- Come on! Let's go!
I'll take out an army with this shit!
Let's load up
and get the hell out of here!
Where's the bullets for this gun, man?
Third drawer, bottom.
We should've brought a truck!
I really like this gun, man.
Just take it and get out.
Thanks.
- I don't believe this!
- What?
- It's the cops, man.
- Cops are on strike, stupid.
Can't you hear that?
- See. What did I tell you?
- I'll fix him.
Did you see that? We got him!
- Beautiful. Come on, man. Let's move it.
- No. One more!
Nice shit, man.
Fucking cops!
Peace officer.
Think it over, creep.
Nuke.
It's not mine, man.
Where is it made?
It's not mine, man. I told you! I'm clean!
I don't know, man!
All I know is where I get it!
Freeze.
Nobody move. This is a bust.
Ladies, stay down.
Somebody! Open the fridge, damn it!
Come on!
Can't shoot a kid, can you, fucker?
Can't shoot a kid...
Throw it home, Dad!
Shut up!
Drop it or the little shit's dead!
I'll blow its fucking head off, man!
Lewis...
...hang it up.
Now, no shit from either one of you!
- And don't try to follow me!
- We won't.
The baby's going with me!
I'll kill it, man. I'll do it. I'll fucking kill it!
We can't have that.
Nice shooting.
See you, Jimmy.
- Hi, Mom.
- Hi.
Don't do it! No! Stop... Stop it, Alex!
OCP defines you as a machine...
...that utilizes some living tissue.
You understand that.
Yes.
And so do you
consider yourself human?
I require an answer.
Stop tape.
You have any idea what you're doing
to that poor woman?
Take a look at her file.
Go on.
Officer, Mrs. Murphy
is bringing suit against OCP.
My name is Tom Delaney.
I'm representing her.
Up to a few months ago,
she wouldn't leave her bedroom.
Then there were hypnotists
and harmonic treatments.
Then you pull this shit!
Driving past her house day after day.
Spying on her. Trying to make her
think her husband is still alive.
She's barely started
to accept the loss.
- You're ripping her to pieces.
- And for what?
Do you think you could ever be
a husband to her?
I mean, what can you offer her?
Companionship?
Love?
A man's love?
No.
Roll tape.
Are you Alex Murphy?
No.
Are you human?
You are simply a machine.
I am...
...a machine.
Nothing more.
That'll do it. Stop tape.
Now, you stay there.
All right, go get her.
Let's be decent about this.
Give them some privacy.
I don't have a problem with that.
Alex?
Don't you know me?
Don't you remember me?
Alex, it doesn't matter
what they've done to you...
Touch me.
It's cold.
They made this...
...to honor him.
- No, l...
- Your husband is dead.
I don't know you.
Why is this happening?
I thought all communication systems
were the same.
I tried to save the company
a few bucks.
It took two days to download specs
from Cleveland.
I lost the account.
It hardly befits my dignity
to have to come to you, Johnson.
Sorry for the slight inconvenience,
Your Honor.
Twenty minutes in rush hour isn't slight.
Not when you're mayor of a major city!
When will you start paying the cops
so they'll go back to work?
We're not a charity.
The city owes us over $37 million.
- You'll have to cut us some slack.
- A deadline's a deadline. Sorry.
How are we supposed to raise
that kind of money?
You aren't.
- What the hell is he talking about?
- We don't expect you to pay.
Let me refer you to our contract.
"In the event of default...
...OCP shall have the uncontested right
of foreclosure on all city assets."
You signed this.
We miss one payment,
and you can foreclose?
We can and we will.
We're taking Detroit private.
So you deliberately undermined
our credit.
That was the easy part.
And you engineered the police strike.
You want Detroit to tear itself apart...
...so you can raid it like you would
any other corporation!
Do you know how many people
are dying?
You're murderers!
I'd advise you to say nothing further.
It might be...
...actionable.
It's bullshit!
- Bullshit, you senile, old bastard!
- All right, calm down.
- We better get out of here.
- I'm okay!
- Calm down. We better leave.
- I'm calm.
- Calm down. Easy.
- I'm okay.
All right, good.
- I'm in control. Everything is fine. It's okay.
- Relax.
I'm fine.
One last thing, gentlemen.
We will sue your asses.
Give it your best shot.
Fuck you, you old, senile bastard!
This is bullshit!
Fuck you!
- This is bullshit!
- Calm down.
I've been very patient, Johnson.
Five months.
- Who's that?
- That's Dr. Juliette Faxx.
Just moved up to head the
Attitude Adjustment team.
Five months. Ninety million dollars!
- I want to see some results.
- Yes, sir. I'll show you what we have.
OCP pioneered cyborg technology.
And now we take
a quantum leap forward.
State-of-the-art
destructive capabilities...
... commanded by a unique combination
of software and organic systems.
In every way,
an improvement over the original.
It gives me great pleasure
to introduce to you, Robocop 2.
You are under arrest.
Stop or I'll shoot.
OCP is proud to present the future
of urban pacification:
Robocop 2.
Ninety million.
They all go crazy.
Robots with emotional problems.
No, sir, not robots, cyborgs.
Cybernetic organisms. We use living human
tissue and that's our whole problem.
The candidates were all fine men,
respected police officers.
I reviewed their files myself.
Sir, police officers may not be
the best candidates for our purposes.
They're a physical bunch.
They're macho, body-proud.
Stripped of all that it's no wonder
they become suicidal.
Our one success was a cop.
Well, yes, Mr. Johnson. Alex Murphy.
Top of his class,
devout Irish Catholic, family man.
Everything in his profile
indicates a fierce sense of duty.
That's probably what kept him alive.
With due respect, Dr. Faxx,
your area of expertise is psychology.
Not robotics.
There's no harm in hearing
the young lady out, is there?
No, sir.
Thank you, sir. I believe that Murphy's case
was unusual but not unique.
We can find someone else, someone
to whom the prospect might even be...
...desirable.
I've never met anyone who wanted
to be a robot.
It would require a screening process,
one I'd would be happy to supervise.
The cost would be negligible.
It would be a shame
to waste all the work that's been done.
It certainly would.
Go to it. Report to me directly.
Yes, sir.
You could learn a thing or two
from that girl, Johnson.
- Not for me!
Decent pay to decent cops!
Union's got a list!
We ain't forgetting who you are!
One at a time!
Please, one at a time.
Don't you know
what's going on out here?
It's the best we can do!
Hello, ladies!
They won't be fucking
with any more cops!
with nobody, man!
Hob. That's him.
Thank you.
Nuke me!
Go ahead. Take two.
There's plenty of Nuke to go around.
I've lost him.
You haven't been around in a while.
Go ahead. This one's on me.
Five degrees south-southwest.
There's the little darling.
Good eyes, Murphy.
Good as money can buy.
Ferdy, you got out.
Well, I'll tell Cain, okay?
Better have something
to give me this time, officer.
One cop per car.
Okay, these are the routes.
Three cars.
- One cop per car?
- That's right.
Sitting ducks. We set up three
snipers and that's all it takes.
- Pay the man.
- All right.
Thank you.
- You didn't count it.
- That's all right.
You should really count it, you know.
It's okay.
Give him something
to help him with his conscience.
No, that's all right. I don't really want it.
Come on, Duffy. I know you need it.
Isn't this a school day?
Cops!
Oh, shit!
Oh, no.
Freeze!
Turn around. Put your hands up.
Shit.
Officer Duffy, have a seat.
You look a little out of breath, bitch.
- You sold us out, Officer Duffy.
- What are you talking about, Murph?
Where is Cain?
I don't know any Cain.
I don't know.
Where is Cain?!
I told you, I don't know!
Where?
River Rouge. The old sludge plant.
You're a rotten cop.
Go.
- You.
- You want me?
Dead or alive.
Then one of us must die.
Dead, then.
Jesus...
...had days like this.
Hounded and attacked like a criminal.
But like him, I don't blame you.
They program you, and you do it.
- I will kill you.
- Oh, you just tried.
And...
...I forgive you.
Why'd you stop? You got it cracked.
I'm tired.
They say he's got a brain.
I want to see it.
You think it was me that beat you?
It wasn't.
It was this.
It's too tough.
Try here at the joint.
Yeah!
Look at that!
Come on. Cut it out.
How's it taste?
What the hell's going on?!
Man, just look at him.
Christ, he's been stripped.
Let's not get carried away here.
We're talking about a piece of equipment.
Don't tell me he can't suffer.
Just look at him.
It's electrical.
Bullshit.
I know every inch of him.
Every circuit.
Every living nerve.
His pain centers are alive.
They're lit up like Christmas trees.
The back-up generator's
just making him twitch.
He's suffering.
How long can he last?
No way of knowing.
Got him on minimal life support.
Keeping the brain going
with microshocks.
- It's damn tricky. He could go anytime.
- Move. Move!
What's happening in here?
OCP is happening. These bastards
won't lift a finger to help him.
This unit needs
millions of dollars in parts.
You can't expect authorization for that
kind of cash overnight. Be reasonable.
If you don't fix him, it's murder.
Settle down. I'm doing you
a favor by talking to you.
You son of a bitch. He's in hell.
Fix him!
We'll be in touch.
Oh, man, you guys are the greatest!
Did you see their faces?
"We're gonna throw away
the key, Duffy."
The cops didn't give you trouble,
did they?
The usual shit from Reed.
They'll never prove anything.
Hey, want some?
Hey, I'm a minor.
Don't want to break any laws.
Here, you take it.
God, I just love you guys!
What happened?
Hey, where we going?
Hey, come on, guys.
This isn't funny, man.
Oh, God, my head.
My head is killing me.
Hey, man. What's?
Hey, Cain! Hey, it's good to see you.
Thanks for getting me out.
- I can't get up.
- You noticed that one.
- Cain, I don't know what the kid told you...
- You told them, Duffy.
- You told them where we were.
- That's not true.
- We know all about it, Duffy.
- You think you're the only cop we have?
Oh, shit!
Cain. Cain, come on.
Man, I'm begging you, man!
Look, I'll do anything!
Okay. You're kidding, right?
Yeah, you're just kidding.
You scared me.
You taught me a lesson, man.
I'd never fuck with you,
because I really love you guys.
- I really do!
- Shut up!
I've been loyal. I know shit
that I still haven't even told you, Cain!
You deserve this, Duffy.
Cain might have been killed.
Okay. Okay.
Maybe you ought to have the kid leave.
- Why?
- What do you mean, "have the kid leave"?
That's a good touch. That's a good touch.
"Have the kid leave."
That's good. "Have the kid leave." Why?
Come on. It's over.
Come on, Cain! Come on, man.
What are you doing?
Come on!
You said you were
just gonna scare him!
Doesn't he look scared?
I can't believe you'd do this.
It hardly matters what you believe,
Mr. Schenk.
But these are criminals.
They're maniacs.
You're giving premature
value judgments.
All right, it may be true.
The subjects are socially misaligned.
Socially misaligned?
These are death row inmates!
And of no use to society. We need a
subject who'll welcome the power...
...the virtual immortality we offer.
Now, I really think this is a good place
to start looking.
- You're out of your mind.
- Is that your professional opinion?
Yes, goddamn it, it is! Yes!
And you are not using my lab to put
that kind of a brain into my cyborg.
We'd dearly miss you here.
You're the one that's gonna be
out of a job.
I'm going to take this directly
to Johnson.
He's just been waiting for an excuse
to get you fired.
Good morning, sir.
I'm sorry to bother you this early.
You seem agitated.
Frankly, I'm shocked.
Mr. Schenk just called.
Dr. Faxx has begun screening
candidates for the Robocop 2 project...
So I understand. It's very exciting.
She's screening psychotics, sir.
Murderers.
We aren't planning to build a toy,
Johnson.
Faxx knows what she's doing.
She's keeping Robocop offline.
It's a public-relations disaster.
You've got to learn to look
at the larger picture. The foreclosure.
You must know how important
that is to us.
With Robocop out of commission, the
chaos down there will increase...
...and the odds the city will fall
into our hands.
But a competent executive would find a way
to deal with the corporate image problem.
Couldn't agree with you more,
Mr. Johnson.
Fortunately, I have found a way.
Yes, Ms. Faxx and I have
already discussed it.
I know you'll help
to implement her ideas.
Of course, sir. Whatever I can do.
Anything else?
- Coffee?
- No, thank you.
Don't forget your shoes
on the way out.
He's my patient and critical.
I must stay with him.
We'll let you know when we need you.
Nobody on your staff has my experience
with him. You need me.
We don't need anybody.
"We." Who the hell are "we"?
You're a lawyer who knows nothing!
You're exactly this far
from getting fired, babe.
Shyster!
He's one of mine.
I want him back on his feet.
Maybe he will be,
or maybe we'll just sell the parts for scrap.
That's up to us.
You see, Robocop's off warranty.
Robocop's command program...
...his set of directives...
It determines his behavior.
It's time to update the program...
...and I would like to hear
from each one of you.
It's about time they asked us.
We're getting a lot of heat
from parents' groups.
Personally, I don't blame them.
I'm a parent.
All that destructive behavior.
He's become a role model
for our children.
- Now, what are we teaching them?
- You have a point.
If he talked things out with people
instead of firing that gun.
Couldn't he take a little time
to address environmental issues?
What was that?
He could speak out
on environmental issues.
Don't see any reason why not.
For all the shooting he does...
...l've never once seen him take the time
to do anything nice...
...like visit an orphanage.
- You're absolutely right.
Or help a cat out of a tree...
...or go door to door collecting
for the Red Cross...
...or maybe even roasting some
marshmallows with some Cub Scouts.
Why, Mr. Johnson, that is wonderful.
Thank you so much.
- It's no good. The program isn't uploading.
- He's resisting.
There's too much data.
- No, it's him. Leave him to me, Schenk.
- I can't... It's not going to work!
You're wasting valuable time.
- Don't resist us.
- Let me up.
I must go.
Go where?
Do what? Go dancing? Fall in love?
What is it you think you are?
Alex Murphy.
That's a delusion.
It's a glitch in your system.
Alex Murphy is dead.
Take away the metal and wires,
you're just a couple chunks on a table.
You're not even a corpse.
What are you?
Respond.
I am Officer Alex Murphy...
...Detroit Police Department.
That won't do.
What are you?
Robocop. Crime Prevention Unit.
OCP.
Better. Much better.
I type it. You think it.
You type it. I think it.
What a wonderful opportunity
you represent.
Psychotherapy, it's such a...
It's a slow, clumsy practice.
But with you this is so simple.
Direct.
You're lucky.
We can do in moments with you what
would take years with a human patient.
I'm really very lucky.
You're free. You're free from doubt.
Free from having to make painful choices.
I am free.
He's ready.
Uploading command program.
I am so glad we had this chance
to dialogue.
Look at you. It's like you're brand-new.
Thank you. Thank you.
You really had us worried there, Murphy.
I'm touched.
Get this guy.
He's touched.
That's enough. All of you,
back to your posts. Come on. Let's go.
How you feeling, Murphy?
I'm just fine, Warren.
Thank you for asking.
Let's get you downstairs.
I want to see what those amateurs
at OCP screwed up.
Pity. It's a beautiful morning.
Shame to waste it.
- Ready for duty, partner?
- You betcha.
- Let's go.
- Nothing I'd rather do.
He sounds terrific.
Something's wrong.
Harder!
It's Robo!
Everybody out the back door!
- It's locked!
- It won't open!
Murph, wake up, will you?
Good morning.
Come on, take him out.
I think we should talk.
What's with you, Murph?
- Where'd they go?
- "Where'd they go?"
They're still here,
the little bastards!
Hands up! Let's go! Everybody up!
Move it. Up against the wall.
Let's go.
Hands on top of your heads.
Nobody move.
You are under arrest.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will
be used against you...
...in a court of law.
- He's dead, Murphy.
- You have the right...
- You're reading Miranda to a corpse!
I'm having trouble.
Oh, my.
This isn't very nice.
Though you may think
you're having fun now...
...you only hurt the one you love.
Think of Mom and Dad.
What kind of lesson are
you teaching them?
And now, a word on nutrition.
Shit! He's fucked up!
Bad language makes for bad feelings.
Let's go!
The point is...
...we all have to work.
I haven't finished.
Hit the gas, Murphy.
The posted limit is 35.
We should set an example, Anne.
Your hair looks lovely that way.
It's OCP. They did something to you.
I'm fine.
Isn't the moon wonderful tonight?
It's still daytime.
It's the thought that counts.
Oh, Jesus, we're heading back
to the station. That's all there is to it.
What the hell are you doing?!
Waste makes haste...
...for time is fleeting.
A rolling stone is won'th
two in the bush.
Go fuck a refrigerator, pecker neck!
Bad language makes for bad feelings.
You're nuts!
Murphy, come on, let's go.
Come on!
Back!
Thank you for not smoking.
Well, there it is. It's OCP.
They screwed him up.
He must be going out of his mind.
It's not as if he can just say no.
They put all this nonsense
into his brain. He has to obey.
Take them out, all of them!
Can't be done,
not with this equipment.
Are you saying there's no way?
I can't believe that.
Sure, there are ways.
You can pull his cranial circuits.
Which would shut down
his life-support.
You could run a few thousand volts
through him.
Probably kill him.