No, no, no. Don't food the dog, darllng.
Thanks, babe.
- You slept late.
- Yeeh, I need to go.
What you got golng today?
I've got to ﬂnlah up some cultalna
for Saturday,
and Nat and Cam are oomlng over.
- Wlth the klda?
- Yeah.
Cammle aald ahe Just needed
to get out of the house.
Tell Nat to take It eaay on her.
Carn ean hold her own.
We need to send In the depoalt
for the beach oondo.
I love you.
- Juat wrlte the check, babe, okay?
- 0kay. Bye.
You, eat.
Yeah, let's keep golng wlth that blt.
It'll go another 10 feet.
We won't get the gravel pack down today.
Why not?
Clouds.
We're gonna have to eell It.
Happy hour starts at 5:00, Dewart.
Not If It's ralnlng.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
They were Just drlnklng and laughlng.
And, oh, my God,
It was llke I was belng In a museum
and I saw the progress from apes to men.
I saw It. I saw the future.
Dewart, that was hlm,
that was golng to be hlm In 20 years.
Let me tell you, you laugh.
You laugh. But thls llttle one In your arms
ls gonna be shufﬂlng In a barJust llke them.
- Yep.
- No.
Don't llsten to her.
- Hannahl
- What?
- You guys okay?
- Yeah.
No. Don't touch.
You understand?
Okay. Come here.
Go play.
Hey, DJ. Brlng the glrls lnslde.
What?
- lt's not my fault. I told you.
- Yeah, all rlght.
All rlght, I'm eelllng It. Shut It down.
- Bye, guys. Thank you for comlng.
- l'll eell you about the Llons Club supper.
- 0kay. Love you.
- Bye, Sam.
Bye, Hannahl
S-T-O-R-M?
Storm.
I gotta get home.
flat and me been looklng Into a threesome.
We've been chattlng wlth thls glrl onllne
from Canton.
Yeah. Blg old glrl.
What's blg?
She's about 250, 215.
She een't be no taller than ﬁve foot.
Shlt, man.
I don't see me and Sam
gettlng Into somethlng llke that.
No. I don't guess you would.
You got a good llfe, Curtls.
I'm serlous.
I thlnk that's the best compllment
you een glve a man,
take a look at hls llfe and say, 'That's good.
'That guy's dolng somethlng rlght.'
Well, It aln't always so easy.
Hell, I know that.
Shlt. I gotta go.
Good nlght.
Hey, baby.
She do all rlght today?
She's stlll not playlng
wlth the others, though.
She een't connect.
Honey, you gotta clean up that trash plle
In the back.
She fished out a board that had nails on it.
I'll get to It thls weekend.
I stlll take off my boots,
so I won't wake her up.
I stlll whlsper.
Curtls?
- What?
- Dld you hear me?
You got to be home, showered,
ready to walk out the door by 0:00 tonlght.
What's wrong?
Nothlng. ljust want her to eat her breakfast
and stop playlng wlth the damn dog.
She's ﬂne down there. She had toast already.
- All rlght.
- What?
Hannah. Come here. Hannah.
- Curtls?
- What?
- You dldn't eat anythlng.
- lt's okay.
I dldn't say you had control
over the weather, Russell.
What I dld say was that the top shelf
has got to be cleared by the 15th.
That's non-negotlable.
Curtls?
Curtis? Where we at on that East 82nd site?
Yesterday slowed us down.
We couldn't get the second pllot hole drilled.
It rained for two hours yesterday.
Two hours,
and our entire schedule went In the toilet?
We lose the permit
If you're not out of there, end of day.
- Yes, sir.
- End of day, Curtls.
All right. Valerle tells me
that the father-son paneeke cook-off...
Hey, I gotta make a stop
before we head out there.
- Thlnk we got time?
- Yeah, there's tlme.
Shlt.
Sonofabltoh.
- We strlpped that bit.
- Yeah.
Well, brlng It up. We gotta reset It.
Curtlsl
- You ever see blrds ﬂy like that?
- What?
Damn It.
Come on, we gotta go.
Jesus.
Honey, I een really use a shower.
So If you continue with the basic voeebulary,
this will allow you to communicate
with your children better.
Between the ages of four and seven,
the focus ls more on the sign.
And then later,
we'll begln adding the alphabet
as more of a support system.
Now, In ASL,
the male slgn ls signed at the forehead area.
For example, 'father,'
ls signed up here like this.
Father. Very good.
- You're not sorry.
- I am sorry.
Well, you stlnk. You smell really bad.
I think I smell good.
Do I smell good?
See? Maybe I should marry her Instead.
Stop.
You okay?
Shltl
You're okay.
It's okay.
Here, honey. Put on your shoes.
- Good, you're up.
- Yeah.
Honey, you're soaked.
I've felt better.
I guess we een stay home If we need to.
Where you going?
It's Saturday.
I was going to take Hannah to my booth.
Yeah.
You look really sick, honey.
I'm all right. It's Just a cold or something.
Let me get you some Advll.
Don't worry about It. Just go. I'll be ﬁne.
You sure?
Better already.
Okay. I got my phone If you need anything.
Don't forget, Sunday lunch ls here tomorrow.
If you're sick, we should eencel.
I'll be all right.
Okay, we'll talk later.
Come on. Let's go.
- You sure?
- Honey, please.
How much you asking for this plllow?
Thls plllow Is 315.
That's more than I want to spend.
This Is all hand stltched.
It takes a really long time.
That's why I charge that.
I'll give you $1 for It.
I een't go that low.
Well, that's my offer.
How about 10?
I'll give you $0, but It's In change.
That's ﬁne.
Lucky for you she likes to count change.
Come on.
Get In. Good boy.
I'm sorry about this, buddy.
We Just gotta work It like this
for awhile, okay?
While rescue workers made several attempts
to reach the family,
- Welter .Iecobe' wlfe and brother-ln-lew dled.
- That's what I don't understand.
If he didn't do anything,
why did you put him out back?
What?
Did you hear me?
I said If he didn't do anything,
why did you have to put him outside?
I Just wanted him to be outside for a while.
He's your dog.
He's always been an Inside dog.
He's my dog, that's why he's outslde.
Look,
right now with Hannah and everything,
ljust thlnk It'd be better.
- Hannah loves Red.
- Hold on.
...the gee cloud spread across
their six-acre property.
The only way off their land
was across the train tracks,
which were blocked by wreckage.
i tried using some wet rags
and some towels to breathe through,
but that just seemed to make it worse.
While rescue workers made several attempts
to reach the family,
Waiter Jacobs' wife and brother-in-iaw died
in the home.
Jacobs survived despite enduring ff hours
of exposure to the gas cloud...
You hearing this?
It's awful.
Eleven hours.
No way out.
Heyl
Hey! Hey!
- Babe?
- Yeah?
You got the number for Dr. Shannan?
You're still not feeling good?
Yeah, we got the number?
Yeah, baby, but he'll be closed today.
Right. Yeah, I'll eell tomorrow.
Honey, If you're not feeling good,
- we got to take you...
- No. Stopl
Okay.
Do you want me to eancel lunch today?
Shlt.
- What Is that?
- l'm sorry.
I'm sorry. IJust...
I got a sore throat.
I'm sorry I'm taking It out on you.
I was gonna leave Hannah with you
so I could go to church,
but I'm not gonna with you like this.
It's ﬁne. I'll be ﬁne.
- No. She needs breakfast.
- I got It.
I'm sorry that you feel bad,
but you need to drop the attitude.
Come on. Just go.
- What's wrong with you?
- l'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Just go.
Hannah's in the den. We have cereal for her.
We're going out.
We're going out. Okay?
It's okay. It's okay.
You stay put, okay?
Let's Just start.
Let's all Join hands for the blessing.
- Where the hell have you been?
- I know. I'm sorry. I had to run an errand.
- You're really late.
- I know.
You didn't even bring your cell phone.
Missed you at church this morning, Curtls.
He knows what to do
If he wants me to stop asking.
Was It a good service?
It was. It was good work.
I'm thinking about cleaning up
that storm shelter out back.
Curtls?
- Curtls, how you doing, bud?
- Hey, Doc.
- How's my girl?
- She's good.
That's good to hear.
Tllt your head back for me.
I don't have a cold.
- Dld she get that down wrong?
- No, I Just told her that.
So what's the problem?
I've been having...
I've been having some trouble sleeping.
I was hoping
you could give me something for It.
How long's this been going on?
About four nights now.
You're not sleeping at all?
Well, some, but real restless.
Well, lthlnk four nights
Is a little too soon to tell.
My advice would be to not eat
or drink anything after 0:00 at night.
Cut back on any alcoholic drinks,
tobacco, eaffelne.
Get some dally exercise.
Well, I think...
- I think I might need to try some medlcetlon.
- Why do you say that?
The reason I've been having trouble sleeping
ls these dreams I've been having.
I didn't think It was anything at ﬁrst,
but then the other day I woke up
and the bed was wet.
- You urlnated In your bed?
- Yeah.
Couple days before that,
I had a dream that my dog attacked me
and It took all day
for the pain In my arm to go away.
You been out to see your mother lately?
It's been about a month.
Okay.
Okay. This Is a prescription
for a pretty mlld sedative.
It's non-habit formlng,
but I'm only giving you enough
for a few days anyway.
Take It and see If It helps. In the meantime,
this Is the number of a good friend of mine
In Columbus. He's a psychiatrist.
It's a drive, but he's the best I know.
Okay.
I'll give him a sell
and let him know you'll be down to see him.
All right.
- Hey, Dewart.
- What you say, Curtls?
Not much.
They want us
to get a pilot hole drilled by lunch.
I ﬁgure worse comes to worse,
we een eat on the rig.
Yeah, we'll get It done. Weekend all right?
Yeah. Same old shit.
No. No, I need the name of the specialist
whose dlagnosls you'll accept.
No. Look It, I've told you this twice. Please.
Just get me the name
andlor the approval code.
Okay.
All right. And the phone? All right.
Great. Well, thank you very much.
All right, this Is the name
and the phone number of the specialist
who the Insurance company approves of.
Just sell and make an appointment.
Now If this doctor signs off,
you should have the Implant procedure
fully covered.
I'm sorry It took so long.
Can I give you a hug?
It's ﬁne. It's ﬁne.
You know, your husband's company actually
has very good Insurance when It kicks In.
Not a lot of Jobs offer pollcles half as good.
You're very lucky.
That's okay. We have your Insurance on ﬁle.
- That'll be $41.64.
- What's the co-pay?
That Is your co-pay.
Hey.
I love you.
I love you too.
Green? How about a red?
It was like talking to a sane person for once.
She made one phone eell. That's It.
I've been trying that 000 number
for weeks. You.
It's great. It's great.
Hey, Hannah.
Are you excited?
We're gonna get you some help.
How do you say, slgn, 'exclted'?
Like this.
Excited? Yeah?
All right. What've we got here?
I got to do you.
Honey, look at this one.
It's a 2-1, and It sits directly on the beach.
Wouldn't that be great? We wouldn't have
to worry about Hannah crosslng trafﬂc.
- What's the rent?
$000 a week.
That sounds real nice.
You sleep well?
Yeah. I did.
You look like you're feeling better.
You want me to come there and do It for you?
Jesus.
Hey, how much food you think you'd need
to live on for a week?
- What do you mean?
- I mean to stay alive.
What do you think you'd need?
- Not a lot.
- Yeah? You think?
I don't know.
You hear about people living for days
all the time off bark and melted snow.
I've never heard of that.
Shit, I don't know. You asked the question.
It's on there.
It's on. Come on.
Damn It.
What?
It sounds like thunder.
What sounds like thunder?
What's the matter with you, Curtls?
Curtls?
Where you going? Curtis, where you going?
- Curtls.
- Hey, Mom.
- Come In.
- Sure.
I'm gonna get some water.
You want some?
Isn't she lovely?
- Mom?
- Yes?
I need to ask you something.
Do you remember what year
we brought you up here?
To the ﬁrst place.
It was '00.
Yes. Beeause Kyle was going to be a senior.
- l was 10.
- Yes.
Can you remember what happened
before you got diagnosed?
- What do you mean?
- I mean...
I Just want to know how It all started.
Before you had to leave.
I don't know.
I remember It was a real stressful tlme.
Your father was gone a lot,
and I couldn't handle things on my own.
Did you ever have any
dreams?
lee, bad dreams?
No. Nothing like that.
There was always...
There was always a panic
that took hold of me.
I thought people were watching me
and listening to me.
It's all right. It's ﬁne.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah. I'm ﬁne.
May I have the number
for Dr. George Shannan?
Thanks.
Hi, Is Dr. Shannan there?
May I speak with him?
This Is Curtis LaForche.
Hey, Doc.
Yeah, sorry... Sorry to sell you at home.
IJust... I don't think I een make It
to Columbus to see that psychiatrist.
Yeah, It's Just too far.
Is there somewhere loeel
you could send me?
Hey.
Sorry I woke you up.
It's okay.
Where you been?
I went to see Mom.
Is she okay?
Yeah. I Just wanted to check up on her.
You should've told me,
we would have gone with you.
No, that's okay.
Come to bed.
lwlll In a bit.
Well, you've kept up with the payments
on the house.
We've been good about that.
I gotta tell you, Curtis, banks aren't
loanlng money the way they used to.
We've got you a loan today,
but the Interest rates are variable.
We have to tie It to your house.
That's ﬁne.
Curtis, I've known you a long time.
Financed your house for you, two vehicles.
I'm telling you,
this Is a risky loan you're taking.
I need the money, John.
Okay.
- Hey.
Sorry I left you yesterday.
- Jlm same by. I covered for you.
- Thanks.
- I need your help with the depth charts.
- Sure.
Fucklng Nat put me In charge
of frying oysters for that Lions Club supper.
You need another burner?
Yeah, If you still got yours, I could use It.
Hey, you think you could help me
with something?
What do you need?
I'm gonna build out the tornado shelter
In my backyard. I could use some help.
The hell you wanna do that for?
Just needs to be done.
What do you need?
I ﬁgure I'll do It on a Saturday,
borrow some equipment from work.
- You sure about that?
- Yeah, ljust need a backhoe, a hauler.
I'll rent the rest.
- Yeah. Whatever. I'll help.
- Thanks.
- You all right, man?
- What do you mean?
I Just don't wanna see you fuck up.
I'm not.
Come In.
- Have a seat. I'm Kendra.
- Curtls.
Okay.
I'm gonna start
by asking you some questions.
Okay. I already answered
all the questions on the form.
Yeah, I know. I looked at them,
but I need to get a proﬁle started on you.
nght. Well...
Out of the ﬁve posslble symptoms
needed to be diagnosed with schizophrenia,
disorganized behavior
and the negative symptoms,
I've had two.
So, I took this quiz In the back of the book.
I scored a ﬁve out of a possible 20.
Schlzophrenla starts at 12. So...
They say It might be
a brief psychotic disorder.
Yeah. Whatever It Is,
I need to know what to do
or what to get on
to get this thing under control.
Look. I'm a counselor.
Certlﬂed, but I'm not a psychiatrist.
I een't prescrlbe anything to you.
I een talk to you,
I een recommend where to send you,
but that's It.
Now, that said, If you want to talk, I'll llsten.
For a lot of people, that's a good start.
Now you said here
that your mother was diagnosed
with paranoid schlzophrenla In her 00s.
And you're at 05.
You wanna talk about that?
Yeah, I don't know my mother's symptoms.
lwasjust 10.
My brother was 11. And...
I don't know. She Just left me In the ear
In the parking lot
at the grocery store one day.
And she didn't come back.
And then they found her a week later
eating trash out of a dumpster
In Northern Kentucky.
My dad had to put her
In the State Hospital In Columbus.
And she's been In assisted living ever since.
Yep.
My dad raised me.
He died last April.
So tell me about these dreams.
I don't know what our schedule will be, but...
That's all right.
But I really do think you should
continue with the sign language.
And any additional therapies
that kids need for the cochlear Implant.
- Absolutely.
- Okay.
- Good night.