Bitch!
You're not aware of what your
officers have done?
How dare you to treat me, the Chief
of the Royal Guards, like a soldier?
Besides, this affair is
none of your concern.
Do you mean Her Majesty
ordered Jaunbie to be killed?
- I did not say that!
- Then, did you?
I know Jaunbie's father was a rebel.
You might fool Her Majesty
with your fake loyalty
but I know your dark intentions.
It terribly worries me that you're
in Her Majesty's good graces.
General!
Did you order Jaunbie to be killed?
What are you talking about?
One of your Royal Guards
tried to kill her.
I don't understand.
Your Majesty, you have no
connection with this incident?
Your anger soars to the skies.
- Put down your sword!
- You have or you have not?
How dare you to march in here
with a sword in your hand?
Throw away your sword!
Get her!
Close the gate!
That way!
Kill her!
Away with you.
So...
did you find out whose doing?
Please punish me for my disloyalty.
I could punish you for treason.
However, I could understand the
circumstances that you're under.
Keep your mind at ease and rise.
Your Majesty.
I've thought about you every moment.
Biharang.
Who are you?
Where is Biharang?
Biharang!
Guards!
Did you not hear me?
Your people do not change
even after 1000 years.
Trying to take away the only
thing that is left!
Starting with you, I'll eliminate
every living thing on this land.
The dead does not belong in a living
body! Come out of her at once!
Kill her!
Jaunbie...
She's no longer Jaunbie!
Talwi!
The Great Emperor of Shilla,
with this Sacred Sword, may
the evil spirit be defeated!
Biharang!
Talwi!
General!
Jaunbie!
- What are you doing?
- Put away your sword.
- General, she's the evil spirit!
- Talwi!
She's not Jaunbie.
If we don't kill her now, we
cannot destroy the evil spirit.
She's Jaunbie.
I can tell by the way
she looks at me.
- General!
- Believe me this once.
We don't have much time.
How can she possibly resist the
monstrous power of the evil spirit?
She's over there!
Talwi!
Get her!
Get him!
That deceitful peasant girl must've
approached Biharang
to get to you, Your Majesty.
We mustn't jump to conclusions.
However, since Biharang
protected her,
perhaps, they planned this together.
Then they are rebels! We must
order them be caught and be killed.
First, we must find their hideout.
What happened with Talwi?
He's not saying a word.
Your Majesty, since this is a critical
time, we should hold a trial.
A trial?
Why don't you talk? You shouldn't
be enduring all these sufferings.
It's not even your fault.
I did not fulfill my duty of
serving my general.
So, kill me.
Master!
I can't believe you sucked out the
poison from his wound.
It will protect you.
My promise of protecting
the 1000 year sovereignty
was a futile promise.
I couldn't even protect you...
Jaunbie.
General.
I've been having nightmares.
Do not be worried.
You'll feel better when you
get some sleep.
Drink.
I also hope for the safety
of Gen. Biharang.
I greatly honor your loyalty to your
general. However,
what if
Jaunbie truly is the evil spirit?
What if Biharang has been
bewitched by the evil spirit?
What if all was a devious
plan of the evil spirit?
It could've been its evil plan to
bewitch Biharang from the beginning.
It's sad.
Who would help him
in his time of troubles?
Talwi will lead us. Hurry.
Yes, Your Majesty.
She just fell asleep.
Tonight, a bloody moon that holds
the hatred of 1000 years, will rise.
When the darkness hides the moon,
the evil spirit will regain
its full strength.
Then, even the Sacred Sword
will be powerless.
Then what about Jaunbie?
If you could keep her away from the
moon, you might be able to save her.
Since her desire to be
with you is so great.
If I can't keep her away, then what
would happen to her?
She'll be nothing but an empty shell.
It would be Jaunbie outside, but
she'll be Auta inside.
We must sacrifice one life
to save millions.
Jaunbie!
I'm scared.
Jaunbie! Jaunbie!
It's too late for me. You must
go and save the General.
He's at the lake.
Hurry!
Let's go!
General BANG has left the palace
to kill the evil spirit.
- Did he bring any men with him?
- Only about 100 men.
And Her Majesty followed
him in secrecy.
Lead the way. I'll meet with
Biharang personally.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Jaunbie! Jaunbie!
You must fight it off!
Jaunbie!
Jaunbie! Jaunbie!
General...
If I can't be who I was again,
I want you to kill me yourself.
Jaunbie! Jaunbie! You must fight!
Jaunbie!
Jaunbie! Jaunbie! Please!
Jaunbie! Jaunbie!
Jaunbie!
Your Majesty, I'll go look first.
Jaunbie! Jaunbie!
Jaunbie! Jaunbie! Jaunbie!
Jaunbie!
General...
Master! Are you ok?
It's all over.
The evil spirit will take over
the Kingdom of Shilla.
- General!
- Biharang!
Here is the mighty general.
Where did you hide her?
I can defeat the evil spirit.
Just give me more time.
Draw!
I'll kill anyone
who gets in my way.
Stop!
General BANG! Whose order
were you following
when it was not I who ordered
you to shoot Biharang?
Withdraw!
Biharang!
Your Majesty, I cannot bear to
watch this with my own eyes.
Destroying your own country for
a shallow passion.
You're no different from
a bitch in heat.
How dare you to plot treason!
General BANG!
This is Her Majesty. Put down
your swords.
I pity your girl. She should've died
when she was supposed to.
It was YOU!
General BANG!
What are you waiting for?
Kill them all!
Your Majesty!
Is there any way we can destroy
the evil spirit?
It's hatred is too great
for us to bear.
So the 1000 year sovereign of
Shilla must end here?
How about the Sacred Sword?
The one that the Great Emperor used
to seal off the evil spirit.
It no longer has any power.
If not the Sacred Sword...
Then, can I do nothing but just
watch my kingdom fall apart?
Jaunbie.
Jaunbie!
It's me!
Please come back.
Please.
I do not know how great
your hatred is,
but I'll take the blame for all.
Let go of Jaunbi.
Take me instead! Take me!
General!
Talwi!
Talwi! Talwi!
It is not her.
Let her rest... in peace...
Talwi! Talwi!
Talwi!
If it was a sin for a queen of
one country to love a man,
then take me instead.
My people are innocent.
Stab her heart!
General.
Jaunbie.
Thank you.
Biharang!
6 month after Queen Chinsong left
the throne to her nephew Yoh,
she died in The North Palace.
38 years later,
the thousand year old
history of Shilla came to an end.