Is this the Roxy Nightclub?
It was, they pulled it down years ago
Him, in the white shirt
Bastard! I'll teach you
to grope girls on the subway!
Jerk! I was groped!
Why didn't you come when I called?
Stop it, you're as bad as him!
What's your name?
Brother Chai!
I'm on your case, you little fart!
Been busy?
Forgotten the sound of my voice?
Brother Chai... give me a break
I promise I'll pay,
but right now I'm broke
I'm freelance, I'm doing my best
Sure you are! Tell you what...
You can have a discount
if you pay me now, okay?
Brother Chai, I...
I really am broke! How can I pay you?
I'll pay you back in six installments,
I promise!
One payment a month, okay?
Is that a joke?
You said the same last time!
And what about the other debts
you said you'd cover?
Your mother, Dee Dee,
Candy, May and Cat's?
If you're broke,
we'll have to take one hand instead
Brother, you're real tough!
Which gang are you with?
Who the hell are you?
You want to hear my triad password?
Get him!
What? You think I'm beneath you?
Calm down, calm down
We can talk it over, no hassle
I was just teasing him,
what's your name?
That's my business, you scumbag!
See if your boss knows Mountain Leopard
You know? As in the mountain cat?
Fine, I'll remember you...
Move!
Kiddo!
You'll pay for this!
Now I'm in deep shit
Uncle... where are you from?
When I...
Never mind, why are you following me?
You want to report me
for what happened in the bookstore?
I need help to kill someone... Interested?
Uncle, stop kidding
Aren't you getting on
a bit to be a hitman?
Who do you want killed?
I'll tell you later
You know somewhere I can lie low?
Hey, what's your name?
They call me Smokey
I'll carry your things
Thanks
Uncle Wah...
I know, mixed,
extra sesame oil and one to go
- Has your ma remembered yet?
- No.
Try it
Haven't had these for ages
Have you been abroad?
The way you talk is... odd
Odd?
Old-fashioned!
It'll come back!
Sure
Yes, I'm just back...
Been in Brazil for 30 years
Brazil? Where the girls dance
in feathers all day?
Famous for soccer too
Did you have a girlfriend?
Scored some goals too
By the way, what do you do?
Checking up on me?
Just asking, you don't have to say
I sell pirated CDs, have the odd fight...
Play a bit of snooker and find johns
for my friends at night! Get it?
Sure, I used to be much the same
What's your name?
I just told you!
I mean your real name
Marlboro
That rings a bell...
Stay here, I have to deliver something
Mister, come on in!
- Nice, legal-age girls!
- No.
Upstairs you can have fun... a drink,
a smoke, a dance...
- No...
- Come on...
Dee Dee!
Hey, I was only joking!
Two can play at that game
Cool it, I won't do it again!
Really?
You know why I've stuck with you
all this time?
Because you didn't treat me
like a hooker!
I know, I really didn't mean it
I was joking, I won't do it again
Go joke with your mother!
Don't bring my mother into it...
Why is she so pissed off?
I made fun of her
She's a hooker?
Make fun of a hooker
and you deserve what you get
What's with your hair?
You live alone? What's all this stuff?
My ma lives here too,
but she isn't here much
We rent storage space
to the stallholders downstairs
So when does it happen?
What?
Don't you want to kill someone?
The police are right opposite!
Keep your voice down!
Hide in plain sight!
Are you really a killer?
What are you shooting?
Nothing, I'm watching
for jay-walking cops
If I catch one, I'll sell it to TV
Who made the bed?
Who are you after?
- Nine Dragons.
- Nine Dragons?
We should go shopping today
For what? I know where to buy a gun
Clothes! Come on
You're going out like that?
Just checking for danger first
So who's this Nine Dragons?
He was notorious
in Yaumatei 30 years ago
We were bitter rivals, evenly matched
30 years ago?
How do you expect me to find him?
He might be dead by now!
Maybe your 'brothers' can help
Ask them where he is and what he's doing
But don't let on that Mountain Leopard
is back in Hong Kong!
If he's not dead,
he'll be around your age
You think he'll come for you?
What's your beef with this guy anyway?
He stole my woman
Two oldsters fighting over a girl?
That's why you want him shot?
He also betrayed his boss
and cheated his 'brothers'
He stole money,
stole his boss's woman... you want more?
I get it
I can see you're a righteous guy
How long have you been at this game?
Who's your boss?
You could say I was born into it
Oh, I took you for somebody with rank!
I thought you were in this big time
You seemed so brave last night
No big deal
Hookers are people too
Right, hookers are people too
Come on
Let me see!
Ma, I'll be making big money soon
We can move somewhere better
Hold it!
Never mind, you can go
Crazy!
Huh, you couldn't be my father
with a face like that!
Let's move, okay?
Where to?
That the hell are you doing?
Taking a dump?
Come on, can we go?
Hi, Smokey
On the job early today?
- Yes.
- Okay, let's go.
Don't I look younger now?
Why are you dressed like that?
Uncle, we're only looking for leads
What if I run into my old girlfriend?
Come on, Smokey
Mister, full service is only $800
Who's first?
We're looking for Nine Dragons
It was really something!
Four of them,
waving choppers, cornered me
Believe me, those were big choppers!
But I wasn't scared
I could see
one of the bastards was trembling...
Those guys are
old enough to be my father
They dye their hair, but they're past it
All they can do is brag
That guy was bleeding from a head-wound
Didn't know where he was!
Be he still came for me with his chopper
So I leapt in the air...
...and gave him a side-kick
Believe me,
I may have kicked him too hard...
The bastard flew in the air...
...right over a truck,
and hit the ground out cold!
There were four of them, you said.
What about the other three?
They stood around watching?
I need a pee, I'll tell you afterwards
Come on, you can't take a pee now
Those kids are just street-punks
Small-time, but full of themselves
Boss...
What is El Nino?
You jerk, you don't even know that?
El Nino is... a big really deal!
It pours with rain, there are hurricanes
Floods, earthquakes...
When El Nino shows up, everyone runs!
You're so dumb, you really are
Boss, you're just like El Nino!
Sure I am
Stop talking and eat!
That bastard son-of-a-bitch!
Dares make trouble in my place?
- Haven't you heard?
- Yes...
That's Third Sister,
she runs these three districts
Doesn't he know we run this joint?
Idiot!
Didn't you tell all the bosses
we turned the sauna into a bookstore?
Yes, exactly as you said
And each gang got 100 discount vouchers
Either that guy meant
to stir up trouble...
...or he's an ignorant jerk
Whichever it is...
...find him for me
Yes, Third Sister
This is a good book,
order 100 copies for me
Yes, ma'am
Can we get the writer in to sign copies?
She's dead
Who'd have thought
she would die so young
She was 90
Bing Xin
Right, Bing Xin
- Bing Xin...
- Yes, Bing Xin.
Bing Xin wrote it?
No mistake, Bing Xin
Right
We're looked everywhere
Want to try someplace else?
Over there...
I want to go back
- It's early...
- I want to go back.
Aren't you feeling well?
It's not even dark yet
and you want to go back!
But you're up at 3
to practice your kung-fu
Is that how killers live in Brazil?
Do all kids in Hong Kong
ask so many questions?
Let's get this straight:
You're not my boss
I thought you were a killer,
so I agreed to help you
I want to make a name for myself
I won't stay a nobody all my life!
But I don't know...
you don't seem like a killer at all
This is a critical time
of day for killers
Can't see clearly in this light
So what?
You might kill the wrong guy!
Most killers go home around this time
Kill which wrong guy?
You haven't found the right guy yet!
Why carry the gun if you're so worried?
There's only one bullet in it anyway
You've been looking through my things?
Give me a break, killer!
A real hitman nowadays uses...
...a Gow 26, a Mark 25 or even a USP
Show some respect, I have many guns!
In Brazil, even beggars have guns!
A hitman relies on a bullet, not a gun
And on his own resolve!
How many people have you killed?
In a year? Or in a month?
Where's my toupee?
Have you hidden it?
I've told you not to touch my things!
I'm going to buy some cigs
I was just talking
You don't have to take it so hard!
But you have plenty of hair,
why take my toupee?
Why did you take my toupee?
Sister Ha,
ask your girls to help find someone
It's a man in his fifties...
...with nine dragon tattoos
- Nine dragons?
- Right.
No-one I've seen... try asking them
No, don't know him
Sometimes they come
before they're undressed
"If I hadn't met you,
where would I be now?"
"Would my days be empty,
my life be dull?"
"If I hadn't met you,
where would I be now?"
Who's he?
Must be a Teresa Teng fan
Uncle, you've sung that song
so many times
Play some games, okay?
Garfield... Paper!
Garfield...
You lose! Drink!
- Garfield... Paper!
- Garfield... Bite!
- Drink!
Garfield... Paper!
Garfield... Bite!
Drink! Your turn!
You lose, drink up!
- Drink!
- You lost, drink!
I only win this
Look who's here!
What do you want?
Nothing
Last time you pointed a gun at me,
I should return the compliment
Let's sit down and talk
We can settle this like 'brothers'
If my friend has offended you...
...he can compensate you
and throw a banquet for you
Everybody shakes hands and forgets it
Crap!
I've just got back from LA
I just came back from Brazil!
You have balls
You really do
You're Mountain Leopard?
Get down and show me how you leap
On the ground... show me!
What's a that? A cat could do better!
Go!
- Go!
- After them!
That way.
These bastards don't know
the underworld code!
They attack me without knowing who I am!
What do bosses teach
their kids these days?
Before, we always spelled out
our backgrounds before fighting
He was right, you looked like a cat
Those girls made me
play that Garfield game
So I had Garfield on the brain
I could've beaten them
if I hadn't been drinking
Okay, thanks
Happy birthday!
Er... yes, sure I got you a present
It's a very big
It's on its way now
Bye
Is it too much to give someone
a piano as a birthday present?
Well, it's too late to buy a tank! Push!
It's starting to rain! Hurry!
- Let's shelter.
- Sure.
I'm drenched.
What's up?
It won't stop raining for some time
Dry my back for me, please
You'll catch cold
That's a really big leopard
This is a really big present
Thank you
Let's have a smoke
You're in love with that Dee Dee?
No, we just grew up together
Our mothers were both hookers
But her ma died of
breast cancer last year
That's why she hangs out with me
Her ma was once the most famous hooker
in Temple Street
Do you remember her?
They called her 'Big Tits'
Rings a bell
And your mother?
My ma...
She's still in Temple Street every day,
looking for my dad
Your dad is missing?
One day, my dad
went to Temple Street to get laid
He was through
before Ma finished one cigarette
But she still got pregnant
So that's why they call you 'Smokey'!
She was smoking,
so she didn't see dad's face that well
So she goes there every day,
hoping to spot him passing by
So far, he's never shown up
What's that half-cigarette?
My girlfriend gave it to me
I've kept it so long
Who was this unforgettable woman?
She's very pretty
I've seen many women in Brazil...
...but hers is the only face
which stays with me
Impossible!
You don't believe me?
She's the prettiest girl I've ever seen
Mind you, at that time...
...I wasn't bad myself
"Temple Street"
You can't have two tigers
on one mountain
We were bound to clash eventually
Neither of us wanted to lose face
It finally happened
one evening in the Roxy Nightclub
Is she staring at you or me?
Me
No, it's me
It's definitely me
What makes you so sure?
Her eyes, I can tell
It's her eyes that tell me it's me!
It's different
Why?
Because I'm also staring straight at her
And you're not
Go ask her if you want
No need
There'd be no doubt about it...
...if only one of us was here
Finally, Nine Dragons lost
I went up to her and asked...
Were you looking at me or him?
I looked at you
while I smoked this cigarette
But it's about to burn out
I won't let it
But Nine Dragons didn't accept defeat
He shot me in the back!
While I was out cold,
he dumped me on a ship
And I woke up in Brazil
I've been there for 30 years!
So Nine Dragons stole your woman?
I gotta find him
Gotta chop off his ears and fingers,
then finish him off
But she wasn't really your woman, though
How so?
You just saw her briefly,
you don't even know her name!
You didn't kiss her!
How can she be your woman?
Don't say that!
When you look at a woman,
and her eyes say "yes"
Then she is
You call that love? No way!
If so, I have lots of women!
If you woke tomorrow
remembering only one thing...
...would it be a woman's face?
Which woman?
All I remember is her face
Good, at least you know
what she looks like!
But even if Nine Dragons
gives her back to you...
...she must be quite old by now
Will you still recognise her?
I know, what I most want
to remember is my dad's face
Ma can't remember it at all
My place is over there!
Just checking that those punks have gone
This way?
This way
Where's the salt?
On the shelf, salt on the left,
sugar on the right
Did you catch a cop jaywalking?
No, just you putting sugar in the stew
Never mind, tastes better with sugar
You can cook! And there's steaks...
I was a cook for years in Brazil.
Stop that!
You were just a cook?
It was a cover for my real identity
For 30 years? Wasn't it boring?
No girlfriends?
Girlfriends? No...
Why not?
Didn't have time
Other things on my mind
And when I felt like having a girl,
I couldn't find one
Too busy... no time
Didn't give it much thought
As time went by, I forgot all about it
I did have one good friend,
called Ronaldo
Ronaldo?
The soccer player?
He was my neighbour,
I was close to his dad
We hung out together
Is this more of your boasting? Hang on...
I'll record this, say it again
What's strange about it?
He lived next door to my restaurant
He kicked a ball around with me
after school, that's all
He has an amazing name...
Ronaldo Luiz Nazario de Lima
It's as long as Pele's real name:
24 letters!
That's enough, stop it!
I need this footage...
...for next time
you say never exaggerate
You think I'm sick?
Looks like it
Look, Ma, recognise this guy?
Look carefully
Why are you with this short guy again?
Look up there
Did you come to this brothel
18 years ago?
I was in Brazil 18 years ago
Weren't you that butcher from Yaumatei?
Believe me...
I was tops in the Thirteen Gang
Chi Hung will confirm it
One time, all of us went to a brothel
in Temple Street
And we wanted to eat afterwards
When we got to Parker's Street...
...where the Washington Theatre
used to be...
It's a McDonald's now
...a hundred men showed up with choppers!
They attacked us without warning!
I was smart
I ran...
...as fast as I could...
...to Yaumatei Police Station
Reported to the police
The police leapt into action
And rescued my 'brothers'
My action saved the whole gang
Brother Kei,
who dared to attack you guys?
Jealous rival gangs, of course
Ever heard of a guy
known as Nine Dragons?
I remember Eight Dragons...
Eight Dragons? That's a joke!
You know Nine Dragons?
Sure I do!
We all knew him
He had nine dragons tattooed on his back
Who are you want?
Smokey... I'm Dee Dee
Dee Dee?
Smokey's girlfriend...
I've seen you before
You may be Smokey's girlfriend,
but I don't think we've met
Anyhow, he's out right now
I came to thank him for the piano
That's okay, I helped him steal it
Garfield... Paw!
Garfield... Bite! Garfield...
Garfield... Bite!
Garfield... Paw! ...Bite!
I've found Nine Dragons!
Is one bullet enough?
He's a gang boss, well-protected
Do I look better in a suit?
Brother Leopard...
how shall we tackle him?
We have to make a plan
First, check if they're all men
Before anything else,
I have to find out where my woman is
Then I...
Shall we go in together or separately?
Are you scared?
You can still back out
My bag is stuffed with US dollars
You go back first
Brother Leopard...
So many people! Something's going on...
Looks like a rumble
What's going on?
Dunno, the boss told us to come
What's happening?
Dunno, Blondie sent for me
Boss, you wanted us here
Oh... right...
What's going on?
The boss told me to come
- You?
- I came with them.
Damn it, what's going on?
- What's going on?
- What...?
Shooting stars!
There's another!
And over there!
Don't let me get chopped tonight!
Chop him!
Smokey, can you see Nine Dragons?
I think he's gone
It's fate
Did you make a wish?
Yeah, did you?
Me too
What was yours?
You first
I just wished my ma
would remember dad's face
Then she wouldn't need
to stand in the street all day
And you?
I wished to...
...remember my woman's face
for the rest of my life
What's the point of that?
It's up to you!
Who can stop you remembering?
You're sure Nine Dragons comes here?
I was tipped off
He watched those shooting stars
with the boss of this sauna
I think he's often here
Can you trust that tip?
We'll soon know
I dreamt of my dad last night
So your wish worked, huh?
What's he like?
Not too tall, but well-built
Looks impressive
you can see right away
that he's righteous
I saw him finishing off some bad guys...
a real hero
That tough?
What does he look like?
Dunno
- No face?
- No face
Not too tall, but strong and righteous
And faceless
And he guns down baddies
Sound more like a fantasy
than a hero to me!
No, in my dream
he was just a regular guy
Regular, but no face.
I'm not boasting about him...
That's just how he was
Did he look like him?
- No.
- The other one.
This guy coming up now?
No!
That guy, then?
Are you kidding?
Have a smoke,
and keep watching for Nine Dragons
It's dark, let's call it a day
It's not even dusk yet!
Not the sky, it's smoke
You can check
Come to see
Let's go home
You dared to chop someone in our shop,
you little bastard?
And still act cocky?
I really didn't know
it was Third Sister's place
You didn't?
Ears wide shut, huh?
How dare you make trouble here?
Drag the police in and they'll think
we're running a brothel here
How could we survive then?
Enough of this, which hand
did you use to chop that guy?
- Get me a chopper!
- No! Don't!
You're a bold one
Some guy groped a hooker
and you chopped off his hand
She was only a hooker
I'm sorry I messed up your place,
Third Sister! Really!
Please let me off!
What was so special about the girl?
Describe her!
I don't remember, Third Sister
Please don't toy with me!
But I want to toy with you!
You'll never leave here
if you don't tell me!
Look, I have so many books here
Find one which helps you describe her
Lock up!
Can you read?
That's good
"TRIADS: THE TRUE STORY"
"NINE DRAGONS VERSUS
MOUNTAIN LEOPARD"
Found something?
Read it aloud
"She... has delicate white skin
as soft as soap..."
"Her ripe melon breasts are too
lare to grasp..."
"Her nipples are so pink..."
"Her butt is tight,
firm and shapely"
"The bill... is $360..."
"But she's worth every penny!
Watch for her in Portland Street"
"She's number XX
at the Golden... Nightclub"
Bring me that book
"PORNO GUIDE:
THE FLOWER OF PORTLAND STREET"
Let him go
Let him go?
Yes
Thank you, Third Sister!
He's bold, but he has good taste!
Bring in the writer for a signing!
Yes
"The Flower of Portland Street"!
Maybe it's me?
Brother Wah, is it true?
Why are you asking?
Leopard has come back
He dares to come back?
He wants revenge on Nine Dragons
Revenge? For what?
Nine Dragons beat him,
but he wouldn't accept defeat
He was disloyal to his boss,
stole money from his 'brothers'
This idiot dares to come back?
Brother Wah, I don't get it
They were both small-time punks
They weren't bosses?
Bosses?
Mountain Leopard did nothing but boast
They were both butchers in the market
One sold pork, one sold beef...
They were rivals
The night the Roxy opened...
...they both came itching for a fight
It's said they fought over a bar-girl
But any excuse would have done
Leopard couldn't fight at all
Isn't he a kung-fu master?
Him? He don't know shit!
Get off me!
I don't know why,
but someone blew some smoke in the air...
...and Leopard was galvanised!
A real fierce fight,
like something from a movie!
Leopard was like a new man!
But Nine Dragons finally won
You'll never beat me, Fatso!
The bastard couldn't take it,
he shot Nine Dragons in the back
I tried to stop him
I had my arm around Nine Dragons,
that's why I'm this way now
So that's why he fled to Brazil?
He thought he'd killed me,
so he ran away
Everyone there swore
they'd get that bastard
And Nine Dragons?
The boss promoted him
He became a big shot
He's now the leader
of the Hung Ying triad
Where is he now?
In hospital, he's in a coma
How come?
That night of the shooting stars...
we all went to a bar
He went for cigarettes...
...and he was knocked down by a car
I have to go
Come by anytime
Oh yes... did that bar-girl
stay with Nine Dragons after that?
No
I heard she went to
the Dragon & Phoenix Nightclub
Thank you
This girl is really pretty
Dee Dee's been waiting for you
I'm not the only one in your heart!
She was bored, so I put on your tapes
She says that woman cop once nabbed you,
is that right?
You fancy her, but you're afraid
she'd arrest you... right?
Piss off!
Piss off, I won't help you any more
Come on, own up to fancying her!
Don't behave like a dog!
Me?!
Who shot a guy in the back
after being beaten? You're the dog!
You found Nine Dragons?
You were just a market butcher!
Losing a fight is okay,
but you ran away...
...thinking you'd killed someone!
Now you dare come back
and talk about honour!
Played the victim to win my sympathy!
Get out!
And you have the gall
to ask me to kill Nine Dragons!
You're the lowest of the low
Take me to him,
I have to see Nine Dragons!
You don't dare shoot me?
You, with your long record?
You betrayed your boss, stole money...
Cheated your friends,
stole a guy's mistress...
I never stole anyone's mistress, never!
Probably not, you're such a worm!
Can you even remember what you did?
Can you remember what you ate last week?
There's so much to remember,
stay with the good things!
What good things are those?
You just boast about everything!
What's good about you?
Stuck on a woman you don't even know!
I've dreamed of her
every night for years
Of course I know her!
You had no relationship!
Thank God you're not my father
If you were,
I'd be ashamed to show my face!
Take me to see him! I have no time left!
I'm a dog, I'll shoot you!
You still dare to see him?
Is he the one?
Nine Dragons
Nine Dragons...
It's Leopard... Can you hear me?
Nine Dragons!
I must ask you a favour
Tell me, where is she?
That bar-girl, I must see her!
Please tell me, I must see her!
Nine Dragons!
I have a gun!
Tell me where she is!
Quiet! This is a hospital!
Are you a relative?
Good, help me wash him
Take off his shirt
Nurse, will he ever come round?
When he recognises you, you'll know
Nine Dragons, do you recognise me?
Nine Dragons...
You know this girl? Look!
You recognise her?
I must remember this!
Mister...
Are you alright? Need a doctor?
Keep the map safe, Uncle!
Don't go out without it!
This is my place! You live over there!
Smokey, your dad was a cop!
What?
I remember now, he was a cop
My dad was a cop!
I really am sick
I have Alzheimer's
Soon I'll forget everything
I used to believe...
...I'd remember what I'd lost
for the rest of my life
Then I realised God
was playing a cruel joke
"You think you can choose
what to remember?"
What could I do?
I came back...
...not to revenge myself
on Nine Dragons...
...but to see her one last time
While I can still remember
Because...
...she's the most beautiful woman
I've ever seen
I asked for your help
because I could see you were a good guy
You helped out a hooker!
I'd never have done that
All I've ever done really is boast
So I hope...
...that while I still
remember this woman...
...I can end my life
I never killed anyone else,
at least I can kill myself
Then I'll be able
to carry her memory to the grave
My dollar savings are in my bag
They're for you
If you ever see my woman...
...please ask her name for me
Please...
I've found your woman!
What do you want?
Nothing, just hand over that guy
All the bosses know he's back in town
Everyone wants to see him
We haven't time now
No time?
What's the time now?
No watch
See? Time's not an issue! Get him!
Move, your woman is there!
Get them!
Stop! Stay there!
Shit! Get them!
This way!
Over there!
Stop!
Hey, this way!
Your woman is up there, come on!
You want to dance?
Stop the car!
How dare you
make trouble in my territory?
Sorry, Third Sister
I didn't know it was your patch
You didn't know? Where are you from?
You don't know your way around
and come on so tough?
Didn't your boss teach you anything?
I've tried my best to learn the rules
You've learned nothing!
This boy is under my protection!
- But the other one...
- I don't care who is him!
I'll be responsible for this, understand?
OK, no problem.
After all, we're all in the same game
When you have time, let's 'buddy up'
Boss, you said that wrong!
The one in the wrong
should do the red thing
Boss, it's a red pocket!
And invite the other to a banquet, right?
Goddamn buffoon!
What's your name?
Nam
Ah Nam...
I'm going to buy cigarettes
What is your name?
Ah Nam...
If you do that, you'll be arrested
Let me just finish this...
Old man...
You mustn't write there
You're defacing government property,
I can arrest you for that
Don't you know... who I am?
I'm Emperor of Yaumatei!
Sorry, Officer,
he doesn't know what he's doing
Let's go home!
Young man, wait...
I've seen you somewhere before
No...
You were in a gang
and now you do social work?
I look after Alzheimer's patients now
Good for you
First time I've seen you smile
How often have you seen me?
I've seen you on TV!
- You're on TV every day!
- No...
- I see you day and night.
- He...
- I meet you at last!
- Goodbye!
You've forgotten everything
except her face!
Where are all the US dollars?
I don't always... remember
When I do remember, I get lost
When I'm not lost, I'm too busy
And since I don't have time...
...I stop thinking about it
Then I forget
- I don't always remember.
- Go...
This is the latest map of Hong Kong
You point, I'll guide you there
It's not an atlas!
Stop fooling around!
Or I won't tell you stories
over dinner tonight
The story of Mountain Leopard
and Nine Dragons?
The one about playing soccer
with Ronaldo when I was young...
What about Beckham?
Beckham, He...
He plays rugby now
What?!