Fong, give me the Gold Buddha!
Right!
I forgot to tell you it's broken!
Now you tell me!
Master!
Fong, ride my staff
with the Buddha
Get it fixed
then come and save me
Master!
Fong!
Who is it?
Show yourself!
Leave quickly
the Priestess will be back soon!
Is it Lotus?
Follow my cloak!
You can't fight the Priestess
Don't look back
just move forward
Remember not to look back
Never come back!
It's getting light
Come and look, brand new weapons
Come and look
You're from Shaolin Temple?
Special price!
I have no money
Who shall I ask?
We use real iron
I'll think about it
For every $10 spent
a free horseshoe!
I'll give you two
I'm only here to beg for food
Beg for food? Get lost!
The world's corrupt
it's hard to find honesty
Let me help you!
Little monk, this place is bad
go elsewhere
Brother, you're a blacksmith
aren't you?
Not much longer
A decent man can't survive here
Will you do business with me?
I don't sell weapons
I don't want weapons
I need repairs
Have a look
You crazy?
If it's seen, you'll be dead
Put it away!
Please help me, it's an emergency!
Is this Buddha yours
or did you steal it?
Do I look like a thief?
Alright then, I'll do a good deed
You are so kind
Thank you
I thought you were going to
fix the Gold Buddha?
What Gold Buddha?
I didn't see any
You just threw it in there!
Leave me alone
I don't want your
business, scram!
Give it back...
I need it to save someone
Give my Gold Buddha back!
Help!
Give it back, or I'll kill you!
I'm being beaten up by a monk!
I don't want trouble
but he stole my Gold Buddha
Gold?
Not gold, just my Buddha
Search him, maybe he's
carrying more gold
I'm not, I'm not...
Get him!
What the hell?
It's the little monk!
It's you?
They stole something from me
Let's go!
Do you want me to help you?
Yes
Your Master owes me $10...
With this, it's a total of $15
They... they stole my Gold Buddha
Gold? Hang on...
Makes it more pricey
an extra 300
Plus a bowl of noodles
that's $320
But I have no money!
Good bye!
But my Master has some
That makes it okay!
I won't cheat you, let's go
Quickly!
Calm down!
It's them!
Brothers...
They're here
...that Gold Buddha is mine...
It should be returned
to it's rightful owner
Who says? Finders keepers
just because you've got a big sword
There are more of us!
Attack!
Let's melt it, goodbye Gold Buddha!
The Gold Buddha!
Oh no, it's melted!
You're amazing?
What's amazing?
Isn't it hot?
I wonder if it still has any powers?
Master is in real trouble now
Don't be negative
there's always a way
Little monk...
Let's go and get money
from your Master
But I haven't worked out
how to save him
That's easy
Hire me to help you save him
I'll give you a special
discount, 2 times $300
What do you think?
Forget it, no deal
Get out of my way!
I'll kill you!
Don't you want to
save your Master?
Of course I do
Then you have to pay me
But I have no money
Will you do it on credit?
Sure! It's a big deal
Wonton noodles!
Hey, you look like
you're starving
Have some noodles!
I told you I have no money
It's okay, I'll keep a tab
You'll have to pay up
when it reaches $1,000
Don't worry
As long as I'm around
it'll be fine
Hey, I don't even know your name
My name's Yin
That's quite a name
It was someone else's name
a high Priest
I begged him to take me
in as his student
But he said he didn't
like people
and refused to teach me!
You see, he's really stubborn!
Maybe if you ask again
he'll change his mind
He's dead now!
He was antisocial
so had no friends
Not even money to buy a coffin!
I've learnt my lesson
money before everything!
Why's that?
With money you can be
whatever you want!
What do you want to be?
A rich Yin!
And what do you want to be?
A good man!
A good man? Like my namesake?
Living a lonely life
You think good reaps good?
All good men end like that!
Someone's in trouble!
Don't worry, it's her!
Help, help! Open the door!
There's a ghost after me!
Hey, it's me, hey...
Ghost... help me
Hey, she's on our side...
it's me...
I've been waiting for you
it's Fong...
You can stop all
the dancing around...
Hey, stop it, stop it
Stop it?!
Who are you?
I'm so scared!
Come over here
I don't get it
Explain what you're doing
I can't, it's all a mistake
Something over there's moving!
Yes...
I know a ghost's after you
Then you must protect me!
I know you need protection
But we're not suited
to each other
Why?
I mean...
I don't mean you're not pretty...
To be honest...
Please don't get angry, but I...
I don't go for your type
that's all
I prefer a longer face
slight buck teeth
Maybe that much taller than me
If you know her
go and ask her to come here
Be careful not to
burn your clothes
You're so bad
You want a manage a trios?
You studious types are so naughty
Hey, come over here!
Lady, just hang on a moment
Wait here, I'm just going
over for a chat
What's the matter?
She's not right for you
but she is for me...
I don't want your money
I'll have her instead
No way!
What, you've undressed her?
No need to undress
let's do it like this!
Give that to me!
No, the clothes are
stuck to my hands!
I said no, I don't know her!
Another piece of clothing?
You don't know her
but you remove her underwear?!
Put it on, put it on!
I don't care, I want her!
I'm paying you instead
I don't want money!
I don't want money, I want her!
No!
Hey, what're you doing?
Hey, now about if I pay you?
Look, I'm giving
you a good deal!
Just stop it, it's been decided
I'm sorry Miss!
It's the first time
I've played this game!
I'm sorry to bother you...
Remember, long face
slight buck teeth when she smiles...
About 6 inches taller
than me, thanks!
What a waste
you didn't even ask her name
How can we find her again?
We're here to save my Master
Not do that sort of thing
If you want it so much
come back another time
Don't worry, Iwill!
Help! Help!
I'll go!
I'm going!
Help!
It's you!
Why are you back here?
I'm so glad
it's finally your turn!
These ghosts are beauties...
...she's even better
I almost mistook the
last girl for you!
Who was here?
Your sister!
Anymore sisters?
We'll be discovered here
let's go upstairs
Right
There's no one else!
Going to keep here for yourself?
Hey. What are you doing?
What?
What are you doing?
Pretending to be intimate!
Pretending to be intimate?
He's Yin, I've employed him
to help save Master
She's Lotus
Hey, what are you doing?
Pretending to be intimate
You don't have to as well
stand aside and watch!
I don't trust you
Damn monk, if you can why can't I?
Don't use business
as an excuse for pleasure
Do you think I want this?
I'm a reluctant victim too
We're not looking
very convincing
Let's get into bed!
Into bed?
If you won't do it, I will!
You won't go to be! I will!
How come I can't?
Come on
It's better if you're on top
Let's make it clear
no more praying!
I'll try my best, what next?
Next we kiss!
Undaunted by the misty fog
Behind the mystery
is a sweet surprise
Dashing through the sun and moon
Dancing to the beat of the gong
Nothing can dempen my chivalry
Stop the noise
this a serious business
Nothing can stop my
will to strike again
Do you know where Master is?
The priestess's got him
but I don't know where
How can we get her to come here?
There's a bell on my ankle
She'll answer it
if she hers it ring
A bell?
So why don't you ring it?
Don't stop, or they might
suspect us, carry on!
Don't stick your tongue
into my stomach!
I won't, we'll just kiss!
That's okay!
I can't bear it
I'm going for a walk!
Hey, don't go!
I can't be bothered to watch
Yin, where are you going?
For a walk!
You can't go, stay here
Go away
What will I do if you go?
I can't bear watching you two
Young student!
Open the door
I'm so scared outside
Let me come in
She's so scared!
What's that got to do with you?
It's Butterfly!
You wait here, I'll handle her
Don't go, the two of us are rivals
Even better, then there
won't be any bickering
You're really a pain
in the neck
Carry on like this
and I won't pay you
Don't mention money
I haven't seen a cent yet
Where's the money? Huh?
Hush!
Lotus, lend me some money
so I can pay him
Just so I can shut him up!
I don't want money
he wants me to take it
I'm happy with alternatives
You can talk, but touch her
So you've got to help me
You two are trouble, I'm going
Let me protect you
Forget it!
So you got thrown out too?
No such luck
Those two fought over me
If not for the fact they've
got more friends coming
I would have left ages ago
Don't stand here, go in and help
Lady, we students love
playing games
Let's have some fun!
Okay!
I said you weren't my type
Don't hang around
Open up, open the door
I have no time for you
I don't believe I'm less
attractive than Lotus!
You can't force your way in!
I want you to fancy me
Seduce me, I'm easy to seduce!
Can't we talk a bit first?
I can't wait
You have no hair! You're a monk!
You're that old monk's student?
Fong, come up!
Demon, take my spell!
Soldiers of wind and fire heed
the spell is cast!
Heaven and earth move
lend me your powers!
Wow!
Follow her!
Damn, she's got my sword
You like playing games?
I'll kill you
Belittling me?
Let's see who wins!
Little monk, I've been waiting
for you to save your Master
I was wondering who
you'd find to help you
and you get a midget
with a giant's sword
You want to amuse me
so I die happy?
Old witch
careful you'll die laughing
Do something quickly!
I haven't begun my chanting yet
Don't scare me
It's too late to look for a spell now!
Shut up!
Let's bet
Yin, chop this side first
Chop...
They keep multiplying
cast any old spell
What spell?
I can't even open my manuscript
I'm going!
Trying to escape?
You coward!
I'll help you get away
Lotus!
Come on!
I almost missed you two
Bastard, you ran away
you've no loyalty
I was sacrificing myself
to distract her
But she didn't fall for it
what can I do?
So that means I get
sacrificed instead?
Stop arguing
Let's get out of Orchid Temple
Let's hide
I can't let the
Priestess see me here
We'll work together
and distract him!
Hey, catch!
Going to fight me with
your little games?
My little games will kill you
Is that all you're capable of?
That wasn't for real
but my next move is!
Miraculous armour, go!
You decide to change
your clothes now?
I'm off
Trying to trick her again?
Let's go!
Priestess, you've been wounded!
How could we let him get away!
Did he think he could hurt me?
You won't get me!
Keep running away like that
and even if you save me...
I'll die of fright!
This is strategy
do you understand?
At least you could
have warned me
I'm saving you and all
you do is complain...
You still owe me money
where's the money?
Lotus
I mentioned borrowing
some money, I...
Not now, I've got to be
careful when I get back
Why don't you leave
Orchid Temple with us?
Your situation's dangerous;
don't go back...
Why not leave with us?
You can be a ghost anywhere
No, I'm used to this
I suffered before
I prefer living day by day
Not like you
not knowing what tomorrow will bring
It doesn't matter not knowing
Don't try and change my mind!
Here I live well and dress well
I'm not related to you
What place do I have
following you around?
I can't talk anyone
I have to go
Forget about me
She said we don't know
where we're going
She's right
Let's take care of ourselves first
That means we forget about her
You said it
Jade, is the Priestess back yet?
The Priestess?
No
Then start combing my hair
If she comes back
say I never went out
What's wrong?
Nothing...
I'll miss you
In two days I'll marry
the Mountain Devil
Whatever happens
you're always my sister
I'll talk to the Priestess
someone else can marry him
Then we can stay together
Lotus, I really love you
I believed
that when you went out
you were a good girl
Tell me where they are hiding?
Priestess, forgive me
I was wrong
Forgive you?
Tell me, how should I punish her?
Jade, you tell me
Why don't we, don't we...
Marry her to the Mountain Devil
Jade, you?
Sold when you're alive
and sold when you're dead
That Demon has many concubines
You'll suffer!
You betrayed me!
Cut off her hair
What a waste of beautiful hair
I've spent so much
time combing it
What a waste!
Scissors!
Jade, didn't you just
call me your sister?
You knew the Priestess
was hiding here
Why did you betray me?
For her own good
I'm going to scratch your face!
Priestess, please forgive me!
Please forgive Lotus!
Jade...
Sister...
Don't worry, I'll marry
in your place
Crocodile tears
But I won't let you get away
Let who get away?
Come here!
You're sisters!
You'll both marry the Mountain Devil
Scratch her face!
Priestess, don't...
Won't you forgive me?
You want me to really
damage your face?
I want her face
scratched to hell
Is this it?
Yes!
Come on!
I'm one of you!
Who are you?
Lotus?
Run away!
Don't be afraid, Buddha'll protect
us, good will win
You better let her go!
Hands off!
Or I'll blow you up
I'll come back and fight later
Come back!
I'm going to eat him first
You can lick me
but no kissing!
Did I save the wrong girl?
You'd better turn
over a new leaf
I will!
I better take you back
you can't be tamed!
I'm back!
I'm off!
Sister, run!
Jade!
You witch, still dare to call
my fighting 'games'?
Next time I'll blow up your nest!
Jade!
We're far away from it now
It doesn't matter how far we go
Why?
What are you two up to back there?
My urn of ashes is in
the hands of the Priestess
Under the 1,000 year old tree
at daybreak...
My soul will have to return there
I promise you I'll find
your urn of ashes
Don't depend on me to help
Concentrate on flying!
Be careful!
What did you just say?
You're going to back out now?
I do one thing, something else
happens, it never ends
So what?
I'll never be able to
work out my payment!
Add you stupidity
plus my naivete and intelligence
You should also add
your greediness and heartlessness
In the end you're
justjealous of me!
Jealous of you?
You two are always
in an hot embrace
I never get a chance!
I don't know what type of monk
you are, but I'm also human
I need love too!
I'm only doing this
to save someone
Stop fighting!
The Priestess isn't easy to handle
I don't think
I'll ever get away
Fong, just pretend this
never happened
I'll go by myself!
Stop putting it on
I won't help you
If you're going
to help him, move!
Even if he begs me
I won't go
But if you beg me
I may consider it
Well, take your time then
Hey!
Fong, what're you going to do?
Get your urn of ashes
then save Master
That would be suicide!
Give yourself a break
It's none of your business!
Look what you've done to me
If not for you I wouldn't
be in this mess
I saved you, and you're blaming me?
You can't fight me
how can you help me?
I'm not afraid
It's getting light
I can't stop you
No one'll help me
I'll have to help myself
Take care
I knew I'd find you!
So many urns!
How to find hers?
Let's look together
I don't need your help
I can't afford you
The likely ones go on this side
I wonder which one
contains Lotus's ashes?
None of your business!
Smart ass!
This might be
Or, this could be too
It's so big!
Lotus wasn't so fat
It goes on that side
How am I going to
carry all of these?
Want me to get
a horse and cart?
Forget it, I can't afford it
Just for you, I won't charge
Abracadabra, show the way!
Look and see if it's in that urn
It really is Lotus!
We found it!
Put it away then!
Tree Devil, how dare you
belittle me!
I'm going to burn you up
Then let's see what you can do?
The old monk!
I've found your Master
Bring him down please!
Okay!
How is he?
I can't tell!
His eyes are swollen
Master!
Move your Master
I'm going to burn the tree
It's raining
let's get out of the rain
If it doesn't stop
raining, we'll run
I'm angry we didn't
burn that old witch!
Master
Are your alright, Master!
Master, your eyes!
Fong!
You finally made it
Fong, someone else is here
who is it?
It's me sir
The nice young man
you met at the market
Good, you decided to change
your ways, and join us
Yes
I'm not as greedy as you think
We should be safe here
There's an inn over there
we can rest awhile
Okay!
Wait!
Why?
What's the matter, Master?
They're here!
Who is?
Those filthy ones!
What filthy ones?
Fong!
Lotus, it's Lotus!
Lotus!
I'll take care of her
Don't Master
she helped us
She's on our side!
Really?
Lotus, I found your urn of ashes
Hold on, there's another one
Fong...
Don't believe her
she's a fake!
Fong, don't believe her
I'm the real one
Which one's real?
How do I know?
Which is the real one, Master?
How should I know?
Fong, don't believe her, Fong...
Reveal yourself!
Stupid monk!
It's the Tree Devil!
Lotus
Fong!
How come we're still
in Orchid Temple?
We never managed to escape
the Tree Devil's grasp!
I know where Fong is
You must go quickly
Of course you know where he is!
You lied to us from
the beginning
Now you're trying to trap us
My soul's always been
with my urn of ashes
Like you, I was set up
by the Priestess
Rubbish, you expect me
to believe you?
I'm going to break your urn
and disperse your spirit
so you won't do more harm
I never lied to you
You think I let the Tree
Devil take Fong on purpose?
Yin, don't you believe me?
Demon, I'm going to destroy you
Master, let's get the old one
and let this one go
Go!
Go on!
Fong is in Orchid Temple
go and save him
Let's go
You dropped your abacus
Forget it, I'll never make
money on this job
Let's go and save Fong
Right
Master, the devil hurt by you...
...is now recovering.
Fong!
Fong, where is he?
Over there!
Can't you see
he's hanging up there
Little monk, I'm going to
suck your energy
Then I'll sell you to
the Mountain Devil
You'll never be able
to reincarnate
and you'll rot in hell!
Butterfly...
You can't even handle this monk
you're useless
Priestess, I can do it!
I'll seduce him, just you watch!
Lotus!
How dare you come back!
Priestess, I'll finish her off
No, I came for forgiveness...
I brought the other
two back with me
They're hiding behind the grass
Damn her, she's sold us out
You witch, how dare you betray us
I should've destroyed your urn!
The underworld is invincible!
Abandon law and order!
Heaven and earth move
lend your powers!
Stars scatter
...sword fly!
Cover the skies!
Oh my gold!
I'll hold them back!
The light of Buddha shines!
Butterfly!
Priestess, help me!
You're wounded, you're useless now
I need your energy
You old Tree Devil
you devour your own people!
No matter how powerful you are
Or that you're in human form
you're still a demon
Go to hell, take my spell
Soldiers of wind and fire
show your power
Why did you betray
my Master and Yin?
How else could I distract
the Priestess and save you?
My manuscript!
Stars scatter!
Heaven and earth move
lend your power
The Mountain Devil...
The Mountain Devil will
come, run quickly
You go first!
Butterfly!
Fong!
Come on, Lotus
Butterfly!
You were right
leave with the monk
At least you won't
end up like this
I was wrong too!
I shouldn't trust them!
Otherwise, I won't be
a wandering ghost!
Quick, help me!
Butterfly...
Help me!
Butterfly!
Let's go Lotus! Come on!
Come with your Master!
We can't get away like this
step on my cloak!
Onto my cloak
Master, wait for Lotus
She's a demon
don't be seduced by her
Fong!
Lotus, quickly, Lotus!
Lotus!
Fong!
Lotus?
Lotus
Fong, I'm over here!
Lotus, your urn of ashes!
Old monk, your student is down here...
Don't you go back to save him?
Soldiers of fire and wind
come, come, come
Buddha be merciful
Master!
Come on up
You kill the tree devil
and I bring you all to hell
Mountain devil is coming!
Thank you for saving me sir
I was only trying to save my student
Master, Lotus is really...
Forget it, there's one
hour before daybreak
Once it's light we'll be fine
Come to hell with me, you can't escape!
Master, we won't make it!
Yin, let's break
a path through it
Right! Heaven and earth move
Lend your powers
The light of Buddha!
We won't make it
I'll use all my life
force to fight it
Come on!
Fong, is it light yet?
Not yet, Master
He's made the skies dark
we're in his clutches
You take care of the monk
I'll distract him
You're no match for them
I'll find a way
Yin!
Mountain Devil
I've destroyed your
bastard sister
Are you afraid to show yourself?
I'll destroy you!
The spell exerts itself!
Here I come!
He's gone!
What can you do?
Master
Fong.
Your body'll hold the
Gold Buddha's energy
I'll send you above the clouds
to absorb the sun's rays
Master, you'll bleed to death!
Concentrate!
Master, Master
Are you alright, Master!
Let me go!
You'll die if you go up there!
If I don't, you'll all die
Monk, if I don't come back
Please bury my urn of
ashes properly for me
Lotus, we're all depending on you
Lotus!
Lotus
We keep trying to be apart
Yet we end up together!
But where we're going
is not for you
I know why I've to go
don't worry!
What're you doing?
I'm afraid I might let go of you
Untie yourself!
If I let go, you'll fall down!
Take care of yourself first!
My eyes!
The sun!
I'm out of breath!
Wow! I fell so far
and I'm not hurt!
Lotus
Hey, help me out!
This is what I get for being kind!
Lotus... Lotus!
Lotus!
It's a shame your spirit
is dispersed
Is this what one gets
for being kind
I hope good will come
to you in the end
Fong
Lotus, Lotus
I thought I'd never
see you again!
Take my urn of ashes with you
and I'll leave here too
Who are you talking to?
All that is left is
this red ribbon!
You mean her spirit dispersed?
Yes!
I must go now
hope we meet again
We've got to go too
bye for now
Good bye
Let's go, Master
Fong, why're you walking so fast?
I can't find Lotus's urn of ashes!
Really?
Lotus, let's get to know
each other better
You reap what you sow
stealing is wrong
I put the ashes inside my gourd
Fong!
I'll find you wherever
you're gone!
Fong, where are you taking me?
The demon said
there's no heaven
Is that true?
Stop talking and do something
Help me up!
Sure!