100%, Utah! Good job!
Hi. Johnny Utah.
Your 9:00 appointment is here.
Special Agent John Utah.
Day number one in LA. Welcome aboard.
- Been going over your personnel record. Very impressive.
- Thank you.
You may very well have been in the top
two percent of your class at Quantico...
but, quite frankly, son, out here you have
exactly zero hours of experience in the field.
You know nothing. In fact,
you know less than nothing.
If you even knew you knew nothing,
that'd be something, but you don't.
- Yes, sir.
- You eat a solid breakfast, Utah?
- Sir?
- All the food groups. Avoiding caffeine, sugar.
I like to make sure that all my people
maintain sound cardiovascular fitness.
We don't drink,
and we sure as hell don't smoke.
- Sir, I take the skin off chicken.
- Good man.
This is us.
Bank Robbery. And you are now in
the bank robbery capital of the world.
1,322 last year in L.A. County.
Up 26% from the year before.
That's correct.
And we nailed over 1,000 of them.
Miss Deer,
take a look at that for me.
Thank you. Do you know
how we nail the bad guys, Utah?
Do you know how we nail 'em?
By crunching data.
Good crime scene work,
good lab work...
and most importantly,
good data-based analysis.
Special Agent Utah,
are you receiving my signal?
Zero distortion, sir.
I love these things.
You're a real blue-ﬂame
special, aren't you, son?
Young, dumb
and full of come. I know.
What I don't know is how-how you got yourself
assigned out hereto Los Angeles with us.
I mean, hell. I guess we just must have
ourselves an asshole shortage, huh?
Not so far.
Okay.
- Pappas.
- Yeah.
Here. Put on a blindfold. I want to see you
retrieve at least two bricks off the bottom.
One-
Two.
I been in the field for 22 years.
- I fired my piece over 19 times in the line of duty.
- Johnny Utah.
I got no idea what a blind man fetching
bricks from the bottom of the pool...
has got to do
with being a special agent.
Added to which indignity...
I have been saddled with some
blue-ﬂamer Quantico cat...
some quarterback punk,
Johnny Unitas or something.
- The shit they pull, huh?
- Yeah!
- Hey, Angie.
- What?
- Here's your guy.
Pappas
- Angelo Pappas.
- Punk. Quarterback punk.
Hmm. Welcome to Sea World, kid.
Good luck, Pappas.
Two bricks, comin' up.
Little hand says
it's time to rock and roll.
- Everybody freeze!
- Nobody move!
Get your hands up
and your eyes down!
All tellers, back away from the counters!
Hands on your head now!
Everybody out from behind your desk!
On the ﬂoor!
Move it!
- Now! Get down!
- What's the matter with you people?
You, out of the cubicle!
Get out of my way! Now back away from
the counter and get your fuckin' hands up!
Bitch, what's the matter with you?
You got earwax?
Back away! Keep your hands
where I can see 'em!
- Hands up!
- Hello, hello, hello...
ladies and gentlemen.
We are the Ex-Presidents.
And we need just a few
moments of your time.
We've been screwing you for years, so a few
more seconds shouldn't matter, should it?
On the ﬂoor, asshole.
Your money's insured,
so it's not worth dying for.
- How you doing, Dick?
- just implementing our own plan...
of deregulation, Mr. President.
- Time, Mr. Carter?
- Sixty!
- L.B.J.?
- We're stylin'.
- Oh, Ron, I've got Nancy on the line.
- Whoo!
Eighty!
- Air Force One is waiting, Mr. President.
- Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
Get your hands where
I can fuckin' see 'em!
- Thank you!
- Thank you very much, ladies and gentlemen.
And, please, don't forget to vote.
I'm not a crook!
Twenty-seven banks in three years.
God. In and out in 90 seconds.
No one ever gets shot.
What are we talkin' about here?
We're talkin' about solid professionals.
- Good moves.
- Yeah. They control the room well.
And they stick strictly to
the cash drawers.
- They don't go for the vault?
- No. They never go for the vault.
They never get greedy.
- Smart. You burn time in the vault.
- Yep. That's right.
Reagan usually does the driving. Stolen switch car.
They leave it running on the curb.
It looks parked from a distance.
And when they run,
they dump the vehicle and they vanish...
like a virgin on prom night.
I mean, they vanish. Pfft!
Surgical.
Look at them separate the dye pack.
Dick and Ronnie know their jobs.
Yeah, the Ex-Presidents
are the best I've ever seen. Ever.
Anytime you two are finished
jerking off watching MTV...
we need to get a look
at these tapes.
Hey, Pappas. You, uh, tell the kid
your theory on the Presidents?
Just take the tapes and go, Babbit.
Hang 10, Pappas.
Like, totally rad, dude!
- I tell you. The department loves it.
- What's he talking about, Angelo?
- Found the drop car on Mulholland Drive. I'd like two volunt-
- We'll go work it.
- Oh, no.
- Angelo.
- Come on.
- Thank you.
- We'll go work it.
- Good.
Excuse me.
I'm working a fuckin' drop car.
I can't believe it.
Working a drop car.
Pappas. What a hard-on.
- Keep 'em away from there.
- All right.
459 called in at about 5:25.
This car doesn't have A.C.
Today was a scorcher.
Sweat secretions in the seat backs.
Are you through, Mr. Wizard?
Let me know if you find jimmy Hoffa
under the seat while you're at it.
Oh, look at this. It's 7:30.
Why, the night is still so young.
The way you're going, you're gonna be able to
solve this case and start another one, huh?
Drop car, my ass. Goddamn.
You've been working
bank robbery, what, 22 years?
Yeah. Twenty-two yea rs.
Man, L.A. has changed a lot
during that time.
The air got dirty,
and the sex got clean.
Uh-huh. So a guy with that kind of time in
must have some theory about these guys.
Leave it alone, Johnny.
Okay, fine. You've given up.
Fine. It doesn't mean I have to.
Hey, hey! Listen.
Forget about it, kid. They are ghosts.
Yeah. Of course.
What am I thinking?
If you couldn't crack it
with all your yea rs of experience...
it's impossible to conceive that I
might have something to offer, right?
- Well, maybe I can do better than some over-the-hill burnout.
- Hey, watch your mouth.
Maybe you ought to just take
some early retirement right now...
and get some rent-a-cop
night security job, tell 'Nam stories.
Listen, you snot-nosed little shit!
I was taking shrapnel in Khe Sanh...
while you were crapping in your hands
and rubbing it on your face!
- You mad?
- Yeah, I'm mad!
- Good and mad?
- What do you want to do about it?
Feels good, doesn't it?
Like you're still alive, right?
- Yeah!
- Well, since you're still alive...
and you're not
in the box just yet...
why don't you tell me this theory of yours
and we'll go get these guys?
Okay, hotshot.
You want to nail the bank robbers
and be a big hero?
- Definitely.
- “Definitely.”
Then here it is.
The Ex-Presidents...
are surfers.
- Surfers?
- Surfers.
It's in our face.
Look at the tan line on this guy.
- Oh, well, he must be a surfer.
- Well, yeah.
So last year, Nixon scuffs the counter
when he's going over.
So, there is a soil sample.
Nonspecific mud.
Traces of asphalt.
Traces of oil.
Traces of sand. Carnauba wax.
So I become a wax expert.
Now there's 80-some uses
for this stuff.
Something like 500 products.
Candle wax. Car wax.
Mustache wax.
It could be anything.
Guy's waxing his mustache
at the beach...
gets sand in it...
takes it off with a shoe,
shoe scuffs the counter.
Would you just shut up a minute?
Just listen to me.
Maybe you'll learn something.
The lab gave us
three possible matches.
This is one of them.
- Sex Wax?
- Yeah.
You're not into kinky
shit, are you, Angelo?
Not yet. Surfers use this.
- They rub it on their boards for traction.
- Thanks for the tip.
You're welcome for the tip.
Well, here's another tip.
Check out... the dates
on these robberies.
It's strictly a summer job
for these idiots.
Four months.
June to October.
- Same the year before.
- That's right.
We have one more month.
We won't see 'em till next summer.
They're traveling on the money,
going where the waves are.
That's right.
The Ex-Presidents...
rip off banks to finance
their endless summer.
Hey, man. A lot of guys
your age are learning to surf.
It's cool.
There's nothing wrong with it.
- I'm 25.
- That's what I'm saying. It's never too late.
Hope you stick with it.
Surfing's the source.
It can change your life. I swear to God.
Why can't I just walk around
with this thing under my arm...
and act stoned, ask a few questions?
Well, look.
Look at 'em.
They're like some kind of tribe.
They got their own language.
You can't just walk up
to those guys.
You have to get out there
and learn the moves...
get into their head,
pick up the speech.
You trying to tell me the F.B.I's
going to pay me to learn to surf?
It's either you or me out there on the board.
You get my drift?
Angelo, this is for little rubber people
who don't shave yet.
Come on. You're the quarterback jock.
It's all balance, right?
And coordination.
How hard can it be?
Hold on.
Use your arms. Paddle. Come on!
Use your arms.
You're all right.
Come on. You're okay.
You crazy son of a bitch!
If you want to commit suicide,
you do it someplace else!
This pig board piece of shit.
You got no business
out here whatsoever!
Hey!
My name's Johnny Utah!
Who cares?
♪ It's been a long, long time ♪
♪ And too many miles ♪
♪ Of hand-shaking strangers ♪
♪ Parading their smile ♪
♪ Of all the faces
that come and go ♪
♪ The only one
I really want to know♪
♪ I want you ♪
♪ I want you ♪♪
That is your surfing contact?
Female. Blue eyes.
Black hair.
Five foot six, 119 pounds.
God, Utah.
Not bad, Utah.
“Tyler Ann Endicott.
Born 11/27/64.”
“Exhibition of speed.
Indecent exposure
inside moving vehicle.”
Hot. Very hot.
What else they got on her?
I still haven't found anything I can really use.
I gotta find an approach, a way in.
Here we go.
Both parents deceased.
Airplane crash. San Diego, '84.
Yeah. Definitely.
See you later, Wayne.
Next.
- What do you want?
- Shrimp and fries.
I mean, what do you want?
- Why do you keep hanging around here?
- I need you to teach me.
Give me a break.
Uh, shrimp and fries.
To go.
Would you like something
to drink with that, sir?
- I'm serious.
- I can see that you're serious.
Forget it. Stick to tennis.
I don't know.
Whatever you do good.
Uh, miniature golf.
Your number's 37.
You don't understand.
I'm gonna learn to surf or break my neck.
What is it? You all of a sudden got this
bug that you just have to go surfing?
This is a line, right?
No. No.
See...
my whole life I've done
things for other people.
In high school I played football
because my old man expected me to.
- Mm-hmm.
- And my parents always figured I'd go to law school.
So I did. Football scholarship.
- Phi Beta Kappa.
- Is this gonna take a really long time?
- Wait. So I'm a big hero to my folks, right?
- Mm-hmm.
But two yea rs ago,
they were killed in a car wreck.
You can't imagine it.
Your whole life changes.
And I suddenly realized
that all my goals had been their goals...
and I hadn't been living
my own life.
So I wanted something for myself.
So I come out here
from Ohio a month ago.
I've never seen the ocean before-
any ocean.
I never thought
it would affect me so much.
I'm drawn to it.
Or something.
I want to do what you do.
It's the truth.
All right. Okay.
Tomorrow, here...
6:00 a.m.
If you are one minute late,
I'm gone.
And, stud, I didn't
take you on to raise, so...
I'll teach you a few things, and after that
you're gonna be on your own, okay?
God.
Stop here.
- Do you agree to do exactly what I say when I say it?
- Sure.
Pop! POP-
You stand straight up, you’re just gonna
fall right over. So let's try it again.
Start over. Just do it again.
Hey. What you doing, huh?
just do it again. Pop up.
You gotta stay low.
You're gonna bite it.
You dragged a knee that time.
You'll just-You'll just wipe out.
You're dragging your foot.
You're gonna be fish food.
Both feet have to land on the board
at the same time.
That's it. That's it.
You're surfing.
- Whoa'. Whoo-hoo'.
- ♪ To rise and fall ♪
♪ Without the hands of gravity ♪
♪ To see it all ♪
- Shit!
- ♪ The hands that cover up my eyes}
♪ And Charles Atlas stands ♪
♪ Upon the beach
upon his head and says ♪
- Whoo'.
- ♪ I will not fall ♪
Yeah!
Oh!
♪ I will not fall ♪
Doing all right, city boy.
♪ To live in the groove ♪
♪ Is everything that I need ♪
♪ To see you move ♪
♪ When grace is just
a simple wisdom ♪
♪ And Charles Atlas stands ♪
♪ Upon the beach
upon his head and says ♪
- ♪ I will not fall ♪
- Whoo'.!
- Yeah'.
- ♪ I will not fall ♪
♪ I will not fall ♪
- You are surfing!
♪ I will not fall ♪♪
That's Bodhi.
They call him the Bodhisattva.
- Yeah!
- He's a modern savage.
- He's a real searcher.
- What's he searching for?
The ride.
The ultimate ride.
Guy's even crazier than you, Johnny.
- Not bad!
- Whoa-hoof
- Yeah!
- Hey!
Whoo!
"- Heads up.
On three.
Hey!
Put me down.
Uh, we know each other.
That's a-
That's a surfboard, all right.
Looks like a '57 Chevy I used to have.
Uh, Tyler, come here.
So, uh, who's the guy?
You replacing me?
- Give me a break. Where you been?
- He surfs real well.
- Come on. He's from Kansas or something.
- He's from Kansas?
Heads UP!
Yeah.
Good catch.
Ready! Set!
Hut! Go! Let's go! Go, go!
- Yeah, yeah!
- Whoo-hoo!
Hut!
I'm open!
Whoo! Yeah!
I What a Pass!
- Yeah!
- Yes, mama! Yes, baby!
Whose ball is this?
Who works here?
You! You! You!
Hut'.
- Get him!
Yes!
Ready! Set! Hut!
Go, go!
♪ Fire in the sky Move ♪
♪ I wanna go ♪
♪ Move AU'
Hey, what the fuck is wrong with you? Don't
you think that's a little out of line?
- Cool it, Roach. Don't you know who this is?
- No, I don't know who this is.
This is Johnny Utah. The Ohio State
Buckeyes, all-conference, remember?
Number nine, man.
How you doing? Nice to meet ya.
Oh, shit. Jesus Chri-Johnny fucking Utah. Sorry, man.
Didn't mean to get in your face.
I knew I knew you. It was the Rose Bowl
three years ago, and you beat S.C., right?
- You? You did this?
- It was him.
- That was one hell of a game.
- No shit.
Yeah. Uh, you got nuked
in the last quarter or something.
Yeah. I got my knee folded back
about 90 degrees the wrong way.
- Whoa.
- That's why you never went pro?
Two years of surgery.
Missed my window.
Limped through law school instead.
Law school? You're a lawyer?
- Wow.
- Ouch.
Well, life's not over yet, man.
You're surfing.
- Lawyers don't surf.
- This one does.
- Let's jam!
- Let's play some football!
Special Agent Utah...
this is not some job ﬂipping burgers
at the local drive-in.
Yes, the surfboard bothers me.
Yes, your approach to this whole
goddamn case bothers me...
and yes, you bother me!
And Pappas!
Oh, for the love of Christ.
Just how the hell
did I ever even let you...
talk me into this whole
boneheaded idea to begin with?
Harp, we're working undercover.
It takes time. We produced a few-
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Let me tell you what you produced.
Over the last two weeks,
you two have produced exactly squat!
Squat!
During which time, the Ex-Presidents
have robbed two more banks!
Now, for Christ's sake,
does either one of you...
have anything even remotely
interesting to tell me?
Caught my first tube this morning...
sir.
Goddamn it.
- Why didn't you leave that thing in the car?
- It sticks out. I can't lock it.
Anyway, what's his problem?
We're handling our caseload.
I'm surfing on my own time.
I know it. Just don't rub
Harp's nose in it.
Look, Angelo, you think
I joined the F.B.I. to learn to surf?
This was your lame-o idea in the first place.
You gotta back me up on this.
Johnny, we better
come up with something real quick.
- My friend-
- What?
Encino Savings and Loan.
Guard grabbed L.B.J.'s ponytail.
Twenty-eight robberies,
and what do we get from it?
One fucking hair.
- Angelo. Pay attention.
- What?
There's gonna be a test afterward.
Lab is showing traces
of toxins in the hair.
Selenium, titanium and arsenic.
The beaches are always being closed
because of waste spills, right?
- Yeah.
- And surfers are territorial.
They stick mostly to certain breaks.
If we can get some hair samples
and get a match at a certain beach...
we'd know which break
the Ex-Presidents surf.
You buyin' this?
- No.
But let's do it anyway.
It will bug the shit out of Harp.
- My man.
- Yeah.
Hey. When you two are done
making out, I need to talk to you.
What's this, fucking narco
entrapment or what, dude?
- Not exactly, dude.
- Oh, shit.
Making a wig for my girlfriend.
Thank you.
- What the fuck? Fucking guy's a narc, man.
- Dude cut my hair.
- So what? He didn't bust us.
- Dude, he fucking cut my hair.
Brah. Brah.
Don't move. You've got some huge sucker
crawling right into your ear.
- Got it!
- Hey!
Leave some fucking hair, man.
- What is it?
- I saved your life, bro.
Close one.
P.C.B.'s, selenium,
titanium, arsenic.
The percentages look right.
- Here's a match.
- There's a match?
Latigo Beach. Nice point break.
- Long, workable rides.
- Surfs up, ace.
Stay off my wave.
Goons trying to drop in.
Paddle, paddle, paddle.
♪ One, two ♪
♪ Three, four ♪
Out of the way, you shit!
Hey!
You dinged my board, dude!
Why don't you watch
where the fuck you're going?
Politeness counts, asshole!
Go back to the Valley, man.
Angelo, I've eaten shit 47 times...
I've got my lights punched out
by some psycho local...
and there must be 20 guys
out here with ponytails.
Patience, hotshot. Patience.
It'll be subtle,
if it's here at all.
There'll be a group
within the group.
These guys are a real tight unit.
You'll see them. You'll know it.
- This the guy?
- Yeah.
Okay.
I know.
This is where you tell me
all about how locals rule...
and yuppie insects
like me shouldn't be
surfing your break
and all that, right?
Nope.
That would be a waste of time.
We're just gonna fuck you up.
Oh.
Eat that!
Get him! Fuck him up!
Johnny, you there?
You better not be trying
to pick up any babes.
Hit 'em! Yeah!
Harder! Yeah!
- Back off! He's with me!
- Kiss my ass.
Back off, Warchild. Seriously.
Thank you.
- Stay out of this, Bodhi.
- What's your name?
- Bunker.
Listen, Bunker.
I'm actually really glad you found me.
Yeah? Why?
- Hey!
- Back off.
Hey, man!
Shit!
Come on! Come on!
Come here!
Fuck.
This is stimulating, but we're out of here.
Let's go, Utah.
Just keep walking.
Hold it. Look.
You two guys seen a kid
run through here with a car stereo?
- He stole it from me.
- No, but, uh...
- there's four guys back there you
might want to check out. - Oh.
- Thanks, buddy.
- Hope you find him.
Don't worry. I will.
You like to start shit, don't you?
- Who are those guys?
- Nazi assholes.
The guy you dropped is Bunker Weiss.
The big one is Warchild,
a.k.a. Lupton Pitman.
The other two-
Hell, I don't know. They-They, uh-
They think they're some kind of
death squad around here.
What's their program?
Brains are wired wrong, and
they're into some bad shit.
Like what? Illegal shit?
Maybe. I don't know.
That's not what I'm talking about.
They only live to get radical. They don't
have any real understanding of the sea...
so they'll never get
the spiritual side of it.
Hey, you're not gonna start
chanting or anything, are you?
I might.
This is me.
So, uh...
you still haven't figured out
what riding waves is all about, have you?
It's a state of mind.
It's that place where you lose yourself
and you find yourself.
You don't know it yet,
but you got it. It's right there.
I saw you with those guys.
You're a pit bull.
You didn't hesitate, and they
didn't back you down an inch...
and that is very rare in this world.
- Well, thanks for steppin' in.
- De nada.
Later. Oh, hey.
I'm, uh, having some people over at
my house tonight if you want to come.
- Sure. Where?
- Come with Tyler. She knows.
All right.
Next time you leave your piece and
shield in the car, you stay in sight, okay?
Okay, dad.
Yeah, I need you to
run a plate for me.
2-Denver-4-Sam-Niner-Five-Niner.
Late '70s jeep.
The jeep belongs to
a Bunker Weiss. My buddy.
Guy's got quite a sheet. Yeah?
Yeah, slap all that.
Give me the greatest hits.
Felony possession of cocaine.
That's good.
Felony “B” and “E.”
Three months in juvie.
Felony assault.
Postgraduate work at Chino.
Excellent. I'm loving it.
These guys really fit the profile.
I say we lay it on Harp.
Here comes the night shift.
Hey, who was that girl?
No, the girl with the really big tits.
This is bullshit. This is a bullshit lead.
This is totally bullshit.
Harp must be fuckin' desperate
if he's listening to you two ﬂakes.
See you bright and early, guys.
Yeah, right.
Here you go.
Cold pizza for you.
It's good for breakfast.
See ya.
When did Harp say
we'd get the warrant?
He's gonna push it through first thing.
You better get some sleep.
This could be
an interesting morning.
♪ If the sun ♪
♪ Refused to shine ♪
♪ I don't mind ♪
♪ If the mountains ♪
♪ Fell in the sea ♪
♪ Let it be ♪
♪ It ain't me ♪
♪ Got my own world ♪
♪ To live through ♪
♪ And I ain't gonna copy you ♪
- Hey.
- Hey, Bodhi.
♪ Yes ♪
♪ Now, if a six ♪
♪ Turned out to be nine ♪
- I taught him that trick.
- ♪ I don't mind ♪
- I like it.
- ♪ I don't mind♪
Watch yourself.
She's a wild one.
- ♪ If all the hippies ♪
- Make yourself at home.
- What's mine is yours.
- ♪ Cut off all their hair♪
♪ I don't care ♪♪
Man! It jacks up.
We drop down into the pit.
It's 25 feet straight down.
And your balls-
Man, your balls are about this big.
And the whole thing's
fuckin' roaring, right?
Pushin' you forward like-
like you're a hood
ornament on a freight
train or something, man.
Yeah, and if you lose it...
the fish will be
picking you out of the coral.
Big-wave riding's for macho
assholes with a death wish.
No, it's not. It's the ultimate rush.
There's nothing
that comes close to it.
Not even sex.
Maybe that's 'cause you're
not doing it right, Roach.
Just paddling out into big surf
is a total commitment.
You can't just call time out
and stroll on into the beach...
if you don't like
the way things are goin'.
So what's the biggest? Waimea?
- Ridden?
- Yeah.
- Makaha.
- Dana Point.
Bells Beach, Australia.
Whoa, whoa. No way Bells is bigger
than Waimea, bro.
Will be next year.
Bodhi believes the 50-year
storm is coming next year.
The 50-year storm? What's that?
- That's kind of a legend.
- No, it's real. It's absolutely real.
Everything moves in cycles.
So twice a century, the ocean lets us
know just how small we really are.
A winter storm comes out of Antarctica
tearing up the Pacific...
and it sends a huge
swell north 2,000 miles.
And when it hits Bells Beach...
it'll turn into the
biggest surf this
planet has ever seen,
and I will be there.
- So will I.
- Yeah!
If you want the ultimate, you gotta
be willing to pay the ultimate price.
It's not tragic to die
doing what you love.
- That's how I wanna go.
- Hell, I ain't gonna live to see 30.
- There's too much testosterone here.
- Whoa!
♪ Over I'm over, over ♪
♪ Over it ♪
♪Over I'm over♪
♪ Over Over♪
♪It♪♪
Bunch of goddamn adrenaline junkies.
Hope you're not buying
into this banzai
bullshit like the rest
of Bodhi's Moonies.
What are you talkin' about?
You got the kamikaze look, Johnny.
I've seen it.
Bodhi can smell it a mile away.
He'll take you to the edge.
Past it.
- Hey, Bodhi.
- Johnny has his own demons.
Don't you, Johnny?
What's going on?
- Whoo!
- Go!
Here. Time for a little stealth mission.
You up for it?
- Let's do it.
- Let's go!
I can barely do this
in broad daylight.
Come on. At least nobody's
gonna see how bad you are.
Whoo!
- I don't think he's ready for this.
- Nah, he'll be fine.
Shit!
Shit! Oh, shit! Fuck!
- I gotta be fuckin' crazy.
- But are you crazy enough?
Whoo-hoo!
Whoo! Tyler!
Whoo!
I can't see shit out here.
I'm gonna die.
Just feel what the wave is doing.
Then accept its energy...
get in sync, then charge with it.
- You don't need to see.
- Yeah, right. Vision is highly overrated.
Okay, Johnny. This one's got your number
on it. Let's jam. Now paddle!
- Go, boy! jam!
- Shit. I'm gonna die now.
Gonna fuckin' die now.
Fuck! Shit!
Whoo! You're surf in', man!
Whoa!
Whoo!
I'm fuckin' surfing!
Yeah!
- Check it out!
- Is this not the best feeling on earth?
Yeah! Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
- Good break, Johnny.
- All right!
Yeah!
Whoa!
Looks like we lost somebody.
- Yeah. Leave the fire for them.
- You hungry?
- Wanna get something to eat?
- Whoo!
- You wanna get something to eat?
- I'm dying. Yeah.
I'm starving.
You had enough?
Yeah.
I just want to sit out here
for a minute.
Look at you.
What?
Well, usually you have
this intense sort of scowl...
of concentration on your
face, like you're doing
all this for a school
project or something.
Or, like, you've got
something driving you.
Look at it. It's gone.
If I didn't know better...
I'd say you looked almost happy.
I can't describe what I'm feeling.
You don't have to.
Goose bumps.
Yeah. It's cold.
Yeah.
Come here.
Oh.
Shit.
- Holy shit.
- What?
Shit!
I'm really late.
I mean, I'm really late.
Holy shit.
Shit!
Oh, shit!
Oh-
I'm really late.
You guys need any help?
I can't believe you're late
to your own raid. What a ﬂake.
Has that worthless quarterback punk
partner of mine shown up yet?
Right here.
Oh, well, very good of
you to show up, hotshot.
Ow! Watch it.
God, you're gonna tear my skin. Goddamn it.
I'm ready to rock, Angelo.
Where you want me?
Okay. Here's how it is. Babbit and Alvarez
are gonna go in the back door.
Cullen's gonna back me up. I want you
at the side window by the hedge.
Now you're strictly backup.
I don't wanna
burn your cover.
Have you got that?
Got it.
Good. Now take your position.
it's showtime.
- Go.
- Asshole.
Scooby? Come on, Scooby.
Scooby, where are ya?
You seen a little dog?
- No, man.
- No dog? Scooby, come on.
Here, here, Scooby. Scooby.
- What the fuck?
- Get up, man. Get the gun.
There's someone
at the front door. Now! Move!
Go, go. Get the guns now.
Get 'em.
- Oh.
- Yeah, what?
Hi. Oh. Have you seen my dog?
I got a little
dog I'm missing. It's a
cockapoo-like thing.
I don't know a thing
about your fuckin' dog.
Wait, wait.
Your next-door neighbor
said he saw it.
Cullen, this is Utah. Get
Angelo out of there.
They're pulling out
a fuckin' arsenal.
Utah, repeat. Say again.
Cullen, you copy? Cullen!
Alvarez!
Don't let him pull his badge!
Fuck! I can't hear jack shit
over the lawn mower. Christ!
Front door.
Somethings goin' down, man.
This ain't right.
Chill the fuck out, man.
It's nothin'.
Will you shut the fuck up?
Check the windows, bro. Do it.
Shit.
...little bastard, right?
Before he goes, he lifts his leg.
He was under my house.
I don't know anything
about a fucking dog!
Hide the shit!
Wait. Wait, wait.
Are you sure it's not in the backyard?
I ain't got time for this.
There's two guys out the back, man.
Duck down.
Oh, shit! Shit! We're fucked!
When that fuck comes
through the door, I'm
gonna pump him up, man.
Swear to Christ.
- Are you sure it's not in the back?
- It ain't back there.
Is there anybody else
around who has seen him?
Get the fuck out of my face.
F.B.I., gorgeous.
- F.B.I.! Drop it!
- Fuck you!
Fuckin' pigs!
No, wait! Hey!
Goddamn! Oh, fuck!
- Oh, shit!
- Shut up!
- You motherfuckers! Motherfuckers!
- I said shut up!
Hey, motherfucker, back up!
Back up, or I blow her fuckin' head off!
Back up, or I'll take her with me.
Back up!
I'm coming out right now!
Back off! Back off!
Let me go! Let me go!
Cullen!
Bastard!
Fuck!
You bastard!
Go!
- Babbit?
- You fuckers!
Hey, hey!
Fuck you up, man!
Speak into the microphone,
squid-brain.
Fuck.
- Give me your hand
- Fuck you.
- Give me your other hand.
- Fuck.
- Fucker.
- This'll feel good to ya.
There you go. You okay?
Fuck!
Oh, God!
No! Aaah!
Don't touch it!
it's been pa per targets
up until today, huh?
It's no different, Johnny.
just a little more to clean up.
You did all right today.
You did real good.
Goddamn son of a bitch!
Ah, you're the cowboys. You're the real
cowboys, right? Batman and Robin.
You know what this is, huh?
You know what this is, punk?
This is two keys.
Uncut. Crystal meth.
Oh, shit.
Special Agent Utah,
I'd like you to meet Agent Dietz.
Works for the D.E.A.
He was working deep cover until you-
You think I like
this hair, man? Huh?
You think I like these clothes?
My wife wants me to stay at Ramada.
I've been working on these fuckers
for three months! Three months!
Now I finally got 'em wanting to play
Wheel of Fortune with me...
so I can find out who their suppliers is
and you fuckin' cowboys show up.
- Nice tattoo, Dietz.
- Oh, you like that, Pappas, huh? Fuck you.
He has a record of your
suspects' movements
for every day over the
last three months.
All I want to know, smart guy-Okay?
All I want to know is,
how are these guys...
robbing Tarzana City
National Bank on August 2...
when they were in
Fort fuckin' Lauderdale August 2?
Why don't you figure that out?
That's not an easy thing
to do, is it, Utah?
You fuckin' jerks.
Oh, shit.
Shit.
Mmm.
...believes it.
Hey. Five-foot walls at Zero's.
Let's go.
Hey, Tyler.
Hey, Bodhi.
So let's go. Time's a-wastin'.
- Now.
- He does this.
Yeah!
No!
You all right?
You look like you saw a ghost.
Forget about it, kid.
They're ghosts.
- I gotta go.
- You gotta what?
Listen, I forgot all about a meeting
I have this morning. A new client.
I gotta jam. Sorry. Really.
I'll call you later.
- So I started trailing him.
- Who, the Zen surf master?
Bodhi, yeah.
I'm on him all day, right?
He goes here, he goes there.
He goes to Tower Records, buys some CDs.
He has lunch
at Patrick's Road House.
He goes into the Assured Trust
Savings and Loan.
- Did he rob it?
- Cute.
He's inside 20 minutes.
The other guy, Roach, waited in the truck.
They were scoping it out, right?
Well, they were scoping it out, or
they were cashing a check. - Wait, wait.
Then they go back
to their beach house...
- and they box up all their shit.
- Yeah?
See, summer's over.
They load it in Bodhi's truck,
and they take it to a public storage unit.
And I lost 'em after that,
but the house is empty.
- They're definitely out of here.
- Goddamn it.
Why didn't you call me?
They're probably halfway to Maui.
Uh-uh. No. They've gotta pick up
some traveling money first.
Assured Trust tomorrow.
Next day outside at the latest.
I definitely got a feeling on this.
Oh, you got a feeling. Last time
you had a feeling I had to kill a guy.
And I hate that.
It looks bad on my report.
Angelo, I'm right this time.
We can still win this one.
Okay.
Tomorrow morning first thing
we'll be at the bank, like stink on shit.
This Calvin and Hobbes is funny.
Oranges, sir?
Would you like some oranges?
- You want some oranges?
- A dollar, sir. - No.
- Nice and big, sir.
- No. We got a lot. We got a lot.
- Dollar, sir.
- No, thanks. Good luck.
God.
“For his turkey cemetery.”
Oh.
It's time for lunch.
Angelo, it's 10:30.
Right around that corner,
there is a sandwich shop.
They sell meatball sandwiches.
Best I've ever tasted.
Would you go get me two?
Come on, partner. Two.
Thank you.
Utah! Get me two.
- Hi. How ya doin'?
- Hi.
Can I have two meatball sandwiches,
a tuna on wheat...
and two lemonades, please?
Okay, that's two meatballs,
one tuna on wheat, two lemonades.
That's 7.84.
- Thank you.
- Uh-huh.
Oh, boy.
Aaah! God. You scared me.
Here. Yours is the one
that looks like a roadkill.
- A roadkill?
- Enjoy.
- Thank you very much.
- Here's your lemonade.
- Thanks. Oh, whoa, whoa.
- Did you see that Lincoln pull up?
I'm so hungry I could eat
the ass end out of a dead rhino.
I should have had you get me
three of these things.
What Lincoln?
- Goddamn!
- F.B.I.! Freeze!
'Got him! 'Got him!
- No! Go! Go!
- Freeze!
Fuck!
Get in! Get in! Jesus Christ.
- Go! Go!
- Fuck!
- Go!
- Gimme a fuckin' break. I am going.
I don't see 'em.
Where'd they go?
- I don't fuckin' believe this.
- I think we're losin' 'em.
- You're losing 'em.
- We're not losing 'em.
Over to the right.
Over to the right. Over to the right.
Go, go! He's coming up.
Punch it, punch it, punch it.
Whoo!
- Where is he, Dick?
- He's still behind us.
Hang on, you guys.
- We're fucked.
- This car's a piece of shit.
Oh, shit.
It's okay. They're on the left.
- I think we lost 'em. I can't see 'em.
- Tell me where he is.
Oh, fuck. Watch out.
- We got ya.
- You ain't got shit.
Oh, fuck. Hang on!
- Goddamn it.
- Come on, come on.
Okay, guys,
Time for emergency sanitation.
Back off, buddy.
Try it, man.just try it.
- What about the old Chevy?
- This guy down here.
- Come on.
- I got him. I got the guy.
- Get away from the car. Move it!
- Come on, get in.
Wait. Wait, wait.
Don't do it, man. Don't do it.
Don't be stupid.
Run!
Why's he takin' so long?
Come on!
- We gotta go now!
- Wait a minute.
- Go! Go!
- Come on!
Down! Get down!
- Oh, shit!
- Let's go! Go!
What the fuck!
Aaah!
Look out!
Hey!
Get the fuck out of this house! Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
'Hey! Hey! Hey!
Oh, no!
Stop or I'll shoot!
Damn!
Say again, 41.
Roger that, 41.
Cal plate 562, Sam, Ida, Xray.
Base out.
- Nothing?
- Nothing.
Johnny, I wanna see you
in my office right now.
Unit 23, Unit 23.
See the manager, 4650 Wilshire.
Roger, 23.
Unit 41, further information
on suspect's vehicle-
I want you to know something.
When you shoot, you don't miss.
- I missed.
- No.
I believe you're either scared...
or you're getting
too goddamn close...
to this surfing guru buddy of yours.
I don't believe you're scared.
Hey. I want you to go
home and get some rest.
You look like hammered shit.
And if I get anything
that resembles your boy...
I'll beep ya.
Now go home.
Goddamn it.
So what's the other guy look like?
Never saw him.
It was your basic hit-and-run.
You look like you got
in a train wreck.
Stupid jerk just kept driving?
Ouch. Baby, I'm sorry.
Johnny, what is it with you?
You've got that look again.
Like you-
You're about to tell me something,
and then... you don't.
Or you can't.
There's something
I've wanted to tell you.
It's important.
It could really affect things
between you and me.
Man. This is harder than I thought.
God. Men are so bad at this.
Shh.
Some other time.
- You act like nothin' happened.
- Relax, Nathanial.
Don't tell me to relax, Bodhi.
He's a fuckin' federal agent.
I should have shot him
when I had the chance.
I'll deal with that fuckin' cop.
No, Rosie.
Do you realize that we have hit
30 banks in three years...
and they haven't been
able to touch us?
All this does is up
the stakes of the game.
Fuck the stakes, Bodhi.
I mean, the only person this is
a game to is you, man. This is real.
I mean, this is serious shit...
and I am scared, okay?
So I say we get the fuck out of here,
now, tonight. Okay?
- Run, you die.
- Come on. Think about it.
This was never about money for us.
It was about us
against the system-
That system that kills
the human spirit.
We stand for something.
To those dead souls inching along
the freeways in their metal coffins...
we show them
that the human spirit is still alive.
So you trust me?
Okay.
Then don't worry about this guy.
I know exactly what to do with him.
A liar! You lied to me.
Tyler, put the gun down.
I'll bet you lied about everything.
I'll bet you lied
about your parents.
You just tell me the truth, Johnny.
Did your parents die
in a car accident?
Did they?
They live in Columbus, Ohio.
I work Bank Robbery.
The guys I'm after are surfers.
- I needed you at first, but after that I-
- Fuck you'.!
Don't you have a soul?
Goddamn you to hell.
Tyler.
Tyler, wait!
Tyler!
Leave a message.
Tyler, look, I fucked up, okay?
I know I fucked up.
I wanted to tell you,
but I couldn't.
I was afraid you'd leave.
Good guess, huh?
Fuck! Why can't I ever say
what I really mean?
I lied to you. I'm an asshole.
But I need you, Tyler.
I want you to know that I've never known
anyone like you before in my life...
and I hope you change your mind.
Tyler, wait. I'm coming.
Howdy, brah.
So come on. We're rollin'.
What's goin' on, Bodhi?
Whoa, what happened?
You cut yourself shaving?
I don't think I wanna
surf right now.
Surf? No, this is different, Johnny.
This is really different.
You are gonna love it.
So we gotta get your stuff
and get out of here.
Okay, uh-Socks.
Shirt.
There you go, man.
Uh-Boots. Here we go.
Okay. Get your stuff on the truck.
We gotta go. Life is short.
You are gonna love this.
- Whoo!
- Yo.
- All right. Here.
- All right.
Take this bag, Grommet.
Come on.
Nathanial, wait a minute.
- Take this too.
- Thank you, sir.
Here you go.
Ever done this before?
No, but I've seen it on TV.
It's 100% pure adrenaline.
Other guys snort for it, jab a vein for it-
All you gotta do is jump.
I'm sure it's a blast, but I sort of
screwed my knee up yesterday.
Oh, yeah, yeah. I noticed you limping,
but hey, don't worry about it.
Don't worry at all,
because we're not gonna land on land.
Oh, well, fine then.
I feel so much better.
Okay, let's ﬂy.
- Three minutes.
- This is a little ceremony...
we always do
at the end of the summer.
- One last speed star.
- Yeah! - Yeah!
By the way, you might want to pull
that little orange thing sometime.
The life you save may be your own.
So, uh...
who packed my chute?
I did. Why? You don't trust me?
You gotta earn trust.
Okay, we'll earn it together.
Here.
Take mine.
Hey, Johnny, I don't think
this is such a good idea.
Bodhi's pack jobs are pretty shitty.
They only open about half the time.
- Less.
- Bullshit.
Why don't you take young
Grommet's here? How'd that be?
Nah, you don't want this one.
This one's set for a neck-breaker.
You're probably better off
with something like this.
We gonna jump or jerk off?
That's my man.
- Here we go!
- Yeah, let's do it.
Johnny, you're about to jump
out of a perfectly good airplane.
How do you feel about that?
Geronimo!
Shit! Whoa, shit!
Whoa, ho, ho!
Sex with the gods!
You can't beat this! Whoo-hoo!
Whoo!
This is fucking beautiful.
Whoo, hoo-hoo!
Oh, yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Hah!
Come on, Johnny. Whoo!
That's it, Johnny. Go for it.
Come on, Johnny!
You can do it! Come on!
Use your arms.
Fly like an eagle, baby.
Whoo!
Keep comin'!
All right! Johnny, you did it.
You're a speed star!
We're goin' like a bat out of hell.
Righteous speed star.
- How do you like it, Johnny?
- Amazing!
Fucking amazing!
This is so beautiful.
I love this ground rush shit.
Okay, break.
Great, isn't it?
You're doin' good.
A thousand feet-Pull.
After you, Alphonse. I insist.
- Pull the rip cord now.
- You first.
- Okay.
- Son of a bitch.
Jesus Christ.
I gotta be losing it.
That's the closest you'll ever get to God.
it's like the palm of your hand, man-
Zoom! Comin' right at you.
- It's ineffable.
- Totally indescribable.
- Significant experience to share, I'll tell you that.
- We did pull pretty low.
- I tell you Johnny'd be just fine?
- Yeah! Damn first.
Johnny, just drop
your chute right there.
Good job.
Pack off your shoulders.
Kick it back, step out of it.
- I'll pack that for you, Bodhi.
- Okay, thanks.
Johnny, come here.
There's something you need to see.
Hop in.
Okay. If I can-
- What's this?
- This is an insurance policy.
It will sting a bit, but, uh,
it's for your own growth, brah.
Press play.
Fuck you'!
She is a wild one, isn't she,
Special Agent Utah?
Fuckin' dead man!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold it, man.
Think. Think it through, man.
I'm the only one
that knows where she is.
I'm the only one, so let me talk.
Let me talk.
- Talk.
- She'll be fine.
Rosie won't do anything as long as
I meet him at a certain place and time-
- Six hours from now.
- You call him right now...
and tell him to let her go!
Sorry. I can't do it, brah.
They're on the road, and where
they're goin', there are no phones...
so you are shit out of luck.
Oh, man.
I hate this, Johnny.
I really do. I hate violence.
Don't you see
that's why I need Rosie?
I could never do that, man. I could
never hold a knife to Tyler's throat.
She was my woman.
We shared time.
But Rosie is a...
mechanism, you know?
Once you set him in motion,
he will not stop.
He's, like, got this gift
of blankness.
But when 3:00 comes...
he will gut her like a pig
and try not to get any on his shoes...
and there is nothing
I can do about it unless I get there.
So I guess that makes us partners...
because we both have
the same goal:
to get me where I need to go, right?
We're wastin' time.
Oh, that's what I love
about you, Johnny.
You are just as sharp as a razor.
Murphy, take the plane down to
Santa Monica. Top off the tanks.
- All right.
- Okay, you guys, party time. Let's move it.
All right, we're on it.
All I'm asking for is 90 seconds
of your life, Johnny. That's it.
See, it's basic dog psychology.
If you scare them and get them
peeing down their leg...
they submit.
If you project weakness,
you draw aggression.
That's how people get hurt.
You see, fear causes hesitation...
and hesitation will cause
your worst fears to come true.
So it's simple.
You project strength
to avoid conﬂict.
Peace through superior firepower.
Oh.
There you go.
Can't have you walking through those
doors with your dick in your hand.
- I can't do this.
- Sure, you can.
Who knows? You might like it.
It's a killer rush.
Bodhi, this is your
fuckin' wake-up call, man.
I am an F.B.I. agent.
I know, man. Isn't it wild?
But, you know, that's what
makes it great, Johnny.
We can exist on a different plane.
We can make our own rules.
Why be a servant to the law
when you can be its master?
- Fuckin'-A.
- I love this fuckin' job.
Okay, 90 seconds, door to door.
It's a small price to pay
for someone who loves you.
She does, you know.
It's not her style to fall so hard.
I don't think she did with me.
Okay. Mr. Carter.
LBJ-
Mr. Nixon.
Well, sorry, Johnny.
Looks like you don't get
to be president.
I'm ready.
Rock and roll.
Everybody freeze!
Okay! On the ﬂoor! Now!
Get on the ﬂoor! Right now! Hold it.
Where you going?
Everybody down! Get down!
on the ﬂoor, asshole.
What's your problem? I blow out your
fuckin' kneecaps, you'll be on the ﬂoor.
Kick in the ass, ain't it, man?
Hey, look. We're on TV. Smile.
Gonna be a little hard to play
F.B.I. now though, huh?
Can we just get the goddamn money
and get out of here?
Nobody move!
Heads down, eyes down.
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen.
May I have your attention, please?
We are the Ex-Presidents.
And as you can see, we are, in fact,
robbing your bank.
So with a little cooperation,
I won't have to blow your heads off.
So I need just a couple of minutes
of your lives, and we're gone.
Dick. Dick, go to the vault.
Uh, you, Miss Jennings.
Would you be a dear and open the gate
for my associate now?
Mr. Duggan's got the keys.
Why are we going to the vault?
We never go to the vault.
Just do it!
Lyndon, go with him.
We're hittin' the vault, man.
Go! Go!
Who's Mr. fuckin' Duggan?
Mr. Duggan, do you want to open the vault,
or do you want me to do it?
Do whatever they want, Terry.
Take the fuckin' keys!
Take 'em!
Move it!
Open the damn door!
I'll fuckin' blow your
fuckin' head off. Move it!
Come on! Now!
- Get out of the way.
- Okay. All right.
Go for the back-The big bills.
Fuck it. We're goin'
in the fuckin' vault.
This is a bad idea.
Put your head on the ground.
Don't look at me.
You're blowin' it, man. You're
breakin' your own rules.
You're pulling too much time.
- Jimmy, how we doin'?
- Sixty-five.
What's happening?
Don't worry, man. It's fine.
It's fine. It's great.
Fuck! Fuck!
Hey. I'm a cop.
SQ?
- Oh, fuck.
- I'm a cop.
Oh, no. Don't.
- You got a gun on your ankle?
- Yeah.
When I make a move, you back me up.
Please don't. Don't.
You don't have to.
- You back me up.
- Don't do it.
Don't do anything.
Don't. Don't.
Please put it away.
Put it away.
Come on, hurry up!
Let's go! We gotta go! Let's go!
Fuckin' move.
Federal agent. Undercover.
Nobody fuckin' move!
Hang on. Hang on.
Hang on, little brother.
Come on. We're out of here.
We are out of here.
Hang on.
I'll get you out of here.
Hang on, little brother. Just hang on, man.
No, man. No.
Are you out of your fuckin' mind?
What's the matter with you?
You got what you want? Did you get
what you wanted? Come on!
You can't take him with.
Let's go.
Oh, goddamn it.
Who's in charge of this camera crew?
This is a crime scene area,
for Christ's sake.
- Get 'em the fuck out of here.
- Come on, out.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will
be used against you in a court of law.
If you so desire, an attorney
will be provided for you free of cost.
Now, do you understand these rights
I’ve just given to you, Utah?
Do you understand? You understand
the rights I’ve just read you, Utah?
Hey! He understands
his goddamn rights.
Jesus Christ, kid.
Are you okay? Here, stand up.
- Get these cuffs off him.
- Leave the cuff's on.
- Get 'em off
- Leave 'em on!
Oh, boy.
Your partner's an accessory
to murder, Pappas.
Utah, there are three dead people.
One of 'em's a police officer.
Let me show you something, pal.
How does that sit in your stomach, huh?
Take your hands off me right now.
Harp. Harp.
Listen. Look at me. Look at me.
Don't send him in with
the black-and-whites like some punk.
Let me ride him in.
Yeah, sure, Angelo. Why not?
That's why I put you two screwups
together to begin with.
You deserve each other, don't you?
You’re just as bad as he is,
only you're a little fatter...
a little slower
and a little more pathetic.
Christ's sake. It's like the blind
leading the blind with you.
Harp, I wanna tell you something.
I was in this bureau when you were
still poppin' zits on your funny face...
and jackin' off to the lingerie section
of the Sears catalog.
Is that right, Pappas?
Yes, that's right, Harp,
and there's one thing...
that I learned out of all these years
that you still haven't got.
Oh, yeah? Why don't you
astonish me, shit-face?
Respect for my elders.
- Plain and simple. Come on, kid, let's go.
- Holy shit.
- Let's get out of here.
- Up, please.
I know where they're going.
I figured you did.
Santa Monica Airport, fast.
- But we got one minor problem.
- What?
We can't arrest them.
- Or shoot them.
- What?
- Did you set the altimeter?
- One thousand.
- What?
Check the rigging, okay?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Fuckin' F.B.I.
I'm not armed.
- But you're not alone.
- Good guess.
There's a gun on you right now.
Where's Roach?
He's around somewhere.
So listen, Johnny, we
are in kind of a hurry.
What do you need?
You gotta tell me where she is.
Oh, and let my policy expire.
Good idea.
Look, Bodhi, man, people are dead.
The ride is over.
Oh, no, no.
I say when it's over.
The guy you killed
was an off-duty cop.
They'll nail you wherever you land.
There's a new thing called radar.
- Maybe you've heard of it.
- What is your-
Nathanial, get in there.
Get back in the cockpit. Move!
I know you, man. When they fall on you,
you won't back down.
They'll have to burn your ass
to the ground.
Uh-huh. And shit happens.
Look, you've got a death wish.
You wanna ride to glory, fine.
But don't take Tyler with you.
I'm begging you.
Tell me where she is,
and I walk away.
- You walk away?
- I walk away.
That is beautiful, Johnny.
Angelo! Don't fire!
They'll kill her! No!
Get out of the way, kid.
Goddamn it!
Damn.
No!
Oh, Jesus.
Jesus Christ.
Angelo.
- Fuck.
- They're comin', man.
- Just hang on, man.
- I'm really fucked up.
Just hang on.
It'll be all right.
Jesus Christ.
Come on.
I'm not ﬂyin' you guys
to San Felipe, man.
Get in the fuckin' plane.
Start those engines.
Oh, good. Tell him where we're going.
Let's go, man.
We are gonna ride this all the way,
Johnny, you and me, so let's go.
Get the fuck up!
Tyler's waiting.
Go, go, go!
Start the engines now.
Go!
Go! Go, go, go, go!
Rosie. Yo, Rosie.
This is Air Force One.
Do you read me?
Do you read me? Over.
Look, man, we've been over Mexico
for the last half hour.
Can I quit mowin' the lawn here?
Gettin' more bushes
in the wheels than I usually like.
Shut your mouth, and take it
to 4,000 feet on this heading, all right?
All right.
I don't think that's
such a good idea, man.
We'll-We'll pop up on their screens.
Doesn't matter.
We're almost there.
Just gotta get you
to a safe jump altitude.
Okay, let's get your rig on.
Hey, man, I'm cold. I'm really cold.
I got your jacket.
Here's your jacket.
Easy.
Oh, fuck!
I know, I know, I know. Easy.
Easy. One arm at a time.
No, man. No, no, no, no.
Johnny.
Throw me that money bag.
Now!
You're cold because all the blood
is running out of your body, Roach.
You're going to be dead soon.
I hope it was worth it.
Don't listen to him.
He’s just scared.
You just keep thinkin' about all
those senoritas and margaritas, gonna be...
nursing you back to health.
- Okay?
- What the fuck are you lookin' at?
Man. Fuck.
Okay, there you go.
Okay.
Rosie? Rosie, this is Air Force One.
Do you copy? Do you copy? Over.
Copy. We have a visual on you.
Tell him to release Tyler.
Do it! Do it now!
You won.
You got what you wanted.
What if your chute fails?
Cancel the order.
She served her purpose. Do it, man.
You owe me that much.
- Okay, you ready?
- Yeah.
On three. One, two, three.
Whoa, easy, easy. Little more. Little more.
Keep your chute clear. Okay?
Easy. Easy.
Okay. See you on the ground,
all right?
All right. I'll see you
in hell, Johnny.
Whoa!
I know it's hard for you, Johnny.
I know you want me so bad
it's like acid in your mouth.
But not this time.
Adios, amigo.
Fuck it!
- What-
- Pull the chute, Bodhi.
- You are crazy.
- Pull the fuckin' chute.
- Why don't you pull it?
- No games, Bodhi.
- Pull the cord now.
- Nah, you pull it.
Go ahead, Johnny. Pull it.
You gotta drop the gun, right?
If you use your other hand,
what are you gonna hold on with?
Pull it right now...
or I blow your fuckin' head off
and pull it myself.
That's the only way it's gonna happen,
my friend. Do it!
- I swear to God I will.
- Do it, man.
Do it or you’re gonna die, Johnny.
Six seconds.
We're gonna be meat wafﬂes.
- Five, four-
- You fucking crazy?
- Three, two-
- Pull it! Pull it!
- One!
- Shit! Shit!
Shit!
Jesus Christ, Bodhi.
Goddamn, you are
one radical son of a bitch.
I'm out of here, Johnny.
That knee again, huh?
Too bad. Looks like this time
you won't be gettin' your man.
This game we both lose.
Let her go.
Let her go!
- Johnny, I-
- Shh.
Some other time.
Oh.
Come on. We're out of here.
Yo, Johnny!
I'll see you in the next life.
We can't leave him here.
We gotta bury him.
There's no time, man.
The cyclone warning is now current...
for coastal areas
between Torquay and Cape Otway.
Experts are saying this
is potentially one
of the worst storms in
Australia's history.
Heavy rains will continue into the night,
with destructive winds...
reaching up to 150 kilometers per hour.
The center of the cyclone
is now expected...
to cross the coast between Bells Beach
and Fairhaven early tomorrow morning.
Residents are advised
to prepare for evacuation.
What do you wanna do now?
Get home and get out of this mess.
I'm freezing.
- Sorry, mate.
- Anybody been out there?
No one's been out.
No one's goin' out.
You gotta be fuckin' crazy, man.
Death on a stick out there, mate.
Lose something, brah?
Special Agent Utah.
I knew I could count on you.
I've been to every city in Mexico.
Came across an unclaimed
piece of meat in Baja.
Turned out to be Rosie.
Guess he picked a knife fight
with somebody better.
Found a passport of yours
in Sumatra.
Missed you by about a week in Fiji.
But I knew you wouldn't miss
the 50-year storm, Bodhi.
Yeah.
Too bad. You finally get your waves
and it's totally closed out.
Just waitin' for my set.
You gotta go down.
You crossed the line,
and people trusted you, and they died.
Yeah, it went bad.
Went real bad.
Life sure has a sick sense of humor,
doesn't it?
Still surfing?
Every day.
Come on, Bodhi.
It's time to go.
You know you gotta go back with me.
Sorry, my friend.
Come on.
No! No!
I told them...
you'd go quietly.
No!
You know there's no way
I can handle a cage, man.
I don't care.
You gotta go down.
It's gotta be that way.
Okay, man. Okay.
I'm screwed.
I'm gonna go to jail and I'll pay...
and Johnny Utah gets his guy.
Right? Good for you.
That's real good.
Gonna be a big hero now.
Look at it, Johnny. Look at it!
This is a once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity, man.
Just let me go out there. Let me get
one wave before you take me.
One wave.
I mean, where am I gonna go, man?
Cliffs on both sides.
I'm not gonna paddle to New Zealand.
My whole life has been
about this moment, Johnny.
Come on, compadre.
Come on.
All of you, this way.
Come on!
Va ya con Dios.
What the fuck, Utah!
What do you think you're doing?
You let him go.
No, I didn't.
No way.
Hey, the guy's nuts.
We'll get him when he comes back in.
He's not coming back.
♪ In my dreams see I'm on TV
♪ Get back exactly
who I wanna be ♪
♪ I'm sick and tired
of getting in my own way ♪
of everything I seem I know ♪
♪ Nobody rides for free ♪
♪ Don't stop and think
'cause I know where I stand ♪
♪ I'm on my way
No, you're not gonna change my plans ♪
♪ If you can break away
and see what I see ♪
♪ You'll understand
what's burning inside of me ♪
♪ I'm sick and tired of talking 'bout
good old days ♪
♪ I'm sick and tired
of everyone in my way ♪
- ♪ Nobody rides for free ♪
- ♪ Nobody rides ♪
- ♪ Nobody♪
- ♪ Nobody rides for free ♪
- ♪ Nobody)
♪ You've gotta pay to play
so don't you stand in my way♪
♪ 'Cause, baby)
♪ Nobody rides for free ♪
♪ Now the water was deep ♪
♪ The current was strong ♪
♪ You thought you could swim
but I guess you were wrong ♪
♪ You sink to the depths
of your misery ♪
♪ Maybe the past
will set you free ♪
- ♪ Nobody rides for free ♪
- ♪ Nobody rides ♪
- ♪ Nobody♪
- ♪ Nobody rides for free ♪
- ♪ Nobody)
♪ Nobody rides for free ♪
♪ Nobody rides ♪♪