Hideaki Ito Yumiko Shaku
PRINCESS BLADE
Shiro Sano
Yoko Maki Yoko Chosokabe
Naomasa Musaka Yutaka Matsushige
Shintaro Sonooka Takashi Tsukamoto
Yoichi Numata
Kyusaku Shimada
Producer
Taka Ichise
Inspired by the Comic by
Kazuo Koike & Kazuo Kamimura
Screenplay
Shinsuke Sato & Kei Kunii
Director of Photography
Taro Kawazu
Music
Kenji Kawai
Special Visual Effects
Shinji Higuchi
Action Director
Donnie Yen
Directed by
Shinsuke Sato
500 years had passed,
and still the country remained closed.
Cut off from the world,
knowing neither hope nor despair...
...the land breathed an air
of quiet stagnation.
Reformers driven to armed
rebellion...
...had been suppressed by the State.
The House of Takemikazuchi...
...were assassins hired
to suppress the rebels.
From ancient times...
...they had been guards to
the rulers of a neighboring kingdom.
That country, modernizing,
had overthrown its monarch.
Driven into exile,
they had reached this land.
Now they were a tribe of assassins...
...who would kill anyone
they were paid to.
The Takemikazuchi...
Mother...
Byakurai wants you.
Anka fled this morning.
He who flees the Takemikazuchi
is a traitor who will sell our secrets.
He's headed across Shikon Mountain.
But with his leg, he won't have
reached the old mine yet.
Yuki...
...take Kiri with you.
I'll go alone.
I'll go!
He'll slow me down.
Take me with you!
Byakurai told you to!
Could you really kill Anka?
Yes.
What if he begged?
I'd still kill him!
I don't think so.
Yuki... it's you...
I'm unarmed. Don't kill me.
Please...
Take my sword.
Tell them you killed me, OK?
- I see I'm no match for you any more, Yuki.
- Who are you?
My name is Kuka.
I served your mother.
I have something to tell you.
It's about who killed your mother.
You were told she died
in an attack...
...but it was Byakurai
who killed her.
- Liar!
- Byakurai killed your mother Azora...
...Princess Takemikazuchi.
You must either take revenge
and succeed to your mother's place...
...or leave.
Tomorrow you turn 20.
On that day a princess assumes
leadership of the Takemikazuchi.
You must choose either
to take over the House...
...or to leave it.
If you choose to leave,
come to the old mine.
I have delivered
the message of Azora.
Did Anka beg for his life?
Did my mother beg for hers?
What do you mean?
Your voice is shaking.
Your mind's racing.
Are you aware what you're doing?
Tell me.
Byakurai... did you kill my mother?
No.
Put up your sword, Yuki.
I'll overlook this.
I didn't want to tell you.
Your mother was killed because
she meant to betray us and flee.
Liar!
Lashing out won't help!
I have no choice. Die!
Wonderful news from
the Union Assembly.
Under our Great Leader,
we are winning the production war.
The Ministry of Consumption
reports...
...living standards have risen
20 per cent over the past year.
Celebrating this news the citizens
have come out into the streets...
...in a spontaneous parade.
Aya?
What is it?
Is this to kill me with?
You're a Takemikazuchi, aren't you.
Who hired you?
Talk.
Where are the others?
There's no one else coming.
I'm not here to kill you.
Liar.
You think I believe that?
Trust me.
Trust you?
You guys kill anyone you're paid to.
If I trust you I'll end up dead.
If I was after you...
...you'd be dead now.
Trust me?
- Doesn't that hurt?
- Yes...
...if you let it.
I saw a girl.
Where is she?
I'm alone here.
- That's my bed.
- Good night.
We lost her at the road
through the Forest Zone.
You came back to tell me that?
No.
Someone saw a truck.
We'll watch the road.
She'll be back.
She wants revenge.
- Someone told her.
- Who?
Hmm...
Yuki's 20 today.
Whoever told her about Azora
knew that, and what it means.
Kuka...
So you think she wants to kill you
to avenge Azora?
That means she'll come here.
If Kuka wanted to talk to Yuki,
where would he call her to?
To his home?
I'd find a better place than that.
How have you been?
It's Kidokoro.
I'm back. There's something
I want to talk to you about.
I'll come today.
No. I'll come to you...
...the day after tomorrow.
Roger.
I'll be waiting at the usual place.
A man had pledged with Azora,
heir to the House of Takemikazuchi.
He swore fealty to the House...
...but Byakurai framed him
as a traitor and killed him.
That man was my father?
You wouldn't remember.
You'd only just turned two.
There were still many
of Takemikazuchi blood.
Byakurai sought to
marry Azora himself...
...and make the House
of Takemikazuchi his.
But Azora refused.
Discouraged, she sought to bring
the Takemikazuchi to an end.
Byakurai found out and killed her.
Then everything changed.
Many were unhappy with Byakurai,
and tried to leave.
But only very few...
...managed to escape.
Princess Azora was killed here.
I'm sure she hoped you would
leave the Takemikazuchi.
She wanted you to succeed
where she had failed.
You need not take revenge on Byakurai.
The fate of the Takemikazuchi
is to disappear.
Princess Yuki...
Your mother had been tortured
almost to death...
...but the final blow came from me.
Kill me if you will.
My life since then has been one
of waiting for this day.
I offered to accompany
her to the next world...
...but she wouldn't allow it.
I was commanded
to tell you everything...
...when you reached 20 years of age.
If Princess Yuki were to do me
the honor of killing me...
Don't say that.
There's no point.
So it was you, Kuka...
Soma...
My, how you've grown!
By your leave...
Kuka!
This is what I wanted!
Princess Yuki! Don't die!
Kill me if you want...
...but don't raise your blades
against Princess Yuki!
That I can't promise.
Kuka!
When I was small...
...I was always happy.
I never dreamed...
...things would turn out like this.
You know why people thought
that way then?
It's because no one had any ideals.
Yes, people died when
we put a bomb in the Assembly.
But it was very effective.
You should be proud.
It was a holiday.
No one was supposed to be there.
You told me that.
Losses are inevitable.
You don't get something for nothing.
Mimura knew that.
His death wasn't wasted.
No one pays any attention
unless a few dozen citizens die.
I'd like to move on to the next
project.
Mr Sugimoto...
...didn't think so.
He called you while I was gone?
Last month.
He's been expelled.
I trust you.
We have to do whatever's necessary
to achieve our ideals.