At exactly 5:30, you will enter
the Net World cybercafe
As usual, most computers will
be occupied at that hour...
and the seat at the entrance
will be vacant
That's the seat you must take
You will at once go to the
website of Universal Bank
Without losing time,
you will get to work
By that time you will be in
the eyes of a few special people.
From my computer, I will keep
track as to where you're going
To go to the Current Account page
from the bank's home-page...
you'll have to type in the password.
The password is magic:3259
That's it. What happens next,
you very well know, Jai
All the best.
I love you, Neha.
ACP Suresh Chauhan. Let's go
Anna...?
- Yes, Jayant?
Switch on the news, Anna. The
internet guy's been caught
The godamn... - The cops caught
him only this evening
No one would imagine he's a crook.
Such a young pisser
Switch it on...
- I am, I am
This arrest proves that it's no
difficult task for the Mumbai police...
to track down a hi-tech criminal
This youth who staked a claim to
a huge booty of 5.5 billion...
will be presented
in court tomorrow..
..surprisingly such crimes
are on the rise
Get lost!
Get out of my way!
- Anna!
Cricket! They've made a stadium
out of my compound!
Give that to me. I'll
play cricket now
These guys will now give up our
profession and turn cricketers!
Whom did I ask to handle the case
of the computer hacking thief?
Me, Anna
You, you...!
all play, no work!
Die!
Cricket he plays!
The cops found him before you. And
you've been playing cricket!
Now listen! That cur won't be
presented in court tomorrow
He's coming here! You get that?
Yes, Anna. I do
Go ahead and bowl. Go on
Toss it up again
C'mon! Move it!
Move it!
He has arrived.
Move.
Go back side.
Move a side.
Come on, come with me.
Come.. drag him along.
Push this wretch inside.
Let me go!
Where do you think you're
going? Come on! - Let go of me.
Don't shoot! Don't!
C'mon, everyone get in. We
need to go back to the station.
Neha.. Neha.. I .. that..!
What are you doing here, Jai?
The cops. They're after me!
Anna's guys tried to kill me!
Well? Why are you surprised?
Didn't you take me by surprise too?
By forcing yourself on me?
Believe me, Neha.
I've never done such a thing,
Neha. I can even die for you!
I love you, Neha. I really love you.
I was so surprised when
I got to know..
..that you had swallowed
sleeping pills for Neha!
You weren't put to sleep...
but our luck surely woke up
Here you are. It'll open up
your brains and your heart
No?
Cheers!
We were hopelessly trapped
And suddenly, I met you outside the
Gurudwara after my fast was complete.
You wanted to die for Neha anyway
So we thought we'd turn
your death into..
..an opportunity of
life for ourselves
Don't take it badly, okay?
I hope you'll understand
that I've done..
..all this only for
the sake of my love
After all, you're a lover too
And God always helps lovers.
So He saved you for our sake
You have no idea what you have
done for a couple in love, Jai
Police!
Open the door!
Would I put to you trouble, if it was
so easy to escape from the police?
No. To be honest, you haven't been
wise in running away from the police
Jai, I am sorry.
You've done so much for us
So that door remains shut, as
long as we finish our drinks
So go on. Save your life
Police!
Open the door! Open it!
Yes, officer? - We're looking for a
man called Jai. Has someone come here?
I haven't seen anyone, no
Sorry to disturb you.
Poor boy
Gone blind? - Stop there...
What's going on? - I haven't
done anything. Listen to me...
Why are you pulling out the gun?
I haven't done anything, I say!
Let go of the gun! Let go, I say!
Get him! He shot me
and is trying to escape.
Catch hold of him.
I love you, Jai.
I can't believe someone
can love me so much
I owe them 60 million
Promise me, that you
will not rob the bank
Why talk about dying? Our
lives have just begun
Sorry, Jai.
'The one I loved, I have found'
'I've found peace, but
I've lost my heart'
'Your charms...'
'have bowled me over, my love'
'I have found the one I loved'
'I have found my peace,
but I've lost my heart'
'Your charms...'
'have bowled me over, my love'
'The kohl in your eyes drives me
crazy. Your beauty drives me mad'
'It's your gaze that guides
me through the ways of love'
'Let me sway, let me kiss
you, here's our chance'
'I'm sure you don't know...'
'this is the kick you
get out of my love'
'Hold me to your lips, my love.
Quench the thirst of your heart'
'In roses, we live. There's
not a thorn in sight'
'My desire for you
awakens an ache..'
'you're the one who
lights up my breath'
'The hues of love...'
'shakes up the world'
Two months later.
You got the 60 million?
Hello! - Congratulations
on a new life, Neha
Vikram...
- What happened?
It's Jai!
There's no one, Neha
Believe me Vikram,
it was a call from Jai!
Jai's dead. Dead. It's two
months since he died
Hey... relax, honey. Go to sleep
Vikram, could you give
me the towel please?
Thanks.
Keep with it you forever. Remember,
I'm always with you
Vikram, open the door
Happy anniversary, my love.
You almost killed me!
- Why?
C'mon, let's go, celebrate!
It's exactly four
years since we met
I didn't even realise how time flew
by, while I've been in love with you
The dress I kept upstairs,
did you change it?
Me...? No, I didn't
The ring? The towel? Did you...?
- What are you talking about, Neha?
I was out.
- He's gotten into the house!
Sweetheart, not a soul
knows we're here
It was his call last night.
And the ring..
..and the dress was
given to me by Jai!
I am telling you,
Jai is still alive.
He's not dead. He's not dead!
Relax! Relax!
Nothing can happen to you,
so long as I'm alive
Love you!
I've lost again.
- Again...?
So you want more money?
How much?
- So much
Good luck. - Thank you.
I need 60 million rupees
I desperately need 60 million.
Neha's in deep trouble, sir!
The underworld will kidnap her if
she doesn't have 60 million, sir
You're a large-hearted man, sir...
- Now listen to me, you sonofa...
No, I don't want to listen to
anything. Just save my Neha, sir
I need 60 million, sir. When shall
I come to collect the money?
That's the problem.
I know you won't show up
Once. Just once, show
yourself to me...
and I'll solve all your problems
Honey...
we've reached home
I lost a big amount
You are angry, no?
No, it's all right.
I love you. - I love you, too.
Where are you going?
- I'll just switch on the light
Well? Scared, are you?
They fear, who have malicious
intent. You forgot so soon?
I have loved you like crazy.
Now I am going to
hate you like crazy.
You take so long to
open the door? - Hey, dude.
Clothes, and the works! There's
nothing more to shop for
I tell you something.
If you stay here any longer,
I'm gonna die of jealousy
Shut up.
Have you eaten?
Yeah, thanks.
Get ready soon, we're going
to the Rain Forest Café
Count me out.
- Your friend is strange
He's always refusing
No wonder he turned down
a lovely lady like you
What lovely? I'm plain stupid.
Had I not seen Vikram
and Neha at the mall...
I wouldn't have informed
Govind kaka
And you wouldn't have taken the
trouble and come here all the way
At least you'd have forgotten
that fraud of a girl
It is unbelievable.
You escaped the Indian police,
wasted your lifetime's savings...
got seriously injured, hid inside
the cargo space of a ship...
and journeyed for two whole months
You even defeated death
to fight with life, buddy
Man, this is a true
love story. - Love story?
Every love story has two names.
But mine has only one
Mine.
And I have pledged that name
to ruin and destroy her.
This is no love story.
This is a hate story.
Thank God that you are enjoying.
May I come with you?
Hello! - So, freak? - You..!?
Well? Does it hurt?
Had I wished, you'd have
found Neha's corpse
What do you want? Come
to the bloody point.
My life.
- What if I refuse?
What if Neha dies?
Do as I tell you. It's
in your interest
All right, Jai. Finally
you've defeated me
What am I to do?
- That what you did to me before
Confess to your crime
at the police station
Tell them that you are
the hacker, not I
How long can you use me as a shield
to save yourself from the cops?
The longer you talk, the sooner
I can trace you, swine
Go on
You started the game, I'll finish it
And yes... I'm not paying
you for this. Get it?
Yes, I get it
I got you. - Good.
Got you!
We've made a terrible
mistake, Vikram
We chose the wrong guy for this job
He won't spare us. He's going to
chase us till we breathe our last
He won't let us live,
Vikram. He won't
He won't let us live
only if he lives
Jai, this time I get you...
you're dead
Phoning me, eh?
You will whistle, eh?
You'll enter our house, huh?
Last time, you landed in a hospital
Tonight, you are going
to the crematorium.
Found Jai?
Yes
Where's he?
- In the car
Babu Anna, 'your' computer hacker
is in Cape Town, alive
Is it? - I have sent him
to Elizabeth Hospital
He's all yours now
Congratulations on starting
afresh, Neha
It's my duty to take care of
you as long as I breathe
I was madly in love with you.
Now I'm going to die for you
Have you found the 60 million?
Honey...
have soup
Drink? - No.
Are you ok?
Sure?
I'll get a sweater
No! NO!!!
Help!
Somebody help me!
Jai, you are making a grave mistake
Have you gone mad?
- Yes, I have.
I went mad the moment you
stepped into my life
You looked at me, I went wild
You spurned me, I
went mad with disappointment.
You accepted me,
I went mad with joy
And now I'm completely deranged
I can do anything with
you right now
But I won't do that, because
I'm not like you
You wanted my life, didn't you?
You should've asked me just once.
I'd have given it up with a smile
Help! Help! - Shut up!
Look at me!
You've ruined my life!
No! I'm not going to cry for you!
Treacherous woman! Forget love.
I will not even cuss you
No expletive can ever define you
C'mon.. come.
Let me go
Open the door, please
You have a table for Jai Malhotra?
Yeah, over there.
Sit
No fuming, please
Anger is bad for health
Especially for Neha's health
Swine!
- Did I ask your name?
Drink it up
It'll cool down your heart and mind
Shut up!
Where is she?
Still alive
But after two hours... can't say
Should something happen to her...
What do you want?
- Your arrest
Confess to your crime
I agree
Good boy.
When will you surrender?
- When will you release Neha?
Surrender, and I'll let Neha go
Let Neha go, and I'll surrender
I want to meet her one last
time, before I surrender
Ok.
She's inside
My mind is ruined waiting
in these ruins
Welcome
I'll settle this for good.
The final time.
Babu Anna? Here!?
- Come on
Hey, wait.
Ok.
Hot stuff! Really
You make me feel like
I'm watching a movie
Let alone steal, one would
even kill for her
What kind of a man do you need?
Tell me. What do you see in a man?
I'd tell you only if you were a man
What daring! What guts!
Just like these guys? Right?
If she falls she'll go wasted, no?
As soon as I traced the hospital,
I put my men on guard
But he vanished.
I came here all the way from India,
still no trace of him
But somehow my white dogs here..
sniffed this slink out
You look different on TV.
Fiddling with the computer
you tried to fiddle with me
Tell me, how will you
return my money?
On-line transfer? Or cash?
I don't have the money
Then?
He has the money. He's the hacker.
- He's raving
No, it's the truth. He stole
the money and set me up
He is lying. - I am not
lying, I am telling the truth.
Stop raving.
- I'm not raving
Mustn't fight in a foreign country
Brings our country to disrepute
You didn't steal the money?
- No
Then you are of no use to me
Listen to me... if you kill me, you
will never get your money back
Because he'll thrust the
blame on me. - Right
So I'll blow him up
No, not him. With him
goes your money too
Then there's only one
way out. The fish!
No wait.
If you kill her, he'll
seal his lips forever
Then am I to blow myself up?
To hell with the money!
No!
Babu Anna! He's right
I'm the hacker
You are on track now
Come with me
See... everything is
set. Get cracking
Goodness! It goes over my head
During my time, it was simple.
Loot at gunpoint
Very easy
Processing will take around 5-7
minutes. In the meantime...
I'd like to fix him
Scoundrels! You conned me
You swallowed my money! I'll
make you puke it all now
Bloody dogs!
I'm not sparing you!
I'll carve you! I'll finish you off
Thanks - What thanks?
I saved you only..
..because your life means
freedom to me. Come now.
You'll die
Let's see
Stay down there, you will live
Stay right there! If you
get up this time...
I'll dispatch you
I want my life back!
Give me my life back.
Neha and you ruined my life
I will kill you.
You will send me to jail, eh?
The two of you made
a mockery of my love
Kill him, Vikram. Finish him off!
You are finished.
You have two or at the
most five minutes on you.
Don't be mean, Vikram. Poor thing.
You forgot? Last time
too we thought the same
Why did you return? Who needs you?
True. How long will this go on?
I keep the strike, while
you keep losing
You are such a loser, Jai.
Actually, he's not
at fault, Vikram
He loves me so dearly that
it's hard to just quit
Besides, he did all
this for my sake
So sweet of him, no?
But you know what?
I feel nothing for you
No love...
neither empathy...
nor mercy
I am sorry, Jai.
Feel nothing? Do you
even have a heart?
You keep the strike,
while I keep losing
Let's try that one last time. Let's
see who strikes and who dies
No! Neha! No!
My love...
The slut deserved it
Yesterday she left me,
today she deserted you
But I must say...
she left after settling our scores
Yesterday, I had love. No money
Today, you have money. No love
5.5 billion is your stake...
but every day you will remember me
Enjoy!
At a time when the world buckles
under treachery, corruption...
communal disharmony and greed..
..philanthropy and humanity
still survives somewhere
Which has been proved
by a mysterious angel
This mysterious person has
donated nearly 5 billion...
to the Missionaries
of Charity in Mumbai
In an exclusive interview, the
Chief Minister told Zee News that...
the country needs such compassionate
and benevolent citizens...
who, unhesitatingly perform their
duties towards the society...
by staying low profile and
have no political motives
Though nobody knows who the
magnanimous person is...
one thing is certain. He will
receive the blessings of millions