Yuan, the Mongolian Empire ruled
by the descendants of Genghis Khan.
controlled China, but anti-Yuan
forces were growing in number.
Taewon Entertainment
Associate Producer: Yoo, Jeong Ho
Co-Producer: Park, Sung Keun
With the assistance of China Film
Co-production Corp & Shanghai
Film Studio
Financing & Distribution
Cinema Service, Co., Ltd.
Shin, Hyun June
Kim, Hee Sun
Jung, Jin Young
Jang, Dong Jik
Original Story: Kim, Hye Rin
Producer: Jung, Tae Won
Directed by Kim, Young Jun
Mother!
My name is Sullie. Sullie.
And you?
Jinha.
My name is Sullie. Sullie.
And you?
Jinha.
Here. From today, you can
practice with a real sword.
My father is finally coming.
But what's the use?
Mother is so sick...
Whatever may happen
stay with me always.
You said I start with
the sword today?
Out of the way!
Insolence!
Leave him. We must press on.
Yes, General.
A fine-featured lad.
What is your name?
I... I'm of lowly birth
and have no family name.
My name is Jinha, sir.
Father, we should go now.
We should be at her deathbed.
Jinha, bring me some water.
We're going to Shao Xing.
Mother's body isn't even cold yet.
I'll ask the officials to
take care of the funeral.
I'm not leaving.
You're my daughter.
You go with me.
I don't want to!
Let go of me!
Let go!
Sullie!
Jinha!
Brother!
Don't!
If he dies, so do l!
Jinha! Jinha!
I'm sorry.
I have to leave.
I won't leave you.
Listen! Every full-moon day, I'll wait
at Yu Hua Pagoda in Shao Xing.
You have to remember.
Yu Hua Pagoda!
Shao Xing. Taruga Manor.
Young lord, just as I heard
you do carry a joke too far.
But isn't it so?
I can't find any serviceable women.
No beauties like Yi, Su Yon of old...
Did it cost too much for you to get
beauties like that, General?
My lord.
What's the matter? Drink up!
Ah, do you lack music?
Who dares interrupt my music?
Quite pretty for a Mongol's servant.
What's your name?
A proud one, aren't you?
Don't you want to change your lot?
Quiet!
You should have slapped him
some more while you were at it!
Fool! No one in Shao Xing can survive
after provoking a Namgung lord!
Why don't you just crush them
like the House of Yu in North Ho?
Shut up!
Why should descendants of the
great Mongols kowtowto that
kind of Han scoundrel?
I said shut up!
Do not mention the Namgung lords
or the House of Yu ever again!
It's been six months already.
Let's leave for Shao Xing now.
Forget about Sullie!
Uncle!
Once you perfect
the Bichun Secret Arts,
there are things that you must do.
I will go to Shao Xing
with or without you.
You almost got yourself killed!
Would Sullie even look at you?
She may be a concubine's child,
but she's the daughter of a rich
and powerful Mongol general!
Wealth and glory are
stretched out before her.
Look at yourself!
You have nothing!
Stop it!
We had a hard time finding you.
Give us the Bichun Secrets!
You'll have to kill me if you want
even a glimpse of it.
Uncle!
Jinha...
You must be exhausted.
Why did you insist on coming here?
There is something I must show you.
This was once the greatest manor
in North Ho.
The great House of Yu.
The master swordsman Yu, Jangok
was neither a Mongol nor a Han.
He was from Koryo (ancient Korea),
a Koryo.
He was a hostage from Koryo
the Crown Prince's bodyguard.
His wife Yi, Suyon, a Koryo woman
was the greatest beauty in North Ho.
The bloody murders were said to be
a strike against anti-Yuan forces.
But actually they were after
the ultimate Secrets held by Yu.
Master Yu!
Go, quickly!
Most tragic of all was Mistress Yi.
After a desperate escape,
she had to abandon the last Yu heir.
And tragically...
Why are you saying this, Uncle?
Young Master! I am not your uncle.
I'm Master Yu's swordman, Kwakjung.
Once you perfect
the Bichun Secret Arts,
you must revenge your parents
so that they can rest in peace.
I only regret that I cannot
reveal who the enemy is...
Forgive my disloyalty over the years.
Uncle!
I heard you come here
every full-moon day.
If you're going back soon
why not join me?
I must wait here until sunset.
What do you mean?
Refuse his proposal of marriage?
He's not my man.
I won't let you behave like a child
as you did in Shan Mei!
Is it the Bichun Secrets
you're after?
How about we stand-ins
fight with each other?
Thank you.
I hope I wasn't interfering.
I am Namgung Junkwang.
What is your name, great swordman?
Jinha.
I am Yu, Jinha.
Brother Yu, you remind me of someone.
Someone no longer of this world.
I myself have only seen her portrait.
Yi, Suyon of the old House
of Yu in North Ho.
When I was a boy
she was my first love.
You don't talk much, Brother Yu.
You seem to have traveled a lot.
Tell me some stories of the world.
Have you ever loved a woman
such that it drove you mad?
I adored her at first sight.
After a lifetime of wandering
a light has come to brighten my life.
I knew it the moment I saw her.
Does she love you, too?
I will make her love me.
Show this when you visit me
and you will be served courteously.
Be sure to drop by once
your business is finished.
I would like to hear
more of the world from you.
So you will.
Excuse me, can you tell me
where Taruga Manor is?
I think it's on the main street.
And the Namgung lord's manor?
Those two houses...
you must be going to the wedding!
A wedding?
You haven't heard?
It's the talk of the town!
Lord Namgung's only son is
marrying the daughter of
General Taruga's concubine.
What a great distinction
for a concubine's daughter!
Where do you think you're going?
Have you forgotten that young
Lord Namgung is coming today?
That is none of my concern.
You will see to him courteously!
This was not my decision.
Is accepting me so difficult?
My lord, you and I are worlds apart.
Please do not mock me.
I never thought to beg
for love in such a manner.
Please accept my proposal.
Are you sure this Yu, Jinha is
of the North Ho House of Yu?
Yes!
I should have recognized him
in Shan Mei.
But I'll end his life yet.
He defeated the men I sent.
He used the Bichun Secrets.
Shut up!
Do you think he knows
about the Yu Manor incident?
Don't worry. If we dispose of him
and gain the Bichun Secrets
we will rule supreme.
Isn't that so, my dear in-law?
So this was the
Yu Hua Pagoda promise?
Defeat me.
Jinha
Take good care of her.
Search everywhere!
Yes, sir!
Young lord, this is
not a place for you to be.
My betrothed is missing!
Who is the scoundrel?
I've told you several times
you've misunderstood.
Tell me who the scoundrel is!
The son of the ruined North Ho Yu's.
His name is Jinha.
He has taken my daughter
as vengeance, no doubt.
You mean the scoundrel
is Yu, Jinha?
Jinha!
Father will kill you! Run!
My lady!
Let go of me!
You're not different from them!
You're the one who should
atone for your crime, Father!
Wasn't it enough to destroy
the House of Yu in North Ho?
Now you want to kill Jinha, too?
Quiet!
Our fates are ill-crossed.
The General seems to want
the Bichun Secrets.
But not l. I can't endure
another man in her heart.
Defeat me. Then you can live.
If you are at a disadvantage
jump to the side.
We'll shoot arrows.
I don't want to fight you.
Sullie doesn't love you.
I will marry him.
Are you going to Ping River?
What did you say?
I said, are you going to Ping River?
Yes.
It'll take a while this time
I'm worried about you.
I don't know how Shao Xing
got so infested with assassins.
The other day, an imperial envoy
was killed in the street.
Mongolians are afraid to
go out at night.
Don't worry about me.
Just have a good trip.
I'll come back as soon as possible.
Don't change the subject
Lord Namgung!
Do you think the Namgungs who
were favored by the Emperor
will be left unscathed?
I haven't lived to this age
without learning that much.
But I cannot invest in
war funds again.
There is nothing left for Mongol
glory but to withdraw from
history's foreground
and go back to the prairie.
Merchants don't trust any rulers.
We only believe in
the ruling principles of life.
Since you're here
why don't you see your daughter?
Still no news from Lai?
None after a sighting
at the Tai Yang Lake battle.
I'm leaving. Say goodbye
to Lord Namgung for me.
You must be stronger than ever now
and live undaunted!
Forget about the
other half of your blood...
We won't see each other again...
You've grown old, General.
Do it!
Let's escape, Mother.
Let's escape somehow,
and go to Ping River
where Father is.
I'm going to revenge myself
on that killer, whatever it takes.
We've secured all of
Namgung's estate.
And, sir, this...
We found it in the storage room.
We saw the title
Yi, Suyon of the House of Yu.
It seems to be
your mother's portrait, sir.
You're dismissed.
Mother! Mother!
Go, quickly! Go, right now!
I said go!
Are you so undisciplined
that you fumble over a trifle?
You're the one who let the
Mongol girl stay in her room!
I should be entitled to that much.
And the child?
The boys are after him
so don't worry about the brat.
Brother, he's awake!
Where am l?
Who are you?
The wound isn't deep.
Jinha... what about Sung?
I beg you. Let him live!
He is everything to me,
the only reason I kept living...
Enough!
Stop it!
Jinha, please...
He's our son, yours and mine!
Long years as a powerful man's wife
has made you this cunning, hasn't it?
The Ping River