Executive Producer:
KANG Woo-suk
Producers:
LEE Kwan-soo KIM Sang-jin
KIM Seung-woo
KIM Jung-eun
BYUN Hee-bong KIM Hae-ok
JEONG In-han KIM Young-0k
JANG Hyun-seong KIM Kyung-beom
Special Guest SEONG Ji-ru
No Litter!
You bastard! That trash!!
You little shithead!
It said 'No Litter'!!
You human trash! Stop!
You're so dead.
What are you doing up there?
Me? I'm waiting for someone..
Written & Directed by JANG Hang-joon
He should be here soon..
After a good lap around my
neighborhood..
- I feel incredibly refreshed.
- I see.
Now, let's talk some more
about your work.
Your latest work
is a masterpiece.
I brought it with me and,
I must say the cover
is simply beautiful.
It's a photo of your late father
with your mother
They look lovely together.
How was your husband's funeral?
He broke my heart again and again,
but, none of that matters now.
My father? Well..
He was a child prodigy.
He finished '1000 Characters Text' by
age 5 and 7 Chinese Classics' by age 10.
His father was a scholar
of Chinese Classics.
Chinese Classics scholar my ass!
His father was a pimp.
And, even as a kid,
he had no interest in studying.
He only liked girls.
When he was 14..
he did it with a young maid
who worked at his house.
I was told he never had
any interest in women.
He was an unsusceptible man
towards women.
I guess I'm like
my father in that way.
He was a hard worker.
He studied all his life
to go to university.
When he was finally admitted
he only slept couple hours
a night to study even more.
He never studied!
His father's pimp money
was his entrance ticket.
And, of course,
he had no interest in education.
He was too busy getting laid.
When did you find out about
his other family?
When Seon-guk was 2
we went to
visit him in Seoul.
And there he was with his
4 other children.
- Bastard!
- He'll go to hell.
But, for some reason..
he really liked spring.
In the winter,
he'd never go outside.
But, when the warm spring breeze
starts to blow,
he'd go out and wander around
like a person under a spell.
SPRING BREEZE
Damn it!
- Teacher
- What?
Can we turn on the heater?
It's freezing today.
You didn't wear your thermals?
No.
Do you pay for the heating?
I told you to wear your thermals.
I'm sorry.
Oh, teacher
- Now what?
- You have to call the publisher.
Ok.
He said, if you don't submit the
manuscript by this month..
I heard you!
The new tenant is moving in today.
- New tenant?
- Yes.
I didn't rent out any rooms.
Is GOH Ki-nam your father?
Yes.
He signed a contract through
our real estate agency.
You see that registered seal?
The contract is legit.
I think the house is too big
for just one person.
You should hide your
registered seal somewhere safe.
So, who's moving in?
Here she comes.
This is your landlord.
Hi. I'm Hwa-jung.
It's very nice
to meet you.
Hello.
A respected man like myself
can't live with
a vulgar woman like her.
Tell her to look for another place.
- I can't.
- Why not?
Your father already
took the lease deposit.
Lease deposit?
How much?
30 million won.
30 million!
This is the room, right?
What the...
Excuse me. But, you didn't vacate
the 2nd floor room.
- The 2nd floor room?
- Yeah
That's the room I rented.
Please vacate it for me.
God damn it!
Wow!
This room can be rented out.
Dad, why are you doing this?
Male elephants start mating when
they're 10 years old.
For Asian elephants, the mating
season lasts for a month per year.
After only a few days with their
female partners, the mating ends.
Yes, she's got the contract
and the receipt.
No, he signed it when he was
alive and took the deposit.
I'm not talking about me.
- I'll get it.
- Why would I lie about that?
So, is there a way or not?
Can he kick her out?
What?
- Welcome!
- Nice house!
Bye.
What are those?
Oh! Come and
say hi to my landlord.
Mr. GOH,
am I interrupting you?
My friends are here for a housewarming
party and they want to say hi.
They don't have to..
Everyone! This is my landlord and
that's Hee-gu.
- Hello!
- Hi!
- Your landlord is very handsome.
- He's exactly my type!
- You're so lucky!
- The one with glasses is so cute!
Look at him smile!
Go and tell those dumb vulgar
species to be quiet.
- OthenNise, get out of my house!
- Yes, sir.
Who is that?
- Hee-gu!
- May I speak with you?
Sure. Come in
- Wait.. First, have a drink with us!
- C'mon. Just one drink.
No. I'mjust gonna..
What the hell happened to him?
Why is it getting louder?
"Clap your hands and sing"
"Everyone look this way!
Shake your body"
- "Champion"
- "Scream your head off"
- "Let the music take over you"
- "Champion"
- "You! You! You! You! Champion"
I'm sorry.
Can I talk to you for a sec?
Me? Ok
I'll be right back.
I'm coming.
- What's up?
- Let me ask you for a favor.
- Sure.
- I have to work. So, can you be quiet?
What do you do?
none of your business. If you
wanna drink, drink quietly or go out
Alright. We'll go out then.
Can Hee-gu come with us?
Go. Go
and get wasted with this
coffee shop girl. Ok?
How did you know I work
at a coffee shop?
Isn't that obvious?
- Wow! You really can drink!
- Thank you.
When I'm in my top condition,
I can easily finish 12 bottles.
Uhm..
What's Mr. GOH like?
- My teacher?
- Yes.
He's a bastard. Bastard!
A real mean bastard.
He's got no friend
and no cell phone.
He still uses a beeper.
He says his work is all that
matters in his life,
but I don't think so.
He likes money! Money!
Fuck you, GOH Seon-guk!
What does he do?
- He writes..
- Writes? He's a writer?
- How did you know?
- You just said he writes.
Wow. That's totally cool!
- What kind of stories?
- A novel.
Right now, he's writing a love story
but it's not going well.
A love story?
That's my specialty.
That's what I know the best.
Talking about love stories..
do you wanna hear
a killer love story?
Damn it's hot!
Shit!
Who turned on the heater?
Is she out of her mind?
Good morning.
- Did you turn this on?
- Yes. I did.
Who said you could
turn on the heater?
No one did. I just turned
it on because it was cold.
I get cold easily.
What's up there?
Uh.. nothing.
Just don't ever
turn it on again.
Why not?
Because it's broken. Broken!
- If you're cold, wear thermals.
- I think it works fine
You don't believe me?
Hello? Hi.
Our heating system broke
No, it doesn't work.
Yes. My address is..
This is broken, too.
I just got it fixed but..
Don't use the phone
or the heater!
ﬁCome and talk to meﬁ
ﬂ Take about anythingﬁ
ﬂ Let's have a drink tonightﬁ
E! can listen to anything you sayﬁ
Hi. I'm Hwa-jung,
the new girl at
Forget Me Not' coffee shop.
Stop by whenever
and I'll be your friend.
Just think of me as your
granddaughter. See you soon.
E I miss youﬁ
E! can fall in love with youﬁ
Hi!
- You're super pretty!
- Super thanks!
Bye.
Forget Me Not Coffee Shop
What's the next question?
Question #7, across..
- Author of "Gone with the Wind."
- I know this one.
What's her name..
Wait.. Maybe it's Clark Gable.
- Which one?
- I'm not sure..
It is her....
Ah! She's the one who tells
the story, so.. Vivien Leigh.
Wow. You are so smart!
Vivien.. Leigh..
How about this one?
Something-egg.
Type of cooked egg.
- 'Fried' egg?
- No. I don't think that's right.
It's gotta be
more difficult word.
How about 'sunny side up?'
- Isn't it 'scrambled?'
- 'Scrambled..?'
Right! Ithink
that's the right answer!
'Scrambled.'
Wait.. The ruler of Catholic Church
is 'Pope', right?
Then it has to start with 'P.'
P?’ Word that Starts with 'P'?
Po.. Pa.. Pu..
hey
Hi.
Are you also here to report
your new address?
- Rice
- Rice?
We came here to receive rice.
I see.
Is he your brother?
Did you eat?
Eat as much as you want.
Come by whenever
you're hungry. Ok?
Can we come
with our grandma?
Grandma?
Of course.
Hi, Mr. GOH!
Kids, say hello to Mr. GOH.
He's my housemate.
Hello.
Who are they?
They're my new friends.
Eat. I got plenty of food. Eat.
So, what's your problem?
I..
I met someone.
Again?
There's this new beauty salon.
I went there to get a hair cut..
and that's how I met her.
It must've been fate..
Teacher, he's ready.
Hello.
She started to gently caress my
hair with her long slender fingers.
Every living cell in my body was
being awakened from a long sleep
In my head, they were celebrating
their freedom from
the monotonous cycle of life!
Pow! Pow!
After the most ecstatic experience
of my life, as I was about to leave,
she said to me with
her sweet voice,
Come again.
And I said to her,
Yes. I'll be back.
You're pitiful.
My heart is still pounding..
- So, did you go back?
- Yup.
I dyed my hair black today.
Do you like it?
No
What did the publisher say?
He's really pissed
about the delay.
Why don't you return
the advance payment?
I already used it
to build my house.
The only source of income I have
is to finish this book.
Or a sudden rise in sale of
.
- Can I use your phone
- Still using a beeper?
You're so cheap. Get yourself
a cell phone, will you?
Give it.
Nobody uses a beeper anymore.
No, there are 180,000 beeper users
in this country.
180,000!!
Hello, sir?
No
I wasn't yelling at you.
I swear I wasn't yelling.. No, sir.
So why didn't you deliver
it on time?
What?
I said 'by 9 o'clock!'
You delivered it
at 10 o'clock!
Why did you do that? I didn't say
'by 10 o'clock!
What? What did you say to me?
I'm your customer, asshole!
I want to talk to your boss!
Put him on the phone, now!
Please may I speak to your boss?
I'll speak to him directly.
Hello?
If you keep doing business like this
I'm gonna kick your ass!
What?
You want a piece of me?!
UFO!
Look! UFO!
- Get him!
- Get him! Get him!
He's here!
- did you say you were in a track team?
- Shut up.
He was too fast.
- You lost him?
- Yes.
- Sir, going to see the publisher?
- Yeah.
Aren't you gonna take your car?
Are you gonna pay for the gasoline?
Did you wear your thermals?
- You're not cold, right?
- No, sir.
It's a story I heard.
I thought it was
quite interesting.
Please take a look at it.
Wasn't it supposed to be
finished by last October?
It's already February.
I'm sorry.
That's not what I want to hear.
How much of it is finished?
It's almost done.
I'm very sorry.
I said, that's not
what I want to hear.
You're really
pushing me this time.
I'm really sorry.
I said stop saying that.
I even gave you the advance
payment like you asked.
Don't you feel
guilty about that?
If I were you, I would finish the
book as quickly as I can.
I'm sorry.
- Damn it! I said stop saying that.
- Then, what should I say?
You made me feel like shit and I
can't even say I'm sorry?
- Should I say 'thank you' instead?
- You're crazy!
Yes, I'm crazy! I'm so fucking
sorry that I went crazy!
I'm crazy! So what! What!!
Crazy bastard!
You don't feel sorry at all!
Look at yourself!!
You said don't say 'I'm sorry!'
Finish it by this month or return
the advance, plus the penalty fee.
Or else, they'll sue me.
Why did you act like that to him?
You don't wanna mess with him.
- How much of it is finished?
- Let's talk about something else.
What's going on with
that beauty salon girl?
I was just there today.
I can't stop
thinking about her.
You know..
love is like hair.
Even though you cut it,
it keeps growing and growing.
Shut up.
Just out of my curiosity,
what happened with that stalker?
- Who? Yong-shik?
- No, not him. The one from Chunan.
- Soo-chun?
- No, not that crazy bastard.
Sang-won?
Last girlfriend I had was..
During '88 Seoul Olympic.
- 1988? During JEON administration?
- No. During ROH administration.
- Why?
- she nagged me to go to the closing day
Before that?
No.. The one who lived with you in
that house with blue front door.
The one with hair like this..
- Oh, Hyun-doo!
- Yes, him!
Are you serious?
While the political
power changed 4 times,
you've only had 1 girlfriend?
You gotta have at least one for
every new administration.
Tell me the truth. Have you ever had
a sleepless night because of a woman?
- No.
- And you're writing a love story?
Why not?
Love is all fiction.
- I told you to buy more beer.
- I didn't think we'd run out.
Is the heater really broken?
That's what he said.
Can I help you?
Isn't this the residence of Mr. GOH?
Yes. But he's not here.
I see.
May I ask who you are?
I'm Hwa-jung.
I moved into the 2nd floor.
- And she's my super close friend.
- I see.
We are writer buddies of
Mr. GOH.
We dropped by for a drink with him.
Would you ladies like to join us?
Of course!
What are you doing? We shouldn't..
Hello? Yes, sir.
How do you do?
Mr. GOH?
His beeper doesn't work
here in the basement.
He's right here with me
Hold on.
It's the publisher.
- Asshole...
- Hello, sir.
I apologize about
this afternoon.
No, I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
Yes. Sure..
Why didn't you tell me about that
amazing story when you came by?
Excuse me?
Passionate but
corrupted love!
It sucked me in
from the beginning.
So, what happens next?
Everyone wants to know.
What do you mean..
That synopsis you left in our office.
The synopsis?
It's a story I heard.
I thought it was quite interesting.
Please take a look at it.
Fine! Take it! Take it all!
This is going to be
the next bestseller!
Thank you. You're too kind.
I get behind schedule a bit,
but you know I deliver the goods.
Where are you now?
At the office?
Thank you!
Mr. GOH, you're home!
Have a seat.
- For our trip to Daeguanryung!
- Cheers!
Daeguanryung?
Oh, we forgot to tell you.
A week after next week, we're going
to the Daeguanryung farm. All of us.
- How about you?
- Sure. I guess..
Let's drink a toast, again!
- For Daeguanryung trip!
- Cheers!
Teacher, are you awake?
The story..
Did you come up with it?
It's Hwa-jung's story.
- What?
- Hwa-jung made it up.
Did you read it? Isn't it good?
She didn't tell me the whole story.
Should I ask her for the rest?
- No, don't.
- No?
Don't!
Yes, sir.
I'll get your breakfast ready.
That can't be.
She's only a dumb coffee shop girl.
This can't be! She's
stupid and vulgar and..
Then what am I? I'm a writer.
A writer!!
Impossible!!
I think your PR really worked.
- It's been full house since this morning.
- Really?
Our comrades from
last night are here, too.
- Hi!
- hi
- How are you this morning?
- Very well.
I came for a cup of coffee with
someone special..
Oh my....
- Get me a cup of coffee
- Yes, sir.
Did you put in sugar?
Why didn't you knock?
Get me green tea! Green tea!
Did you read it?
What do you think?
Congratulations.
Conventionality
and corruption.
Modern but classic!
Heartwarming! It's great!
You gotta tell me
what happens next.
So what happens?
What happens?
Well..
Is Hwa-jung home?
- No. Why?
- Then can you help us?
- Why should I?
- Our grandma..
She passed away.
Grandma..
She's alive!!
Grandma!
Call the ambulance!
What's wrong with your phone?
Our phone line is disconnected.
Can we use your cell phone?
I don't have a cell phone.
Please.. Help me..
She fainted due to
malnutrition.
Fortunately,
she doesn't have any major illnesses.
She'll recover by tonight.
Okay
Are you her guardian?
What? How much?
We're sorry but she doesn't
have a health insurance.
Wait
You heard, right?
That's a lot of money for me.
You have to pay me back. Ok?
Ok
You promised. And with interest
would be even better.
Alright
- Sir..
- What?
I'm hungry.
The worst kind of people are those
who never pay back what they owe.
You don't wanna be like those
people, right?
- Hey, guys
- Hwa-jung!
Hwa-jung!
I can't get pass this part.
What?
It was nice what you did today.
Me?
Oh, that. They'll pay me back.
I'm kinda busy. Do you mind?
Oh, sorry.
- Wait!
- Yes?
About that story you told Hee-gu..
- The one with a woman drowning..
- What about it?
I'm curious what happens next.
Can you tell me the rest?
Sure.
But, why?
Are you gonna write
that into a novel?
My story will get published?
For real?
You know my writer buddy Mr. SHIM?
Of course.
He wants to make it into a novel.
So he asked me to
get the rest of
the story and tell him.
Why didn't he ask me?
He's little shy.
I see.
So, can you tell me
the rest of the story?
- Completely.
- Completely?
Ok. I haven't thought
about the ending, yet
But I can try.
When she turns her head
she sees him sitting in a bus,
right across from her bus.
She's so happy to see him.
And as she's about to get off,
the bus leaves.
Why didn't I think of that?
The handkerchief that holds the
fragrance of his mother..
- Wait.
- of his mother.. And?
He starts to run.
And keeps running.
Crashing into every obstacle
that lies in front of him..
Then he sees the light.
How long has it been since he last
saw the light? His eyes glisten.
It's great.
I guess you'll really
finish it by this month.
Ithink so.
Hey, join me at Hwa-jung's coffee
shop. I'm going there right now.
- Why?
- Just to kill time.
No. I'll pass. I need to rest.
I pulled all nighter last night.
Ok. Bye.
Hey, join me at Hwa-jung's coffee
shop. I'm going there right now.
What? He used me to get
the story from you?
Yes! I can't believe he lied!
Liar! Liar! Liar!!
No!
Hello? Where are you?
- I'm almost there.
- No!
What's wrong?
- Just come to my place.
- Why?
- It's urgent!
- What's wrong with you?
You come out.
I'm almost there.
Just stay there and
don't talk to anybody!
Do I make you feel uncomfortable?
- What?
- It's just that
You could've asked me directly. You
didn't have to go through Mr. GOH.
Mr. GOH?
What about Mr. GOH?
Move, Move!
Get outta the way!
About the story.
You mean the one
Mr. GOH's writing?
- No, the one you're..
- No!
What's up with your hair?
Mousse.
I need to talk to you..
- Why don't we talk here?
- Yes. Stay.
What? Hwa-jung likes me?
She said that?
Her boyfriend is in prison.
In prison?
When he gets out next month,
he's gonna come after you.
Why me?
He's jealousy incarnate.
Imagine what he'd do when
he finds out
that the love of his life has
betrayed him?
Would he hurt her?
No. He'll kill you first.
Avoid being seen
with her anywhere.
That is the only way
you'll live!
Did I seem little strange
this afternoon?
Yes. You looked like a lunatic.
I couldn't tell you, but..
Yesterday, I told you Mr. SHIM is..
too shy to ask you for the story, right?
- Yes.
- I lied.
But I can't tell you the truth.
No, no. You should know.
Mr. SHIM..
He's sick in his head.
Really? No..
He doesn't seem like so.
You can't tell byjust looking at
him, but when he has his fits..
I shouldn't tell you this.
I promise I won't tell anybody.
- Shh!
- Okay
When he loses control of himself,
he grabs his head like this..
and smashes it like this.
- And his nose bursts out in blood!
- God..
Especially
when his pride is hurt.
He strangles himself
foaming in his mouth..
If people find out that he's writing
your story into into a novel..
That's why you rushed to come over
with all that mousse in your hair.
It was a close call. Very close.
Now that I think of it, it was weird
how he always changed his hairdos.
It's the worst when he has a perm.
I'm sorry, buddy
I had no choice.
Daeguanryung?
Why would I go there?
You said you'd go. That's what
you told everybody.
I didn't mean what I said.
I'm not going.
So, I'm not going, either?
Why would you go if I'm not going?
Isn't it obvious why they're going?
They're gonna have a barbecue
party and get drunk.
With coffee shop girls
in their arms,
their goal is to get laid.
So vulgar and stupid.
What? He said I'm mentally sick?
Yes! And he told you I have
a boyfriend who's in prison?
Yes! And the story is yours?
Yes, it's mine!
He has no conscience!
- Bastard!
- Asshole!
- Coward!
- Shit head!
Teacher, what's the matter?
Let's go to Daeguanryung.
Mr. GOH, have you ever
been to the Daeguanryung farm?
- No.
- They must have milking cows there.
The white ones with black spots.
- Probably.
- I wonder how many. A lot, right?
I love animals.
I never miss an episode
of 'Animal Kingdom' on TV.
I bet you like that show, too
Last week was about
desert animals..
I hate animals.
And, especially, that stupid show!
I can't believe she's been talking
about animals for last hour.
- Yes?
- I'm sorry to bother you, but
my friend is hurt.
Can you please give us a ride?
- We're kinda behind schedule..
- Poor kids.
We'll pay you.
Thank you so much.
We're very sorry.
Assholes!
Ungrateful punks!
- Poopy heads.
- Poop.. Poopy..Poopy heads!
Bastards!
Those who don't
give a ride
are as bad as those
who steal cars.
We gave rides to everyone. But,
how come no one's giving us a ride?
Car's coming!
He's a bastard, too.
- I'm freezing.
- I'm freezing, too.
I'm starving.
I'm starving, too.
Why the hell did I come?
Look! Light!
Wait for me!
TV is going crazy again.
I told you to buy a new one!
Nonsense! This will last us
for another 10 years!
Hello?
Who is it?
Yes?
Hi. Can I please use your phone?
We don't have one.
I'm sorry to bother you
but I don't have a place to stay
for the night. May I stay here tonight?
- Sure. Come in
- Thank you so much.
I'm sorry, but there's
one more person.
C'mon! Come!
Please help yourself.
- Thank you.
I can't believe
those bastards!
If it was me, I would've
taught them a good lesson!
What would you have done?