Sir.
What's your mission today?
Save hostages, Sir.
What?
Kill hostage is more proper.
Such a lovely girl
was destroyed by you.
Can't you differentiate enemy and friend?
Did I tell you how many hostages?
No, Sir.
So you thought there's only me.
And you, rolling in and firing
at the same time are cool, right?
Didn't look behind you?
If I were the one who got up,
I'd be shot by you.
Then you have to handle my funeral
and also my parents.
Look at you, can you afford it?
Is it enough?
Yes, Sir.
Good, no more scolding then.
From tomorrow onwards, I'll be promoted
to a better life.
You'll be on your own.
Yes, Sir.
Give me five...
Are you happy that I leave?
Let me tell you.
I'm happier than you.
Sir Chow, your file hasn't come back yet.
Madam will see you later.
Alright then.
I know you may think I'm boasting.
But you think about it.
When I sit in that room,
I'll give out orders.
How can I not be proud of myself?
I'm lovelorn.
I'm finally promoted.
Lovelorn!
You're lovelorn?
Is it possible? You've dated before?
No.
That is!
We're pen pals.
Pen pals.
We've corresponded for three years.
Recently, she stopped writing to me.
Why?
Cause I sent her a photo.
You asked for it.
How can you send a picture of your face?
Right, that's why I sent yours.
My picture?
Yes, your picture,
and then she never writes me back.
Well, it's not your fault.
It's not a sin to have an ugly face.
What's love, one may sacrifice for it.
In the dark... all is ended.
Your mother...
Did I ask for cold water?
Have you ever seen me drinking cold water?
No.
Then why did you pour me cold water?
Behave yourself, this is police station.
So what?
I like to beat her, and she likes it.
So?
Do you like it?
Yes.
- Speak up.
- Yes.
- Louder.
- Yes, I like it.
Then go and get me water.
You're jealous I have lots of women?
Getting a statement.
- Let me finish it.
- Yes, Sir.
- Come here.
- Where?
- Over here.
- Come here right away.
Just questioning, no need to use a hammer?!
Questioning? After the beating.
Hold him, don't let him move.
Hey.
Wait.
What are you doing? Sit still!
Ah Tat...
This isn't right.
Have you questioned any suspect before?
No, but you'll be in trouble if you hurt him.
How would this hurt him?!
I'll put a phone book on this chest
and hammer on it.
Then there'll be no evidence.
Better don't make trouble at this time.
Any phone book?
How come there's no phone book in the station?
It seems I haven't bring along.
There is.
Put on his chest.
I really don't agree what you're doing.
Don't worry, it'll be alright.
Come, put it here.
Count to three.
Sir, your phone book is so small. It'll kill me.
Open it.
Three
It'll kill me too.
Take your hand off, hold him.
Hold him.
It's not my fault, I'm forced to do so.
Three
Don't play around.
Hurry up.
Two...
Hey, wanna die?!
Release him, I wanna fight him man to man.
Don't.
Release him.
That's it, I don't care.
Hey, you fight him or me?
Fight him.
Sing.
What?
Relay.
Didn't you say man to man?
You're a man too.
I knew it.
Wrestling, man?
Relay... relay.
Sing... relay.
What a shame to know you.
Don't talk anymore, quick, come...
Hurry...
Hey, give me a cigarette.
No, it costs money.
Relay...
What?
Let's see.
You asked for it.
Why did you beat him?
Such a big man insulted a woman.
I hate those men who don't respect women.
You can report if you think I'm wrong.
I wanna report...
I'm beaten by the policemen...
Have your files been back?
No.
Mr., sorry, according to the procedure.
These two ain't policemen.
What? Then why did they beat me?
There's nothing wrong. We're reasonable.
If you wanna sue these two men,
I have to charge...
you three ganged fighting.
Interested?
Why did you let these two mad dogs beat me?
I have to report them.
I have to report you too.
Don't think that I wouldn't recognize you.
I remember you, short, fat and wrinkled.
Gee, my eyes.
I'm the top in this district.
If you wanna report, come to me.
Did anybody see I hurt his eyes?
Yes.
Then I'll take one more
and kick your bottom too.
See if anybody believe you?!
Let's go.
Yes, Madam.
Did anybody see I kick him?
Yes.
What about a short, fat and wrinkled me?
No.
Good!
Madam, it's a misunderstanding just now.
But...
I'm responsible for it.
I was happy to hit that guy.
If Madam thinks I'm wrong,
you can nail me anytime.
You two did very well
in the firearm case last month.
Yes, because.
That's nothing, it's our duty.
Nothing special.
Don't be so humble, what do you wanna do?
Which department is the most dangerous
in the police force?
Regional Crime Unit.
I wanna go there.
If you go there, what about me?
Then I'll go to the Transport Unit, right?
What have I done wrong?
Sigh... Hopeless.
Oh my god.
Turn it off, license, ID card.
Great trouble!
It's Brother Sing.
Don't be afraid.
You guys are getting more stupid.
Brother Sing, we'll be alright, right?
You guys are lucky.
It's me this time.
Be more careful.
We can go then?
Go...
Why did you degraded
to be a traffic policeman?
Yes...
Turn it off, license, ID card.
Don't joke around.
Ignore him.
I'm not joking.
Get of the car,
put both hands on your head.
Hold them tight.
I'm now charging you dangerous driving,
attempted murder.
I'm not the driver.
Shut up.
You have unlawful sexual intercourse
with a girl under 16.
I haven't.
Shut up! Look at it yourself.
Go...
Bastards, am I degraded?
It's called desertion.
Slow down.
Sing...
Tat.
Wow, in such a good mood for BBQ.
Of course.
Give me a sausage.
There're more for me.
How's the uniform?
Good, colorful and comfortable.
- Really?
- Yes.
Then you wear it longer.
You should have made Madam happy.
She's lucky that I didn't beat her up.
Not like you, I don't date old woman.
Hey, it's not me who date her.
It's she that keeps following me.
I'll get her for sure.
Look at your ugly face.
I wonder what she likes about you.
She likes everything about me.
You're the No.
1 shooter in the SDU, aren't you?
Sir, the car's gone.
Oh, I'm going. I'm following a big case.
What case?
Big case.
Is there anybody from the other team?
I've got a hard band transmission.
We have company, gentlemen.
Is it the Urban Council
to clear the garbage?
Check it out.
Don't shoot, we're police too...
We've got an undercover up there.
Everybody's safe.
That's our undercover.
He's investigating a terrorist case
at an international school.
Those terrorists
have already exploded 2 schools in Britain.
They came to Hong Kong this time,
which school is the target?
We're still investigating.
Thank you Peter, your turn Lydia.
We haven't received any message about
the undercover from the Special Branch.
Do we have to inform you everything we do?
Peter, don't get mad. You both ain't wrong.
Little friend, what's your name?
Transport Unit, P.C. No.167,
Chow Sing-Sing, Sir.
Any backing?
Backing? No.
Good, then you can be
the scapegoat for the case.
Agree?
This is to make me a scapegoat.
Yes, it's a shame.
I shall beat him up.
Right.
You think so too?
Right...
I'll beat him up now.
Hey, be gentle.
Don't kill him.
It's hard to say, I can't control myself.
Don't use so much force.
I'm a strong man.
Yes, you're right.
Who can afford my punch?
I think there's no one.
Okay, I'll fight.
Hey, watch out for my Madam.
I'll beat whoever makes me a scapegoat.
- Yes...
- Am I right?
Yes, then hurry back for coffee.
Do you wanna go for a coffee?
Yes, coffee.
Then go for coffee first.
I tell you,
I'm not afraid of anything.
Whoever blame me, I'll beat him up.
Auntie, have a cup of tea.
Good boy.
Mom, don't force him.
When did I force him?
You say it, have I forced you?
You say it.
Theoretically, no.
Your mother wouldn't force him.
I'm talking to him. Don't interrupt.
Oh, yes.
Have you thought of getting married?
Under normal logical morality, yes.
What does that mean?
It means no.
It's because I've got no money.
No money? I don't believe.
You've got no money for working so long?
Are you joking?
The money needed for wedding dress,
cash gift, cakes,
banquet, honeymoon, new house,
and other things.
I couldn't afford it.
I heard policemen have
five hundred million income.
That's a long time ago.
It's not your business.
Five hundred million? Yes, I have it.
But I've spend it all on those.
What? Those worth five hundred million?
Yes, they do.
It's only paper.
Yes...
Right now, you just cost me
hundred and fifty million.
Is that too expensive?
Hey, you've got money.
Where?
This account, we own it.
I remember, each of us contributed $10.
It's worth more than $10 now.
$100,000? You've saved that much.
Hey, you've contributed too.
Don't you remember?
It's helpless. My daughter is like me.
You're lucky, get ready for the wedding.
Mom, don't worry. He'll manage it.
Okay.
Hey, Sing.
There's some important matters
you've got to help.
Special Branch and Regional Crime Unit
are cooperating for the first time.
I'll be exposed this time.
As a prostitute?
No.
Then why exposed?
No. I mean I'll be visible.
How should I say it?
Be extraordinary.
Yes... extraordinary.
That's what I've just said, right?
Yes, then what?
All these English I know,
but not understand.
You explain to me.
I see, this is about...
- Hum...
- What?
- Is it true...
- Hum...
- What?
- What's the matter?
Madam, please think twice.
I believe about this case, besides me.
You shouldn't find
another person to do it.
Tat is our best.
He'll finish the job with no problem.
Say it yourself, are you able?
Well, let me tell you
those terrorists are crazy.
Don't pretend, say it.
I know... The report is very detailed.
This case is very dangerous,
but I'm not afraid all along.
Don't overestimate yourself.
Your superior told me you're
not suitable for traffic.
I've considered to transfer
you to Tung Lung Island.
That's an deserted island.
Yes, there's no traffic.
Wow, then you'll be very comfortable,
congratulations.
Those junior grade people, please go out.
We're having a meeting.
Sorry, I'm not junior.
Actually, I'm not part of the police force.
I resign.
River flows to the east.
The younger generation has
no cultivation nowadays.
We're lucky to have you.
Don't be so loud. People will be jealous.
Sorry.
Sing... I've found you several jobs.
You listen.
The electronics factory's vacancy
with high salary, good benefit
and transportation is provided.
Not suitable?
How about this... as a watchman?
It'll fit you. They provide uniform.
No?
Hey, this one will do. A movie company
is looking for a leading actor.
No bad habits, young,
strong and good-looking.
Hey, everything fits you.
Is it?
But, there's a little incompatibility.
What?
They're looking for
a dog to do a love story.
Just a little difference.
Doesn't hurt to try.
You're not thinking you're worse than a dog?
Not that bad!
Sing, you've got to have a plan.
You're still young.
Don't destroy yourself?
No matter what, I've decided.
What? If it's business, count me in.
Doing what I do best.
Right, the dog leading role
is suitable for you.
Undercover at school.
I have to go back to school
as a undercover.
I need a few assistants.
They have to be strong, fast and smart.
That's why I find you guys.
No.
You're fooling us.
How do you know?
We're not as
what you've described.
Don't think we're stupid.
That's right.
We're stupid, but not a fool.
Won't be fooled by you so easily.
No way.
No way... No.
How much money you want? Say it.
$15,000
Each one $15,000.
On a monthly basis.
Hong Kong dollar, not Yen.
Deal.
Thank you boss...
Let's eat...
Let's go together.
I don't understand why you have to do it.
That's right.
Because I wanna tell them,
I'm the No. 1 in the SDU.
Last time the firearm case, I was the best.
I should have been the
Chief Superintendent or Chief Inspector.
It shouldn't be
in Transport Unit P.C., No. 167.
You understand?
I do.
You're lying.
You're stupid, how would you understand?
Sing, I'm not stupid.
If the British Government, within a week,
that is before the coming
Christmas Eve midnight,
doesn't release the head of the terrorists.
They'll make trouble
in one of the school in HK.
Sing, why is Hong Kong involved
with the British Government?
Right.
Do you have a holiday
on the Queen's Birthday?
Yes.
Then you're involved.
That's right.
But there's so many schools.
How do we know which one?
I've analyzed.
The undercover just died,
is working in
the Adam Smith International School
and those studying in this school
are the children of the ambassadors.
If I were the terrorists,
I'll make trouble there.
But what if you're wrong?
Then I'll beat you up.
Is it real?
As real as the 999 real gold.
Now you guys get ready, I'll go apply.
Sing, don't guess wrong.
Excuse me, is Principal Kim here?
Is it Manager Kim?
It's Principal, not Manager.
It's the same.
The first one on the left ahead.
Is it Principal Kim?
Come in.
I've got customer. Talk to you later.
Hello...
What can I do for you?
I wanna apply for school.
Which one?
Adam Smith International School.
Which grade?
Form 6, four of us.
There're seats available. I'll arrange it.
Chow Sing-Sing, how old are you?
18 years old.
Really? You look like at least 28.
Is it real?
No matter what age you are.
Don't underestimate yourself.
If you're willing to learn, we'll teach.
That's good.
The tuition fee is $4,000 each,
$16,000 for four.
And books fee, each is $3,600.
Sport uniform fee, each is $2,800.
The total is $41,600.
Thank you, boss.
Hey...
What are you doing here?
Studying.
Where's the office, Mr?
Are you serious?
Say thank you.
Thank you, Mr.
Mr. Bond would see you later.
Wonder whether the head of
discipline is bad or not?
Can't be worse than Mr. Lam
in the previous school?
Idiot, we pay to come here, right? Sing?
It's Uncle Tat.
No, call me Bond, James Bond.
You're James Bond, then I'm Batman.
Listen, I'm your head of discipline,
James Bond.
Not Batman, or Superman.
And also not Uncle Tat.
Come... Hit me if you dare.
Those guys from Special Branch
are watching us outside.
I don't care, I come here for study.
You're the head of discipline,
you can't hit people without reason.
Not hit people.
The order is to hit you only.
Come, let me hit you and finish the job.
I'll treat you a meal.
Am I stupid? How can I eat after you hit me?
Don't worry, I'll be gentle on you.
If it hurts you, you can fight back.
- Then it's okay.
- Come.
No need for a meal, cash $1000.
- $500
- $800
Deal.
Wow, are they enemies?
Hey, you earn $800 from me.
Can you treat me for dinner?
I'll treat you a banana.
Why are you such a miser?
Hey, it's so dull to be
just left and right.
I'm so tired.
I'm not tired,
and you've already complained?
My neck is tired from all these turning.
Any other style?
Yes.
Why is there a rod?
Sing, are you alright?
Yes.
What about now?
Looking for a chance to beat him up.
No, I mean what's the next step?
The next is to collect
information on this school.
I wanna know what Mike
has done in this school before.
I see, we'll go then.
Where are you going?
That way.
For what?
None of your business.
What kind of manner is this?
Sing, where are we going anyway?
Anywhere can do.
Fool around? Kid.
Are you finished?
Almost, Sing, be patient.
Hurry up.
Sorry, man.
It's Miss.
I don't know if you didn't tell me.
And you know now.
Not really.
Apologize.
Apologize...
Sorry miss.
Is it done?
- Sing...
- Go.
Sing, we haven't found our room yet.
Ask someone.
This one must be a girl.
Hey, sister, where's the classroom?
Sweetie, would you
tell me where's Room 507?
- Downstairs.
- Thank you.
This novel isn't suitable for you.
The story is romantic and terrifying.
But the main leads are dead at the end.
Such a tragedy.
Too gloomy.
You should read something delightful.
Delightful?
Yes, such as Yik Shu's "Spring Dream".
Tsukasa Hojo's "City Hunter".
Akira Toriyama's "Doctor IQ".
Jademan's "Oriental Heroes".
I think they're all suitable for you.
Sing, don't know that you're
an expert of literature.
You're great.
Don't understand why did
people say you're senseless.
Yes.
- And not fair.
- It's unreasonable.
Sing, I've just got a hanger-on.
You?
Yes, I'm surprise too.
Say big brother.
Big brother.
Hello, how are you?
How much do you want? Big brother.
How much of what?
Every big brother asks for money.
What does it mean?
Albert joins all the clubs in school
from school club to gang club
and he pays all the fees.
Is there any triad here?
Yes.
That one belongs to gang B.
He's black, not necessary
be a triad member.
Black people has a triad too.
That one belongs to gang C.
C?!
C for Ca Li Fra Ga
Lis Tic Ex Pe Ala Docious.
I see.
In fact, I just wanna
ask you about one person.
Follow me.
Pay for it.
Thirty dollars.
Make it cheaper, we're friends.
Forget it...
- Sweet Potato.
- Yes.
Is it done?
I've already found some informers, Sing.
Absolutely no problem.
I have paid for it.
Sister.
Sweetheart.
Do you want some?
Ten dollar one stick.
Good taste.
Reckless.
Isn't it good? We can do anything.
Or is it better to be in a jail?
- It's really No. 2.
- What No. 2?
No. 2 of the 5th race.
Hey, the 6th race will soon begin.
Are you interested in my banker?
10% discount.
No? Stocks? Gold, options, currencies.
Hey, the Yen is appreciating.
How about it?
No? Women? Different nationalities,
18-year-old.
No? Men? Animal? Dog?
Mouse?
Excuse me.
Hi, Sir, nice haircut.
Sir, the book is for you. How is it?
It's good.
Read it carefully, really something good.
I don't watch football.
Why don't we take attendance first?
Sandy Lai.
Sandy...
I'm here.
And this one... is a new student.
Stephen Chow.
Here...
It's Chow.
Mr. Chow, welcome to the class.
Matthew, chapter 27.
At this time, when Judas,
the betrayer of Jesus
saw that Jesus would be nailed, he repented.
Play Mahjong.
Good, how much?
What are you doing?
Goodbye, Sir. Play mahjong.
Your punishment is to copy
the Old arid New Testament once.
What? Why so serious?
Didn't you say play mahjong?
Few years later, the Bible is so thick.
You don't even think of playing mahjong
for these 2 years.
It can't be?!
Returning to the repentant Judas.
He put $30 in the church.
Then left, and hanged himself.
What depressed him so much to end his life?
Do you think what Judas
who betrayed Christ is a good man?
He's alright.
If he did not betrayed Christ,
then Christ would not be nailed to the cross,
then you won't have a cross on your neck.
You'll be unemployed, fear?
The betrayal is arranged by God.
That means... God purposely cheated Judas.
God, please forgive my violence.
Please show me how to save this student.
Sing, it's reckless here.
You can do whatever you want.
What? Do you wanna copy the Bible?
It's nothing.
I don't care if God saves my soul.
Right now, I wanna beat you.
Sing, you're great. Your fighting is good.
But I've sensed something bad is coming.
You shouldn't have insulted Minister Wong.
He's the most powerful in the school even
bigger than me and the Principal.
He can kick you out anytime.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I forgot.
Go...
See how you can beat me up.
Go!
You're something, Head of Discipline.
Of course, don't run.
Head of Discipline.
What?
I wanna ask you something in the washroom.
Why have to be in the washroom?
Only takes you a second.
Why not here?
Washroom is better.
Don't go away, Head of discipline.
It's the school regulation.
I don't wanna beat you.
Come on, I ain't that stingy.
I haven't killed you right?
I ain't angry at all.
Yes... It's very kind of you not to kill me.
Thanks a lot...
I'm always good for you.
Worth treating me a meal right?
Sure...
Can you bring
some dim sum to me too?
That guy is weird, what's he doing here?
Don't care about him.
As long as he doesn't intervene
with what we're doing.
Most important isn't letting
him get close to Sandy.
Sir, I really won't do it next time.
You fool, see if you dare
to do it next time.
Yes, but can you be gentle next time?
You won't be scared if I'm gentle.
That's right.
Go back to the classroom.
Thank you, Sir.
Is Sandy really involved?
Brother Sing, you're really great just now.
Personal show of the ball trick.
It really amazes all of us.
- Am I that good?
- Very good.
It's the top.
Did any girls yell?
Not only yell, some moan.
- Who?
- Them.
Brother Sing, remember you can
just catch the brush before.
Now you've already attain such
level with the ball
and also play it with such style,
you're great.
I can catch not only the brush now.
Then what?
I can even catch bullets.
Wow, you've got to perform a show.
There's chances. Just be patient.
Then I'll wait for you.
The Special Branch has already
put their people here.
That proves I'm right.
There's something going on in this school.
Good, I don't have to be beaten.
What're you doing? Any information?
No, thinking of my girlfriend.
Me too.
What? Is it time to go now?
Go home and do the homework.
Chow Sing-Sing, the Special Branch
invites you for coffee.
Big Brother... I wanna go too.
What're you doing in the school.
I've said before we're there to study.
Sir.
Teacher?
Which subject are you teaching?
You must be teaching Shit, no, History.
I warn you guys.
Don't follow him to school.
Or else, I'll lock you up.
What?
What can I do except study?
I'm a student only.
Yes, you can't stop people from studying.
Chow Sing-Sing isn't our man anymore.
Is it right, Tat?
Are you scared of him?
No, not me!
Listen, study hard.
No more investigations
and no fooling around.
Not to beat the Head of Discipline.
Yes Sir!
Get out.
Goodbye, Sir.
Thank you, Sir.
Dismiss.
If there's anything went wrong,
you're responsible.
Let's go.
Did you arrange that?
Can you not ask what I'm up to?
Yes, I'll trust you then.
Are you alright with your face?
Shut up.
Roger.
Why it doesn't work?
Anyway, the informer said
they're here. Move in.
Okay.
How come no one's here?
Be careful, they must be here.
Alright, we do it as planned.
The target is
Adam Smith International School.
But the cops are already at the school.
Cops? So you're afraid of cops.
Now? Let's go to teach them a lesson.
Sing, this guy knows our identity.
We're in danger. How about...
Please don't kill me.
If our secret spread out...
No, I've already joined you guys.
Finish the homework
if you wanna get out of trouble.
It's done.
Sing, where's your Hi-Fi?
Sold it already.
Up-grade?
No money, you guys already
spent my $100,000.
I have to sell it.
Brother Sing, don't be worried.
I'll introduce you to a loan shark.
Who?
Sing, it's 6 o'clock, I'll charge you
overtime if we're not dismissed.
Dismiss.
Miss Ho, long time no see.
Yes.
Well, talk to you later. We're off.
Off?
Bye-bye.
Ming.
Hey, they said they're off.
Yes, just came to fix the plumbing.
Plumbing?
They're learning to be plumber.
My hair's getting long.
No problem, sit down.
Thank you.
Mr., how many of you?
One.
Have you reserved for the wedding banquet?
Yes.
Where's the Hi-Fi?
There's no need, isn't it?
I've got you. It's the same.
What're you talking about?
That means your singing
is better than a Hi-Fi.
I've made a appointment
with a realtor tomorrow.
Remember to bring the cheque book.
You wanna make a deposit?
Don't be this hurry.
What? You've got no money?
No, whatever you gave me
last time I've got them.
But then, if you make the deposit,
that means you have to pay the mortgage.
Yes, you can apply for civil allowance.
There's no more.
Why not?
I'm an undercover.
Undercover? You said you're promoted?
Yes, still an undercover.
I'm a commander of the undercovers.
Not anyone can take this post.
You should be happy for me, are you?
Smile then.
Will it delay our wedding?
It'd better not
or else I'll lose my life.
What're you doing?
Nothing.
Keep going.
More?
Yes.
You said so...
Come on, hurry.
Today, I'll teach you judo.
To be good,
the waist is the most important.
Besides, the feet as well.
Come on, hurry.
See it?
In fact, judo is dynamic.
Sandy, come demonstrate with him.
Yes.
Sir, she's a girl.
I purposely pick the smallest one.
The others will kill you.
Ready.
Cut.
Why are you dancing Cha Cha? Fight!
Thank you...
Alright, get even then.
You're done with the shower?
You've played judo?
No.
Why you took a shower?
We're partner.
Sandy isn't related to this case.
Sandy?!
I don't understand, I'm just a student.
Then you shouldn't talk
about dating girls.
No.
Then did the girls date you?
Look at your own face.
Your side and your head.
Which part will
the girls love?
No.
That's it.
You've got it, give me ten.
I've got it, give me five.
If it is, it's only Sandy.
Why are you kissing?
But not letting me in?
Next time.
Don't touch her anymore.
Give me some hair conditioner.
Thank you.
Don't say thank you, say thanks is okay.
Thanks.
Brother...
Do you know that girl with short hair?
Which one?
The one with the comic book
who looks wild
That's Jacky, Sandy's sister.
Everyone's afraid of her.