Cinema Service In Cooperation
with Infinite Technology
Investments
Produced by Fun & Happiness
LEE Jung-Jae, LEE Young-Ae
Executive Producer... KANG Woo-Suk
Producers: KIM Mi-Hee, KIM Sang-Jin
Screenplay: PARK Jung-Woo
Cinematography-LEE Suk-Hyun
Lighting-PARK Hyun-Won
Music-JO Sung-Woo (M&F)
Editing-LEE Hyun-Mi
Line Producer-KIM Sang-Oh
Directed by OH Ki-Hwan
Hello! We're Korea's funniest
comedians, Jung Yong-gi!
And Yang Chul-soo!
Hi! Of the many variety shows,
'King of Comedy'...
being the most popular...
We wanna perform on those shows...
Unfortunately, we haven't been
discovered yet.
That's right. Thank you all who are here
at the King of Comedy studio today.
Now we'll begin the show for all of you.
- Good work. We're going into taping.
- Oh, okay.
Okay, everyone. Give us a hand!
Applause!
Alright, let's keep this spirit
up to the end, okay?
You now know Korea's funniest
comedians, Yang Chul-soo!
And Jung Yong-gi!
- Thank you.
- Thank you very much.
- Oh, hello.
- Hello.
- Are they laughing a lot?
- Yes.
Keep up the good work.
We're better off playing nightclubs
than doing this crap.
You're gonna say, 'it's stupid
but it's still TV, right?'
If you want it so bad then
fatten some wallets or kiss up...
You're gonna say, 'Am I a butt-licker',
aren't you?
I don't see the answer...
Where is our answer?
Oh, stop your whining!
Why is it so hard to get on a show?
How many times do I have to tell you?
I said, no!
Oh, Yoo-shik, lovely!
You should say hello. Hey, move it!
- Huh. Now he won't even say hi.
- Let him be. He's made it now.
Made what?
You mean, his face is made up?
Hey, let's go...
Yeah, it's a great opportunity
but there's no one good right now.
Sure, PD Kim.
Look into it and call me again.
Okay? Later.
Man, plenty of spots
but no one to fill them.
You get it? The crane...
So this crane is you?
I heard about you two.
They say you guys have talent.
But only talent.
You got it, 'only'!
You know 'only' is what turns
the lights off on a bright future.
More talking will just hurt my jaw.
At least, they say you have talent...
How about placing your future
in my hands for 3 months?
If you don't make it by then,
I'll leave this field.
Then what do we have to...
First, bring me 10 grand by next week.
Let's start with a show.
What do you think?
Excuse me? 10 grand?
Guys, has anyone made it by banging
their heads on the ground?
You've gotta invest.
Yong-gi, did you pass the talent test?
No.
- Any connections?
- No.
Did you ever buy a producer drinks?
No.
There you go. No wonder you're
crawling at the bottom.
- Why? Too rich for you?
- It's not...
Try running barefoot 'cause you can't
buy shoes. What would happen?
- Bloody feet.
- Exactly!
Wear fancy shoes and run your ass
off. You're on your way.
Forget about it!
What are you saying right now?
I don't wanna get on TV
by paving the way with money.
What do you take us for?
I can't believe guys like you
are still around...
What are you doing? Let's go!
- Come on.
- Yong-gi.
Yong-gi...
Mr. Yong-gi!
- He took my card, right?
- Yeah, Chul-soo did.
He won't do nightclubs
for the life of him.
- Why the hell won't he? Huh?
- He says it's embarrassing.
Embarrassing? Crazy son of a bitch!
Hey, if you wanna succeed,
didn't I tell you to dump him?
How can I? We've been a duo
since high school.
Duo... then become a panhandling duo!
Bro, don't be so hard on him.
After his son, Woo-jin died,
...he took a couple of years off.
Actually, he's much funnier than I am.
That's why he's all wrong.
Is that a pro?
Can't he separate work and home?
Leave him to me.
Give us a job, a cool one.
You told me to live like a man.
Oh, brother. Where did I put it?
Why is this so small?
Why do you say no?
We'd be better off apart than
living like this.
Because it's damn embarrassing!
Think about it. To get married after
everyone was dead set against us.
And then, we break up now?
How could I hold my face up?
Hold your face up? What face?
It's not like you make any money.
Why are you home so late?
Crazy bitch!
Do you even love me? Huh?
Of course.
I love you. I do love you.
Hey!
Dammit...
- You worthless...!
- Honey!
Are you asking us to accept
an orphan into this home?
It's not enough that you're a clown?
Get out! Rotten, worthless brat...
But father, if you'd just meet
Jung-yeon once...
- Still with this! You brat!
- Dear, no!
Listen! Don't even come near here...
Rotten brat!
- What are you doing? Come!
- Yes.
Give it! Come on!
This is Jin-young,
can you believe it?
Look at her hair and clothes.
How tacky.
I have to say I was really cute.
How adorable.
- Yeah, she was really cute.
- See.
What do you mean she was cute?
The duckling grew into a swan.
What? Duckling? Swan?
Hey. What's this?
Friendship... Love... J.Y.
How can you be so corny?
Look at these.
They're not corny!
It's from all the boys
who chased after me.
Do you even have any corny stuff
like this?
Of course. My walls were plastered
with leaves. What did you expect?
Look at her lie.
- I didn't see any in your room.
- I took them down long ago.
- When would that have been...
- Oh, you didn't see, huh?
"80 Gongsoojun Elementary,
Fall Field Trip"
What is your wish?
To turn the lights off in our house.
Abracadabra...
The lights are going,
the lights are going!
The lights are going, the lights...
Hey, Shim Jin-woo, you ass!
Why are you doing this to me?
The finals are days away and
you don't have any judges yet?
- Well...
- Shut up!
Are you guys really gonna shit
around like this?
If I see you screw up during taping,
I'll crush your skulls!
Get out! Out!
You guys get out, too! Out!
What am I gonna do with those morons?
Dammit.
Um, excuse me. Oh, can I help you?
Yes.
How do you do?
Who... are you?
Oh, yes... I'm Yong-gi Jung's wife.
- Who?
- The comedian.
Comedian Yong-gi Jung.
So?
How did you get in?
I have something to ask you...
- Have you had lunch?
- Yes, I have.
Huh, this TV station...
what kind of security...
- Do you want to go for some coffee?
- I'm busy.
'Pre-show: Yong-gi Jung, Chulsoo Yang'
Idiot.
What?
Have you been enjoying the night air?
Is that a way to talk to your husband?
What?
You know what tomorrow is, right?
Mommy!
'Jung Woo-jin: 1998.4.20'
Let's go...
He wishes he could brag about
his father to his friends.
When will you grow up? My God...
- How was that?
- It's a little weak.
Then I'll have to hit him.
What can I do?
That's a little too much.
This isn't even funny. Let's skip it.
Okay. Let's take it out when we tape.
That's better.
Let's take a break! I'll be outside.
Thanks for filling in.
This is how it is.
Go eat. See you. Let's go, Yoo-shik.
What did you learn in Kindergarten?
Dewey Rain? How do you do that?
- Hi, hello.
- Hello. Who may you be?
- Are you the wife of PD Hwang?
- Yes. And you are?
How do you do? I'm the wife of
comedian Yong-gi Jung.
I heard Yong-gi worked with
PD Hwang a couple of times.
I see.
Ah, you're so pretty!
Do you want one? Here.
Oh, how adorable.
Excuse me, take this back with you!
Then do what you want!
Where the hell is it?
Jeez, so much make-up.
Is she going out for Miss Korea?
I'll pay you back every cent.
How much?
Is that all this store is worth?
I see... Alright.
Welcome.
- How old is your child?
- What? Oh, 35.
Jung Yong-gi is your husband, right?
- Well...
- Yes...
Can he really get a regular spot
on a show for that money?
Well, if I say that, I'm a con-man.
How can I put it... it's to grease
the way to getting connections.
Anyway, Yong-gi needs
family support right now.
- If that's the case...
- Oh! Sorry.
- Hello? PD Park?
- Mr. Kang, this is Jung Yong-gi.
Oh, right. I can hear you fine.
Yeah...
I'm calling because I gave it
some thought and I think...
What? Hello?
Hello? Hello?
Oh. Well, I do know someone
who's good.
PD Park.
You always call when you need...
You got disconnected, right?
- Hello? It's me...
- Sure, I'll call you back.
Give me a call.
- Look here!
- Yes?
- You're a con-man, aren't you?
- What? No, I'm not!
Where do you think you're going?
- Let go!
- I got you, scumbag.
- What's wrong with this woman?
- Let's go to the police.
What, police? Let me go!
- Hey, Hakchul! Get the car!
- Why? Why...
Get in, quick! Start the car!
- Hey, look... There!
- What? What?
Damn...
You're scaring me.
I didn't even touch her, really!
I just gave her a little push.
Hey, she was gonna call the police.
A little push and she passed out?
- Yeah! It's insane, right?
- Guardian for Park Jung-yeon?
- Guardian?
- How is she?
Are you the husband?
What? Well...
How is my sister-in-law?
How could you bring her in now?
She was fine just
until a moment ago...
What?
- How good of you...
- Yes.
I can't understand how
you didn't know until now.
- Listen.
- Yes.
It's almost a miracle she's alive!
But why are you getting mad at me?
How could you not know
while living under the same roof?
She must have been in incredible pain.
Didn't you even hear her moaning?
- Did you hear it?
- Uh-huh.
I'm very sorry.
Doctor! The patient's disappeared.
Funeral Home
Daddy, let's go.
Look at this mess!
Damn losers,
I should cut their electricity!
Sleazy crooks.
Is he gone?
Why is life so pathetic?
Why is my life like 4 walls caving in?
I'm going crazy!
Trying to con a lady like that...
We're lucky lightening didn't strike us.
Shut your trap!
You're the wall, the wall.
Hello? Hello?
Oh, Yong-gi!
- Have you gone insane?
- What did you do with it?
- What?
- My store's lease!
Oh, I used it for something.
For what?
To get a loan. I needed some money.
Are you out of your mind?
Do you know what that is?
Oh, I'll pay it back. I will!
Hey, it wasn't even worth much.
Don't even think about throwing that...
I won't take it anymore!
Hey, you almost hit me! Dammit!
Get it back, at once!
Shit...
I'm sorry about the last time.
I'm in your hands.
Where did you get this money?
Actually, my wife has a small shop.
I got a loan off it.
Do you have any insurance?
Insurance?
What?
Just wondering
if you broke your insurance...
- Thanks.
- Don't mention it. I thank you.
When I say thanks, just accept it.
- I'll be in touch.
- Yes, I'll be waiting.
Next week, let's start with
a variety show.
A variety show...
- See you next time.
- Bye.
Bro!
Dammit.
Forget about it! Just forget it!
I'll just call everything off, okay?
Okay? God-dammit...
But sir, this, I...
Wake up, buddy!
You can't even take care of your own
wife! And you want to be a success?
Just take your money back.
Go away! Okay?
There, you happy?
I don't know what you mean.
Your wife's dying right now.
Jung-yeon! Jung-yeon!
Jung-yeon.
Park Jung-yeon, where are you?
You, you... why...
- Why... why...
- What? Just say it!
Your husband's home.
Why won't you even look at him?
Since the home's a mess,
no wonder I can't succeed outside!
- Let go! Let go!
- What's the matter with you?
- You can't go in!
- Don't do this!
What are you? You, a doctor?
- Who is he?
- Park's husband.
How can you leave a patient like that?
Whatever she said, you should have
forced her to get treatment.
What did you do, bastard?
You call yourself a doctor?
Then... what did you do?
Let me.
Here.
What?
What is it?
Can't you see? It's your shop's lease.
Why'd you bring it back? You acted
like you were gonna hit it big.
I was just teasing you to see
how you'd react.
Is it so much fun for you
to drive me crazy?
Is it?
Yeah, it is.
I live for that.
What are you gonna do?
Rotten bastard!
'Traditional Treatment Methods
for Women Disease'
Oh, I thought you were on the phone
with some guy...
Lee Won-jae?
It's the 20 grand we talked about.
Count them.
That's okay.
You don't have a sick person
in your family, do you?
What? No. Why?
Oh, just checking...
Let's start with a variety show
next week.
Show, show, show! Good?
Quite a show you're putting on.
Take this back.
- This is all a con!
- A con?
Fraud, don't you know?
You bad people...
Lee Won-jae, Jung Ae-suk,
Kim Young-man,
Teacher Kwak Hyung-min, what's this?
- You want us to find these people?
- Yes.
Why do we have to?
These are the people my wife
wants to see for the last time.
So, why do we have to find them?
Are we a reunion website? To hunt
down classmates and teachers?
There's no one else I can ask.
So you do it.
How can I leave my wife's side
when she can go any day?
Whatever, just don't bother me. Okay?
All I can think of is the 20 grand.
Go away.
Are you gonna make me call the police?
- Hello?
- Hey, hey.
- Don't put on a show, man.
- Hello. Police Department.
What's wrong with you?
There isn't much time left.
You're driving me nuts. Damn.
Bro, this can be more rewarding
than cheating people.
And also, this Won-jae, see?
This Lee Won-jae, you have to find him.
- Lee Won-jae?
- Yes, him.
Please.
You said nightclubs
were too embarrassing.
He's got no more face
to be embarrassed about.
Hey, in my hey-day,
to live like a man...
We'll do our best.
We need... our money up front.
- Go!
- Come on, bro.
We got no bread.
You said for us to live like men.
We got a good deal, don't you think?
Please stop doing this.
This is pointless.
I'm afraid people will find about
the kid's clothes from last time, too.
Then don't tell anyone.
I'll bring it up to him once but don't
get your hopes up too much.
When women interfere in men's work,
it becomes trouble.
Oh, what's wrong?
Are you okay?
Wake up!
Jungyeon!
Yong-gi, are you okay?
That crazy bastard always hits
someone when he gets drunk.
Come, sit here.
So why'd you keep talking back for?
Hey, I'm okay so...
go and get the rest of our money.
Okay, okay...
Double nose-bleed...
Oh, you're awake.
- Who... brought me here?
- A lady.
- Where is she now?
- She's talking with the doctor.
Hello? Is Jung Yong-gi there?
It must be hard for you to understand.
Why? Is it a crime to be sick?
You see, my husband,
he needs to be able to smile.
- Is that so important?
- It is.
It is most important to me.
I haven't done anything for him.
I don't want to get in his way.
I beg you, please keep my secret.
I wanted to do something for him...
What's this?
- What?
- Don't you know what this is?
Oh, that? I got paid with that.
When I was done, they whined about
having no cash and gave me that.
I threw a fit saying I wouldn't take it...
You mean, they sent it home?
Hey, why don't you take it?
What was the job?
Oh, just a little show...
I filled in at my friend's club.
Why do you live like that?
You're all talk...
Is that the best you can do?
Oh, well... It's supposed to be
good for women so have some.
You take it!
Just take it if I say so!
- Hey, bad move.
- No, it's not.
Dammit, that's a penalty!
Told ya, it was a bad move. Idiot!
- This sucks.
- Quiet!
Well, look at this. Go on, go on.
Who's Young-man?
Hak-chul, go ahead.
Why are you picking on me, huh?
I was just watching. Shit!
Quiet and I won't hurt you, okay?
Just be still.
You know Park Jung-yeon, right?
Jung-yeon Park or fucking whatever,
what do I...
Who?
Park Jung-yeon.
Don't you remember?
Your seatmate in grade school.
Jung-yeon... What about her?
What are you doing? Come on.
Do you know that show,
King of Comedy?
I'm gonna be on it next week.
Woo-jin told me to work hard
and win first prize.
It's not a nightclub.
Jung-yeon was a sweet girl
who kept to herself mostly.
I don't know why but I liked her a lot.
But I found out she liked
someone else.
Jung-yeon, I found out!
He transferred from Seoul.
He's really good at soccer.
He's even gonna be a pro player!
I have no idea why she'd want to
see me.
Why would I see her?
And she has no reason to see me.
If we got together,
it'd be immoral, not right.
Well, there is such a thing
as memories...
Memories? That's nonsense!
I'm busy earning a living.
What good are memories?
- Hak-chul, pull over.
- You gotta pee?
- Get out.
- Why?
Just get out. You talk too much!
If I say get out, get out!
Look, dickhead. She's better off
not meeting a dickhead like you.
- But you said...
- Never mind.
Go play your cards! Let's go.
Hey!
I'll kill you!
I told you, what did I say?
They won't even open the door!
They won't wear it. Why'd you go
to the trouble of knitting 2?
Let's go.
We'll come back another time.
How have you been?
Father... how are you feeling?
I feel well enough to die.
I see...
And you, mother?
I live because I can't die.
You ran out saying you wouldn't be
back! Why are you here?
Oh, father. The ties between parents
and children can't be easily...
- Please.
- Before I throw this...
Say what you're here to say.
And get out!
My wife and I are living very well.
Our happiness is...
- Why you brat...
- Please, dear!
Father... I have something to tell you.
Yes, it's been a long wait.
The second half of King of Comedy
will now begin!
- Hyo-jin.
- Yes.
I'm excited to see what stars
the second half will bring.
- Yes. Welcome our first contestants.
- Who are they?
- Warriors.
- Welcome!
Arrogant pig, today is your funeral.
Attack!
The difference between
Eminem and Jay Leno?
Yo, my name is Eminem.
Hey, folks, this is Jay Leno!
Vocal mimicry of Sin Mun-sun.
It's short so listen well.
Thank you.
Why did you follow me? Why?
Bang! Bang!
The bitch is not home yet.
I'm gonna...
- Mother, I'm sorry.
- You brat!
What have you been up to all night?
- Actually, mother, it's not that.
- Close your mouth!
In our family, you know if you lie,
you'll be petrified!
- Yes, mother.
- Good.
Now answer my questions truthfully.
Where did you sleep last night?
- At a friend's house. Ah!
- You!
You didn't sleep at a friend's house!
Did you sleep with a man last night?
No, mother. I didn't.
Oh, did you sleep in that position?
Did you?
You have brought shame on
our family name!
In my 30 years as a widow,
I never did anything like what you did!
...quarter finalists, Comedy Valley team!
Warriors!
And the Jung Yong-gi and
Yang Chul-soo duo!
Congratulations.
We'll see you next time...
Warriors!
And the Jung Yong-gi and
Yang Chul-soo duo!
Congratulations.
We'll see you next time. Good-bye.
Wow, my wife waited up for me?
Where did you get so drunk?
What's the matter with you?
Can't I have a drink?
What's that now?
Even the asses at the TV station
gave us this instead of cash.
Do you think you're making sense?
Am I? Did I buy this with the money?
Anyway, they say it's really good
for you...
...so boil it for a long time
before taking it.
You asked me to keep you
in luxury, right?
Just wait a little.
Today, I was a hit!
Do you know how funny
I was at the TV station today?
Jung-yeon. Don't look down on me.