If you pair of deuces
are lookin’ for work,
I suggest you get your
scrawny asses in here, pronto.
Now, up on Brokeback
the Forest Service has got designated campsites
on the allotments.
Them camps can be 3 or 4 miles
from where we pasture the woollies.
Bad predator loss, ’cause nobody’s
lookin’ after ’em at night.
Now, what I want
is a camp tender
to stay at the main camp
where the Forest Service says.
But the herder, he’s gonna
pitch a pup tent on the Q.T. with the sheep,
and he’s gonna sleep there.
You eat your supper and breakfast at camp.
But you sleep with the sheep.
A hundred percent.
No fire, don’t leave no sign.
You roll up that tent very morning
in case the Forest Service snoops around.
Yeah?
No.
No!
Not on your fuckin’ life.
You got your dogs, a .30-.30.
You sleep there.
Last summer I had a goddam near 25% loss.
I don’t want that again.
You...
Fridays at noon to by down by the bridge,
with a grocery list and mules.
Somebody with supplies,
will be there at the pick-up.
Tomorrow morning we’ll truck you up
to the jump off.
Jack Twist.
Ennis.
Your folks just stopped at Ennis?
Del Mar.
Nice to know you, Ennis Del Mar.
My second year up here.
Last year, one storm,
the lightning killed 42 sheep.
I thought I’d asphyxiate from the smell.
Aguirre got all over my ass,
like I was supposed to control the weather.
It beats working for my old man.
Can’t please my old man, no way.
That’s why I took the rodeo.
You ever rodeo?
Yeah... well... I mean once in a while.
When I got the entry fee in my pocket.
Yeah.
Are you from ranch people?
Yeah, I was.
Did your folks run you off?
No, they run themselves off.
There was, uh,
one curve in the road in 43 miles...
and they missed it.
So, uh...
the bank took the ranch, and
my brother and sister, they raised me mostly.
Shit!
That’s hard.
Can I?
One thing...
don’t ever order soup.
Them soup boxes are hard to pack.
I don’t eat soup.
Well, watch it there.
That horse has a low startle point.
Don’t think there’s a filly that can throw me.
When you get in this damn saddle
it’s kinda not so bad.
Shit.
Can’t wait till I get my own spread
and won’t have to put up with Joe Aguirre’s crap no more.
I’m savin’ for a place myself.
Alma and me, we’ll be getting married
when I come down off this mountain.
That stay with the sheep,
no fire bullshit.
Aguirre got no right makin’ us do
something against the rules.
No more beans.
Something wrong?
Yeah.
Why didn’t we get the powdered milk and the spuds?
It’s all we got.
Well here’s next week’s.
I thought you didn’t eat soup.
Yeah, well, I’m sick of beans.
Too early in the summer to be sick of beans.
Come on.
Whoa there, whoa, whoa!
Where the hell you been?
I been up with the sheep all day,
I’m hungry as hell and all I find is beans.
What in the hell happened, Ennis?
Come upon a bear, is what happened.
Goddam horse spooked, and the mules took off
and scattered food everywhere.
Beans is about all we got left.
Got whisky or something?
Dumbass mule!
God-damn!
Let me see.
Shit.
Well, we gotta do something about
this food situation.
Maybe I’ll shoot one of the sheep.
Yeah, what if Aguirre finds out, huh?
Supposed to guard the sheep, not eat ’em.
What’s the matter with you?
There are thousands of ’em.
Stick with beans.
Well, I won’t.
Whoo-wee! Yeah!
Was getting’ tired of your dumbass missin’.
Then we won’t.
Ain’t nothing you can do with fish
that can’t do with no elk.
Hey, I’m commutin’ four hours a day.
I come in for breakfast.
I go back to the sheep.
Evening get ’em bedded down,
come in for supper,
go back to the sheep.
I spend half the night checking for damn coyotes.
Aguirre got no right making me do this.
If you wanna switch,
I wouldn’t mind sleepin’ out there.
That ain’t the point.
Point is we both oughta be in this camp.
Goddam pup tent smells like cat piss or worse.
I wouldn’t mind bein’ out there.
Well, I’m happy to switch with you, but...
I warn you, I can’t cook worth a damn.
I am pretty good with a can opener though.
Well you can’t be no worse than me then.
You don’t get much sleep, I tell you that.
Yeah. Come on
I saw a coyote up there.
A big son of a bitch.
Balls on him the size of apples.
Looked like he could eat himself a camel.
You want some of this hot water.
It’s all yours.
I don’t rodeo much myself.
What’s the point of riding
some piece of stock for 8 seconds?
Money’s a good point.
Uh-huh.
If you don’t get stomped winnin’ it.
Yeah.
Well, my old man,
he’s a bull rider.
Thanks.
Pretty well-known in his day.
Though he kept his secrets to himself.
Never taught me a thing,
never once come to see me ride.
There.
Your brother and sister do right by you?
They did the best they could
after my folks was gone.
Considerin’ they didn’t leave us nothin’ but
$24 and a coffee can.
They got me a year of high school.
That was before the transmission went on the pick-up.
Then my sis left,
met a rough-neck and moved to Casper.
Me and my brother, we...
we went and got ourselves some work
on a ranch up near Worland...
... till I was 19.
Then he got married, and uh...
No more room for me.
That’s how come...
...me end up here.
What?
That’s more words than
you spoke in the past 2 weeks.
Hell, that’s the most I spoke in a year.
My dad, he was a farm roper.
He didn’t rodeo much though.
He thought rodeo cowboys was all fuck-ups.
The hell they are.
Well...
- Yeehaw.
- There you go.
Burn his guts out.
Wavin’ to the girls in the stands!
He’s kickin’ me to high heaven!
I think my dad was right.
Tent don’t look right.
It ain’t goin’ nowhere.
Let it be.
That harmonica don’t sound quite right either.
That’s ’cause it got kinda flat,
when my mare threw me.
Oh yeah?
I thought you said that mare couldn’t throw you.
Oh, she got lucky.
Yeah well, if I’d to listen to that harmonica,
I woulda broke it, too.
#I know I shall meet you
on that final day.#
#Water-walkin’ Jesus.#
#Take me away!#
My mama, she believes in the Pentecost.
Yeah?
What exactly is the Pentecost?
I mean, my folks they was Methodists.
The Pentecost... I don’t know.
I don’t know what the Pentecost is.
No one ever explained it to me.
I guess, when the world ends, and...
fellows like you and me,
we march off to Hell.
Speak for yourself.
You may be a sinner,
but I ain’t yet had the opportunity.
Thank you.
I’m gonna go up to the sheep now.
Damn, it’s too late to go to them sheep.
You got an extra blanket?
I’ll just roll up out here.
Catch forty winks.
I’ll ride out first light.
You’ll freeze your ass of
when that fire dies down.
That’s good enough.
Ennis!
What?
Quit your hammerin’ and get in here.
What’re we doin’?
See you for supper.
Come on.
This is a one-shot thing we got goin’ on here.
It’s nobody’s business but ours.
You know I ain’t queer.
Me neither.
Twist.
Your Uncle Harold’s in the hospital
with pneumonia.
Doctors don’t expect he’ll make it.
Your ma sent me to tell you,
so... here I am.
Bad news.
There ain’t nothing I can do about it up here, I guess.
There’s not much you can do about it down there, neither.
Unless you can cure pneumonia.
Jesus.
Them sheep’ll drift if I don’t get back up there tonight.
You’ll get pissed in a storm like this.
And we sure ain’t tryin’.
Close it up.
Well, what are we supposed to do now, huh?
Get on in there and untangle
them sheep out of ours, I guess.
...where is it..?
Maybe the Goddam sheep rachers were off.
We’ve gotta try.
The least we can do is get...
...the count right for Aguirre.
Fuck Aguirre.
Oh yeah, fuck Aguirre.
What if we need work next year?
You ever figure about that?
We gotta stick this out, Jack.
You’ll run them sheep off, if you don’t quiet down.
What are you doin’?
Aguirre came by again.
Said my uncle didn’t die after all.
Said to bring ’em down.
Bring ’em down?  Why?
It’s the middle of August.
Said there’s a storm comin’.
Comin’ in from the Pacific.
Worse than this one.
But that snow barely stuck an hour.
That son-of-a-bitch, he’s cuttin’ us out
of a whole month’s pay.
It ain’t right.
Well, I’d spare you a loan but
I’m short on cash.
I can give it to you when we get to Signal.
I don’t need your money.
I ain’t in the poorhouse.
Shit.
All right.
Time to get goin’, cowboy.
This ain’t no rodeo, cowboy.
Ennis... Ennis.
Come here.
Some of these never went up there with you.
The count ain’t what I’d hoped for, neither.
You ranch stiffs,
you ain’t ever no good.
You wanna give it some gas?
I can’t believe I left
my damn shirt up there.
You gonna do this again next summer?
Well, maybe not.  Like I said,
me and Alma’s gettin’ married in November.
So... I’ll try to get something on a ranch, I guess.
You?
Might go up to my daddy’s place.
Give him a hand through the winter.
I might be back.
If the army don’t get me.
Well, I guess I’ll see you around, huh?
Right.
What the fuck are you lookin’ at?
Huh?
...forgive us our trespasses
as we forgive those who trespass against us,
And lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil.
For Thine is the kingdom, the power and the glory,
for ever and ever. Amen.
Under the powers vested in me, I now
pronounce you man and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
And if you don’t, I will.
You all right?
Stop!
No, you stop!
My old lady’s tryin’ to get me to quit this job.
She says I get too old breaking my back
shovellin’ asphalt.
I told her, strong backs
and weak mind runs in the family!
I told her it keeps me fit.
Yeah!
Well look what the wind blew in.
Hi, Mr. Aguirre.
Wonderin’ if you was needin’ any help this summer.
You're wastin’ your time here.
What, you ain’t got nothin’?
Nothin’ up on Brokeback?
I ain’t got no work for you.
Ennis Del Mar ain’t been around, has he?
You boys sure found a way
to make the time pass up there.
Twist, you guys weren’t gettin’ paid
to leave the dogs to babysit the sheep
while you stemmed the rose.
Now get the hell out of my trailer.
How are you girls doin’?
All right.
Jenny’s still got a runny nose.
Ennis, could you wipe Alma Jr’s nose?
If I had free hands I could!
Shh, come here.
- Girls all right?
- Yeah
Jenny’s still got a cough.
I think you should take the girls into town this
weekend and get ’em an ice-cream or somethin’?
Can’t we move to town?
I’m tired of these lonesome old ranches.
No one for Alma Jr. to play with,...
...besides, I’m scared for Jenny,...
...scared she has another one of
them bad asthma spells.
No, rent in town’s too high.
There’s a cheap place in Riverton
over the laundromat.
I bet I could fix it up real nice.
I bet you could fix this place up
real nice if you wanted to.
I know you’d like it, too.
A real home,
lots of kids for the girls to play with.
Not so lonely like you were raised.
You don’t want it to be so lonely, do you?
I ain’t so lonely now.
You sure the girls are asleep?
Sure.
Come here.
Let her rip..., boys
He’s hangin’ on for dear life
Watch out there, he’s coming for ya!
Send in the clowns!
Shit.
Never mind folks,
there are the rodeo clowns!
I’d like to buy Jimbo here a beer.
Best damn rodeo hand I ever worked with.
Thanks, cowboy. If I was to let every
rodeo hand I pulled a bull off of
buy me liquor I’d a been an alcoholic long ago.
Well, bullseye for you buccaroo, it’s just my job.
Save your money for your
next entry fee, cowboy.
You ever try calf ropin’?
Do I look like I can afford a fuckin’ ropin’ horse?
- Do you wanna go in a little closer?
- No, this is fine, Jenny’ll get scared.
Woo-wee!  Look at this crowd!
Bound to be a lot of pussy on the hunt
in a crowd like this!
...scroll up.
...like a frog.
Where’d you figure the most pussies at?
- Las Vegas?
- California.
...one town in Wyoming, I take Wyoming.
Hey, you might wanna keep it down.
I got two little girls here.
Fuck you.
I don’t want any trouble,
but you need to shut yourself up.
Listen to your old lady tonight.
What about it? You wanna lose
about half your fuckin’ teeth?
It’s all right, buddy.
I’d sure rather not.
Here she comes, ladies and gentlemen!
Oh boy, look at her fly!
It’s Lureen Milton from right here in Childress, Texas.
Come on folks, she’s one of yours...
Let’s give her a big hand.
She’s cleared on two.
She’s around three.
Come on folks, help her home!
Come on, come on!
And the time is...
...sixteen and a half.
Ma’am.
Next up is a newcomer, Jack Twist,
all the way up from Lightning Flat, Wyoming.
Let’s see what the judges say...
I tell you what.
That sure looked like a winnin’ ride to me.
You know that girl?
I sure do. That’s Lureen Newsome.
Dad sells farm equipment. Big farm equipment.
$100,000 tractors,
shit like that.
What you waitin’ for cowboy? A mating call?
Wait, hold on.
You don’t think I’m too fast, do you?
Maybe we should put the brakes on?
Fast or slow, I just like
the direction you’re goin’.
You are in a hurry!
My daddy’s in a hurry.
Wants me home with the car by midnight.
- Hey, Monroe.
- Hey, En.
Is Alma here?
Oh yes, she’s in the condiments aisle.
The what?
- Ketchup.
- Thanks.
Hey honey! What are y’all doin’ here?
I’m in a big hurry.
My boss called and, uh,
he wants me to go up the ranch.
Seems all the heifers decided to calf at the same time.
I figured I could drop the girls off with you.
I got a million things I gotta do
before I leave.
I don’t get off for another three hours.
Mama, I need to pee.
Not now, honey.
Ennis, please, you promised
you’d take them tonight.
I can’t afford not to be there
when they have these calfs.
I’ll lose my job if they lose any of ’em.
And what about my job?
OK, all right.
Call my sister see if she can take ’em.
All right, all right.
Be a good girl for mama, all right?
I’ll be half the night...
Oh boy!
Monroe, I am so sorry!
It’s ok, it’s ok.
I’ll clean this up, just as soon as
I call my sister to come get the girls.
Really, Alma, it’s ok.
- Forget it.
- Alma, come with me.
Watch your feet.
Alma.
I got two whole boxes of formula for you.
- 120 cans
- 120?
Dear, where’d you put ’em?
Oh hell.  Back seat of the car where I left ’em.
Rodeo can get ’em.
I can already see what little Bobby looks like.
Good job, little girl.
He’s the spittin’ image of his grandpa.
Isn’t he just the spitting image of his grandpa?
Hey.
Hey Ennis, you somebody name of Jack?
Maybe. Why?
’Cause you got a postcard that
come general delivery.
Friend, this letter is long over due.
Coming through on the 24th.
Drop me a line say if your there. Jack.
Is it somebody you cowboyed with, or what?
No, Jack, he rodeos mostly.
We was fishin’ buddies.
Maybe we could get a babysitter.
Take your friend to the Knife and Fork...
Jack ain’t the restaurant type.
We’re more likely just...
...go out and get drunk.
If he shows.
Ok, we take one more bite then
we finish with dinner?
There, that’s a good bite.
All right, you’re excused.
Jack fuckin’ Twist!
You son-of-a-bitch.
Alma, this is Jack Twist.
Jack, this is my wife, Alma.
- Howdy.
- Hello.
- Oh, you got a kid.
- Yeah, I got two little girls.
- Alma Junior and Jenny.
- I got a boy.
- Yeah?
- 8 months old. Smiles a lot
I married the prettiest little
gal in Childress, Texas. Lureen.
So me and Jack, we’re gonna head out,
and get ourselves a drink.
- Sure enough
- Pleased to meet you, ma’am.
We might not get back tonight
when we get to drinkin’ and talkin’ and all.
Ennis?
Could you get me a pack of smokes?
If you need smokes there over there in the
top pocket of my blue shirt in the bedroom.
- 4 years, damn!
- Yeah, 4 years.
Didn’t think I’d hear from you again.
I figured you was sore from that punch.
That next summer I drove back up to Brokeback.
Talked to Aguirre about a job.
Told me you hadn’t been back
so I left
Went down to Texas for rodeoin’.
And that’s how I met Lureen.
Made $2,000 that year bullridin’.
Nearly starved.
Lureen’s old man makes serious money.
Farm machine business. Of course he hates my guts though.
- The army didn’t get you?
- Nope, too busted up.
That rodeo ain’t what is was in my daddy’s day.
Got out while he could still walk.
I swear to God, I didn’t know
we was gonna get into this again.
Oh yes, I did. I red-lined it all the way,
I couldn’t get here fast enough.
What about you?
Me?
I don’t know.
That Brokeback got us good, don’t it?
What are we gonna do now?
My God, there’s nothin’ we can do.
’Cause I’m stuck with what I got here.
Makin’ a livin’s about all I got time for, now.
Hey.
Me and Jack’s headin’ out for
the mountains for a day or two.
Do ourselves a little fishin’.
You know your friend could
come inside, have a cup of coffee.
Oh, he’s from Texas.
Texans don’t drink coffee?
You sure that forman won’t fire
you for takin’ off?
That foreman he owes me.
I worked through a blizzard last Christmas.
You remember that?
Besides, I’ll only be a couple of days.
Bring fish, dad. Big, big ones.
Come here.
See you Sunday at the latest.
I’m starvin’. Wanna get something to eat?
- Yep.
Last one in…
Is there anything interesting
up there in Heaven?
I was just sending up
a prayer of thanks.
For what?
For you forgettin’ to bring that harmonica!
I’m enjoyin’ the peace and quiet.
You know, it could be like this,
just like this, always.
Yeah?  How’d you figure that?
What about if you and me had
a little ranch, somewhere?
Little cow and calf operation?
It would be a sweet life.
Hell, Lureen’s old man, you bet he’d
give me a down payment to get lost.
He more or less already said it.
No, I…
I told you, it ain’t gonna be that way.
Well, you got your wife and baby in Texas.
You know, I got my life in Riverton.
That so?
You and Alma, that’s a life?
You shut up about Alma,
this ain’t her fault.
The bottom line is…
We’re around each other and
this thing grabs hold of us again…
...in the wrong place...
...in the wrong time...
...we’re dead.
I tell you…
There were these two old guys
ranched up together, down home.
Earl and Ritch.
And they was the joke of town,
even though they were pretty tough old birds.
Anyway, they found Earl dead
in an irrigation ditch.
They took a tire iron to him.
Spurred him up, drug him around by his
dick till it pulled off.
You seen this?
Yeah, I was about 9 years old.
My daddy, he made sure me and
my brother seen it.
Hell, for all I know,
he done the job.
Two guys livin’ together?
No way.
We can get together once in a while.
Way the hell out in the middle of nowhere, but...
Once in a while?
Every 4 fuckin’ years?
If you can’t fix it, Jack,
you gotta stand it.
For how long?
As long as we can ride it.
There ain’t no reins on this one.
It’s nearly supper time, where in the hell
do you think you’re goin?
To work.
- Hell, I thought you got the day off.
- Well you thought wrong.
- The girls need to be fed.
- Well you take care of it.
Alma!
- Supper is on the stove!
- No-one’s eatin’ unless you’re servin’ it.
I already promised I’d take the extra shift.
Fuckin’ tell ’em you made a mistake, then.
Goddamit, Alma!
Alma!
- You girls need a push or somethin’?
- No.
This is the hard part, gentlemen.
You’re not gonna get that with your Caddy.
I told yous you could do it,
now I’m gonna show you.
- Say, ain’t that piss-ant used to ridin’ bulls?
- He used to try!
Ennis, see you in a couple weeks,
fish should be jumpin’. Jack.
Honey...
Have you seen my blue Parka?
Um, last time I seen it you was in it.
Day we had that big ice storm.
Well, coulda sworn I seen it here.
You know, you been goin’ up to Wyoming
all these years…
Why can’t your buddy come down here
to Texas and fish?
’Cause the Big Horn Mountains ain’t in Texas.
And I don’t think his pick-up could
make it down here anyway.
A new model comin’ in this week, remember?
You the best combine salesman we got.
You’re the only combine salesman, in fact.
Yeah, well, I’ll be back in a week.
That is unless I freeze to death.
And I’ll freeze if I don’t find that Parka!
Well, I don’t have the Goddam Parka!
You know you’re worse than Bobby
when it comes to losin’ stuff.
Speakin’ of Bobby, did you call
his school about gettin’ him a tutor?
- I thought you were gonna call.
- I complain too much.
The teacher don’t like me.
Now it’s your turn.
Ok, fine, so I’ll call later.
All right, fine.
Bye.
- I got 14 hours of drivin’ ahead of me.
- See now, it don’t seem fair.
You goin’ up there two or three times a year
him never comin’ down here…
Ennis, they got an openin’ at the power
company, might be good pay.
Well, if they’re as clumsy as I am,
probably get electrocuted.
Hey daddy!  The church picnic’s next weekend.
Will you be back from fishin’
by next weekend?
Please, daddy, please!
All right, as long as
I don’t have to sing.
You forgettin’ somethin’?
You’re late!
Here we go. No hands!
Come on... Come on...
It’s Saturday night. You know we could still
smarten up and head on over to the church social.
That fire and brimstone crap?
I think it’d be nice.
Ennis, as far behind as we are in the bills,
makes me nervous not to take no precaution.
If you don’t want no more of my kids
I’d be happy to leave you alone.
I’d have ’em, if you’d support ’em.
Custody of the two minor children, Alma Del Mar Jr.
and Jennifer Del Mar is awarded to plaintiff.
Defendant is ordered to pay child support
to plaintiff in the sum of $125…
per month, for each of the minor children
until they reach the age of 18 years.
Del Mar divorce granted,
this 6th day of November, 1975.
ENTERING WYOMING
What are you doin’ here, huh?
Got your message about the divorce.
Come here.
This here’s Jack, Jack these are my little girls.
This here’s Alma Jr. and Jenny.
Hey.
- Say hi, girls.
- Hi.
I got your card the divorce came through.
So, here I am.
I had to ask about 10 different people
in Riverton where you’d moved to.
I guess, I thought that this means you...
No... Jack, I...
I don’t know what to say.
See, I got the girls this weekend, and...
I’m sure as hell sorry.
You know I am.
See, I only get ’em once and month and I missed
last month, so I just… because of the round up...
- So, uh… well,...
- Yeah, all right.
- Jack…
- Well, I’ll see you next month, then.
Here we go.
Here we are!
Hold up there, Rodeo.
Stud duck do the carvin’ around here.
You bet, LD, I was just…
savin’ you the trouble.
Bobby, if you don’t eat your dinner
I’m gonna have to turn off that television.
Why mama?  I’m gonna be eating
this food for the next two weeks.
Hey, you heard your mama.
You can finish your meal,
and then you can watch the game.
Daddy...
Daddy!
Hell, we don’t eat with our eyes!
You want the boy to grow up
to be a man, don’t you, Dolly?
Boys should watch football.
Like Hell.  He’s gonna finishe eatin’ a meal
that his mama too three hours fixin’.
You sit down,
you old son-of-a-bitch!
This is my house, this is my child
and you are my guest.
Now you sit down before I knock
your ignorant ass into next week.
Daddy, tell about when
you rode broncs in the rodeo.
Well, that’s a short story honey,
it was only about 3 seconds I was on that bronc.
Next thing I knew,
I was flyin’ through the air.
Only I was no angel
like you and Jenny, here.
I didn’t have no wings.
And that’s the story of my saddle bronc career.
There you go.
You oughta get married again, Ennis.
Me and the girls worry about you
bein’ alone so much.
Hm… Well, once burned…
You still go fishin’ with Jack Twist?
Not often.
I used to wonder how come
you never brought any trouts home.
You always said you caught plenty,…
…and you know how me and the girls like fish.
So one night I got your crail case open,
night before you went on one of your little trips.
Price tag still on after five years.
And I tied a note to the end of the line.
It said, “Hello Ennis. Bring some
fish home. Love Alma."
And then you come back, lookin’ all perky.
Said you caught a bunch of brown ones
and you ate ’em all up.
D’you remember?
I looked in that case first chance I got
and there’s my note still tied there.
That line hadn’t touched water in its life.
It don’t mean nothin’, Alma.
Don’t try and fool me no more, Ennis.
I know what it means.
Jack Twist?
Jack Nasty.
You didn’t go up there to fish, you…
Now you listen to me.
You don’t know nothin’ about it.
I’m gonna yell for Monroe.
You tell him, I’ll make you eat the fuckin’ floor.
- Get out!
Get out of my house!
Daddy!
Alma!
Bye, Daddy.
Bye!.
Hey asshole, watch where you’re goin’!
You stupid fucker!
Goddam…
... what I’m sayin’ is, if the tax don’t get you,
the inflation will eat it all up.
If you’d see Lureen, punchin’
numbers in her addin’ machine.
She’s gonna crack the zeros.
Her eyes gettin’ smaller and smaller.
Like watchin’ a rabbit tryin’ to squeeze
into a snakehole with a coyote on its tail.
That’s some high-class entertainment
if you ask me.
For what it’s worth.
You and Lureen, it’s normal an’ all?
Sure.
She don’t ever suspect?
You ever get the feelin’...
...I don’t know...
…when you’re in town and someone looks at ya?
Suspicious?
Like he knows.
And then you go out on the pavement and
everyone’s lookin’ at ya like they all know, too?
Maybe you oughta get out of there, you know?
Find yourself some place different,
maybe Texas.
Texas?  Sure, and maybe you can convince Alma
to let you and Lureen adopt the girls.
And we can just live together,
herdin’ sheep.
And it’ll rain money from LD Newsome, and
whisky’ll flow in the stream, Jack, that’s real smart.
Oh hell. You wanna live your miserable fuckin’
life, go right ahead
- I was just thinkin’ out loud.
- Yeah, you’re a real thinker, there.
Goddam.  Jack fuckin’ Twist.
Got it all figured out, ain’t ya?
Just finished my shift.
Wanna dance?
Well, I was on my way to…
- I’m Cassie, Cassie Farrah.
- Ennis. Del Mar.
No more dancin’ for me, I hope.
You’re safe.
My feet hurt.
It’s hard work, is it?
Yeah!
Drunks like you, demandin’ beer after beer,
smokin’...
Gets tiresome.
What do you do, Ennis Del Mar?
Well, earlier today I castrated a calf.
What are you doin’?
Tryin’ to get a foot rub, dummy.
All right.
That good?
…then I pledged Tri-Delt at SMU.
And I sure never thought I’d end up in
a pokey little place like Childress.
Then I met old Randall here at an Aggie game
and he was an animal husbandry major .
So we been here for a month, and he got the
foreman job over at Roy Taylor’s ranch.
Like it or not, here I am.
Was you Tri-Delt?  I was Kappa Phi myself.
Well, even though we ain’t quite sorority sisters,
we might have to dance with ourselves, Lureen!
Our husbands ain’t the least bit
interested in dancin’!
- They ain’t got a smidgen of rhythm between ’em.
- It’s funny, isn’t it!
Husbands don’t never seem to want
to dance with their wives.
- Why do you think that is, Jack?
- I never gave that theory any thought.
- Wanna dance?
- Yes!  Thank you.
- Do you mind?
- No, no problem.
That’s very nice.  Thank you for asking me
to dance with you. I appreciate that.
Randall never does.
It’s a good thing you and Lureen happened along
when you did, otherwise we’d still be stuck on the
side of the road in that there pick-up.
I told Randall we oughta take the car,
of course he’d never listen to me!
He wouldn’t listen to me if
he was goin’ deaf tomorrow!
I told him it’d take more than chewin’ gum
and bailin’ wire to fix that there pick-up.
Well, he’s never been very mechanical, though.
You ever notice how a woman’ll powder her nose
before she goes to a party.
Then she’ll powder it again
once the party’s over?
Why powder your nose just
to go home and go to bed?
I don’t know.
Even if I wanted to know, I couldn’t get
a word in with Lashawn long enough to ask!
- That woman talks a blue streak.
- A lively little gal.
You’ll like workin’ for Roy Taylor.
- He’s solid.
- Oh yeah, Roy, he’s a good old boy.
He’s got a little cabin, down on Lake Camp.
Got a crop house, a little boat.
Said I could use it whenever I want.
We oughta go down there some weekend.
Drink a little whisky, fish some,
get away, you know?
When I was right out of SMU I coulda had
my pick of pretty much any job in North Dallas.
So my pick was Neiman Marcus,
which was a disaster, ’cause honey,
where clothes is concerned, I got no resistence.
I was spendin’ more than I made,
more than Randall ever will make!
We come out here thinking ranchin’ was still
big hats and Marlboros.
Boy was we behind the times!
Hey there, Junior?
You ready?
What do you think?
- Your daddy ever see fit to settle down again?
- I don’t know.
Maybe he’s not the marryin’ kind.
You don’t think so?
Or you don’t think I’m the one for him?
You’re good enough.
You don’t say much but
you get your point across.
Sorry, didn’t mean to be rude.
Hi.
You’re stayin’ on your feet, cowboy.
Excuse me darlin’.
So I’ll pick you and Jenny up
next weekend, after church.
Fine.
- You all right?
- Yes.
Are you sure?
Daddy, I was thinkin’...
Well, with a new baby and all,
mom and Monroe are bein’ awful strict on me.
More on me than Jenny, even.
I was thinkin’, maybe I could...
maybe I could come and stay with you.
I’d be an awful good help,
I know I would.
Well, I...
You know I ain’t set up for that.
With the round-up comin’,
I won’t ever be home.
It’s all right, daddy.
- Well, you know, I’m not sayin’ I wouldn’t...
- It’s all right, I understand.
All right, well, I’ll see you on Sunday, then.
Bye.
Bye, sweetheart.
Gonna snow tonight for sure.
Yep.
All this time, you ain’t found
nobody else to marry?
I been puttin’ the blocks to a good lookin’
little gal over in Riverton.
A waitress, want’s to go
to nursin’ school or somethin’.
I don’t know.
What about you and Lureen?
Lureen’s good at making hard deals
in the machinery business.
But as far as our marriage goes…
... we could do it over the phone.
Kinda got this thing goin’
with the ranch foreman’s wife over in Childress.
I’m scared I’ll get shot by Lureen or her husband
each time I slip off to see her.
Well, you probably deserve it.
Tell you what...
The truth is...
Sometimes I miss you so much
I can hardly stand it.
I guess I’ll head on up to Lightning Flat.
See the folks for a day or two.
There is somethin’ I been meanin’ to tell you, bud.
Well, it’s likely November before
I can come out here again.
After we shift stock and afore winter
feedin’ starts again.
November...
Well, what in the hell ever
happened to August?
Christ, Ennis.
You know had a fuckin’ week to say
some kinda word about this.
Why is it we’re always in the friggin’ cold?
We oughta go south, where it’s warm.
You know, we oughta go to Mexico.
Mexico?
Hell Jack, you know me.  About the only
travellin’ I ever done is around a
coffee pot lookin’ for the handle.
Come on Jack, lighten up on me.
We can hunt in November.
Kill us a nice elk.
I’ll try if I can get Don Wroe’s cabin again.
We had a good time that year, didn’t we?
There ain’t never enough time, never enough.
You know, friend...
This is a Goddam bitch of
an unsatisfactory situation.
You used to come away easy,
and now it’s like seein’ the Pope.
Jack, I gotta work, huh?
I mean, in them earlier days I’d just quit the job.
Well you…
You forget what it’s like bein’ broke all the time.
You ever hear of child support?
I tell you this.  I can’t quit this one,
and I can’t get the time off.
It’s hard enough gettin’ this time.
The trade-off is August.
You got a better idea?
I did once.
You did once.
Have you been in Mexico, Jack Twist?
’Cause I hear what they got in Mexico
for boys like you.
Hell yes, I’ve been in Mexico.
Is that a fuckin’ problem?
I’m gonna tell you this one time,
Jack fuckin’ Twist. And I ain’t foolin’.
What I don’t know,
all them things that I don’t know,
I’d get you killed if I come to know them.
I ain’t jokin’.
Well try this one,
and I’ll say it just once.
Go ahead.
I tell you what.  We could had a good life
together, fuckin’ real good life.
Had us a place of our own.
But you didn’t want it, Ennis.
So what we got now is Brokeback Mountain.
Everything’s built on that.
That’s all we got, boy, fuckin’ all.
So I hope you know that
if you don’t never know the rest.
You count the damn few times that we have
been together in nearly 20 years…
and you measure the short fuckin’ leash you keep
me on, and then you ask me about Mexico.
And then you tell me you kill me for needin’
something that I don’t hardly never get.
You have no idea how bad it gets.
And I’m not you, I can’t ...
... make it on a couple of high-altitude fucks
once or twice a year.
You are too much for me, Ennis.
Son of a horsin’ bitch.
I wish I knew how to quit you.
Well why don’t you?
Why don’t you just let me be, huh?
It’s because of you, Jack, that I’m like this.
I’m nothin... I’m nowhere...
Get the fuck off me!
Shh, shh, it’s all right, it’s all right.
Damn you, Ennis.
I can’t stand this any more, Jack.
And now you’re sleepin’ on your feet like a horse.
My mom used to say that to me when I was little.
And sing…
I gotta go.
See you in the mornin’.
Excuse me.
Hey, Ennis Del Mar.
Where you been?
Here and there.
I left word for you, with Steve, at the ranch.
But you musta got those notes I left at your place.
Looks like I got the message in any case.
Carl?
Yeah, Carl’s nice.
He even talks.
- Good for you.
- Yeah.
Good for me.
I don’t get you, Ennis Del Mar.
I’m sorry.
I was probably no fun anyways, was I?
Ennis, girls don’t fall in love with fun.
Jack, how about November 7 for you? I can meet
you at pine creek. Ennis Del Mar
(DECEASED)
Hello.
- Hello, this is Ennis Del Mar.
- Who?
- Who is this?
- Ennis Del Mar.
An old buddy of Jack’s.
Jack used to mention you.
You’re the fishin’ buddy…
…or the huntin’ buddy, I know that.
Woulda let you know what happened, but
I wasn’t sure about your name or address.
Jack kept his friends’ addresses in his head.
That’s what I’m callin’,
is to see what happened.
Oh yeah.
Jack was pumpin’ up a flat on the truck
out on the back road when the tyre blew up.
The rim of the tyre slammed into his face
broke his nose and jaw...
...and knocked him unconscious on his back.
By the time somebody come along
he had drowned in his own blood.
He was only 39 years old.
Hello?
Hello!
- Was he buried down there?
- We put a stone up.
He was cremated, like he wanted.
Half his ashes was interred here,…
...the rest was sent up with his folks.
He used to say he wanted his ashes
scattered on Brokeback Mountain.
But I wasn’t sure where that was.
Thought Brokeback Mountain mighta
been around where he grew up.
Knowin’ Jack, it might be some pretend place…
where bluebirds sing,
and there’s a whisky spring.
Well, ma’am, we was herdin’ sheep
on Brokeback one summer.
Back in 1963.
Well, he said it was his favourite place.
I thought it meant to get drunk.
He drank a lot.
Is his folks still up in Lightning Flat?
They’ll be there till the day they die.
Thank you for your time.
I sure am sorry.
We was good friends.
Get in touch with his folks.
I suppose they’d appreciate it,…
if his wishes was carried out.
About the ashes, I mean.
- Want a cup of coffee, don’t ya?
Piece of cherry cake?
Yes ma’am, I’ll have a cup of coffee,
but I can’t eat no cake just now.  Thank you.
I feel awful bad about Jack.
Thank you.
I can’t begin to tell you
how bad I feel.
I knew him a long time.
I come by to say... if you want me to take
his ashes up there on Brokeback...
...like his wife said he wanted to,…
...then I’d be happy to.
Tell you what.
I know where Brokeback Mountain is.
Thought he was too Goddam special
to be buried in the family plot.
Jack used to say,…
"Ennis Del Mar," he used to say,
"I’m gonna bring him up here one of these days,
and we’ll lick this damn ranch into shape."
He had some half-baked notion the two
of you was gonna move up here,
...build a cabin,...
...help run the place.
Then this spring...
...he got another fella gonna
come up here with him.
Build the place, help run the ranch.
Some ranch neighbour of his
from down in Texas.
Gonna split up with his wife
and come back here.
So he says.
But like most of Jack’s ideas ...
it never come to pass.
I kept his room like it was when he was a boy.
I think he appreciated that.
You are welcome to go up
to his room, if you want.
Yeah, I’d like that, thank you.
Tell you what...
We got a family plot.
He’s goin’ in it.
Yes, sir.
You’ll come back and see us again.
- Hey there, Junior.
- Hey, daddy.
- Like the car?
- Yeah, is it yours?
It’s Kurt’s.
- Well, I thought you was seein’, uh, Troy?
- Troy?  Daddy that was 2 years ago.
- Troy still playin’ baseball?
- I don’t know what he’s doin’.
I’m seein’ Kurt, now.
- Well, what does Kurt do?
- Works out on the oil fields.
- So he’s a roughneck, huh?
- Yeah.
I guess you’re 19, you can do
whatever you want, is that right?
Sure.
- Daddy, you need more furniture.
Yeah, well, you got nothin',
you don’t need nothin’.
So, what’s the occasion?
Me and Kurt.
We’re gettin’ married.
- Well, how long you known this guy for?
- About a year.
The wedding’ll be June 5th
at the Methodist church.
Jenny’ll be singin’,...
and Monroe’s gonna cater the reception.
Now this Kurt fella...
He loves you?
Yeah, daddy, he loves me.
Was hopin’ you’d be there.
I think I’m supposed to be on the round-up
down near the Tetons.
You know what?...
I reckon they can find themselves a new cowboy.
My little girl is getting married.
To Alma and Kurt.
Jack, I swear.
Subtitles - painstakingly transcribed by Mark!