Okay, I'll drop it
"I would sacrifice my life for you
if only I could know what you want"
"I would agree to everything,
my beautiful one"
"Hahn! I know you, very very well"
"If you want to be with me then,
you better fulfill what I ask of you"
"Hoye 'hoye 'hoye, you are my life"
"You are my beloved"
"The festival of
Lodi is here? - Aha"
"Take your partners? - Aha"
"Grasp the wrist of your beloved"
"and never let it go? - Aha"
"Never let it go"
"don't tell lies? - Oho"
"don't be guilty of blasphemy? - Oho"
"Every oath you swear,
has been broken by you?"
"Oho...?
- Been broken by you"
"as soon as the sun sets every evening
You drink with your cronies"
"The sun goes down and you get drunk
What sort of life is this?"
"You're perfectly right and
henceforth I shall keep it in mind"
"just let me drink today,
from tomorrow I shall not touch a drop"
"Yes, now he will come
straight home at sundown"
"I would sacrifice my life for you"
"My dear one, my fair one,
my handsome one, my beloved"
"My life, O'dear one,
O'beautiful one"
"Everyday I see you playing cards.
More beloved than me..."
"are your fives, sixes and sevens?"
"Why?"
"My card playing foolishness
will end forever"
"Now there will be only two cards
in my life, the king and the queen"
"My life will be yours
if you give up these decks of cards"
"I know you, very very well"
"Hoye 'hoye 'hoye, you are my life"
"You are my beloved"
"The festival of
Lodi is here? - Aha"
"Take your partners? - Aha"
"Grasp the wrist of your beloved"
"and never let it go? - Aha"
"Never let it go"
"don't tell lies? - Oho"
"don't be guilty
of blasphemy? - Oho"
"Every oath you swear,
has been broken by you"
"Oho...? - Been broken by you"
"Whenever I ask you to bring something
you can never remember"
"I asked you for some ribbons for my hair
and you bought sweets"
"Now I have this notebook
in which I will write..."
"so that I can bring exactly
what you ask me to get"
"Yes, slowly he will mend
his ways completely... yes?"
"I would sacrifice my life for you"
"My beautiful one,
my innocent one, my life, my beloved"
"My dear one, my fair one,
my handsome one, my beloved"
"Whether you change or you don't,
you will always be mine"
"I want that in every birth
you should be mine"
"Beloved, in every birth
I'm your worshipper"
"You were mine, you are mine
and you will always be mine"
"Yes without you he will be lost"
"Now every desire of
your heart will be fulfilled"
"The festival of Lodi is here,
take your partners"
"Grasp the wrist of your beloved,
and never let it go"
"don't tell lies,
don't be guilty of blasphemy"
"Every oath you swear,
has been broken by you"
Here you are Bauji. God knows where all
Maati's sent me to look for you
Breakfast is getting cold. Come quickly.
I've got to leave. Come on
come here son... sit
What happened Bauji?
What're you looking at?
I'm looking at my lifetime's
achievements... my legacy, my village
Up until now I was very proud of myself
that I have done great work...
that I've developed this village
from nothing. But yesterday...
that young girl asked me
an innocent question. And I realised.
That I haven't done much...
there's still a lot left to do
Son, in the few years left of my life,
how much can I really achieve?
And after I die this village
will be orphaned
all the work will be left incomplete...
so I was seeing a dream and wondering...
if my dream will come true or not?
- What dream, Bauji?
I saw that after Maati and I are gone
you are here riding my bicycle
Your wife is sitting behind you;
the village is not orphaned
Nothing is left incomplete...
that's what I was seeing...
So why won't this dream come true?
Now that you've become
Squadron Leader Veer pratap Singh...
you'll settle in the city.
Why would you worry about the village?
No Bauji. I am your Veeru
first and foremost
and if you've seen a dream it will
come true. Only I won't be circling around...
on a cycle. I'll use a helicopter.
Will that do? Okay come on now...
otherwise Maati's going to shout.
- Oh there's one more thing
In my dream, I've also seen the girl
sitting behind you on the cycle
Looks like you've already had
some rum is morning Bauji she's a Pakistani
She's pakistani, chinese or japanese,
I don't care. I can just see...
that when this girl sits behind
you on the cycle...
Their hand will rest on your shoulder,
she'll never let you fall...
She'll never let you take a wrong turn.
Come here, sit. Listen...
when the right woman comes
into a man's life...
that's when his life becomes complete.
I chaudhry Sumer Singh am incomplete...
without your Maati. And you
Squadron Leader Veer Pratap Singh...
you will be incomplete without zaara.
That's why... you first understand...
What your heart is telling you;
and then quickly tell her
Otherwise son, it'll be too late
Bauji tell me one thing... - Yes?
Since it's your dream,
is it okay if the wife sits...
the front seat of the cycle?
- Yes it's okay. Should I go tell her?
No please only I will tell her...
- No, no I'll tell her...
No, I do the talking.
- She's downstairs? I'll tell her
Who's marrying? You or I?
- One and the same
One and the same...?
- Never mind. Hey lucky girl...
May I leave, Maati?
- Oh are you leaving?
I'll let you go only on one condition,
you have to promise to come back
Okay I promise. But in return you'll
give me permission for something?
What?
From now on...
may I call you Bebe?
I think we should leave
Or it'll get late.
- I'm ready. I'll go get my bag
You're leaving? - Yes Maati
You'd asked me to come here for Lodi
no matter what. So I came
But I've got leave for only two days.
I've to report at headquarters tonight
I'll put zaara on a bus to amritsar and...
- absolutely not
You'll take zaara to atari
and see her onto her train. She's all alone...
what if something happens to her?
- She's become your favourite in a day?
You used to get upset when it was time
for me to leave and stop me
Today you want me to leave quickly?
- I don't have time for your nonsense
I've made some laddoos for
you and ranjit. Take them
Oh Ginda where've you been?
- Veeru's getting late
Bauji I was filling up diesel.
- Is this any time to fill up?
Let it be
Okay now bless me...
May you live long, son
Tell her, huh? - Yes yes, I'll tell her
Shall I? - Stop pressurizing me
Maati control him
Where are you going?
What's in this?
Not for you. - No...? I see...
for your son...?
- Bauji...
What are you doing?
Here girls don't touch the feet
But daughters ask for blessings before
they bid farewell to their fathers?
May you live long my child
Give your parents a message from me
Tell them that a sixty year old Indian
salutes the values they've put into you
What d'you think?
Will Veeru tell her?
He's chaudhry Sumer Singh's son,
why won't he tell her...
didn't I tell you?
Stop it... - What... where're you going?
Listen...
Squadron Leader Veer Pratap Singh
thank you very much
For what?
In exchange for my one day...
you've given me a lifetime of
memories and relationships
It was a promise from an Indian
to a Pakistani If I didn't fulfill it...
my country's honour
would've been tarnished, no?
I think getting Bebe's ashes here
was God's way to get me here
I was destined to meet all of you.
- Do you believe in destiny?
Of course
don't you? - Not until now
But now I've begun to believe
are you all right?
You aren't all right,
you're hurting?
Look let's rest here for a while...
- No, I'll miss my train
You won't miss your train...
You lean on me... put your hand across
Your anklet
I'll keep it. I'll give it to you later
come... hold on tight...
How many times are you going
to save my life?
As many times you put yourself at risk...
actually there's
a lot of hustle for seats
The festival of Idd is coming up.
At this time...
a lot of people go across the border.
But you don't worry, I'll find a way
Thank God you're all right.
I just got off the train from Lahore
I was finding out about Kiritpur,
when I saw you
Your father has returned. He sent me.
Let's call home and say you're fine.
Then we'll prepare for our return
and you are...?
This's Veer.
Squadron Leader Veer Pratap Singh
Thanks to him, I've managed to get here.
This is raza. Raza Shirazi, my fiance
The seats are done,
we should be leaving now...
So silly of me... I went on talking
about everything...
but I forgot to tell you of raza
- You made a big mistake.
What!
You made a big mistake
zaara I'm a very simple man. I speak
frankly and understand things simply
It's the first time I started thinking
differently because of Bauji and Maati
The entire journey I kept thinking up
a way to stop you, not to let you go...
and tell you that I really like you
and if you think I'm okay then...
let's get married
and we'll breeze through life together
just like these past two days
But the guy up there has strange ways
He kept building my confidence
and then when we got here...
He changed the entire story
You must be wondering why
I'm telling you all this right now
please don't get me wrong. I understand
that you belong to someone else...
and there's nothing between us
nor can there ever be...
but where ever...
whenever you need a friend...
just remember that there is a man
across the border...
Who will give his life for you
c'mon zaara we must leave
Mr. Veer...
zaara told me how you saved her life.
Now I'm indebted to you.
So tell me how may I repay you?
- Just keep zaara happy...
the debt will be repaid
careful Mr. Veer...
lest I get the impression
that you've fallen in love with zaara
what is love... I don't know.
But yes...
I do wish from the bottom of my heart
that zaara never has tears in her eyes
That she always keeps smiling
If that's what you call love,
then love it is
Mr. Veer, you're talking about
my fiancee to my face
I don't know whether to consider this
a compliment or an insult
If you think of this as nothing,
it's better. For the truth is that...
I'm nothing to her
and you are everything for her
Good Bye
Let's go
"just for two moments,
the caravans of our dreams made a stop"
"and then you went your way
and I went mine"
"just for two moments
existed the story of our hearts"
"and then you went your way
and I went mine"
"Was that really you
or was it a luminous sunbeam"
"Was that you or was it a blossoming bud"
"Was that you or was that the
monsoon of my dreams"
"Was that you or was
that a cloud of happiness"
"Was that you or was it
a full blooming flower"
"Was that you or did I find a
beautiful new world"
"just for two moments,
the caravans of our dreams made a stop"
"and then you went your way
and I went mine"
"just for two moments existed
the story of our hearts"
"and then you went your way
and I went mine"
"Seven eighty six"
dinner time
and Ma'am your visiting time is over
You'll have to leave now
I'll come back tomorrow
Sorry, your story is left incomplete
come on, Ma'am
and seven eighty six, I'm sending
someone to take the plate in ten minutes
Eat quickly or you'll have to sleep
on an empty stomach again
Have you ever wondered
why his number is seven eighty six?
What...?
Have you ever wondered...?
From the thousands of prisoners here...
how come this lone Hindu prisoner
has got allah's holy number?
This is not a mere coincidence,
this is God's great miracle...
His way of telling all of you that this
This God's own man. Treat him with respect
Next time you speak to him
so rudely...
give a serious thought
to what I've just said.
These are Ladoos.
My mother sent them for you
please have some.
She has sent them with her blessings
What happened?
You don't like it?
No... no... these are just like
the ones Maati used to make
Things made by a mother's hands
are the same everywhere
May I have one more?
Yes please, these're all for you
Tell your mother she's filled
my entire childhood into this little box
delicious
all night, I was telling
my mother your story
My mother cried a little
and went to sleep
But I stayed up waiting for dawn.
Kept thinking how and why...
did you get here...? Kept wondering
why didn't this story end at that station?
This story couldn't have ended there.
Because so far this was only...
a tale of Veer's love.
Zaara's love had not yet begun
and without knowing what zaara felt
Veer's story and Veer's life...
would both remain incomplete
jehangir Hayaat Khan, zaara's father
and the pride of Lahore
Since the inception of pakistan
the name of the Hayaat Khan family...
was synonymous with respect,
power and glory
jehangir Hayaat Khan was taking
his first step into politics...
with the help of abdul Shirazi...
another rich, respectable man
of Lahore...
he was raza Shirazi's father
zaara and raza's marriage
was no ordinary relationship
all these people's futures were
dependent on this alliance. In this situation...
zaara's coming to India all by herself
was a very irresponsible act
and to forgive such an act
was not jehangir Hayaat Khan's nature
It was a month since
zaara had returned...
but her father had not
yet spoken with her
God Ma'am, I'll burst with happiness
what an elegant outfit...
and look, I think this
jewellery set is an antique
I think it belongs to
Mr. raza's ancestors
Our zaara is very lucky. Mr. raza has
everything. Respectability, money
There's no doubt in that.
He has everything by God's grace
There could not be a better match
than this. Just pray for them
There's a man across the border
who will give his life for you
Ma, can you give up your life
for papa?
Of course. He's my husband.
I can do anything for him
and would papa give up
his life for you?
What kind of a question is that!
Pray to God...
such an
occasion does not arise
But if such an occasion were to arise?
Then can you say for sure that
papa would give up his life for you?
Have you gone mad?
Shabbo give me some lime
my hands have become sticky
That means, you're not sure?
Listen baby, between a woman's love and
a man's love there's a huge difference
a woman loves with
all her heart and soul
Men do not have the strength
to love like that. I know why...
you're asking me this question.
But don't expect this from raza
just give him your heart and soul
and fulfill your duties
and I am very sure that
he will fulfill his duties too
But he won't give up his life
for me, no...?
You're talking nonsense
Here Shabbo, you put it.
This girl is going to drive me mad
There's a man across the border
who will give his life for you"
But I know someone who will willingly
give up his life for me
a person whose eyes are honest
and whose words have honour...
a man who can forsake everything
for a woman's love...
a person to whom it makes no difference
that I'm a Pakistani and he's an Indian
Who're you talking about?
What've you been up to?
Tell me the truth... swear on me!
He hasn't even touched me Ma,
but I have lost my heart and soul to him
don't you know your father?
Till now he's not talking to you
If he finds out about this he'll kill you!
Don't you realise?
You're getting engaged today!
You're going to be married soon
Now it's wrong to think of
anything else zaara
Oh Stupid girl, love is only found
in books, and poetry! Not in life
That's what I thought until now...
until now...
Shabbo please put some sense into her,
otherwise a storm will hit this house
just understand one thing zaara.
Your future is with raza
Now neither you can
change this, nor God
What's all this zaara...?
It's love Shabbo
It doesn't come with reason
Sit
Since you're my only child
I've given you a lot of freedom
You've been brought up more like
a son than a daughter
Normally a mother explains
a daughter's duties to her
But since I think of you as my son,
I myself shall do the honours
You're aware...
that your grandfather was one
of the most respected politicians of Pakistan
But he died just a few days before
he could reach the pinnacle of his success
Ever since...
being his successor I've been trying to
get his party to that same level
I've been unsuccessful so far.
But now thanks to raza's father...
success seems near
In a few days you'll be going to their
house, taking my honour with you.
That's your duty to understand
the sensitivity of this bond...
...to spread
happiness in good times and bad...
to strengthen the bonds of
every relationship
and no matter what, safeguard
their honour as well as ours
any small mistake on your part
can destroy everything
I hope you understand what I'm saying
Yes
do you have anything to say?
Then would you please come here?
It's been a long time since I've
seen the dimples of your cheeks
I hope you haven't
left them in India
That's my girl
"dearest behold..."
"The distances have gone"
"I am here, here, here and here"
"Beyond all borders and encumbrances"
"I am the secret you can never hide"
"I am the gesture you can never forget"
"Why are you surprised
at these vibrations"
"Because I am the sound of your heart"
"Listen, if you can to the
rhythms of your heart"
"I'm here, here, here and here"
"Beyond all borders and encumbrances,
here I am..."
"here, here and here"
"I and only I am now
in your thoughts"
"I am in all your questions
and your answers"
"I occupy all your dreams"
"I am in the radiance of your sight"
"You can see me wherever
your vision goes"
"I am here, here, here and here"
"dearest behold..."
"the distances have gone"
"I am here, here, here and here"
"Beyond all borders and encumbrances
I am here, here, here and here"
Tell him to get out of my sight!
I see him everywhere
He's embedded in my soul Shabbo!
Ask him to leave
Please tell him Shabbo
...please tell him
Yes, Squadron Leader Veer Pratap Singh
Hello, captain Veer Singh?
I'm Shabbo speaking...
Shabbo...? I'm sorry I can't place you
I'm calling from zaara's house
an unknown girl whom I'd never met
before, was giving me...
the biggest news of my life.
She very simply told me that...
zaara is in love with you and she's
about to get married
come to Lahore, take zaara away
She'll never be able to take
this step all by herself
She says that you can give
your life for her
and then she asked me
one last question
How much do you love zaara?
I didn't have an answer
to that question then
Neither do I have one now
How much do I love zaara
I don't know
I know
an Indian air Force Pilot
is not permitted to come to Pakistan
So I know that the minute
you got this news...
you resigned knowing fully well
that you will never be able to rejoin
Then without telling anyone
you left for Lahore...
not knowing the outcome of the journey.
Would you reach on time?
Would you meet zaara?
Would zaara come back with you?
Or would you yourself be able to return
...you didn't know anything
But you still left?
perhaps you don't know,
but I know...
how much you love zaara,
I know
Welcome sir, I'm Shabbo
I'm sorry I couldn't arrange for
anything better than this
Wow, you can see
the entire city from here
There can't be a better room than this
in the whole of Lahore
I didn't tell zaara
that you're coming
I was scared that
she would stop me
day after tomorrow is her wedding.
She can't come out of her house
But tomorrow she'll be going
to the shrine with everyone
This is Munir, my younger brother.
He'll bring you to the shrine
Then we'll leave it to God
So Munir, my fate is in
your hands now
Well, I'll leave
Leaving...?
I got to leave, if I'm away for long
they'll start wondering where I am
If you need anything Munir's here
Thank you Shabbo
I didn't think you'd come,
but now after meeting you...
I'm sure you'll take zaara with you
How could I not come?
My Babuji says, true love happens
only once in a lifetime
and when it does
no God or allah can come in its way
Tomorrow we'll know how true
my love is in allah's eyes
"I have broken all the
barriers of society"
"I have left the world
and come to you"
"a besotted lover has
come to your door"
"Has come, has come...
- a besotted lover has come"
"a besotted lover has
come to your door"
"Besotted by you, besotted
by you, besotted by you..."
"a besotted lover has come
to your door"
"He is completely devoted to you"
"He is completely obsessed by you"
"He will die for your love"
"a besotted lover has
come to your door"
"If I see your face"
"I will forget all my sorrows"
"These tears that are flowing,
- This is all they are saying"
"You are beyond where I am
But I have come here"
"If I could have one favour
just a glance from your eyes"
"I would give my breath and heart
I would give my entire life"
"Like the moth dies on the flame..."
"a besotted lover has
come to your door"
"What a turn this story has taken"
"He has to die for your love
- What a turn this story has taken"
He's conscious
but he doesn't want to be
He's listening to everything
but he doesn't want to hear
He's festering the shock deep within
as if he's punishing himself
The next 24 hours are very critical.
He may not be able to take another shock
The nurse is here and I will keep coming
every three or four hours
don't worry, sister-in-law,
they were all our own people
Thank allah that the news hasn't
spread in the city
anyway tomorrow after the wedding
all the wagging tongues will stop
after all that's happened
raza's still ready to get married?
Mariam Ma'am, this marriage is not only
between raza and zaara
There's a very deep and a serious pact
behind it. It's on this foundation...
that your husband's and after him
raza's career rests
raza is very well aware of this.
Now zaara has to understand this...
if this wedding doesn't
take place tomorrow, then...
jehangir Hayaat Khan's daughter's name
will be linked to an Indian man forever
Mr. Khan's years of hard work
will be ruined...
he'd lose the elections for sure and
he'll face a lifetime of disgrace
He will not be able to bear
the weight of that shame...
he won't be able to bear it
prepare for the wedding, Brother abdul
Tomorrow there will be a wedding
in this house
Where're you going?
To zaara's house...
Please don't go anywhere!
Let tonight pass
raza is looking for you everywhere!
The house is completely silent
You can't go there and do anything.
Abbaji is in deep shock
I am the cause for the shock
and the solution
I hadn't come here just to see
zaara's face
If nobody speaks,
there's bound to be silence
Someone has to make the first move,
whether it brings on a storm or a wedding
My name is Mariam Hayaat Khan.
I'm zaara's mother
But perhaps today I have lost
the right to call her my own...
because my daughter's
not mine anymore
She's yours now
I've come to ask you to give
my daughter back to me
please give us back our daughter!
Otherwise her father will die
He won't be able to bear the shame,
he'll die
I've heard that you save lives...
you're the one who saved zaara's life
So now please save her
father's life
I beg of you, please save his life
Else he'll die...
he'll die...
a mother never has to beg to her son,
she just has to order
zaara has always and will
always belong to you
did you think that I would've taken
zaara away without your permission?
People say that love is blind,
so we were also blinded by our love
We could only see each other
We didn't see if we were harming anyone...
hurting anyone or...
if someone's life was at stake...
we couldn't see anything
But now everything's clear
Love can't be more important
than someone's life. Don't you worry...
zaara will marry the person
of her parent's choice
You prepare for the wedding.
I'll talk to zaara
I promise you that she will
willingly agree to the marriage
Is every son from
your country like you?
I don't know that
But yes every mother in my country
is exactly like you
If you think that I've made
a wrong decision...
then just tell me. No one will be able
to stop me from taking you to India
Your decision is absolutely right
This has happened because of
one silly mistake on my part
I'd made a promise to myself
that I won't break
If only I'd been able to stop myself
when I saw you yesterday...
That...
one silly mistake of yours will heIp
get me through the rest of my life
If you'd taken that away from me
then what would I take back with me?
Why is God doing this to us?
I've never done anything wrong
in my life
So why is he punishing me like this...?
I'm keeping two moments of
your life with me
and I'm giving two moments
of my life to you
These two moments are the symbol
of our love
These two moments make our love story
Now we'll live our lives on
these two moments...
but with a smile
Neither will our love weaken
Nor will our duties
remain unfulfilled
You'll honour your parents
by being a good wife
and I'll fulfill Bauji's dreams
back in the village
and after you've had
eight-ten children...
you bring everyone along
for a visit
I'll take you for a ride on a cycle
and show you a new village
But after having eight-ten kids
I won't be able to sit on a cycle
Yes, you've got a point.
Then I'll arrange for a tractor