MING DYNASTY
DURING WAN LI PERIOD
THE FORBIDDEN PALACE
THE IMPERIAL LIBRARY
THE PRIZED SUNFLOWER VOLUME
I found it.
The Prized Sunflower Volume?
Leave us!
The Prized Sunflower Volume
is a secret volume of martial arts.
It was written in the third year of the
Hong Wu period. It contains mystical...
Enough!
This is a very serious issue.
The Western Imperial Secretariat
has always worked against us.
If they found out that this has occurred
in an area under ourjurisdiction,
they will definitely go to the emperor
and tell him everything.
If the emperor takes any notice,
it will be the end of us.
There has been so much turmoil
in the Imperial household,
and now with trouble ahead,
I doubt we'll be able to avoid recrimination.
Do you need me
to make preparations...
...to find a scapegoat?
The Forbidden Palace
is extremely well guarded.
An outsider would not be able
to enter and steal things.
Check and see if any Imperial officials
have recently retired or asked for leave.
Be mindful not to involve too many
strangers in this issue.
I understand.
To avoid complications,
we'll only involve our own people.
FUJIAN PROVINCE,
FUZHOU DISTRICT
In the past ten days, two people left the
Imperial Household. One died from illness.
The other is Imperial official
Lam Jan Nam.
His arch rival became his supervisor.
That was his reason for resigning.
He didn't retire then,
but instead waited to retire three days ago.
He's our prime suspect.
This is his ancestral home.
Lam Jan Nam is inside the house.
We've blocked off the surrounding roads.
We've arrested everyone
coming in and out of the house.
Now all that's left to do
is for Your Eminence to seize him.
Sir, as we control this area, why are we
still so cautious, when we can attack?
If we raise the pennant
of the Eastern Imperial Secretariat,
and our retrieval fails, and rumour of it
gets out, how am I to explain it?
We must blame it on someone else.
Lam Jan Nam's family
won't make it through the night.
Why the panic?
What's the problem?
Sir, someone has crossed
our defensive line.
Quickly unblock
their meridian points!
Yes!
We have a martial arts expert.
- What happened?
- Someone's gone into the house.
Everyone, be on your guard.
Someone has crossed the line.
We don't know who it is. Quickly hide
the gunpowder and arm yourselves!
Arm yourselves with swords and knives.
Be alert! Hurry up!
- Be careful!
- Okay!
Sir, didn't you ask
some people to come to help us?
Could it be them?
Soldiers have to be deceitful. We need to
stay calm and see whether it's friend or foe.
Is it Grand Master Ngok?
Are you from Hua Mountain Sect?
I'm Ling Wu Chung of Hua Mountain!
What the...?
I'm under orders to request an audience
with Official Lam Jan Nam.
Shoot!
Hey, hurry up!
We've got their full attention!
How can we be this discourteous?
May I ask who in this crowd
is Official Lam Jan Nam?
I am no longer an Imperial official. There's
no need to extend me that courtesy.
Then why so many
officials and soldiers outside?
Are they your men?
- They are...
- Wait... You're correct.
You have already resigned,
yet you can still mobilise so many troops.
We almost couldn't get in!
We who have been officials
naturally have many enemies.
The Imperial Court values me,
so it sent troops to protect us.
So you two are...
Like I said before,
I'm Ling Wu Chung of Hua Mountain.
- I'm from Hua Mountain...
- Ajunior student. He's like a brother to me.
I blocked two of your men's meridian
points. Let me go and unblock them.
No, don't bother.
They have not studied martial arts
well enough. Let them suffer.
Guards, take them to the kitchen,
and feed them if they're hungry.
- Yes!
Our sifu sent us to deliver
something to you, Mr. Lam,
but there's also a letter. You have to read
the letter before opening the package.
- Ngan, get it out.
- Okay.
My sifu said I had to hand it directly
to Official Lam, I mean, Mr. Lam.
Bring it over.
Hurry up!
What were you thinking?
Where did you put it?
It's not here?
I think I gave it to you.
- When did you ever give it to me?
- I'm sure I did!
I was afraid to lose it,
so that's why I gave it back to you!
- Where is it?!
- So sorry for keeping you waiting.
Reporting in, your Eminence.
We found a letter on the mountain.
The martial arts expert
must have dropped it.
"My dear friend Jan Nam.
Due to other matters,
my arrival has been delayed,
so I sent a senior student,
Ling Wu Chung,
to deliver a box of sleeping gas,
to aid you against your enemies.
Don't forget that
the box is booby-trapped.
Please do not open it
unless it's absolutely necessary.
Your Eminence,
look at the smoke.
There must be a problem.
If we attack them while they are helpless,
we'll be sure to overcome them.
This is obviously a trap!
They want to trick me with a letter!
We will do nothing!
Your Eminence is right.
We almost fell into a trap.
Put out the fire!
Quickly, get lots of water!
Hurry up! Get water!
There's gunpowder here!
Don't use water!
Use cloth to extinguish the smoke!
Ifound it! Ifound it!
This isn't it.
That's a fortune-telling note?
You airhead!
Find the letter!
- Grab those two!
- Yes!
Who are you people?
Forgotten already?
We're from the Hua Mountain Sect.
Yeah.
How do I know you're not fakes?
- What do you mean fakes?
- Wait...
You can test us.
As Mr. Lam is good friends
with my sifu,
he must recognise
Hua Mountain Sect swordplay.
Let me demonstrate,
then you can all pass judgement.
Please step aside,
there isn't enough space.
Up on the tall mountain peaks,
travelling alone on the plains,
the wind blows away
the fallen leaves,
making the bare branches
look even more lonely.
The angry sword
makes the skies tremble.
The thunder echoes
in the softly falling rain.
There is no stronger warrior
in the Shu kingdom.
I turn to attack,
I gaze upwards to the moon,
I gaze downwards and reminisce...
Be careful with the flame!
I got confused!
In my excitement, I added my own moves.
It wasn't Hua Mountain style.
- Let me restart!
- It's enough.
I believe you're
Hua Mountain Sect students.
If it's enough, then I'll stop.
Brother...
Is there something
you have difficulty expressing?
What's important is not whether
we are students from Hua Mountain,
but whether you are really
the venerable Mr. Lam,
because our sifu has a message
which we have to communicate personally.
All right.
The Lam family's "Iron Palm",
including the move "Razing mountains,
draining seas" is relatively well-known.
I defer to your judgement.
Bravo! "Razing mountains, draining seas"
lives up to its name! Very powerful!
He did it behind his back.
How could you tell that was it?
He's got himself out of breath.
If you don't applaud, and are so tactless,
how are you going to progress in society?
- Bravo! Bravo!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
I've shown myself to be Lam Jam Nam.
What is the message?
He said...
- He said he...
- Come down quickly!
Say it louder. I can't hear you.
Hurry up! Move it! Move it!
Can you be more quiet?
- Everyone, be quiet fora moment!
- Please repeat what you said.
My sifu says he's busy and
he'll come next time. Did you hear that?
- Let's continue what we're doing.
- That's it?
- Yeah.
- Hurry up! Hurry up!
Escort the guests upstairs!
Apologies for not taking care of you
properly. Please rest upstairs.
Escort the guests upstairs!
Please.
Don't worry.
We won't come down.
Come and practice singing
together! Hurry up!
I haven't even caught my breath yet.
Must we keep practising?
Practise less? We're surrounded
by four-sided Chu songs.
What's a four-sided Chu song?
How do we sing that?
Sing?! We're surrounded
by enemies inside and outside.
We're pretending to sing to pretend
everything's okay, that's all.
I see.
Actually...
There are two groups of people,
inside and outside.
Once they start fighting,
we need to leave immediately!
Wow, it's so exciting!
It's really been a trip
well worth the effort!
I'm going to stay and watch.
Hey! Continue playing!
You're a good enough
fighter to stay and watch?
Sifu doesn't know
you came with me.
If something happens to you, I'll never be
able to go back to Hua Mountain again.
Then why don't we leave now?
I don't want to get you banished.
I've no idea how many
martial arts experts are outside!
If it's that simple to leave,
everyone would have left already.
We'll wait till it gets dark,
then it'll be easier to leave.
Yes.
Something's wrong. There may be
another martial arts expert coming.
- Protect his Eminence!
- Yes!
Protect his Eminence!
I, Jo Lang Sim, Five Mountain
Ranges chief, pay my respects.
Be careful!
He's behind the screen!
"Cold Ice That Takes Lives!"
"Driving Great Waves
to Rise Up!"
I, Jo Lang Sim, Chief of the Five Mountain
Ranges, pay my respects to Lord Gu!
Lord Gu!
- Your Eminence!
- Lord Gu!
- Rise, everyone.
- Yes!
Fall back.
I am fully aware of who's loyal to me.
Although you're a practitioner of dark arts,
you've worked hard as my advocate.
I'm just a loyal dog playing fetch. Serving
your Lordship means my future is limitless.
This time your Lordship
wants me to retrieve a book called
The Prized Sunflower Volume.
I've not had much chance to study,
to avoid making a blunder.
May I ask what kind of book
the Prized Sunflower Volume is?
Hey!
It's a hand-written scroll.
It only teaches the art of gardening.
If it's only about gardening,
then it will be an easyjob.
I will do as Your Eminence wishes,
down to the last detail.
You don't have to know what
the Prized Sunflower Volume is.
You have my warrant issued
by the Imperial Court.
Acting according to
my wishes will suffice.
Rest assured, Your Eminence, I will do
my utmost. Should I leave anyone alive?
- Try your best to avoid complications.
- As you wish.
I'll begin at nightfall.
Brother, the water's really cold.
You're not dressed!
Who wears clothes to bathe?
Quickly bring my robes over here.
Still you rely on others!
You should have got
some clean clothes ready.
All this just because I asked you
to get me some clothes?
If you don't, what am I going to wear?
Hurry up, I'm cold.
Please don't.
No. If! help you once, you'll rely on me
every time. Get them yourself.
You even said
we were like brothers!
Who is it?
- I've come to deliver dinner.
- Coming!
Put on your clothes.
Coming! Coming!
They're trousers!
They're also trousers!
My guests!
Give it to me.
As we're in the countryside,
we go to bed early. Please retire early.
Okay, okay.
As we're renovating downstairs,
you'll have to dine in your quarters.
Renovating?
I thought you were demolishing.
See if the water's cold.
If it is, add some hot water.
Yes.
Don't come here! The water's hot enough.
Do you want me to boil to death?
Don't come over here!
Leave me alone!
He's boiling with rage! The water's
hot enough. You don't have to add more.
Okay, we won't add any then.
Enjoy your dinner.
Okay, okay.
It's getting dark.
Put your clothes on, quick!
If you're going to be disguised
as a man again, don't bathe, skinny boy!
Wow!
There's so many people here!
Are you all waiting to leave too?
- Yes, yes, yes.
Hurry up
and extinguish the light first!
You have the guts to knock,
but not to show your face?!
If you prefer to be a coward,
then stay out and freeze!
The Chief of the Five
Mountain Ranges has arrived!
I am Jo Lang Sim, the Chief of
the Five Mountain Ranges.
Last month
we fed to the crocodiles
a man masquerading
as the leader of the Five Lakes.
The Five Mountain Ranges area
produces many heroes.
On what grounds are you
the leader of the Five Mountain Ranges?
With no obvious grasp of humility,
why don't you just call yourself king?!
Lam Jan Nam, I'm not going to waste time
talking to a useless fool like you.
Quickly surrender the scroll!
If you were well-educated and well-bred,
you wouldn't be seen as a shit-eating dog!
A shit-eating dog
is better than being dead!
Light the gunpowder fuse
when the innkeeper turns around.
Hey, I dropped something.
Pick it up quickly!
Brother, I think I lit
the gunpowder!
Did you hide
a lot of gunpowder here?
- Yes.
- Let's run away quickly!
- Hurry up! Let's go!
The gunpowder will explode!
Let's go quickly!
We can't! There are still people inside.
We have to let them know!
Are we going to make it in time?
Fine. As you're illiterate, you can take
a lucky guess from all my books.
The gunpowder's been lit!
Get away quickly! Get away quickly!
It's been lit?
Let's go!
It's a trap!
He was just supposed to keep the heat
off us, but he's done this instead!
- Extinguish the fire!
- Yes!
- The Hua Mountain style swordplay?
- Skinny boy!
Don't fight one of your own!
Mr. Lam? Your leg!
I'm injured.
We can't stay here long.
Have you seen my wife
and son, Lam Ping Ji?
Lam Jan Nam! I know
you're hiding in the reeds!
Jan Nam!
My lady!
Hurry up and show yourself!
Let's make a deal!
Let's see what you have to offer!
If you want a sample of what I have,
I'll show you!
- Jan Nam!
- Don't make a move!
For their safety, we decided
to take separate escape routes,
but it's been
to their detriment instead.
You won't be able to save them.
Let's think of something else.
I'm really at a disadvantage now!
You want to bargain?!
Take action! Break her arms!
Help!
Jo Lang Sim! You're a member
of the martial arts world!
How dare you use such despicable
methods against an unarmed old lady!
I have no mercy for criminals
condemned by the imperial court!
Jan Nam!
Catch!
What is it?
It's... an eyeball.
Jo Lang Sim! Stop immediately!
I'll come out now!
It's almost dawn now.
My men are very good at qing gong.
Very soon you won't be able to hide!
I've been in a sea of danger
my whole life.
Now that I've lost my position
in the imperial court,
I was afraid my descendants
would be under threat from my enemies.
This is why I wanted
a means for self-defence.
I didn't think it would result in
the family break-up and death.
Ling Wu Chung,
if I don't make it out alive today,
then I need to ask you
to fulfil my last wish.
Mr. Lam, I'll do as you wish.
But you have to swear to the heavens
to keep your promise.
I, Ling Wu Chung, swear to the heavens,
if I break my promise,
bolts of lightning will kill me and
my corpse will remain unburied.
Tell my son, Lam Ping Ji, that I hid our
family treasure under the water wheel.
Remember that.
My son's left shoulder has a scar
shaped like a cross
from a martial arts accident.
Lam Jan Nam!
You're heartless like a wolf!
Don't you want your woman anymore?!
You animal!
Why haven't you stopped?!
I've already cut out her tongue. Even if
she wants to scream, she can't anymore!
Fight me to the end!
You have to make the best of the situation,
and leave this place by yourself.
No, I want to be with you!
I have to go save them!
Sifu didn't realise it would be this serious
when he asked me to come.
Find him and tell him.
I'll going!
Brother!
Mr. Lam!
Chief! I think there's a student
of the Hua Mountain Sect behind Lam.
Bow and arrow!
Mr. Lam!
An arrow!
Remember my message...
As long as you're able to tell
my son Lam Ping Ji,
then my death
will be worth something...
Mr. Lam!
Skinny Boy! Let's go!
Your Eminence!
You've done very well.
You've burned all the corpses of the Lam
family, but as so many people have died,
sooner or later,
the local magistrates will be alerted.
Don't worry, Your Eminence.
I've arranged matters with my men.
There's a Sun Moon Sect here,
a Miao minority group.
They specialise
in smuggling salt in this area.
We can blame them.
If the local magistrates pursue this
Han Chinese and Miao minority conflict,
the Miao could rebel.
SUN MOON KILLS LAM FAMILY
Someone will be punished
when news reaches the capital.
They won't be able to take
responsibility for this.
It won't matter.
It'll just be forgotten in the end.
You really know how to react quickly.
You react so quickly. If I'm not careful,
then you might even get ahead of me!
Please forgive me for making decisions
without first consulting you.
Young man, if you take on too much
yourself, you might lose your head!
- Get up.
- Yes, Your Eminence.
WANTED:
SUN MOON SECT CRIMINAL
Uncle, there's so many people
on the pier. Is the boat late?
They're sending someone off.
- Oh...
- The Head of Seun Fung Tong is retiring.
After he leaves, no-one knows
what will happen in the future.
We don't know how long
the new Head will last.
We all grew up
relying on this body of water.
I've been in service 41 years, and although
not everyone is in harmony with each other
there are only minor eddies of dissension
between each other,
and we haven't had to
weather a storm yet.
Hey! I think I've seen these people
in the Lam family home.
- Let's leave quickly!
- Yeah.
Where's the backpack?
Who is it?
- If you want to know, ask him yourself.
- Fine!
Without conflict, there would be no world of
martial arts. There would be no heroes.
I am now relinquishing the burdens.
I'm handing over the management
of Seun Fung Tong to you now.
Venerable Head of the Tong,
don't worry.
In the past few years,
more boats are travelling on this river,
and the imperial court is also
paying close attention to our well-being.
I won't make major changes,
just minor adjustments,
so that we can all lead
peaceful lives.
Iwill not lead us against the tide.
Whatever the tides are like,
it's the people who are most important.
- Leave!
- Get out of the way!
No-one may leave this place!
Our officials are here attending
a ceremony! Do not cause a scene!
I want to search your boat.
I suspect this boat is carrying someone
from the Sun Moon Sect.
Don't worry, uncle. We're not members
of the Sun Moon Sect.
lam.
I have an old friend on the boat.
I don't want him to be disturbed.
These upstarts
aren't from round here.
If we give them some money,
they'll go away.
- Master Chau, I'll take my leave.
- Please take care of yourself.
I'm Ah Sei, the head guard.
If you want to cause a scene,
come with me to the courthouse.
- Come! Come!
- Someone's causing trouble!
Kuk Yeung, you're a member of
the Sun Moon Sect. Don't come out.
Set Sail!
I have a warrant from the imperial court.
Anyone in my way will be seen as a rebel.
Although there's more of you,
to us from the imperial court,
you're just a handful of people.
Don't try to catch the arrow!
He's has a lot of nei Ii!
The dog trying to catch the cat
has instead caught a mouse!
There was a Sun Moon Sect
member on board.
He's Jo Lang Sim,
a practitioner of dark arts.
The Imperial Eastern
Secretariat minion.
He killed the Lam family!
What? Luckily he doesn't know how
to swim. He won't dare to give chase.
What conspiracy is this now?
Unfounded hearsay is the reason why
we haven't met in over 40 years.
Over 40 years have passed.
At least we can both retire today.
This is a problematic district.
We shouldn't come back here anymore.
We haven't seen each other in so long.
Remember the song from our youth?
Hey, we haven't played music
together in a long time.
Young man, we composed this song
together when we were young.
You can sing along with us.
THE PROUD LAUGHING
WORLD OF MARTIAL ARTS
The blue seas laugh
Surging against both shores
We are carried by the waves
We are only concerned with
the here and now
The azure skies laugh
At the disorder in the world
Only the heavens know
Who will win and who will lose
The rivers and mountains laugh
The clouds and rain are far away
After the billowing waves are spent
How beautiful the vulgar
world of mortals seems
The clear breezes laugh
And they provoke feelings of solitude
Noble sentiments leave us melancholic
like a long stretch of moonlit nights
MANUAL FOR PLAYING THE QIN
The green earth laughs
Solitude is no more
Noble sentiments still make us laugh
like we don't care
It's Seun Fung Tong's big boat!
Small boat in front!
Lower your sail!
Hey, lower your sail!
- Turn the rudder!
- Yes!
- Ram the small boat!
Who's on the big boat?
We're also from Suen Fung Tong!
Ignore him! Ram the boat!
Come with me!
Jo Lang Sim, take this!
The way of heaven brings prosperity,
rebellion brings death.
- You're spineless!
- That's how things are!
You traitor!
I'm clearing the way
for the Imperial Court.
Jo Lang Sim!
You son of a bitch!
"Storm Clouds covering the Skies."
- Let's go!
- Into the water!
Take this!
Old friend!
Old Kuk! Old Kuk!
Are you all right?
Old friend, I'm okay.
You be careful!
The boat has a hole!
Quickly, seal it!
- Hurry up!
- Hurry up and seal it! Hurry up!
- Venerable Mr. Kuk, your arm!
- Look after my old friend. I'm managing.
Brother!
They're both badly injured.
I understand. I'm looking
for a place to go ashore.
No need, young man.
Everywhere is the same. Look at how nice
the wide sea and blue skies are...
We don't have much time left.
Old Kuk, we haven't finished singing
"Proud Laughing World of Martial Arts."
Old friend, I'm really useless.
Come over and help me.
After all these years, I've never heard
you call yourself useless.
You're admitting
you're getting old, huh?
The blue seas laugh
Surging against both shores
We are carried by the waves...
We are only concerned
with the here and now
The azure skies laugh
At the disorder in the world
Only the heavens know
Who will win
and who will lose
The rivers
and mountains laugh
The clouds and rain
are far away
After the billowing waves
are spent,
How beautiful the vulgar world
of mortals seems...
Brother!
Venerable Mr. Lau, he's...
- Sir, we've reached the shore.
- Take it slow and easy.
I'm not going back.
I give to you this qin and "The Proud
Laughing World of Martial Arts."
Consider it fate, the fact that we were able
to be together and share a boat ride.
In the future, when you find
an audience for it, pass it on.
I hope that you young people
will be able to achieve
what we, the older generation,
haven't been able to do.
Old friend, I hope that we haven't
given the qin to the wrong people.
We'll use up this barrel of wine.
SUN MOON SECT HAS
DESTROYED THE LAM FAMILY
He's dead.
Have you found
all the weapons yet?
We've found all of them.
- Continue the search.
- Yes.
Official Au Yeung.
Your Eminence, Lam Ping Ji is dead.
We still don't know the whereabouts of
the Prized Sunflower Volume.
But before he died,
he did reveal that the two who escaped
were Hua Mountain Sect students.
One of them
is called Ling Wu Chung.
From the Hua Mountain Sect?
The Shaolin have fist-fighting,
the Hua Mountain Sect their swordplay.
I fear that a dog like Jo Lang Sim
won't be able to bite them.
I'm not sure what he's up to.
In the beginning, we only used him
to keep the heat off us.
But instead, he's flashing the warrant
we gave him all over the place.
As a precaution,
should we do away with him?
You're a very practical man.
It's not easy to keep
a useful, obedient dog like him.
If you kill him, who will guard our door
and bark at strangers?
As you're so able, why don't you
make the decision for me!
I don't dare.
I know he's like a dog,
but a dog will bite anyone
when cornered.
We've mobilised
so many people this time,
could we be over-exaggerating
and risking not getting the right result?
You are indeed a miscreant!
So many suggestions.
You just want to know what
the Prized Sunflower Volume is.
Thank you, Your Eminence,
for enlightening me.
The Prized Sunflower Volume
is rumoured to be a record of the Sunflower
Modus of Telekinesis and Teleportation.
Martial arts folklore says that
someone who has telekinesis,
can teleport through walls.
He can use his powers from afar.
It's hard to believe.
But I heard that our Emperor
has witnessed it himself.
Ifl had known earlier that
the Forbidden Palace had such a book...
You may not believe it,
but in martial arts, masterful experts
are often surpassed.
Some think that
they can do something very unique.
But they don't realise
there are others who can!
Take this!
Our opponent is a very skilled swordsman.
Be careful, everyone!
There's no need to give chase.
That person has a lot of nei Ii.
He evaded my attack, which means
he's more than a match for any of you.
Lam Jan Nam must want
to use him to deal with us.
Au Yeung Chun!
Take a few men. Try to blend in with the
Hua Mountain Sect crowd on the way!
Capture Ling Wu Chung
and bring him back to me!
Yes, Your Eminence.
Skinny Boy, are you all right?
- Brother...
- How are you feeling?
Brother...
I want to return to Hua Mountain.
The world of martial arts
is too scary...
Don't talk so much. You've got a fever.
Rest a bit, then we'll talk later.
If sifu hasn't arrived
at the Lam family home,
he must still be harvesting herbs.
We'll find him and
return to Hua Mountain together.
Don't dwell on things too much, okay!
Press down on
your Hegu meridian point.
- Yes, like that. Good girl.
- I want to go back to Hua Mountain.
Someone's coming!
Who's there?
Old uncle, it's very dangerous here!
Don't be around us!
Get away quickly!
I'm already running away.
Now you're asking me to leave.
I'm so old,
where do you expect me to go?
Old uncle, what are you doing here?
I'm cooking.
May I fill my stomach before I leave?
Look at your friend. He must have
got sick from a lack of food.
Don't panic. The world is a big place.
There must be somewhere you can go.
By starting a fire here, the smoke
could easily alarm the animals outside.
I have dry rations with me.
You put out the fire,
and I'll treat you to dinner tonight.
That's settled then!
Be my guest.
You're still very warm!
I don't even know if I'm biting into
your bun, or if your bun is biting into me!
It's tougher than my old bones!
What's wrong?
Old uncle,
we have to get away from some people.
Once you get out in the open,
go west.
When the sun has risen behind your back,
then you can return.
As long as you're not with us,
you'll be all right.
I still have some dry rations.
Skinny boy, I'm going to go out
and divert them.
Make your getaway east, that way,
so you don't run into the old uncle.
I'll be able
to find you again, okay!
- Brother! Be careful!
- I'll be fine.
Old uncle,
you were meant to go west!
It's pitch black.
I can't tell which way's which.
I don't know him! I'm Ling Wu Chung
of the Hua Mountain Sect!
If you need something,
just ask me!
You've got fair, smooth skin.
You're quite to my taste.
"Coiled dragon swallows tree."
Go back and practice
with your delicate fingers!
Wow! The yin energy
from his palm is so strong.
Kid, your trouser belt has come off!
You're lucky I'm here,
or you would have flashed your bottom!
But you leaped out pretty well.
"A large roc spreads its wings."
We'll throw...
throw, throw, throw, throw, throw, throw,
throw, throw, throw, throw, throw...
Sword! Sword! My sword!
- Leader, shall we...?
- Yes.
Reverse!
Ling Wu Chung!
Observe carefully!
"Swinging sword manoeuvre."
"Wave-like sword manoeuvre."
"Lower-the-sword manoeuvre."
"Whirling sword manoeuvre."
You may not leave!
- Let's do it together!
- Okay!
"Hacking sword manoeuvre."
"Splitting sword manoeuvre."
Yet another group to lose
their souls by the sword.
We are all flesh and blood.
Why do we have to make
such a mess of the world?
Sir, may I ask which sect
you are the grandmaster of?
Brother, what's the point of caring
so much about reputation and fame?
It is the cause of countless disasters
and turmoil in the world.
Sir, your martial arts are so skilful.
Why do you still live
such an itinerant life?
What's the use of
being skilful in martial arts?
Even heroes
are made of flesh and blood.
Once the corrupt and the wicked
have captured your family
then you just become their pawn.
For their safety, I retired from the
martial arts world, and left my family.
Emotions are stronger
than any martial art.
You're a student of the
Hua Mountain Sect.
You have to beware of your sifu.
He's not as righteous as he seems.
Why do you say such things
about my sifu?
So many sects in the martial arts world
advocate righteous platitudes,
but it's just power play.
Years ago, due to differences in opinion
about martial arts in Hua Mountain,
there was
an internal power struggle.
Students were divided into
the chi and the sword sects.
From verbal combat
to physical combat,
the result was dead bodies
strewn all over the place.
At the heart of the matter was
a power struggle to become leader.
Your sifu sacrificed many students to
fulfil his ambition to become leader.
That's why you need to be careful.
How come you know so much
about the Hua Mountain Sect?
If you have a chance in the future,
ask your sifu.
Ask him who Fung Ching Yeung is.
Fung Ching Yeung?
The sword manoeuvres I taught you
are called "Nine Solitary Swordplays."
Each manoeuvre evolved from
manoeuvres that had met with defeat.
In martial arts, how many are willing
to study unsuccessful manoeuvres?
You have to remember them.
Maybe they'll be useful in the future.
Although I did
teach you a few things,
we needn't formalise
a teacher-student relationship.
Let's just acknowledge each other
and be good brothers.
Fung...
Old brother Fung!
MIAO REGION
Sir, we've discovered the Hua Mountain
Sect people are staying in a barbarian inn.
- Stay here, everyone...
- Sir, the civilian clothes are ready.
Change into them.
Think of some way to lure
the Han Chinese to the barbarian inn.
There are strangers downstairs.
I smell blood.
Sifu, we haven't heard from our brother
Ling Wu Chung and sister for so long.
Could it be them?
I'll go down and take a look.
Inner chi is like bubbling, flowing water.
Inner peace is like an immobile mountain.
Be patient.
Everyone, sit and meditate
to gather your chi.
Damn!
Is this what you call service?!
There are Han Chinese.
Sifu, do you think
it's our brother?
Help!
Sifu! I'll go downstairs
to check it out!
He's not dead yet.
Carry him upstairs!
You've had a close call.
Thank you.
- Take them all away.
- Yes.
Sifu, as per your instructions,
we've buried the two dead people.
We also found something on them.
Sifu!
It's a warrant issued by
the Imperial Court.
We, from the martial arts world,
never discuss politics.
Just as a river
doesn't interfere with a well,
I don't want to know
about your affairs.
If you don't mind,
please leave
as quickly as possible.
We of the Lam family have suffered
the pains of extermination.
I don't want more people to sacrifice
themselves for me.
Kind sir, I will never forget this
benevolent deed of saving my life.
I'll repay you one day.
Goodbye!
Brother,
take this money with you.
There may still be people who want to
harm you. Buy a sword to defend yourself.
Take it.
You've been too kind to me.
Someday, I will repay
your kindness.
All you kind sirs! Please accept
three bows from me, Lam Ping Ji.
Lam Ping Ji?
The descendant of Mr. Lam?
You've been resurrected?!
Ping Ji!
You're Lam Ping Ji?
How time flies.
I haven't seen you
in more than a decade.
- We don't recognise each other any more.
- You are?
I'm Uncle Ngok from Hua Mountain,
Ngok Bat Kwan.
You're Ngok Bat Kwan!
Uncle Ngok, there's hope after all.
You're my only kinsman now.
A decade or so ago,
I, Ping Ji, was young and ignorant.
I didn't realise how dangerous
and perilous the world was.
Now, everything's been
distorted beyond recognition.
I, Ping Ji,
am no longer the same Ping Ji!
I understand.
What's all this noise about?
The Miao people are having a wedding.
Don't speak so loudly in Chinese here.
Let's split up and look for our sifu.
As the sun and moon bring each new day,
our gods bless our tribe.
The Chief is risen again!
The fake groom doesn't need
to pretend any longer.
Let's inspect the goods
that have been delivered.
Yes.