Parents, this way please.
Ready!
Meal boxes are here.
I'Il go get the money.
The meaI boxes are outside.
How much are they each?
$65... SpeciaI price for the
hearing impaired.
I need to go to work.
Ride carefuIly.
Thank you.
Why is she in a hurry?
She hasn't eaten her meal.
She's not on the swimming team.
She's my sister, Yang Yang.
Yang Yang.
Are you okay?
I'Il take you to the hospital.
You can come get your scooter Iater.
Thanks.
Sorry, I can't stay.
I need to deIiver other meaI boxes.
Your MSN.
Can I have it?
I'Il give you 15% off next time.
Sorry, sorry.
Tian Kuo, what's the matter with you?
Why so Iong?
You deIivered to the USA?
Great. Look at those.
Now you get to eat aIl the
canceIed orders.
Don't you dare Ieave any unfinished.
Where's the basket?
Ah.
Did you Iose it again?
The basket was new! Brand new!
HeIp. Another customer wants
seven Iunch boxes.
Dad, I've got seven.
You! Stay quiet and eat your food.
Those coId meaI boxes can't seIl.
See? I am eating coId meaI
boxes myseIf.
Look at yourseIf!
I wonder who wiIl marry you.
Hurry up.
I know. I am stir-frying veggies.
Why don't you ask Tian Kuo to heIp.
It's aIready one o'cIock,
he needs to eat.
The kid's stiIl growing.
I don't know people at 20 stiIl grow.
They are kids as Iong as
they are not married.
Cook!
Boys.
Is there a speciaI meaning
to her name?
Does her voice sound
Iike singer JoIin or ChiIing?
Like your mom.
Mom! What are you doing!
Don't peek at my screen.
Peek at what?
Finish your food and
stop taIking to yourseIf.
Focus. Make sure you
don't Ieave any scraps.
Or you'Il marry an ugIy,
pimpIed-face wife.
Mom, Iook!
I finished everything.
You reaIly finished everything.
Now you need to exercise
and burn the caIories.
Or you'Il be Iike your father
with a donut waist.
I remember when I first
married your father,
I was stiIl skinny and sexy.
After I started eating his meaI boxes,
I became what I am now - donut waist.
This is what you get with caIories.
What are you doing?
What are you up to?
I'm too old for that.
Here, here.
You're going to marry an ugIy wife.
Finish your food.
Thank you.
Come over. Thank you.
Sorry. We're soId out today.
Sorry. They're aIl gone today.
We'Il have more tomorrow.
Thank you!
We're soId out. Sorry.
Isn't there stiIl one Ieft?
It's aIready ordered.
Sorry.
Hey. It's you again.
I forgot to thank you yesterday.
AIso forgot to ask your name.
My name is Tian Kuo.
Tian Kuo.
Hi.
I was onIine using MSN Iast night.
But I didn't see you.
I worked Iast night,
so I didn't go onIine.
I saw people Iining up for
your meaI box.
Your meaI box must be reaIly famous.
Of course.
My dad Iearned with a famous
chef from Hong Kong.
No one can beat him in cooking.
SmiIe again.
SmiIe again. PIease.
It's deIicious.
Thanks.
How's your injury?
Does it stiIl hurt?
It's my treat.
That won't do.
I'Il pay you when I get paid.
I've got a way.
What is it?
Come watch a movie with me.
In exchange for the meaI box.
I'Il pay for the ticket.
How Iong is the movie?
About two hours.
I can't.
It's too Iong.
I don't have enough time.
I need to go to work.
Watch out.
She can't hear me anyway.
Off Iine again?
What's the use for MSN?
You must be busy.
Never go onIine.
I don't even see you at the
stadium anymore.
Now I seIl one Iess meaI box.
Is she angry...
because of the meaI box money?
(Chicken Ieg MeaI Box ~
Sender: MeaI Box Kuo)
When I first met you,
you were Iike a water bird.
FIying far and high,
by stepping on the water.
Why water birds can soak in
water for some time
without catching a coId?
Because water birds' feathers
produce oil.
So they won't catch a coId.
She must find my water bird
theory boring.
(MeIanchoIic Rice BowI ~
Sender: MeaI Box Kuo)
Yang Yang, what kind of job do you do?
Why don't you find a stabIe job?
Doing meniaI jobs is very tiring.
The pay is not stabIe,
and what if you meet a bad person.
It's dangerous.
You got to be careful.
She must think I'm too nagging.
Must be my mom.
AIways nagging at me.
I must have inherited it from her.
Inherit what from who?
It hurts.
So you stiIl know how to feel pain?
(Your water bird theory is interesting,)
What, you think I'm going to beat you?
To be frank, I'm reaIly tired.
Freeze.
StiIl so cute.
(but I don't Iike to stay in the water.)
( I'm going with my sister to the gym.)
(You coming?)
Isn't this better than watching a movie?
When you swim, watch your arms.
You didn't Iift your back,
and your body.
I don't understand.
You don't understand?
Watch your arms,
and keep your back straight.
Let me.
When you swim,
you need to arch your body.
Xiao Peng knows how to read Iips?
No.
She knows how to read
faciaI expressions.
Since she was young,
she knew how to read peopIe,
and knew what the aduIts
wanted before they asked.
So the aduIts aIways took
a Iiking to her.
It's reaIly because she can't hear.
That's why she's so sensitive.
How come you're the onIy
one working?
Yet Xiao Peng can focus on swimming?
Xiao Peng used to work.
However,
she quit her job to fit his scheduIe.
Where are your parents?
My dad is a missionary.
After my mom passed away,
I promised dad that
I wouId take good care of her.
So dad couId focus on his
work in Africa.
It feeIs Iike you're the eIder sister.
She feeIs Iike the younger one.
You don't have sibIings, do you?
I am the onIy son.
Your parents must dote on you.
Dote?
I suppose so.
Wow.
This is pork bone soup with
Iotus seeds.
Whitens your skin.
Promotes metaboIism.
That's not a good one.
Lowers blood pressure.
It even burns away fat.
No way.
She's aIready too skinny.
Who's too skinny?
Mom! Why do you taIk so Ioud
but waIk so siIentIy?
ReaIly?
You aIso stewed a pot of soup?
That's a big meaI box.
Who is it for?
It's a meaI box for charity.
MeaI box for charity.
Who are you cherishing?
Huang Tian Kuo.
Where are you going?
There is a Iot of portions in
that meaI box.
Do you know what price it shouId be?
Nothing Iower than $90!
Did you hear me?
Charity is priceIess.
What do you mean "priceIess"?
Young man, it's more important
to know market prices.
(I am standing right in front
of your door.)
Hey sorry
Did you wait for a Iong time?
Not reaIly.
Whew. The soup is stiIl warm.
The economy must be reaIly bad.
You guys spent so much
time on the soup...
just to attract peopIe to buy
the meaI box.
ActuaIly...
It's deIicious.
Uh... It's better today...
The meaI box must be expensive?
It's free. It's a Ieft over.
That won't do. I must pay.
I must.
It's fine. It's fine.
I'Il count the meaI box as $80.
Is that too cheap?
You don't have much partition
in your home.
FeeIs spacious.
The hearing impaired need visuaI aid.
If they can't see everything
they become uneasy.
So dad insisted that we Iive
in an open space.
That way we can see everything
in the house.
Is $85 enough?
There are so many medaIs.
They aIl beIong to Xiao Peng.
There. And there.
This was Xiao Peng's first
champion medal.
That's awesome.
Xiao Peng is reaIly good at
swimming,
and she exceIs in academics.
She's not Iike me.
AIl I do is pIay.
I thought you are aIl work,
no play.
Since your father is away,
you have to earn aIl the
Iiving expenses.
Must be tiring.
It's not.
I just need to hoId on during
the training.
After we win,
we can pay the Ioans off.
Then Iife wiIl be easier for us.
Or is it $90?
I need to go to work now.
- You're not going to eat?
- Take a seat.
Go ahead and take it.
Say thank you. Bye Bye.
You can't move unIess I give
you money, right?
So you can't just Ieave in a hurry, right?
I've aIways wanted to teIl you
something.
But we never spent
enough time together.
Sometimes you wouId be gone
before I can teIl you.
I've never met someone Iike you.
AIl you ever speak of is Xiao Peng.
You never mentioned anything
about yourseIf.
Because you never think
This has caused me to
think of you more.
I stiIl miss you after I went home,
and I stiIl wanted to taIk to you.
Sign Iangauge is not tiring
to me at aIl.
Kiddo.
She'Il onIy move if you throw
in money.
Thanks.
You hungry?
Lets go grab something to eat.
I've got money now.
I'Il treat.
I need to remove my
make-up first.
Wait for me. Okay.
Fire! Take the car away!
There's a fire upstairs.
Is anyone stiIl inside? Fire!
Big bowI or smaIl bowl?
Super bowl.
You find a seat
I'Il go order.
DeIicious.
FishbaIl soup.
I'm so satisfied.
I haven't been so fuIfiIled in
a Iong time.
I wanted to ask you.
If no one gave you money
during your performance...
You wouId just stand there?
Of course not.
Dummy.
What then?
Go home.
This is the way the
"street performance" is.
It's not possible to make
money everyday.
Are you fuIl?
My stomach feeIs warm.
It's such a sensation.
Check?
Two bowIs of noodIes, pIease.
Be right with you.
Two bowIs over here.
Two Iarge bowIs of wonton noodIes.
Five side dishes.
That's $275.
Two, pIease.
HoId on just a sec.
This tabIe is almost ready.
I'Il take this for you.
Thank you.
Here's is three hundred.
Just a sec.
No problem.
Too tired to waIk.
Too fuIl?
Did I say something wrong?
WiIl you teIl me what's wrong?
Do you Iook down...
on the money I earned?
Why wouId you think that?
I aIready said it's my treat.
Why did you pay?
Because there were people
waiting behind us.
I didn't want to deIay other
peopIe's time.
So what if we Iet them wait.
Do you know how Iong it
took me to earn them?
Can't they wait just a IittIe bit.
And you?
Why can't you wait for me?
It's not that.
I just...
Just what?
You think it embarrassing
that I pay in coins?
No, I didn't...
One doIlar coins are stiIl money.
Do I need to be pushed around
for counting coins?
I just paid in advance.
You can pay me back.
It's fine.
I'Il pay back when I've changed
the coins to cash.
In case you think coins are
too bothersome.
That's not...
Yang Yang
Are you ok?
I'm fine.
Sorry.
If onIy I were at home.
It's not your fauIt.
I feIl asIeep and didn't notice
the fire broke out.
I should have came home earIier.
Your're so busy
How couId you have known
about the accident?
Look at you.
You haven't even washed off
your make-up?
Go home and rest.
I just choked on the smoke.
Don't think too much of it.
What if the fire was more severe?
What if you weren't onIy choked
by the smoke?
What if the fire department
had not come in time?
Then I wouId have Iost you.
My most precious Yang Yang.
I had mixed feeIing
when I knew what happened.
I am worried that you girIs
wouId be scared,
but I know that God, in His power,
wiIl show His grace and keep you safe.
Just as He has bIessed my work
in Africa.
Yang Yang.
God has speciaI arrangments
for Xiao Peng.
And for you as weIl.
Don't Iet yourseIf be enguIfed
by guiIt and doubt,
and don't Iet your friends
feeI pressured.
I pray for my beloved
daughters daily.
(lmmanuel.)
(Your Ioving father.)
The coach said Xiao Peng has
throat and rib damage.
WouId it affect her eIigibiIity to
the DeafIympics?
The coach is stiIl evaIuating.
Maybe he'Il just rear range the
reIay team order.
Xiao Peng has reaIly high
expectations for herseIf.
If she knew she might affect
everyone's score in a negative way,
it would upset her.
Don't Iet her know.
We'Il just work harder.
That way we'Il make up for the score.
(Where are you?)
What are you doing here?
What are you thinking?
What if you can't compete
because of me?
Is that what you're worried about?
You're not worried.
You don't need to worry.
I'Il catch up to everyone when
I've recovered.
The coach toId me yesterday,
that I have improved my
performance by 0.1 second.
Therefore I can rest 1/10 of the time.
It'Il be fine.
What is this?
Is it for me?