Get out!
Block the north side!
I'll cover the south!
Go! Go!
Will this be a problem?
With a billion of them,
do you think they'll miss one or two?
The embassy's asking for the release
of his personal effects.
Send them a big wreath of flowers...
with my condolences.
How much should I spend?
This much.
Here are your assistant's
personal effects, and here...
are some photos of your hero
killing another Chinese citizen...
on the French soil.
There's a time for diplomacy
and a time for action.
Diplomacy is dead.
- You should go to the hospital.
- Do you have a needle and thread?
You know, since I began my work...
I have received five of you young men.
Fast, proud... like you.
Four have died...
the last one right in my arms.
Before my time is up here,
I would like to send one home alive.
I'll go for some bandages
and disinfectant for you.
Hi.
- Need any help?
- No.
I have some experience.
You know, the longer that
that thing stays open,
the more risk there is of infection
setting in, and then you are in for it.
I once had a scrape that I ignored.
I let it go for a couple days.
- It turned into staph infection.
- All right!
But only to sew it.
- Then you must leave. Okay?
- Yeah.
Doesn't like me standing outside, huh?
Your uncle.
Well, I don't blame him.
If I were him,
I wouldn't like me
standing out there either.
Now, this is gonna sting.
Believe me, if I had any other
place to stand, I would.
It's just all the good spots
get taken by the others and...
You would not believe how much business
some of these girls do.
- Guess how much some of them do in a day.
- I don't know.
- Well, guess.
- I can't.
- Sure you can. Pick a number.
- Five.
Five? How about 25?
- 25?
- Mm-hmm.
That's the record.
But at least 15.
- Can you believe that?
- No.
Yeah. Me? I'm lucky
if I can do five in a week.
- You ever been with a hooker?
- No.
- Not even once?
- Are you gay?
- No.
That'd be okay if you are. I think
everyone should be who they want to be...
- And do it with who they want to do it with.
- I'm not gay!
All I'm saying is, I don't hold
nothin' against nobody that way.
- Are you finished?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There.
Mmm. Here you go.
Good as new.
Oh, my God. Look at that scar.
Let me see.
I'm fine. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You did a very good job.
I used to sew up pigs.
That was my specialty.
Used to have this big, fat mama sow,
and she tore herself along the barbwire when...
she was trying to get to the other side
of the fence to get at these apples.
- You gonna be around long?
- No. I go home as soon as my business is over.
Hmm. And so, what is your business,
- If you don't mind me asking?
- Shrimp.
Oh, yeah.
Pretty aggressive shrimp.
You should probably be more careful.
- No wife?
- No.
Haven't met the right girl, I bet.
- Right?
- My work... It's hard to meet any girls.
Any interest in an ex-junkie hooker...
who can cook, clean, sew
and who likes Chinese food?
No, thank you.
I'm just kidding.
Hey, look.
See? My daughter.
- My angel. Sweet, huh?
- Yes.
Why do you do this kind of... job?
Well...
There was this guy, and, uh,
I met him after I had my baby.
And where I come from, girls without
husbands just do not have babies.
And if they do, well,
it's kinda hard on 'em.
So, anyway, this guy I met...
He's this French guy.
He's really cool
with this great accent...
and always talking about art and books
and movies and everything.
And, boy, when you're, you know...
When you're young and really desperate,
you know, this...
And this guy could really...
I mean, he could talk. You know?
And so... I don't know.
The next thing you know,
you're on the street.
Why don't you just... quit?
It's a little more complicated than that.
What do you mean?
I should probably get back.
See you later.
Nice talking to you.
- Lupo!
- Practicing embroidey on the clients?
No, no, he's not...
Lupo, he was just...
He had a cut on his arm.
I though the was gonna call the medics,
and they'd be blocking off the street,
and then the clients couldn't come,
and I couldn't be standing on my spot,
and I couldn't make any money for you,
so I thought if I just took five minutes, then...
Shh.
Get back to work.
Lupo, he had nothing to do with...
I said, get back to work!
Excuse me.
I'm really sorry to interfere
in your business.
But I would really appreciate it...
if you...
don't do that again.
The little statue speaks.
You know, I don't care
if you fuck her, bleed on her.
You're still using her time,
and her time is my money.
You've kept her busy
for 20 minutes.
- Do you know the going rate for 20 minutes?
- No.
Five hundred francs.
Ah! Five for her time, now five for mine.
My kind of client.
Lupo, we should get back...
Hello, Max?
Fuck!
What happened?
Down!
Fuck!
Ah! Damn... F... Oh!
Oh, God!
Oh, God! Oh, my God!
Oh, God. Oh, God.
What're we gonna do?
Respect his wishes.
Listen.
The longer you keep information from me
about this psychopath you sent over,
the longer my city will bleed
innocent blood.
I assure you, Inspector,
we have kept no information from you.
Good.
- What're we gonna do now?
- I don't know.
- I can't walk the streets all night.
- Walking helps me think.
- Walking hurts my feet.
- Then go home.
Oh, just like that.
First you put me in this mess,
and then you think
you can just get rid of me.
I put you in this mess?
You were the one
who came to the shop to pee.
who offered to sew me up.
I didn't ask you for anything!
I only asked to be left alone.
Oh, yeah, that's you...
don't need anything, don't need anybody.
Just have yourself and your stupid job
selling shrimp chips.
I don't sell shrimp chips.
Yeah, I figured that out. I mean,
I'm stupid, but I'm not that stupid.
- I'm a cop.
- I'm Santa Claus.
Who is Santa Claus?
A big fat guy, red suit,
flying reindeer?
Jesus, God,
don't you know anything?
Take me here.
Why do you want to go there?
The best thing to do. When you lose
your way, you go back to the beginning.
Beginning?
Beginning of what?
My work. Last night.
You... You were there last night?
Working with the French cop.
- Richard?
- You know him?
Yeah. I was there too.
The redhead.
Yeah. No, it was a wig.
It was...
- Come on.
- Wait a minute!
- A second ago you couldn't wait to get rid of me.
- You're my proof.
I will take you to the embassy,
and you will tell them everything.
No, no. I'm in deep enough.
I'm not gonna be your witness.
You're the only one who can save me.
Don't you listen?
Richard has my daughter.
But you don't think about that, do you?
No!
You don't think what's gonna happen to her,
you don't think what's gonna happen to me.
Of course not!
You only think of your job.
Because that's all that matters to you,
because that's all you've got in your crummy cop's life.
You take Richard down, and it's
gonna leave a space for another bastard,
one who we pray will be less of
a bastard than the one before him.
And that's reality!
Maybe it's not your reality,
but it's my reality every day, 24-7.
And there's nothing you or anybody else
can do to change that.
Wait.
If I get your daughter back,
will you help me?
I'm... I'm...
I'm really screwed this time.
My government will protect you.
They will give you safely away.
Away where?
To China?
I mean, I like the chips,
but no, thank you.
Listen to me.
I know you've had some bad experiences
trusting people.
But if I gave you my word,
you will be safe.
Yes, Minister.
We're doing all we can, Minister.
But we are not magicians who can pull
killers out of hats like they're rabbits,
especially one who is trained like this.
I'm just a cop trying
to do his job. Yes.
I'll call you back.
Richard! My God, Richard!
You're not gonna believe this.
Try me.
I... This crazy little Chinese...
Lupo picked the perfect spot,
except it smelled like shrimps.
And how can I get any clients
when I smell like a shrimp?
So anyway, I was trying to work,
and Max and Lupo come along.
They went into the shop,
and the next thing I know,
the little fucker goes nuts,
you know, and-and... I mean...
Max tried to protect me,
and the Chinese guy killed both of them.
I believe you.
And then?
And then he takes me as a hostage.
And he made me carry this stuff, and he dragged me
all the way up to that church...
You know, the big church
on the top of the hill?
And then... You know...
And he made me...
help him do these things... these weird
things with incense and pajamas.
- And every time I tried to run...
- He stopped you?
Yeah.
You know...
You know those movies...
with that Chinese guy who's always
kicking and screaming all the time and...
- He used kung fu on you?
- Yeah. Yeah.
He did. Look.
Wow.
And then he made me go to this
restaurant while he ate this goop...
with weird things in it, you know,
like snails and frogs' legs and...
That is when you escaped
out of the bathroom window?
- When he fell asleep.
- In the restaurant?
He... Yeah.
Richard.
Please, don't... don't do that.
Do you think he is still there
in the restaurant?
Well, he drank a whole lot of beers.
That's why I came here.
- 'Cause I thought if I helped you...
- What?
I could show you where he is.
- You're not too tired?
- Oh, yeah, for sure. I could probably sleep for a week.
But, I don't know. I...
You want me to come?
I don't know.
What do you think?
I think... I should come.
I think you should stay.
Okay. He's... He's at
the Mandarin in Belville.
But... But I'll do what ever you want,
though. I mean, I just...
I want you to trust me.
I trust you.
Ow! Wait. Wait.
And if I discover I can't,
I know where to find you.
What about my daughter?
She's safe, just like her mother.
Watch her.
So, what's a girl gotta do
to get fed around here?
Okay. Okay.
Wait a minute. What do you think I am,
the village idiot?
No. First you go get my sandwich,
and then I give you your dessert.
Hello?
- Don't do that!
- You get it?
No, I always walk around handcuffed to
a steam pipe with a turtle for company.
So you didn't get it.
Is it just you, or do all cops
lack a basic sense of humor?
Now will you help?
Relax your arm.
I can't relax it anymore.
Come on, you know about handcuffs.
- You sure you got all of them?
- The deal was I get you all the tapes in his office.
Are you gonna live up to your end
of the bargain or what?
Are you listening?
Hello!
- No, no. No needles.
- No needles. No.
Ow!
- How did you do that?
- Chinese magic.
- Let's go to the embassy.
- No.
- First we get my daughter.
- No, first the embassy, then I get your daughter.
Bullshit. I'm not gonna sit someplace
safe while my kid's life's in danger,
so forget it!
Which way?
She escaped?
What do you mean she escaped?
How could she escape?
It's here.
See you around.
What is this place?
It's an orphanage.
- Do you mind?
- What?
Oh, no.
Shit.
Oh, come on.
There it is.
Section "B", bed 13.
Okay.
What's wrong?
I don't know.
I guess I'm kinda nervous.
I mean, I haven't seen her
in almost a year.
Then don't make her wait.
Go.
Ow!
- Are you okay?
- I don't think so.
Somebody help me!
Here, sweetie.
That's for boys.
Don't you have any Barbies?
All my Barbies are working.
I had a turtle,
but your mother took it.
When am I going to see my mommy?
Soon, darling.
Very soon.
My daughter?
Calm down.
Everything's gonna be okay.
But he has my daughter.
And we have them.
Don't worry.
Everything's gonna be fine.
No. You don't understand.
My life is not some fairy tale.
My life is hell.
Richard is the devil,
and he has my daughter,
and he's gonna kill her,
and then he's gonna kill me.
And then he's gonna find a way
to get out of it clean.
You're wrong.
They will arrest him,
and they'll take care of you
and your daughter.
"They"? "They"?
I don't give a shit about them.
I don't trust them.
I trusted you.
For the first time in...
God, I don't know, forever...
I don't know why I trust someone.
You promised you'd take care of her.
Yes.
You're tired.
I think you should sleep.
- Hello?
- I want the child.
- I want the cassette.
- I gave the cassette to my government.
- They will know what to do with it.
- Bad move, Johnny Boy.
Now that the kid has no value,
what am I going to do with her?
She's too young to work.
Maybe not.
- What do you think?
- I think you should come to the window.
Now I know where you are.
I'm coming up.
He's coming up.
Hey, monsieur...
Sound the alert!
Fight!
Come on! Come on!
Get those out!
Move it! Move it!
This is not a drill!
Go now!
Ah, Johnny, Johnny,
I'm disappointed in you.
Coming to Paris for the first time,
and instead of enjoying yourself,
you're doing all this useless
running around.
- I don't like to get bored.
- Me either.
And right now I'm finding you very boring!
Wait!
You're making a big mistake.
- Ah, really?
- In the second...
it takes for you to kill her,
I will have all the time I need to kill you.
I got you.
Yes, you did,
but I also got you.
Isabel?
I'm a friend of your mom.
Can you wait outside?
Okay.
Good-bye, mister.
What did you do to me?
I put a needle in your neck.
- That's it?
- In a certain point, very forbidden.
It's called
"The Kiss of the Dragon."
Kiss my ass!
The blood from your whole body
goes to your head.
It stops there, never comes down.
But soon it will come out from your nose,
your ears, even from your eyes.
And then...
you will die, painfully.
You're really a smart guy, Johnny Boy.
My name is not Johnny.
- I slept long?
- Only a minute.
My daughter...