Subs converted and synched by ShooCat
This is a routine pursuit.
Main Force repeats,
this is a routine pursuit. Code 44.
Listen, you tell them we need help.
This should be an open-code blitz
and you know it.
You have your information.
Come on, sweetheart,
this one's a heavyweight!
Main Force repeats,
you have your information.
This is a routine pursuit.
Please liaise with Big Bopper.
Jesus, March Hare to Big Bopper.
Assist on Code 3 Red Alert.
Big Bopper. Gotcha, Hare.
What's going down?
- We've got a cop-killer.
- You're kidding!
Be warned, Sarse...
... this is non-compliance.
The Main Force will not tolerate
such action.
This pursuit is designated
a standard Code 44.
Please respond only to that code.
Code 44 indicates no requirement
for a blockade.
A Pursuit Special has been stolen.
Hall Captain Fifi Macaffee
doesn't like this any more than you.
However, we must not compromise
territorial range.
Remember that
only by following instructions...
... can we hope to maintain
a successful highway program.
March Hare to Big Bopper.
We're three minutes off the intersection.
Can you make it?
We'll make it! Move over!
I'm driving!
Not this again! I've been assigned!
Hang on. I'm supposed to drive this crate!
Hey, Sarse, what's the form on this thing?
A twisto bikey, scoot jockey.
A few hours ago, down in Sun City,
he goes berserk.
Breaks custody, wastes a young premmie
and takes off in a Pursuit Special.
We've been on him ever since.
This one's right up the air, Roop.
I've seen the style before.
Terminal psychotic.
What's he driving?
That's what hurts. It's one of our V8s.
Pursuit Special on methane. Very toey!
We're about half a mile off Anarchy Road.
You'll see him any minute now.
Rip the guts out of it. Give it the B-Jesus!
See him yet?
Got it!
I'm gonna blow him away!
I'm gonna ram him!
Hey, fellas, you okay?
Acknowledge, Big Bopper.
Acknowledge, are you okay?
Do you see me, Toecutter?
Do you see me, man?
Keep going, we're okay.
We got you, we're going.
Born with a steering wheel in his hand...
... and lead in his foot.
He is the Nightrider...
... cruising at the speed of fright!
I am the Nightrider,
and we ain't never coming back!
I'm a fuel-injected suicide machine!
I am a rocker! I am a roller!
I think we're still mobile.
For Christ's sake, shove over!
You're blaspheming again.
I don't have to work with a blasphemer.
I am the Nightrider!
Big Bopper to March Hare.
We're still in the game, okay?
Understand this.
That scag and his floozy...
...they're gonna die!
Main Force to Gosling One.
Code 44, standard pursuit. Please respond.
MFP to Gosling One.
Main Force to Gosling One.
It was like slow motion.
He leaves his seat
and goes through the windscreen...
...headfirst straight into the tree, right?
And then bounces back
through the windscreen.
By the time we got to him,
he was just sitting there...
...trying to scream with his face ripped off.
What's the matter?
Not hungry, am I?
Give it here.
- I'll tell you what"..."
- Look at that.
- Christ!
- Strewth, at it again.
Catch you later, Goose.
Christ, they're heading for population!
What's this I hear about you and Jonathan?
- What about him?
- You were seen with him two nights ago.
So what?
It's this way.
He's gone.
Bastards!
Shit!
You're gonna get it this time.
- He had his indicator on.
- Shut up!
No, you're not going on. Stay off the road!
Of course, I'm going on. Shut up!
People's lives are in peril!
Stay off the roads!
I'm gonna have him!
Get off the roads!
- I got him! Shut up!
- Stay off the roads!
Oh, my God.
I am ready.
I am ready for your best.
Oh, my God, what happened?
I don't know, man. I just got here myself.
I think he broke his leg.
I want to find out what's happening.
Max, can you hear me?
Main Force Patrol...
...we're out of the game...
...unable to continue pursuit.
You'd better send a meat truck.
Charlie's copped the saucer in the throat.
Hey, Max?
Max?
Go ahead.
We are 100 percent SNAFUed.
You okay, Goose?
Nothing a year in the tropics wouldn't fix.
Much damage?
You should see the damage, Bronze!
Metal damage...
... brain damage?
You listening, Bronze?
I am the Nightrider!
I'm a fuel-injected suicide machine.
I am a rocker! I am a roller!
I am an out-of-controller!
I am the Nightrider, baby...
... and it's me and my Marmaduke,
and we ain't never coming back.
The Toecutter, he knows who I am.
I am the Nightrider!
I am the chosen one,
the mighty hand of vengeance...
... sent down to strike the unroadworthy!
I'm hotter than a rolling dice.
Step right up, chum, and watch the kid...
...lay down a rubber road right to freedom!
What's wrong?
- Baby, what's wrong!
- Nothing.
It's going.
There'll be nothing left. It's all gone.
Stop!
That feels good.
After three days, that feels so good.
I got a right hook in the mouth
this morning.
Sprog?
I told him to always lead with his left.
You know, I think we've got
a monster on our hands.
Yeah, takes after his old man.
What's that?
Monster!
Montazano, who called himself
the Nightrider...
... had broken from custody
and escaped in the police vehicle.
You made the news again.
Who was he?
I don't know.
Just another glory rider, I guess.
Jessie, I told you.
The Goose wants me there early.
What for, he didn't say.
You know the Goose.
Coffee's ready.
I'm not grumpy.
Get out of here.
Okay.
I gotta go.
What's that?
Crazy about you.
All supplies must be requisitioned
from the people's bond.
Please do not exploit your privileges.
Doing so is an offense.
Memorandum Seven:
The Captains of the Hall have
asked that pursuit officers...
... refrain from using the slang "Bronze"
for the Main Force Patrol.
The word is considered disrespectful...
... and citizens should be
actively discouraged from its use.
Memorandum Eight.
Hospital vouchers are available again.
MFP personnel may sign on
with the following sector captains.
One, six three, two four, one one two...
... five seven, and two six.
Kick it in the guts, Barry.
She's the last of the V8s.
You can shut the gate on this one.
It's the duck's guts.
Yeah, she's the last of the V8s.
Sucks nitro.
Phase 4 head.
- Twin overhead cam.
- Tell him about the blower.
- 600 horsepower.
- The blower, man.
She's meanness put to music
and the bitch is born to run.
- He's in a coma, man!
- He loves it.
How the hell did you get all this together?
It just happened, Max, you know?
A piece from here and a piece from there.
- So easy?
- Yeah.
Come on, Max. You've seen it.
You've heard it...
...and you're still asking questions.
When do we go for a ride?
He loves it.
I think we've got him.
I hope so.
Yeah, we've got him.
Your top pursuit man wants
to quit the road...
...and we have to seduce him with candy?
People don't believe in heroes anymore.
I know, Macaffee. You want
to give them back their heroes.
You will not try this one on me again.
I do not enjoy wasting money.
Goodbye...
...and good luck!
Thanks, Labatouche.
You're a real human being.
Get out of my way!
The old meat grinder's humming tonight?
Yeah, Max took out a couple of crazies
over the high side.
Will you shut up!
The hot mops and the towees.
It's in the food.
Another one for your books, eh?
Have you eaten yet?
No, not yet. I'll pick up something later.
That Code 3 you ran down
a few days ago"..."
- The Nightrider?
- The Nightrider, yeah.
- Got a problem.
- What's that?
His friends. Word is they're out to get you.
- Scoot jockeys?
- Yeah, nomad trash.
Well, I'll add it to my threat collection.
Good boy, Max. You're a good boy.
Good afternoon.
We're here to meet a friend.
Come in on the train.
Nothing come in on the train
except a couple of crates and a...
...coffin.
Our friend.
You'll have to see the agent
and sign the papers.
Where do we find...
...this agent?
Wait.
That must be your friend there.
Didn't leave much of him.
Must have cut his heart out?
Yes, that's what I meant.
Poor bastard.
The Nightrider.
That is his name.
Remember him...
...when you look at the night sky.
I will.
Take your hat off.
Anything you say.
Anything I say.
What a wonderful philosophy you have.
Take him away.
Bubba. Johnny.
Push me, shove you!
Oh, yeah? Says who?
Nightrider!
No worries.
Anyway, my name is Jim Goose.
Rockatansky.
We have incident at Wee Jerusalem.
Nomad bikers, bulk trouble.
Okay, we're on it. We gone.
Goose, come on.
What's this?
It's a "Get Out Of Jail Free" card.
- Any more details?
- No.
Okay, we're gone.
- Max, he looks"..."
- Yeah.
Hey, fella, stop!
What a turkey!
Hey, fella, you're a turkey, you know that?
We'll come back for him later.
There's more up ahead.
Nightrider. My "Niqueur."
Pursuit units in sectors,
eight, nine and ten.
A cyclecade of nomad bikers.
A fast run out of Wee Jerusalem.
Your instructions are to locate.
Do not engage.
Sector Eight. Nomad bikers.
Bronze!
Gonna get you!
It's okay.
It's all right. No one's gonna hurt you.
It's all right.
This one's whacked out of his skull.
Whacked right out of his skull, man!
He ain't never coming back.
It's all right.
I'm gonna let this go now.
I know you're frightened, girl...
...but no one's gonna hurt you anymore.
My name's Jim Goose,
and everything's gonna be all right.
The Nightrider!
Hey, Jimbo.
- Remember that Code 3?
- Yeah.
Remember him when you look up"..."
Nightrider!
Well, well, well.
Johnny the Boy has done it again.
This time it's a scrubber.
He's never gonna learn.
But we are going to teach him, Bubba.
You are going back for him.
No way! Not me, not for him!
But it's not for him.
It's for me, Bubba.
You're wasting your time!
The Scag don't rate!
He's nothing like the Nightrider!
Code seven progress, eight one.
Code seven progress, eight three.
Code seven eight six, eight one, eight zero.
MFP Code 1.
Captain Macaffee in convoy from
the courthouse to the Halls of Justice.
Code one progress.
Hey, mister.
What happened to the car?
What do you think happened?
Looks like it was chewed up and spat out.
Perhaps it's the result of an anxiety.
Hey, Roop.
Stay here, mate.
I think they're out there.
Take your time, Charlie.
We got plenty of it.
Good day and good luck.
I can see the Interceptor.
What do you say, Scag?
Got no place special to go?
We'd better prep him.
Scag, did you bring your toothbrush?
- You'll have to sit on the Goose.
- Why?
No contest.
Hey, Fif! What's going on?
- What happened?
- Let him go.
What's he mean, "Let him go"?
Who's this?
- Keep out of this.
- What's going on?
No one showed, okay?
Forget it, Charlie. Just let him go.
No one showed. No one.
What's he mean, "No one showed"?
They didn't show.
Nobody! The punks didn't show.
The girl didn't show,
the townspeople didn't show.
Nobody showed!
We're screwed! It's the law.
What do you mean, "No one showed"?
Where were you, man?
It means, old man, you haven't got a case.
No contest.
Jesus Christ! You're not gonna
let him walk out the door, Fifi?
That's exactly what you're going to do!
- Shut up!
- Keep going, Charlie!
It's alright.
Hey, Bronze, look at you,
a cripple and a mute!
Scag, he sings and I tap dance!
Hey, you know what you are?
The courts will hear about this.
I promise they'll hear about this disgrace.
He wearing that face for a bet
or does he really look that stupid?
This man is grossly offensive!
Get him out of here, Max!
- I can make a case of it!
- What case, you fool?
You saw what they did to that girl!
For God's sake, she was the town bike!
He's my prisoner,
and he's not walking out that door!
- Get him out of here!
- Who is this guy?
Goose, settle down, boy.
Jesus, Fifi.
Fifi, Jesus.
Look, they're laughing at us!
Can't you see they're laughing at us?
They don't believe us!
See you later, Goose.
It's been a pleasure.
Skiffington, go home. Go.
Goose!
You can't do anything about it!
We know who you are, Bronze!
We'll see you on the road, Scag!
See you on the road
like we saw the Nightrider!
We remember the Nightrider,
and we know who you are!
Okay.
So long as the paperwork is clean,
you boys can do what you like out there.
Here he is, the walking armpit!
There's a fire in my belly,
and she's the woman to put it out.
Off, brute!
This angel is hot in the tubes for me!
I'm on fire!
Joviality is a game of children.
- She's mine.
- I should be a surgeon with these hands.
Mudguts, get out of there!
Cundalini, put her against the post.
We have a problem here.
She is not what she seems.
Bubba Zanetti has it on good authority...
...she's sent by the Bronze,
full of treachery.
The Bronze, take our pride.
If you're gonna waste the Bronze,
you gotta do it big!
You just don't have the style,
do you, chicken shit?
Goes to water on a dummy.
It's all right. It's okay.
Just remember...
...to keep your sweet...
...sweet mouth shut!
MFP to Gosling One.
Main Force Patrol to Gosling One.
We have a curfew violation.
MFP, Gosling One.
Gosling One.
Code 333 in progress.
Main Force.
Would someone inform the Goose...
Yeah, baby!
All units again progress.
... units to Three Day Angel Patrol.
Nice to have you back Big Bopper Two.
Sun City Sector 3,
Code 4 Trauma in progress.
Sun City Sector 9, Code 4 in progress.
MFP Eight One.
A Memorandum:
For the cannibalization...
MFP, copy.
Hey, it's the Goose.
You're a lucky boy. Not even a road rash.
Hey, Midge...
...don't write off the Goose,
until you see the box going into the hole.
Yeah, well, don't wreck me truck now.
- I'll bring it back tomorrow.
- Yeah, no hurry.
Hey, you sure you're all right?
Couldn't be righter.
Jimmy the Goose,
larger than life and twice as ugly!
Light me, Johnny.
Light another.
This is a threshold moment, Johnny.
Step through.
Toecutter, this isn't what I want.
Light it!
The Bronze,
they keep you from being proud.
Look at him. He looks silly,
doesn't he, upside down?
Do it for freedom and the Nightrider!
I can't. No!
You scum-sucking trash!
Throw it!
I can't stand the pain!
Max.
That "thing" in there, that's not the Goose.
No way.
I was hungry.
Peanut butter and honey.
I just can't get it clear in my head, Jess.
He was so full of living, you know.
He ran the franchise on it.
Now there's nothing.
Here I am, trying to put sense to it...
...when I know there isn't any.
I'll be all right,
once I get it clear in my head.
- What's this?
- I'm through.
- Again?
- No, not again.
- I'm through. I'm quitting.
- Sit down.
No, I didn't come here to discuss it,
I came to say it. I'm through.
Now, just a minute!
All right, so the Goose bought it.
That's the way
he always came at the world.
Off beat.
Max, you'd be the first to admit
it was long overdue.
All right, I'll tell you how it is.
You're a winner, Max.
You're on the top shelf...
...and I'm not gonna lose you because
of some crazy notion about quitting!
They say people don't believe
in heroes anymore.
Well, damn them!
You and me, Max...
...we're gonna give them back their heroes.
Do you really expect me
to go for that crap?
You gotta admit,
I sounded good there for a minute?
'Bye, Fifi.
Come on, do you want me to beg?
Do you want me on my knees, crying?
Now just a minute.
Give me a reason.
I'm scared, Fif.
Do you know why?
It's that rat circus out there.
I'm beginning to enjoy it.
What is this, funny week?
Any longer out on that road,
and I'm one of them, you know?
A terminal crazy.
Only, I've got a bronze badge
to say I'm one of the good guys.
You know what I'm trying to say?
I'll tell you what I'll do.
Take off a few weeks?
Grow yourself a beard.
Draw flies. Just think about it for a while.
If you still feel the same way
when you come back, it's okay by me.
Go on.
I'm not gonna change my mind.
Get out of here
before I decide to come with you.
'Bye, Fif. Thank you.
You'll be back, Rockatansky!
You're hooked, Max.
And you know it!
I've never been able to say things to you,
Jess, about how I feel.
Guess I always
counted on you understanding.
When I was a kid...
...me and my father
used to go for long walks.
I remember staring down at his shoes.
They were special shoes, brown.
And he always kept them really shiny.
He was tall,
and he used to take long strides.
And there I'd be right alongside him...
...just trying to keep up with him.
I don't think he ever knew
how proud I felt of him.
Or how good it felt
just to be there alongside him.
Even now, when I think back on it,
I still feel"..."
The thing is, Jess...
...I couldn't tell him about it then,
but I can tell you about it now.
I don't wanna wait 10 years to tell you
how I'm feeling about you right now.
Get a load of that!
We had a blowout a while back.
Raunchy, very raunchy.
What's the donk like?
Yeah, the donk's fine.
Look, about this tire"..."
Don't do much work on these myself,
except to scrape 'em off the road.
Yeah. Hey, how about this tire?
Have it fixed in no time.
I can sell you a set of 'lops
for next to nothing.
I can't remember where I got 'em,
but I got 'em, know what I mean?
No, we'll be all right
just as soon as we get this fixed.
- Max?
- Yeah?
Listen...
...Sproggo's talked me
into buying him an ice cream, so...
...I think I'll see you later.
Sure, there's a shop just down the beach.
They'll appreciate the business.
Sure, thanks.
Toodlepip.
You just trucking around?
Good time for just trucking.
Wish I could do a bit myself.
Which way you heading? North?
Maybe.
Look what's turned up for Sunday dinner.
Main course and dessert.
My favorite kind:
Female.
Watch the tongue, lovable.
I've seen him lick his own eyebrow clean.
Must've spent some coin.
Like the sign says,
speed's just a question of money.
How fast do you wanna go?
- Max, quick, get in.
- What's wrong?
Just take my word for it, get in!
- What about the tire?
- Please, Max!
Your tire, man.
Hey, fella, what about your tire!
Crazy people!
The world's full of crazy people.
That wagon, was it here?
A couple with a kid.
I was just fixing their tire.
They left their goddamn spare.
Not a bad one either.
- Who are they?
- A couple, passing through.
Said they were heading north. Maybe.
You want to drive the car? Yeah?
Well, we wouldn't have a car anymore.
Into the back.
Here you go.
I can still see his face now.
Looked as if he'd just swallowed a brick.
What a mean old lady you are. Huh, boss?
That's enough from you, mate! Enough.
What's the matter with you?
What you got there, mate?
Yeah, that's the way I see it, too.
Sure. It's been nice talking to you". '"Bye.
Take it you agreed with him.
They're not worried, I'm not worried.
What about that?
I figure it's lost property.
If no one makes a claim to it,
I say we can forget it.
Sounds okay to me, Jess.
Don't know.
If Ziggy says so, believe me, it's okay.
May's expecting you
up at the farm sometime.
You'll have no more trouble up there.
Just green grass.
How are you doing?
I'm getting there.
I reckon you ought to connect
the doohickey to the gizmo.
Come here, you.
You touch me with those hands
and I'll rip you apart. No!
Look at them! No!
May told me about the little beach
down by the trees. Do you want to come?
Love to.
Except that I've gotta fix the fan belt,
or we're never gonna get outta here.
Okay, Tarzan,
I'll bring you back some bananas.
If you meet Benno down there,
don't let him bother you.
He's only a baby.
Sure, May.
- The men.
- What men?
Now you calm down
and you tell me what's the matter.
Very, very naughty.
- Now, you tell May what you...
- May.
May, you call The Dark One.
And you tell him
to get here as fast as he can.
Why? What's going on?
I think we've got some hoon trouble.
It's gonna be all right.
Come on, darling. Come on, Jessie.
Well, let's go into the house.
You've had an awful time, darling.
But it's all over now.
Everything's going to be all right.
I've just got to go and make a phone call...
...and then we'll have a nice hot cup of tea.
The Dark One, and hurry it up, will you?
It's May Swaisey.
Sprog? Oh, no!
Sprog?
Sprog!
Well, well, well.
It's our little mother.
That there is Cundalini...
...and Cundalini wants his hand back.
I want my baby.
Tell you what...
...l'll swap you.
Please, give me my baby.
Jessie.
You've not got a sense of humor.
You've got a pretty face, though.
Awful pretty.
I suppose...
...you don't need a sense of humor
with a pretty face.
The only trouble is though, missy...
...if you should...
...lose the face...
Please, don't hurt my baby.
...you've got nothing!
What do you want from me?
- Don't change the subject.
- Hold it!
Right there!
- I hate guns.
- Old lady.
Stand back!
- Stay back!
- Woman!
Stay back!
Anyone so much as breathes,
I'll cheese him!
Open that door.
Everyone of you, in there.
Put the babe on the ground.
Jessie, get the van.
Don't stop. Just go right through.
Now what?
- The motor!
- What are you trying to say?
I don't know, it just died on me.
Jessie!
Where?
Lord, have mercy!
What do you reckon?
I'm a doctor, not a fortuneteller.
This your subdural?
- Yes, that's her.
- Lot of problems?
Multiple traumas, spleen,
liver, lung, flail chest...
...left neck of femur, renal shutdown.
Reads like a grocery list. She salvageable?
Yeah, sure,
we got all her signs back last night.
- Relatives?
- The husband.
They lost the kid. DOA.
Listen, tell him she's going to be all right.
Tell him not to worry.
Tell him, if he wants, I'll talk to him.
I don't think he wants to talk to anyone.
He's been standing there
like a zombie all day.
Bubba Zanetti, is that you?
You come for the grunt?
She won't be ready until this afternoon.
Still having trouble with the front forks.
They're mongrels to work with.
You asshole!
What the molly fuck
you think you're doing?
You and me are gonna talk
about the Toecutter.
Never heard of him.
What the Christ are you?
I wanna know about the tattoo.
I mind my own business, don't I?
I mean, they'll kill me, won't they?
I'll say the names,
and you say "yes" or "no"."
Nightrider...
...Toecutter, Bubba Zanetti.
- Yes.
There's more?
- Johnny.
- Johnny the Boy?
- Yeah. Some others.
- Where?
Out at the beaches, looking for fuel.
Are they coming back?
I don't know. They gotta get their bikes.
For Christ's sake!
I don't know.
Code Unspecified.
We have a query
locate on a black Pursuit Special.
Unauthorized use by a Main Force Officer.
This is designated as a potential
Code 3 Red Alert.
Quit toying, Bubba.
Easy. I know what I'm doing.
Hi.
This isn't what it looks, man.
I just came down here
to check it out, and...
...this guy, he's already snuffed it.
Nothing you could do for him.
Ankle.
It's okay.
What are you doing, man?
Hey, listen, I had nothing to do
with anything going on back there, man.
Listen, man, will you? Listen to me!
They were a hell of a lot of
crazy people back there, man.
Some kind of bad people.
I'm not responsible for anything.
What are you doing, man?
What do you say? What are you doing?
Hey, listen. I'm not a bad man.
I'm sick, see? Sick.
What do you call it?
Psychopathic, you know.
Personality disorder.
The court, man, he said so.
You're not gonna hurt me, are you?
Jesus! You can't kill me!
Not for stealing a man's boots!
He was dead, for Christ's sake!
He won't need 'em anymore.
What are you doing?
I wanna know what you're doing.
The chain in those handcuffs
is high-tensile steel.
It'd take you ten minutes
to hack through it with this.
Now, if you're lucky...
...you could hack through your ankle
in five minutes.
Go.
You're mad, man!
You think I look silly, don't you?
Don't bring this on me, man.
Don't do this to me!
Please, sweet Jesus. I was sick!
Don't bring this on me, please!
Subs converted and synched by ShooCat
stick_shoocat@hotmail.com