Executive Producer: Raymond Chow
Associate Producer: Leonard KC Ho
Producers: Wu Ma,
Jeff Lau, Corey Yuen Kwai
Writer: Barry Wong
Production Manager: Chen Peihua
Executive Planning: Hu Puzhao
Starring: Sammo Hung, Yuen Biao
and Wu Han
Joyce Godenzi, Ha Chi-chun, Charlie
Chin Hsiang-lin, Billy Lau Nam-kwang,
Corey Yuen Kwai, Lam Ching-ying,
Cheung Kwok-keung,
Yuen Woo-ping, Yuen Wah
Director: Sammo Hung
1976, America
These Westerners are so dumb.
Szeto Chin. Hong Kong Chinese.
Drug Dealer - 15 years.
The Ching Brothers. Hong Kong
Chinese. Arms smugglers - 20 years.
Stuttering Keung. Malay Chinese.
Armed Robbery - 15 years.
Yun Yen-Hay. Hong Kong Chinese.
Bank Fraud - 20 years.
Ma Puk-Kau. Hong Kong Chinese.
Kidnapping and Murder - 20 years.
Judy Wu. Vietnamese Chinese.
Arson and Blackmail - 15 years.
Nguyen Siu-Tran, Phan Man-Lung.
Vietnamese Chinese.
Armed Robbery and Murder - 15 years.
Tung Ming-Sun. Vietnamese Chinese.
First-Degree Murder - 30 years.
The US government needs your help.
You will undergo training
for one month.
Then you'll team up
with a special commando unit
to undertake a top-secret mission.
Until the mission is over,
you are still convicts.
But once the mission is accomplished,
you are free men.
You will be given US citizenship
and you will receive $200,000.
- Anyone here want to opt out?
- No.
Hey, do you think these are real
people or just dummies?
Why don't you find out?
They didn't move a muscle.
They must be real.
Hey, Grandpa...
how do you plan to spend
your $200 grand?
Half for my daughter,
and the other half for my girl.
Oh, so you're married?
A married man needs no girl, but only
a married man has a daughter.
That's too deep for me.
I don't get it.
Dai-Hoi, how do you plan to spend
the money then?
That's none of your business.
- Brother, don't be like that!
- Shut up!
Fine, I don't need to know.
Hey, how will you spend the money?
I... will... go...
OK, tell me next month.
Ming, I was thinking about
the past...
Don't think about the past.
Lieutenant, this is a cruel operation
for you and your men.
War is cruel.
The order from above is for you
to divert the enemy's attention,
so my commandos can accomplish
the mission.
Don't try to be a hero.
So you want me to do nothing?
I know you, Lieutenant,
but the Vietnam War is over.
We're risking our lives, thanks to
the mistake the Americans made then.
Lieutenant, I want you
to do a favour for me.
That's my brother, Yeung Lung.
The day we withdrew
from the ammunition dump,
he was wounded
and had to stay behind in Ngau.
Locate him if you can
and get him out of Vietnam.
I'll do what I can, Colonel.
Good luck.
- What's going on?
- Six of them. They are drinking.
The plane will arrive at any time.
Try to finish them off. And no guns.
Look at me! Up here! Look at me!
Let's go.
I can't take this!
Where the hell are we going?
Calm down, brother.
It doesn't matter.
We need to be prepared. If we're
going to Europe, I'll need a jacket -
If we're going to Africa, I'll strip!
In hell you just need a shroud.
Am I talking to you?
Do you want me to throw you out?
Don't be like that, brother.
Be quiet.
Ming, I'm really worried.
Do you think we will...
Don't think about it.
Anywhere is better than prison.
Being behind bars all that time
was enough.
You're lucky. At least you spent a
year in America before going to jail.
I was caught
after only three days on shore.
You got caught because you broke
the law. Ming's case was different.
- Like you were any better.
- Did I say anything?
In any case, once the job is done,
let's enjoy life
as law abiding citizens.
This plane has been heading east/
south-east at 420 miles per hour.
That means in three hours,
we will be flying over Vietnam.
Vietnam? Bullshit! Dumb ass!
What? Did you call my brother
a dumb ass? ls that what you said?
Brother, don't be like that!
He means Vietnam is a dumb ass.
That's right.
Can't he bad-mouth his own country?
Hey... just forget it.
You are a dumb ass! Of all the
countries you had to say Vietnam.
I just meant we'll be over Vietnam
in three hours.
Be seated.
No need to be nervous, relax.
We won't be there
for another three hours.
Listen up. To avoid being spotted by
the enemy, we can't fly any lower.
If you open your chutes too early,
you won't land in the right place.
Once you jump, you must count to 20
before you pull open your chutes.
We must pull the parachutes open
ourselves?
Lieutenant, we didn't learn this
in our training.
Don't embarrass yourself!
You just have to pull the rope.
- What if the chute doesn't open?
- Then you'll be the first to land.
If you do,
say hello to my late uncle.
Tell him I didn't burn any offerings
for him,
so he'll have to go on welfare.
Any more questions?
I have...
Have what?
I tried so hard to escape.
I never thought I'd be back.
Remember to count to 20
before pulling the rope.
- Count to 20.
- I... I...I... know...
Go!
Why did they all go into
the coconut plantation?
Lieutenant. Lieutenant.
We're Cambodian guerrillas.
We received orders to assist you.
- Where are my men?
- In the plantation.
Help me get them out.
Where is everybody?
Keep your voice down. Follow me.
Is everyone all right?
Are we all here?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6. All here.
Be serious, will you?
We're missing Stuttering Keung.
Split up and look for him.
Stuttering Keung!
Hey! He's here.
- Stuttering Keung!
- S-s-s-s... sixteen...
Stuttering Keung!
He's dead.
This mission was aborted
before I jumped.
I hope you'll still help me.
Looks like we don't have
much of a choice.
That's right.
Do you need to consult them?
No. They're already scared to death.
Consulting them
will only make matters worse.
I've already mapped out the route
you need to take.
Starting from here...
There's been a change of plan.
We need to go to Ngau.
Ngau village?
Those weren't our orders.
The orders were changed
at the last minute.
I can't stand the stench!
- Are you all right?
- Yes, please continue.
She's not your type. She's a girl.
You can't really call her a girl,
you can just about call her female.
Closing my eyes is not a problem,
but to hold my breath
for her... that's impossible!
I'm not going for her.
I need to go.
Hey, don't try the impossible.
I mean I need to go to the toilet!
There aren't many Vietcong in Ngau,
but there's an army camp nearby.
If alerted, the Vietcong
would be there in 20 minutes.
It would be easier if they'd ordered
the village blown up last week.
Vietcong!
What is it?
What's going on out there?
- What?
- Brother...
Don't question my intelligence.
Hey, an American cigarette packet.
That's strange.
Never mind.
Over there!
Fire!
- What's happening?
- Help, help.
No, please, no! I surrender! No!
Onion Head!
Onion Head...
Let's stop here.
Don't worry, Onion Head!
Everything will be all right.
It's just a flesh wound.
A bit of iodine and you'll be fine.
You won't die. Don't even think it,
because I won't let you.
Onion Head...
What's so bad
about spending your days in prison?
Why come here
and get yourself killed?
Brother...
Hell, brother, we're dying here
one by one, soon it will be our turn.
I quit, Lieutenant!
I'd rather go back to jail.
- Dai-Hoi!
- It's none of your business!
Brother, don't be like that!
Just leave like this?
What if he shoots us from behind?
If you want to leave,
I won't stop you.
Brother!
I'm just following the majority vote!
Think it over, brother.
This is Vietnam!
We don't even know our way!
What if the Vietcong find us?
If you're not careful, you could
fall into one of their traps.
Then you'll die horribly, right?
If we leave now the Vietnamese
will take all the credit.
That would disgrace the Chinese.
OK, I'll go back,
but only for that reason.
Changed his mind again? Wait for me!
That's it.
Three of us will go to the village.
No matter what happens,
don't risk your lives for us.
We'll meet on the hilltop
in two hours.
Be careful.
If something happens,
are we going down to help them?
All right, make way,
let me through, come on!
Make way, make way!
Roll up, come and get it.
I've got everything you need - all
the latest products from the West!
It's real. What's this for?
Uncle Kao from the next village
said if you can get a ship
and take his family to Hong Kong,
he'll give you a big case of gold.
But you must hurry.
Tell Kao to wait for me
at the Village Hall tomorrow.
OK.
- Here, this is for you.
- Thanks.
Look at the mess they've made.
Well, Buddy, did he hurt you?
I saved you this time.
How will you return the favour?
Ring a ring of roses,
a pocket full of posies...
Hey, stop acting like a loony,
will you?
Tell me where the treasure really is.
Once we get rich,
we'll fly out of here together!
Fly?
Fly, fly, I want to fly to the sky...
No problem! We can even go to
the moon! As long as we have money.
So tell me, where is it?
- It's...
- Tell me!
It's here.
What is it, pal?
- Drink this!
- What, is it my birthday?
No, not your birthday,
it's your ticket to hell.
Thanks to this fake wine of yours,
my men still have the runs!
You must be joking!
Drink it and you'll see
if I'm joking.
Drink! I'll count to three.
If you don't drink, I'll kill you!
I'll drink it. You just watch.
Just watch.
Brother!
You bastard! Think you can frame me
with your dirty tricks?!
Don't let me see you
until next month! Get lost!
Where's my God of Wealth?
Mr Yeung, don't be alarmed.
I was sent here by Colonel Yeung-Foo.
Yes, I recognise you all!
You're Fozzy Bear!
You're Kermit the Frog!
And you're Miss Piggy!
Come on,
let's play cops and robbers, OK?
You'll be the cop
and I'll be the robber. I'm off!
Yeung Lung, listen to me!
I'm really...
Someone's coming.
Are you taking a pee, sir?
What do you think -
I'm taking it out for fun?
Don't do it here, it's beneath you.
Go into the lunatic's house.
I need to borrow your toilet.
Sir.
There are Gi's here.
- Three American Gi's.
- Here?
In the wardrobe.
There's one in there.
The other two are over there.
Stop bullshitting me, you nut!
You don't believe me? I'll show you.
Sir, take a look!
They're really here!
They're here! They're really here!
Hey! Why don't you believe me?
Lieutenant, he's got a screw loose.
Take him away, then we'll talk.
Buddy! Buddy!
Don't do anything stupid. If you
fire, the Vietcong will hear you.
Let's talk this over.
Keep out of this
and we may spare your life.
We just want to take Yeung Lung.
Take Yeung Lung?
That's worse than killing me.
Besides, he's a nutcase.
He won't tell you anything.
- What do you think he'll tell us?
- Surely you know about the treas...
- Never mind.
- Put down your gun and come with us.
Otherwise, I'll have to kill you,
even if it means being discovered.
You win.
Let's go.
Hey, stop pointing that thing at me.
If it weren't for Buddy,
I'd have taken your knife long ago.
You see?
Move.
Chieh, why are you driving an ox-cart
and not your bike?
I'm going into town to get married.
This is my fiancée.
That's her father and her brother.
Hello.
Here! These are for you!
Thanks. On your way!
Thank you.
Help...!
Don't shoot! I surrender!
It's me, Rat Chieh!
Inside!
We'll be cut to ribbons this time.
It's not fair to let me die with you.
Let me surrender.
Well?
Don't shoot! I surrender!
It's me, Rat Chieh!
Those bastards!
Give me a gun! I'll shoot every last
one of them. Give it to me.
Why not?
Lieutenant, let me lure them away,
so you can get Yeung out.
And sacrifice yourself?
He's right, you don't
stand a chance by yourself!
You three go out that way
and I'll take Buddy away.
Shut up!
You're hurting my ears.
Bring the cannon.
Come on, hurry up!
Shit! How can so few of us
fight so many of them?
Lord, I want to have a long life.
I don't want to die!
Fire!
You sure have
a lot of reinforcements!
Shit! My motorbike!
Are you OK?
What are you doing here?
I told you not to come!
See? Now we get shit
for saving their asses.
Brother, don't be like that!
That's right! The troops are on
their way. Let's get out of here.
Right! Let's go!
Walk faster, you clumsy ass! Move!
- Brother, don't be like that!
- What?
If you're not going to help,
at least stop cursing him.
Put him down.
He's lost a lot of blood.
Get the bullet out now.
Hey! Don't you dare touch Buddy!
Buddy, are you all right?
Who the hell are you?
Who am l?
You're asking me who I am?
I helped you get this far,
I kept you away from the Vietcong,
and now you ask me who I am?
Come here.
Lieutenant.
Miss...
I don't know if it's your
personality, your looks,
or your figure,
you're simply amazing.
That's the truth.
I don't know if it's
your personality or your looks,
you're simply horrendous.
That's the truth.
Don't feel embarrassed.
I must try harder.
Are you kidding?
Each of us will get $200 grand US?
Tell me,
have I ever lied to you?
No, but I haven't known
you very long.
- Don't you trust me?
- Looks like I've no choice.
- But Buddy...
- Now he's everyone's buddy.
Just get us out of here quick.
You don't have to worry about that.
This is my turf. I...
- Hey! Our friends are approaching.
- I need knives!
Protect him.
Let's hide.
I don't need it. See you later.
You, that way.
The rest follow me.
Spread out!
It's me.
Brother, stop spying.
This is not spying, it's observing.
Whether it's spying or observing,
it's still not right.
When was I ever right in your eyes?
No matter what I say or do,
you always find something wrong.
Can't you just get off my case?
Brother, not so loud.
I have to be loud.
How else will you get the message!
Nag, nag, nag! You've been nagging me
since you were born!
Good! Big dog bites small dog,
small dog runs away.
One more word
and you'll be singing in the rain!
My fault I offended the dog.
Still trying it on?
Forget it, brother. Stop fighting.
- Keep observing.
- It's not observing, it's spying.
Hey, old dog, stop moving.
You're making the ground wet.
You go rest, I'll take over.
That's OK, big sister.
I just don't understand you three.
Why aren't you married?
All the way from Cambodia
to risk your lives?
- We're doing this for our freedom.
- Don't bother.
He doesn't know what a guerrilla is.
You think I don't know?
Guerrilla means a bunch of slackers
who are vulnerable and unreliable.
You're right to be mad.
I'm not kidding, I'm serious.
Come on! Can't you take a joke?
Well done!
I hope we'll see you
blow out a candle again next year!
Don't talk such rubbish!
Raining non-stop day and night!
When do you plan to stop?
It's unending!
Don't blame the heavens.
It's just bad luck. Here.
Actually I'm purposely hiding things
from you. Such as the time...
Don't say another word, Ming.
Even if we don't know, we understand.
You're doing this for all of us.
This relentless rain
is getting to us all.
Can't sleep?
I woke up suddenly from a dream.
As a gentleman, I am duty bound.
I can't bear to see you
stuck out in this wind and rain.
I have to give you some warmth
and support.
I don't need support,
but I am also duty bound.
You stand here,
I'll go over there.
Try and be a man.
Keep a sharp eye out
for anything unusual.
One day I swear
I'll melt the iceberg!
Who was that? Answer or I'll fire!
Take it easy. It's me.
I'm just taking a leak.
Not there!
Do you want people to see you?
Yes, that's why
I've come to pee here.
In this rain, you can't tell
whether it's rain or pee!
Hey, don't you dare aim at me
or I'll shoot!
Yeah, right! Shoot me then!
Vietcong!
There's Vietcong!
Help! Help!
Help!
Move!
Keep it moving!
Get your bets in.
Come on, let's get on with it.
Place your bets.
- No more bets? Let's play.
- Fine with me.
Heads or tails?
- Heads.
- Tails.
Heads.
Take him to the water cage.
- Are you trying to kill him, idiot?
- I wanted to get a confession.
That man's made of steel.
Let me talk to my superior.
Boss, you can't die.
- Let's do it.
- I don't think I can.
We have no choice. Come on.
What are you doing?
Someone is coming...
Where are you taking me?
Go on! Go! Climb!
On your knees!
Come on, we're all counting on you.
This time we'll win for sure.
Lost again!
This time you'll lose for sure.
This time I'm gonna win, ready?
They've lost.
What's the matter, are you afraid?
I'm not afraid, I'm not afraid.
Hey, enough games! Take him back!
Good luck, kid.
Stop fooling around you lot!
Take him back!
I need to interrogate him some more.
Why are you playing with them?
We won!
Yes... yes, yes.
All I know is
they're going to Pine Slope.
I'll let you know
as soon as we have anything new.
I understand.
Get down!
You nearly got me killed!
- What's going on down there?
- Nothing.
- Then why were you shouting?
- Come here.
- Come here, come here.
- What?
You lot come here!
What do you want?
Why all the shouting?
Did you hear that the US troops
are coming again?
I wonder what it's like
in Ho Chi Minh City?
The girls are great there.
Hey, you look like that fat guy
in the water cell.
Not like him, I am him!
- Get them out first!
- Go!
Get out of here!
- Brother!
- Big brother!
It... really... hurts!
Don't move! Don't move! Help! Help!
Big brother.
Big brother, wake up.
Don't die! Help!
If my brother were still alive,
he'd have been the same age.
Don't comfort me with that bullshit.
He was killed during the outbreak
of the Vietnam War.
I was only seventeen.
Was your brother as nagging as mine?
No.
Well, I'm not irritating
and impulsive like you.
I'll never be like that again.
No matter how irritating I am now,
there'll be no one here to remind me.
If you change, then your brother's
death was worthwhile.
Worthwhile! What do you mean by that?
Brother, don't be like that!
You're all a bunch of animals!
Let's bury him and be on our way.
What did you say? On our way?
Fine! You tell us then!
What exactly is our mission?
What did my brother die for?
I still can't tell you that.
Then I'll tell you.
I'm quitting for real this time!
Lieutenant, I don't want to die
without knowing why.
I don't want to die either,
no matter what it's for.
If you don't tell us now,
I would rather die here and stay
with my brother than follow you.
Lieutenant, we've risked our lives
many times.
It's time you told us the truth.
All right. We're not too far from our
destination anyway. Our mission is...
Hold it!
You think I'm crazy.
I pretended to be crazy because
I didn't know who you people were.
But now I know
we have a spy amongst us.
A spy?
That's right.
The spy is...
Don't!
Use frequency 1246
to contact our leaders
and ask for a course of action.
We vowed to fight the VC,
none of us would do that.
Shit! I give up!
You said she'd pick up
the transmitter for sure.
So it's someone else?
I told you the Vietcong are sneaky.
You can't expose her so easily.
You said she deliberately left cloth
behind for the VC to follow us.
You saw her talking to the Vietcong
on the phone. So what?
Actually, no one would believe
you're Vietcong.
Even if you were,
I still wouldn't believe you.
- Tell me, are you Vietcong?
- No...
I know you'll say no.
But you really are Vietcong, right?
Say it! No need to say it? Yes...
Lau Shun-Ying, I've always treated
you as a sister, a life long friend.
How could you?
Spare me the lecture,
just pull the trigger.
Don't look at me.
I never want to see your face again!
General.
Whatever their mission is,
kill them all!
Yes, General!
I heard the guerrillas escaped.
We worked so hard to catch them!
It's over there.
Go round again.
If we can capture that helicopter,
we've hit the jackpot.
Lieutenant, it's not that difficult
to get to the bridge.
There are only two machine guns
at this end.
But getting to the other end
is not so easy.
There are two more guns
waiting for us there.
If we just charge ahead, the bridge
would become our entrance to Hell.
If we don't cross here,
how long will it take?
For a young man, about 2-3 days.
For an old fart like him,
at least a week.
Did you hear that? An elderly man
shouldn't get in a youngster's way.
I heard you.
Don't worry, you won't get old.
Can you two cut the crap for once!
Lieutenant, I think we have a better
chance crossing by night.
Hey! Come here!
Look.
They'll be here in about three hours.
We have no time to lose.
We're like cornered rats here.
I'd rather run
and live to fight another day.
The only way is to let me cross
the bridge and destroy the guns.
Once you two hear the explosion,
fix the two guns on this end.
The rest of you,
cross when you hear the explosion.
- Everybody got it?
- Yes.
- I don't.
- Just follow the others.
There's a truck coming.
Let me get on the truck first.
Is there really a $200,000 reward?
It's more than that now. Let's go!
Move and we all die.
Lay down your guns and sit down.
Don't try anything.
Stop!
- Is it safe on the road?
- So-so.
- Have you seen any guerrillas?
- No.
- Stay on the alert.
- Yes.
- What happened?
- Guerrillas.
No! Don't cross now!
All for one and one for all!
- Watch out!
- I've been doing that for 70 years.
You can't be that old!
Judy Hu, are you all right?
Grandpa, are you all right?
Don't cry, Grandpa.
I'm hurt too.
Let's fight!
Judy!
- Grandpa!
- Judy!
Grandpa, hang in there!
I've been hanging in there
since I was born.
Don't you worry. Even if I get blown
to pieces, I'll still carry you home.
Then my guts
would be turned inside out.
No, it's better to wait for death.
You go.
If Dai-Hoi can't carry you alone,
I'll help him out.
Save it.
All my daughters are married.
You're still talking rubbish
at a time like this.
What should I say, something noble?
I wanted to leave, but I couldn't.
I don't want to die. I can't.
At least I will die in the East,
and not in the West.
You guys go and finish the mission.
We'll meet again soon.
Ming, you go first.
No, we're going first.
- No need to take care of us.
- I...
Ming, I've always liked you
because you talk straight.
Don't ruin it by stopping now.
I won't say much either, take care.
If you're still alive, look us up.
Promise me not to die too soon, OK?
We have to leave now,
the troops are arriving!
We've got to leave now!
Go on!
See you on the way back!
You corpses sure are heavy.
Judy... hurry up!
Here they come, Grandpa.
Do you think I'm deaf?
Grandpa, let me do it.
Do you think I'm blind?
I wouldn't dare mock you, you've gone
through so much more than me.
I can see you're an honest man,
because all this time you still
haven't lit that cigarette.
My friend gave me this
for safe-keeping before he died.
Well, soon you can return it
to him personally.
Here, let me.
- What did your friend die of?
- Lung cancer.
Here they come!
I know.
Closer and closer!
I know!
Right where we want them.
Ready...
Fire!
We got them!
Good, now we can die.
Grandpa, I'll see you down below.
Wrong, it will be up high. We've
been living in hell all our lives.
How can we be going to hell again?
Look up.
What's the colour of the sky?
It's blue. I guess we're going
to the right place after all.
Wrong...
it's black.
Fire!
The entrance is here.
Follow me.
- Who knows how to start a generator?
- I do.
Come with me.
It's here. Break it open.
Nothing's happening.
It's starting!
Wow! If the Vietcong get their hands
on this lot, lots of people will die.
We've already lost enough.
- Let's install the detonators.
- Detonators?
Hey! You're not going
to blow them up, are you?
That's right.
There are nine ammunition dumps here.
Each dump has its own security units.
We must install time bombs
in every dump.
- Set the timer to 30 minutes.
- Hold on.
Lieutenant, you can't blow up
the artillery.
This could be very useful
to our guerrillas.
My mission is to destroy them.
Let's help each other out.
- Lieutenant!
- Don't move! Drop your weapons!
Don't move! Drop it!
- Drop it!
- It wasn't me. I didn't move.
Lieutenant, don't push me.
Why did we endure so much
to stay in Vietnam
if not to wipe out the Vietcong and
stop them from ravaging our country
and killing our people.
Lieutenant, I admire your loyalty
in doing your duty,
but you're wounded now,
you're no longer responsible.
Let us keep the artillery
so we can fight the Vietcong.
Tung Ming-Sun,
install the detonators now!
You made me do it.
- Don't move!
- Big sister!
Don't move!
Buddy?
Tung Ming-Sun, the bombs!
Let's give him a hand.
Be careful!
Don't shoot the artillery!
I'm coming to see you, Grandpa.
But I'm bringing some friends.
Let me blow up these bastards.
It's useless! The artillery must
never get into the Vietcong's hands.
Help them install the detonators now.
- Kiddo!
- Big sister, don't worry about me.
- Lieutenant!
- That way! I'll help you.
Heroes don't need guns.
Are these people all dead?
Wait for me!
Let's go before this place blows.
Let's go! We're running out of time.
- What's happening?
- Run!
Run, fast before it blows!
Mum, why didn't you give me an extra
pair of legs so I could go faster?
No, not this way.
The gate is locked and there
are loads of Vietcong out there.
So we're sitting ducks then?
Escape by water!
Pull harder!
Hurry!
- We made it at last. Now what?
- We wait for the plane.
- Are you sure it will come?
- The Lieutenant said so.
But that was
before we changed the plan.
I don't know if it will come.
We have to try our luck anyway.
- Try our luck?
- It's the damned Americans' fault.
If it wasn't for them we'd be fine.
If that's how you feel,
where will you go?
America, of course!
Subtitles by
European Captioning lnstitute