...you don't even deserve sympathy
Hear Chuni Babu?
A courtesan talking of romance
Am I to learn of her what love is,
what romance be? What is amour?
Love mirrored in your soul, amour
God's gift to life's design, romance
How regrettable Chuni Babu
Your friend possesses none...
of soul, or intent or purpose
That thing you flash
time and again Dev Babu...
the money, it lies at the feet
of harlots in brothels
If you be so vain, return to me
what I spent on you
Two nights
You owe me 2 nights, Dev Babu.
No more shall I dance...
not until you come.
These eyes will await you
"F" for friendship, she came seeking,
you found a foe. You owe two nights
O'faithless lover
Music plays
Let slip the veil
Let the revelry begin
- Revelry awaits you, Chandramukhi
- No Appa. Not until Dev Babu arrives
Pure gold.
Custom made, in Lucknow
I also have a gold nose ring
I wish to tie the dancing bells
to your feet, Chandramukhi
Do wear the nose ring and
allow me to unscrew it afterwards
Desist from such ardour Kali Babu.
Get too close and you will burn...
in the very lamps that light up
nights of revelry
At the next instance of insolence
I'll give you a nose ring and...
the rest of the revelers
may take pleasure in unscrewing
In a marketplace
full of beauties...
such spirit
is what draws me to you
But the one you
await so eagerly...
has no interest
in you or your music
It was some Paro's firefly that ran
into your fires crying Paro-Paro
- Never will he return, Chandramukhi.
- He will come, he will Kali Babu
- You will see. That's from my heart.
- Why not take on a bet?
If he doesn't come before
the candle has burnt out...
then you will wear these
dancing bells...
- ...only for my pleasure.
- I accept
And if he comes...
then you shall leave
wearing these very dancing bells
Agreed
Whose footfall?
Whose shadow?
Who knocks at my heart?
Who is come?
Who paints me this emerald?
My joy...
is killing me
No Moon I ever desired...
nor stars I ever seeked...
complaints I have none...
every sorrow I have hidden...
every taunt I laughed off...
thorns I embraced...
their blossoms have wounded me
But whenever I have prayed...
of The Lord...
I have always seeked you
Who paints me this emerald?
Is killing me
I'm slain
Slain
You aren't accustomed to the drink.
Why drink beyond your limits?
What fool drinks
to stay within limits?
I drink that I may force myself
to stay on...
looking at you,
tolerating you...
that I may lose my senses,
to help me forget Paro
But Chandramukhi...
such are memories of Paro,
they won't even let me lose my senses
Why, after all I drink, do memories
of her haunt me day and night?
Why...
oh why?
Why, does man become so naive?
Why make mistakes?
Why... for foible...
so harsh a punishment?
Why?
As to be rent asunder?
One enters matrimony,
and the other...?
Slain
In what fain folly...
he forsakes the lotus...?
For a paper flower?
Dev Babu!
I... I fall
- Dev Babu
- Don't touch me! I despise you!
I can't bear to see woman
come to this. Begone
Never again shall
I stand at this door
But yes, whenever
I come to think of Paro, I shall
And come the guilt pangs,
I shall come
For where else can I go?
- There... I have sentenced myself.
- Why punish yourself so?
Because every day,
my heart is put to trial
Me Lord!
Me Lord!!!
"Every day,
this romance is tried"
"I... I object..."
But every day,
the verdict is the same
"Saraf Narayan Mukarji I object,
objection overruled!"
"Devdas Mukarji I object,
"You are convicted"
"You are guilty and you...
you drink till death."
"Yes Me Lord"
"No objection"
No...
No... No...
Paro
The new bride has laid to rest
all my worries
With Parvati's arrival our
lost days of joys are here again
Meet Yashomati's mother-in-law.
This is Parvati
To Bhuvan Chaudhary,
you'd more likely be...
- ...a daughter than his wife.
- Whatever I am to him...
you and I are like sisters.
We should be embracing each other
But you are many years
my elder
From what I see, in Manikpur,
wives are better endowed than daughters
- No Badi-Ma?
- Our daughters, we send away...
in hope that they will be cared for,
but we're disappointed. No, Badi-Ma?
Yashomati.
I was eager to meet you
We ought not to be cross with kin.
You and I are of the same age
So you decide,
how we will relate to each other
Mother and daughter?
Or friends?
Ma
- What's this, Ma? All this...?
- Gifts, from your Ma
You'll look great
Parvati, will you keep to your daughter?
Won't you give us company?
I do not like the smoking pot.
The smoking pot has pride of place, Parvati
I don't think so, no pride in what
goes up in smoke
Wonderful, mother-in-law!
I delight in your words
I have been so eager to see you.
We missed each other's weddings
My obeisances
Touching your feet was a pleasure.
I have been given my wish
How I wish I had attended
your wedding...
if only to have my wish of
pulling you up by your ear
Why, pulling you up by the ear
was a pleasure
This first acquaintance,
I shall always remember, mother-in-law
Remember the relationship too
Dev Babu. What happened?
Dev Babu
If I am so despicable, if my touch
be so abhorrent, then why...
did you come into my life?
In my solitude I was content.
Why be my messiah of misery?
Chandramukhi?
That stopped the spasm didn't it?
Divert your attentions and...
- ...the deepest wounds may be healed.
- Which is what I am upto
Stop it, you've had enough
Why not say I've lived enough?
How could I...?
You have Paro, memories of Paro
All I have is you, my Midas
A touch
and iron is made to gold
Are you pricing yourself or me?
In a world of relationships...
what value a woman
of easy virtue?
Nothing
Besides, you won't even give me
the right to touch you
- Are you in love with me?
- Or you could ask me if I breathe
You breathe, Chandramukhi
What will you get out of it?
I have no home, no heart
Loving isn't only about receiving.
Love, I have traded many times
But loved, I have but once
Pour more into a chalice filled,
and what happens?
It spills,
to the ground
So too my cup floweth over,
with Paro
More can only spill...
to fall, and in the falling,
take you down too
But in the spilling, the wine
must've been caressed by the chalice
Then spill...
some more
Where is Devdas?
I must see him
- Asleep. You can't see him now.
- Can I not? I'm here to take him
I'm not leaving him
in this hell
Dharamdas!
- Master...!
- Who gave you my whereabouts?
Chuni Babu
Babu-ji...
Babu-ji won't even see my face.
Why has he sent you?
Anyway, he will be displeased
to see me as I am
Sir Narayan Mukherjee will have
to hang his head in shame
- Go! Go Dharamdas, go away.
- Listen Deva...
Your father is no more
Too bad
All of a sudden... how...?
He was a nice man
Such men aren't born too often
He was a good man
Babu-ji has earned...
another title, no?
Late Sir Narayan Mukherjee
We loved each other dearly
But too bad, this is too bad
Late, Sir Mukherjee...
was a good man
- Does Devdas drink every day?
- When doesn't he drink?
Alcohol, day and night.
Lives on it
- Why don't you stop him?
- But only if he'd stay at home
Rarely does he come home.
There he lies in Chitpore...
in Chandramukhi's brothel, all day
The room upstairs is practically
Deva's residence
Devdas! He lives in a brothel?
Oh God
Such days I have lived to see
- Have you seen Chandramukhi?
- When I went to fetch Deva...
...I saw her.
What is she like?
Sweet deceit, as they say.
Famous courtesan, uses her charms
She plunders, he squanders. We must
rescue our Deva from the hell, Paro
I cannot tell him anything,
but he'll surely listen to you
He holds you in high esteem,
he can't refuse you
Please Didi, tell her
Only you can stop him, Paro.
Only you can stop him from drinking
- Dharamdas, get a hold on yourself.
- You'll see him won't you?
Paro, do you want me to malign you,
to give you a bad name?
Had we given ourselves a bad name,
we might've ended up together
- You're happy, aren't you Paro?
- Oh it's a different world, Dev
Huge manor, vast estates,
important people, great debates
Great debates!
You've matured Paro
You even look like an aristocrat.
Huge red dot, large eyes...
big dreams...
huge manors,
vast estates...
and grown-up children
Paro... Paro, Paro. Ei!
Those large eyes,
I can keep watching
But I can't bear to see
big teardrops in those eyes
Just as well that you came by.
I got some things I wish to return
Who knows, I might never return
Come Paro... come
Stand right here
Look...
at yourself. Remember...?
"Arre O'Deva"
What happened Paro?
"Deva, I lost my anklets.
Have you seen them?"
No, not I
I stole them
And you knew I did it
and why I did it
All day, the chime of your anklets,
and-Deva-this-and-Deva-that...
And your pot
And here, the memento
of our love, our parting
You just left, that was the end
of the relationship
But I'm still tied
to all these, Paro
And I am tied
to memories of you
- What's that?
- A few coins
- Three Rupees.
- All they're worth are memories
Mine, aren't they? You thief
I'll take them back,
but only with usury
- How much interest will you take?
- Two percent
At two percent...
six cents a month
72 cents a year
For 13 years...
13 years, Paro
9.36
You've become good at arithmetic.
Circumstance taught me, Paro
Let's talk of something else
Paro, why not turn matchmaker
and find a bride for Devdas?
- I hear Manikpur girls are nice?
- Yes, but you want a beauty, no?
No, not a beauty.
Just someone like you
- Someone who is pleasant?
- No, must be a bit naughty
Should be able to quarrel with me.
Like I said, she should be like you
- You can find them by the thousands.
- Spare me the thousands
Just let me come to grips with
only one, of the likes you. Enough
- Give up drinking, Dev.
- No, Paro.
- Try.
- No
You can give it up. Promise me
that you'll never drink again
Can you promise
you'll forget me?
It's rather late, Paro
Dev!
I'm not leaving
until I have your word
- I can't.
- You can
- One can do anything one wants.
- Can you elope with me tonight?
- What are you saying?
- Can you elope with me?
- You've no one to look after you.
- I had only one dream. To serve you.
- If there's love, there's no fear
- One chance to fulfill my dream?
- Can you elope with me? Can you?
- Come with me. I'll care for you.
- Can you elope with me, Paro?
I can't bear to see you like this!
I feel like dying, Dev
I feel like dying
If serving me makes you happy,
then so be it
I promise you, before I die
I'll surely come to your doorstep
Swear... Swear that, by me
Heartless
Your mother is squandering money.
Given so charitable a disposition...
- ...soon the coffers will be empty.
- Absolutely right, Kumud
But how can I stop Ma?
You're such a complete fool
- You can't. But I can stop her.
- You will stop her? But how?
The keys to the vault? With you?
Ma has been looking for them
Kumud!
I've hidden the keys.
You will say that the keys are lost
- What...?
- The vault keys are lost
And the vault has been robbed
The key...
to the money
Brother-in-law! You...?
So early? In the offices?
And alcohol...? Without as much
as a care for the family prestige?
What will people say?
What will your mother think?
You didn't consider that
when you were stealing the keys?
What will people say?
What will your Chhoto-Ma think?
The wealth of our forefathers
may not be squandered over alcohol
The keys left by our forefathers
may not be stolen like this
I'm making this clear.
Under no circumstance...
- ...am I parting with the keys.
- You will turn in the keys
Today and now
Right here
To my mother
Do not think I am so weak.
I too hail from a family of landlords
I have seen money by the chestfuls
in my father's house
Have you seen the streak of madness
that runs in the family?
Dev!
- What are you upto, Dev?
- Brother you surely agree that...
...I have as much right as you to the
wealth that our forefathers left us
Yes.
Why are you pouring alcohol?
I'm putting on fire my share.
Save your share if you can
- Dev, I'll give you anything you want!
- As of now...
- ...only the keys.
- Which you will never have
Kumud! Give him the keys.
Else, he'll burn down the office
Let him do whatever he wants.
I'm not scared of empty threats
He's actually burning the place down!
Call Chhoto-Ma
- Give him the keys, Kumud.
- No
He's crazy!
Are you out of your mind, too?
- No!
- Give him the keys
What's up Kumud?
What's happening in this house?
Chhoto-Ma
Chhoto-Ma, you were looking for the keys
to the vault, weren't you?
I caught him with the keys
and he threatened me
He won't part with the keys
and he wants his share
Else, he'll burn the house down.
I pleaded with him...
You want your share?
That is your only share, Dev
No one in this house
ever understood you
All of us are responsible
for your ruination
Before we lead you to worse,
leave this house
Babu-ji said leave the village.
Everyone said, leave Paro
Paro said, leave drinking.
Now you say, leave this house
One day, He will say...
leave this world
Hereby I rescind all my rights
to everything in this house
But I am part of you.
That right no one takes away from me
Not even you
Do you know, what you're asking for?
It's no easy undertaking,
it's an ancient ritual
For the ritual, one must fetch
the soil from a courtesan's doorstep
In that soil, is built
the image of the goddess
I know
And go where men daren't even walk
in daytimes for fear of censure?
Why Badi-Ma? Don't humans live there?
Is there no air...?
No sun in those quarters?
Do rains refuse to visit them?
Nature doesn't discriminate.
Should we?
Parvati is right.
Even Subhadra wanted it done
Very well,
as our Parvati wishes
- But remember, it's the Durga Puja.
- Rest assured
I'll tell Mahendra
to facilitate your journey
Devdas lives in a brothel?
A lady is here, wants to see you.
She's also asking about Dev Babu
Must be Paro
Paro...?
- How did you know I'm Parvati?
- Dev Babu told me...
...should a woman come asking for him,
she can only be Paro
What are you doing?
My obeisances to the woman,
whom I shall never be able to replace
I have heard of exotic women here,
but you possess the wile too
Only if you'd see,
I have a heart too
Chandramukhi...
isn't that your name?
They also call me Devdasi
- You are famous.
- Not anymore
Why?
At angel's touch, I learnt
of a sacrifice I never knew
How strange of a courtesan
to swear by fidelity
Curious too...
what draws an aristocrat
to a courtesan's doorstep?
Where is Dev?
I too am eager to hear his footfall.
Six months it has been...
- ...since I set my eyes on him.
- You lie
- If you don't trust, look around.
- Or do you assume I won't?
How long do you think
you can keep Dev here?
Only so long as the beauty,
the youth, the money?
What's your endgame?
You must have fleeced Dev
I'll pay you more. I can't bear
to see Dev suffering this hell
How strange
The very Paro who drove Dev Babu
to insanity, wants to buy him
And what may you have to offer me?
Can you offer social recognition?
Can you possibly
make him love me?
Or make it possible
that I may touch him, just once?
Dreams, longing, hopes,
that he has kindled in my heart...
might you make them come true?
Can you?
No, you cannot deliver
- And I will not give you Dev Babu.
- And I will take him away
And no one is stopping me. Not you,
not social sanction, not even Dev
Not to forget, courtesans
aren't destined to have husbands
Courtesans have no destiny, lady
From your perspective,
you can see nothing. From mine...
you will find him everywhere
Look, there he is,
in the flame of the lamp
There he lies,
in folds of the covers
In that half a chalice...
his thirst lies, unquenched.
His fragrance still lingers
Take it all, if you can. The light,
the folds, the fragrance, all of it
All yours
- But I cannot give you your Devdas.
- You love Dev so dearly?
I only worship him
Now I'm assured.
Dev isn't lonely anymore
Oh I forgot what I came here for.
I want to perform the Durga Puja
From your doorstep,
I want soil
May I...?
- What is this?
- I came for Dev. Instead...
it's something I entrust you with
I will expect you for
the Durga Puja. Do come
Chandramukhi...
I'm so happy to have you here
I'm glad
How could I refuse your invitation?
I had to come
Have you met Dev?
Parvati?
Who is this?
Chandramukhi, my friend.
She comes from Calcutta
Bless you, consider this your home.
Parvati, don't let her go too soon
Sure. You will leave only after
the celebrations
No Paro! I can't stay here
Why not? It's been ages since I had
a heart-to-heart chat with someone
Come, let celebrations be the ruse
for forgetting our woes
Let's sing, dance,
give ourselves a little to live
- No...
- Our joys might touch Dev
- Paro, listen to me.
- No refusing. For Dev's sake
Come Kali Babu, the chess game
isn't over yet
The real chessgame
is being played here
Devdas' Chandramukhi comes.
To meet Devdas' Paro
- Who's Paro?
- Mother-in-law
Parvati. One move and
I've checkmated all four
Paro
Chandramukhi
Bhuvan Chaudhary
Devdas
Deva...
Deva, the day is dawning
But forever, this heart
will live in darkness
- Shall we go now?
- To whom?
One by one,
all my relationships are over
Between my father and I
there was no love lost, right?
I was his tempest
and he was my whip
Even my brother figured first
in mother's lullaby, right?
My brother and I never hit it off.
He's practical, I'm impractical
One inculcates a humorous
relationship with a brother's wife
I was the one who ended up
being the butt of the joke, right?
And there was Paro
and I love her...
you know...
so much
So much, right?
Paro!!!
Now she is estranged too
But there's one...
one Chandramukhi.
Loves me dearly
But...
priest?
Priest...
- Are you familiar with the last rites?
- Of course
- Will you perform the ritual?
- Of course. Who is the deceased?
- Devdas Mukherjee
- Are you insane, Deva?
- You'll perform your last rites?
- Give me my last rites
Priest, go away
Deva! What madness is this?
Come back
Unto the departed Soul...
grant salvation, Lord
Come back, I beg of you
The throb...
sways my heart
I dare that evil eye
or let thunder strike
I'll wear my dancing bells
In my anklets...
I will give in
to the ecstasy...
of the throb...
that sways
my heart, my soul
What chimes?
What's that love in eyes?
Why the crescendo?
Is it longing?
He's in the red dot I wear
He's in the dream in my eyes
You're obsessed
Your heart beats for him
I remember him in the chime
I remember him in the tinkle
You've given me a world...
of your own happinesses
Never desert him
Marry him
To him you are priceless
I am worthless
Wonderful
What a display of true colour
An aristocrat and a courtesan
come together
- What are you saying, Babu?
- That which you see, Badi-Ma
And what everyone is watching
This woman, whom Mother-in-law
calls a friend, is a whore
Yes Mother-in-law?
What am I hearing Parvati?
- Why are you silent? Answer.
- She is embarrassed
Landlords did keep whores
Now even a lady of the manor makes
friendships in brothels. Wonderment
That's stripping without touching, Chandramukhi.
You started the farce. I ended it
No Kali Babu, if men could
enact farce, what need for whores?
You would've had
your brothel too
Chandramukhi!!!
You know it
and it's commonplace
It is the aristocrat
who brings cheer to the brothels
And bastards are born
of aristocrats of your ilk
Call them illegitimate if you will,
but aristocracy runs in their veins
Company of the aristocracy doesn't
confer status to the courtesan
Absolutely correct, Badi-Ma. But why
should the lady be embarrassed?
If she spoke a few kind words to me,
it's because she considers me human
He who frequents the alleyways
of disrepute ought to be ashamed
The very dens littered with trophies
of the lust of his forefathers
Have you thought, Kali Babu? You might have
a sister somewhere in the brothels
Why sister? You might even
visit your daughter's...
In the soil
at the courtesan's doorstep...
is moulded the image of the goddess.
The soil isn't impotent
Now the farce ends
I return, lady...
back to my world,
to those disreputable alleys...
where I might someday find
Dev Babu again
Farewell
Before leaving,
I wish to apologise
Talking in public
about Chandramukhi was a mistake
I didn't make the other mistake.
I told your husband and Badi Ma...
about your friendship with Devdas
You liked twisting my ear?
I would cut your nose to spite your face
Goodbye
Not at Parvati,
fingers will be raised at us
The matter must end
here and now
- Did you ask for me?
- Yes Parvati
- I would like to know...
- ...who Devdas is?
Devdas is a childhood friend,
he was body, I was soul
He is my love and he is my vanity
and he is with me, always
- Do you realise what you are saying, Parvati?
- Same as what you told me
You're now the lady of the manor, Parvati.
The mother of my children. No doubt
- But Subhadra, I can never forget.
- Subhadra was my wife
Subhadra was your first love.
Devdas is mine
First love, like years
can never be obliterated
Parvati, you are forgetting.
You are the lady of the manor
Maybe that's reason for my guilt?
I'll accept any penalty you decree
Of course you will be punished, Parvati
The very men who paid obeisances
to this manor are enjoying a farce
You may never step out of the manor.
This is your punishment
But what punishment, Parvati?
We are the ones being punished
The lamps we lit in celebration
have set fire to our house
Always put out the fires
that threaten your home
Fun, frolic and friends
Without you, life was desolate.
With you, comes the cheer
Why care for outcomes?
Let's raise cheer
Yes friend?
Let clink the glasses
Let clink the glasses,
whatever the outcome
And hear the chhalak-chal in the swirl
Music, when my cup floweth over
And hear the dhamk-dhamk-dham
inside your heart...
when you clink the glasses
This madeira...
This madeira showers
a rain of memories
In every spill, madeira
cheats the heart
The madeira coursing down tells...
tales of hearts
Like lightning in hearts,
it strikes clouds of sorrow
And when it reaches the heart...
it evokes...
memories of her
Oh for a glimpse...
Oh for a glimpse of her
That's...
what little I pray for
So little I pray for
Mira dances for her
Ghanshyam...
she dances in gay abandon
Hear the jhanak-jhank-jhan
in the chime of her anklets
I'm in love,
I don't care for censure
And how...
Now hear the thirak-thirak?
That's my heart dancing away
Even a drop of alcohol
is poison for him
Any moment may be treacherous
Try to keep him in good cheer
Oh God!
What is this Dharamdas?
Cry and you will make me cry too
And people will call me a courtesan
who cannot enact a farce
We got to keep Dev Babu
in good cheer, no?
Game over. I win again
No point playing with you!
You've robbed us blind
A few more games with you and
you'll make me sell this brothel
Stop giggling and get lost
Time for your medicine.
I'll send it over
- In a chalice. Else, it won't work.
- Even contemplating it is lethal
Met Paro?
- How did you find my Paro?
- If love be personified...
Paro's would be the being,
hers the very heart
Forbidden though it is, I always
end up with a metaphor about eyes
One Paro
and one, Chandramukhi
One, sentimental, vivacious
And you...
how delicate, how demure
She is fickle, like a doe,
gushing like a river...
the liar, the butterfly, the Moon
and you...?
Poem? Ballad?
Some tears, sometimes fire
- Everyone loves her.
- And you, unloved by all save me?
Chandramukhi...
What is this, Chandramukhi?
I was likening you to fortitude
What you turn out to be? Wax doll?
Look at you, melting away
Will you let the candle melt away
and cast me in dark?
You've done much for me, Chandramukhi.
One more favour
- Let me leave.
- No! You know not what you suffer
- You know it and I suffer.
- Then why must you...?
I must face myself
before I'm lost
May a servant follow you?
I cannot bear to see my death
mirrored in your eyes
I have been given heaven and earth
Will we meet again?
What the Judge of virtue and vice
will pronounce for you I know not
But in the afterlife, should we meet
I won't be able to renounce you
Deva...
- Deva, what is the matter with you?
- What's the matter...?
Are you all right?
- How come you haven't left?
- I'm not leaving you all alone
- Are you afraid I'll drink again?
- Alcohol is poison for you
- One drop...
- And I'm dead?
Yes! You were delirious,
that's why I didn't leave you
And enough of this journey.
You've had your say and I've had enough
At the next station, we change the
train and we go to see your mother
At the next station,
you go back to your compartment
- Why are you so stubborn?
- Put out the lights
And tomorrow, I'm taking you
to a doctor. Always fickle
Passengers to Sonarpur, Garia,
Phoolbagan to detrain
Dharamdas, you're back?
Chuni Babu?
Friend! How are you?
Small world it is, that's why
we keep bumping into each other
- So where and how have you been?
- Right here and I'm fine
- Tell me how you have been.
- What with me, I'm soaring
But you look... pale.
What gives, friend?
For a moment I was in a quandary.
Is this my star of Chitpore?
- No, I'm all the same.
- Even if you aren't, here I am
Let's raise cheer.
It's been long, let's have a party
So what if we aren't in a brothel?
Even train compartments will do
If not the dancing bells,
let's cheer the rhythm of the rails
If not Chandramukhi,
let it be between her paramours
Here you are
- No Chuni Babu, I don't drink.
- Someone has extracted a promise?
- No.
- Then do it, for friendship's sake
After ages! Let's live it up.
Why not?
In a tomorrow, may we be?
Might not
You'll be. As for me,
you never know
My share of life I've lived,
now I'm counting on my heart
What with the world, it will even
grudge you your last breath
Encore! How sweet!
That's poetry
Shards of the heart,
they call poetry. I don't care
Encores? Wonderful
Encore, encore
Hey Dev Babu...
what's happening?
What's ailing you?
Have you taken a cure?
I'm incurable, Chuni Babu
- Then why did you drink, knowing...?
- For friendship's sake, Chuni Babu
Friendship? You take me for
a stranger? Not again, not again...
No stranger, Chuni Babu.
You're the closest to me
I've even imbibed your metaphor.
The Sunrise of life...
the salutations...
then the solace...
and in seconds, time takes
such a turn Chuni Babu...
- ...all ties with life are severed.
- No Dev Babu
The Sun...
the song, the serenade,
sympathy between friends
- But separation... no...
- It all ends, Chuni Babu
No
Silence? So deathly?
As if I'm dead already?
I swear by our friendship...
this silence...
is stifling
And you know Chuni Babu,
miles to go...
before my thirst is quenched
Oh when will my thirst
be quenched?
- Chhoti-Ma! Chhoti-Ma!
- What happened?
- What happened Chhoti-Ma?
- What happened to Chhoti-Ma?
Blood...?
Pandua. Passengers to Manikpur,
Mirzapur, Mirgaon, detrain
If serving me makes you happy...
I promise you, before I die
I'll surely come to your doorstep
Swear... Swear that, by me
Are we there?
Dev Babu, the journey has just begun.
What's wrong with you?
Devdas... come to me, my darling
All day tramping around the village
with that Paro
Not another moment
for you in this house
- Deva! I'm not letting you leave!
- Dharamdas! Don't let him go
Stop Dev
Faster, please
Very little time left
Yes sir
Babu-ji said leave the village.
Everyone said, leave Paro
Paro said, leave drinking.
Now you say, leave this house
One day, He will say,
leave this world
Here's Manikpur.
Brought you in before sun-up
Whom are you seeing in Manikpur?
Paro...
Who...?
I'm here, Paro
- What is the matter, Parvati?
- Someone called out to me
So late at night? Go to bed.
You must be mistaken
Picked him up at Pandua station.
I don't know...
something happened to him overnight.
Never said where to, in Manikpur
What's that crowd outside?
Some stranger has been lying there
all night. Counting his last, maybe
Poor soul, must've come to return
something he owed in this lifetime
God rest his soul
No chance of survival,
Mahendra Babu
He's breathing his last
- Paro...
- She is manifest in Death
She is the life-force
Paro!
What is the matter, Parvati?
These letters might provide a clue
She is Eternal peace
If you are inattentive Parvati,
you needn't say the prayers. Leave
For some wish unfulfilled, must be,
he isn't giving up his ghost
The policeman has identified him.
He's from some Tal Sonapur
Tal Sonapur...
- What's the name?
- I don't know
- Mahendra Babu knows.
- Will you please call Mahendra?
- I said, call Mahendra.
- Yes
Mahendra Babu!!!
- Yes?
- Chhoti-Ma wants to see you. Now
- Yes Chhoti-Ma? You summoned me?
- Yes, who's the man lying outside?
Someone from your village,
one Devdas Mukherjee
- Who?
- Devdas Mukherjee
- How do you know?
- Two letters in his pocket
- One, to Dwijdas Mukherjee.
- His elder brother
- And to one Kaushalya.
- Yes, his mother
- The name was tattooed on his arm.
- At a fair. It rained
- Incomplete tattoo...
- Also a torn necklace of pearls
Hit me here...
Where are you going Chhoti-Ma?
By now
they must've taken him away
Chhoti-Ma, stop...
- What happened to Chhoti Ma?
- What's going on in this house?
Why this screaming?
What's up Mahendra?
- Ma is going out! For some Devdas!
- She has gone insane, stop her
Stop, Parvati!
Don't let her step
outside the manor
Stop Chhoti-Ma
Stop! Babu-ji forbids you
Secure the doors