The path of life...
...are dreams,
like the length of the path
The storm on the way...
...pass by as you go along
In the world...
...how many ways can one dream?
Looking for dream-like love...
...and the path goes on
Life is what...
...dreams and desires are made of
Somewhere in the dream...
...there are traces of tears
Where to go to?
To find where my heart wants to go
The wind seems to sign in the dream,
and the path and I go on
It suddenly rains and suddenly shines
Please have a pity on us travellers!
Stop!
Run!
Have mercy, sir!
Take it back!
How dare you steal my money?
Damn you!
- Stop!
Is it wanted convict?
Go away!
Stop! Stop!
Is it him?
Doesn't look like him! Go.
Thank you!
Don't go!
If you are not wanted, stay away!
Stay away, go!
Stop!
Not him!
Tell him to leave!
Stop!
Who's screaming?
Over there!
Stop!
There's a wanted convict!
Who told you to stop?
Pilgrimage? How hilarious!
You have all my money!
Don't advantage from me!
Don't say that, I don't need it!
You may need it sooner or later!
Thank you!
Want a room, Sir?
Get the luggage for him.
There's a nice room.
Sorry,
but I'm a collector from Tsi Pao Chu.
Collector?
Without rules!
Why is it a different man each time?
The ex-collector was killed
on his way home.
Why don't you just do me a favour.
Since you might get killed with the money?
Stop collecting.
You must be joking.
Can I see the counterfoll?
It's the new rule.
New rule? Show me!
Sorry, no!
What kind of a record is that?
It's in such a mess.
I can't return without the collection.
Sorry to bother you.
I owe you nothing.
Your book shows it.
Don't deny it
or I'll take you to court.
Inn keeper, where can I
spend a night without paying
Go to the Lan Ro Temple!
Old lady, I didn't lie to you.
Where's Lan Ro Temple, please?
Lan Ro Temple?!
3 1/2 miles to the East.
Where there is a spocky temple!
Thank you!
Sorry! Excuse me!
Old lady, are you going
to buy it or not?
Well done!
Master, you've good taste,
make an offer!
I don't even have money
for travel expenses.
Good taste, but no means,
what's the use?
What are you doing?
I'm taking your measurement
for your coffin!
Thank you!
Remember,
there are wolves in the woods.
You may come upon them when it's dark.
Stop...
The fire cannot go out.
If it does,
I can't get out of the forest.
Lan Ro Temple.
Anybody in?
Have you finished?
Hsia-hou, we're fought
for 7 years and you're always lost
But you're quite persevering
You follow me wherever I go.
You've been in the Temple for a fornight
and you've improved your swordsmanship!
But you've wasted your youth too.
You're ambitious, but not aggressive.
For the sake of the title,
you've become biased
You're petulant but not concentrated enough.
Your blows are violent but ineffective.
You've to cool down
if not you can win lust.
I'm here to duel with you,
not to listen to your sermon
Yes, he's right!
He's not your match.
You shouldn't have
said that to disgrace him.
He's right too.
You shouldn't have followed him.
Lay down your swords
and touch him with love.
The universe is limitless
and love is eternal.
Love conquers the world.
Love is the most powerful weapon!
Because you said too much!
I'm not trying to follow you
Your clothing is torn.
Hell with your love!
The kind of love you need,
you should find in a whorehouse.
I'm trying to find a place.
It's not convenient!
Why not?
Are you bold or not?
Yes!
Look over there!
I just shout, you then hide up.
If there's a real tiger,
where should you hide?
What?
It really has a tiger?
No!
But we've something even
more scareful than a tiger.
Do you always keep so close while talking?
I've had breath
and this will keep you away.
Get out of here!
Your love can't save you.
Yes!
Me too!
Hsia-hou, you're ambitious but,
after death, you're still a nobody.
I won't expose your body
in the wilderness.
You never change,
you fight even when dead.
Pao-Yeh-Pao-Lo-Mi!
It's lucky that water isn't deep.
Otherwise I'll get wet.
That monster's out again!
Shit! Is he still be there?
I meant no harm.
I'll throw it away if you're afraid!
What's it?
Where's my veil?
Veil? I'll find up for you!
It's deep!
Come up quick!
Come up!
Thank you!
It's too dark, I can't see.
I'll find it up early tomorrow.
This water is both deep and cold!
Your hands are colder than mine.
Because you're warmer.
You're sick, you look so pale.
Go to see doctor.
I need your warmth.
I'm not willing to push you.
If not, I'll spit on you.
It hurts.
I shouldn't have pushed you.
It's cold.
I'm wet,
you'll feel colder lying on me.
Do you feel painful or cold?
Hold me and take me inside.
Holding you?
I can't, you're too heavy!
I need some help...
You look nice,
but you're in the wrong place.
Otherwise,
you wouldn't have died for nothing.
Why am I still in water?
Miss, you forgot your lute!
Why are you following me?
Why are you leaving?
A villain!
I must run for my life!
Who?
I can't see it!
Stepping you to death.
Let's go.
Snake!
Where's the snake?
Don't shout!
The villain just passes by.
Which one?
The bearded one
on the East of Lan Ro Temple.
If he discovered us, we'd be killed!
The one living opposite me?
I could tell that he no good
You're too dangerous!
On your own I'll take you back.
No, my family won't permit this.
They're very strict.
Miss,
let me lure him away then!
Run when he tries to get hold of me!
Don't let him see you.
Here's your lute, Miss!
What's your name?
Ning Tsai-shen!
What's yours?
Nieh Hsiao Tsing!
Tomorrow night...
Tomorrow night I'll come to see you.
Stop running!
It's dangerous.
Stop!
You can't get away!
If you think you can scream,
I can scream too!
Damn Taoist,
both of us want shelter here.
Actually,
all the men I killed deserve it.
Why have you been annoying me?
I'm not.
I'm hiding in this hellish place
to stay away from hatred
the fighting in the world.
We've the common objective
to annihilate criminals
for the good of mankind.
We're in fact are fellowmen.
Fellowmen? Nonsense!
You're hurting me too.
One day, you'll be in big trouble,
then I'll finish you off.
You're a good man.
Don't come to me anymore.
Hsiao Tsing!
The big beard
Man of love,
Did you come upon anything last night?
I've touched everything in the house.
Did you see anything eerie?
Including you?
Idiot!
I'm serious. Why are you joking?
Who knows, if you're
serious or not?
You're always joking?
Get out of this place.
It's haunted.
Show me the ghost if you can.
Stupid fool.
Do you think you can see a ghost that easy?
Then they must not be a ghost.
They won't show up in the day.
Big beard, don't scare me.
Tell them to come at night,
if not in the day.
Don't regret it.
Why don't you believe me?
If I see you at night,
I'll throw you out.
Come on, do that!
No, I'll kill you.
There's no better way to help him.
Hope that can save his life.
Ghost? He must be kidding.
Where's my lower portion?
Damn big beard!
Where have you put it?
Your lower portion?
Isn't it connected to your upper portion?
Don't talk nonsense!
Take it!
He's incoherent.
No point in helping him.
It's illegible anyway,
I'll fill it in myself.
Have you really lived in Lan Ro Temple?
It clearly shows 70 taels.
Pay up.
Take it.
Thank you.
Inn keeper!
You scared me.
What do you want?
I was scared too.
Excuse me, excuse me...
Hsiao Tsing!
Can you hear me?
Stop.
Did you hear me, stop!
Don't go!
Who said that? Who did?
Let me see who's a wanted convict.
Don't you listen I said stop?
That man of taste is here again.
Boss!
Why are you here again?
Boss, where's that painting
"The girl washing hair"?
I'll get it for you at once.
Boss, what are you doing?
Why's it missing?
No one has ever asked for it.
Well, come again tomorrow.
I promise I'll find it for you.
Well, I'll come again tomorrow.
How could all 3 lanterns be blown out?
When the wolf comes,
see how I'd cope with you.
Can't you see the Yellow River's water,
keeps flowing into the sea
without returning?
Can't you see the mourning of those,
with grey hair before the mirror?
Don't face the moonlight without a drink.
Can't you see the Yellow River's water,
keeps flowing into the sea
without returning?
Can't you see the mourning of those,
with grey hair before the mirror?
Don't face the moonlight without a drink.
Give and spend and God will send.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7
7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1
Understand the bible,
and you have the sword for ten years
Then you've the credits.
I scare to leak out
If you stay, then I'll go.
I can hardly breath.
Why is there no wolf?
The wolf'ss coming!
Nieh Hsiao Tsing...
Hsiao Tsing...
Open the door, Hsiao Tsing!
Why are you here?
I came because I heard the lute sounds.
Come in quick!
You can't come here.
I'm leaving tomorrow,
I must say goodbye!
Tomorrow?
Yes, but I'll try to come to see you.
Don't!
Someone's coming!
She has a sharp nose.
Hide under the water,
and she can't smell you.
In the water again?
Sister Tsing!
I know the matron's waiting impatiently.
I'll go out after I've made up.
Tramp!
You're hiding a man!
I am not!
Don't deny it!
Here's the proof!
See for yourself.
Why have you written such stuff?
You obviously do that
in defiance of my order.
I must punish you.
You bitch!
Don't forget the ordeal you suffered!
Do as I tell you
or I'll destroy your ashes,
and you'll evaporate like thin air.
Tonight...
get me a living being...
to increase my vitality,
and lengthen my span of life
You'll be forgiven
for this first offence.
Bring medicine for your sister.
Yes.
You've been betrothed the Lord Black.
In three days you'll be his wife!
He's a bit old.
But he's not good-natured.
When he flares up,
even we can't control him.
After you marry him,
you'll never return.
Hsiao Tsing!
Yes!
Try it on.
Your bridal dress.
Come here and have a look.
Seems there's some sort of smell.
The smell of a living man.
My dress is torn.
Why are you so careless?
I must wash my hand!
Ching, let me help you.
Thank you!
Don't mention it.
Why are you doing that?
Sorry.
Don't keep offending her.
I didn't mean to.
You haven't cleaned up yet.
You did it on purpose, I give up.
Take it off so I can mend it
Tsing, what are you doing?
I must take a bath before going out!
If not I can't get you a living.
Good girl.
Ching, learn from her.
I won't let you down tonight
Come!
Hurry up!
3 days later after I get married,
this room will be yours.
Dress up! I won't look at you!
Come!
You...
Go!
I've a lot to tell you!
Go to the temple first!
I'll wait you there!
Yes!