(NEYTIRI WHOOPING)
Okay. This is video log 12.
Time's 2132.
(SIGHING)
Do I have to do this now?
I really need to
get some rack.
No, now.
When it's fresh.
Okay, location, shack,
and the days are starting
to blur together.
(SPEAKING NA'VI SLOWLY)
(REPEATING TENTATIVELY)
JAKE: The language is a pain,
but, you know,
I figure it's like
field-stripping a weapon.
Just repetition, repetition.
Navi.
"Nari."
Nari.
(IMPATIENTLY)
"Narrri"!
Narrri!
Txur nì'ul.
Stronger.
(INHALES)
JAKE: Neytiri calls me skxawng.
It means moron.
This is a very important
part of it.
Norm's attitude
has improved lately.
I see you. I see you.
But it's not just,
"I'm seeing you in front of me,"
it's "I see into you.
I See you."
It's good he's back on board,
but he thinks
I'm a skxawng, too.
"I'm accepting you.
I understand you."
So you gotta
get this, okay?
I gotta run! Okay?
Let's go.
My feet are getting tougher.
I can run farther every day.
I have to trust my body
to know what to do.
Yeah! Check it out!
Oh, crap!
Every day it's reading the trails,
the tracks at the waterhole,
the tiniest scents and sounds.
(CUBS SQUEAKING)
She's always going on about the
flow of energy, the spirits of animals.
I really hope this tree-hugger
crap isn't on the final.
This isn't just about eye-hand
coordination out there, you know.
You need to listen
to what she says.
Try to see the forest
through her eyes.
Excuse me.
This is my video log here.
With Neytiri,
it's learn fast or die.
You gotta be kidding me.
(SCREAMING)
(BRANCHES CRACKING)
(GRUNTING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(PANTING)
(GROANING)
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
I talked Mo'at into letting
Grace into the village.
It's the first time since
her school was closed down.
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
Whoa... No, you don't.
Come back here.
Bon appétit.
(CHIRPING)
(POWERING OFF)
(GENTLY)
Come on, Marine.
JAKE: I'm trying to understand
this deep connection
the people have
to the forest.
She talks about
a network of energy
that flows through
all living things.
She says all energy
is only borrowed,
and one day you have
to give it back.
(GROWLS)
(MOANING)
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(STABS)
A clean kill.
You are ready.
JAKE: Learning to ride an ikran,
we call them banshees,
is the test every
young hunter has to pass.
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
But to do that, you gotta go
where the banshees are.
Oo-rah.
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
Now what?
(COMMANDS IN NA'VI)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(NEYTIRI WHOOPING)
(SCREECHING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(NEYTIRI SPEAKING NA'VI)
(SPEAKING SOFTLY IN NA'VI)
(PANTING)
Jakesully will go first.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(SCREECHING)
Now you choose your ikran.
This you must feel inside.
If he also chooses you,
move quick like I showed.
You will have one chance, Jake.
How will I know
if he chooses me?
He will try to kill you.
Outstanding.
(EXCLAIMS)
(HISSING)
(GRUNTS)
(EXCLAIMING)
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(ROARING)
(SPEAKS NA'VI)
(HISSING)
Let's dance.
(LAUGHING)
(SCREECHING)
(WHOOPING)
(GRUNTING)
Make the bond!
No!
(EXCLAIMS)
Jake!
(LAUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
(IKRAN SCREECHING)
(SHOUTING)
Tsaheylu, Jake.
NEYTIRI:
Tsaheylu!
(YELLING)
Stop!
(SPEAKING SOFTLY IN NA'VI)
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, that's right.
You're mine. Huh?
First flight seals the bond.
You cannot wait.
Think, "Fly!"
Fly?
(EXCLAIMING)
(SCREAMING)
God damn!
Oh, shit!
(YELLING)
(SCREECHING)
Shut up and
fly straight!
(JAKE PANTING)
That's it.
Bank left!
Level out!
That's it.
(HUNTERS WHOOPING)
WARRIOR:
Whoo! Jakesully!
(WHOOPING)
(SPEAKS SHARPLY
IN NA'VI)
(CHUCKLING)
(NEYTIRI HOOTING)
Hey!
Let's go!
Yeah, baby, I got this!
Oh, shit!
(WHOOPING)
JAKE: I may not be
much of a horse guy,
but I was born to do this.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah!
I came like this.
This you. Yeah, yeah.
I turn. I feel the wind.
I turn very strong.
Look, yeah, see,
I banked so hard...
(GASPS)
(SPEAKS NA'VI)
(LAUGHING)
(JAKE WHOOPING)
GRACE:
The Tree of Souls.
(TRANSLATING INTO NA'VI)
It's their most sacred place.
See the Flux Vortex
in these false color images?
Yeah, that's what messes up
my instruments.
There is something really interesting
going on in there biologically.
I would die to get samples.
Outsiders are strictly forbidden.
GRACE:
You lucky swine.
JAKE: I was a stone-cold aerial hunter.
Death from above.
Only problem is,
you're not the only one.
(JAKE AND NEYTIRI
EXCHANGING YELPS)
Dive!
(ROARING)
(SCREECHING)
Go, go!
(NEYTIRI IMITATING BIRD CRIES)
Follow me!
(ROARING)
(SOFTLY)
Whew.
(ROARING)
(BOTH HOOTING)
(SPEAKING SOOTHINGLY IN NA'VI)
(SHUSHING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Our guys call it
a Great Leonopteryx.
It is Toruk.
Last Shadow.
Yeah, right.
It's the last one you ever see.
My grandfather's grandfather
was Toruk Macto.
Rider of Last Shadow.
He rode this?
Toruk chose him.
It has only happened 5 times
since the time of the First Songs.
That's a long time.
Yes.
Toruk Macto was mighty.
He brought the clans together
in a time of great sorrow.
All Na'vi people know the story.
(INHALING DEEPLY)
JAKE:
Everything is backwards now.
Like out there is the true world
and in here is the dream.
(SIGHS)
It's hard to believe
it's only been 3 months.
I can barely remember
my old life.
I don't know who I am anymore.
(SNIFFLES)
Haven't gotten lost in the woods,
have you?
Your last report was
more than 2 weeks ago.
I'm starting to doubt
your resolve!
The way I see it,
it's time to terminate the mission.
No, I can do this.
You already have.
You give me good, usable intel.
This Tree of Souls place.
Yeah, I got them
by the balls with that
when this turns
into a shit fight,
which it will. Yeah.
Now it's time
to come in.
By the way,
you gonna get
your legs back.
Yeah. I got your corporate approval.
It's a done deal.
Gonna have you
on a shuttle tonight.
I'm a man of my word.
I gotta finish this.
There's one more thing.
Ceremony. It's the final stage
of becoming a man.
If I do it, I'm one of them.
And they'll trust me.
And I can negotiate
the terms of their relocation.
Well, then, you'd better
get it done, Corporal.
JAKE: The Na'vi say that
every person is born twice.
The second time is when you earn
your place among The People forever.
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(SNIFFLING SOFTLY)
(LAUGHING)
Come. Come.
(LAUGHS)
This is a place for prayers
to be heard.
And sometimes answered.
(SIGHS)
We call these trees
Utraya Mokri.
The Tree of Voices.
The voices of
our ancestors.
(VOICES WHISPERING)
(VOICES CHATTERING DISTANTLY)
I can hear them.
They live, Jake,
within Eywa.
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
You are Omaticaya now.
You may make your bow
from the wood of Hometree.
And you may
choose a woman.
We have many
fine women.
Ninat is the best singer.
But I don't want Ninat.
(BLOWING)
Peyral is a good hunter.
Yeah, she is a good hunter.
(EXHALES)
(SOFTLY)
I've already chosen.
But this woman must
also choose me.
She already has.
(GASPS)
I am with you now, Jake.
We are mated for life.
JAKE: What the hell
are you doing, Jake?
(MACHINERY RUMBLING)
(BRANCH CRACKING)
(MACHINERY APPROACHING)
(GASPING)
(ENGINES RUMBLING)
Ma Jake!
NORM:
Don't forget your phase integration.
GRACE:
Jake! No, no, the middle button.
You gotta eat something.
Yeah, there you go.
Jake! Jake. Wake up!
Jake, please!
Don't make me
force-feed a cripple.
(CHUCKLES)
Grace, I don't want... Hey!
(POWERING DOWN)
(GRUNTS IN ALARM)
Jake!
(CHUCKLING)
Okay.
(GRUNTING)
Here. I'm done.
Let's go.
And when was the last time
you took a shower?
I don't need a shower.
Jesus, Marine.
(GRUNTING)
Jake!
Jake! Wake up!
Hey!
Stop! Stop!
NEYTIRI:
Jake!
Go back, stop!
Hey, boss.
Hey!
(BULLDOZER POWERING DOWN)
What?
I got a native
doing the funky chicken here.
He's blocking my blade.
Well, keep going.
He'll move.
SELFRIDGE: These people have to learn
that we don't stop. Come on, go, go, go.
Stop! Hey!
Go! Go!
There, see?
He moved.
(GRUNTING)
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Dude, dude. Whoa, dude!
Dude, no!
Oh! I'm blind.
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
Jake!
Neytiri!
Here, come on!
(NEYTIRI SOBBING)
(INHALING)
QUARITCH:
Freeze it right there.
Scale up.
Enhance.
SELFRIDGE:
Son of a bitch.
Unbelievable.
Get me a pilot.
Yes, sir.
(HUNTERS HOOTING WAR CRIES)
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(ALL SHOUTING WAR CRIES)
You do not speak here!
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(ALL SHOUTING WAR CRIES)
JAKE:
Tsu'tey! Don't do this.
You! Listen. Brother...
(SHOUTS IN NA'VI)
(SHOUTING IN NA'VI)
You mated with this woman?
Oh, shit.
(STERNLY)
Is this true?
We are mated before Eywa.
It is done.
(BREATHING TREMULOUSLY)
JAKE:
Brother, please.
Do not attack
the Sky People.
Many Omaticaya
will die if you do.
You are not my brother!
(YELLING)
And I am not
your enemy!
The enemy is out there,
and they are very powerful!
Go! Go! Go!
I can talk to them.
No more talk.
NEYTIRI:
Tsu'tey!
I am Omaticaya.
I am one of you.
And I have the right to speak.
(SIGHS)
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(IN ENGLISH) The words
are like stones in my heart.
NORM:
Sir, I'm sorry. No! Hold on!
You can't interrupt
a link in progress!
It's very dangerous!
NEYTIRI:
Grace!
Oh, no.
Wait!
Stay down, sir.
(BEEPING)
Okay. Look...
I was sent here to...
(CROWD MURMURING)
(GRUNTS)
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(NEYTIRI YELLING)
(GROWLING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(GASPS)
Are you out of
your goddamn mind?
You crossed the line.
Wheel this meat
out of here.
GRACE: Jake!
What the hell is going on here?
QUARITCH:
You let me down, son.
So, what,
you find yourself
some local tail
and you just completely forget
what team you're playing for?
Parker, there is time
to salvage the situation.
Parker...
Shut your pie hole!
Or what, Ranger Rick?
You gonna shoot me?
I could do that.
You need to muzzle your dog.
Yeah, can we just take this down
a couple of notches, please?
You say you want to
keep your people alive?
You start by
listening to her.
Those trees were sacred to
the Omaticaya
in a way you can't imagine.
You know what?
You throw a stick
in the air around here,
it's gonna land
on some sacred fern,
(MOCKINGLY)
for Christ's sake! I'm not talking
about some kind of pagan
voodoo here.
I'm talking about
something real,
something measurable
in the biology of the forest.
Which is what, exactly?
What we think we know
is that there is some kind of
electrochemical communication
between the roots
of the trees,
like the synapses
between neurons.
And each tree has 10-to-the-4th
connections to the trees around it.
And there are 10-to-the-12th
trees on Pandora.
Which is a lot,
I'm guessing.
It's more connections
than the human brain.
Get it?
It's a network.
It's a global network,
and the Na'vi can access it.
They can upload and download data.
Memories.
At sites like the one
you just destroyed.
(IN AWE)
Yes!
(LAUGHING) What the hell have you
people been smoking out there?
They're just goddamn trees!
(LAUGHING)
You need to wake up,
Parker.
No. You need to wake up.
The wealth of this world isn't
in the ground. It's all around us.
The Na'vi know that,
and they are fighting to defend it.
If you want to share
this world with them,
you need to
understand them.
I'd say we understand them just fine,
thanks to Jake here.
Hey, Doc, come take a look.
They're not gonna
give up their home.
make a deal.
(SCOFFING)
For what? Lite beer?
And blue jeans?
There's nothing that we have
that they want.
Everything they sent me out here
to do is a waste of time.
They're never gonna
leave Hometree.
So, since a deal
can't be made,
I guess things
get real simple.
Jake, thanks.
I'm getting all emotional.
I might just give you
a big wet kiss.
(SIGHS)
I'll do it with minimal casualties
to the indigenous.
I'll drive them out with gas first.
(SIGHS)
It'll be humane.
More or less.
All right, let's pull the trigger.
MAX: Come on, people.
(SIGHING) Oh, man.
MAX:
Let's pack it up, let's go.
This is how it's done.
When people are sitting
on shit that you want,
you make them your enemy.
JAKE:
Then you're justified in taking it.
Quaritch is rolling the gunships.
He's gonna hit Hometree.
My God.
Dr. Augustine!
You cannot be up here!
Back off!
Parker. Wait. Stop.
These are people you're about to...
No. No, no, no, no.
I said back off!
They're fly-bitten savages
that live in a tree!
All right?
Look around!
I don't know about you, but I see
a lot of trees! They can move!
Can you guys just please...
Yes, sir.
There are families in there.
There are children. Babies.
Are you gonna
kill children?
You don't want that kind of blood
on your hands. Believe me.
Just let me try
to talk them out.
They trust me.
Calibrate fast.
We're going in, right now.
FEMALE TECHNICIAN:
Calibrating 3 and 4.
GRACE:
Run sequence.
MAX:
Initiating. 30 seconds.
(POWERING UP)
Listen to me.
You've got one hour.
Unless you want your girlfriend in there
when the ax comes down,
you get them to evacuate.
One hour.
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
Look, tell them they're gonna
be here soon.
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(IN ENGLISH)
You have to leave, or you're gonna die.
Are you
certain of this?
Look, they sent me here
to learn your ways
so one day I could bring this message
and that you would believe it.
What are you saying, Jake?
You knew this would happen?
Yes.
Look, at first
it was just orders,
and then
everything changed.
Okay? I fell in love.
I fell in love with the forest and
with the Omaticaya people.
And with you.
I trusted you.
With you. With you.
I trusted you!
Trust me now, please.
(SHOUTING IN NA'VI)
You will never be
one of The People!
I shouldn't have...
We tried to stop them!
Neytiri, please!
Please.
(MO'AT SPEAKING NA'VI)
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(GRACE SPEAKING NA'VI)
You have to go.
They're coming!
(SHOUTING WAR CRY)
(ALL SHOUTING WAR CRY)
DRAGON PILOT:
Time on target, 1 mike.
SCORPION PILOT:
Copy. We have a visual.
Roger that.
Stay on heading 030.
SCORPION PILOT:
Roger, 030.
(BOTH SHOUTING IN NA'VI)
Run to the forest!
They're coming!
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
They will destroy this place.
Neytiri, you must go now!
(YIPPING)
Run to the forest!
Run!
(SHOUTING IN NA'VI)
Run! Run!
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
No! God damn it, run!
(SPEAKS NA'VI)
That is one
big damn tree.
Well, well, well.
I'd say diplomacy has failed.
All right, people,
let's get this done!
I want every gas round
you got right in the front door.
Roger.
CS .40's going hot.
Fire.
Firing.
(ALL SCREAMING)
(ALL COUGHING)
Bingo.
Mighty good shooting, ace.
(SCREAMING IN NA'VI)
Sir, they've
opened fire.
(ARROWS CLATTERING)
You've got to
be kidding me!
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(ALL COUGHING)
These dumb bastards
ain't getting the message.
All right,
let's turn up the heat.
Switch incendiaries!
Switching incendiaries.
Fire.
No!
(SHOUTING IN NA'VI)
(SPEAKS NA'VI)
And that's how
you scatter the roaches.
(EYTUKAN SHOUTING IN NA'VI)
JAKE:
Neytiri!
We gotta move!
He's gonna blow the columns!
My God!
(COMMANDING IN NA'VI)
(PROTESTING)
(SHOUTING IN NA'VI)
Mo'at! No!
If you are one of us,
help us.
All call signs, switch missiles.
Give me HE's at the base
of the west columns.
This way!
OFFICER ON RADIO:
Rider section, switch missiles.
PILOT 1: One's good.
PILOT 2: 2's rocks up.
PILOT 3:
3's up.
Yeah, baby, get some!
Charlie Oscar,
Gunrunner standing by.
Bring it down. Cleared hot.
(ALL GRUNTING)
Come on, Grace, move!
Down! Head down!
Come on, come on! Down!
(GROANING)
PILOT 1: Solid hits.
PILOT 2: Solid rocks on target.
Screw this.
Hey! What the hell
are you doing?
I didn't sign up
for this shit!
OFFICER:
Repeat. Ripple fire.
(WOOD CREAKING)
Go! Go! Go!
(VILLAGERS SCREAMING)
(YIPPING)
(SHOUTING IN NA'VI)
(SCREECHING)
No, no, get back!
Back!
(YELLS)
(EXCLAIMING IN PANIC)
(ALL SCREAMING)
Come on!
Come on, move! Move!
(VILLAGERS SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING IN HORROR)
That's good work, people.
First round's on me tonight.
Let's boogie.
PILOT:
Dragon coming left, heading home.
OFFICER:
Gunrunner coming left.
Thunder copies.
Rider section copies.
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(MOANING)
(WAILING IN NA'VI)
(GROANING WEAKLY)
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(SOBBING)
Neytiri!
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(WAILING IN GRIEF)
I'm sorry.
(SOBBING)
Get away.
(SHRIEKING)
Get away!
Get away from here!
Never come back!
(WAILING)
Pull the plug.
No, you can't do that!
WOMAN:
You can't do that!
Calm down! Calm down!
No! Please!
(GIRL SHOUTING IN NA'VI)
JAKE: I was a warrior who dreamed
he could bring peace.
(ALL ARGUING)
Sooner or later, though,
you always have to wake up.
(DISTANTLY)
Let's go!
Put him down!
You murderer!
(VILLAGERS SOBBING)
What's going on, brother?
Long time no see.
SECURITY MAN:
Hey.
Personally, I don't feel these
tree-hugging traitors deserve steak.
They get steak?
That's bullshit. Let me see that.
(CHUCKLING)
Yeah. You know what that is. Down.
Trudy!
All the way down.
(GROANS)
Max!
Trudy, fire up the ship! Go!
Here.
Clear. Come on.
Here you go.
Max, stay here. I need someone
on the inside I can trust.
Okay. Go.
NORM: (SOFTLY)
Clear.
(ENGINE POWERING UP)
Come on, baby.
Colonel? Sir?
I got a situation here.
It's Samson 1-6.
Unauthorized engine start.
NORM: (GRUNTING)
3!
Come on!
Mask on!
Gas, gas, gas!
I'm taking fire!
Let's go!
Grab my hand!
Come on, we're in. Let's go!
Come on, let's go!
Let's go, go!
Colonel!
(AIR HISSING)
Yeah! Yeah!
NORM:
All right! Yes!
(LAUGHS)
(WHOOPING)
Crap.
TRUDY:
Everybody all right back there?
JAKE:
Oh, yeah, baby!
Norm, you good?
NORM:
Yeah!
(GROANING)
This is gonna ruin my whole day.
Grace is hit!
What?
Get the trauma kit.
Trauma kit!
Keep the pressure on,
Grace.
Trauma kit's forward,
on the bulkhead.
Hang on, Grace.
Doesn't matter.
It's fine.
(STIFLES GROAN)
JAKE ON RADIO:
You're good to go.
Take it up!
TRUDY ON RADIO:
Hold on. I'm pulling pitch.
You're clear!
Just keep going north.
Get us deep in the mountains.
TRUDY:
Copy that.
Norm, you all good up there?
Yep! Still here.
Well, at least they can't track us up here.
Not this far into the Vortex.
It's strongest at the
Tree of Souls, right?
Yeah.
Good. 'Cause that's
where we're going.
Ouch.
You big baby.
We're moving.
I'm gonna get you
some help, Grace.
I'm a scientist, remember?
I don't believe in fairy tales.
The People can help you.
I know it.
Why would they help us?
JAKE:
The People say Eywa will provide.
With no home, no hope,
there was only
one place they could go.
(SOBBING)