- Who did you say was getting married?
- Isn't it the eldest son?
No... I think it's the younger daughter
- Long time no see
- How are you?
Did you check out the groom?
- He's pretty cute
- I'm so jealous
Hey, what's up?
Yeah
Hold on a sec
Why are you so late?
Hey, the bouquet!
You're not supposed to do that
Come here you little brat
You folks are here
- Ain't this little Wonny boy?
- You should say hello to him Won
You've grown so much
How old are you?
Five?
It's great that you're doing so much
for the wedding. It must be a handful for you
- Don't mention it... mother's over there
- Okay
- Congratulations
- It's such a pleasure to see you all
- You must be thrilled. Congratulations
- Thanks
When I received the invitation
I thought it was the elder one
What can I say... they surprised me too
You're a bit
disappointed though, aren't you?
Well, the second one's already married
Besides, I don't think
people care these days
But still, it's not the same
We'll see you later
Good to see you
So, when will we hear
the big news from you Professor?
- I'll see you later
- Sure. Take care
You holding up okay there?
It's not like I'm getting married
You remember
Kyu-jin's brother, don't you?
Sure
Don't forget, 3 o'clock sharp
And, don't fuck it up
Pleasure seeing you Mrs. Kim
Nice seeing you too, Kyu-jin
You must be very excited
Actually, I'm stressed
out about Joon-young
Why don't you set
him up with a nice girl?
Actually, I'm setting him up
on a blind date today as we speak
- Really?
- Yes
Who might this be?
She's my girlfriend's close friend
and she's very nice
That's great
You should convince him to stay with her
He listens to you
- I wouldn't worry too much
- Okay
Where's your brother?
- What?
- Really?
- He was here before
- Oh yeah?
Should I go find him?
He probably left already
He missed the picture for my
wedding too. Don't worry about it
Here we go people
All the way over there...
The gentleman with glasses...
will you push in a little?
Please look over here everyone
Looking good One, two
Marriage is a crazy thing
3 o'clock in front of KFC on College St
with a rolled up newspaper
That was supposed to be the sign
for meeting a woman named Yeon-hee
Enjoy your meal
May I help you?
Are there other KFCs around here?
No
What's wrong?
Someone asked the same
exact question a little while ago
Not bad at all
Let's hope that the girl's
that much hot a least
Excuse me
Can I borrow a light?
Aren't you Kyu-jin's friend?
Are you Yeon-hee Kang?
I'm sorry I'm late
I was just about to leave actually
I'm so sorry. I was taking a nap
Coffee's on me since I almost stood you up
Let's go
Blind Date
Were you really gonna leave?
I thought I was stood up
Strangely enough there was
another guy next to me
with a rolled up newspaper
Really?
I just stood there for a while
but then felt a bit uncomfortable
so I wanted to leave
So, do you know Kyu-jin from college?
We've been friends since Junior High
I heard a lot about you from Yu-ri
Honestly heard some really nice things
What did she say?
She said that you were attractive and nice
Guess she was right and wrong
No...
you're much more attractive
than I originally expected actually
I know...
I was talking about the latter
May I ask what you do for a living?
What?
Yu-ri didn't tell me much about you
You know the drill...
age, occupation, schools
I don't think they're that important
Well, sometimes people like to get
minor things out of their way
If they were really important
wouldn't you wanna save it for last?
That's very true
I teach part time at a university
What do you teach?
English Literature
So, how do you make a living?
Well... I'm early in my career
so I'm barely getting by for now
How about siblings?
I have a brother and
a sister and I'm the eldest
Right
If you get married...
My chances of making this
beautiful woman mine was very slim
She made it seem like this was
only one of the many blind dates she's been on
But then
I was no stranger to blind dates either
What can you cook best?
Bean Sprout Bibimbap
Bean Sprout Bibimbap?
That's all you got?
Our dull and empty
conversation continued
And her smile reminded me of a kind
you only see in impersonal portraits
That's what made it so hard for me
to tell how she really felt about me
How did you like it?
It was whatever I guess I mean...
it had absolutely no plot
Yeah... but it was still entertaining I think
Guess that's the beauty
of a Hollywood feature
I'm kind of hungry
You wanna go get dinner?
The problem wasn't the movie
I was following
the typical blind date procedure
How about a drink?
Not a big drinker really
A glass of beer won't kill you
- Guess I'll just have one
- Thanks
Cheers
You can drink very well
I guess today's one of those days
The bus is taking too long
How's the tea?
Well... it sure goes well
with the Gayagum sound
I know
One more Pine Leaf Ale please
You sure you can handle that?
Thanks
Let me get that
To tell you the truth
I already saw that movie
I actually went on another
blind date the other day
Don't you find it funny that
I had to sit through
the same movie twice?
I mean, how sad is this?
I went on more than ten
blind dates this month alone
I don't know if marriage is
worth doing after all this trouble
Excuse me
Can we get another glass over here?
That was good, thanks
Yeah, I had fun myself
I bet the train stopped running
I think the bus stopped running too
What do we do now?
We should just hope
that we don't blank out
Where are you going?
I'm getting a cab
Okay
Can you get home alright?
Why? Are you gonna
take me home or something?
Why not
I think...
it'll be much cheaper
to check-in to a motel though
You know what, you're right
The cab fare will probably be more
Don't take it off
Put it in now
What?
Don't take it off and just put it in
One sec
Put it in
You're not even wet yet
I like it better that way
Pull out before you cum
The guy was ugly, wasn't he?
Who are you talking about?
The guy that was
next to you with the newspaper
Oh that guy...
Actually he was okay
Really? No way
- You know him?
- I met him last night on the internet
He insisted on meeting me
so I was gonna weigh out
you two and choose
Was he really good looking?
Sure
That really sucks, huh?
Probably should've met with him, right?
He called himself a stud
Supposedly an engineer
and even owns a store or something
He even seemed rather innocent
Said he was seriously on a mission...
to find his mate on the internet
So why were you so late?
I missed the bus
Should've caught that one
What kind of a loser looks
for his mate on the internet?
Stop
I could be on a date with that
hot KFC girl too if it weren't for you
KFC girl?
Yeah
- Was she pretty?
- Sure
She had her hair tied back with a hat on
She was much younger
and prettier than you actually
What if...
You ended up with that other guy...
and me with the KFC girl?
What do you think
would've happened then?
Are you sleeping?
Guess you'd be sleeping
in the next room with that girl
Anything better than that?
Then you'd be asking her
the same exact question
What do you think
would've happened to me
if I went on a blind date as planned?
The main character of this poem Prufrock
...is a cynical character with
a rather strong sense of self
Should I just suck it up and propose?
No... it's not worth doing
Yet, great poetry is made possible
by these personal and trivial daydreams
Professor
Here... have this
Thank you. Appreciate it
You know that video tape
you were talking about earlier?
What video tape?
You briefly talked about
that movie before the Elliad lecture
Oh... you mean Requiem?
Yeah, that's it
Is there any chance that
I can borrow that from you?
It's actually a video CD
and I still haven't seen it
And it doesn't even have a Korean subtitle
I still really want to watch it
Well... I guess you're no
leaving me with much of a choice here
Thank you
Should I just watch it with you
when you're watching it?
Well...
That's a promise
I don't think you even know my name
It's Sae-un Ryu
The Date
What are you smiling about?
Don't you find all rites of passage
like birth and marriage depressing?
You're the one that's depressing
No one's left but you now
Mind your own business. I'll be just fine
Anyway, congratulations Yu-ri
Fine my ass. Then why does
your mother always ask me...
if there are nice girls out there?
Relax
You're getting married late too
Oh yeah, how did it go?
What do you mean?
Yeon-hee
Right. How was it?
I set you up on a blind date
and no feedbacks?
- Hello?
- Joon-young?
It's me Yeon-hee
Oh... Yeon-hee
Oh... Yeon-hee? That's it?
Did you get home okay that night?
It's about time you ask me that
Why didn't you call me afterwards?
I was actually just about to
Guess I should've called later
I'm free tomorrow. Shall we meet up?
Sure
What do you want to do?
You wanna go for a bike ride?
Guess it's better than the whole
rolled-up newspaper scheme
Don't take it off, just do it
Why do you always have to
run to the bathroom after you cum?
I can't stand having cum on my body
You know, that's a huge turn-off
How come you never let me take it all off?
Because then, I can't get aroused
Why not?
When I look at someone
that's completely naked
it reminds me of chunk of meat
But then when the person has clothes on
I can really feel that person
You know, that unique
trait that gives you intimacy
From underwear?
Sure
That makes no sense
whatsoever I bet your ex-boyfriend
just had the same underwear as me
You never missed any bus that day
What?
You were there on time
You were hiding someplace so
that you can check out the both of us
Then you figured I was
cuter than the other guy
so you just waited till
the other guy left, right?
Whatever
If I were given the same choice
you had I would've gone for the KFC girl
Wait
How's this?
Don't I look young and cute also?
From behind you do
Well then, think of me
as that KFC girl from now, okay?
- Can't do it
- Why not?
Cause she actually seemed nice
Good one
Let's go
Where?
You're not gonna
stay here all day, are you?
Right on then
We'll be very formal
to each other from now
You'll take me to nice restaurants
...buy me roses and a teddy bear
when I go home, okay?
Why?
Because nice guys do all of that
Let's go to the mall first
Are you really going
to buy me all of that honey?
No, it's my nephew's birthday tomorrow
- Where are you going?
- What?
This is the home appliance corner
It is?
So let's take a look around real quick
Sure, ma'am
This is crystal
You can put this in an oven
or microwave, right?
We can put that on our dining table
Okay, enough
One sec
How about this honey?
They match
I'm good
C'mon... just for a minute
Don't you think we'll
look really good in these?
You have a great husband
I know
This is very popular
among the newly weds
You two look great in them
Really?
I guess we really do look
like newly weds, right?
I don't know about that but you can sure as
hell act. You should consider a career in acting
- It's just fun
- You think so?
Then we should do this
for the rest of our lives
For the rest of our lives?
Sure
Are you proposing?
No
Then?
We'll put on an act just like we did now
My mother would be so thrilled
No way
It's actually a lot easier than you'd think
What is?
You live separate
but for holidays you'll act
like a married couple
Holidays are what's tough
for singles, you know
That will never work
People will find out
No, you can be like a weekend couple
And then when parents come to visit
...complain about how your
husband never helps around the house
Then they'll never know
that it's all a show
What about friends?
That's actually quite simple as well
Just constantly complain about
the typical marriage problems like petty fights
Say things like
"My husband sits in his ass all day"
..."We always fight over who's
supposed to do laundry day and night"
- Sounds pretty easy
- It really is
What about sex?
- That should be real
- You are such a jerk
You're right though about
the whole marriage thing
I look at my friends that are married
and they all have the same problems
Every marriage is pretty much the same
It's like some sort of a franchise
Where are we going right now?
You have to get your nephew a present
Let's go
The skyline's so beautiful from up here
I know
Whenever I look at something like this
I immediately think of god
And how he must have this kind
of a bird's eye view of the world
Everything looks so beautiful
and peaceful from here
But then at this very moment
I'm sure God himself has
his mind on something else
Why?
Because there's a really
beautiful woman sitting in front of him
You didn't like that?
I liked it even if it was a lie
Just wish I could date people and
only have to hear nice things
like that for the rest of my life
You think my nephew
will really like what I got him?
I'm sure he will
Tell him to name all five of 'em
I'm getting setup with
another guy next week possibly
Did you just hear what I said?
Yeah
You think I should see him?
Do whatever you want
I knew you would say that
It's not like I can stop
you from seeing him
Guess you're right
But still
if you told me not to meet him
I would've at least acted
like I wasn't going to see him
Are you seriously thinking of marriage?
Of course. I'll get married
as soon as I find the right guy
Oh yeah? You? Marriage?
What? You don't think I can?
If you get married...
don't you think that
that's sort of a crime?
Whatever
I'm not talking about the virginity thing
If a woman like you get married
...do you think you can be
satisfied with just your husband?
You think that's possible?
Absolutely possible
I'll never ever get caught
One thing's for sure
You and I both always loved
someone ever since grade school
You think that's gonna change
that easily when you get married?
We don't stand a chance
You really think so?
Besides, you're not looking
for love on your blind dates anyway
What?
You're looking for certain conditions
Not the person, but who they
are and what they can offer you
What do you know anyway?
I wouldn't have gone
on that date regardless
I didn't measure up
to your high standards
so I was good for pleasure
Am I wrong?
I just wanted to know how
you would react, that's all
I never had any plans
for blind dates anyway
The Wedding
Hello?
It's me, Sae-un. Sae-un Ryu
Oh yeah
You remember the promise
from last time, right?
Sure
Do you have that CD on you?
Yeah, I brought it... where are you?
Just hold on one sec
I'm almost there
Hello, Professor
Hi
Are you enjoying the movie?
Frankly, it's sort of boring
but watching it with you is fun
What kind of after shave do you use?
I really like the smell
Oh yeah?
You can finish the rest and
return the CD to me later if you want
Okay, I will
Professor
Ever since I took your class
I wanted to kiss you
Why?
The way you taught was so cute
Oh yeah?
Thought you looked out
the window more than anything
Did I really?
Do you have someone you love?
Yes
Then you'll probably
get married soon, right?
Hello?
What are you doing?
Have a seat
How have you been?
Okay, yourself?
What are you doing here?
You're getting married tomorrow
It just sort of happened
I got things to say
to Ji-young and stuff
I need to go
Hey Ji-young! Ji-young!
It's not just about
Ji-young, you know
I just don't know about
this whole commitment thing
Are you afraid of
giving up your bachelor life?
If I could run away I would. Man
This really sucks
Asshole. You don't think
it's the same for Yu-ri?
I don't know man...
don't be surprised if
I don't show up tomorrow
Do you, Kyu-jin take Yu-ri as your
beloved wife for the rest of your life?
Yes
I was sort of counting on
Kyu-jin's marriage for some time
Because I thought it would be
a natural way of seeing Yeon-hee again
To be honest, I was regretting
what I had said to her earlier
I was positive that she would be
there since she was friends with the bride
But I couldn't find her
throughout the entire wedding ceremony
- Hey
- What?
- The flight's at seven o'clock, right?
- Yeah
If it's seven, they should
leave here at four at the latest
- Are you okay?
- What?
You're not the one
that's going on a honeymoon
Stop worrying and eat
Guess they're running late with
the after-ceremony. You want a drink?
I'm good
Please look at me
Oh, I'm sorry
Oh... thanks
Here are my friends
from Junior High
- Nice meeting you
- Nice meeting you too
You've seen Joon-young before
- This here is Eun-mi
- Hi, I heard a lot about you
- And this here is Ji-young
- How are you?
Where are you going
for your honeymoon?
To Bali. Make sure to come
over for our house forming party
Yu-ri, we're running tight on time
Hi
Hi, how are you?
Have fun
I'll call you
We shouId go drink more
We can't end it like this
So how long have
you all known each other?
Since Junior High
And you're not sick of them?
I don't really get to see them too often
so they're much better than my husband
You mean that?
Yeah
Uhhh...
I lost a turtle
I looked all over, but can't find it
Should I buy you another one?
I'm just saying that I lost one
One out of the five
If you lose all five, call me
I'll buy you all five of 'em again
Choice
How have you been?
Not too good
Just waited for the turtles to die
I'm serious
Whenever I had extra time
I would lean over
the tank and stare at them
Then my nephew
would walk by and ask
"What are you doing uncle Joon?"
And I would answer
"I'm waiting for the turtles to die"
So what's up?
Thought I would never
hear back from you
I was just around here for
a chore and remembered your number
That's all?
- Are you done?
- Yeah, one sec
I went on that blind date
Oh yeah? Who is this guy?
He's a doctor
All his siblings are doctors
Guess you found the one
But he's not
the most attractive person
How bad is he?
You wanna go do it?
No
How come?
I have to go date a doctor too
Doctor?
I think I'm gonna go
for a hot chick doctor
That hurt
My mother's ill
Is she gonna be okay?
What's this?
- It's a photo album
- Photo album?
Yeah, my history
Aren't you curious?
Oh yeah?
That's my mom
She's beautiful
They look really happy together
I know. Mom only knows dad
You were pretty
when you were little
Who took this?
I did
Really?
I didn't know that
you had such a talent
Actually, my dream was to become
a photographer when I was young
That's it over there
You can drop me off right about here
Thanks. Later
You sure the doctor
guy doesn't work here?
There just wasn't
a right place to make a turn
Well, thanks anyway. Bye
Good-bye
You wanna come up for a bit?
- Mom
- Yes
I brought you a gift today
- How do you do?
- Oh, hi
She's one of the many
girls that follow me around
Stop it. How are you?
You didn't have to bring this
Just take a seat over here
- I got it
- Come over here and sit
Sit. Do you need anything?
- Mom, relax
- I got it
It's okay, just sit
I would've prepared something for
her if I had known you two were coming
It's really okay Mrs. Kim
Mom, this is a hospital. Relax
I know... but still...
I'll do it
Don't. It's okay
- I'll got it Mrs. Kim
- It's really okay
Just let her do it mom
She knew exactly
what she was doing
With her eyes set down
she peeled the apples
skin into a perfect spiral
It was one of those typical
Korean mother & daughter in-law poses
Try this
I should've at least put on
some makeup or something
Don't mention it
Hope you get better soon
Don't worry mom
I'll bring a girl everyday
All you have to do is pick
Maybe we made a mistake
She held on to my hand
and asked me a lot of things
I feel terrible
Don't worry about it
I told her that you were just a friend
You did?
Now that you said that
I'm actually a bit disappointed
Why?
I don't want to do it
You're the one
that wanted to come
This is such a headache
Why?
One's a doctor
two's a salary men
the other's a businessman
and then you
I don't know who I should pick
Leave me out of it
Let's start with assumptions
First, marrying the doctor will
provide me with life's amenities
...but it will be a dull, fixed life
with his stuck up family to deaI with
Not to mention having to
get used to his ugly face
Then there's the life
of a salary man's wife
This is good because I get to live
with a man that's younger than me
But then, he's too short
Stop it
Next is also a salary man
This guy graduated from a top
notch school and even owns an apartment
And he seemed very nice and all
but he's such a mommy's boy
He wouldn't stop talking about
his mother. My mother this, my mother that
So why am I included?
You?
You're honest and
your mother seems very sweet
And?
And... you're good in bed
But I see us struggling financially
and you'll probably cheat on me
Every chance you get
you'll sneak around with other women
Why does everything have
to be so damn complicated?
Nothing has to be complicated
Forget about the ones
that aren't wealthy
Why?
Cause you would never
be able to give up financial freedom
Who are you to say?
If I were in your shoes
I wouldn't be able to give it up either
I'm taking 'em out
I'm going to choose from two
Congratulations. Pick a date then
I haven't decided yet
if I wanna go with you or the doctor
It'll never work with me
so pick a date with that doctor guy
Do you really have
no intention of marrying me?
It's not you. It's me
What do you mean?
TaIk to me
I just don't know if I can live with
someone and have to lie all the time
Wish we couId just
go away somewhere
Professor... Professor
Thank you
Maybe I won't get married
Why? Is he that bad in bed?
Did he ask for
money for his practice?
He has a huge mole under his eye
and I can't handle it
I'm serious
We've been fighting
all week because of that
I mean... this was a fight
on something terribly stupid
So imagine what would happen
when we have to agree on
what to buy for our house
It's gonna take months to settle all the issues
we need to go over before marriage
He also wanted to
get married in Woolsan
because his relatives
happen to live there
Does that make sense to you?
Maybe I should really
reconsider this marriage
No, you are right on track
What do you mean?
Same thing happened when
my brother was getting married
I really thought that the marriage
was over. They fought non-stop
I thought, "Do people really need
to get married after all this trouble?"
But then I found out that that was
the due process for getting married
That's all you have to say?
Are you busy today?
Did you decide
what you're gonna buy?
I have tons of things to buy
You should've
at least made a list
You sound like my fiance
You're tired, right?
Are you almost finished?
Just take a look
at the dress for me
Almost done now?
Yeah, all set
How is it?
You look great
He's the most
unenthusiastic groom ever
Maybe I should leave now
- You're not gonna come in?
- I'm good
Aren't you curious?
Come in
Hold on a sec
This is real wood
What do you want to drink?
Anything is fine
Thanks
Now I'm really glad
that I let you go
At least you know
What?
It was you that let me go
Whatever
You would've come
this way regardless
That's possible
But if you weren't so intent
on not getting married
I would never have made the
decision to give up on you so early
The house was perfect with
the sun shining through
The evening tempted you to say
"Are the kids home yet?"
What if your scent remains here?
Are you scared
you might get caught?
No, I'm just worried
that I'll get too horny
Just don't call my name when
you're do it with your husband
What?
I can't get it up
You're not going in?
I don't want to do it here
Where are you going?
Where are we going?
On a trip
A honeymoon
Honeymoon?
Aren't you glad we came?
Sure
Wait a sec
You prepared for this, didn't you?
I told you before that I wanted
to become a photographer
Stand right there
Forget it
Smile for crying out loud
Do you know where we are?
No
Wow, look at the stars
Why don't we go downtown?
Let's do a home-stay
You sure you don't wanna check-in
to a hotel on your honeymoon?
What kind of graduate
student couple stays at a hotel?
It's still a honeymoon though
No, can't do it
We have to save up
to buy your parents gifts
Oh, how lovely
Okay, how about
three more dollars?
I already gave you
a good discount
Oh, c'mon. Three more dollars
Okay
Thank you
Not bad, huh?
We can still go find a decent
place downtown, you know
This is just fine
It really is
I know
Stand right there
Stop taking pictures
Just stay there
Okay, that's the last one
Okay
When you get your tenure
we can look at
the pictures and laugh
Let's clean up first
You go get a broom
I'll do the laundry
And we can each look out for
each other when taking baths
When I need to
go to the bathroom
you'll follow me with a flash light
This is so much fun, isn't it?
- It's a rat
- Yeah
Miyao
Turn off the light
Okay
If you need to go to the bathroom
it's around the corner
I'm going to sleep now
Okay
Take it off for me
Just do it inside
No
Why?
You need to work
You're so warm
How come you never talk
about your ex-girlfriends around me?
Why are you asking this?
This is our honeymoon
I just don't think it's right to talk
about past girlfriends with a new one
You are such a player
I bet the first girl was like "This is mine"
And the second, "This is my lolly pop"
- Then the third one...
- What number am I?
What?
How many boys did
you sleep with so far?
You're the first one
You don't believe me?
I believe you
Why?
Cause it's our first
night on a honeymoon
Weekend Couple
Our next poem 'Flea'
written by John Dan
primarily works with
conceit and metaphor
As stated in the prologue
these characteristics have been prevalent
throughout the metaphysics of the 17th century
Weeks have passed
I just waited for her improbable
phone call like a bad habit
Yeah. Yeah. Okay No
Whenever I missed her
I wouId try to picture
her new married life
I was certain that she would be taking
on the duties of a housewife perfectly
She probably prepared Miso soup for
her husband right around 6 o'clock each day
And she will have
joined the swim club
so that she can stay in
shape to please her husband
On weekends, she would
go shopping with her husband
Those thoughts helped me
forget about her for the time being
It was two months into her
marriage when she had called
Do I look like I'm married?
No
How have you been?
I've been quite busy
I have this
translation work right now
Are you still Iiving out
of your parents' house?
They keep bugging me about
getting married so I want to move out
...but it's just not the right time
Is it money?
What else?
I can help you out, you know
I have some
retirement money leftover
Do you like your new job?
Yeah
I knew it would suit you well
But it's sort of boring
What do you usually
do on a regular day?
I fix him
breakfast in the morning
and then go to the swim club
...followed by some
shopping in the afternoon
Then you'll fix dinner and
greet him with a smile, right?
Pretty much
What can you cook?
Pretty much everything
But sea bass soup and hardboiled
hairtails are some of my best I must say
Do you also have drinks and talk
about your days from time to time?
Are you jealous?
Did you think that
I would call again?
If the swimming instructor
wasn't attractive enough, yes
I never thought you would
actually show up at my wedding
You have no idea
how surprised I was
Thought you could do better
You think?
I have to get going now
Okay, later
- Think about what I said
- What?
About moving out
I really want to help you
Thanks. But I'll pass
It's not charity, you know
I'm lending it to you
Just think about
it Joon-young
Okay? Good-bye
Everything's fine except
it's a bit too small, don't you think?
You think it's small?
For the both of us at least
You want more
water in your coffee?
Yeah. This is good
You think you would've don't
the same for me if we were married?
I'm not getting married so that
I don't have to do things like that
What?
You know, doing the dishes
making coffee, or fighting over love
Mr. Know-it-all
We should put our
honeymoon picture up there
and place the dining table here
And maybe a vase on top
That way, I can see if you're
coming home or not while fixing dinner
That's so cheesy
When I was little
that was my ultimate dream
I don't care if it's cheesy
If we were married
we probably would've ended up
living in a place like this, right?
Aren't you glad that
you went for the other guy?
Yeah
We would've
easily gotten a divorce
Make me a key
Why are you trying
to see me again?
I feel so fresh here
That's too big for two
This one looks good
I like the color too
- How much is this?
- 130 dollars
130?
This is too much for the room
It's better of
using hangers instead
Why don't we put
this next to the bed?
This is much better than that
We can put TV on top
How much did
you say this was?
I'll give it to you for 140
There was a scratch on it
- What's this?
- What?
There's nothing we can eat
Just wait. I'll make
you some Miso soup
We'll split the bill even
You pay for all of it
That's not fair
I don't need any of this stuff
Hey, here
HeIIo?
That's not possible
I left it on the whole time
I'm with my friends
I think I'm gonna run a little late
Are you working
overtime tonight?
I'll see you at home
Now it looks like
a newly wed's room
You just made
the room all cramped
It looks like a friggin' play house
You're not supposed to sit there
This is a floor mat
not a sitting mat
Who cares? It's new
Don't act primitive
This isn't my taste
You still like it though, don't you?
I'm starving
Wait, I'll fix dinner right away
How's this?
Don't I look cute in it?
I'm hungry
This over here too
- You wanted spinach last time
- Yes
We have it fresh today
I'm good for today
- So what do you do anyway?
- Excuse me?
I see your husband everyday
but you're sort of on and off
I work outside the city
So you're a weekend couple
Guess we are
A pack of cigarettes please
You're here
You're home?
I'll fix you nice dinner
We're a weekend couple
Do we have to do this?
It's fun
I always wanted
to do it this way
Oh my!
Go watch the soup
- That's enough now
- I'm almost done now
Go brush your teeth
Your breath stinks from the fish
I won't do it unless
you brush your teeth
This is why married couples
lose their sex appeal
- Honey
- What?
Will you grab the shaving cream
and a razor on your way out?
Why?
I wanna shave for you
Shave?
It stings when I kiss you
- Be careful with the blade
- Okay
Do you do this
for your husband too?
Not bad
When I was little, it just looked
so cool the way my father shaved
Ever since, I've been wanting
to shave for someone I love
Stop it. You're tickling me
If you wanna get cut, do it
- I wanna get cut
- Stop
Yeah. I'm out
I'll be back soon
Did you eat?
So, you'll be late then
Come out
- You're leaving?
- Yeah
Why are you opening my mail?
I think it's a she
Professor, this is Sae-un
I have tickets to a concert
So I thought of you
I don't remember
the movie we saw together
but I do remember your scent
I remember it vividly
Please give me a call
Are you dating a student?
She's just a student I know
This is no ordinary
teacher student relationship
She's just a student
When did you
start meeting her?
Did you sleep with her?
What do you want to know?
It's none of your
business anyway
None of my business?
Yeah... why should you care
about who I'm sleeping with anyway?
Okay
I don't care if you're sleeping
with that student of yours
But never bring her to this room
What?
I decorated this room
Another girl's presence
is not welcome here
You always have it your way
What?
You don't think I'm sick of having
to smell another guy's cologne on you?
I'm the one that
should be pissed
Okay then
Good luck with that student
I'm sure you told
her the same thing
"I don't believe in marriage"
In reality you're the one that
more picky about the women you meet
You can always
just leave like that
What?
And then when you miss me, you'll just
come back and pretend everything's okay
Well, I'm different
You can just run away whenever you wish
but I feel like shit being left here all alone
Your shit's all over the place
and your hair is all over the pillow
Do you know how that feels?
Closure
Hello?
It's your mother
Are you still sleeping?
Yeah
Why don't you
come over for breakfast?
I have your
birthday breakfast ready
- You know I don't eat breakfast
- Do you even know that it's your birthday today?
I know. I'll call you back later
You're here
What brings you here?
You're eating
instant noodles again?
I told you to cook
even if it's a hassle
Did you get bored that easily?
I thought you
would never come back
Didn't you miss me?
You lent me the money so that
you can do this from the beginning, right?
Can't say no
Hold on
I baked it myself
Doesn't it look tasty?
Is that all I get?
Do you know how hard
I worked to bake this all day long?
Where's the decoration?
It was here before
Don't answer
It's him
He was all suspicious
last time I didn't pick up
Hello? The cIass
just ended and
I'm going to get some
food with the people here
I don't think I can
be home so early
I told them that I would treat
Yeah, maybe an hour or two
Make sure you eat
and I'll see you later
What kind of class is it?
I told him I'd take
English classes in the evening
After all, I am an English teacher
Happy birthday. Cheers
Do we really have to do this?
Of course. It's a must
Aren't I the best?
I remembered your birthday
Hey, have some
I bet its much better
than the ones you buy
It's good
Really?
Does he like cakes?
What?
Oh... I guess
What else does he like?
Bulgogi, sea bass soup
and pretty much everything I cook
I bet... since you're a good cook
Why are you
asking me that though?
You never talk
about my husband
I was just curious
Curious about what?
Of course I'm curious
Then ask me questions
Well, you and your husband...
forget about it
What is it? Talk to me
It's nothing important
I feel like I'm in
a remote island somewhere
That would be
awesome if it were real
Don't you have to go now?
I got time
- Don't drink that
- Why not?
He'll be suspicious
if he smells alcohol on you
Then maybe
I'll just sleep here
Dude, let me stay with
you for a few days
- What happened?
- We decided to take a break
A break? That's great
What is it?
Forget about it
She knew all along
I found out yesterday
You know, the Ji-young thing
She knew for quite
some time now
Does Ji-young know too?
She said she would never call
She felt guilty
or something as a woman
What about you?
What about me?
What are you gonna do?
I don't' know man
Why don't you
straighten things out this time?
How? With whom?
Do you know how long I waited?
Why did you have
your cell phone off?
I met Kyu-jin today
What about him?
I spoke to Yu-ri
this morning too
It was that woman
in black at the wedding, right?
Shouldn't he get a divorce
with Yu-ri if he loves her so much?
It's not that easy
Once they get a divorce
he won't even have a place to live
And Yu-ri will probably
have probIems of her own
If he's so scared of things
like that, how is he in love?
Can you do it?
I know I can
No. You can't do it
I can
I'm confident that
I'll never get caught
Don't come here anymore
Why not?
That's just what I want
Not what I want
This picture came out nice
You're not a bad
photographer yourself
This one came out real nice
Maybe I'll send this
to a woman's weekIy
Aren't you scared?
Leaving records like that?
I don't get you sometimes
What are you gonna
do with that anyway?
I'll give it to you as
a gift when you get married
Do you know what
I'm making right now?
What is it?
Bean sprout soup
and prepared bean sprout
And...
Bean sprout rice
I'll just have instant noodles
You don't want Bean sprout rice?
It's the best
The best for you not for me
Just make me
some instant noodles
Are you complaining about food?
I'm doing my best here
You don't have to do that
Don't eat it if you don't want it
Just don't ask for it later
Where are you going?
To buy instant noodles
Hold on, wait
Get some pepper too
I don't put pepper
in my instant noodles
You'll get it, right?
Here
Your wife bought it
with bean sprout
She did?
You were gonna get it anyway
You had instant noodles
Yeah, but somebody had to
get up and buy pepper anyway
You're really gonna
eat instant noodles?
You're such a cry baby
Come on... it's getting cold
Eat that if you're gonna try me
Don't try me
You want me to eat
this all by myself?
Let's end this right now
We're slowly getting
sick of each other
Can you do it?
We can't do this forever
I never thought that it would be
over a stupid Bean Sprout Bibimbap
Can you really do it?
It's about will power...
If it's hard forgetting you
I'll try to find someone else
I'll do just the same
I might come back
to see you though
Don't
If I come back to see you
Please tell me to leave
I don't even feel any
kind of guilt anymore
I just feel a lot busier
than most people
Just don't come back
I don't know
if I can send you back
Thinking that it was
last got me more aroused
Her hair, eye movement
the sheet like skin, and
the feeling of her moving fingers
I wanted to hold on to every part of
her body that was no longer mine
Uncle Joon's here
- Uncle Joon
- How have you been Wonny?
- No one's home?
- Wonny's mother went to get her hair done
What brings you here?
You never come home without calling
You must be hungry
Let me fix you some lunch
Are you getting along
with your friends okay?
I can beat them all
You're supposed to
be friendly with them
There's only two, huh?
I don't know. They're gone
You should take care of them
Do you eat right?
Yeah, I'm fine
What happened to that nice girl
you came to the hospital with?
Oh, she got married
I haven't gotten
a call from her in weeks
Now that I come to think of it
it was every other week that she came by
Why she came by every other week
I'll never know. It's just funny that
I'm suddenly curious about all of this
Our relationship just
had so many flaws
We never shared
things most couples had
I'm looking at the album that
Yeon-hee left me for the first time
She's been diligently taking pictures
to make this album for quite some time
I just never really
cared much about it
It just seemed like one of her pointless
and dangerous acts that she did
At least in the pictures
we looked very happy together
But in the end
we ended up taking a different road
I think I know now...
Why she worked so hard
to take these photos
And I also know what
she wanted to tell me