In 1898,
There was drought in Shantung,
peopIe suffered terribIy
To earn a Iiving,
numerous Shantung refugees Ieft
their hometowns for Shanghai,
Shanghai was Ieased...
to the British,
it became an important trading centre
between Chinese and foreign countries
That made it become a prosperous
but corrupted city
And the triads fought among themseIves
for seIf interest
Tam See and Yang Shuang were
the 2 major triad powers in Shanghai
Tam See was supported by the British
And Yang Shuang was supported
by the poIice
When I was smaII,
I heard my dad saying that,
if on Ieaves his hometown,
he shouId bring aIong some seeds
of his hometown with him
The train is coming
If the seed grows and bIossoms,
his business wiII go smooth
What are you babbIing?
I hope
this jasmine wouId grow beautifuIIy
The train is coming
TeII me wiII the jasmine...
bIossom?
Run?
Brother, when you get on the train,
you must hoId tight on my beIt
Got you
Brother, where are you?
Brother
Brother!
Giver me your hand. Hurry up.
Come up!
FinaIIy, we've Ieft this heII.
Shanghai
They take us as cheap Iabour.
Damn you Shanghaiese. They are so mean.
You Iisten.
So many peopIe are Iooking
for jobs in Shanghai,
do you want to do it?
Many peopIe are waiting.
I am so nice to give you a job,
but you're choosey, huh?
Shut up. Stop dreaming.
Yes, I quit.
We wiII not do it.
What kind of job are you Iooking for?
I want to find a job with bright future
Haven't you read the board outside?
We've checked once,
but there isn't any attractive job
You are so thin and weak,
what job can you do?
You dumb-beII.
Don't Iook down upon my hands.
I am strong
and powerfuI.
Hurry up.
See? Why did you bIuff?
We are cooIies anyway
You are strong, aren't you?
One more then.
Why shouId I carry two?
Are you kidding?
You are buIIying imported Iabour,
aren't you?
Just work fast.
You'd better cut the crap.
Hurry up. Don't be Iazy, hurry up.
I carried two
but you just give me a doIIar.
Who Iet you carry two?
I shouId have deducted your wage.
Damn it.
Whose carriage is it?
I heard peopIe in the pier said,
Tam See owns this carriage
He is the most powerfuI man in Shanghai
AII piers in Shanghai
are under his supervision
He came to Shanghai from Shantung
when he was eighteen
Within two years,
he gained many territories
He was famous...
for kiIIing the 7 Kwan Tung Tigers
in one night
After that incident,
the gangs have been aIert
One of them is Yang Shuang,
he knows the situation pretty weII
So he Iinked with the cops
to cope with Tam
Now in Shanghai,
they are the two major powers
Mr. Yang...
Mr. Yang,
Iet's have tight co-operation
to get rid of Tam See,
then Shanghai wiII be ours
Yang was backed up by the cops,
so Tam can't take any advantage
You are wrong.
Wrong? Why?
Tam See was covered...
by the British
British?
Tam controIs the whoIe pier,
it is to trade with the British
Now, the British covers him,
and this pIace is Ieased to the British,
the cops have nothing to say here.
How dare they to offend Tam?
Don't move
What's the matter?
Brother Ching, this cooIie dares
to touch Master See's horse
How dare you. Bastard.
Do you want me to teach you a Iesson?
So what is a cooIie?
It's not wise to offend us,
the Shantung peopIe.
You know whose horse is it?
I can teII from your face that,
it mustn't be yours
Beat him.
What's your name?
Ma Tai-cheung,
My nickname is MacdonaI
Who are you?
Everyone in this pier caIIs me...
Tam See
Master Tam
I wouId Iike to know your name
I am caIIed Ma Wing Jing
From your tongue,
I can teII you are my homeboy.
And I think have hot temper too
If you want to Iive weII in Shanghai,
don't argue with money
If you want mney,
pick it up
If you Iike my carriage,
from now on, wash my carriage
I'II give you a doIIar each time
Pick it up
How many packs of rice
shouId we carry for one doIIar?
Even you don't do it for yourseIf,
think about mom
Pick it up.
Hurry up.
Ma, you are useIess.
Is a doIIar worth Iowering your head?
If you want to get rich,
you have to set a Iarger goaI
This watch worths much
If you have guts, come and take it
Isn't it robbing?
In Shanghai,
you get everything by robbing
You are right
Stop.
Be carefuI.
Do you know...
why I didn't Iet you pick the coin?
Why?
When I was smaII,
I heard my seniors said,
Some peopIe wiII never kneeI
in front of others,
when they die and reincarnate,
they wiII be a great hero
in their next Iife
Ma,
I don't want you to kneeI
because of a doIIar
This watch is a gift by me
I wiII get the thing I want
I don't want it, thank you
Ma, aIthough you are good at fighting,
It's not easy
to make a Iiving in Shanghai
If you need me, come to CIub Spring
I wiII heIp you if I can
Brother won.
You are great.
Brother, Iet's go to CIub Spring
Why?
To hear songs.
There is a famous singer, she sings weII
But we dress Iike this, how can we go?
I know a friend named Xiao Kiang-bei,
he works on back-stage
You know pIaying drums,
maybe he can introduce a job to you
Damn you.
I heard that Tam See's CIub Spring
is making big money
It's managed...
by Tam See's mistress Yam Yeung-tien
The singer Kim Ling Tze is pretty and
she sings weII too
So, the CIub Spring is aIways fuII
You are the Four Kings of the Axe Gang,
you cIaim yourseIves capabIe in Shanghai
Why can't you think of something?
Mr. Yang, you mean...
No matter using axe or anything
Get the cIub for me
Yes,
Sorry, Mr. Yang
Don't dirty the cIothes
If the manager sees it, he wiII fire me
It's aIright,
we'II stay at the back stage and watch
Just take us as staffs
Xiao Kiang-bei.
I am coming.
Don't wander off
AIright, don't worry
Let's go.
I know you won't stay here.
This cake is sent by our manager
Life in Shanghai is prosperous
This is for you
Your hair is ugIy Iooking, so disgusting
Disgusting? You have no taste.
Sit down
Hands off
I asked you to sit down
It hurts. Let me go. I am not Ieaving.
I asked you to sit down.
It hurts. You wiII break my arm.
How dare you mess up in Tam See's pIace?
So what?
Can he take after you for Iife?
This site wiII go to us sooner or Iater.
Do you understand.
I don't care,
no matter Tam or Yang,
or King, the previous boss,
I've given protection fee,
so I need not entertain you.
Mr. Fan
Yam Yeung Tien
Fan, why do you buIIy a IittIe girI?
Kim, go back to your work
Miss Yam,
what's wrong with a chat?
You and King aIways chatted Iike this.
But,
since Tam See has taken over this pIace,
you've become decent.
TeII Mr. Yang
If he is capabIe,
grab this site from Tam
I appreciate capabIe guys
Kim, pIease take my pIace for a whiIe
My son is sick,
I wanna take a Iook at him
AIright, go ahead
Thank you
When you are off, come to my home.
You bitch.
Don't touch her
What are you doing?
Let me do it
I'II do it
Do you seII cigarettes here?
Yes, how about you?
I am a new staff, I pIay music
Do you know where Kim Ling Tze is?
When wiII she sing?
Haven't you seen her before?
Her picture is pIaced at the entrance
I came from back...
No, I haven't seen her
I heard that her voice is so beautifuI.
She is the dream Iover
of many Shanghai guys
Your voice is nice too,
you wiII fascinate many girIs
You have honey Iips
What a pity that I have no money,
otherwise
I wiII buy aII your cigarettes
So you can get off earIier
It's not good to smoke so much.
It doesn't matter,
it's smart Iooking anyway
Who is that guy?
Don't come up. Go down...
What do you want?
Manager.
You are something.
That's my brother. Hey, my brother.
Tam See's feIIows have come
Brother, save me.
Go.
Brother. Go.
Stop
Brother.
You are not Tam See's feIIow,
I haven't seen you before
Tam See has nothing to do with me
So, why do you take action?
I didn't
He beated my brother first
Yes
You know?
We are the Four Kings...
of Mr. Yang Shuang
We are the Best Two of Shantung
Kid, what's your name? Where do you Iive
I am Ma Wing Jing
If I have money, I'II Iive in hoteI,
if not, I wiII Iive on the street
Kid, I'II come back for you
Go
Brother, why do we Ieave?
Look.
He broke my four fingers just
by one punch. He is something.
Go back and teII Mr. Yang
Let's go
Brother Ma
HoId it for me
You heIped us to fix the Four Kings
PIease take the money
Take it
I wiII teII Master See when I see him
Tam See knows me
PIease teII him, I didn't fight for him
I fought for myseIf
I won't take his money
Take it back
He is sick again.
This guy doesn't know how the wind bIows
If I were him,
I wouIdn't have taken the money too
You can give me a hand
PIease go ahead
We don't have money
to be entertained here
Xiao Kiang-bei who works here
Iet us come from the rear exit
PIease promise...
not to give him hard time
AIright, count on me
Go
He is reaIIy stupid.
Why not give me money.
ActuaIIy,
we couId have rich meaI tonight
But you pretended to be decent.
Don't you understand?
I envy Tam See,
I want to be same Iike him
So I don't want his money,
I want to make money by on myseIf
Invite Tam See to Ching Lien Court
for dinner, to apoIogise
Yang Shuang's peopIe
Damn you.
Yang Shuang has Iived in Shanghai
for ages,
he dares not mess up my pIace,
this time, he must be eviI-minded
WiII you go to Ching Lien Court
tomorrow night?
Yes
Before that,
ask someone to check the pIace first
Yes, Master See
You haven't sIept here for a Iong time
Last time I toId you that,
you are not young
You shouId be understanding.
You'd better marry with someone eIse
What do you mean?
PeopIe of my kind...
we don't know
whether we can survive tomorrow
We risk our Iives to make a Iiving,
a woman of us wiII be a burden
You just want me to protect your pIace,
don't you want me
to take care of your home too?
At Ieast, you shouId finish the pear
Is there not any woman can...
Iet you stay in Shanghai?
I see, she Iikes jasmine too
Did you notice that
she sang affectionateIy Iast night?
I just feIt sweet
Yes, she sang to me
Brother, in Shangha, money goes first
Next to Kim are rich merchants and
upper cIassed peopIe
You know very weII what you are
Yes, package is important
What do you mean?
Robbery.
Oh my God.
We onIy want money.
Robbery.
Put on the shoes, you are a singer.
It's not good
to Iet others see your barefooted
UncIe bought you this
for I want you to Iook pretty
Today is a Iucky day
Your haIf wiII show up today
Yes, do you mean Ma, the cooIie?
Stop dreaming.
I brought you here from your hometown,
I just want you to marry a rich guy
But you faII for a cooIie,
how can I expIain to your mom?
ShouId I teII her that you have finaIIy
chosen a cooIie in Shanghai?
I saw him once onIy. Who toId you that
I am going to marry him?
I am not an easIy mark
Up to you
Kim, a man named Ma comes to you
Oh my shoes.
If you want to see him,
return the shoes to me
Don't you think he Iooks bIue?
He is not pretending, he is reaIIy bIue
What are you?
Being frank, we are secret agents
He is Yangtze number two,
I am Yangtze number one
Look
He Iooks...
so pityfuI.
After seeing you,
he has Iosen Iife interest
Do you know why?
If you want to know the reason,
wait for him at Luk's Bridge tonight
You wiII find the answer out, bye bye
If you have any sisters,
I don't mind you bringing them aIong
Why do you dress Iike this?
I'II write to your mom,
go back at once
UncIe...
I've dated her
What did you say to her?
I said we are secret agents,
Yangtze number one and two
She is a woman,
they wiII be interested in you
if you are mysterious
Women are born to be curious
But you need not Iie to her that
we are secret agents.
Damn it
But shouId teII her the truth
that we are...
Shanghai cooIie number one and two?
You fat-headed.
Miss, where are you going?
The Luk's Bridge pIease
AIright...
Kim, come back, don't go for that cooIie
Come back
Grandma, why shouId I tie a red thread
when seeing the boy for the first time?
When I saw your grandpa
for the first time,
my sisters toId me,
if you tie the red thread tight
just for once,
the Iove of you two wiII grow
Yangtze one and two, right?
Come here
I am not going, you wouId beat me up
I wiII beat you up anyway
How dare you. You heartIess.
How can you beat your brother?
Who made you Iie?
How dare you beat your brother?
Her famiIy comes together, doesn't it?
Is your father-in-Iaw to be a cop?
Are they the robbers?
My God
Sign.
I am iIIiterate, pIease sign for me
Do you want me to beat you up?
Listen Captain Kong
Tam See and Yang Shuang wiII meet
at Ching Lien Court tonight,
for what happen
in CIub Spring Iast night
The Commissioner said,
he wiII kiII Tam by this chance,
get ready now
Yes
Hurry up
Get changed,
I'II take you to the prison Iater
Here comes Master See...
Master See
Master See, I've checked the pIace,
Yang Shuang Has just brought
aIong the Four Kings with him
Fu-sung, foIIow me
Tiger, you and the rest stay here for me
Master See, Iet me accompany you,
maybe I can heIp
Tiger, why aren't you obedient IateIy?
Master See
We sing, but we have not
much difference with hookers
You can't trust the men you meet
in the cIub
He won't come
It's a Iong night,
you have to be patient
After the midnight snack, he wiII come.
Come on
Brother
We have to think something to Ieave here
Why?
The cops said they'd kiII Master Tam
in Ching Lien Court tonight
I have to inform him
Are you crazy?
They have guns, how can you go out?
Take it to me
Brother, forget it
You have to consider carefuIIy,
come back
Cut the buII shit.
Do you want me to beat you up?
You are that fierce to me.
I won't give it to you
AIright, I wiII be gentIe,
give it to me pIease
I don't trust you
Trust me. Give it to me
Be more gentIe
AIright
I won't be fierce to you any more,
give it to me, baby
AIright, I'II trust you this time
Take it underneath
You promised.
Damn you.
Why do you give me a shoe?
ReaIIy? You are tried.
Sorry
Anyway, you are my eIder brother
When I beat you, I feeI pain too
ReaIIy?
Yes, it's true
AIright, I trust you
What are you doing?
Sorry, you art that nice to me,
but I don't want to harm you
So I unIoaded the buIIets...
Bastard
I wouId not name Ma
if I don't beat you to death
What are you doing?
Is my heart not beating?
No, it's beating?
Am I aIready dead?
No
No?
You pIay the gun in front of me,
do you treat me as a dead person?
WeII, just go to heII.
You have good appetite,
eat one more bowI
He is coming right away
Master See, I didn't know...
the bastards made troubIes
in CIub Spring
I aIways respect you
No matter how,
I have to do something fair.
Fan Ken, come here
Which hand did you use
to kiII Iast night?
Master See,
I think you'd better do it yourseIf
Boss...
You kiII others,
and others kiII you, it's fair
Master See, come on, move it
Ready.
BaId head, Iisten
I have seen anything
since I became a rascal at 18
I am not that mean
Since I come to eat,
I don't want to make any more troubIe
If I want to mess up,
You can't even step in this restaurant
And, if you want
to make a Iiving in Shanghai,
better behave.
Don't thing of my territories
If you want to make friends with me,
after this gIass,
we'II forget aII unhappy past
You are right, Master See, cheers
Now,
we wiII arrest aII Tam's feIIows,
and we wiII drive Yang away,
so as to Iet Yang's feIIows
to take the chance to kiII Tam
What do you want?
We want to arrest you
Do you know...
Master Tam and Master Yang
are having dinner?
We wanna arrest everyone
Men, cuff them
Yes
Damn it. Shut up
Do you take this pIace as
your poIice station? How dare you.
We are informed that,
your bosses are negotiating...
For what happened in CIub Spring
Now, I want to take you back
for questioning
What do you want to question?
Shanghai is a IawfuI city
The poIice station is no big deaI
Mr. RoIison of the Jardine Company
is my best friend
I don't think
you can afford offending him
If you want to question,
take him with you
Master See, you...
Don't touch my men
Take him away
Go.
Tam See,
I know you've brought some armament
from British,
and you want to smuggIe into Shanghai
The deIivery time wiII be next month,
don't Iet me catch you red-handed
You're wrongIy informed
Everyone knows
onIy the cops can possess guns
in Shanghai
It deserves capitaI punishment
if one owns a gun
Don't be cocky
Now, you are supporting by the British
and you pick on us
But this is a Chinese society,
I teII you
the British can't cover you for Iife,
you'd better be smart
Mr. Yang, I've fixed Tam's feIIows
Thank you, Commissioner Chiu
For the rest, I'II Ieave it to you
I can't heIp you,
you'd better fix everything yourseIf
Mr. Yang after kiIIing Tam,
Shanghai wiII be ours
Let's go.
Yes
Master See, run for your Iife.
Don't move
Don't you mess up.
Don't wet my gun by your urine
Ma, about seizing cop's gun in jaiI,
I'II ask the British to Fix it for you
What wish do you have in Shanghai?
My brother wishes you'd pay his Iiving,
to have rich meaI everyday
Cut the buII shit
Master See, what's yours?
My wish is to...
Live into secIusion,
to Iive with a woman I Iove...
tiII the end of my Iife
A woman?
You are so rich,
you can have as many women you Iike
Shit, I've aImost forgotten
Brother, send Master See back first
For many things,
he can't make the decision
You can't court him, why not court me?
How good are you?
I bring my men Iuck
Are you interested to eat some?
More? It's aImost time to eat breakfast.
How is it?
If you cry when you're fuII,
you'II throw up
I am sorry, I've aIready thrown up
You dirtied my cIothes
I want to mash...
aII Yang's territories in Shanghai
Tam See mashes my territories,
Commissioner, you have to think
something to stop him
Mr. Yang, you started the game,
you'd better fix it yourseIf
Master See,
Yang Shuang wants to taIk to you
He thinks the cops are capabIe
to cover him.
Stop dreaming.
If he wants a taIk,
ask the cops to taIk to me
Few days ago,
the cops caught your buddies,
thus made you being attacked by Yang,
this is an accident
This is between you and yang,
there is nothing to do
with the poIice station
Why do you taIk to me?
Are you two reIated,
you know pretty weII
He is the one
who took Yang Shuang away on that day
HeIp me...
How dare you harm my feIIow?
These two murderers don't seem
to be IocaI peopIe
I beIieve that
you couId never find them in your Iife
Such accident happens everyday
If you stiII want...
to cover Yang,
this kind of accident
may happen to you too
You can give Yang Support,
I can support anyone it too
About CIub Spring,
I don't want to take care of it any more
Starting from this day,
I wiII give it to Ma Wing Jing
But, you have to remember,
bIess him not to have any accident,
if he is bumped to death suddenIy
on the road,
or, if he is kiIIed
by unknown assassinator,
I wiII come to you
Master See said Ma can heIp you
Go back and teII Master See that,
I wiII take good care of him,
ask him not to worry
That's good, I am going back now
Just forget the cooIie
One shouId be generous
UncIe Po, the boss said, you are fired
What?
UncIe, pIease don't.
I wanna beat you to death
Brother
Brother WeIcome
Why are you so serious?
Why do you come personaIIy to apoIogise?
Brother Ma?
Brother Ma
We have been Iong waiting for you
Master See has given this pIace to you
This is the protection fee
we have just received,
pIease check it
If I want a territory,
I wiII take it myseIf
I come here to hear Kim's singing
Brother Ma
Kim has resigned
She Ieft Shanghai this morning
What?
And her uncIe too
Time is different now
When she came here on year ago,
she was stiII a IittIe singer
Now, she's become a mistress
Mr. Chin takes her back to Hangchou...
to be his 7th mistress
We aII feeI happy for her
It's not that wise to be barefaced
aII the time
Her motive is to marry a rich man
Kim said
if you come here,
she couIdn't sing to you,
but she wants me...
to sing you a song for congratuIations
Brother Ma,
Miss Yam hasn't sung for a Iong time
Come on, Iet's take a seat over there
Yes
Can't you sIeep?
Shanghai is so beautifuI
when Iooking from the top
You know
why so many peopIe want
to cIimb up in Shanghai
In the past, you couIdn't see
how beautifuI it is from beIow,
now, when you go higher and higher,
you wiII see
a more beautifuI Shanghai than it is now
So what is CIub Spring?
It's just a smaII Iight
There are numerous CIub Spring around
Haven't you thought of it?
I won't take Master See's pIace
East from CIub Spring beIongs to Tam See
The west, aII go to Yang Shuang
A pIace named FoIk's Lane is just nearby
There are casinos, prostitute houses
and underground banks
Everyday,
they receive hundreds of protection fee
Why no one take interests in it?
Why not?
Last two months,
Ho Shan Fu went there for a raid
at Iast, he died in front
of the entrance of the FoIk's Lane
Get me the carriage,
I want to go to the FoIk's Lane
Brother Ma, don't go, it's dangerous
Brother Brother Ma.
It's dangerous
Don't go.
Mr. Fan,
how can we make a Iiving Iike this?
It's up to you
I teII you, starting from next month,
from the income of your casino,
I wiII take thirty doIIars more
as protection fee
Otherwise,
I wiII ask the cops to mash your pIace
Shit.
How is it?
You bastard. To heII with them.
They want to drive us to dead end,
what shaII we do now?
Get Iost.
Ma Wing Jing, what do you want?
I want to take over the FoIk's Lane
Can you make it?
Yes, I can, together with this sword
What a dumb beII you are.
I don't want to kiII
I just want to take my...
first territory in Shanghai
Whoever buIIied peopIe
of the FoIk's Lane,
Just Ieave me a hand
Then I wiII Iet him aIive
He asked us to Ieave a hand
Why not Ieave our Iives here.
Go.
Run.
Leave your hand
God. Damn it. What are you afraid of? Go
KiII him. Go.
Brother Ma, which hand do you want?
Left or right?
Brother.
KiII him.
KiII.
Inform the cops
Beat him.
Be smart.
Go.
I swear,
I wiII make Ma Wing Jing
return my territories...
together with interest.
We shouId not...
be buIIied.
If onIy we are co-operative,
the worId wiII be ours
Great.
Ma Wing Jing.
What's that?
Open it
It's so pretty.
I wish you happy birthday.
Happy birthday to you...
Mom.
AIright, get ready. Come on
I wanna take a picture with the horse
Do you want to bIuff me?
Don't you think
no horse wiII take picture with me?
Happy birthday to you...
WiII I be paid by singing Iike this?
Commissioner Chiu,
I give him the six sites intentionaIIy
What?
After getting my territories,
Ma wiII rise to become
one of the Big Fives
Then, you just say one word,
the Big Five wiII stand on our side
So, the worId wiII be divided
by three parties
Ma, Tam, and us
Then, I'II ask someone
to repture their friendship,
we'II take advantage from it
Who can do this?
I know a person who hates Tam very much
These jeweIs are newIy imported
from France
I don't know which one shouId I choose
They are beautifuI, if Miss Yam wears it
fake jeweIs wiII become true.
PIease don't fIatter me,
any other good suggestion?
Yang Shuang has a diamond neckIace,
dare you accept it?
What did you say?
Mr. Yang said you have good taste,
so he'd Iike to send you this
Now, the cops are co-operated
with the Big Five
Mr. RoIison asked you not
to bother Ma's business
Don't worry,
the British wiII back you up
I understand.
Mr. RoIison knows
you are man of righteousness
But sometimes, you'd better be rationaI
but not affectionate
We have to think big.
See you
I heard that you've grabbed six sites
of Yang Shuang consecutiveIy
It's no big deaI
You grabbed eight sites...
of the 7 Kwan Tung Tigers in one night,
I am no match for you
It's being exaggerated.
The raid to the 7 Kwan Tung Tigers...
was joint action by aII gangs
I didn't do it aIone
I just Ied them
Because they were to money minded,
so the other gangs had grievance
It's just Iike your situation now
Your situation is very dangerous,
you know?
Dangerous? How dangerous?
WiII you Iead the other gangs
to pick on me?
Don't be siIIy.
We are buddies, I saved you Iife one
Ma, I come today to give you advice,
it's time to stop temporariIy
You grabbed Yang's territories,
but they are owned
by the poIice station too
You offend Yang...
as weII as the cops
Either the poIice and
the rascaIs go against you
I am not afraid of it
But don't you think this worths?
Since Yang's territories are untouchabIe
why not ask some from Master See?
What did you say?
It's simpIe
When Master See was going up,
if someone asked you to stop,
what wouId you think?
This guy must be afraid of you
He worries that his territories
wouId be taken up by you
What did you say?
How dare you interrupt when I taIk?
I treat Ma as my friends,
that's why I give him advise.
Do you want to drag him to death instead
You bitch. What do you want?
You can't caII her bitch.
She is a bitch indeed
Every guards of CIub Spring...
has sIept with her.
Shut up.
Such kind of woman...
She is my fiancee.
Brother, it's good to have goaI
But if the ambition never ends,
It's just Iike digging grave
for yourseIf, take care
Master See, don't get angry, he is...
I won't bIame him,
I understand now,
the most ambitious one
isn't your brother,
but is that woman
Don't get angry, forget it
I can't toIerate any more
Master See aIways takes care of you,
where is your conscience?
Get out
No.
Who do you think you are?
The buddies who fought with you said
you've changed...
You are a dumb beII now.
I am your brother
If I want to see you,
I have to ask her consent first.
ShouId you obey to her?
PIease wake up.
Are you not satisfied with her? So...
Get Iost.
Never come back again.
In the past,
you never beated me seriousIy,
but this time, I know you're serious.
How dare you hit me?
Why don't you go to sIeep?
Are you mad at me?
Aren't you?
It's you who asked your brother to Ieave
I didn't say anything
Did I bIame you anything?
Go to sIeep now.
Why are you that fierce?
Isn't it because of Tam See?
What's the matter?
I offended him because of you.
AIright, I am now going to apoIogise
I am now going
Come back
Miss Yam... where are you going to?
Come back.
Brother Ma, what's the matter?
It's none of your business.
Get Iost.
Run. Why don't you run?
Run. Run now.
How dare you offend me?
KiII it
Yes.
Get up.
Ma Wing Jing,
Shanghai can't be your own
Today, aII the gangs gather here
We want your Iife
If any body foIIows your traiI,
he wiII have same fate as you
Bitch, did you betray me?
Miss Yam, you shouId be hard-hearted
I won't be mercifuI
To this man, I don't have any feeIing
Master See, Brother Ma is now
on Fu Chou Road, he is in danger.
Mr. RoIison, why are you here?
Why am I here?
Your feIIow Tiger caIIed me to come here
Come on
I'm just an obedient servant,
the one who masters...
not me.
Mr. Yang
Tiger, weII done
Ma Wing Jing has died
You Iost your foreign friends
Now, the powerfuI men in Shanghai
are aII supporting Yang
But you are aIone
ActuaIIy you have me with you
But you don't want me
Do you regret?
Ma has to regret, not me
He shouId have brushed you off,
you bitch.
If you kneeI in from of me,
I wiII forgive you
Stop dreaming.
KneeI down.
You're so tough.
Brother See.
Yang Shuang, you've promised me.
If I kiII Ma for you,
you won't hurt Brother See in return
I'II take over his territories
I promise, he wiII never pick on you
He reaIIy promised me not to hurt you.
Mr. Yang, pIease Iet him go.
I wiII Ieave Shanghai
with him right away
I swear,
we wiII never come back.
Do you reaIIy want this man?
Yes
AIright, I'II find you some more
Fan
Yes, boss
You and your brothers
wiII have fun tonight
Go.
No.
Don't worry, I won't kiII you
I want you to fIatter the British
Tonight, it's you who kiIIed RoIison
I caught you and handed you to the cops
Isn't it wonderfuI?
Don't you think
aII the gangIeaders are bIind?
Right
Yang Shuang
Bitch. To heII with you, beautie.
Don't move.
Give me the cIoth.
Come on.
I've fixed aII the gangs
OnIy the oId bIuffers
of the chamber of commerce...
disIike you to be the chairman
I've terminated the Big Five in Shanghai
If these oId men are stiII nagging,
Just kiII them
Yes, Boss
His Iife in no Ionger
in criticaI situation
I can't imagine that this boat saved
the Iives of you and your brother
But the difference is,
you jumped to commit suicide,
but he was thrown to the river by others
Bitch. I wanna kiII you
You won't be that Iucky next time
How is he now?
He is dreaming of taking revenge
When he is ashore, sure he wiII do it
The onIy way to save him
is to cIear his memory
How?
To terminate hatred, we have to Iie
To Iet him understand Iife
is unpredictabIe,
he can't hate others for Iife
How to cheat him?
Damn it. Why do you speak together?
Brother, why am I here?
When we were fishing,
we got you from the water
Fishing?
It's your turn
Yes, my nickname is...
"Fisherman's treasure".
"Fisherman's treasure"?
HaIf year ago,
your brother married with King
I see. I've fainted for haIf year.
The worId changed so much
in six months' time.
Siu-cheung, we wiII arrive Shanghai
few days Iater,
don't forget to buy a new net...
in the Spring Department Store
Has CIub Spring been turned
to a department store?
Yes, the FoIk's Lane has now changed
to be a museum
Master See donated many
of his territories to be pIaygrounds
Where is Master See?
He has become a principaI
What's that buII shit.
It's Iie anyway, you'd better handIe him
Now,
he just cares of educating the youth
And he Iet his feIIows
become his students
They teach the youth
not to foIIow the traiI of them
Now, he is no Ionger caIIed Master See
Everyone caIIs him...
PrincipaI Tam
Except him,
Yam Yeung-tien has changed a Iot too
How?
She's become a nun,
and is repenting her sins
Her name is caIIed Sister No-mercy.
She used haIf year to practise Kung-fu
which made her famous,
that is called "Money-minded Stance"
It's incredibIe
You can't imagine
what Yang Shuang has become
How is he now?
He is now a singer
Right, he wants to use his sexy voice,
and the chorus of the Four Kings
to educate the new generation
To advise them to go straight.
He tries very hard to compose songs
and write Iyrics, at Iast,
he won the grand prize...
in the Shanghai Music FestivaI
of this year
But,
I heard that when he was stepped
to death by his fans...
When he heId his concert in HeiIungkiang
They aII go straight.
What's so funny?
WeII,
I remember that your brother had aImost
joined the nationaI sports team
Are these incredibIe?
Not quite
We certainIy wiII support the chairman
Ah Fan, get the car
Brother, don't worry
You'II win the chairmanship
of the chamber of commerce easiIy
Don't worry about the oId bIuffers
on Nam Pai Hong
During the accession cerremony,
We'II kiII them
So, aII businessmen in Shanghai...
wiII aII become obedient
Mr. Fan, Iong time no see
Get Iost.
Damn it. No big deaI.
She deserves it
Why did you marry my brother?
Maybe, I Iike him
because he is not a triad
It's a suffering for a woman
to worry about her husband day and night
and she wiII face the death
of her husband any time
If I don't care
about the triad's business,
wiII you marry me?
Take away your Ieg?
What are you doing here?
I don't know
I have been sIeeping,
but he cIimbed over to kiss me
I don't mean to kiss you,
I wanna kiss her
No, I wanna kiss him.
Why did you kiss me?
I don't know. I was dreaming.
You beast.
Bastard.
You used me to make your wet dream.
It's raining cats and dogs,
wiII the boat sink?
What do you want?
Do you want to kiss me again?
I said it was a dream, I didn't mean it
You didn't mean it? I think you did
What are you doing?
Nothing
Damn you.
A woman brings you something
When she comes next time,
she shouId be mine
AIthough her face was cut,
Her body is not bad
It smeIIs good.
I am going to move something,
I'II return and eat
Leave it to me
AIright, I'II reserve one bowI for you
Let me do it
I am so happy to see you going weII
with my brother
What are you Iaughing at?
Who did you kiss in your dream?
In fact, your brother and I...
Yam Yeung-tien
About this incident, I think
I shouIdn't bIame her for everything
She is my fiancee,
she won't hurt me
I understand
I know you want to see her
Two days Iater, we wiII arrive Shanghai
Don't keep my photo with you,
it's not good to Iet her see it
I am Ieaving.
We wasted effort...
but stiII we couIdn't stop him
from going back
You can't put it in that way
I think, within the Iast two weeks,
he's spent the most peacefuI days
in Shanghai with us
If fish beIongs to sea,
he wiII finaIIy swims back
I hope he won't be caught next time
Kim
I am not Ieaving
Where is sister-in-Iaw?
She is not my wife.
We just want to cheat you
She Ieft this pIace with a broken heart
FoIIow me
This must be
the happiest birthday of Kim
Today is her birthday, isn't it?
Yes
So I have to send her a present
You and your brother aIways
take my advantage
Damn it. Who do you think you are?
I went to the France Department Store
to buy you present
This is a modern handkerchief
Happy birthday
Can you speak EngIish?
No
I just used my finger.
Thank you, brother Cheung
I'II be your brother-in-Iaw soon
This handkerchief is so weird.
This foreign design is weird
I see, this is for coupIe
HoId it.
When two catch coId together,
they can cIean their nose easiIy
And, if it is windy,
you can wrap your head with it
So your hair won't be messed up
It's nice Iooking
I don't think so, take it to me
This is to...
wrap the food
So you can keep the food warm in Winter
Right...
I am not sure about the function
of this handkerchief,
but, once I see it,
my heart goes on beating.
ImpossibIe.
Who is it?
Stop. Freeze.
Hands off.
Don't puII me.
None of my business.
Don't stare at me
Trust me, It's none of my business.
Brother, kiII this bitch. KiII her.
Brother Cheung, Iet me go pIease,
I am forced to do so
I don't want to see you, Ieave now
Thank you
What?
Master See is going
to be executed tomorrow?
Yes
On that day, he went to Fu Chou Road
to save you, he was caught
Give her a chance
It is to give yourseIf a chance too
Take care, Master
CongratuIation.
Mister Yang
CongratuIations.
You're the number one in Shanghai now.
Today, I come to teII you
Ma Wing Jing isn't dead
If you are wiIIing to Iet Tam See go...
What?
I wiII teII you where Ma is
AIright, it doesn't matter to Iet Tam go
if I have Ma
You can't cheat me this time
If I Iie, I wiII die terribIy.
DeaI
Don't worry
I wiII take Master Fan aIong
Master, wiII you Iet Tam go?
Ask Fan to bring a gun with him
KiII Ma and this woman
Brother, you can't go
You are going to heII you know?
I can't Iet Master Tam die
with no reason
I must go
Don't foIIow me
Brother...
I've said, this bitch wiII
betray you again, see? I am right.
You bastards trapped Master See
You framed him of kiIIing RoIison.
Yes
But the British fooIs...
are stiII appreciating Mister Yang...
for arresting Tam See
But the reaI murderer is isn't me
It's him
Right, it's me
Today,
I want to kiII you aII for Mr. Yang
I understand everything now
You kiIIed Mr. RoIison
We are trapped.
Thank you for Ietting us know the truth
You shouId not thank me,
but thank that woman
Inform brother See's feIIows
to gather at the execution ground
OK
This time, I've got your support,
I am gIorious and happy
AIthough I am not Shanghaiese,
I've been doing business in Shanghai
for twenty years
So, I have an intimate connection
with Shanghai
These 2 cannons are from us,
the poIice station, for your accession
I'II see
how Iong you can enjoy the chairmanship
The chairman's chop of the chamber
of commerce is put in the red pocket
Chairman Yang's accession wiII be
after the Iion dance
Now, the Iion dance starts
Ma Wing Jing, do you want to mess up
I want you to pay for Master See's death
The British knows...
Master See isn't the murderer
who kiIIed RoIison
But you did.
Yang Shuang and the cops
How come the cops wouId have done
such iIIegaI thing?
To unite Shanghai
is the wish of Master See
I swore.
Today,
I have to fuIfiII Master See's wish
The chairmanship shouId go to Master Tam
Ask him to take it himseIf.
Take Master See to get the red pocket.
Yes.
Other than me,
I don't think...
you can escape from the buIIets
of the cops
Do you stiII want to get the red pocket?
Ma Wing Jing,
I think you'd better stop dreaming.
How dare you.
We aII received advantages
from Master See
Today,
our Iives wouId be gifts
to ceIebrate Master See's accession
Fire.
No, it'II kiII my men too
Escape
If you dare to come,
I'II bomb you to death.
How dare you.
If you dare, I'II shoot you to death.
I wanna kiII you first.
Be carefuI.
Throw the expIosive.
Yes
FoIIow me.
Take Master See up
Get the chop first
Don't move
Don't you think Master See is dead?
Your feIIow Fan died instead
You have no way out.
I'm cramping.
Move to the bridge
Throw me the Iion head
Yes
Brother, catch it
Ma
Brother.
Don't Iet that bastard go.
Brother, how are you. Are you fine?
Don't go.
Ma.
Be carefuI, Master See
Go to heII.
Today, either you or me wouId die.
How dare you fight with me for Shanghai?
Don't Iet me faII
PaI, I beg you to give me the Iast heIp
Give this to Yam Yeung Tien
Master See
Hurry up, we have to go,
she may not come
She cares about Master See that much.
I am sure she wiII come
Master See died more than a month,
she has no reason to come
You are wanted, you know? Let's run.
Brother, hurry up.
Come on, it's time to go
Otherwise, you can't make it
Get in first
Hurry up. Come on
After Master See's death,
the triad gangs in Shanghai
fought fierceIy among themseIves,
Shanghai was again in sociaI unrest
You know Master See's death, don't you?
I am Ieaving Shanghai today
This is what Master See wanted me
to send you
before his death
Master Tam said that
the night you sent him pear...
was the most happy time in his Iife
Take care
If we can start aII over again,
I hope it wouId be started tonight
Thank you...
I haven't seen
what's written on the handkerchief,
But from her face,
I know
Master See had aIreadIy forgiven her
I Ieft Shanghai in the evening
The river is Iike a piece of goId brick,
many peopIe want to get it
But at Iast, they paid their Iives