That's her!
Myon?
Myon!
Very impressive!
"send message"
Hello?
"delivery failure"
"One Way/Osaka-Tokyo"
You live around here?!
Right under your nose, huh?
Um, wanna ride?
C'mon.
You wish!
You've got it all wrong!
Oh, sure.
I live with my sister, my dad lives with
a younger woman.
It's a joke.
Mom left one night when we bailed out.
Sorry I haven't kept in touch.
My life's kind of a mess, well, still is!
Don't worry!
Nice to see you're still the same... size.
Haven't they gotten bigger?
My breasts?
Huh, no, your feet! Let's find you a drugstore!
Better yet, a love hotel.
Hey!
Don't move!
Thanks!
Ouch!
What're you doing?
Nishi...
Um...
Would you be sad
if I went out with someone else?
If I married him?
Married...
In junior high, I wrote her a note,
just "I like you a lot."
Next day, her turn, "me too."
Knocked me off my feet!
We were just 13,
never even held hands after school.
Being shy made things awkward right after...
...and we could only exchange letters, mails!
Two years later, during a school trip...
Would you be sad
if I went out with someone else?
"Hotel Tariff"
Made me think! I never had the guts
to make a move, always playing it safe.
Always waiting for someone
to help things develop!
Nishi, what do you want?
You don't fight, you don't get hurt,
you want me to do all the work.
But that's unfair. 'Cos I'm scared too!
We're not school kids anymore, y'know?
What?
I...
I still love you. Don't marry that guy!
I've loved you since I was 9!
You should marry me!!
I'm...
I'm really happy!
But I love him too.
But I'm so happy now!
Myon, I'm not sure I get it,
but give me some time!
Give me a chance, please.
OK, Nishi! Give it your best shot!
You bet!
Nishi?
Nishi? Nishi!
Think I'm too young to marry?
Yeah.
So, you'll be off limits to future suitors!
Some are crying themselves to sleep right now.
Well I hope you'll be really happy.
Too bad... you don't like me
like you used to...
What are you talking about?
I love you forever!
You haven't changed.
You can be sure about that!
You want to eat yakitori?
Sure!
My sister and I have our own place!
Really?
Gotta make a living!
We've given up on the loans.
I'm gonna run forever!
Cool!
- Hi. Hey, Nishi!
- Hi!
Nishi! What a surprise! Come sit over here!
Thanks!
Long time no see!
Yang, today's special, and a beer.
Have a drink first!
What've you been up to?
Working on your Mangas?
Yes! Got a job on the side.
You're going to Tokyo, right? Tokyo's great!
Lots of good looking women trying to make it
in TV, modeling.
When I got married,
I often went there on business!
I'd get invited to hostess bars where there'd
be a bunch of girls like that.
And I'd pick one out and... yum yum!
Students promoting stuff on the streets,
game show assistants...
- Sir...
- They sure were hot!
- You cheated?
- I was having fun, but they'd fall for me!
I had quite a rep, five girls in Tokyo,
three in Osaka, those were the days...
- Don't listen to him!
- Sorry about this.
Meanwhile, these two popped out and...
- You don't sound too thrilled!
- Had to take care of them!
So that was it!
Y'know, if I'd gotten together with
that promo-girl...
I wouldn't be broke now.
Stop dreaming!
That's him.
Yep, dad hasn't changed at all!
His girlfriend's the same age as me!
Picked her up at a loanshark's office!
Riko? She's not quite on par with
the others though!
So you just forgot about her?
What a waste! Like keeping roses in the can!
- What?!
- Your wife! You didn't deserve her!
Why are you taking her side?
'Cause I love the women of the Uchida family!
You were surrounded by
three of the most beautiful women!
I even planned a trip
to your home town last year!
Thinking the place'll be
swarming with girls like them!
Had to see the source!
Myon, maybe you should marry Nishi.
You'd be happier that way.
What're you talking about?
You love him. You wrote about him
all the time when you were in school!
- Wrote what?!
- Oh, Nishi this, Nishi that, Nishi, Nishi...
Dad!!
Ryo's nice too! But I prefer Nishi!
Hi!
Ryo.
Sir?
Don't mind him!
This is Nishi.
This is Ryo!
Hi. Heard a lot about you! Pleased to meet you!
Same here.
Beer?
Yes!
Did you hear about Kenta's accident?
Yeah.
So please be careful.
Here Nishi!
Thanks!
You do Mangas, right?
Nishi promised to do one about me!
Yes, something naughty and sexy!
Can't wait...
Stop it!
Something nasty and kinky!
I wanna see that!
Good looking guy, great bod',
seems trustworthy...
But wasn't something a little...
...odd when you came in?
We were talking about ME,
'bout how I'm the one for Myon.
You're in the way pal, a third wheel,
can't you see it?
I shouldn't embarrass her by competing
with him. Don't want to make them feel awkward.
I'll get my truck on the 25th!
Congratulations.
Carries a 5 ton load! I'll be making money!
- You're a truck driver?
- Thanks.
I used to do things like that! Hard stuff!!!
Had no idea, Nishi.
Well, my body's all I've got going for me!
A real man alright...
Sensitive can mean neurotic. Women are
happier with these rough and simple types!
Nice smile too! I'm history. She's yours...
Hello...
Here...
It'll dry soon!
Something wrong?
Your beer...
Hey!!
- You know this guy?
- The owner!
He's off today! I'm only here part-time!
I'm not sure where he is. Sorry.
OK!
Settle down Atsu! We're gonna wait for him!
Right here...
I think he said he was taking
a couple of days off somewhere!
I knew it, off to a holiday resort!
With MY World Cup tickets, having fun.
Stop it! I'll call the police!
Say, you're kinda cute.
What the fuck are you doing you scum?
And who do you think you are?
Stop it!
Ryo!
Atsu, that's enough, put that piece away!!
I said put it away!
- What?!
- You don't know what's going on, bro!
I do.
No, you don't! My little Riko,
that old fuck, he...
He co-erced her!!
I know Atsu, but you don't mix business
with private stuff! We're professionals.
Y'know, I've been meaning to tell
you - you've got no taste.
Teen car, fag watch, just plain bad taste.
Me, I'm different, I'm a player!
Not a business man, but an artist!
Personal stuff IS my business!
Watch your mouth! You don't even know
the meaning of the word artist!
Oh... Atsu, sorry man,
didn't know you felt that way.
Do whatever you want!!!
I'm cool, it's just,
I get mad when I think about that guy!
Raping my Riko, keeping her locked in...
Yeah, well if you put it that way,
it's your call!
Say Atsu, can I add something?
NO!
Too bad he's out... he'd understand how I feel,
my hurt, my grief!!
If he sees ME raping HIS girlfriend right here!
I don't know this guy,
first time he comes in here.
Well it's true!
Bro, this bitch is lying!
You cunt!
They give it up so quickly!
All of 'em!
Wow, great boobs!
Don't move!
That's right, like that!
Shut the fuck up!
Say, those are sexy undies!
Kinda sparse down there, don't move,
show it to me!
Nishi, are you there?
Nishi?
Is he here? Where is he, this way?
This ball couldn't be him, now could it?
Where are you?
This you? Curled up like a ball?
You wanted some, didn't you?
Well, turn around, take a look at that pussy.
You know you want to!
Your turn after, amigo!
Come on, get up and get IT up!
I...
I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
Hurt you!
No way!
Ha! Did you hear that, gonna hurt you he said!
Put a bullet in him, on cue, just when he said
"hur!" Out the front before "t!"
Miserable loser!
That's not funny.
I was looking at you, you're gross!
What are you saying bro'?
Too gross. Don't move! You piss me off!
- I'm sorry, forgive me, please!!
- Don't move!
I'll do anything!!
ATTEN-TION!
Say "shit-pee-dick" 10 times. Very fast.
And add a kiss to the last one!
Bro'...
Add a kiss and I'll forgive you!
Shit-pee-dick... shit-pee-dick...
shit-pee-dick...
Er, Shit-pee-dick-smack!
You promised...!!
Think about what you did on your way to hell.
Sorry about the trouble,
but it's the owner's...
Ah, forget it!
I'll have a beer and a stick!
If I only had one of those magic time belts,
turn it back...
"RECAP"
"ANGER BAROMETER"
Nishi, are you there?
Where is he, this way?
This ball couldn't be him, now could it?
This you? You wanted some, didn't you?
Well turn around and...
I...
I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
I'm gonna hurt you!
- I'm
- No!
- Gonna
- Stop!
- Hurt You
- Stop, please!
"sucks, doesn't it?"
"lame, aren't you?"
"a fart, no?"
"snot?"
OK, I get it! I'm not cool!
I'm useless! And no fun!
"bird shit?"
I'm a snot, I know! So, stop this!
Stop! Stop!
STOP!!
Something's wrong with my eyes!
I keep changing, right?
You can't decide what I should look like!
Who are you?
You know! It's flickering there in your mind!
Come on, let it go.
What's the first thing that comes to mind?
"G-O-D"
G... God!!
There we are!
Not that how you call me matters!
A, B, they're just symbols anyway!
Confused? Wanna see my tits?
The only way to make it stop is to be honest.
Easier to see the truth that way!
The truth for you, that is!
Too late for counseling though.
Since you're DEAD! What a shame!
Dead... I'm... dead?
Really?
Just like that? Gone at 20?
Why was I born then?
So you could have fun at my expense?!
What's wrong with that, huh?
Yeah, so I made you on a whim!
I made you, dipshit, for my sheer enjoyment!
What's wrong with that?
Oops, I have to go!
- Got a date!
- A date?!
Time's up. Go straight that way
and keep walking. You'll soon disappear.
And my next life?
- Huh?
- Next life?
Your what? Told you it's over. Start walking!
And disappear? No afterlife? We're done?
It's really over?!
Really, really, really over?! God?
Will you shut up! You saw how you got here,
multiple p-o-v's of you brain exploding.
A shocking documentary of your death,
deftly edited by moi!
You are DEAD!
I'm officially dead?
Them's the breaks Nishi.
Straight ahead and disappear...
So if I go the other way...
Hey! What're you doing?! I'll be late!
Wait!
Let me through, I'm going back!
Not down for the count, huh?
You're gonna fade away, that's how it works.
See, you're already fading.
I don't believe you! I'm not gonna disappear!
I'm going back!
Won't happen!
I'll make it, I'll get there, you'll see!
Not bad, can you keep it up?
With that brain? Body?
I'm gonna take care of that creep.
Be stronger. Determined!! Free and happy!
Live life to the fullest!
Pretty good...
Alright give it your best shot!
YES! I'm going back! I'm gonna do this!
I'm on your side... I'm on your side...
Your turn after, amigo. Get up and get IT up!
Never... never...
Never again!
Don't move!
Yang, come here.
I'll blow your head off if you move,
I'm done being the loser!
Give me the car keys!
Nishi...
You're on your own sir, come on, let's roll!
Hey!
Get in!
Wait...
Atsu got wasted!
My fault... They're in my car, we'll get them.
My apologies!
Nishi, watch out!
Help!!
And a hero is born...
Hands on the wheel!!
Don't worry, I'm on it! I'll protect you!
I love you both!!
Moron, eyes on the road! Why are we running?
We should go to the police, self defense, right?
No! No! No! No cops, no questions,
no regrets! I'm through with that!
Making a break for it, with you two!
Like I want!
No one's gonna get in my way!!
I'm following my heart's desires!
Like an outlaw!
Hey, can you hear me?
I do hope you realize you were living
in paradise till today.
Like angels flying around in heaven.
But now you're on a super express to hell!
The guy you smoked, that bald S.O.B, Atsu?
Fine football player and athlete,
known as the Maradona of Osaka!
For good and for bad reasons.
Beautiful bod' like a wild animal!
Not that it has to do with anything.
You knew Atsu was packing,
that the car was full drugs,
money, you knew all that, you planned it.
A clear cut armed robbery and murder case.
His folks abandoned him,
he grew up without love!
Got tickets for the World Cup,
for him and his girl.
A model Japanese footie fan.
But just before the game,
a young guy like you puts out his light.
Ah, the ever-egocentric,
unfeeling youth of today!
Immature adults on the loose,
everything a blur except their friends.
Living life like a video game,
finger on the reset button!
You're a roller-coaster with no breaks.
It's not true, you're making it up.
Typical story, nice and easy
for the cops to follow!
What I'm sayin' is, nobody's on your side!
This is it, kids! Make it a good game!
Nice speech old man.
Will you stop it!
- I can see you sweating in front of a prompter!
- Nishi!
It's improv!
Sure!
What?!
This roller-coaster you're trying to stop
is a genuine Angel Express!
And I can see you moved to tears
as you watch that mystic angel...
...spread its wings and disappear into the sky.
The fuck?!
Fuck!
Nishi!
Offside!
Asshole, this ain't football!
Now get in as close as you can!
Offside-trap!
STUNT DRIVING!
My nose is bleeding!
Mine too!
The bridge!
What the fuck are you doing?!
My Pitch, my little pitch!
Pitch. You came back! Pitch!
No more fooling around.
We'll get 'em on the bridge.
Perfect defense plan. Even Zidane and Figo
couldn't get through. We'll get 'em.
Whale?
What, you again?!
Not just yet!
You there, Nishi?
Are we... dead?
You both there? Wait a sec...
Where is it?
Bingo!
We're alive...
Thank God!
Seawater? Can't see shit.
Near the harbour, maybe.
Smells fishy...
Have no fear!
Fear takes the shape we're willing to give it!
Let's light a candle in our hearts,
make it gleam.
Try to enjoy the moment!
In spite of this turn of events.
"This is FUN"
This will shed a new light on things!
Remember our days in grade school?
When it was all play,
no restrictions or tomorrows?
We didn't end up here 'cos we were chased!
We came here seeking adventure!
An epic journey!
Let the party begin!
Hey, there's a boat!
Let's check it out!
Lane No.1, Nishi! 3rd Grade! And I'm off!
Hey, let's go.
Lane No.2, Myon!
Also, 3rd Grade, and here I go!
Wow, what a wreck.
Where are we?
Stinks!
I'm starving! Good for my figure, though!
Your body is DOPE!
Which you haven't seen. I just look slim.
Show me then!
No way!
Please!
Nope!
Sugar on top!!
Nah!
- Aw, c'mon!
- Nishi! What now, huh?!
You almost got us killed!
Sure they were scum,
but you also popped a guy!
What's with the "enthusiasm?"
I was killed! Shot by that creep!
What the hell are you talking about?
He's the one that's gone dodo!
Before that. See, I was so scared
I lucked out on getting angry.
And that's when he shot me! Cueball mother!
Then I was sucked up to heaven and...
You've lost it.
But I believed in myself,
believed like nothing else, and I was back!
To live true to yourself,
sincerely, without restraint!
I realized it's the only weapon
against any wall!
OK, you've lost me.
But THIS is where it got us!
We're only here 'cos we were lucky!
It's a miracle we're alive!
But if this keeps up, we'll be dead in no time!
I... I...
I...
I've got... a radio!!
A radio?
This place is dangerous, we need to move!
Hurry! Hurry!
- What the fuck?!
- C'mon, hurry!
- What is this?
- An earthquake? A tsunami?
- You guys are reckless!
- The fuck, old man?!
Hurry up! Grab an ore and row!
- Tidal wave?
- Tsunami!
Move it, people!
Over there!
Almost there!
Hang on!
Meal time's over. We're OK now!
Let's go up!
Wow! It's like a top secret lair!
TV, microwave, audio set, PC,
you've got everything!
So they just washed up?
Ah, and food!
And sexy lingerie!! You dirty old man!
Let's see what's inside.
No power, huh?
This stuff's just for show, then?
Gross!
Think of it as modern art!
Want to freshen up?
Plenty of clean hot water?
- You mean have a bath?
- Yes! Yes!
I'd like that!
Yeah? Me too!
This is bliss!
But boy we're in some mess! It's surreal!
I mean, we're in God-knows-where
enjoying a total stranger's hospitality!
Having a bath... Unbelievable.
Well, he's on the way to a Happy Meal,
but he seems nice!
Once a perv, always a perv, huh?
I feel like it's the first time
we're having a real talk.
We'll leave clean clothes here!
Those bastards! Not very subtle are they?!
Let's pretend they're costumes!
Hey, find something we can actually wear!
Wow! Looks amazing!!
You made this?
Gramps?
Should've seen him at work!
Really? It's like a NY sushi bar!
Where'd you learn to cook, gramps?
Whoa!
Yeah, it's delicious!
Five stars in my book!
Bon appetit!!
Wow.
What a meal!
Thanks!
Much better than some fancy
rotating sushi bar in Kita.
They started serving
Westernized sushi last year.
Rotating sushi bars.
Rotating sushi.
Rotating sushi...
Not like that...
No, no.
In front of the customers.
Mines dead too!
It's a cell... phone?
A phone, a mobile phone?!
I knew it!
So, can we make contact with
the outside world??
Can't! It's soaked! Probably a goner!
So, um, do robots exist now?
I saw a robot isle at the hardware
store the other day!
Yeah?
Yes! I knew it!
- How about flying cars?
- Huh?
Hmm, how long have you been here exactly?
More than 30 years!
I had a big deal going down...
Hid my stash in a comic book case...
But I took the wrong one...
Coastguards and DEA knew all about it anyway.
Was running, lights flashing everywhere...
When a huge whale swallowed me!
Couldn't believe it.
And then what?
Got caught in the waves!
It was pitch dark when I came around!
Tried to escape but the waves were too rough!
"TIME BOY"
Tried again! And again.
I couldn't have survived without my friends.
Um, where's the toilet?
The washroom? Straight ahead! I'll take you!
Nah, it's okay! Straight ahead, right?
Oh my God.
Hey, keep talking!
- Where's the "exit?"
- All the way down there!
- Oh, right.
- But of course!
Back to square one!
Got to know your own limits!
We're outta here!
We can go this way.
It's wobbling!
It's the only way, c'mon!
It'll be alright!
You'll get killed!
He's hungry again!
Hurry!
Come back.
Wait!
- The water's coming!
- Nishi!
There! The exit!
Put these on!
Nishi! Come back!
Nishi!
Hey, let go of me!
What the...?!
Nishi, you're awake!
What a relief! He's come around!
And here's something to cheer you up!
And a "Happy Mornin" to y'all!
Wow, is this a beautiful day or what?
You wouldn't believe how blue the sky was
this morning.
In line with the solar system is...
Thought I'd drive
all the way to Brazil, y'know?
Well, it's gonna be booming
at the resorts today!
Certainly not a day for school
or work, I tell ya!
Now, now, now...
C'mon, cheer up!
You're homesick, I've been there.
I cried and got angry too.
But I realized after coming here...
Oh, whatever.
Got an idea! There's a place
that'll cheer you up.
Great friends too!
Let's go! Everybody!
So wrecked cars are popping up everywhere!
Must've been some monster car chase...
You haven't eaten properly in three days!
You're not gonna last that way!
You need to eat for your breasts' sake!
And Nishi, you've eaten nothing!
Forget about getting it up!
Hey!
Just shut up, okay?
Gramps, will you take me to that fun place
you mentioned about?
Wanna go? It'll be fun!
I need a change!
That's the spirit! You'll love it!
Nishi?
You too!
Nah... count me out!
It'll be fun! You can meet my friends too!
Hearts'll soar!! Heads'll explode!
Cut it, Gramps! I'm not in the mood!
Just leave me alone!
Join us later if you feel like it, okay?
Let's go, Myon.
Let's go, let's go!
This'll be a blast!
You'll love my friends.
Fuck!! The look on his face!
He doesn't have a clue!
I only said those things
'cos he was being inconsiderate!
How about a little kindness, huh?
I'm hurt!
I have doubts about humanity!
What about my start in Manga?!
What about my glorious campus life, huh?!
Asshole!
Loser!
"Help me God I'm sorry"
30 years... 30 years...
Gotta drink your milk, honey!
30 years...