I surrender!
If you were brave enough
to ask me playing soccer,
why did you surrender?
Do you play and loose with me?
I can't stand for it anymore.
My bone seems broken.
I'm the pitiful creature!
Please let me go to see a doctor!
Put it onto your head!
You see. You look like a dog.
Do you have any self-respect?
I don't want to see you.
Put it onto your head quickly
and go to see a doctor.
Yes, I'm a dog.
I don't have any self-respect.
First Big Brother is coming back.
What?
I've a feeling that they are back.
- Do we still have any weapons?
- No more!
The final attack!
Oh, my God! I couldn't get it.
Help!
Thank you! You make us
to get our kung fu back.
Thanks for coming back!
Thank you!
Don't be like this.
I'm the real one who needs
to thank for all you guys.
Oh, my God!
I'm going to be rich! Thank you!
We're failed.
Please give us an opportunity...
...to join into your team!
Please!
Please, give us a chance.
It's a pretty big exploration.
The Evil Team'll be
the champion in the world.
Who?
The lame?
- Why not?
- I'm sorry.
I've already played
soccer for many years,
- You want to stop me?
- The person in charge is not here now.
Golden Leg!
What are you doing?
- Hung!
- Hung, he...
Okay...
Hung, my team wants to sign it up
for the soccer game!
It's an open competition,
everyone has the right to sign up.
You're wrong.
I'm the chairman.
I've the right to decide
who can sign it up.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
What's the name of your team?
Come on!
This is Hung.
Hung!
This is a rare soccer team!
I really want to watch them
playing soccer.
What's the name again?
This is Shaolin...
OK...
Go and sign it up quickly.
I really want to watch them.
If you need, I can pay
for your application fee.
Thank you!
It's okay! You guy, the lame,
is my friendly brother.
My shoe is dirty again.
White color is easy to get dirty.
So...
I help you to clean it up!
I'm good at cleaning. Let me try!
This is my duty!
Hey! Let me try!
Hi!
What are you doing?
Who are you?
Where do we go?
Why are you so quiet? I need to go home.
I'm waiting for a long time.
I'm sorry. Please, wait a moment.
Try this.
No. I just want to see the quality of it.
Touch it.
I'll make it dirty.
- No problem. Go ahead.
- No...
- Touch it.
- No.
- How about that?
- So smooth.
- I promise I'll buy one for you.
- I touched it already. It's enough.
Tomorrow, I'll go to play soccer.
Really?
I must become a famous star player.
But if you didn't
help me to repair them...
I would never play soccer.
You know, you're so important to me.
Tell me what you want.
I can pay for you very soon.
If you become rich and famous,
please buy me sneakers.
No problem!
But you should have confidence.
Actually, you're a beautiful girl
good at kung fu.
You know, you are perfect.
You can't let your hair down
and cover your face like this.
Come on.
- Come on. Look at me.
- No...
Look at me!
So beautiful!
Really?
Yes, of course.
Is it fly?
Yes. But I didn't catch it.
Did you catch it already?
I did.
I'm sorry. I make your hand dirty.
No problem.
You know, you're the most beautiful girl.
Do you know that?
Yes. I do.
Thank you! Thanks so much!
Do you know?
Where you go?
I let you bring a girl here because
you promised me to clean the store.
Hurry up! If you haven't finished
the work on time, I'll be in trouble.
Go home. I'll call you later.
Okay?
Remember! You should have confidence.
You're the best.
I like your shirt.
I like your socks, too.
- Let's exchange to wear.
- Good...
Hey, guys! Didn't you
ever see this occasion?
Just play as usual as training.
There'll be hundreds of reporters
and audiences outside.
You guys should keep smile...
...and let the reporters
take pictures with us.
You also need to say hi and
thank for the audience's support.
Thank you!
Thanks for your support!
They're just cleaners.
Cleaner is also the audience.
Thank you!
Shut up!
This auditorium is so small and empty.
You said...
This is just the first round.
So we should play well
and get into the finals.
- Great! Get into the finals!
- Shut up!
Shaolin Team?
Look at this guy!
Look at that guy!
What happened?
No smoking here?
It's impossible! Just an illusion!
What are you doing?
It's okay, just an illusion.
I think we should
show off our real power.
Great!
What's wrong?
Please don't play like this!
I really want to play soccer!
Hung, it's your call.
I'm not scared. It's just an illusion.
What? Forty versus zero?
Yeah!
Got a goal! Iron Head!
Yes, we use Shaolin kung fu
to play soccer.
So kung fu is great, wonderful!
- We lie low...
- And...
I want to thanks for my parents
and my Shaolin master.
Even though they passed away already.
I want to thanks for my good friend, Mui.
Mui... How are you?
Did you have your dinner already?
Hi! Can I help?
I want...
I understand. Let me take care of you!
Would you mind show us your kung fu?
Yes, of course, Sixth Small Brother.
1, 2, 3!
Great!
Can you show us one more?
- Sure!
- Big Brother, one more please.
Take it easy!
My Brothers,
today we say bye with our old sneakers.
Don't throw anything here!
Sorry...
Mui?
What's up?
I can't believe
you are this kind of preson.
What is it?
I know what you are doing.
What? You are bad.
You can't frighten me.
I'm not afraid of ghost.
What do you mean?
Nothing. It's for you.
I think...
I think I've a little bit difference.
Truly.
You've confidence right now.
I want to tell you something.
What's up?
I like you!
I like you, too!
Is this love?
You...
You're kidding.
No. I'm serious.
Absolutely not. This is not love.
We're friends forever...
Don't you think it's good for us?
Okay! It's fine.
So you'll come to see me often?
If your shoes are broken,
I'll help you to repair them again.
No, thanks. If my shoes are broken,
I must throw them away.
We should look forward to our future.
I'll never wear any broken shoes.
Don't be like this.
What's wrong? You're crying?
Don't do this.
I understand.
Thank you!
Come here!
- Mui, you are very nice today.
- Cheers!
After winning this,
we'll go to the finals.
Go to the finals!
But we can't look down our opponent!
Look down our opponent!
We're the real powerful team.
I won't let you get into the finals.
Oh, my God! How come?
It's the special effects?
Good morning, Hung!
Good morning!
Come here!
You're a lucky guy.
You're so lucky to get this great team.
Thank you.
Actually, Iron Head and Iron Shirt
are sorts of performance on the street.
It's amusing for your guys
to use kung fu to play soccer
and then to get into the finals.
You did a good job.
Don't waste our time!
Give up the finals
and join into my Evil Team!
It's not a dishonour check.
You can get the money
before sign up with me.
It's lots of money.
Probably, I can break my left leg
and then get retired.
Sure! We're brothers.
Thank you.
But I think I can't take it.
What? Don't you think I'm afraid of you?
I think your team has great potential.
So maybe we can join together.
Don't be so easily upset.
Think about your future.
Forget the hostility. Okay?
Hung, I didn't keep
the hostility in mind.
I know, they were all my faults.
I couldn't blame anyone.
You're lying!
I know you much. You're so greedy!
You're right!
I'm so greedy. My team is greedy, too.
But we've not
an insatiable greed for money.
We've an insatiable greed
for the champion.
See you on the soccer field.
Wait! Wait for a moment! Thank you!
Mui!
She died already!
How come?
I killed her!
Oh, no!
Mui is the master-hand of Tai Chi.
She must be treated unjustly!
What do you want?
Revenge!
Don't be silly! It's just a joke!
She's still alive.
She just doesn't work here.
Why?
You know, my stalling store
is well-known of sweet steamed bread.
But now the steamed bread...
she made becomes salty and bitter.
She really ruins my business.
I don't have another choice.
Salty and bitter?
Yes.
What's your name? Can I help?
No, thanks.
It's time to go!
Boss, how many goals
do you expect to get today?
Getting goal is not the only way to win.
I've a great idea to get win.
Impossible.
I can't imagine how wonderful
of the American medication!
Actually the referee, linesman,
soccer association, soccer federation
and soccer committee...
all stand on my side.
How can they fight with me?
No problem!
- Great!
- Fit!
Wonderful!
Throw-in?
He did it on purpose.
How could you judge to be throw-in?
Hung, you're fighting or playing soccer?
Yes, we are. So what?
I should break all you guys' legs
and let you become cripples.
Cripples! Cripples! Cripples!
How dare you fight with me?
I'm sorry. I should take a break.
It's okay. You just physically leave us,
but your spirit
will keep in our mind forever.
Bend over! It's my turn.
Sixth Small Brother!
What's wrong? Why don't you stop it?
All you guys are badly injured
after the first half match.
How can you play the second one?
Go home! It's no way for you guys
to play the second half!
Nothing interested!
Maybe I can go down to dance for a show.
No! It's not your turn. It's mine!
Bullshit!
Get out!
You guys don't want to play anymore!
Who did it?
Anyone saw it?
Hit my face, if you're brave enough!
Rub gently.
I can't imagine
they're much lawless than me.
I can't believe that...
my reputation was ruined.
I've already known that
they must do something for us,
but I can't imagine they are so cruel.
Evil Team is not so terrific.
They must take pills or have injection.
Call police!
Anyway,
we should try our best to keep going.
We'll get the final win!
My house is on fire, I need to run!
I'm sorry. My mom is
per mature birth right now.
I should go home to take care of her.
Can you ask her to wait
until the end of the game?
You can't give it up!
They're not playing soccer.
They're killing us!
I beg you. Please don't leave us!
I beg you back.
Please let me go!
Calm down!
Yes, he's right!
We should keep going.
Now, we just have eight players.
If there is one more injured,
we'll fail.
We must try our best
to fight for the killer kick.
How come? If you fight for
one killer kick, I'll fight for three.
What are you talking about?
Calm down!
Shut up!
I'm not sure if I can fight for it.
Shaolin Lou Han Array!
Array?
Can't stand for a shot!
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine!
Chun!
- Tin?
- Yes.
I've kept a secret
in my mind for many years,
but I really want
to tell you at this moment.
Chun, I love you!
Do you think if we're so cruel?
- I don't think so!
- Really?
So we can be harsher.
Brothers! Go!
What?
Be careful!
Watch out!
Shit!
Hurry up! Don't act injured!
You're so smart! I'm fine.
Time is almost out! Use the final attack!
Final attack?
It's useless for you guys...
...to stall for time.
Win!
Shaolin Team.
Now, you just leave seven players.
If you don't have any substitute players,
I'll stop the game...
and announce that the game's over.
Any substitute players?
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
My turn!
I'm the substitute player.
I'm the goalkeeper.
Why did you make up as E.T.?
I don't know how to cut my hair,
so it will be good for me to shave it.
For what?
I want to help you.
How can you do that?
Go back to the Mars,
the Earth is so dangerous.
I really want to help you.
Trust me! Let me try!
- No way!
- You see,
your shoes were broken.
Put these on.
The opposite side.
Go!
Great!
Watch out!
What happened?
Boss, watch out?
Damn it!
Boss!
Shaolin win the champion.
Evil team use drug permenant suspension.
Leader Hung was sent 5 years in jail.
Wait! Stop it!