Good morning grandma
good morning dad, good morning mom
Man Fai, how dare you
Sister
You can't fool her They've all gone out
Wo
Miss Man Fai, today's the day
Don't you dare
Got to go
Man Fai, practise your music at home
I'll teach you English when I come back
And don't go out, alright
We don't want trouble from grandma
She doesn't want you to be seen on the street
I hear you
Let's go
Wo, we are off to school
See you
Miss Man Fai, mind the steps
How do I look My clothes
Pretty in pink, very cheerful
Let's go then
Miss Man Fai, alright, hold on to me
Mind the steps
Wo, why even bother
San, stuff it
Look at her
What a baggage to tuck along
It's embarrassing
What did they say
Nothing, it's just noise
Careful now
Hold my arm, we're on a big road
Are there lots of
trees and birds around
Yes, now that you mention it
Actually, there are trees on both sides
Really
They block the sun, I take this
road to the market everyday
I smell cooking
That's right
it's the smell of soya sauce
What is the color of this smell
Soy is black
and the colour of the smell
Is the color of soy
Stand here stay still
What is that
It sinks
It's a motor car
Careful
What is that
A bicycle
Just remember, stay out of their
way They can run you over
Why the car stinks and
the bicycle doesn't
The motor farts all the time
that's why it stinks
Price gone up again
Inﬂation When the civil war breaks out
we'll have nothing to eat
Alright, I've have a piece
It's a puppy That's right
Miss Man Fai, squat down
and touch it Sure
Just what you need, Miss
When it grows up, it can be your guide
Let's go, forget about him
You want it, Miss Blind
Shut you face, you dog
Miss, be careful
There you go
Are you blind I want liver
not the knuckle
My fault
Sit here, be careful
Have a piece of cake
What's up Are you still angry
How do you know
I can tell from your face
My face Sure
When you are happy, you are like this
When you are angry
you are like this
I can tell at once
When you are happy
you look really good
Wo, I wish I could see
just like you
Miss Man Fai
actually you can see too
Only you see in a different way
We see with our eyes
and you see with your hands
I don't always see clearly
But you can see through
things with your heart
She's blind
Stop it Hey you Get lost
Have you any manners
Don't you have parents
Don't you kid know anything
Scrum bags
Go away Get lost
She must have done something
bad in her previous life
Her dad's got crabs
No, I can't do that
Mother, this isn't such a good idea
I don't understand your thinking
I said long ago she should
earn to play music
If you've listened, she would
have a skill to make a living
Mother, we can't force Man Fai
to be an entertainer
She can make a living by herself
Better than being a burden, forever a
burden to her brother &amp; sister
This is for her own sake too
I'll buy her a ﬂat
she can live off the rent
Wake up Civil war has
broken out in the North
I see hard times ahead
Mr. And Mrs. Ching, why not let
your girl be a songstress
There are famous masters in Fu Shan
If she gets famous
the family can be proud
I've already taken the deposit
Mother
No, don't sell me off Man Fai
Mom, I beg you
Trust me, mom won't sell you off
Man Fai, how dare you How dare you eardrop on us
Grandma, I beg you I don't want to sing
Take her to her room
Calm down
What'll we do now
Wo Madam
How dare you Who said you could take her out
You want the whole world to know she's blind
You want the whole family to be a laughing stock
Madam, it's my fault I didn't
know what's best for Miss Man Fai
But, Madam
Please don't sell
her off to Fu Shan,
Enough...
Madam, I better go
Mom, I beg you Silly girl
be good, come on, sit down
You shouldn't have done that
You mustn't contradict grandma
Grandma will be very angry
Don't sell me off please
I promise I won't
Am I a burden to you
Why does grandma hate me so much
She is the head of the family...
She can be kind
Just like...
When I married you dad,
She drank my tea minutes
after I knelt down
Sure, many brides had to
kneel much longer
Mom, I am scared
I am afraid you and dad
will dump me sooner or later
Man Fai, Iwill take care
of you as long as I live
I just worry that
we would die before you
You'll be all alone
I only hope we can outlive you...
so you'll always be taken care of
Mom
I must have done something
bad in my previous life
Your misfortune is my punishment
Look, how bright is the moon
It's just like the
Mid Autumn Festival
Wo, what were the street
kids saying today
They didn't mean anything
No, mother also said
something about punishment
Why am I blind
I don't know
Yes you do No, I don't
You brought me up, Wo...
Right
So, you must know
I... I do, but I can't tell you
If I tell you
your grandma will be mad at me
No, she won't, please tell me
If I tell you
don't hold it against your parents
I won't
You weren't blind when you were born
You looked so lovely
You loved staring at the lights
When you were 6 months' old
your mom took you to hometown
One day, your eyes
got all blood shot
Your mom took you to
a local herbal doctor
Don't worry, just a ﬂu
Drop 6 times a day
She will recover in 4 days
Man Fai...
What's the matter
Look, her eyes Man Fai
Bring her to the doctor at once
Doctor, how is she
What's wrong with her eyes
The optical nerves were all damaged
She wouldn't be able to see anymore
Man Fai...
Had I died then, mom wouldn't be so miserable now
You're being silly
I mean it If I die, everyone will be happier
If you die, I'll be shattered
Wo
Why do you love me so much
I owed you in my previous life
What's previous life
Previous life is...
previous life
B... I... R... D... Bird
How many new words
have you learnt
Brother taught me
ﬂower and bird
What
I am so happy
Let's see
It weights a tael
A present from my boss
Lucky you, a gold chain on
your little master's birthday,
may he have many birthdays then
Yeah
And not like Wo, stuck with
that blind girl for good
I am not called Blind Girl
I have a name
Miss Man Fai, good morning
Wo said she is happy with me around
Wo is getting old, she can't
take care of you forever
Without her, you will be miserable
My mom said...
You folks will die, your brothe
and sister will get married
My dad will buy me a house
I can live off the rent
In time of war
a house can be tombed out
Money will depreciate
And you can get sick too
Accept it, it's your fate
Your grandma is right, why not...
I want to study, I want to
make a living on my own
I want to study
Leave her alone
she won't understand
I worry about Wo What a weird
child she is serving
I go to school
S-C-H-O-O-L School
So Still not working
Stay still...
Why doesn't it work
Got it
Miss Man Fai
I got some newspaper for you
Little master, do you want to
get the station in Philippines
No, he wants to get the radio in Shanghai
Really But it's far
we're in Canton
They're pretty
This is from Hong Kong
These are for you
Thank you, mom
This is for Man Fai
It's nice
What color is it Red
Is it a happy color
Red is happier than pink
Hold on, keep this for her cousin,
wouldn't matter
what colour for Man Fai
Come on
keep that for Man Fai
We don't want it
save it for others
Who do you think you are
Queen of the maids
Think you're grandma
Wo, don't be angry
Why are you laughing
Your mom said, Who do you think
you are My mother-in-law
What's that like
Wo, you're so nice, were you
blind in your previous life
Madam
You're right, keep this for Man Fai
Man Fai, I'll get the tailor to
make you some new clothes
Thank you, mom
Got it... I've got it
How is it
Come on...
What are they doing
They are dancing
I want to dance too
Brother, sister...
Dad What are you doing
Man Fai, come with me
we're taking you out
Let me come with Miss Man Fai
You stay Dad
What are you doing
Where are you taking her
What's this You think
lam going to sell her
Will this work
I hope so, the doctor is from England
He may have a cure
How is it, doctor
The tissue of her eyeballs
are totally damaged
Can that be cured
We are testing comeas transplant
But it's not yet fool-proof
Rickshaw man
Go back with Man Fai ﬁrst
I've got work in the ofﬁce
Be careful...
Dad Thank you
But the doctor said you
couldn't be cured
I know, and I know you care
Go
Stop...
Man Fai, what's the matter
Mom, listen
What is this place
Pui Tao Girls School
Look at the blackboard
What is blackboard
Teacher writes on blackboard with chalk
I want to go to school, I want to learn
Child, it's no use
You can't read from the blackboard
You can never go to school
Mom, I promise
I will never mention about studying again
Move, please
P-A-I-N-T-I-N-G. ..
Miss Man Fai, let's go...
No, I haven't ﬁnished my lesson
Go home now Come on
Are there delinquents around
No, let's go...
Go...
What's up Go
What's the matter
Oh my shoe
Sit down
I will ﬁnd a shoe smith to mend it
Here is a whistle
If anyone bully you, blow it
The police will hear you and
I will hear you Understand
I will be right back
Miss Man Fai
Stop, I am a good man
I like Wo very much
I am the meat vendor
Wo comes to the market everyday
Over time, I got fond of her
She... She has this spell on me
Miss Man Fai, Wo loves you very much
Say something nice about me
in front of her
She is coming back
Miss Man Fai, please help me
The name is Kan, thank you
Miss, it's ﬁxed, put it back on
Are you alright
I am ﬁne
Let's go then
If we're late, grandma will ﬁnd out
Let's go...
It's late, go to bed
It's only 10:30
WoWhy didn't we have pork tonight
I wasn't in the mood to buy any today
Do you want portk
No, but the pork wishes you to buy it
What did that good-for-nothing say
He didn't say anything to me
Don't you try lying
He said he misses you every day
and you drive him crazy
Nonsense Tell him to drop dead
Do you ever think of getting married
If I wish to get married,
I would have married years ago
There was a famine in my village
We were starving
For money, my step mother forced
me into this marriage
Only my husband turned out to be...
I escaped Canton to be a maid
I swear I would never marry
And I don't want to leave you
Even if you get married
I will go with you
I won't marry, let's never marry
This one... that one is better
Whatever you say
What would you like
Wo, whatever you want, you get
No, what do you want
I want you
Listen, leave me alone
I chatted with you before...
just to get a better
bargain from you
Stop dreaming
I won't get married
Alright So be it
Wo, what's that singing
here is a girl over there
she is blind, too
Miss Man Fai, what's up
Mister, Madam, I've sung two songs
Have pity on me
I just want thirty cents
If I don't get it
my master will scold me
Mister, I beg you...
Get lost
Wo, do you have thirty cents
Give it to her
Alright, Here Forty cents
Thank you Madam
I am just a maid
Thank you Madam Maid
Are you alright
She is Miss Man Fai
Thank you Madam Miss
What's your name
I'm Blind Girl
No, you're not
Don't ever let others
call you Blind Girl
Although we can't see...
we can't let others call
us Blind Girl
Us Give me your hand
No, 40 cents are plenty for me
Come on, we're the same
Show her your hand
Why's your hand so cold
Are you sick
I haven't eaten for two days
It's raining, let's go over there
Follow me, be careful, follow me
Come over here... Hold the tree
Wo, go get something for her to eat
Alright, don't leave here
Why are you afraid
It's just raining
What's your name
I was called Jade
When I was ﬁve
I became blind after a fever
My dad said a blind person is useless
So he never called me Jade
You have a dad
Not anymore
I remembered that day, my dad
took me to Canton by train
After we got off
he had me walk in front of him
Without him in front I kept falling
He didn't help me
just told me to keep walking
We walked for hours
Then dad said he would get me
food and asked me to wait
He told me not to move
OthenNise the police would
take me to feed the tigers
I was so scared
Then he went off
It was raining heavily
just like now
I stood there
I dared not move nor speak
I waited and waited
At last, I fainted
My dad never came back
Come on, have some cake Go on
My master adopted me and
taught me to sing
Madam Miss
Jade, just call me Man Fai
I wish I would be half as lucky as you
Wo, the rain has stopped
let's take Jade home for dinner
No, if master and madam ﬁnd out
I'd be in trouble
You can think of a way
What way
I know you can
No way...
You can... Let's go
Man Fai, it's not good
How dare you not be earning your living
You're so useless
Stop that
What do you want
Miss likes her singing, so we asked
her to stay, So what
Master... Here are 40 cents
40 cents
And, we want her to sing for
our family tomorrow
If she sings well, she will get paid well
Sure, she will come tomorrow...
tomorrow
Jade... Jade...
Be careful
Keep your voice down
Jade...
Go inside ﬁrst, go in
Take Jade to my room
Don't let them ﬁnd out
Come on, Jade, go to my room
MomYou scared me to death
You scared me to death
What's going on
Wo, who is she
She is... She is a beggar
Miss Man Fai took pity
on her, so... How dare you
Don't send her away
she is my friend
Fﬁend
My very ﬁrst friend
Well... Wo, give her a bath ﬁrst
Alright Go now
A bath, from head to toe
Alright
Get Man Fai's clothes for her
Alrigh
Wo, give my happy pink dress to her
Alright
Where is Grandma
She went to the temple
won't be back until tomorrow
Go to the kitchen
get something for her to eat
Thank you, madam
You're a good girl
Come on, I will take you to the garden
WoMark the cutlery that she used
Don't mix up with ours
Yes
And... next time when she comes
let her use the marked ones
Yes, Madam Don't forget
Yes
Here is the table, Jade
sit down
Miss Man Fai, have some fruit
I'll leave you two
Alright
Jade, have an apple
I never have apple before
It's delicious
It's got skin
Never mind, you can eat that too
it's nutritious
Delicious
Yes
Starting from tomorrow,I'll teach
you English point alphabet
No, I don't know English at all
Why don't I teach you sing
it's easier
Once you learn to sing others will
want you to sing for money
I won't sing in front of other people
I want to study, it's safer
Only ifl sing well will I be safe
I need to beg, so my master won't beat me
Be brave, I will teach you
a point alphabet each day
Let's do this
From tomorrow onwards,
I work hard in singing
And you work hard in studying
What's wrong
I swallowed a seed
It doesn't matter, it's tiny
You ate the skin too
Poor thing Your tongue must be sore
I don't know
It's lychee
I'm so sorry Jade
Never mind, it's delicious too
Only it's a very big seed
What took you so long
Blind Girl, where are you going
Just shut your mouth
You'd be blamed
We are going to
Pui Tao Girls School...
You mean she's going to school
No, I mean to the back of the school
Go now
Sure
Here we're, stop...
Miss Man Fai, let's get out
Be careful, take a big step...
Thirty cents, keep the change
That's the tips from Miss
Thank you, Miss
Let's go
Sit here
I am going to the market
I'll be back soon
You go along, I've a class to go to, too
Slow down please
Who is it
Don't be afraid
I am Miss Leung of this school
I'm going to bring a book
I'm going to bring something
I'm going to
They read too fast, I can't catch up
It's incredible You know so many English words
Every night, my brother &amp
sister would teach me English
What about English point alphabet
They won't know that
It's God God granted it to me
I mean it
Amateur radios, pay attention
This is CY station from Canton
please answer if you hear me
Please answer...
Amateur radios, pay attention please...
No answer
Let me try in Mandarin
Amateur radios, please pay attention
Silly girl, this is the antenna
This is CY Station from Canton calling
I've a blind sister
I am Ching Man Fai
I wish to know how a blind can read
Speak in Mandarin
My sister wants to know how
a blind can read
Yeah...
If you receive our message
please contact us
This is CY Station
Master, does it work
Sure, I made contact with Hong Kong once
But only America has schools for the blind
Brother, is America very far away
Yeah, but we should still try
Yes, God will show us a miracle
What's this
It's the Bible
Let's pray, then God will
show us a miracle
God, please grant us a miracle
God, please help me...
Miracle
Let's go
Why are you stay up so late
Man Fai, how naughty you're
Madam, be careful
Station, pay attention, CY Station
pay attention
Someone is talking
CY Station, pay attention
Here is CY Station
Here is DV Station
You've a blind little sister
haven't you Yes
I'm an American doctor
I live in Manila
I can't cure your sister's illness
But I can write to USA &amp
ask them to send you information
Please give me your address
We are Chinese, we live in Canton
Ground Floor, Number 18
Wai Oi Road, West
Who wants to open it
This is sent to Man Fai
Man Fai, you open it
Go ahead
It's so tightly wrapped
Sure, the sender is a doctor, isn't he
Professional practice, that's all
Let me help
What is this
Just like a carrot slicer
It's got many tiny holes on it
Also an awl and a wooden pad
And a card too
With English letters on the card
They are all pointed alphabets
For two &amp; three, there are 6 marks
for four, there are 7 marks
I got it Me too I don't
The blind can't see, but they can touch
But they are pointed
What an idea
Miss Man Fai
You scared me, where have you been
Wo, she is Miss Leung
Ching Man Fai, I'll do my best to
get our principal's consent...
for you to study in this school
But, you may have a hard time
I am not afraid of that
Me too
Miss Leung, if you are willing
to teach her,
I will worship you like kitchen god
Is she really that nice Yes
Let me tell dad and mom
No
Why
They won't agree
Dad won't let me study, the school fee is expensive
Miss Man Fai, don't worry
I will pray for you, alright
Can you pray for me
Sure
I know God better
You tell me, and I tell him
that's alright
Do you remember last time
We prayed and you learnt
point alphabets
Sister, will God love a blind too
Sure For God love all of us
Did the Bible say why some
of us are blind
Is it because I did something
wrong in my previous life
Isn't it
Wait, let me read the Bible now
It's mentioned here, listen
Jesus said the blind didn't
commit any sins
Their parents didn't commit
any sins either
But God wants to show the
glory of God through them
What's the glory of God
Give me a minute
Mother Master, Madam
What's the matter
You'd better ask her
Wo Did you bring a blind girl
to play with Man Fai everyday
Speak up
Not everyday, just a few days
Who told you to do that
This is not her fault
So, is this your fault
This is my fault
I brought her to see Miss Man Fai
What made you do so
I just want her to know more friend
You asked a beggar to be her friend
The neighbours are all
laughing behind our backs
Wo, were you blind in your previous life
Why are you always protecting the blind
Ask Man Fai to come out
She has gone to her friend
The blind girl again
No, a new friend
She went by himself
No, she went with her brother and sister
What new friend
A foreigner
What foreigner
Jesus Christ
Yes
Oh my God
She goes to church to pray
for Jesus's help
What
To bless her and make her
hope come true
What hope
Is Ching Man Fai here
I'm looking for Ching Man Fai
God loves me
What took you so long
That teacher from Pui Tao
Girls School was just here
She agreed to let Man Fai study
for three months
Is that true Oh my God
God loves me...
Bible always tells us...
Dad, please let me study
This is a rare chance
You can't see, you can't read
from the blackboard
How can you catch up
I can be her tutor at night
I can read the books to her
So what She is still blind
Grandma
She should have gone to learn singing
Dad, I beg you
Dad, let Man Fai go to school
Please let Man Fai study
Why can't you understand
Inﬂation is spiralling
My boss already left here for good
I may soon be jobless
you still want to study
I don't have money for you to study
Master I have money
Master, I think this should be
enough for her to graduate
Where have you got so much money
You must have cheated from
the grocery expense
This is my entire saving in 20 years
I want it to be Miss Man Fai's dowry
I think it's better
to let her study, right
Miss Man Fai What's wrong
Hush Hush, don't cry
Miss Man Fai is going to school
In the future
if you want to do anything
Just go ahead if you think it's right
I will support you always
Be good
Have you seen Jade
Tell her the good news
How come no answer
Jade and her master live here
Just call out loud
Jade...
Jade
Hey
Hey what I have a name
The blind girl left already
Where did she go Hey you
Miss Wo
Brother Kan, where have they gone
One-eye Ying took her to Kwangsi
They left minutes ago
Go chase them
It's all your fault
Why were you so nice to her
One-eye Ying was afraid of losing Jade
Your good intention hurts Jade more
Hurry up Hurry up...
Jade
Miss Man Fai, there they are
Jade...
We can't catch them up
Miss Leung
Good morning
Come on, Man Fai
Miss Man Fai School bag
Teacher is coming, back to your seat
Stand up Bow Sit down
Lesson six, turn to page 49
We are going to learn a poem
Pay attention to the blackboard
I'll write the name of the poet
This lesson is over, raise your
hand if you have a question
Look, her eyes are disgusting
Yeah, it's watery
How can she study in our school
Don't be nosy, let's go
Hello
I sit behind you
and your head block my sight
Can we switch seats...
since you can't see
Man Fai, you are back
Grandma, dad, mom
Can you follow the lessons
Yes, the lessons are ﬁne
How about your classmates
They are all very nice to me
Tell us more
Come on, tell us more
I am really happy
I understand everything the teacher said
the classmate are nice
They teach me mathematics
we play together during recess
They all sit around me
Miss Man Fai
I am really scared
I don't know how big
the classroom is
I worry I would mistake
another's seat as mine
Without you, I don't know
what is around
They said I could never
catch up with them
They all treat me as a blind peron
Miss, have you forgotten
your old friend
Who
Jesus Christ
I really hope he would be with me
He is a VIP He is busy
He always go here and there
right
And he said, you've to
solve your own problems
What can I do
Tomorrow, go and chat
with your classmates
If you are nice to them
they wouldn't reject you
They said my eyes were watery
and awful looking
Wait
Miss Man Fai, be careful... Sit...
Don't move, try this on, don't move
What's this
It is wonderful
It is your dad's sunglasses
Wear it, and you'll look different
Really
Yeah, wear this tomorrow
Pretend you can see them...
but they can't see you
Since they can't see your eyes
they won't look down on you, Right
May be
Miss, actually you're very pretty
No
You see, kindness is what counts
Kind people are the best looking people
Wo, you're so kind, you must be pretty
Miss Man Fai, remember what I told you...
I am Ching Man Fai, can I play with you
Sure Alright
Ching Man Fai
Canton to be Liberated
War again
What is the 8th Route Army
Students, go back to the classrooms
What's liberation
Go back to classrooms
No, I can't act No
Don't be afraid, you don't have to move
Just sit and be the king
Yeah, you only have to sit
That's pretty
Alright, let's rehearse
In front of His Majesty
I testify against your crime
Alright, let's have a duel in front
of His Majesty Come on
Do I have to say any line
That hurts
I didn't mean it
This is for real
Stop...
Are you rehearsing or not
In the name of the Emperor
I order you to stop ﬁghting
Attention, attention...
Since the situation may
become unstable,
the school will be closed
until further notice
All students should go
home immediately
It's war
What'll we do
How am I to go home
Students, civil war has
spread to Canton
Air attack may be launch any time
Go home immediately
Man Fai, what're you...
I am waiting for Wo
she will come and pick me up
Miss Man Fai... Wo
Let's hurry
Why are you sitting here Let's go
When did you become an emperor
My subordinates have all gone home
You've to run too
Your dad is taking us to Hong Kong
He is packing up at home
Let's go...
Let's go, Your Majesty
Follow me
Miss Man Fai, be careful
Wo, where have you been
Come and help
Man Fai, pack up quickly
we have to go
Take only the important
things with you
We are leaving, follow us
Forget the books
Wo, take her with you
No, I've to take my books
to Hong Kong
You can't We don't have
any empty space
My homework, where is my homework
Be careful...
I will take it for you
Man Fai, here is your homework
I am taking it for you
Thank you, brother
Miss, how are you
I feel dizzy
Just hang on, let's go
Let me help you, be careful
Be careful, walk slowly
The job interview, how did it go
What are you doing
What's the matter
Pawn it
Let's eat...
I think embroidery
work suits me better
Recruiting female worker
Yes Half day work
is available too
Really Yes
you can also work from home
Yes, it's easier for
a woman to ﬁnd ajob
Look at that vacancy
This is the most I could
get from the pawn shop
Miss Man Fai, what are you doing
Typing ajob application for brother
Wo
The three of us have decided...
Sit down ﬁrst
I prefer to stand, Madam
Sit
I prefer to stand
You know how things have been
Yes
We don't have money to pay you...
I didn't say you've to pay me
But we have to pay for your food
Grandma, don't ask Wo to go
I rather not studying
You think this is my idea
Your dad wouldn't say it
That's why I had to say it
Madam, I just got a job in the factory
We can use my salary for the family...
...just so I can take care of
Miss Man Fai,
I mean this from my heart
Wo
Madam, I really mean what I said
please let me stay
We can't owe you wage forever
Sooner or later, you'll
get used to it, Master,
I really don't mind
I'll send you to school before work
I'll bring you lunch at noon
And I'll pick you up at night
That's too much
It doesn't matter, I can handle it
Here we are Sit down and eat
You used your own money
to buy me food, didn't you
I know what I'm doing
You're lucky to study
in such a famous school
Now eat
Oh, I just learned Chinese
point characters
Really
So, it'll be easier to take notes
That's good
What's wrong with your hand
It's nothing Wo, you've some too
I ate already
You are lying, come on, eat something
You eat, or the food will
get cold Eat now
Master, you needn't help, it's my job
I've nothing to do
Let me wash, go out please, Master
Wo, keep this as a record
of what I owed you
I don't want it
Keep it Master, I don't want it
Keep it, I owed you so much money
Ifl can't repay you
ask my children to pay you
Master, you...
Who is it
What are you doing Cutting classes
No, I feel dizzy...
Man Ching Miss Man Ching
what's wrong with you
Doctor, how is she
She's got nephritis
you should prepare for the worse
But she is so young
Sister
Let's pray together
My dear God
please give my sister eye-sight
Let her see this world
And give Wo good health
Let her take care of
my sister forever
We'll meet in heaven
alright
You've my word
I miss you the most
Listen, my soul will
come back to ﬁnd you
How can I tell it's you
I will give you hints
Then you will know that's me
What will you say
I'll say
Here I'm
Did I scare you
May be I will say...
Why don't you ask me
Have you studied hard
You've my word
You wrote an essay, didn't you
Read it to me please
Composition Free topic
Ifl can see this world
I will be surprised by so many colors
I used to think wind is white
Happiness is red, and sadness black
I hate green the most
Cause I know green herbs made me blind
But, green is pretty
Green grass, green trees
Red ﬂower
White cloud
Blue sky
Where're dad and mom
They are down the hill
they won't come up
They can't bear to see their child go
Burn this for Miss Man Ching
Sister, see you
You've my word
Stop, stay still
Quiet
What is this place
Want some music
Are you making radio again, brother
I've no money to buy parts
But this'll do
What's that
It is the only radio station in
Hong Kong, they charge a fee
This welfare center is a subscriber, understand
Brother, don't Don't take it apart
If you break it, we can't pay them back
You underestimate me
Don't be afraid, all we need
is to hook up this wire
Do you like it
Yes, I haven't listened
to radio for ages
Let's dance
Man Fai, what's the matter
I thought of sister
Try not to think too much
After today, I won't play
with radio anymore
Help me to sit down
I will get ajob to support our family
No one will admit dad's qualiﬁcation
So it is difﬁcult for dad to ﬁnd work
Have dad and mom aged a lot
Yes, mom looks so broken
That's why I won't play with radio any more
I will quit studying
No You're the only one going to school now
You must work hard
You give up so much for me to study...
Man Fai, don't say that
I promise, I will work hard
and be somebody
We'll all work hard together
alright
Let's play dwarfs, come on
Where are we now
We're at a British army barrack
They're hiring workers
for their Iaundramat
It's good working hours
And pay well
Come over here
Stay here, wait for me
Who speaks English
I need someone who speaks English
Ido
Flower and bird I am very good
You're OK OK
OK, follow me
What's going on
Miss Man Fai, wait for me
right here Alright
Jade
Jade... Jade
What's the matter
This isn't a playground
It's your turn to record
Thank you
Let's go inside
Do you know Jade Why do you know this song
Every blind person would know this song
Your time is up, time to die
Spare me
I can't breathe
You're dead meat, my boy
Please, I just escaped from prison
Please let me go
Please let me go home
You really think you can go back alive
I'll strangle you with this chain
Stop, set the kid free
Kid, you'll die
Let him go
I got a whistle, I will get police
What's she doing here
Go away
I got someone outside
he's tougher than you
Kiddo Did you kill him
Mom, mom...
I am alright, mom
Mom
Dear listeners, has David
Copperﬁeld escaped from danger
And what hatred is between
the prisoner and him
How will the story end
Please tune in at same time
tomorrow, good bye
What happened
Where did David Copperﬁeld
ﬁnd a mother
I couldn't think of anything else
Who are you Do you know
we were on air just now
Who let her in
I am so sorry...
You think of a way out
for tomorrow's show
Sorry
Did I scare you
Don't you know this
is a radio station
Radiusion
You are
I do radio plays
Listen
Miss, I'm gonna kill you
I'm here, are you scared
Sister
I don't know your sister's voice, I can't mimick that
Miss Man Fai, you scared me Wo
How come you're here
Does he look like sister
He is a young man
Let's go
Why did you come here
I had to look for you all over
Let's go home
Miss...
Oh, it's you
Yes, I am Lam Yu
My sister's spirit was speaking
through you, right
Are you kidding
You forgot your whistle
Thank you
Thank you, Mr. Lam
You're welcome
I am Ching Man Fai
That was easy work, washing clothes
Really
And I made ten dollars
I'll buy you some snacks later
All these biblical stories you know
My sister told me those
Don't miss her so much
I am sure she's gone to heaven
Let's go to a movie some day
I mean listen to a movie
You'll feel better
if you learn more stories
Did I mess up your radio play
It's alright, I came up
with a perfect explanation
How
The woman became very angry
with David Copperﬁeld
She said, You lied
I ain't married,
how can I be your mother
I don't care if you get
killed or not, I'm leaving
That's it
If Wo heard that
she would have laughed to death
Has she taken care of you for long
Yes
I keep thinking...
It may be my misfortune to be blind
But my biggest fortune is having Wo with me
She spent all her savings on me
She is 50 years old
But she brings me lunch everyday
She wouldn't even take the bus
just to save money for me
And she moonlights at home
to make more money
It seems we are destined
to be together
She gives and I receive
I don't know how I can
ever repay her
Mr. Lam
How are you
Miss Man Fai, let's go
Miss Man Fai, that Mr.
Lam seems a nice chap
He is handsome too
Oh, Miss Man Fai is embarrassed
No, I ain't
Don't deny it, you face is all red
Wo
Reverend, here are
Man Fai's qualiﬁcations
Good, I'll send these to Pakins
School for the Blind in USA
See whether they will grant a
scholarship to someone in Hong Kong
Thank you, Reverend
Congratulations for being
recruited by the BBC
Thank you
You must be leaving soon
If Man Fai can study in USA
that'll be fantastic
You've done all you can for her
But, you think she can handle it
Our neighbour association
would like to employ Miss Man Fai
She's qualiﬁed to teach
the blind point alphabets
We will pay her well
That's good
Wo, hurry up
In time, she'll be promoted
to be instructor
But Man Fai is
This isn't a demanding job
What do you say
How much can she get a month
Dad, mom, I've got a scholarship
I can study in
a university in the USA
What'll we do now
Miss Man Fai should study in USA
She should work for a living
We've supported her long enough
It's time she help support the family
Master, Miss Man Fai is capable
of much greater things
I don't know anymore
Mother
She can earn $30 per month
These days
we can barely make ends meet
Madam, we're old
nobody lives forever
Wo, shut up
This whole study business
is all your fault
You even let her go out
for a movie date tonite
She can't see
What happens if she falls
in love with that boy
Mom, she is only a little girl
If she were lucky, she would
have been happily married already
If that boy dumps her,
Man Fai will only get hurt
Then what
Madam, the boy isn't like that
So what
Man Fai is blind
how can there be a good ending
Man Fai
You been here long
Yes
They were saying...
I heard everything
Don't worry about them
let's go to the movie
Man Fai, I've come to say goodbye
I leave for an internship
in England tomorrow
It's very rare to be
able to study abroad
Therefore you mustn't
give up easily
Why didn't you tell me
you'd leave soon
We haven't known each
other for long
I couldn't say goodbye
right after we met
Be brave
Let me see you without
your glasses
Have more conﬁdence
in yourself
And you won't even
need this anymore
We'll write each other
won't we
And send my regards to Wo
Stop quarrelling
let Man Fai decide for herself
No, she has to work to
make her keep
She has to study in the USA
You're getting senile
who is the boss here
You are an old fool
you never think for the children
Man Fai is my grand-daughter
you've no say here
No, Man Fai is my daughter
I say she must go to the USA
You are so stubborn
beware of God's punishment
Oh, my God...
Mom
Here are your papers
visa and air ticket
Someone will pick you
up at the airport
Thank you, Reverend
Can you manage by yourself
Hasn't God arranged
for everything
Sure Best wishes to you
Miss Man Fai, it's late
what're you doing
Wo, Ifl am not around
what'll happen to you
It will take a while
to get used to
I am not going
This letter is to decline
the scholarship
What
The scholarship only
allows me to go alone
How can I just leave you
in Hong Kong
I can ﬁnd another job
until you come back
But I can stay here, too
After high school, I can
work for the blind
No, you must study, you've
to go to USA
Don't worry about me
Wo
If you go abroad, you'll set
an example for the blind in HK
They can learn from you
Remember what you teacher told you
If you fail, the blind in
Hong Kong will fail too
If you accept this scholarship,
may be they'll grant another
scholarship to other Chinese
After your graduates, you can
teach the other blind people,
so they don't have to rely
on foreign help alone
Don't back away from this
I'll still be happy, even if
you're not around me
But how can I live without you
Learn
Starting from this minute
Remember, the objects
and utensils you've used,
just put them back to
where they were before
I've sewed markings onto your clothes
A pearl means pink
A cross means white
Remember that and you can
match the clothes yourself
And, tie the socks
together before washing
Separate the long ones
from the short ones
Wo, speak slowly
Alright, I will speak slowly...
No, you must learn now
we don't have much time
I won't be with you for very long
Wo
Don't hold a grudge against Grandma
She is stubborn, but she is getting old
You've to take care of her
Don't worry, I will take care of her
Man Fai
Brother
Man Fai, come back
if things don't work out
I can make it Don't worry
Dad, mom, I will be back
If there're better
opportunities there, then stay
No, I'll be back
Man Fai
There's so much
I couldn't do for you...
You must be strong, stronger than me
Don't cry
Careful in everything you do
Man Fai Grandma
Take this red pocket as my blessing
Thank you
Time to board the plane
Can I lead her to the plane
Hurry up
Goodbye, Man Fai
Please stay here
Let's go up ﬁrst
You better go
I don't need this anymore
Alright
Wo Miss Man Fai
You've to go now
I will, I just want to
see you a little longer
You go...
Your ticket and visa please
Go
Follow me please