100 years ago,
this island in Taiwan...
had nothing
Only romance
Legend has it
There were two lovers
And one day
The man was fishing
His boat sank
The woman...
saw it onshore
She swam out
No one ever saw them again
Some say
they became dolphins
All dolphins around this island...
came from them
They all make...
"Bu... Bu" noises
Nice story?
So snooty
You told a horror story
Don't get involved
Have some melon
No
You're like...
those dolphins
So picky
You named me Bu
I've told you so often
Don't mix Mandarin...
with Cantonese
Bu's Mandarin and Cantonese...
are now both accented
That's awful
You teach her Mandarin then
Get off my case
That's Cantonese again
Which I don't speak
What did you say?
Tell me
Skipper Restaurant
Open bar, folks
One more round
Drink up
Go in and take a seat
Long time no see
One more round?
Not tonight
Can't afford it
On the house
Bu, 6 beers, on me
They come everyday
Never pay
Add water...
to the beer
That trick again?
Bu Yes?
Hurry
Here
Did you add water?
No!
No, very good
C'mon
Cheers
Why, Bu?
Idiot
You could've spared me
They sing
Watch TV
Or pick fights
This island
Has no room...
for romance
Done
Beautiful
I learned it...
from a magazine
Bu
I brought you something
I've never seen...
an oyster this big
Any pearls?
No
Must be expensive
NT$3,000
Thanks
And this
It's my friend's shop
He'll give us a discount
I'm...
Proposing?
No, I just want to...
Yes, I'm proposing
With...
a big oyster?
Of course not
The oyster's not...
Marry me
Okay
I'll consider it
Poor Longyi
This oyster's not cheap
He proposed to me
Really?
You love him?
Well, he's actually...
Not bad
Your answer
Shouldn't be over 4 words
You love him, or you don't
You left Hong Kong...
to marry dad, why?
He was quite a hunk
A good cook too
You're a good cook
He's better
He cooks with love
What's loving someone like?
You miss him
The sight of him thrills you
You ache
When he's gone
You could watch him forever
Even when he's sleeping
You're in love
If you feel like that
Okay?
You miss Hong Kong?
Yes, especially its Chinese Pot Rice
I see
You don't love Longyi
Take mama's advice
Trust your heart
Do what you have to do
Bu
Hey, kid
Got some news
Longyi proposed
Don't laugh
Somebody said
Men and women...
exist in pairs
Till separated on earth
Then they go through life
Searching for one another
Bu
Where are you going?
Bu!
I'm waiting for you!
Hong Kong, Albert?
How romantic!
You're telling me something?
You choose for me
You just decided my future
Excuse me
You know a good cafe?
Sure, we'll go together
Thanks
Typical Taiwanese!
Pardon me?
You speak Cantonese?
Surprised?
Never flown before?
It shows?
Yes
You can get lost in Hong Kong
I'll show you around
I know...
all the trendy spots
I have fans everywhere
I'm a fun guy
Okay?
What?
Are you twins?
Please forgive me
Excuse me
Gangster's girlfriend
disappears
Morning, sir, working out?
No time
Bill, are you ready?
Good
Let's start
Morning, Mr. Chan
Any news from Wall Street?
Lion Fund...
is borrowing heavily
Even at...
a 20% interbank rate
Check the following
How many Nikkei Futures...
did they short?
Is Yen...
appreciating?
Is the lease for the US base...
in Japan expiring?
If both answer are affirmative
Buy whatever they sell
But this hedge fund
Is run by 2 Nobel Prize economists
Should be invincible
They're too greedy
on margin trading
Leveraging 10 times their worth
They're doomed
So go ahead
Yes, Mr. Chan
Thank you
Send this with 100 roses...
to Carman
During office hours
Didn't you break up?
We're still friends
Find someone and
settle down
Like who?
Those women around you
All so beautiful and elegant
Too elegant for me
What do you want?
Someone amusing
Make yourself at home
That bottle floated to Taiwan!
And you came...
all that way
How brave and romantic
However...
What?
I'm gay
No
Yes
Really?
Really
No
Yes
Honest?
Honest
The bottle's for your boyfriend?
Ex—boyfriend
What?
Such a waste
VVhy?
You're a hunk
I'm not
That's stunning
That's what inspired you
I moved here because of it
Find a motel tonight
Fly home tomorrow
I've never traveled
This is a first
Think I'll stay a while
But Hong Kong...
is boring
Fly back tomorrow
My friend said
Hong Kong's fun
Great restaurants too
I'll find you...
a motel
I can't afford one
Hands off Wait
Let me stay here
Women can't stay here
I'll go nuts
Please
Sorry Please
I came all this way
To such a big let down
I don't deserve this
Goodbye
Bu
What?
Your suitcase
Your bag
I can't stand crying
Makes me feel so guilty
Okay, stay
I'll be your aide, in whatever you do
I'm a makeup artist
Best...
in Hong Kong
Exquisite
That's it
Hold that
Good
I'm starving
We'll wrap soon
How much longer?
6 hours
What?
Keep that door shut
We're reloading
You'll fog the film
You sound so nervous on the phone
What's the emergency?
No... no emergency
I just miss you. You don't miss me?
Sit down, I'll get you a drink
Tell me, what's going on?
Maybe you'd better go
C.N. you're cruising and
didn't invite me?
Why bother, here you are
The press says you're romancing my girl
You believe them?
Grow up, LW
Is it true?
Yes
We've been competing since grade school
You've been interested in...
our stock lately
I'm interested in all stocks,
not just yours
My associates and I
Hold a majority of the shares
You can't touch my company
We'll see
You're on my yacht
Dating my girl
And you talk to me like this
Why did you want me here?
For an apology
To make it easier on you
I'm leaving now
Call me...
to apologize in...
5 minutes
What time is it?
5:30
Why wear...
a watch
That can't tell time
I like the diamonds
Watch him
If he doesn't call me in five
Throw him overboard
But give him a buoy
Yes, boss
Call me
Bye, boss
Call him
Or you'll get wet
Make it snappy
I've got a hot date
Don't force us to do it
Get a buoy
Right
Come
Hands off
Easy
Almost
Bye
Here comes the buoy
It's Fatty
Fatty fell over
Don't go
Help him up
Over there
Scared me
Yo u o kay?
I'm fine
Call you
Where is he?
Yo u o kay?
Don't fall over again
You! He's here!
In the rear
Help...
Hold tight
Close
You see him?
No
Look again
Over there
He got away
Wait
The boss wanted him...
overboard with a buoy
Job's done, right?
Right
It's a wrap
Thanks
Yo u o kay?
You're...
Name's Bu
Bu?
You a refugee?
Yes
From Vietnam?
Right again
How many of you?
Just me, why?
Who's driving?
Give me a hand
I can't, I'm starving
Aren't you?
No, but I could use a snack
Let's talk
so I forget the hunger
About what?
What do you like?
Nothing?
Not even cars and women?
Don't just smile
Okay, what don't you like?
Nosy people
What don't you like?
Growing up,
I like being naughty
Nosy?
Naughty
And no one...
pampers you anymore
What do you like?
A shower when I'm sweaty
Snap out of bed...
to a cup of coffee
I'd like one now
Hong Kong stars are lovely
Stars are...
the same everywhere
If you care to look at them
What?
Shooting star!
Really?
Mom said when you see one
Touch your pocket and make a wish
And it'll come true
But I'm out of luck, no pocket
Another one
What's your wish?
Can't tell you
Or it won't come true
I'm so sleepy
A boat! Help!
Over here!
The Silicon Valley stocks?
They'll go even higher
Check one thing
Does LW control...
his company's shares?
Buy me a new mobile
It drowned
There's no transport...
around here
I'll give you a ride
Just tell me where I am
and I'll walk back
We're out
in the boonies, Miss
Name's Bu
B '2
oo. Bu!
Just get in
Sure
Not you, this lady here
There are only 2 seats
I know
Here's 20 bucks
Around the corner...
are buses and cabs
Compulsive liar
Come in
Huge place, you live alone?
There's a butler
Must get crowded
Wait here
Can I look around?
Help yourself
Thanks
I'm starving
Some food please!
Need something?
Fish food
They're electronic fish
Come over here
Why electronic fish?
I never change the water
Fish never die, it's perfect
And if the power's out?
You invite friends over?
Don't have any
So boring, and lonely
Now what?
You like to fight?
Some golf,
some race horses
I box and work out
What's the octopus for?
You're so nosy
Sorry
This should fit, change in there
Betty, call me a cab
20 minutes? Great
There's a room...
behind the mirror
How would I have known?
Hungry?
Starving
Me too
Any Chinese pot rice?
What?
Best take out food ever
My favorite
A fancy kitchen and you don't cook?
I hate the smell
Don't stare. Eat up
Sure
Now what?
You're amusing when you eat
Are you rich?
I guess so
What do you do?
I'm into trash
C'mon
No, I sell trash
Be that way
Can I have a soda?
Juice is better for you
Bu took the lift down
What's wrong?
Stop moaning
You know
That bottle's very special
So special that...
all of a sudden
I'm feeding and sheltering you
Just like that
Remember I told you about...
C.N.? More than once
Last night...
You told me that too
I think he's... nice
Nice?
These magazines are published weekly
And he changes girlfriends just as often
He's not nice, he's a playboy
Let's see
An ex—girlfriend says
He doesn't say sweet words
But he's a romantic man
He appears stem and talks tough
Inside he's like a kid
He's competitive and chases novelty
Never regrets any decision
With him...
You feel insecure
Meaning?
Chases novelty, so he fools around
No regrets,
so he enjoys dumping women
Maybe those women deserved it
They were insecure...
to begin with
Spare me
Hong Kong's boring anyway
Going home?
No, C.N. is fun
You have to hook him first
Can't just walk up
And take off your clothes
That sure won't work
But you never know
He's competitive and
chases novelty
I have a plan, I need your help
No way
Please
Sorry
Please tell me
where your daughter is
She found a bottle
She's in Hong Kong
I have to get Bu back
Chow Yun Fat!
Mr. Chow
Wrong guy
You speak Mandarin?
I'm not Chow Yun Fat
Don't try to fool me
Sir, is he Chow Yun Fat?
Mr. Chow, you're back!
Fresh form Hollywood?
Please sign Can I take a picture?
You mind? OK
But... 1,2,3... say cheese
My turn, miss
Point a gun at me
Ready, 1,2 Ready1,2,3...
Thank you, Mr. Chow
Give me a hug
Thank you Mr. Chow Thank you
I'll send you the photos
Bye You're so sweet
Same as the photo
Print me a copy
He's such a hunk Bye
Bye
My bag!
We checked LW's company
Last year,
rumover grew 13%
Profit: over HK$1 billion
Stock price is undervalued by 30%
We have acquired...
16% of the company
LW and his associates...
still hold 65%
But...
they're not selling
Dump all my stocks
If we dump them,
the price will plunge
We bought high, we'll take a huge loss
Just do it
I need to see K.K.
Yes, sir
Who's K.K.?
Head of Environmental Protection
Going up or down?
I was seeing friends upstairs
There's no upstairs
Really?
Actually they live downstairs
Names?
I forgot
So quiet here
Can you get an 80% mortgage?
You messed up my wall
Excuse me?
Look!
Easy there
Let go
Who sent you?
Let go first
Like my writing?
Enough. I don't know kungfu
I'm just a messenger
Message?
My back pocket
Bully. You messed up my arm
Happy reading
Gangster's girlfriend...
disappears
What happened?
Fell down some stairs
Yo u o kay?
I'll live
Will he buy...
I'll a gangster's girlfriend?
How should I know?
Will it work?
Of course
What's next?
Showtime
Where are your pals?
You know we're bad
We're here to waste you
React!
My boyfriend... Speak Mandarin
Is a Taiwanese gangster
The sworn enemy of our boss
He wants you defaced
Frog, your turn
Believe it or not
You're front page news
Everyone's looking for you now
Yes. Looking awesome
Yo u o kay?
Yes, and you?
It's you!
Yo u o kay?
Yes
I don't know these goons
What?
Nothing
You can't be ID'ed
They're damn good actors
Back off
Stay here
Yeah, or I'll kill myself
You're bleeding
We'll spare you today
Don't provoke him
Cops will go after them
Not us
Hi, there
Sunny, sit... Sunny, sit
Thanks
Someone reported a fight
We were attacked
They leave any evidence?
Baseball bats
Sunny, smell
Any clues?
Sunny, you're clueless
Let's get help
My site, very safe
It's so trashy
I told you I sell trash
Expensive stuff too
Expensive? Trash is trash
Before you were...
a Vietnamese refugee
Now you're...
A Taiwanese gangster's girlfriend
So who are you, really?
A dangerous woman
Scared?
Never
Thrilled to be with me?
How'd you land the girlfriend's part?
I lived near a police station
with posters of wanted criminals
One of them was a hunk
I saw his poster everyday
And I fell in love
And?
I found him, stole his heart
How was he?
Cute, a great dancer
Really romantic
For being a dancer?
You dance?
Of course
This?
Sure
Tango?
That too
So common, nothing more exciting?
Sure Really?
Teach me
You'll be scared
No way
Hold me
Give me your legs
Right
Ready?
Help!
Exciting enough?
Yes
No more?
You aren't scared?
Never
More moves?
Just hold tight and
stay still
Enjoy the variations
Really? Okay?
Okay...
There
Run, 1, 2, 3
Wow! This is fun
Man's so busy
Making trash
The recycling business is a gold mine
They say...
What others abandon, I take
You did well last time
Slapped Lion Fund in the face
They all know you're my protege
I'm flattered
Thank you
Don't thank me, thank yourself
Any new plans?
I heard you're buying LW's company
You know
what's the best win?
Winning one's battle...
with the enemy's respect
Stock Exchange's closed
And?
Our stock dropped 20%
Closed at $6.50
Our drop in asset value?
Over 2 billion
It's Chan,
he's dumping our shares
What's the news on him?
Rumors are he wants...
to buy our company
Then...
why dump his shares?
After buying them so high?
Boss
What happened to you?
We wanted to get even. We ambushed Chan
Was he hurt?
Not a scratch
Thank God
Else...
I'd blame myself
And if...
Well,
you actually were hurt
And see, I feel guilty
It was your dad's idea
He screwed up
Ordering an ambush
Why not shoot Chan in the back?
That's much faster
Let's do it
No, it's wrong, it's cowardly
Challenge him openly
Right
Yes!
Let's hire a fighter from overseas
Tougher
Smaller
And...
Handsomer than Chan
He'll be devastated
What's that?
The signal means "Dismissed". Beat it
Tricky signals
Have you seen her?
That's Mary
No, that's Bunny
No, that's Mary
That's Bunny, come with me
No, that way
No
Another Bunny?
A masseuse
A masseuse?
Why not?
Oh my God, what's he doing?
Albert!
Do I look pretty?
Yes
What?
Your outfit
My Sunday best
Go to...
Jean—Paul's Boutique
I'll call him,
let him dress you
You feed, shelter,
and clothe me
You're my guardian angel
Your wish is...
my command
Bye
What?
How should I behave at dinner?
You're playing a gangster's lady
Use method acting
Teach me
Just act snooty
Feed, shelter, and clothe her
I'm an angel
She forgot something?
Yes?
Help!
It's you!
Where's Bu?
Please tell me where she is
Mr. Chan
Thanks