Quick question:
is it good in there?
Get in line.
Three good reasons: Good mood,
we look amazing...
Just a quick question! I know her!
We're true Berliners!
I was just talking.
Wait, I'll get us in, dude!
- Guys, it's over! Out you go.
Clear the way!
It's cool. It's cool.
- You won't get in without money.
I put on my dancing shoes specially!
- Take him with you.
Brother, Fuss wants to dance!
- Off you go!
One day the club'll be ours.
Yeah, say what you like.
Whatever...
One day this club will be ours!
Understand?
We'll buy your club!
Watch out, man!
Now it's your car?
Man, let me have a chat!
That's Boxer...
- Just a quick story...
Fuck. We left the keys
in the club, dude.
Fuck me, it's really open!
Hey. guys. wait...
Hands off the car!
Fuck off!
Are you fucking mental?
Are you fucking insane?
Yeah, man, calm down!
Get the fuck away!
Shut the fuck up!
- No, you fuck off, man!
Do you want to come
to my birthday party...
and then we can...
Fuss, don't push it!
- It's just 'cos it's my birthday party...
As if you knew the English!
East Berlin! East Berlin! East Berlin!
- Shut the fuck up!
Quit talking about my sister, Fuss!
How do you say 'Spétkauf'?
What's up?
You wanna add something?
Let's get some 'Molle'.
Happy?
Happy? Are you happy?
...or really happy?
Or a little bit happy?
A little bit happy?
He)'. guys.
Give me some cash!
Give me some cash. Cash!
Blinker, hey!
I need cash.
We have no money.
What do you want me to pay?
Give me some money.
- Wait, wait.
Fuss, got some paper in your pocket?
Fuss is in a different world.
Wait here a moment.
Don't start any shit.
I'll get some beer.
Man, you scared me!
Cut it out, man!
Let me talk to her, retard!
Do you need any help?
Go away. Let me...
Yo, Farouk, dude!
Guys!
Boys!
- Hey! She stole it all.
Stop pretending!
So you stole again?
- Yeah. Coming from you!
Hey, Victoria! Come here!
Come here, dude. Do you know
how to drink schnapps?
Stop that bisexual shit, man!
What kind of faggot are you?
Cheers!
- Cheers!
'Zum Wohle' is better than 'Prost'!
Speak proper German with her!
Hey, cut that shit out!
I dropped the soap, Boxer!
I dropped the soap!
Oh, shit!
Stop that crap!
Hey, guys. Chill a sec.
Time for his little show.
You can't do that!
At last you've got
someone to impress!
Now you've got someone!
For your old school shit!
Pistols? Got pistols on you?
What's going on?
What? What?
Quick question...
Get lost.
- Boxer, back off.
Boxefl
- Piss off!
Fuck off, you pussies!
Stop it, Boxer!
Stop this shit!
Back off. Everything's OK.
Boxer, what's wrong with you?
Please, man, it's a party!
It's his birthday. Cut it out.
Boxer, please!
Man, you're always causing trouble!
Chill out, hey.
Relax. It's the cops.
Good evening!
Let's smoke a joint.
To peace! Peace!
Those sons of bitches!
Let's smoke one here!
They're coming back.
They're coming back. Shit.
We're on a zebra crossing. We're fine.
It's actually legal,
but let's go anyway.
Let's get out of here.
Let's hit the roof, boys.
Let's hit the roof!
No ego trips, man.
- I'm not...
You've messed up my cigarette.
Hey, guys. Don't break anything!
I'm going ahead. See you later!
- Where to? Where to?
Looking good, Sonne!
I'm out of here!
I'm never coming back!
See that? Escort party,
dude, escort party!
Guys! Blinker! Come on!
She's screaming, man!
Fuss, where are you?
- I'm coming!
Talk louder, why don't you?
I'm not a faggot, man!
That's true?
- Quit laughing.
It was the news. There was an interview.
- Blinker was in the news, too.
Don't talk so loud!
I'm just saying...
Blinker used to steal
these pizza mopeds...
Definitely.
Shut the fuck up!
Who cares?
I don't wanna get her hooked!
- Oh, you're so righteous.
Quit laughing, moron.
- I'm not laughing...
Bro, I wasn't laughing about you.
It was something else.
Sonne, dude, please.
- What?
I am quiet.
You shut the fuck up!
You gonna take her home?
I'll see you.
- Where?
I'll just take her home.
- You're coming back?
No ego trips, dude.
- It's not an ego trip, retard!
Goodbye, wankers!
We'll wait for you!
- Yeah, wait!
Such a Casanova!
Are you nuts? This is a pavement!
Relax. You know what time it is?
Bye. It was fun.
Thank you.
- My pleasure.
Hey, chin up...
Yo, my man.
I'm here, in the cafe.
Why did he call?
I'm in the cafe, dude!
Man! At the...
At the organic cafe.
What does he want?
Yeah, what do you want?
Hello?
What's up?
He called.
- Yeah, you said!
Can't I just talk in peace?
- Let's go!
What's going on?
Do we have to meet him?
Of course we have to!
- Yes, but why now?
So let's go!
- OK!
OK, retard!
- Where are we going?
Boxer, where?
- We're going now.
We're coming, Boxer!
We're coming with you!
Just leave me alone...
Dude! What are you doing?
Get on with it!
I'll get in and shift across.
Front seat?
OK!
Victoria. I'm sorry!
Hey! Wait outside.
Don't puke here, you retard!
Everything's cool.
Water, please.
- I've got water!
Have a drink.
Sit up.
Calm down, Fuss. Breathe deep.
Dude, like this.
Relax, everything's cool.
Wake up, man!
Get your shit together.
We've got ten minutes.
He'll make it!
Man! Just fuck it!
Call him and tell him it's off! Fuck it!
We can't!
- We don't have to do it tonight!
He wants four of us!
- But not tonight!
I gave him my word!
Boys! Relax!
- Don't let me down!
Don't let me down!
Get up, man!
Boxer, three's enough!
He just wants us in and out...
He doesn't want any stress!
Fuss isn't going to be any help.
Just call him and postpone it!
We can't postpone!
I owe him!
You know what I mean!
Let's just go, the three of us,
bang bang, and out!
Right, Boxer?
Three? Three guys! One driver!
What don't you get?
Ask her to come along.
I don't care.
Quick job, then back to the cafe.
Ask her!
- Are you crazy? We just met!
Just do it!
Don't touch me, retard!
I hate that!
Boxer, don't touch me!
Ask her!
- I will. Shut the fuck up!
Come on, Fuss, let's go.
- What happened?
Get out!
- Just fuck off!
Man, fuck you! Wait.
Piss off!
I'm asking her now!
Then let's go!
We've got five minutes.
Five fucking minutes.
I was talking to a girl, you wanker.
Are you stupid?
I was asking her!
And don't talk to me like a retard!
I hate that!
She's doing it!
- Just calm down.
You need to calm down!
- You both need to calm down.
Let her drive!
Let her drive. You don't have
a license, you stupid wanker!
He's such a moron.
How do you say 'gerade aus'?
Now be nice to her, please!
Fuss, brother?
Can you all be quiet a moment?
Quit laughing, man!
Dude, she got it!
Just tell her she's safe, OK?
Shut the fuck up.
I took care of that, wanker.
Yeah, man, Boxer,
he really did.
We'll just talk there, right?
So what are we doing?
- No plan, dude!
He wants to see we're ready.
- Exactly. It's a test!
Thanks for your wisdom, Blinker!
Calm the fuck down!
Afterwards we're bringing
her straight back.
I don't want...
I don't want to talk about it.
Sonne, of course we'll bring her back!
I'm fucked.
No: I'm good!
We're meeting a real gangster.
That's interesting!
Shut! The fuck! Up!
Got it, Boxer.
Everything's cool.
Give me another, please.
Stop frightening the girl, retard!
We're not frightening her.
Where are we going?
Where are you going, man?
With this shitty stolen car?
Boxer, where are we going?
Stop calling it a fucking stolen car.
It'll scare her.
She doesn't understand,
so shut the fuck up.
Sonne?
- What?
You're not afraid, are you?
- I'm not afraid.
Sonne, we'll make it.
Give me five.
Victoria, everything OK?
OK, give me a light, please.
Here, hang on.
Shit.
Shit!
Do we wait inside?
Are you fucking serious?
Get out.
I'll be in touch.
These are your boys?
- Yes.
Who's the bitch?
Are you guys fucking her?
- The bitch is our driver.
You don't say.
Get out.
You're the driver?
Done this before?
What the fuck?
She doesn't speak German?
Your problem.
Let's get your tools.
Hand them round.
- Are they loaded?
Yes. You wanna throw candy?
Come with me.
The bitch, too.
This is the floor plan for a private bank,
Limburg & Co, Zimmerstrasse 26.
There's 50,000 Euro in a small safe
for a customer, Mr Weigert.
He'll collect the money at 7 a.m.
to buy a vintage car.
You'll be there already.
Ten grand's for me.
The rest is for you.
Right now?
Yes. You got something better to do?
Well...
You don't have to.
I can't force you.
Then we won't.
We won't do it.
Boxer, back in jail you
enjoyed my protection.
You owe me. Ten grand.
And I want that money.
I'll get the money.
You had no money for cigarettes
and now you'll find ten grand?
Give me a week, OK?
One week? OK.
While you're getting the money,
I'll keep the bitch.
We'll do it.
We'll do it!
Hey, we'll do it, OK?
We'll do it, man!
OK. Are you sure?
- Yes.
Yes.
- Good.
So, this is the entrance.
ATM, two security doors.
Here's the counter.
Six desks for the account managers.
Over here is the main target.
Mrs Neumann sits here.
She's the bank manager.
She has the alarm codes
and the combination for the small safe.
Mr Weigert will collect the money at 7 a.m.
Mrs Neumann and two clerks
will be in the bank then.
The second clerk arrives
between 6:30 and 6:45.
That's your target. She'll bring you
through the second security door.
Alright? There's gloves and masks.
Show me what you've got.
You stay here.
She stays with me.
- Yes.
I hate you.
Gimme that shit!
Take some gloves.
- Got 'em.
We don't have much time.
- Yes!
OK, boss.
Shit!
Should we start in the car?
Whatever.
- Let's start inside.
Wait, the gloves!
Go!
Wait, wait!
- Open the door!
Open the door!
- Do it yourself!
The lock, dude!
Come on, come on!
Let's go!
Everybody on the ground!
Shut the fuck up!
- No one make a move!
Down on the ground!
Shut the fuck up!
I said, down on the ground!
Give me the fucking money!
Shut up, stay down!
Give me the fucking money! Go!
Give me the cash!
Go! Go! Go!
OK. stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Good.
Who's the pressure guy?
Who's putting on the pressure?
Who's calling the shots?
He calls the shots.
Don't all shout at once.
Mrs Neuman needs clear instructions.
When you enter...
- The door thing won't happen again.
First leave the car...
then go. Don't run!
When you enter, two shots
to make things clear.
What's the bank's name?
Limburg.
Limburg & Co, Zimmerstrasse 26.
Bitch!
Zimmerstrasse 26!
Good.
Remember that.
Tilidin, cocaine.
Take some.
It makes you confident and aggressive.
If you're busted, you'll do less time.
- You first.
Bitch, you too.
Forget the silent alarm.
You'll be out in two minutes.
A bit more, Boxer.
Give me a bit more...
A little more.
More, more. Another bit.
Time to go.
Give me some!
Afterwards go home and stay put.
I'll be in touch. Have fun.
Go!
What is this shit?
Boxer?
Boxer, what the fuck is this shit, man?
Boxer. Man, I can't breathe!
My heart!
I can't breathe!
My heart! Stop the car!
I'm not joking!
Open the fucking door.
Boxer, Boxer, I can't.
Help. My heart.
Calm the fuck down!
Get up. man! Get up!
I don't want to die!
Get up!
I don't want to die.
Give me the fucking cigarette.
I'll do it alone.
Guys, for once:
everyone together.
Come here.
Blinker, come here!
Blinker, come here, man!
No, let's go, let's go!
Relax, for once.
But we're taking her back first!
Get up, man.
OK, man. I'm coming.
I'll take Mrs Neumann.
I'll take Mrs Neumann...
You keep the others covered.
We're doing this.
We're going to make it, OK?
Nice and easy. In and out. Two minutes.
OK?
- Yes, man!
OK, brother!
- Yeah?
Blinker, everything alright?
- What?
I already told her.
Blinker, you're OK?
- Yes.
Hey. Blinker.
- I'm calm, I'm calm, I'm calm...
Is that her?
Hey! Wait!
Hey, that's her!
Quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet!
Down on the ground!
I said, get down on the ground!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Come on!
Man, just drive!
Drive! Drive! Drive!
Why don't you go?
Go! Go! Go!
Throw your jacket out!
Throw your fucking jacket away!
Throw it out!
Throw everything out!
Relax, please!
Calm down! Calm down!
Sister, you go back.
- Hey, calm down!
Just think! Where are we going?
We've got to get off the streets!
Let's get out of here!
- Hide! Get down!
Boxer, you whore.
50,000 Euros!
A pharmacy bag.
That was some sick shit.
Show me: how much we got?
Hey, guys!
I just want to say I love you.
Boys, let's get going.
Grab your fucking guns!
Guys! Sonne! Sonne!
Grab all the shit.
Just take everything.
Grab the gun and don't leave a trace.
Wipe them off!
Let's go party, man!
Let's go party!
Wait, wait!
- Alright, man.
Throw away this shit.
My jacket!
- Throw it away, dude.
Hey, man!
- Fuck it.
A bit of pocket money?
Give me some pocket money.
Let me see!
Evening.
Get going!
Six Euros!
It's us again!
Here's one hundred. And two hundred.
Good evening!
- Remember? You wouldn't let us in!
Here you are.
Take it, take it, take it, brother.
Give me a whisky, dude!
Just give me whisky, please.
Give me everything you've got.
- Give me two whiskies.
I told you, the club belongs to me!
It's over now.
What do you mean, it's over?
Of course it's over. That's why we're partying.
Sorry, it happens sometimes.
Our day is over!
Come on, get on with it!
This isn't your kind of place.
What's up with you?
- Come on! Off you go!
We're dressed and ready to go!
Dressed and ready to go!
Let's gm!
Get out!
Let her down, man.
The place is ours!
- We go, we go, we go!
Hey, man, don't push it!
Hang on a second.
Did you see that?
Give me a kiss.
Let's check what Fuss is doing,
you stupid morons!
I totally forgot about him!
I competely forgot him!
Hey, Blinker, you retard!
Man! Blinker! Man!
Just run slowly!
- OK, OK, OK.
Fuck your shoes.
- Don't panic. Act normal!
Blinker, hey!
Blinker! Come on!
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Stay calm! Stay calm!
We'll make it!
Pull your fucking trousers up, man!
Where did they come from?
We fucked up!
Really fucked up!
Cops.
I swear on my mother's grave!
Cops!
- Wait! Stop shouting!
Wait! Shit!
Wait!
Go! Go, man!
Move your fucking ass!
Don't run!
Go! Run! Run!
Go left!
Left, man!
Fuck you!
Police! Freeze! Stop!
Throw your guns down!
Fuck off!
Stay where you are!
Drop your weapons!
Drop the gun!
Freeze!
Fuck you, you wanker!
Put your weapons down
and come out now!
You bastards!
Come out!
You don't stand a chance.
Come out with your hands up!
Stop!
Stay where you are!
Leave the money!
Come on!
- Drop the gun!
Drop the gun, or I'll shoot!
Boxer, come here!
Come on!
Where? Where?
There's no way out!
Where, man? Where?
He") me!
Fuck off!
Throw your guns away!
Put down your guns!
Come out with your hands up!
Take the money!
- You're coming with us!
You're coming with us!
Just get the fuck out of here!
Don't look at me.
Turn around.
Where do you live?
- Upstairs. Upstairs!
Where do you live!
- Upstairs, one floor up!
Let us in!
Move your ass! Go, go, go!
- OK, OK!
Hurry UP!
On the floor!
Shut the fuck up! In the living room!
You too!
Shut the fuck up!
Stay on the ground!
Don't look at me!
OK?
Shut the fuck up!
Shut...
Why'd you let me
into your shitty flat with a baby, man?
I don't know...
Are you stupid?
You can't let me in when there's a baby here!
How stupid are you?
How stupid are you, man?
Shut the fuck up.
Well, we're finished.
Attention, residents! This is the police!
Please stay in your homes.
Keep your doors closed.
Don't let anyone in!
We will inform you once
the situation is under control.
Attention, residents! This is the police!
Secure your doors and windows.
No! -
Not my baby!
Listen up!
Give us the baby!
Give us...!
- No, no! Please, Sonne! No!
Yeah, come on!
- I've got it!
Where's the money?
Everything's OK.
Hey, it's OK.
Lie down! Lie down!
Everything's OK.
No, no!
Shut the fuck up!
Shut your fucking mouth!
Police!
Stay where you are!
Hands up.
Take a step down.
Stop, stop.
Sparrowhawk to HQ?
I've got two individuals in the hall.
Two youths...
No. HQ, I need a
situation report now!
I've got two individuals, mid twenties.
- We live here.
They have a baby.
Give me a description!
They've got colourful clothing and a baby.
Come down here, please.
- We live here.
What happened?
Secure upstairs.
- What happened?
Stay here.
You'll be picked up.
My colleagues will pick you up.
Just stay here.
They told us to get out fast!
Move around the corner.
Yes.
Shit!
Morning.
- Good morning.
Good morning.
Greetings, sir.
- Hello!
Straight on for now.
- OK.
Just straight on...
and then left...
Your first fare?
- No, my last.
Yeah?
- Left here?
Yes, just go left.
You got it.
Can you just take us...?
Just take us to a hotel.
What kind? Fifty or five hundred Euro?
- Doesn't matter.
Round here?
- Yeah.
OK.
Then let's try the Westin.
It's just round the corner.
Sweet.
Give me the money.
I'll give you a hundred.
I can't change that.
Ah, no problem!
Why, thank you!
- We just came from the slot machines.
Very generous!
So, here we are.
- Perfect.
OK. Thank you.
- Have a nice day.
Yes.
- Bye.
Bye.
...the police identified the getaway car,
which led to the first thief's arrest.
There was a shootout between police and
the thieves here in Kochstrasse...
One of the thieves died at the scene,
another one on the way to the hospital...
Two suspects, a man and a woman in
their twenties, are still at large. Police...
Come here!