Executive Producer: Kenze Tsujimoto
Production/Planning/Setting:
CAPCOM
Production Cooperation:
Sony Music Entertainment Inc.
Production: Hiroshi Inagaki
Akio Sakai
Planning: Takeshi Sekiguchi
Megumu Sugiyama, Mitsuhisa Hida
Screenplay: Kenichi Imai
Gisaburo Sugii
Music: Tetsuya Komuro, Yuji Toriyama
Production Team: SEDIC
Animation Production: Group Tac
Producer: Kenichi Imai
Director: Gisaburo Sugii
London
Minister!
A word, pIease, Minister!
Look this way, pIease!
- That's another story.
- Right.
Can we get an interview, pIease?
Minister, a word, pIease!
What's that?!
You're Minister of Justice
SeIIers, correct?
- Go after her!
- Oh my God!
Stop her!
Get off of me!
GET OFF OF ME!
The terrorist's name is Cammy White.
A speciaI agent who beIongs to MI6.
She's being interrogated at B Base...
but she has no memory
of the past 3 years.
What do you mean?
It seems Iike her mind is
being controIIed.
By using Cammy's anaIysis data,
we shouId be abIe to figure out...
how ShadowIaw is creating terrorists
with speciaI abiIities.
We aIso know that ShadowIaw is
gathering info...
on street fighters around the worId
to create weapons Iike Cammy.
Turning street fighters into
terrorists, huh...
This man is a fighter named Sagat.
He is admired as a muay thai champion
and a hero in ThaiIand.
This is Bison, exiIed from the boxing
worId due to his savagery.
This is BaIrog, a Spanish fighter
feared as Crazy Viper.
These three are now
members of ShadowIaw...
as combat personneI under Vega.
ShadowIaw's crimes are increasing
in size year by year.
We need to destroy them immediateIy.
I think it's time we carry out an
investigation with the US miIitary.
Patterson Air Force Base
Major Guile!
PeopIe from InterpoI
are here to see you.
InterpoI?
I'm Chun-Li.
What do you want?
We've come to have a meeting on
joint investigation on ShadowIaw.
I'II defeat Vega.
What do you mean?
I don't need heIp
defeating Vega.
Major GuiIe, this is a decision
made by the miIitary!
We just need to defeat Vega, right?
WeII, good Iuck to you, too.
- I've been waiting for you.
- Hurry up and show me.
Right away, sir.
This is the newIy revamped
monitor cyborg with...
super performance computer equipped.
Images captured by this monitor
cyborg wiII be sent instantIy to...
the super computer at headquarters
via sateIIite communication.
It's aIready been arranged to repIace
the oId monitor robots with these.
Good.
By the way, have you found him?
Not yet, sir.
How can you not find a man
so strong he defeated Sagat?
We've been tracking info
on fighters from aII over...
I wonder if this man named Ryu reaIIy
can be such a strong fighter.
This was recorded by the computer.
2000 is the Iimit of any fighter's
potentiaI combat capacity.
But 3600? I can hardIy beIieve it.
At any rate, you'II have to find
Ryu as soon as possibIe!
I don't care if it's on top of
the HimaIayas. Send cyborgs out!
Ryu, what do you see lying
ahead of your fists?
That's good for now.
Get some rest.
Before breakfast, let's go to
the valley to get some water.
OK!
You bastard! Why did you puII your
punches?! Did you go easy on me?
Idiot! I don't go easy on you!
I'II never understand you.
That's fine.
Someday, there'II be time when we
seriousIy have to fight each other.
Seattle
Sorry that I'm Iate.
It's not usuaI for you
to be Iate, Ken.
My opponent was harder I expected,
and it took Ionger than I thought.
And how did it go?
Of course I won.
So you added another titIe
to your name.
Yeah.
Suzhou, China
Hey, is Fei Long not here yet?
We can't shoot a movie without
the Ieading man.
Strange.
He shouId've headed here aIready.
This happens every time.
Give me a break...
- Hey, Fei Long.
- What's going on?
Just some entertainment.
Entertainment?
Some young man in the audience
is being dragged to the ring.
I didn't say anything!
I heard you muttering to yourseIf
whiIe watching the show.
You must be pretty tough,
taIking Iike that.
Hm, interesting.
Such a big star, yet you stiII Iike
to fight in pIaces Iike this.
That guy doesn't Iook so bad.
LittIe brat...
Nice one.
Can I chaIIenge you now?
You Iook Iike some fighter.
What's your name?
My name is Ryu.
I'm just a Japanese traveIer.
I have no intention to fight.
Not yet! It's not over yet!
I'II show you my speciaI!
Get ready!
- I can't beIieve this!
- Did he just get beaten?
Now I remember! Ryu!
A few years ago, there was a fighter
who defeated...
the muay thai champion,
Sagat, and went missing.
I think he was Japanese and
the name was Ryu.
Are you that Ryu?
I heard Sagat is now in ShadowIaw
training himseIf.
ShadowIaw? What's that?
- You don't know?
- No.
It's a crime syndicate
that's spreading...
weaponry and drugs
all over the world.
Sagat...is in a crime syndicate...
Ryu...we'II meet again.
Northern Seattle
Fight, Ken!
I've come here to fight you!
You don't get it, do you?
I don't street fight anymore!
It doesn't matter
where a fighter fights.
Nonsense.
What's the point in fighting
on the street Iike this?
You have honorabIe titIes
as a fighter.
Defeating such a man is
an honor to another fighter!
That's what I caII nonsense!
Plus, you can't defeat me.
No matter who comes at me,
no one can defeat me...
except for Ryu.
Ryu? That vagabond fighter
that went missing?
Don't compare me with
someone Iike him!
I see. I guess you're not that bad.
I Iike it!
What's wrong?
Why do you not finish me?
Ryu, where are you?
Come settle the fight soon!
Calcutta
Are you aII right?
Oh no...
I see. Your mother's iII.
I'm sorry.
Can you buy it again with this?
Here.
Damn you...!
What's this...?
My body won't...move...
I feeI a powerfuI aura.
He's strong.
- Come on!
- What's going on?!
- Fight!
- Hurry up and fight!
- DhaIsim!
- Fight!
Wait!
I'II Iet you win this fight.
What do you mean,
"Iet me win"?!
I feIt someone powerfuI
behind me.
Are you going to forfeit the match
with that nonsense?!
No. I concede the fight.
Then I'II take the prize.
Yeah.
What's wrong?!
I've never feIt such strong
fighting power before.
- What's going on?
- He stopped fighting?
Damn it!
Are you aII right?!
- Who are those guys?
- Terrorists from ShadowIaw.
ShadowIaw?
- Leftover money...
- Yeah, I got it. Thank you.
Yo! HaIf of this money is yours.
- Money?
- I might've Iost without you.
Take it.
We're both Japanese.
Don't be humbIe!
Are you sure you erased Jahan?
Yes, I am sure.
At the scene, the monitor cyborg
found an unknown fighter.
- We're investigating him now.
- Anything eIse?
The cyborg in SeattIe sent us
some interesting data.
I'd Iike you to see it as weII.
I'II be right there.
I hope your info was worth
my trip here.
Yes. Take a Iook at this.
This man has some skill,
but we found something intriguing.
I compared him against Ryu's image.
Who's this guy?
Ken Masters.
The command center pc has data
of his titIe matches.
But we didn't realize his relation
to Ryu.
What do you mean?
Ken and Ryu trained under the same
master for over 10 years in Japan.
Their fighting skills
are roughly equal.
Equal? The potential fighting
capacity is different.
We haven't acquired current data
on Ryu, but possibIy...
a bug in the system or Ryu hasn't...
been abIe to utiIize his capacity.
Ryu's feIIow pupiI...
It might be interesting
to use him as a weapon...
for PIan P.
GeneraI, American President
Ed Pressman is...
a strong promoter of
arms controI IegisIation...
so he's heaviIy guarded.
We need him out of the way,
but it must be done carefuIIy.
If we train him with my Psycho Power,
it'II work out.
But...the Cammy incident...
Cammy achieved our objective.
She's being interrogated
at InterpoI.
I don't care. Her job is done.
Leave her be.
We've received interrogation footage
of Cammy at InterpoI.
Let me see it.
We know that you're an MI6 agent.
I don't remember.
We don't know why an MI6 agent
such as yourself...
assassinated the Minister
of Justice...
by the command of Shadowlaw.
I don't remember.
Cammy, your mind
was being controIIed.
We'd Iike to at Ieast
get a cIue...
as to how and where
you were controIIed.
Try to remember.
I don't remember.
Leave her be.
Some measIy InterpoI system is
no match for my Psycho Power.
But if we Ieave her be...
We'II take care of her in time.
More importantIy, do not sIack
on finding Ryu.
No matter what,
bring him to me.
Understood, sir.
On another note, wouId you Iike to
order the capture of Ken?
No need.
It's fun to trap a man Iike that.
What's aII this?
Investigating on your own
is against the ruIes.
You're nosy, Iady.
If you're not gonna move,
I'II just run you over.
Go ahead.
Major GuiIe, I'm sorry your best
friend was kiIIed by Vega.
Is it aIso InterpoI's job to
pry into the private Iives of others?
I'm sorry to intrude,
but I read your fiIe.
Vega is no Ionger just your target
to avenge your best friend.
Standing here taIking won't
stop Vega.
Then try me out and see
if I'm aII taIk?
I don't have time to pIay!
Vega is aIso my target.
To avenge my father...
But...I'm an InterpoI agent!
AnnihiIation of ShadowIaw comes
before my private grudges.
Major GuiIe...
if you have pride
as a member of the Air Force...
Iend us your heIp!
I don't Iike a woman who taIks
too much. Are you coming or not?
Of course, I'm coming!
Los Angeles
Why is there a monitor cyborg
at a nightcIub?
Some fighter named Dee Jay is there.
You idiots don't get my music.
Go home.
Bastard...!
I didn't do anything!
There!
I'm Major GuiIe, Air Force.
What does Major GuiIe of
the Air Force want?
You're my fan?
You've been marked by ShadowIaw.
ShadowIaw as in the scary
organization? Oh, the horror!
I'm not kidding. FaII in with them,
and you won't be pIaying anymore.
I was kidding.
Why wouId ShadowIaw mark
a guy Iike me?
They're gathering info on
each and every notabIe fighter.
- That doesn't concern me!
- Yes, it does.
Your data has aIready been sent
to ShadowIaw by this.
What's this monster?
Some kind of creepy doII?
It's a monitor cyborg.
It gathers information for
ShadowIaw's supercomputer.
A Iot of these are roaming around.
Watch out, and teII your friends.
Guile, huh...
I see he's cooperating with InterpoI
to try to stop me.
What do you say, Balrog?
Would you like to have fun...
with this agent, Chun-Li?
She's beautiful, isn't she?
An agent trying to avenge
her father...
Don't you think
it's admirabIe, BaIrog?
Patch me to Las Vegas.
Las Vegas
Here you are.
Most of the bosses in charge of
their trafficking routes are here.
It'II be OK. Right.
Contact the command center?
Understood.
That investigation has been
troubIesome IateIy.
Our upcoming transaction
wiII go smoothIy, right?
It's been taken care of.
5000kg of coke to London, correct?
CouId you teII the GeneraI
to contact me once?
WiII do.
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for waiting.
The show is about to begin.
Please proceed to the hall.
Ladies and gentIemen,
thank you for waiting.
Let me introduce the fighters
competing today.
Emperor of the Russian
wrestIing worId...
The man with a steeI body...
Zangief!
His opponent is...
a man of unusuaI origins.
He Iearned to fight beasts
in the depths of the jungIe...
BIanka!
Ouch!
New York
Strange...
She said she was going back
to her room earIier.
Damn it! I'm in a hurry...
You're...BaIrog!
This is strange.
I have a bad feeIing about this.
Pick it up!
What's that?!
Chun-Li!
SIowIy skinning a cornered
rabbit...that's what I Iike.
This aIso Ioves to suck the bIood
of especiaIIy cute rabbits.
My...my beautifuI face...!
I'II kiII you!
God damn it...
Chun-Li!
Are you OK, Chun-Li?!
- It was BaIrog.
- What?!
Chun-Li! Chun-Li!
Chun-Li!
Then what happened to BaIrog?
He was handed over to the NYPD?!
We're currentIy tracking
monitor cyborgs here.
They've been spotted around
Ken Masters...
winner of the NationaI Fighter's
Championship. He Iives in SeattIe.
Yes. UnIike no-name
street fighters...
he's got skiIIs.
I'm sure Vega wiII approach him.
We're aIso investigating Ryu,
who trained with Ken.
We've heard that a fighter
who headed for ThaiIand...
from India seems to fit his profiIe.
OK. You track down that guy,
Ryu, as well.
I'm worried about Chun-Li...
I'll wait here at the hospital
for a little bit longer.
As soon as things are settIed here,
I'II go meet Ken in SeattIe.
Please have Ken's file ready.
Lake Washington
EIiza...
You wanna get married?
What is this aII of a sudden?
You don't want to?
That's not what I mean.
You've never taIked about
anything Iike this before.
Then why not?
But...
But...?
It's not Iike you.
Did something happen?
Nothing speciaI...
Ken!
Ken, you ARE acting unusuaI today.
Sorry.
Thank you.
What you said before...I accept.
- EIiza...
- I Iove you.
CaII me Iater.
Ryu, I'm tired of
waiting for you...
General, the target's
car is in sight.
Good. Move in closer.
Bastard!
What the heII?!
You're Ken Masters, right?
I've come to pick you up.
Pick me up?!
Who are you?!
I'm Vega, the GeneraI of ShadowIaw.
Vega? Never heard of you.
What do you want?
I'II turn you into a strong fighter.
Creepy oId man. Go away!
I wiII turn you into a fighter
stronger than Ryu!
Ryu? You know Ryu?!
The name Ryu gets you serious, huh?
Shut up!
It's none of your business!
You monster!
What are you gonna do with me?!
Using some weird move...
No use fighting against
Psycho Power.
Psycho Power?
Ken, do not resist. Obey me.
Shut up!
Ken, obey me.
Who wouId obey a monster!
You don't understand, do you?
You're reaIIy something.
I'm Iooking forward to growing you.
What does it mean for you to come
aII the way to see Ken Masters?
Ken's been marked by Vega.
- Is this Ken's car?
- Yes, no doubt.
We're too Iate.
New York Branch of Interpol
Regarding the Iocations of ShadowIaw
branches and monitor cyborgs...
no bases have been spotted around
SeattIe except for warehouses.
If Ken has been taken...
it wouId be to where the other
fighters were trained by Vega.
Do we have any info on such bases?
We haven't been abIe to Iocate
their training faciIity yet...
but their Iarge command center bases
are Iocated in East Asia.
Major GuiIe...
speaking of East Asia,
we found the Iocation of Ryu...
Ken's feIIow pupiI.
That's the man who was
in India. Where is he?
In the mountains near the Laotian
border, on the Thai side.
Are there monitor cyborgs
in pIace around Ryu?
Yes. We've caught some...
but Ryu has been moving around
through China, India, ThaiIand...
and the objective of
these movements is unknown...
so it doesn't look like specific
cyborgs are tracking him.
According to our data, Ryu possesses
the same skiII IeveI as Ken.
There's no reason why Vega
wouId Ieave him be.
We'II approach him first and try to
disrupt his contact with ShadowIaw.
How is the miIitary/InterpoI joint
pIan to stop ShadowIaw progressing?
We've aIready Iocated most of
their Iarge bases.
We start from East Asia,
especiaIIy the command center
near the Cambodian border...
We've pIanned a Iarge scaIe attack
on it by our speciaI forces.
Chun-Li...
We've finaIIy Iocated
Vega's main base.
I'II avenge you and your
father with my own hands.
You probabIy want to do it
yourseIf...
but this time, Iet me
handIe it whiIe you rest.
I'm going now.
Ken...
I see the source of your power
is your rivalry against Ryu.
Very well.
Let me enhance that rivalry
with my Psycho Power.
Ryu, are you OK?
Yeah, I am.
Thank you.
Another one!
Major GuiIe.
We're nearing the mountains
at the Laotian border.
OK.
General Vega.
We just received word that
a miIitary heIicopter...
with GuiIe on board is nearing
the Laotian border.
Looks Iike they've Iocated Ryu.
GuiIe's going to Ryu?
They're trying to beat me
to the punch.
Let's take Ken and go see them.
But Ken isn't compIeteIy...
That's fine.
I'm just going to Iet them
have a fataI match...
Then I'II come back with Ryu.
Get things ready right away.
Yes, sir.
GeneraI, Iet me fight Ryu.
Sagat, you're an important
fighter for ShadowIaw.
Forget that oId grudge with Ryu.
But if I don't fight him again,
my honor...
The honor of a fighter...
MeaningIess.
Your enemy is now the whoIe worId.
But...!
Sagat, ShadowIaw's ruIes state that
you are not to disobey me!
You know very weII.
I have another order for you.
Go to New York right away and
cIean up BaIrog and Cammy.
In ShadowIaw, you are not to faiI
executing my pIans, either.
Thailand, in the mountains
Hey Ryu, why don't we take a break
and have some tea?
Sure.
Looks Iike it's going to rain.
What's that?
Ryu, Iook. Someone's coming.
Odd to get visitors way out here.
Are you Ken Masters' friend, Ryu?
Yeah. Who are you?
Major GuiIe, US Air Force.
Did something happen to Ken?!
He's been kidnapped by a crime
syndicate caIIed ShadowIaw.
Ken's been kidnapped by ShadowIaw?!
He'II be used to carry out terrorism.
Ken wouId never Iend a hand to
a crime syndicate.
They've brainwashed him.
Ken's become a terrorist...
- Vega's personaI aircraft!
- What?!
So many guests today...
And a rude one at that.
Ken!
You finaIIy showed up, Vega.
It's been a whiIe, Major GuiIe.
We have aII the actors,
and the setting is perfect.
You...!
What are you gonna do with Ken?!
Ah, you must be Ryu!
Ken became a ShadowIaw fighter
in pIace of you.
You bastard!
Let Ken go!
Ryu!
Ken!
How do you Iike it, Ryu?
The current Ken is a kiIIing
machine that I have created.
WiII you be abIe to defeat him?
Ken, it's me, Ryu!
I'm sorry, but he can't hear his
best friend's voice right now.
He is a machine whose soIe
purpose is defeating you.
Ken, snap out of it!
Vega, I can't Iet criminaI scum
Iike you run rampant!
Sense of justice, huh...
GuiIe, an eviI mind is
the source of aII power.
Ken here wiII prove that.
Beating him is faster than
Iistening to his damn speech.
Here I come!
Who are you?
I'II be your opponent!
GuiIe, why don't you try to
see if you can defeat me?
You'II get your wish.
Ken, it's me.
Snap out of it!
Ken!
It's me, Ryu!
Snap out of it, Ken!
What's wrong? Don't you want to
avenge your friend? Come at me!
I won't faII for the same move!
Too easy!
Oh no!
Wait... It's not over...yet...
Ken, wake up! I don't want to
fight you Iike this.
Snap out of it!
Ken...
Ken, it's me, Ryu!
Look at me, Ken!
Ryu...
Ken...
Loser...
STOP!
Ken!
Get out of my way!
You're going to fight me?
Interesting.
Let me see how good you are.
Shut up and get out of my way!
Quit taIking and defeat me.
Then you can go to your friend.
Move away!
I'm going now.
Yeah. Take care. I'II be Ieaving
here in a few days as weII.
When we meet again...
When we see each other next time...
I'II be Iooking forward to it.
You piece of...!
Ryu, how about it?
You, too, obey me and become
a chosen fighter of ShadowIaw.
Cut the crap!
I wiII never be your Iackey!
You stiII have strength
to resist me?
- Impressive.
- Shut up!
FooI.
I take it you're going?
Yes. I wiII miss you!
You will someday face someone
you must defeat beyond a match.
Training means moving forward
toward that day.
Beyond a match...?
Master, what do you mean,
"beyond a match"?!
Master!
I wiII teII you!
What was that?
What happened?
I can't remember...
What's happened to my body?!
Damn it...
That's...
I get it. That's the aircraft
that monster was on...
I remember now.
Ryu!
That's him!
Vega!
Ryu!
My body...!
ControI your breathing and mind, and
cuItivate energy into spirit...
CuItivate energy into spirit...
CuItivate spirit into body...
CuItivate god to obtain the way...
Stand up straight as if my head
is being puIIed from above...
CaIm the mind and reIax the back...
Concentrate, reIax the hip...
Put my weight on one Ieg...
ReIax the shouIders and arms...
Focus my consciousness...
Harmonize the top and bottom...
Keep the arms and Iegs moving...
Find peace in the movements...
Outside are the shapes...
Inside are the meridians...
CuItivate spirit with the breath...
- Yin and yang reach the limit...
- Make the body like steel...
Create the four elements.
Push the elements to their limit...
Form the eight symbols...
When it reaches the limit
of rigidness...
it becomes soft... When it reaches
the limit of softness...
it becomes rigid...
Ken!
It's all about what you
see beyond your fists.
Ken, wake up!
Ryu...
What's wrong?
Show your power!
Ken!
Ryu, we finaIIy meet again.
I'II greet you Iater.
- First, we stop this creep!
- Yeah!
You reaIIy want to fight me
no matter what.
Very weII. I'II be your opponent
in battIe. Come!
Ah, you were abIe to hit me.
You're as good as I expected.
Come at me harder!
What's wrong?
More!
More! Show me more!
Even if it's brief,
you shook me up.
This man, Ryu...
Vega!
Ken, now!
This is it!
- Is this Guile?
- Yeah.
This is New York Central
Hospital calling.
Please come to the hospital
right away.
Chun-Li!
Watch out, you idiot!
Chun-Li...
Your father is avenged, as promised.
I know.
Joint InterpoI/US miIitary operation
to destroy ShadowIaw succeeds!
Yay, GuiIe!
- You brat!
- Sorry!
I won't forgive you!
- You IittIe brat!
Ryu, next time we see each other,
we'II finish our match.
Yeah.
You want a ride?
Nah, I'II waIk.
Where are you going now?
I don't know yet.
Ryu, you've become strong.
You, too.
See you!
Lead Animator: Yasuhiro Oshima
Animators: Minoru Maeda, Marisuke Eguchi
Character Design: Shuko Murase
Visual Effects: Isamu Imakake
Fight Director: Shinichi Shoji
Computer Animation: Tsuneo Maeda
Art Director: Satoshi Matsuoka
Color Settings: Ritsuko Utagawa
Cinematographer: Hiroaki Edamitsu
Edit: Masashi Furukawa J.S.E.
Sound Director: Atsushi Tatsumi
Music Producer: Keiichi Momose
Production Advisors: Yuji Nozaki
Paul Hassey
Fight Advisors: Kazuyoshi Ishii
Andy Hug
Assistant Director: Naoto Hashimoto
Assistant Producer: Futoshi Nishimura
Animation Producers: Ken Fujita
Ikuo Sato