You again!
You threw up in my cab.
Took me hours to clean it!
You're not worth the $15 fare!
Shut up!
Stay back, or I'll kill her!
Stay back!
Calm down, Mr. Wong
Let me see your boss Eric Chow
Or I'll kill this bastard
Tell me! How did you cheat me of my money?
I didn't, sir, I'm sorry
You seemed arrogant enough just now
You were forcing me to repay you.
Now you're backing out?
Stay back!
Mr. Wong!
Calm down, Mr. Wong!
Stop talking and call the press!
I'm prepared to die
Fine
Where's the press?
There's a grenade; I'm not going there
Calm down Mr. Wong, the press is here
Say anything, just calm down
Please
Point the camera at me
Come out, Eric Chow
You leach, you forced me
to gamble on stocks...
You said I'd make big money
and everything would be fine
Told me to use company funds
You want my life?
Here it is
Eric you bastard, come out!
Come out!
What are you doing?
Stay back! Calm down!
Nobody move!
Inspector Chan! Get the hostage!
Open the manhole cover!
There! Quick!
Get down!
Are you all right?
I'm fine, disperse the crowd
Go! Give me back my money!
Thank you, Officer Chan
He's crazy
In stocks, some win, some lose
Throw the book at him
Put him in jail
I'd be broke if everyone's like him
Who are you?
Here's my card
I'm Eric Chow
Call me if you want to speculate
Don't just stand there, move it,
collect the evidence
Yes, sir. I'll help you
Good thing you wore two bulletproof vests
Look at you, so you've got a few awards
So proud of yourselves
You think we're that good?
Chiu, you worked crowd control
How did all those people get past you?
All the reporters became hostages as well
A lot of people could have been hurt
Were you controlling the crowd
or was the crowd controlling you?
Come here, Hong
How can you let the criminal
draw faster than you?
Didn't I teach you how to draw? Show me
Your jacket is in the way
Your pocket is too full
Put in a lucky stone
Listen to your future brother-in-law;
stay sharp!
Yes, sister
Everyone, take lunch
Great, lunchtime!
Wing, don't you have something
to say to me today?
What?
Don't you have a birthday message
for the rest of your team?
Do I have to?
Happy birthday; let's eat!
Open the safe!
Open it!
I'm just a worker
We're the bomb!
Do you have a phone?
Yes
Call the cops!
Don't hurt me, I'm just a worker
Just a worker
Police! Drop your guns!
They're heavily armed --
Three, four...
Five! Okay!
Five, six...
Calm down!
Yeah, man!
Go!
Don't move!
Drop your guns!
Check the alley Yes, sir!
Clear
Kin!
The Bank of Asia was robbed today
by 5 masked gun men...
Listen, Joe gets 100 points.
Fire and Tin Tin 80 each, me 60.
20 points for hitting a cop
30 points for an officer
10 if you blow up a police car
That's $1 million per point,
The rest goes in the pot
But Sue you dropped the money,
You lose 200 points
Nonsense! No one helped me!
How can you do this to me?
Stop fighting about money.
Money is not important
Sue, another mistake and you're out
The police held a press conference
Senior Inspector Chan said:
3 hours
We're confident we'll get them in 3 hours
Their actions of challenging the police...
show that they're just naive crooks
I guarantee to the public...
we'll put them away
Are you okay?
Sam
I almost died
I want to get out of the hospital
and catch them myself
Don't worry, we'll get them tonight
You have any leads?
My informant found their hide-out
They plan to use police officers as targets
Notify SDU
Don't you know, I am the SDU!
Don't worry, Sam
We're better than the SDU
Yes, you guys...
Some thugs from a finance company
came to see you today
Don't worry, I'll pay the debt
If you need help, tell me
I'll do what I can
Sure
Wing...
Show no mercy in dealing with them
They're crazy
Sneak out for a drink tonight if you can
I.D. them tomorrow if you're okay
I admire your self-confidence
You must quit gambling
Stay in the car, relax,
let me take care of this
Looking for a promotion?
Why not? Hurry, I have things to do later
Me too
I must pack for my vacation tonight
Leave it to me, sir!
Nice try
It's not your turn yet
Get to work
We'll relax at dinner
Separate into two teams, A Team goes first
Yes sir!
Move!
Clear! Clear!
Someone's there! Calm down
Don't move or I'll shoot! Don't move!
Split up into A and B, two men stay here
Copy!
Time to play!
What?
Don't panic!
Inspector Chan...
Tin Ming?
He can't hear you
Tin Ming!
Rick!
Hoi, stay here with the men
Yes, sir!
Hong, come with me
Where are they? Where did they go?
Stay back!
Freeze!
Tin Ming!
Open up!
Quick!
Gunfire!
Where are they?
Quiet!
Hold on
Come out!
Kwong...
Inspector Chan...
Stay calm
Someone's there
Hong, stay!
Hong!
Stop!
Inspector Chan, help me!
Brother-in-law...
Hong! Brother-in-law...
Hold on, Hong!
What happened?
Help me...
Where are you?
Come out! Why did you do this?
The fact that you're still alive
doesn't mean you're better
It just means we're not done
playing with you yet
Who are you?
We're cop haters
Let them go
After you drop your gun
Let them go!
No!
Chiu!
I'll say this once
What do you want?
To play with you
You're the police pistol champion right?
You must know how to field strip a gun
let's see who does it faster
Come on!
What are the rules?
These are your men's guns
Whoever assembles them the fastest wins
We're playing for two men
Okay
Ready, One...
Two...
Three!
Help, Brother-in-law!
You lose!
No!
What else do you want to play?
My turn!
You're the police combat coach
I bet I can beat you in 20 seconds
For two men
Sure
Ready... Go!
Good-bye!
No!
You lost again!
Kill me too!
Aren't you the bragger who said...
you'd get us in 3 hours?
You're less sure now, aren't you?
Let them go!
On your knees
Kowtow!
Please let them go
Okay, one more chance
Same rules
Come on
Okay
For four this time!
Bravo!
Okay!
Ready? Go!
Great!
But you took 3 seconds too long.
Take one for each second
Yes, sir!
No!
Why?
Brother-in-law, go
Hong, hang in there!
Don't kill him yet
Hong!
Wake up!
You're okay, hang on
Bombs! I've got to get them out
Hong, hold on! I'll get you out
Help!
Stop the robbers!
Out of my way!
Move it!
Move it! Get out!
You drunk!
His wallet
He's a cop
Just for that, let's go!
There are so many great things waiting for you
Forget the past, turn your pain into your power
Who are you?
PC 1667 reporting for duty!
I'm your partner Frank Cheng
I don't need a partner
I'm taking a year off
Inspector Tai cancelled your leave
Don't touch my stuff
But it's a mess
Your attitude is unacceptable
In order to change your life,
You must first change yourself
Throw out useless things...
so you can find what you want
Stop nagging and get me some water!
Your girlfriend was here
She has something very important
for me to give to you
A ring
Don't touch it, just go
I have more to say
Please listen to me
Listen
The bank robbers from 3 months ago
pulled another job...
we lost many men
Inspector Tai wants you to handle this case
Of the thousands of policemen
in Hong Kong, why me?
I don't know why, he didn't say
They're insane they're not doing it for money
and recently...
they've turned your case into an online game
I think they're using the online game to
Don't talk about the case anymore,
get out of here!
Go! Go away! Listen to me sir...
Go!
Inspector Chan, it's me
You again! Leave me alone!
I'm at your girlfriend's home
Is something wrong?
Of course
What happened to her?
Why else would I call?
How is she?
Come quickly
Don't go anywhere, I'm coming
Smells good!
It's better with more olive oil
Let me taste
It's hot
It's good
Of course
I've given him the ring
He was shocked to see it
He cares for you
He just can't forgive himself
Who is it?
Just come in
Sit down
What are you doing here?
I only did what you asked
and now you're kicking me out?
You asked me to buy it, It's about $200
and $500 for hurting my eyes
I thought you forgot
He chose the cake, I just delivered it
Happy Birthday to You...
Happy Birthday to You
It's a happy day, smile
Make a wish, blow out the candle
Oh, I forgot the door
Sit down
Eat while it's warm
What are you writing?
Nothing
I know
sorry
Why don't you throw them away?
Why should I?
You can't throw away the memory
I know you won't forgive me
That's only what you think
I'm a nurse and all the time I'm wondering...
If there's a cure for missing someone
What do you think?
There is
It's to see the person you miss
What if you don't?
In time it becomes...
a memory
I understand
I can't forgive myself
Does drinking help?
You want to avenge your team,
But all you're doing is...
drinking yourself to death
So catch them as fast as you can
How else can you get even for your men?
I've researched them for you
They're not after money
Let me finish
My research indicates...
they love video games
The weapons they use...
are European imports which indicates...
it's not cheap stuff. These guys are rich
Go home
Help! Over there!
I've been robbed!
Police! Freeze!
My bag!
How dare you?
Get him!
Go to hell!
No...
Get away!
Wake up! Stop him!
Chan, you're a policeman. Stop the thief!
You again? Move it!
Move it!
You're a policeman!
You asked for it!
Ow!
Let go of me, drunk!
You'll break my arm...
I was greedy and I...
took her bag, sorry
I feel very...
How do you spell guilty?
I... forgot
Guilty?
As in I am guilty?
Look it up in jail; you'll have time
Then you'll remember it
Write gully, it's close enough
Madam
I need a tissue
I'll get it
How do we get them to their cells?
Just do it
I mean, how?
Sorry, I'm new here
Go
Say a good word for us
Thank you
Stop crying
Remember to look up guilty
What did they do?
Misdemeanor
I'm Frank Cheng senior inspector...
I'm not done yet
I'm the senior inspector's partner
PC 1667
I...
I'm Sasa, technical support
Look everyone, our hero's back
What award do you want this time?
You're not ashamed?
You're not welcome here
Who are you, the Police Commissioner?
Who are you?
PC 1667, sir!
Who's your superior?
I'm on the Bank of Asia case, sir
I didn't know I had a partner
I didn't mean you. I'm with Inspector Chan
I'm in charge of this case, not him
Go ahead, go with him
I transferred to be with you, not him
Can he solve this case?
Let me tell you Chan's story
He led 9 men on a mission
They all died, didn't you know?
All of us here have lost...
someone close
Because of his arrogance!
Tell me, who's responsible for their deaths?
Yes, sir!
But I know he solved...
every other case before the Bank of Asia
He's here to finish the job
So if you're afraid...
he'll solve it faster than you...
I'll completely understand, sir!
All right, I'll let the two of you work on it
See who solves it first!
What's at stake?
The loser kowtows and apologizes
I accept
Who asked you?
Inspector Chan?
I refuse to bet
He offered
Loser will resign
Stop!
Deal!
Where are we going?
Home, to sleep
We made a bet
We'll lose for sure
Why did you bet?
I don't want to be a cop
But I'm your partner!
Why must you investigate this case?
Who are you?
PC 1667
And?
I am Kwong's younger brother
Remember your teammate Kwong?
I'm his brother
I must get the gang that killed him
So you know your way home
Where were you last night?
I had a meeting, none of your business
You're my wife!
If I can't handle you,
how can I handle the police?
What are you, just trash!
You're just a cop
People are nice to you because of my dad
Lucky your son's not like you
You think you're great...
because you're a superintendent
What are you talking about?
I've worked hard to get where I am
Your son is just like you, trash!
What? You spoiled him!
What kind of a father are you?
All you do is beat him
Get up! Trash
Look at the time
Look!
All you do is surf the web
and spend money all day
I'm the chief superintendent,
you've made me lose face
Look at yourself, you're not like me at all!
Trash!
Joe, don't mind him
If you don't want to work today, stay home
Mommy will give you some money
Do what you want, okay?
Recently, citizens complained...
about police attitude
I say again
When on duty, police officers...
must be lawful and fair
I guarantee the police will...
handle problems properly and justly
You know, guys, when you found that
one thing that gets you really excited,
it's higher than any drug in the world!
Oh, man!
I told you they love video games
They turned your case into an online game
Who are they?
Hard to say, they posted it
on servers from different countries
Sasa
This is the alley behind the Bank of Asia
Watch this criminal...
before and after entering the alley
The bag
Sam ran into them there
That means he's with them
Sam?
Why do you always wear this?
This jacket is important to me
What do you want?
Sam Wong
Who is Sam Wong?
One of your bosses
He used to be a cop
Sam Wong?
Don't know him; beat it!
Don't shove me!
Careful!
Move it!
How dare you?
What are you doing?
Police!
Help!
Calm down!
You hit a policeman
Don't come out!
Oh! He's the man!
Wing
What's up, Sam?
Why are you hiding here?
I'm not hiding, it's business
Sam
What?
Boss wants you
What's up, boss?
Why are the police here?
Don't think you're so great
because you're a shareholder
It won't happen again
Next time I can't protect you
Yes sir
Get out of here!
I'm here about the robbery
Only you were in that alley
Wing, I really can't remember
I can't remember
You were a policeman, shouldn't
you have been more observant?
Do you remember...
a woman with a bag?
You're talking nonsense, kid!
Wing, I really can't remember
Don't ask me again
I quit the force because of this case
I welcome you as a friend
But if you want my help, I'm sorry
Sam
They were like my brothers; Help me
All I know is, one is a woman
They love to play X-Games
I pulled this watch from her
That's all I can do
Why didn't you tell us earlier?
Be careful
This is the X-Crusader's logo
A gang of X-Gamers
They're at the roof of Shing Mau Center today
Got it, Thanks, bye
X-Game
B-Team, follow them
How stupid!
The red-haired one
Move in!
Move, police business!
The cops are here
Try to get out, I'll meet you downstairs
Find them for me or you'll be sorry
Be careful
Everyone quiet!
Your friend