...and what these Leviticus verses
have to do with anything.
- What are you doing?
- Getting started.
- You can keep talking if you want.
- Don't you need to look over these?
I got it.
Cat!
How'd you get in?
No one has asked me about
Magda in over 40 years.
Why would a lady like you want
to know about an awful murder?
- It interests me.
- Does it?
Her husband was the first suspect.
The husband is always
the first suspect and usually the last.
But not this time.
We moved on to a neighbor.
Then a vagrant.
Once you get to strangers,
it's only a matter of time...
...before you get to gypsies and you
know you're never going to solve it.
How exactly was she killed?
- Miss?
- Salander.
Miss Salander. I hope you don't mind
me asking, but when did you last eat?
I have a high metabolism.
I can't put on weight.
I'm asking because it is better to look
at what I am about to show you...
...on an empty stomach.
If a man's offering is a lamb,
it shall be a female without blemish.
He should lay his hand
upon its head...
... slaughter it, empty its blood
on the base of the altar...
... and he shall be forgiven.
- How is he?
- He needs surgery...
...but there's no DNR in place.
So it's up to the family to decide...
...should the occasion arise,
whether to resuscitate or not.
And they're not good at decisions.
So how was it with Miss Salander?
She said yes. Do you think
I might be able to see him?
He was asleep the last time I looked,
but let me check.
- Thank you.
- Don't check.
Tell him to pack his things
and leave.
- Mother, please.
- Don't use that tone with me.
Isabella, Mr. Blomkvist
works for Henrik.
- We should put this to a vote.
- Don't be an idiot, Birger.
We all know what Henrik wants.
Can we just do that?
Henrik is fighting for his life in there.
This is the last thing he needs.
Excuse me, Mrs. Vanger,
there is no smoking in here.
Go back to Stockholm.
When we need a family chronicle
written by a libelist...
...we know who to call.
All right. Thanks.
This way, miss.
If a woman approaches any beast...
... and lies with it, you shall kill
the woman and the beast.
Their blood shall be upon them.
My family's impossible.
That's why the company's
such a mess.
I apologize for my
mother's behavior.
I'm used to it.
It has nothing to do with you.
It's between her and Henrik.
She lost it when my father died,
and her drinking and her...
Got so bad Henrik took me
and my sister away from her...
...and left her excommunicated
in the old house...
...on the other side of the island.
She hasn't forgiven him.
You must stay.
You're the last chance Henrik has
at some kind of resolution.
Put this to rest one way or another.
I'll keep my mother away.
But please, hurry.
Of course.
Lisbeth.
- I'll get that.
- It's okay.
- Martin Vanger.
- How do you do?
Fine.
- It's a girlfriend, or?
- Assistant.
Thank you so much.
- Good night.
Problems finding the place?
Everyone in town knows
who and where you are.
That's comforting. Are you hungry?
I can make you a sandwich.
No.
I used to have a motorbike,
a Triumph.
I know.
The five cases from Harriet's list.
And five more she missed.
Three I'm sure of.
Rebecka was the first,
just as you thought.
The second, M.H., is Mari Holmberg,
a prostitute in Kalmar...
...murdered in 1954,
matching Leviticus 20:18.
Right. "If a man lies with a woman
having her sickness...
...he has made naked her fountain
and she has uncovered...
...the fountain of her blood."
Raped and stabbed, but cause of death
was suffocation by sanitary napkin.
- Okay.
- R.L. Rakel Lunde, 1957.
A cleaning woman
and part-time palm reader.
Tied with a clothesline, gagged, raped.
Head crushed with a rock.
Leviticus 20:27.
"A woman who is a medium
or sorceress...
...shall be put to death by stoning."
- I usually like to smoke outside.
- Sara Witt, 1964.
Daughter of a pastor.
Tied to her bed.
Raped. Charred in the fire
that burned down her house.
Leviticus 21:9.
"The daughter of a priest who profanes
herself by playing the harlot...
...profanes her father
and shall be burned with fire."
Magda Lovisa Sjöberg, 1960.
Found in a barn.
Stabbed and raped with farm tools.
The cow in the next stall
had its throat slit.
Its blood was splashed on her
and hers on it.
Leviticus 20:16.
"If a woman lies with any beast...
...you shall kill the woman and the
beast. Their blood is upon them."
Lea Persson, 1962.
Found by her sister in their pet shop.
Raped, beaten.
The killer uncaged the animals,
smashed the aquariums.
There was a parakeet inside her.
Next, Eva Gustavsson, 1960.
A runaway. Raped, strangled.
A burnt pigeon tied around her neck.
Lena Andersson, 1967. A student.
Raped, stabbed, decapitated...
- Okay.
- I'm not finished.
We're looking for
a serial murderer...
...but what could that have to do
with a teenager living on an island?
She was looking for him too.
Rape. Torture. Fire.
Animals. Religion.
- Am I missing anything?
- The names.
They're all Biblical.
The first woman, the whore,
the Virgin Mary.
Rebecka, Sara,
all from the Old Testament.
Which means they're all Jewish.
One thing the Vangers have more than
their fair share of, it's anti-Semites.
There's one right there.
I can sleep on a couch.
Okay.
Right.
Oh, yeah, there might be
a cat somewhere.
- Good night.
- Night.
Harriet's name isn't.
Isn't what?
- Jewish.
- No.
- What are you doing?
- Reading your notes.
They're encrypted.
Please. Have some coffee.
Okay.
Then we're gonna have
a very serious conversation...
...about what's yours
and what's mine.
It's amazing what you figured out
with the parade photos.
Thank you.
- It's too bad you don't have hers.
- Whose?
Her.
Can l...? Sorry.
Yeah, all right.
Close that.
No. Not that.
That's the one. Yep.
Where the fuck is that? That's down
there, isn't it? Okay. Oh, yeah, yeah.
And...
What does that say there?
- "N" something "R-S-J."
- That's "Norsjö," yeah.
Then something "K."
Something "R-l-F."
"Carpentry."
Well, we need to find a carpenter.
Fuck!
The carpentry shop is gone. I don't
even know if he worked there or not...
...but if he did, maybe he used
to come in here for hardware.
I don't recognize him. Sorry.
Well, I had to start somewhere.
I'm no detective, but 1966, I would
have started at a retirement home.
This is Brännlund's kid.
Do you know where I might find him?
The son?
Next to his father at the cemetery.
He was killed in an accident
on a construction site, years ago.
But...
...she might still be alive.
His widow.
Do you know where
I might find her?
Please drive to highlighted route.
In 1966, you were in Hedestad
with your husband.
Who took these?
A local photographer.
You were taking pictures
too that day...
...and I'd love to look at them
if by some miracle you have them.
It wouldn't be a miracle.
We were on our honeymoon.
But why?
This girl here. Here, you can see
her better in the enlargement.
See, that's you there.
Just after this was taken...
...after she'd seen something
across the street, she was murdered.
How awful.
- There you are.
- Thank you.
Would you mind if I made
a copy of this?
No.
I can't give you any of this stuff without
authorization from Mr. Armansky.
So call him.
Next time,
fill out the proper paperwork.
Which one are you?
Going down.
How's your sex life?
I didn't care much
for your last report.
It felt perfunctory,
like your heart wasn't in it.
Let's see a little more enthusiasm
for my recovery in next month's.
Don't speak. I don't want to hear
your voice, just nod.
Start looking for a shrink
you can bribe...
...to swear under oath he can find
absolutely nothing wrong with me.
And stop visiting
tattoo-removal websites.
Or I'll do it again...
...right here.
- Is that dental floss?
- Yes.
You're gonna sterilize that, right?
Couldn't we just use tape
or something?
No.
What?
Thank you. Jesus!
- Drink.
- Okay.
Just be careful. It's my eye.
- Don't move.
- You're not a doctor.
- Take off your wet clothes.
- What?
Yeah. Thank you.
Yeah, I think it has stopped bleeding.
It still fucking hurts, though.
Madness.
I mean, madness.
This is fucking madness.
You're okay, you're okay,
you're okay.
Jesus, that hurts. Fuck.
This is insane.
I mean, these people...
Somebody was shooting at me.
I mean, it wasn't an accident.
No one's shooting at you now.
You know, I'm pretty sure
this is a bad idea.
Why?
I'm old and we work together...
You work with what's-her-name
and that's worked out for you.
Yeah, well, I do have some standards,
believe it or not.
You need to stop talking.
Oh, shit.
Do you want me to open the window?
- I like working with you.
- I like working with you too.
- It could have been a stray shot.
- Not by Gunnar.
If he wanted to shoot him,
he wouldn't be here.
And then we have poachers.
They shoot at anything that moves.
Or he's right, Dirch. What if he is?
This has to stop.
Do you want to stop, Mikael?
Look, I have police reports, photos...
...Henrik's notes, my notes,
Lisbeth's research.
What I don't have is Vanger Industries'
records. That's what I want.
- Why?
- Will you authorize it?
What, the private corporate records?
Well, how far back?
Henrik said I could have access
to everything. This is what I need.
- That's not what he meant.
- I'll sign a nondisclosure statement.
Just a minute.
I think Henrik would say yes.
That's why he has me, to protect
him from himself. It's insane.
What have we got to hide?
After 120 years of business,
probably a lot.
If this is what he needs to finish,
he should have permission.
What am I looking for?
Any connections between
Vanger Industries...
...and the towns
where the women were killed.
And everything about Frode.
Your father was taking pictures
that day that no one has seen.
- I'd like to take a look at them.
- So ask him.
- I was wondering if you could do that.
- I don't speak to him.
Could you make an exception
in my case?
Are you afraid to be
in the same room with him?
I'm not saying you shouldn't be.
So you won't help me?
Sorry.
Please?
- Are you finished?
- I need to know where all factories...
...offices and projects
were from 1949 to 1966.
- You already have everything.
- No, I don't.
Nothing on subsidiary corporations,
partnerships or suppliers.
- You'll have to do without.
- Mr. Frode said I have access...
...to whatever I need. I need this.
- You have access to this floor.
Call him.
Thank you for seeing me.
Come in.
- Tea?
- Please.
Sven Olov Lindholm.
Me.
Handsome.
Birger Furugård.
Me.
Per Engdahl.
But your interest is in my more
candid photographic work.
Friends, relations, that kind of thing.
Please.
"Blom" or "Bloom"?
Blomkvist.
I'm not a recluse.
I don't close my door to anybody.
Thank you.
They just don't visit.
Well...
...perhaps if you redecorated.
Hide the past like they do?
Under a thin, shiny veneer?
Like an IKEA table?
I am the most honest of all of them.
- The family?
- Sweden.
Landscape?
Some nice landscapes there?
Who is this?
The blurry one.
I can't tell.
Oh, that's Gottfried's boy.
- That's Martin.
- Yeah.
Handsome but useless young man,
like his father.
Like his father.
- We're closing.
- Nowhere near finished.
- I'm not authorized to stay late.
- I am.
And I need access to everything,
including anything that's locked.
Call Frode.
Leave the keys with the guard.
Come on.
Shit!
Martin?
Mikael.
Hi there.
Your evening stroll?
Yes, that's right, I...
- How are you?
- Good.
I stopped by the hospital
on my way home.
Henrik asked me
to ask you something.
What was that?
Come on in. I'll make you a drink.
Hello, Martin.
Shut the door. It's quite windy.
- What happened to you?
- When?
Just now.
I fell in the dark.
You don't have a flashlight?
I'll get you one.
I just wasn't being careful, that's all.
How's the investigation going?
- Nothing new to report.
- No?
Dirch says the girl is really clever.
Maybe she'll turn something up.
Maybe.
Thank you for that.
- So, what did he say?
- What?
You said Henrik asked you
to ask me something.
- Well, I just did.
- What?
- How's the investigation?
- Oh, yeah.
That was his question.
Do you hunt?
We should go hunting
together sometime.
Sure.
Nothing at all new to report?
No. Nothing.
- I can see you're anxious.
- No.
No, I mean to get home
after the walk.
Yeah, well, I suppose I am.
To have dinner with your girlfriend.
Assistant.
We'll have better luck with a gun.
- I'm sorry?
- When we go hunting.
A gun. Rather than a knife.
I want to show you something.
Bring your drink.
Leave my knife.
To the right.
Hi, leave a message. I'll call...
You know what's harder
than shooting someone?
Just missing him.
That was a very good shot
up at the cabin.
It didn't work. I'm here.
Mikael, it did work. You're here.
Inside.
Spilled your drink.
Why didn't you just go home?
May I?
How did you do it?
What did you find?
We can talk
or we can just get on with it.
I found a photograph...
...no one has seen.
- Of?
- You.
In an Uppsala prep school blazer.
What does that prove?
You lied about
where you were that day.
- Did I?
- Or rather, when.
So what? People lie all the time.
It also says that you and Lena
Andersson were schoolmates.
Lena...
That was a long time ago.
Where's this photo now? Is it with
all the other crap on your desk?
There's a copy on my laptop.
There's another copy...
...on a secure website.
- Secure website.
That's a lie.
How much does the girl know?
I hope it's as much as you do.
That'll make it fun.
Where is she?
Stockholm. She went this morning.
That's a lie.
She's at our offices
looking at more old crap.
I got a call
from our archives manager.
She was very perturbed
with this girl Lisbeth.
I like that name.
Lisbeth.
So when Lisbeth leaves,
I will get a call from security...
...so I can be at your cottage
to greet her.
I can't thank you enough
for bringing her to me.
Hey, hey.
So, what do you wanna know?
You're a journalist,
ask me questions.
What do I do with the girls?
That's a good question.
Well, before, I do what we're doing:
Sit down, relax, have a drink.
I like that part a lot.
Having a chat when both of you know
that one of you is going to die.
And afterwards, I just get rid of them,
far out at sea.
Unlike my father,
who left them scattered...
...all over the place, like trophies.
That's not very smart, if you ask me.
Well, he was a loud
and garish man.
Frankly, he got what he deserved.
You can't be a sloppy technician
like that.
You can't drink to excess
like he did.
This takes discipline.
It's a science of a thousand details.
The planning, the execution.
It's the cleanup.
I guess I don't have to tell you...
...but you're going to create
quite a mess here.
Let me ask you something.
Why don't people
trust their instincts?
They sense something is wrong...
...someone is walking too close
behind them.
You knew something was wrong.
But you came back into the house.
Did I force you?
Did I drag you in? No.
All I had to do was offer you a drink.
It's hard to believe that
the fear of offending...
...can be stronger than the fear
of pain, but you know what? It is.
And they always come willingly.
And then they sit there.
They know it's all over,
just like you do.
But somehow,
they still think they have a chance.
"Maybe if I say the right thing.
Maybe if I'm polite.
If I cry, if I beg."
And when I see the hope
draining from their face...
...like it is from yours right now...
...I can feel myself...
...getting hard.
But, you know, we're not that different,
you and I. We both have urges.
Satisfying mine...
...requires more towels.
It might amuse you to know...
...that while you were upstairs
having moose with me and Liv...
...who, by the way,
finds me very conventional...
...I had Irina down here in that cage.
Who is Irina, you might ask?
Just another girl.
Just another immigrant whore.
- Who misses them?
- Your sister wasn't.
What?
Your sister Harriet
wasn't just another girl.
You found her?
What happened to her?
You killed her.
You useless fucking detective.
This too tight to talk?
Good. I'm tired of talking to you.
I've never had a man in here before.
In fact, I've never touched a man...
...except my father.
That was our duty.
Harriet's and mine.
Hey.
There's a gun.
There's a gun on the television.
- May I kill him?
- Yeah.
How come a 23-year-old...
...is a ward of the state?
I'm mentally incompetent
and can't manage daily life.
Since when have they said that?
Since I was 12.
What happened when you were 12?
I'm sorry,
that's none of my business.
I tried to kill my father.
Burned him alive.
Got about 80 percent of him.
I made some coffee.
- Who's that?
- It's Harriet.
I found it in Martin's basement
among his souvenirs.
No, Martin didn't deny
killing anyone.
But when I mentioned Harriet,
he was confused.
He got angry at me because I couldn't
tell him what had happened to her.
He didn't kill her.
His father didn't do it.
He was dead the year before.
What if she did somehow manage
to get away?
I mean, if...
...she is still alive...
...then there's only one person in this
family who'd know where she is.
Fuck me. Fuck me. Fuck me.
Your turn.
Right.
Here.
Hi. Look, I'm sorry to bother you.
What do you want?
- Has no one called you?
- About?
Your cousin Martin.
- What about him?
- He died in a car accident...
...last Thursday. There's going
to be a memorial in Hedestad.
I'm not interested in any memorial.
- Well, I understand.
- What do you understand?
Well, that you don't care
very much for your family.
- Look, I just thought you should know.
- Now I know.
How'd it go?
Okay, I think.
She's on.
And she's shopping.
She's still playing solitaire?
- And she hasn't called anyone?
- No.
We have her cell phone too?
I was so sure
she was gonna lead us to her.
Put your hand back in my shirt.
There's only one reason
she hasn't called Harriet.
She can't. Because Harriet is dead.
I was just thinking that...
- Just one second.
- Okay.
What were you going to say?
I was just thinking,
there could be one other possibility.
Well, we could, absolutely.
What is it now?
Before he died,
your brother hung me from a hook...
...Harriet.
So you sent the flowers.
Yes, I did.
We found in the Swedish Family
Registry that Anita was married.
- But the family never knew, did they?
- No.
So I'm guessing she then came here
on her married-name passport...
...and you followed
on her maiden-name passport.
No, actually,
it was the other way around.
She thought that it was safer
if I traveled with Spencer myself.
Well, what did he think about that?
Nothing. Only that he loved her.
She said, "If you love me,
you'll do this and not ask why."
And he never did.
And they both died 20 years ago.
Car accident.
You found that out too.
Is that you?
I was 14 the first time he raped me.
Martin.
No, my father.
Martin only started
after he had died.
- Well, why didn't you tell somebody?
- I did. My mother.
- Henrik would've done something.
- I almost told him.
But I was afraid
because of what I'd done.
- I...
- You still don't understand, do you?
A year after the first time...
...and there were many times
during that year...
...my father got drunker
than usual one night...
...and he started bragging
about the women he'd killed.
He quoted from the Bible
as he tore my clothes off.
He tied a belt around my neck.
He wanted to kill me.
I got out of the house.
I went down to the dock.
He came staggering after me.
I could never fight him off
in a small space...
... but out in the open...
...I was strong enough
to deal with an old drunk.
When it was over...
... I looked up and Martin was
standing there, staring at me.
And all I'd accomplished was
substitute one for another.
A couple of months later, Henrik
sent Martin to school in Uppsala.
And I thought that maybe, just maybe,
the nightmare was finally over.
And then I saw him
the day of the parade...
... across the street.
And I knew
that it would never be over.
So how did you escape?
Anita. She...
She insisted
that I leave everything behind.
If I took anything the police might have
suspected that I was still alive.
As everyone ate dinner, I was no more
than 20 meters away from them.
I spent the night there.
That's when the search started.
In the morning,
she came to get me.
I'd grown up with that bridge
as my link to home...
... but all I could think is...
...if I could just
get away from them...
... just get past the police...
... then I might be safe.
And I was.
Until you showed up.
You're safe now.
How did you get away?
Someone saved me too.
- How are you feeling?
- I'm fine.
Thank you, Anna.
I made you a promise...
...whether you found
anything or not.
So, what do you have to tell me?
What's this?
Hello, Henrik.
I barely remember Wennerström
working here, much less being fired.
How could you?
It was such a long time ago...
...which is kind of more to the point than
the money he embezzled from you.
You're referring
to the statute of limitations...
...but I had no idea this is what
Henrik was holding out.
If I had, I never would've let him
bring you up here.
He wasn't trying to deceive you.
He knows you can't try somebody
35 years after the event.
- I like Henrik, but he knows that.
- A man's reputation means something.
He believes that. He thought
you could destroy Wennerström...
...in the court of public opinion.
- The court of public opinion...
...celebrates people's bad behavior.
- He's an elderly man.
He promised me
Wennerström's carcass on a plate.
This isn't even the plate.
- I can't do anything with this.
- Yes, of course.
What happened with Wennerström?
How did he get you?
I was stupid. I heard something.
I got it from an anonymous source...
...who I'm now sure
was one of Wennerström's lackeys.
It was fake.
Which he easily proved in court.
You were emphatic
that the way I looked into your life...
...was illegal and immoral. Would you
feel the same about Wennerström?
- Go on.
- I did some work on my own on him...
...before you hired me.
I haven't looked at it all...
...because you
and Harriet-fucking-Vanger...
...have kept me busy.
But I may have something.
You may have something?
Maybe.
They launder money
from arms and drug sales...
...and crime syndicates in Russia.
And that money accounts for all
but 5 percent of his holdings.
The rest ends up in accounts
in the Cayman Islands.
- And how do you know this?
- This time you don't want to know.
This time I do want to know.
I have access to his computer...
...and his accountant's and lawyer's.
- And how do you have that?
I could've gotten it from a source
inside the company.
- You didn't.
- But that's what you'll say.
And what will you say to me?
Well, that depends
if you really want to know.
I do.
Mikael, how did you get access?
Financial journalist
Mikael Blomkvist...
... who, this time last year
was convicted of libel...
... in a Stockholm courtroom...
... doesn't seem to have learned
from his mistakes.
Or maybe he has.
In the current issue of Millennium
magazine, he now charges...
... the company that sued him,
the Wennerström Group...
The shit hits the fan.
... of criminal activities
on a global scale.
What happens now?
Well, he'll say it's a personal vendetta,
which won't wash.
The police will investigate,
FI will investigate.
It'll go to court.
Maybe he'll go to prison.
You think?
Probably not.
These guys never do.
What's wrong with you?
- It's embarrassing.
- Tell me.
I need to borrow some money.
Fifty thousand.
I have a chance to make an investment.
It's a smart, safe investment.
- I really don't think I've got 50,000.
- Yes, you do.
You have 65,000
in your two accounts.
I'm sorry that I know that.
You'll get the money back,
I promise.
Okay.
You want a coffee?
These allegations, like the last one
from this so-called journalist...
... are as ridiculous
as they are untrue.
I'll be seeing Mr. Blomkvist in court
again, and I'm looking forward to it.
What about his documentation?
Fabricated. All of it.
The Securities Fraud Office isn't quite
as certain as Mr. Wennerström of that.
If a fraction of what Mr. Blomkvist
alleges proves to be true...
... not only will there be
a securities investigation...
... but an organized-crime inquiry
as well.
Mr. Blomkvist names no sources.
And we can't force him to.
But we can look for them.
- Beginning where?
- Those closest to Mr. Wennerström.
Only someone in the inner circle
of a corporation like this...
... has access to this kind
of information.
Mr. Wennerström isn't available
for comment...
... but I'll be happy
to answer questions.
- Where is he?
- At home, I imagine.
No, he's not.
Has he left the country?
I don't think so.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Welcome to the Dolder Grand, miss.
May I have your passport, please?
With his failure to appear...
... before a Security Exchange
Commission panel...
... a warrant has been issued
for the Wennerström Group CEO.
I can confirm that he left Sweden...
... on a private jet
that landed in Paris last week.
Whether he's still there,
we don't know.
He can be anywhere by now.
Thank you.
I have accounts at Bank
of Kroenenfeld, Cayman Islands.
I'd like to transfer them
and convert to bonds.
- Naturally, you have the clearing codes.
- Naturally.
How many accounts
will you transfer?
Thirty.
- This will take some time.
- You will receive 4 percent commission.
- I will.
- Then it won't be a waste of it.
A Swedish tourist vacationing
here in Barbados...
... says he knows where fugitive
financier Hans-Erik Wennerström is:
Here, in this Caribbean island's
capital, Bridgetown.
Police released this photo and
believe it is the disgraced billionaire.
How many of these would you like
to convert for deposit?
All 50, into five accounts.
Yes. That looks correct.
The man who is now being called
Sweden's Charles Ponzi...
... may no longer have a country
to call home...
... but does have enough money
to buy one.
According to the International
Banking Commission...
... Wennerström, a week after
the Millennium article appeared...
... on newsstands,
began emptying accounts...
... at Bank of Kroenenfeld
in the Cayman Islands.
That money,
approximately 2 billion euros...
... was then spread over
a number of accounts...
... with the help of this confederate,
seen here in Zurich.
- Hey.
- The money I borrowed.
- Already?
Thank you.
No, I quit.
It was a good investment?
It was okay.
What are you doing later?
I'm seeing my daughter.
Okay.
You look nice.
It's Christmas again.
I'll see you soon.
Mr. Wennerström
won the libel case...
You got that call in the office.
I miss our meetings.
I'm sure you don't. Why would you?
I was always such
a headache for you.
Never showing up with good news,
only problems.
I have good news now.
I made a friend.
I mean, one that you'd approve of.
I'm happy.
A man who authorities here
in Marbella have confirmed...
... is fugitive Hans-Erik Wennerström,
shot three times in the head...
... in what police are calling
a classic gangland execution.
The investigation
into Wennerström's ties...
... to crime organizations worldwide
will now turn into speculation.
Which of them caught up with him
before Swedish authorities could?
Wennerström spent the last days
of his flamboyant life...
- It's nice.
- Your father?
- A friend.
- Must be a very good friend.
- We're late.
- Fashionably late.