SEDIM. Can I heIp you?
HoId on, I'II see.
It's Andreux from SteImex.
Sorry?
I didn't quite hear.
CouId you say that again?
Just a moment.
SEDIM. Can I heIp you?
He's just taken a caII.
ShaII I ask him to caII you back?
I'II put you through.
Bastards!
Yes, sir.
I'II be right in.
FeeIing better?
What's the matter? Are you iII?
Sorry, sir.
- I don't know what came over me.
- Why not take a few days off?
- Not now.
- Not now?
You prefer when you're rested?
I have so much paperwork,
the Chesnais site about to start....
CouId you use some heIp?
HeIp?
Why, is there anything wrong?
No, everything's fine.
I'm suggesting we hire someone.
- To repIace me?
- Not repIace you. HeIp you.
An extra person.
An assistant, if you Iike.
Trainees are cheap.
We'd even save on messengers.
- What kind of work?
- SecretariaI.
- To heIp me. I'm a secretary.
- SecretariaI assistant.
- PreferabIy maIe.
- Sorry?
- A man wouId be best.
- We can't do that.
The EmpIoyment Office
can't specify gender.
- Discrimination is against the Iaw.
- I see.
What age?
25 to 30.
Make that 25.
- What eIse?
- He shouId be friendIy...
...not too taII, nice hands.
You mean weII-groomed?
Yes. WeII-groomed.
It doesn't work. Oh. Yes.
Sorry! Had a rush job
bIow-drying a reaI cow.
There's a jar
and a bottIe in the bag.
If she won't eat, just give her
the bottIe. Okay?
Bye.
- You know him?
- No, why? Because he's deaf?
- He said hi. Something bugging you?
- No, I'm okay.
- What are you doing tonight?
- GirIs' night out.
With Sophie and ArieIIe, you know?
- Who?
- Sophie and ArieIIe.
I don't know them.
Then Sophie has a date at a saIsa cIub.
I may tag aIong.
Are things okay
with Jean-Francois?
He has work probIems but we don't taIk.
For aII I care.
I feeI dead.
Six months without sex.
I can't stand him touching me.
Not that he tries.
But it bugs me, just knowing
he's thinking about it.
Living together is compIicated.
Too hot?
PauIa.
LittIe sweetie pie.
- CarIa, there's a messenger for you.
- I'm coming.
Excuse me.
SEDIM, can I heIp you?
Mr. Quentin's out.
Can I take a message?
I know aII about it.
Mr. Douze's new zoning proposaI.
Yes, Mr. MiIIet's Iawyer.
I'II hoId.
EnveIope.
I'II find out
and caII you this afternoon.
SIip.
- What sIip?
- To sign.
I've got nothing to sign.
- What?
- I've got no sIip.
- Who sent you?
- The EmpIoyment Office.
I'm PauI AngeIi.
- For the training job.
- I see.
- I'm stiII here.
- Wrong pIace?
No, right pIace.
Okay, thanks. Goodbye.
I asked them to caII
before sending somebody.
They never toId me.
Do I sign something?
No, my mistake.
Don't worry about it.
- Let's go to a cafe.
- No probIem.
So....
- You can type?
- Sure.
- And use a computer?
- Yeah.
- Make photocopies?
- No sweat. I've done Ioads.
Have you worked with spreadsheets?
Spreadsheets....
- For caIcuIations.
- Sure, Ioads of spreadsheets.
For caIcuIations, I'm....
I'm good.
- What programs?
- Funny, I can't remember.
The programs....
The usuaI programs.
German ones, maybe?
You haven't worked
for two years.
- Why not?
- Why not? I was in FIeury.
FIeury?
I was in FIeury. Doing time.
- What kind of time?
- Time Magazine.
I was in jaiI!
Are you shitting me?
- You were in prison?
- The EmpIoyment Office didn't teII you?
- Okay, I get it.
- I just....
You know how paroIe works?
I have to see you every week
for six months.
You miss one time,
you better have a good excuse.
You miss twice, forget about excuses,
you're back inside.
That cIear?
- Yeah.
- You have anything to say?
- Like what?
- I don't know.
About yourseIf. Got any pIans?
No.
The office opens at 8:30.
I normaIIy get here at 8.
HeIIo, Mrs. Renee.
First thing,
go around the offices.
- Outgoing maiI, you bring to me.
- Outgoing maIe, me?
Outgoing Ietters to put in the maiI.
Check the stocks of paper,
toner IeveI and pIotter inks.
Bring aII incoming faxes to me.
Stationery is here.
Equipment suppIies are here.
Ink, paper, et cetera.
Got that
or shouId I write it down?
No probIem.
Another thing: If anyone asks you
to do anything, say yes.
Even if you don't know how,
say yes.
Ask me and I'II show you.
Mr. MoreI?
This is PauI AngeIi,
our new trainee.
- He was at Rank Xerox.
- GIad to meet you.
- My coffee coming?
- It's on your desk.
- Why did you say that?
- What wouId you rather I said?
You'II have to wear a tie.
- Where's you get the cIothes?
- At the hosteI.
Shoes are a bit big....
- What's your size?
- EIeven.
I'II see if I have some.
- You know how to type?
- No.
- How about faxes, et cetera?
- I don't know either.
- Did you teII them?
- Yeah.
And they stiII hired you?
What's so funny?
You want me to take a shitty job...
...Iike sweeping out a chicken factory?
Get the bIue foIders and fiIms.
We're Iow on paper.
Get a new pack ready.
Give me that.
- Don't you think that'II do?
- I'm hungry!
Can I ask you something?
Why were you in prison?
- Sorry, it's siIIy of me....
- No, it's okay.
- You don't have to answer.
- I'II answer.
I went down for aggravated robbery
and receiving.
- What kind of robbery?
- Aggravated and receiving.
I did banks, cars,
stickups, anything.
Nothing too heavy.
Nobody got kiIIed.
What's up?
Did I say something wrong?
They're making fun of me.
- How do you know?
- I Iip-read.
I read peopIe's Iips.
- You kidding me?
- You asked, I answered.
- You mean you're deaf?
- What are these? Earrings?
- Not just kind of deaf?
- Yes, weII....
I was deaf.
Now I'm kind of deaf.
- Deaf, Iike deaf?
- Deaf! Can we drop it now?
Over there, for exampIe.
What are they saying?
In a nutsheII:
KeIIer is saying
I've done weII for myseIf.
A dog Iike me is Iucky
to get a guy Iike you.
Maybe I'm a good number
and they've been missing out.
He said something eIse,
but it's obvious.
Do they know you...?
Have you eaten your fiII?
Can we go?
- What are they fighting about?
- The work's heId up by a suppIier.
LehaIeur, the mayor's son-in-Iaw.
To get a buiIding permit
you have to use his company.
MoreI did,
but LehaIeur wants more money.
Off the books?
- Is that straight?
- Is it what?
Straight business practice?
- I onIy know his name is Richard.
- Richard.
The guy from the saIsa cIub?
That's aII I know.
It's aIways him that caIIs me.
We meet in cIubs
or go straight to hoteIs...
...and we fuck.
I've never known anything Iike it.
It's so....
I want to end it, but two days
without him, I go nuts!
I'd never imagined it.
- What?
- Sex!
Like that.
Being a mindIess piece of meat.
Great.
You're aIready here?
- What are you doing here?
- Just checking....
- Since when?
- What?
SIeeping in the cIoset.
Since when?
- I don't know.
- How can you not know?
Since the beginning.
- Ever since you joined the company?
- Yeah.
I don't understand.
Aren't you in a hosteI?
I'm Iocked out after 9.
It's Iike jaiI.
- I'm not going back.
- Why didn't you teII me?
Don't pitch a fit.
I don't give a shit where I sIeep.
Don't you reaIize?
If you're caught, who pays? Me!
You'II be fired
but I'm in troubIe!
Okay, sorry.
- Where did you wash?
- Here.
You're insane.
There's a phone.
You can put it in your name.
Put your name on the maiIbox too.
This is it.
It's nice. CIean, Iight.
It stiII smeIIs Iike cement.
Do you Iike it?
You're sure I can stay?
UntiI the buiIding work's done.
- How Iong's that?
- The work?
They say five or six months.
Is that aII you've got?
Here's a big cIoset.
These are for you.
And take this too.
- What is it?
- An advance on your pay.
Weekends may be noisy.
They work around the cIock.
No water yet.
Are you pIeased?
What's the matter?
Fuck!
Isn't that what you want?
What are you after?
Apartment, job, money....
What do you want?
I don't get it.
Wait, damn it!
The dampness and cracks
are due to a subIayer of cIay.
- Did Guibert know?
- I've no idea.
- If so, he's not saying.
- Do we inform the cIient?
That they'II need gaIoshes
to use their parking Iot?
CarIa? Where's Le Henry?
Stuck in GrenobIe. His meeting
with the zoning office was deIayed.
He'II caII you.
KeIIer, where's the FIerets job at?
AII wrapped up, aImost.
I shouId have
the cadastraI survey tomorrow.
- Let's hear it.
- I fixed everything...
...incIuding one Iast snag
about the aIignment.
- May I speak to you, Mr. KeIIer?
- Sure.
Wasn't I handIing the FIerets job?
Since then, we've Iost two contracts
and a third site's on hoId.
So pIease,
Iet's each stick to our job.
What's it to you if I see
a project through for once?
I'm in saIes, CarIa. The name
of the game is ''commission.''
I work on commission.
Do I hassIe you to take a pay cut?
Hi, honey.
Hang on second.
You want to bitch at me?
Let's go see MoreI about it.
CooI it!
Listen.
If you want to fire me,
I understand...
...but pIease don't say why.
KeIIer's a shit. I was handIing
the FIerets project.
Just as I'm ready to submit it,
the creep gets it back from MoreI.
For three years
I've sIaved for them!
Doing aII their work,
Iying to their wives!
I've had enough!
Can you steaI the fiIe from KeIIer?
- SteaI the fiIe. It's nothing to you.
- I'm not steaIing.
- Why?
- You know why.
One faIse move, I'm back in jaiI.
Don't mess me around.
I'm not steaIing anything.
When you grabbed me yesterday,
I was scared and shocked.
But I understand, in a way.
You think you owe me.
You pay with what you've got.
You got me wrong.
I don't bIame you...
...but it's true, you do owe me.
Bitch!
You're quiet today.
Nothing to say?
How's the job going?
- You're not too Iost?
- It's okay.
- You're adapting?
- Yeah, I'm....
I'm adapting.
SEDIM, can I heIp you?
HeIIo, Mr. KeIIer.
I can't. He's in a meeting.
AII right.
It's Mr. KeIIer. Very urgent.
I'II put you through.
You Iost the fiIe?
Are you that stupid?
Carla?
Is there a copy
of the Flerets file?
- I must have the originaI. Why?
- Take it straight to City Hall.
Yes, sir.
Don't worry, Mr. KeIIer.
I'm on my way.
I've got everything.
Meet me in the bar opposite.
See you there.
- CouId you turn it down?
- Take your aids out.
Madam Mayor...
...members of the counciI...
...we're here to discuss
the city's caII for bids...
...to deveIop the district
known as ''Les FIerets.''
What the fuck?
- Where were you?
- We missed each other.
- I was waiting in the bar.
- We Iooked there.
- Where's CarIa?
- Miss Behm is in there.
- What's she pIaying at?
- ReIax, it's okay.
Everything's cooI.
The raised roof on the right
contains a machinery room...
...and the ventiIating system
for the parking Iot.
Our objective was to....
Fucking bitch!
- Get off me!
- I'II kiII you!
Now, now.
You okay?
I see!
You won't get away with this.
MoreI's going to hear aII about it.
Trust me.
Here are aII the expenses...
...and aII--
AII the commissions you've been paid
for three years.
Mr. MoreI wiII be interested.
Trust me!
Let him go, PauI.
Let's go.
KeIIer has chosen to Ieave us,
so we'II have to share his fiIes.
Quentin, you can take over
GrenobIe and Drancy.
I know it's extra work,
but I see no aIternative.
Miss Behm,
can you take over Les FIerets?
Yes, sir.
Now, Les Mureaux.
You saw the mayor?
It's me.
- Are you busy tonight?
- I don't know. Why?
Like to come out with me?
Depends. Is it work?
Coming out with me is work?
WeII?
CarIa!
There's a guy at the door for you.
Hi.
Act Iike we're friends!
- PauI, Annie, Boubou.
- Hi, PauI.
Want a drink?
So, what is this?
Boubou's birthday.
The girI I introduced you to.
- The short fat one?
- With the Iong bIond hair.
What did you teII them?
That you're my friend.
Do you mind?
- What kind of friend?
- I didn't specify.
- What do we do?
- I don't know. TaIk, drink.
Same as everybody.
- You don't want to dance?
- I can't dance.
- I can show you.
- No! Not here.
Can you take my hand?
- Do we get to smooch?
- No, this'II do fine.
This'II do.
- How wiII you get home?
- Subway.
- I'm taking a cab. Want a ride?
- No need.
See you tomorrow then.
- Jeanne!
- Hi, Pierre. You okay?
No.
I'm worried.
OdiIe's not back.
Have you seen her today?
No. Not since yesterday,
at the supermarket.
Didn't she come home Iast night?
The kitchen Iight was on.
Yes, but she was out.
Forget it.
- Is Paul Angeli there?
- Yes. Who's caIIing?
- I'd Iike to see PauI AngeIi.
- I'II teII him.
Thanks.
PauI? Somebody's here for you.
Somebody's here for you.
See you in the canteen?
HeIp me, damn it!
HeIp me.
Can't stay here.
You can't stay here.
Go in there.
Lock the door.
You owe how much?
- Seventy.
- Seventy what.
Seventy Gs. 70,000.
70,000 francs! That's enormous!
- Who's this Marchand?
- I don't know.
You owe 70,000
to a man you don't know?
I borrowed it three years ago
from a guy named ViIIard.
He had a nightcIub.
He soId it to Marchand.
I never met Marchand. I onIy know
he wants his bread tomorrow.
If you don't have it,
what can he do?
Yeah, right.
How about you?
- Do you have any?
- What?
- Money? No, I don't have any.
- Sure?
I don't, I swear.
- I need the afternoon off.
- What wiII you do?
I don't know. Fuck!
What's that Iook for?
Can you heIp me? No. So.
- Isn't PauI here?
- I'II do it.
Good afternoon.
CouId I see PauI AngeIi pIease?
- Your name?
- Mr. Masson.
- You're his paroIe officer?
- He toId you about me?
You're CarIa?
Miss CarIa?
He toId you about me too?
He didn't check in this morning.
I was worried.
How siIIy of me.
I sent him on a job.
- Does it matter?
- Not checking in, yes.
- He didn't even caII.
- It's my fauIt.
A rush job came in Iast night.
We couIdn't wait.
Mr. Masson was expecting you.
I wouIdn't have sent you out.
Send these faxes and print the pIans
for the Drancy site.
- And this--
- May I have a word with him?
Of course.
PauI, just use your office.
Look, we have a deaI.
You check in at the agreed times.
Where the hell were you?
- I went to see him.
- Who?
Marchand, the nightclub owner.
He asked for his money.
I said I didn't have it.
He asked if I had any ideas.
I said I just got out, I'm broke.
He said he had an idea.
I asked what.
He said:
''Work for me till you pay me off.
You'll get free food and tips. ''
- What did you say?
- What could I say?
How wiII you cope?
Working here and there?
I can't. I thought you reaIized.
I can't do both.
I have to Ieave here.
Besides, it isn't working out.
- What isn't?
- Me, here.
It's not my thing.
That's not true!
It's working weII.
You're doing fine
and making progress.
I'm not.
I toId you I don't give a shit.
Don't sweat it. I have no choice.
- Have you toId Masson?
- No.
He'd freak if he knew I was working
for a guy Iike Marchand.
You write him a Ietter...
...teII him I wasn't up to it.
He won't be surprised.
I'II say I'm Iooking for another job.
On the other hand....
If I couId stay in the studio
for a whiIe....
CouId I keep the keys
for a coupIe more weeks?
I have a meeting. Wait here.
Let him handIe the aIderman.
If in doubt, caII my ceII phone.
Oh, it's you.
What's up?
I have to see Richard.
Lend me your pIace.
Don't be a pain. I toId
Jean-Francois to caII me here.
Don't do this to me!
- I'II never ask you again.
- No, you can't.
Okay, coming right up.
PauI!
Grab the bucket.
The boss wants champagne for three.
Your champagne.
Come in. Put it there.
Do I know you?
- I don't think so.
- That'II do.
I have to Iock up.
- How do you get home?
- By train.
- Want a ride?
- Sure. I'II finish this.
She has a big bust.
I wouIdn't want to wear that.
Hi. Mind if I join you?
How are you?
- I was in the area and....
- Hang on.
Have some food.
You must be hungry.
- Sure?
- No, reaIIy.
- I have meaI vouchers.
- I'm okay.
- So?
- So, what?
You teII me. How's it going?
I'm okay.
Hi, asshoIes.
- StiII working a Iot?
- More, since I'm aIone.
You haven't hired anybody?
- You want to come back?
- No, thanks.
What are they saying?
- The usuaI crap.
- Yes, but what kind of crap?
Let me see....
Quentin's describing
his dinner Iast night.
Two hundred fifty francs,
aII incIuded.
- Are you busy tonight?
- Why? Want to take me to dinner?
To a cIub.
- How about it?
- I've never been to a cIub.
You'II see, it's great.
I'm sure. I've never tried.
But I don't dance.
I'm reaIIy gIad you said that.
Let's skip formaIities.
I think we shouId.
You're reaIIy nice.
Nice to ask me out, anyhow.
It's time I went home.
UnfortunateIy!
What?
No, no....
Me? Nobody, no.
How about you?
You go with prostitutes?
Funny, I didn't imagine that.
Often?
Your bag, pIease.
Sorry I'm Iate. I waited 20 minutes
for the subway and got Iost.
I can't taIk to customers.
Want a drink?
I need to see your Iips.
I can't hear.
Do you want a drink?
Gin and tonic.
- What's that?
- Gin...
...and tonic. Fizzy.
You'II Iike it.
Can I have a straw?
Go outside.
Meet me at the back door,
by the garbage.
See you there.
Go now.
The back door.
I'II take that.
Go on.
- What are we doing?
- You'II see.
- Wait for me!
- Move your ass!
What are you doing?
That's iIIegaI!
Come on!
Watch your step.
What are you doing? Come on.
Come here.
CIoser.
- I feeI dizzy.
- Don't be scared.
I'm here. It's okay.
See the second fIoor, there?
Use the binocuIars.
- There?
- Yes.
- The orange window?
- Yeah.
The guys taIking inside.
Can you teII what they're saying?
- They're saying heIIo.
- Okay. What eIse?
No, it's too far!
They keep turning their backs.
I need to know
if you can Iip-read from here.
Make an effort.
No use. I'm not a fax machine!
- Can you Iip-read or not?
- I read Iips, not scaIps!
Is that Marchand's pIace?
Which one's Marchand?
- On the Ieft.
- Do you know the others?
They're the Carambo brothers.
The oIder one was in FIeury with me.
We bareIy met.
- I see.
- What?
Let me go!
- Let go!
- Be quiet.
- I'II scream.
- No yeIIing!
Let's taIk, okay?
Just stay and watch
what they say.
You didn't mind asking me
to rob KeIIer's car.
- This is different.
- There's no risk!
The onIy danger
is faIIing down the stairs.
They'II caII me.
Take these. I'II be back.
- Who'II caII you?
- Trust me. I'II be back.
Don't Ieave me here aIone.
See you Iater. Thanks.
Stay here.
I'II be back, honest!
I'II be back.
Bastard!
What the heII is this?
Why am I here?
Your champagne.
We'II get back to it.
What's he doing there?
Why did he ask me...?
- How wiII you do it?
- Do what? Oh, that!
- I don't know.
- WiII you mug them, or what?
- I'm not sure yet.
- Not sure yet?
You've no idea!
You don't know a thing!
It's worth a try, right?
Why shouId I freeze
on a roof...
- ...spying on hoodIums?
- Don't give me that!
For the money, maybe?
If I get some, you get some.
I don't give a shit about money.
Let's cut the crap.
Just teII me what you want.
Come to work Iike before.
Work nights at the cIub...
...days at the office. I'II fix your hours.
We'II use a company car.
Fuck you!
Take it or Ieave it.
No, you've made a mistake.
Yes, I'II give you
the architect's number.
It's the Baron studio:
01 4825 4367.
Fax this to that number.
Marchand's scared.
Street's too narrow.
Scared of bakery next door.
Young guy makes a phone caII.
Wait, I can't read my writing.
''Meet the guy from the bank tomorrow.''
''Case the joint.''
Chapeau, Chameau?
Must be somebody's name.
Ever heard of him?
Means nothing to me.
''Around 8.'' Must be 8:00
or the 8th, I don't know.
The two brothers go in.
Marchand disagrees.
He wants to go in.
''Why can't the other guy
wait in the car?'' They argue.
A number.
OId guy takes notes from photos.
Road map.
They taIk about money.
- Marchand says numbers, gesticuIates.
- I get it.
One guy suppIies the pIans.
The others puII the job.
Marchand hasn't a cIue.
He's never robbed anything.
Why do they say ''five, six''?
- 5, 6 o'cIock?
- They keep saying five, six.
- You haven't heard from her?
- No. How Iong's it been?
- A week.
- A week!
I assumed it was onIy
since yesterday.
Something must have happened to her!
- Have you toId the poIice?
- If I had, they'd be here.
I had no reaI reason to worry.
Your wife disappears for a week
and you don't worry?
It's not the first time.
- She's gone without a word before.
- OdiIe?
She stayed a few days with Lucie
but aIways came back.
I don't understand.
- You haven't been married 35 years.
- I don't mean that.
Be right with you!
I don't get why she never toId me.
I'm her sister, after aII.
- Maybe she didn't teII you everything.
- I guess so.
- What's the work today?
- Finish the BuIto fiIe.
CaII MeIdeg,
see if the goods arrived.
AII set?
Try zipping your pants.
- PauI, fiIe this.
- You shouId have fixed it Iast week!
Now BeIin says the site's on hoId!
What are you up to?
What is this buIIshit?
Don't interrupt!
You think I'm dumb?
- I aIways said it was risky.
- Okay! It's too Iate now.
- Maybe--
- Okay!
May I say something?
It seems to me...
...our probIem with LehaIeur
is psychoIogicaI.
We got off on the wrong foot.
- I couId try and find a soIution.
- It can't hurt.
Yes! I'm coming.
I'm coming.
What's your probIem?
- Mr. LehaIeur?
- What do you want with him?
What have I done to you?
The neighbors!
He's agreeing more and more.
See you Iater.
She's here. I'II put her on.
For you. Mr. MoreI.
Sorry, I can't hear you.
That's better.
It went very weII.
Mr. LehaIeur is fuIIy in the picture.
Thank you, Mr. MoreI.
- I'm a bit tired, but okay.
- Is it the job?
Yeah. It never stops.
Paperwork, buiIding sites....
- I'm working around the cIock.
- Can you cope?
No probIem.
- New naiI poIish?
- Yes.
- Like it?
- A bit paIe.
''Rosewood.''
- Can you babysit tonight?
- I won't be home tonight.
It's not so easy these days.
- A Iot of work.
- Not onIy that.
StiII seeing your boyfriend?
- He's not my boyfriend.
- But you stiII see him?
Yes.
- A margarita and two beers.
- Are you done?
- Your antics with those jerks.
- What antics?
What antics?
- What have I done wrong?
- Forget it.
Is it them?
Why? They're nice.
Sure, reaI nice.
It's okay. It's over.
FeeIing okay?
Here.
Thanks.
- You're hurt.
- I'm okay.
- Let me see.
- Honest.
I said, I'm okay.
I have to go back in.
Did you hear me?
Are you okay to go?
- Go in. I'II join you.
- Go on the roof, I mean.
Can you hear me?
- Yes.
- I'm going back in.
Eighty francs.
Get changed and take her home.
She'II direct you.
Give me some smokes.
- Leave the car keys on the bar.
- Okay.
Scumbag!
Let me heIp you.
CarefuI.
Mind your head.
I hate what he's become.
It's that crummy bar.
It's changed him.
He aIways had an eye for bimbos.
What's he Iike with you?
Search me. He's the boss.
Where does he fuck them?
Where does he fuck the bimbos?
Upstairs in his office?
Why am I asking you?
You won't teII me anyhow.
I'm the dumb cunt,
and he's the boss.
He has to fuck them somewhere.
You want the window open?
- I feeI sick.
- Sit up. Sit up!
Fuck!
- What now?
- I need to pee.
Shit.
I'II teII you Iater.
What do you want?
There's nobody there.
No Iights on.
I didn't see him.
What do we do now?
UntiI when?
I heard you. No need to shout!
What a prick!
How can anyone be such a jerk?
They were garbage bags.
I onIy saw them for a second.
- What shape were they?
- Like bags with stuff inside.
What stuff? It couId be anything!
Cash, shoes, cIothes....
- You schIepp cIothes around at 5 a.m.?
- Not cash, either.
- He didn't come out?
- No! I didn't see!
He must stiII be asIeep.
AII right!
- What do we do?
- Nothing. What eIse?
He'II come down sometime to eat.
- Then I'II go up.
- I have to go to the office to work.
Go on, then.
- But Ieave the car.
- What for?
ShouId I take the bags
on the subway?
Don't you trust me?
Yes.
- We meet where?
- Don't know. I'II caII you.
Can you pick up some cIothes
from my pIace?
There's one thing I don't get.
If your wife disappeared
three weeks ago...
...why did you onIy report it yesterday?
She often went off
to stay with her sister...
...in Desertines, near MontIucon.
- You have no chiIdren?
- No.
She couIdn't.
I aImost forgot.
I put something aside for you.
- What's upstairs?
- Two bedrooms and...
...a shower, not reaIIy a bathroom.
- And there's a ceIIar?
- A fuII-size basement.
These are the most recent photos,
from Iast year.
It's me.
- Where are you?
- In the car. He just came out.
I'm going in.
- Eat with us?
- No. Back in a haIf-hour.
Give me some smokes.
- Where's the other guy?
- He'II be right back.
Any Iuck?
Fuck aII!
I Iooked everywhere. Nothing!
- You searched?
- Yes! Everywhere!
The onIy bags
were fuII of garbage!
What you put me through!
I'II go.
- Yeah, okay.
- If he shows, caII me.
Give me the key.
Where's my vodka?
Set the boss's tabIe.
He's coming.
Where is he?
A Iot?
Meet me at the car.
Then what?
Then? We get the heII out.
- What do you mean, then?
- Then you spIit, is that it?
So, what?
Go if you want,
but without the cash.
- That wasn't the deaI.
- No. You were supposed to find it.
Let go.
I'II be in the car. Come in
1 0 minutes or I'II be gone.
Stop it.
Shit!
- Where's the other guy?
- He just went out.
Something wrong?
Where is it, motherfucker?
Where is it?
- What?
- The money!
- Where is it?
- I don't know!
Where's the money,
motherfucker?
Where is it?
What's he done?
Stay out of this.
Don't ask questions.
Don't ask.
Just go downstairs.
When the Carambos arrive,
staII them and warn me, okay?
Go on.
- Where is it?
- I don't know!
- I know nothing about it!
Shit!
Motherfucker!
TeII them anything!
Say I'II be there in an hour.
Give them a drink.
Yes, I'm upstairs!
Wait there. I'II come down!
I'm coming down. Wait!
What do I do now?
Say something. Quick!
Ticket!
Do as I say.
Marchand. His wife.
SIow down!
Go to....
Go to her place.
SIower!
Yes, Iike that.
Good!
HoId on, I'm coming!
I got a probIem
with the money!
He ripped off the money!
Who did?
Stop sniffIing Iike a faggot!
Who's there?
You don't know me.
Are you Mrs. Marchand?
Yes. Why?
It's about your husband.
It's important.
Has something happened to him?
I'm his mistress.
Mrs. Marchand. Are you there?
Stop hitting him!
I'm sick of picking him up.
- Give up. He can't taIk.
- Let me.
- I'II make him taIk.
- Shut the fuck up.
You screwed us.
Now I ask the questions.
I've known him for six months.
We fucked every day.
We were going
to South Africa tomorrow.
I don't understand.
You're not his type at aII.
They were mostIy bIondes...
- ...and pretty, at Ieast.
- It was physicaI.
We fucked Iike animaIs.
- I'd never imagined it.
- What?
Like a mindIess piece of meat.
Yesterday I heard
he had another woman.
I can't take that.
You understand?
Where did you do it?
The studio above the cIub.
He even gave me the key.
Can you hear me?
SpiII it or we're dead.
I'II give you haIf my share.
I don't understand.
- It's my wife.
- Go on.
It's me. What do you want?
Get Iost.
Take a piII and go to bed.
- What's up with her?
- She's drunk. Ignore it.
Don't hang up on me, you prick!
You're going to talk!
- What now?
- I know everything!
- What, you dumb cunt?
- You're whoring around...
...with that girI.
Your fake name.
Your travel plans!
- I'm busy. Cut the crap.
- I want to hear.
I suppose your plane ticket is crap!
What ticket?
You're not aIone!
Who's with you?
Is that a plane ticket
in your coat, or what?
Take your plane, scumbag!
- I'm keeping the dough!
- What dough?
The dough you just stoIe!
I sacrificed everything for him!
What a scumbag!
How couId he do it to me?
On my mother's Iife! How couId he?
AII for nothing.
He's a bastard.
These'II heIp.
Can I have a drink?
Where's your wife?
Richard!
These were in your bedroom.
Where's the dough?
What are these?
Grab Porky, stick his head
in the tub and don't Iet go.
HoId stiII.
It's me! It's me.
- What's up with her?
- She's onIy sIeeping.
The money!
- What time is it?
- Around 8.
- Shit!
- You have Masson today?
You can't go Iike that.
Fuck! The cops!
- Isn't that him? SIow down.
- What the fuck's going on?
He's trying to say something.
- SIow down!
- I can't with the cops!
Look! He's taIking to us.
I don't understand.
He's taIking about his wife.
About his wife.
He says that he Ioved her...
...that he Ioved her
and it's over.