Lifeforce - Sci-Fi Horror Tobe Hooper
Classic [H264-mp4]
[male narrator] August 9th, 2:30 PM,
Greenwich Mean Time.
The HMS Churchill outward bound.
On board a joint British/American
space team.
Their mission:
To intercept and study
the comet bearing
Dr. Edmond Halley's name.
The Churchill is the first spacecraft
equipped with the Nerva engine.
It propels the Churchill
with constant acceleration,
enough to create Earth-type gravity
for the first time
on an extended flight.
The Churchill is on course
for its rendezvous.
Sir, this is odd.
What?
I'm getting a very small
radar cross section,
just ahead of the nucleus
in the coma of the comet.
I've got it too.
Check the length, Brendan,
it's at the limit of my angle of scan.
- What's going on?
- Did you chaps run an equipment check?
[female] I've been checking
every five minutes, sir.
Radar state's 150 miles.
- 150 miles what?
- Length.
Hundred and fifty miles long?
What's 150 miles long?
[beeping] It's a radar trace.
Something right ahead
in the coma of the comet.
Show me.
[male] EGR's confirmed.
[female] Looks good.
[male] EGR's optimal,
track three on three.
[female] Rogen.
What's the height of the thing?
I've got a vertical reading
of two miles, at least.
[digital voice]
Ambient temperature six degrees.
Iron less than 2%,
traces of manganese, titanium...
Try and raise base.
Tell them we have an artificial object
out here hidden in the...
Are you sure you want
to say hidden?
Tell them it's located
in the head of the comet.
Keep sending that
until they acknowledge.
Use a secured downlink.
Sorry, Commander, every-thing's
being swamped by the coma winds.
We can't get anything
back to base.
How longs the blackout period?
All the way.
What are you gonna do?
We're going in.
We're only gonna get
one chance, Derebridge.
That thing won't be back
for another 76 years.
And we'll both be dead.
We have to take a look now.
Shut down Nerva.
Shutting down.
Down one. [Click]
[male]
Deltas plus one in two seconds.
- Solar panels retracted.
- [female] Check.
Give me a readout, Bob.
[male #1]
Executing E.V.A. manoeuvre.
[male #2] Where do you suppose
this thing came from?
Was it exploring the comet,
do you think?
[male #1]
Come on guys, let's do it.
Surface looks badly pitted.
In that case,
it's been here a long time.
[male #2]
It's derelict, whatever it is.
[male #1] Stand by, Churchill,
we're going in.
[male on radio]
Roger, Carlsen, we copy.
We have you going in.
[female] Churchill, looks like
some sort of giant artery... organic.
I almost have the feeling
I've been here before.
Oh, boy.
[breathing]
[male #1] This is incredible.
I hope you can appreciate
the scale of this on the video.
Roger, we're getting it.
It's all on tape.
Oh, shit.
Well, here they are.
Churchill, it looks like we found
the occupants of the ship.
They look like bats... giant bats.
[female] Churchill, there must be
hundreds of them.
[male]
Thousands... dead, I hope.
[breathing]
[male # 1] Looks prehistoric.
[crackles]
It's completely desiccated.
[breathing]
- Crumbled.
- Yes.
It would.
All the fluid's been lost to space
over the years.
[suit rockets firing]
We'll bag this one,
take it with us.
[male] We're deploying
the specimen bag.
[male] Jesus,
what the hell is that?
Commander,
the ship has just deployed a...
It looks like some sort
of big structure
that's just unfolding...
It's enormous!
God, what is it?
[female]
Better get out of here, sir.
Nobody's going anywhere,
stay where you are.
Churchill, this is Carlsen.
What's happening out there?
The thing stopped opening.
The only way to describe it is...
It's... it's like a giant umbrella.
Good god, it's...
It's absolutely enormous.
Churchill, what's it doing now?
Nothing, sir.
It stopped opening.
It's just sitting there.
Tell what it's made of?
Not metal.
It's radar transparent.
Okay... if it starts up again,
let me know.
Any activity out there,
you understand?
Yes, sir.
That's where we're going.
Something there.
Commander, this is Churchill.
We're losing our signal.
We've lost VT R.
Come in, Commander.
Bodies, three bodies.
Perfectly preserved.
They look to me to be like in...
Some-thing's happening to me.
What's wrong...
with me, wha... What's wrong?
[Churchill] Commander, come in.
This is Churchill.
Do you copy?
They seem to be in some sort
of suspended animation or sleep.
[male]
Hold on, we're coming down.
[female] Churchill,
Churchill, if you read,
there are two nude males
and one female.
This is Churchill,
we have no picture.
Come in, Tom.
Churchill... I said we found
a young girl.
Girl? You mean human?
Definitely humanoid.
[male] I'd say she's perfect.
I've been in space for six months
and she looks perfect to me.
[female]
Derebridge, what's wrong?
[sighs] What's wrong...
[sighs] How many
do you want to take back?
I say we take back all three.
One of the dead things
in the other chamber.
Well...
let's see
if we can break 'em free.
[Clunk]
[male] Churchill, come in,
this is Mission Control Great Britain.
Do you copy? Come in, Churchill.
If they're going to pick us up,
they should get us this close.
[male] Simply aren't receiving,
Dr. Bukovsky.
Automatic circuits
don't even respond.
They're radio dead.
Christ.
I hope it's just
their communications.
[male] ...do you copy?
Come in, Churchill.
[male] Churchill, come in,
this is Mission Control Great Britain.
Churchill, come in,
Do you copy? Come in, Churchill.
How's their orbit look?
You can see it's stable,
but they're slightly off.
They should have adjusted coming in,
but they haven't.
[Dr. Bukovsky]
What do you make of that?
[male technician] It would appear
that they, uh, set their course
just after they left the comet.
I'd say it hasn't been
updated since.
[sighs]
The Columbia?
The Columbia.
[male]
Lift off, we have lift off.
[radio chatter]
Control, this is Columbia.
Are we clear
to initiate docking procedure?
[male on radio] Go ahead, Columbia,
you are looking good.
Stand by for soft dock.
[radio] Soft dock.
[rumbling]
Soft dock confirmed.
[breathing]
Columbia,
the ship's completely gutted.
Oh, my God.
Houston, we have a problem.
There's been a fire.
I'll take a look in the tug bay.
You two try the top deck.
[breathing]
Columbia, they're all dead.
Nothing down here, Columbia.
I'm going on in to the tug bay.
I'll get the tapes.
Somner, I think there's something
you ought to see in the tug bay.
[chimes sounding]
I see... how did you open
the girl's case?
We didn't, Minister.
We were just talking
about how to get it open
when it popped open
of its own accord.
Did you x-ray the crystal cases?
We're not certain they're crystal.
The casings are not metallic.
I'm not even sure they're organic.
The casing is right there
in front of us without being there,
if that makes any sense.
And the bodies from the cases?
We're going to do
our first dissection now.
Provided, of course,
that Dr. Fallada agrees they're dead.
[phone ringing]
FaHada.
I don't know that I'm qualified
to pass judgement on alien death.
You would agree
that they're less alive than we are?
[male on TV] Yesterday
in Hong Kong, gold closed lower.
In light trading
on European currency markets,
the pound closed mixed
against the dollar
and West German mark.
There will be a full market report
after the late news.
This is James Graham reporting
from the city.
Now back to the newsroom.
Developments as they arise.
Halley's Comet is now dominating
the northern skies,
stretching over a hundred million miles
across the heavens,
occupying one-sixth
of the entire visible horizon.
On this exceptionally clear night,
a group of enthusiasts are
commemorating.
Dr. Edmond Halley's great prediction
by holding an outdoor watching
from the site of his original
observatory at Greenwich.
Our viewers may be interested
to know that comets
were once considered
to be harbingers of evil,
and that one of the earliest words
for comet was disaster,
which in Latin means evil star.
And it may indeed be an evil star
for the deep space probe, Churchill.
There's still no word
from Her Majesty's Government
as to the fate of the crew,
whether they're alive or dead.
We can only await
further developments.
[breathing]
[breathes]
[yelling]
[moaning]
[alien voice] Use my body.
[male] Bukovsky.
Bukovsky, where...
Where's the girl!
She's gone.
I saw her.
She did that.
[buzzes] Security.
Hello, Professor Fallada here.
I'm calling at Dr. Bukovsky's orders.
Get me the Duty Security Captain now.
Yes, sir.
Don't worry, a naked girl is not going
to get out of this complex.
Four nine to Control.
You'll never believe
what I'm looking at.
Control, can you say that again?
I believe you heard me.
There's a girl on the loose
in the building.
She must not leave.
Pardon me, but I thought you said
she was naked.
That's right, that's what I said.
Surely, you can find her.
Must be some kinda joke.
I don't believe it.
All right, Miss,
just stay where you are.
You heard 'em,
they said grab her.
Take it easy, Link,
she's not in her right mind.
Control, Control, we have located
the girl in the main lobby.
[whispering] That's it, come on.
[buzzes] Yes.
We've located the girl, sir.
- Where?
- She's downstairs in the main lobby.
Right.
She's in the main lobby.
- You all right to go down there?
- No.
Come on, nice and easy.
Come on.
Come to me.
Come to daddy, come on.
Make it stop, make it stop!
Come on, let's get her.
[Yells]
[dog barking]
- You all right, mate?
- Yeah.
[mixed chatter]
[sirens approach]
[siren louder]
[male on PA] Will all non-involved
personnel please clear the area.
I repeat... Will everybody who has no
business to be here,
please clear the area
for your own safety.
This is a police announcement.
Please keep right back...
- Sorry, gentlemen, no photos please.
- Hey!
Sorry.
May I ask which of you
is Dr. Bukovsky?
I am.
I'm Colonel Caine.
From the S.A.S.?
Gentlemen, that last remark
is not for publication.
This is a D Notice situation.
Not too close.
And this was murder... you say?
Tell me again how the girl
overpowered you.
She, uh...
was the most overwhelmingly
effeminate presence
I've ever encountered.
I was drawn to her
on a level that...
Was it sexual?
Yes, overwhelmingly so.
And horrible.
Loss of control.
And the man, the guard, was dead
when you came into the room?
You found him as he is now?
Yeah.
And the girl, she came
from the ship, Churchill?
Uh-huh.
She spoke to you?
In English?
That's right.
How would she know English?
Now, going back-
you say the ship's tapes
were destroyed in the fire?
No, they weren't destroyed
in the fire.
That's what we were told
to tell the public.
They were erased.
Erased?
Also, the Churchill's escape pod
is missing.
What's that mean,
did someone escape?
They don't know.
Unfortunately,
the condition of the bodies
make an accurate count impossible.
Could the heat from the fire
have launched the pod?
No, no, no.
What started the fire?
The ship's oxygen system ignited.
It was a terribly hot fire.
Yet, you say the three cases
containing the bodies were untouched.
- That's correct. [Sighs]
- Where were they found?
In the bay where the space tug
was stored.
Where everything else
was charred.
Incredible.
Is it not?
[Click]
Have you examined the cases?
Using every technique we have.
X-ray scans of the cases
yield only blurred images.
What does that mean?
They're not precisely physical objects.
More like a sort of force field.
We're a bit out of our depth here.
The whole thing is...
Yes, I know.
Incredible.
Have they done an autopsy yet
on the guard?
No, I suppose not.
What about your two other bodies?
Colonel, may I be excused?
I seem to be feeling a little more
nauseous than I thought.
Yes, of course.
I notice from your door, Dr. Fallada,
that your area is biochemistry.
But I understand
your real interest is...
Death, Colonel Caine, correct.
Thanatology is the name for it.
Death for you, Colonel, is a
bureaucratic problem-who did it?
When and why did they do it?
A problem to be solved,
am I correct?
And for you?
Well, I'm fascinated
by death itself...
What happens as we die,
when we die.
What happens after we die?
You mean, life after death.
Yes.
- Is there?
- What?
Life after death.
Do you really want to know?
No.
But to answer your question,
yes, I think there is.
If I am correct,
the life force is conserved
always and in all things,
even after death.
And you think that applies
to what's happened here tonight?
Yes.
Yes, I do.
I think that girl, creature,
drained energy, life force,
partially from Bukovsky
and totally from the guard.
A vampire?
It could be described that way, yes.
I mean, in a sense,
we're all vampires.
We drain energy
from other life forms.
The difference is one of degree.
That girl was no girl.
She's totally alien to this planet
and our life form.
And totally dangerous.
Jesus.
[whispering]
Do you believe those blokes are alive?
I'm not paid to believe nothing, am I?
I believe they're alive.
Don't look bloody dead to me.
[alarm sounds]
We've had some trouble,
but every-thing's under control.
I think you better
come down here.
Yes, sir... very good, sir.
It would appear these two
are no longer dangerous.
Well, there's certainly no possibility
of doing a full autopsy on them.
I would like to examine the guard.
Have they started the autopsy
on the guard yet?
I believe so, sir.
This is an autopsy on the body
of a young man,
dead approximately two hours.
Did you say he was about 20?
Yes, that's correct.
[clangs]
[roars]
[groans]
Get the Colonel down here,
quickly!
[groaning]
[moaning]
God.
Put him in an isolation cell,
quickly!
Sergeant.
[moaning and yelling]
I had no idea
that it could be passed on.
What do you suggest?
I would recommend that you place
this body in another cell.
It was two hours ago
that the guard was attacked.
I won't be at all surprised
if we're seeing a pattern here.
- Do as he says, Kelly.
- Yes, sir.
Also, I want the two other bodies
that were shot... the males.
Collect the pieces and watch them.
Get me the Home Secretary
on the line now.
Sir.
Call for the Colonel, sir.
Sir, you have a call.
Caine.
Sir, we've found
a naked girl in Hyde park.
The body is
in an indescribable condition.
I'll be right there.
They've just found a body
in Hyde Park.
A naked girl.
They say she's
in an indescribable condition.
Could that be your girl?
- Well?
- That's not her.
Inspector, what about the two boys?
Oh, yes, they were
in the park earlier, sir.
[chimes sounding]
Yeah, we saw her.
I think.
Earlier.
Any rate,
that looks like her hair.
- What a mess.
- Was she alone?
No, that's why we notices her.
She was with a dark haired girl.
Real good looking bird and all.
Didn't have a lot of clothes on either.
We thought they might be...
Well, you know.
Yes.
Well, did you see where they went,
where the dark haired girl went?
No, no, we didn't.
We angled on back
to see if maybe we could...
You know,
see 'em doing something.
- That's when we found her.
- How long ago was that?
Half an hour ago.
Yeah, this lad phoned us
and then we phoned you, sir.
Yes, thank you, Inspector.
Obviously, the work of the girl.
You think we can have this body sent
back to the centre with the others?
Yes, I suppose that's a good idea.
Inspector, let me know if you find
anything else, will you?
We'll be taking her back with us.
Very good, sir.
[sighs]
Now she has clothes.
There's something
I want you to see, sir.
[banging]
[yelling]
Dr. Hans Fallada, Sir Percy Heseltine,
the Home Secretary.
You're just in time.
[banging]
It's exactly two hours.
[whispering] Please help me.
This is the guard who was originally
overcome by the space girl.
[Yells]
Please.
[growling]
As I feared, once transformed,
the victims need
regular infusions of energy.
Otherwise...
Otherwise what?
[whispering] Oh, my God.
Dear God.
And down here we have the pathologist
who was attacked by the guard.
[banging]
- See.
- He too needs feeding.
[growls]
The same thing is going to happen
to that girl we found in the park.
In about one hour.
[high-pitched humming]
[beeping]
[mixed voices]
She's the last?
Have there been
any further reports, Kelly?
No, sir, we set up
to get the calls here
the instant one comes in.
- What?
- Nothing.
You say these creatures were brought
back from the Churchill?
Yes, sir, but not this one.
She's a victim of the creatures.
Yes, yes, but where did
the Churchill acquire them?
We have no way
of determining that at present.
- [male] Perhaps that's all changing.
- What?
I've just received a call
from the JPL in Pasadena.
Seems the Goldstone tracking disc has
just picked up something
they think is Churchill's escape pod...
Re-entering the Earth's atmosphere.
Where?
Texas.
[mixed voices]
[male]
Come on guys, hurry it up.
[mixed voices continue]
All right, take it easy now.
Hey, buddy, you all right?
Where?
Walter Reed Army Hospital?
Is he hurt?
Just exhausted, you say.
Well, get him the hell over here!
Colonel Carlsen,
they're expecting you, sir.
Colonel Carlsen, sir.
[Bukovsky] Tom.
I thought you were dead.
Bukovsky.
Colonel Carlsen,
allow me to introduce.
Colonel Caine
of the Special Air Services.
How do you do?
You already know Dr. Fallada.
Colonel.
Take a seat, won't you?
I'm sorry to drag you
over here like this, Tom.
I'm sure you'd rather be recuperating
with a pretty nurse.
Tom, we've got to know
what happened on the Churchill.
Yes, of course.
It may be, uh... very difficult for you
to accept what I'm going to say.
We'll have very little difficulty
believing anything
you have to tell us, Colonel.
Do go on.
You know something?
There was a fire
aboard the Churchill.
You might be interested to know
that the bodies of the three humanoids
were not destroyed in that fire.
They survived in their cases.
They were brought
down here to London,
and the female has escaped.
She's killed three people already.
Oh, my God.
So you see, Colonel, whatever
you have to tell us is rather pressing.
Please tell us what happened.
We found the bodies
aboard the alien spacecraft.
What alien spacecraft?
Colonel, take it
from the beginning.
Assume we know nothing.
Which is understating the matter.
We approached within 9,000 miles
of Halley's Comet,
when we detected an object
in the comet's coma.
After we discovered the bodies,
we transferred them
to the Churchill.
We have in tow,
the three humanoid creatures
and one of the bat-like things.
[male on radio]
This is Churchill, we copy.
Welcome back.
You gotten through
to Earth yet, Rawlings?
No, sir, and the tail
of the comet's heating up.
What's the matter Derebridge?
I don't know, Tom.
I feel drained.
Do you?
I feel invigorated.
YOU Okay?
Yeah.
- I'm fine.
- Okay.
Everybody back
to their stations.
Let's get the hell outta here.
On the trip back to Earth,
the crew began to die...
One by one.
Rawlings, the radio officer,
was the first to go.
Rawlings denied any knowledge
of what he had done.
I don't remember.
Rawlings,
besides myself, you're the only one
that's been up here
in the last hour.
I've been feeling weak recently.
Not myself.
Just don't remember. [Sighs]
We found Rawlings' body
the next day.
Exactly how did he die, Colonel?
The life just drained out of him.
One by one...
the rest of the crew
began to die.
Somehow...
I don't know how...
I held out.
It just seemed to be
a matter of will.
[click] [motor starts]
I always thought...
[Clunk]
The girl...
Yes, the girl?
I can't remember.
What I remember next is the view
out of the observation window...
Coming in to Earth's orbit.
I couldn't expose the world
to what we'd brought back with us.
[high-pitched humming]
[Clunk]
I was determined
to destroy them all.
It was the hardest thing
I ever did.
We understand.
Must have taken great courage
to try and make-
No, you don't understand.
Part of me didn't wanna leave.
She killed all my friends
and I still didn't want to leave.
Leaving her was
the hardest thing I ever did.
Colonel Carlsen
looks exhausted to me.
I think we should allow him
to get some sleep.
Continue with this later.
Very well.
Thank you, Colonel.
[Clunk]
NASA tracking and ours
have just reported and unusual
structure leaving Halley's Comet.
It's headed for us.
What is it?
Radar ranging reports
the object is a needle-like shape,
one hundred and fifty miles long.
Its present course projects out
into a perfect Earth orbit
in a little more than two days.
Oh, and I've just received a call
from the Prime Minister.
There's going to be a meeting
at Downing Street.
[sighs] PM wants answers.
[laboured breathing]
Close your eyes.
You're giving me your life.
You're taking it.
You're draining me.
You're taking too much of me.
[screams]
It was a dream.
Just a dream.
What dream, Carlsen?
The girl, she visited me.
Visited you, visited you how?
In my mind.
She... she... she...
she had some kind
of mental contact with me.
She's draining me.
Tell us about the dream, Carlsen.
I can't, it's gone.
It's faded.
I can't remember.
Carlsen, have you ever
been hypnotized?
No.
Do you mind
if I have a go at it?
It may help you
with your dreams.
Yeah, let's try it.
Not now, he's too exhausted.
Fine, fine, in the morning.
Just stare at it
until your eyes feel tired.
Then close them.
You'll feel very tired.
Very sleepy.
She seems to...
speak to me in my dreams.
She...
the girl, I feel...
What do you feel
for her, Carlsen?
I feel very...
close to her.
Is she in touch with you?
I feel...
as if my mind...
is not entirely my own.
If she is in contact
with your mind, Carlsen,
perhaps you are
in contact with hers.
Can you see her?
Can you see where she is?
Yes.
Where is she now, Carlsen?
A place, I don't know
the name of it.
She's walking.
She has a different face.
But it's her.
[Fallada] A different face,
how can that be?
She's using a different body.
[Faflada] What is she doing?
She's looking for a man.
[Faflada] What man?
Any man.
A healthy man.
[FaHada]
Does she intend to kill him?
- No.
- Why not?
She's afraid of being caught.
[Faflada]
How could she be caught?
The body'd give her away.
[Faflada]
So, what is she hoping to do?
She wants to...
draw some energy from him.
Not enough to kill him.
[Fallada] She can do that?
Yes.
There's another mind.
[whispering] Yes...
the girl's name is Ellen.
You mean there are
two people in one body?
Two minds?
Ellen and the vampire?
Yes.
She's watching a man.
[Faflada] What is the man doing?
He's parked...
Doing something with his car.
[whispers] License number.
Can you see
the license number of his car?
[whispers] Yes.
Read it out.
F-M-C
1 -2-9-E.
Or, uh... R.
[Faflada]
What is the make of the car?
A white Volvo.
[Faflada] What is she doing now?
They're driving.
[Faflada]
Does she ask him his name?
She's...
pulling her skirt...
over her knees.
She's...
He's...
putting his...
his...
hand...
on her le... on her leg.
F-M-C-1-2-9-E or possibly R,
belonging to a white Volvo.
The driver of the car picked up
a girl named Ellen.
I have to know who the girl is
and where we can find her.
She's connected with the case.
I can't explain
over an open line.
Thank you.
[phone clunks]
Do you think he's telling
the truth about the girl?
Well, we'll soon see.
How brilliant if she is moving
from body to body, mind to mind.
Taking only a small amount
of energy from each victim.
It would make sense
that we're finding no new victims.
She's hoping to leave no trail.
If the girl is no longer
in her original body,
where is her body?
Hidden.
Let's find it.
Supposing you're right
about all of this,
what about that ship up there?
What's it doing?
We can't know that.
But we've got
to assume the worst.
Maybe they're like
the vampires of legend.
How's that?
They would carry
their earth with them...
In their coffins, wouldn't they?
[male] We have
a three meter feed from Hawaii.
[male #2] Here it comes.
[male]
Put it on screen number one.
Coming in 240,000 miles.
My God, it's immense.
I say, Hugh, do you have
that skin tissue sample I asked for?
Oh, good.
Yes, of course I'll follow
containment procedure.
He's here now.
And Hugh,
send in that soldier, please.
Oh, thank you.
[knocking]
Dr. Fallada?
Just one moment, Sergeant.
Thank you for coming around.
I'll be with you shortly.
Bloody awful job,
tracing that car.
It belongs to a man named Ned Price
who lives in Yorkshire.
We have him under detention now.
What about the girl?
The girl he picked up was
a nurse named Ellen.
As you said,
Ellen-something-or-other.
He doesn't know her other name.
And he dropped her off
at Thurlstone Hospital
after spending
the afternoon with her.
He was most reluctant
to talk about it.
The man's totally exhausted.
Thurlstone.
Isn't that an asylum
of some sort?
Yes, for the criminally insane.
[helicopter rotors]
How do you do, Home Secretary,
I'm Dr. Armstrong,
director of the hospital.
Come with me to my office.
What a cold night.
Bitterly cold.
This is the nurse's house.
Ellen Donaldson is number five.
Thank you. [Chimes sound]
Shouldn't I come up
and introduce you?
I'd rather you didn't.
Come along, Dr. Armstrong,
you and I have several matters
to discuss.
Come along.
[female on intercom]
Yes, who is it?
Miss Donaldson,
my name's Colin Caine.
Dr. Armstrong brought me over.
Id' like to talk to you.
May I come in?
[door buzzes and clicks]
Yes?
What do you want?
My name's Colin Caine.
This is Colonel Carlsen,
United States Air Force.
May we come in and talk to you?
We have seen Dr. Armstrong.
May I sit down?
I want to ask you about the man
you spent the afternoon with,
Ned Price.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I think you do.
Let me see your hand.
Beg your pardon?
You're in there, aren't you?
I don't know.
Tell me.
No!
Carlsen!
It's gone from her,
it's in another body now.
How do you know that?
I can see it in her mind.
[whimpering]
She's resisting.
I'm gonna have
to force her to tell me.
Despite appearances,
this woman is a masochist.
An extreme masochist.
She wants me
to force the name out of her.
She wants me to hurt her.
I can see the images
in her mind.
Do you want to stay?
Otherwise, wait outside!
Not at all.
I am a natural voyeur.
Are you in there?
[Cries]
Are you there?
Let go.
NOW!
[screams] Now!
Well?
I've got a physical description.
Doctor, you'd better send someone
to look after Nurse Donaldson.
Is she all right?
If I described one of the inmates
to you, could you identify him?
Possibly.
Big man, fat, gray hair.
Birthmark on his face.
Jeffrey Sykes,
the child murderer.
Where did you get
his description?
Where is he now?
He's in solitary confinement.
He's been naughty.
Look, what is this about?
What we're looking for
has moved.
We could be here some time.
I better call London.
- May I use your telephone, Doctor?
- Certainly.
We have to see Sykes now.
Oh, couldn't this wait
until the morning?
Oh, all right, I'll arrange it.
Anything to oblige, Commander.
[Click]
I wish this were not
so mysterious.
If the police are involved,
haven't I a right to know?
I mean, if you're going to start
messing about my patient.
Dr. Armstrong, I sympathize
with your position, of course.
However, I can tell you it is a matter
of national security.
I see.
But, don't you think
that I should be present in any case
to represent the interests
of my patient.
- You see-
- Can I talk to you for a second?
Of course.
Uh... the man has the IQ
of a child of four.
Well, that's a decision,
I'm afraid,
I shall have to defer
to Colonel Caine.
Yes, of course
you can come along.
Can we start now?
What are you going to do to him?
I'd like to hypnotize him.
What's that?
Pentothal and morphine.
I'd recommend it for pre-hypnosis
and patient management.
Well, he seems quiet.
We're ready when you are.
- Lamson.
- Sir.
[snares]
Can the injection be dangerous?
He should have
no difficulty tolerating it.
There's always a risk, sir.
May I have that?
Well, I'll wake him up.
- What are you doing!
- Stay where you are.
He's sick, Lamson, help us,
I can't explain now.
[Yells]
There's our killer, Sir Percy.
[mixed voices yelling]
It's madness.
I want to question him
before it wears off.
Where can we take him?
Up the ramp, sir.
[voices calling out]
We need to be alone
for a minute, Lamson.
How the devil
did you know it was him?
In the nurses quarters
he touched me on the shoulder.
I saw into his mind.
What?
The Colonel appears to be able
to see in the minds
of people who have been possessed
by the girl creature, sir.
It happens when I touch 'em.
Let's get him on the table.
HOW?
How do you know
she's still inside Armstrong?
What's to prevent her
from moving to someone else?
She's trapped.
I can feel that.
Are you sure?
No.
- Lamson.
- Sir?
Can you bring me another dose
of the hypnotic drug?
I suppose so, sir.
One dose is usually enough.
This is not a usual situation.
How long does the stuff last?
A dose like that?
A couple of hours.
We'll definitely need more.
Bring me three doses.
- Three?
- I'll take responsibility, Lamson-—.
Sir Percy and myself,
just get on with it.
Yes, sir.
Is a second dose safe?
Surely it can strain his heart.
Look... you don't know
what we're dealing with here.
If he slips out from under,
she'll escape.
Armstrong, can you hear me?
Armstrong, if you can hear me,
just say yes.
It... it...
won't let me...
ta... talk to you.
[Yells]
Armstrong, Armstrong!
Can you see what it is
that's holding you prisoner?
Yes, yes, she...
Tell her she has to talk to me!
Tell her!
- [knocking]
- Yes?
Pentothal,
I brought the pentothal.
Thanks, Lamson, that'll be all.
No.
Hold him.
[female alien voice]
There's no need for that.
No need.
You in there,
can you still hear me?
Can you get into his mind?
Her mind?
Not with this drug,
it's like a wall.
Perhaps you've given him
too much.
- Perhaps we...
- Shut up!
Listen, you bitch,
I'll keep you in this state
for weeks, if I have to.
Now, you talk to me.
Carlsen, be with me.
What do you want from me?
I love you.
What are you?
Why are you so human?
So perfect?
What are the bird creatures
on the ship?
Our bodies are unimportant.
As you and your men
have approached in your ship,
we changed them.
For you.
We entered your minds
and found there new bodies.
I took my shape from your mind.
I took your language.
I became the woman
I found there,
in your deepest thoughts,
your deepest needs.
I am the feminine
in your mind, Carlsen.
[whispering] Where are you?
Where are you!
Where's your body!
Let me go! Let me go!
Touch me, Carlsen.
Let me go.
Let me go!
Let me go. Let me go!
Let me go.
- It's already spreading.
- How?
You didn't stop it,
it's too late.
That's impossible, we've been only
half a step behind her all the way.
Sir, this gentleman's
stopped breathing.
There's no pulse either.
Sir, I think his neck is broken.
Lampson, prepare two stretchers.
One for Sir Percy
and one for Dr. Armstrong.
Prepare all your remaining doses
of the drug for travel.
Yes, sir.
You said the thing
hadn't stopped,
it was still spreading.
Why did you say that?
I don't know.
Could the girl have been deliberately
leading us away from London?
Is it possible we didn't find
all of her victims?
If we didn't find all
the victims,
if there are others
besides the girl in the park.
The thing would spread.
And a chain reaction,
geometrically, until by now...
[whispers] Oh, Christ.
Lieutenant, can we use the radio
to get through to the S.R.C. in London?
Just a moment, sir,
there's something coming through.
It is the S.R.C., sir,
for you and Carlsen.
Go ahead.
[male on radio]
Caine, can you hear me?
Fallada, speak up,
I can't hear you.
The two males didn't die.
They jumped to the bodies
of the two soldiers who shot them
and transformed the soldiers bodies
into their own likenesses.
That's the difference between them
and their victims.
The victims can't leave
their bodies.
Only the original three
can do that.
But I've killed one of them.
- One of which?
- One of the two male vampires.
One of the transformed ones.
How did you kill him,
Fallada, how?
The old way, Carlsen.
A leaded metal shaft,
penetrating not through the heart,
but through the energy centre
two inches below the heart.
Not steel, but leaded iron.
Right, Carlsen?
Are you there, Carlsen?
Yes.
Carlsen, you too, Caine,
it is my belief
that the vampires of legend
came from creatures
such as these.
Perhaps even
from these very creatures.
I know it sounds incredible.
Do you hear me, Carlsen!
It's more than a belief, Fallada...
it's true.
They visited Earth before.
What about
the other male, Fallada?
He's free.
You have the girl?
Yes.
We'll be with you
as soon as we can, hold on.
We'll try.
This came through
while you were talking, sir.
- What is it?
- A scrambled cryptogram.
It's to Sir Percy
from the Prime Minister.
We're to proceed directly
to the Citadel at Whitehall.
Came...
[Yells]
Lieutenant, the controls!
[screams]
[Carlsen]
We've lost her, she's gone.
Where?
Her body's in London.
Where in London?
Carlsen, you've got to tell me
what happened,
what really happened
on the Churchill.
It wasn't Rawlings who destroyed
the radio equipment.
And the ship's tapes.
It was me.
Why?
I didn't want the Churchill
to be able to reach Earth.
And if it did, I didn't want anyone
to know what happened.
What did happen?
I opened her sealed
animation case.
Either I did it or She did it.
I couldn't help myself.
I've never experienced such...
I was in love on a level
you've never known, Caine.
It terrifies me.
My memory plays tricks on me.
She was calling me.
Her power was... spiritual.
She wanted me, Caine.
It was more than spiritual.
She took some of my energy.
And she gave me
some of her energy.
They must have been living off
of each other when we found them.
There were only three
of them left.
She killed all of my men.
One by one.
But I survived.
She wanted me to survive.
She chose me!
Why, why!
Carlsen, she's not human,
she's not a woman.
She'll destroy you.
She's destroyed worlds.
There's something
you might want to hear, sir.
A special bulletin from the BBC.
[male announcer]
It's obvious that tonight,
London is on the brink of the worst
devastation since the blitz.
From where I'm standing,
I can see large areas of the city
burning out of control.
And thousands of people are now
rampaging through the streets here
in a frenzied last effort
to avoid the plague.
Martial law has been enforced now
for three hours.
But for the moment,
it hasn't stemmed what is obviously...
[clamouring]
Yes, sir, we've been
expecting you.
Thank you, carry on.
- Carry on, Sergeant.
- Right, sir.
- Higgins, around the other side.
- Right.
[mixed voices]
[male] Is everything ready
for the cabinet to evacuate?
[male #2] Yes, everything.
[female]
Please take a seat, gentlemen.
Sir, I have Colonel Caine
and Colonel Carlsen here for you, sir.
Very good.
The Prime Minister
will see you shortly.
Uh, would you care for a cup of tea,
while you wait?
No, our business is
rather urgent.
Yes, I'm sure the Prime Minister
understands that.
- Oh, uh, gentlemen?
- Prime Minister.
I'm Colonel Caine,
Special Air Service,
and I'm sure you've heard of
Colonel Carlsen, late of the Churchill.
Oh, ye... yes, indeed, uh, gentlemen,
I look forward to hearing your report.
By the way, uh,
where is Sir Percy?
Dead, I'm afraid.
Oh, that's a great pity.
Sir, we have information regarding
the object in space,
which is bearing down on the Earth
at this moment...
Ye-ye-yes, gentlemen, look, if you'll
excuse me just... just for a moment.
Mi-Miss Haversham,
please come this way.
Miss Haversham, here,
for a moment.
I'll be back, gentlemen,
I'll be back.
[PM whispering] Miss Haversham,
Miss Haversham, come this way.
Miss Haversham, please.
[clamouring]
[male] Mind his head.
[female] Go and get
the doctor immediately.
Hey, what's happening
down there?
[male] Need a doctor over here.
GO! 90!
[Yells]
Lieutenant, do you have
any weapons aboard the craft?
No, sir, uh,
there's a flare pistol, sir.
Where is it?
Just close the breach
and it's ready to fire.
Sir, while you were with the PM,
I had a call from base operations.
The city is now
under martial law.
We've been placed
under NATO command.
- NATO?
- Yes, sir.
My unit's been mobilized
across the river
to a staging area at Blackheath.
Land at the S.R.C., Lieutenant,
we've got to talk to Fallada.
I've been ordered to land
at Blackheath, sir.
The city's now
under air quarantine.
If we don't do as they say,
they'll shoot us out of the air.
Hello, zero, this is x-ray 3-1-8
requesting clearance to land... over.
Zero roger, x-ray 3-1-8,
you are clear to land.
Come away from the aircraft.
You are under quarantine.
Over here, please, sir.
Don't come any closer,
stop there!
I want to talk
to your commanding officer.
I am Colonel Caine,
Special Air Service.
And this man
is Colonel Tom Carlsen,
United States Air Force and former
commander of the Churchill.
[male on PA]
C company, be on stand-by.
Is Dr. Hans Fallada here
from the S.R.C.?
He knows who we are
and what's going on.
No, not that I know of.
- Has anybody heard of him?
- No.
Must still be in London.
Colonel, what exactly do you know
about what's happening over there?
All we know
for certain, Colonel,
is that a terrible plague
of some sort is sweeping London.
The incubation period
appears to be two hours.
And until that time has elapsed,
I cannot release you
from this compound.
Colonel, we know
what the plague is.
We are not infected.
I know what I'm talking about
and we're wasting valuable time.
We have totally isolated London
in order to stop further contagion.
If that fails and the surrounding
areas are threatened,
Yes?
Sterilization by thermonuclear device
has been approved.
We have this
from General Ames in Brussels.
He's coming up
with that decision in... [sighs]
Just under three hours.
Have you heard anything
about the ship?
[female] Corporal Adams...
- The ship?
- The thing from Halley's Comet.
Oh... [sighs]
It's parked itself
in a geostationary orbit... [sighs]
Directly over London.
[male on PA] Would air adjutant report
to Major Grover in GHQ.
All those little blue lights going up
toward the clouds,
they're human souls.
How do you know that?
I feel it.
The process of conversion
releases a life energy.
Then it can be collected.
Collected?
Is that what the umbrella is?
Collector?
The energy doesn't go free.
It goes up there.
[clamouring]
[Carlsen] The male vampire's
collecting life energy.
But he has to send it through her
to get it up to the collector.
Where is she, Carlsen?
Over there.
I get flashes coming
from her body.
Sensitive to its environment.
Picks up things.
[Caine] Can you find her?
[Carlsen]
If I can get across to the city.
[Caine] What about the male?
[Carlsen] He'll come
if he senses I've found her.
She's drawing me, Caine.
[female alien voice] Carlsen.
[Carlsen] I've gotta go.
[whispering] Why?
She wants back
the energy she gave me.
When they take on
a new life form
they have to learn
from that life form.
Mate with it, in a sense.
The girl chose me.
But when she mixed with me,
she gave me a part of herself.
And now she wants
that part back.
Is there any sign of activity
in your sector?
- Over.
- No, sir.
Okay, keep me posted... over.
Colonel, listen to me.
Carlsen believes
he can locate the source.
There are only two carriers.
If we can destroy them, it may not
be necessary to destroy London.
But we only have
an hour and a half.
[machine gun firing]
[male] What was that?
Cease firing!
Carlson?
Where's Carlsen?
He knocked over two of my men
and took an armoured Land Rover.
Oh, bloody hell, did he say anything
about where he was going?
He wanted to know where
the Space Research centre was?
Rogers told him, the next thing I knew,
I was on the ground, sir.
Right, whose is this car?
- That, that's the Colonel's, sir.
- Give me the keys.
- What?
- You heard me.
Give me the bloody keys,
I'm commandeering the car!
Give it to him.
And your side arm.
Are you sure you know
what you're doing?
You realize once you're inside there,
we can't allow you out.
[male] Where is he going?
[clamouring]
[honking]
Colonel Caine, S.A.S.,
I'm crossing the river.
You don't want to go
in there, sir.
I know I don't.
Get them gates in position!
Secure this post... move!
[clamouring]
[honking]
- [clunk]
- [groaning]
[female alien voice]
Carlsen, Carlsen.
[growling]
Carlsen.
Carlsen. Carlsen.
[grinding]
[grinds gears]
Carlsen. Carlsen.
[clicks]
Fallada?
Caine.
I'm glad to see you alive.
I reciprocate the sentiment.
Is he really dead?
This time?
The only way they can be killed.
Where's Bukovsky?
Dead.
HOW?
Like the rest.
How did you survive?
You're looking for Carlsen.
Has he been here?
No, perhaps he misled you.
What do you know about it?
I've been doing some more work.
Go on.
I discovered
there is life after death.
How do you know?
There is a certain
mental transference, telepathy,
that occurs between the vampires
and their victims.
Carlsen is after the girl.
How did you know that?
Oh, I...
I seem to sense it.
Where is she, Fallada?
Don't you know?
Carlsen knows.
Where, Fallada?
She's in the cathedral.
She's been there
since she escaped.
Rather a nice touch,
don't you think?
The crypt of kings and queens.
Stay where you are.
Stay where you are!
[laughs]
Here I go.
[explosion]
[growling]
I knew you would come, Carlsen.
I'm here.
Now can this madness end?
Come.
Be with me.
I need you.
It was always intended
you should find us
and bring us to Earth.
The web of destiny carries
your blood and soul
back to the genesis
of my life form.
Come.
Be with me.
Come with me, Carlsen.
[clamouring]
[shrieking]
It'll be much less terrifying
if you just come to me.
I'll do just that.
[yelling]
[screeching]
Carlsen!
What are these feelings?
Why do I feel so close to you?
Need you?
Because you're one of us.
You always have been.
You're like me.
Be with me.
Just a little more.
Carlsen!
Caine!
[yelling]