Why laughing?
You can tell from my tattoo
l am naive and nice
Look at your tattoo,
want to scare others?
You guess first
Guess what?
Guess the outcome?
l don´t know the outcome of mine
but you must have none, open it
How come?
Must l kiss you? You didn´t
even know l exchanged your dice
Eat beans!
Your turn
What game do you want?
Poker
But l have a condition
l know you´re not that nice, tell me
lf you win, you may
take away all the cash here
lf you lose, leave one of your hands
Why must you bet on human limbs?
This is the rules of my casino
Everyone who challenges
me must comply with it
l don´t mind telling you
l come, not for your dirty money
l come to tell you l, Jersy,
can defeat you, Tetsuo!
OK, just don´t regret
Begin
Hey, 3 Diamond serve first
You´re host, but why so mean?
OK, l´m host, you serve first
A pair or K
A pair of 2
Straight Flush, you have that?
2 Heart, you have 11 cards on hand
l know how to change cards too
But l thought you wouldn´t use
this trick as you´re expert
Kid, you´re not up to it
l´ve lost
But... may I keep my hand?
OK?
Not necessarily
Ass-hole, drip wax on me?
Hello?
Tetsuo speaking
There´s no common topic
between us, l´m afraid
Your friend is here with me
Who?
The guy with you last night
l´ve said l love watching wax dripping
But not trying it myself!
Man, weaker flame, slowly please
Do you hear him?
He has nothing to do with me
You´re so cool?
Cool!
Hold it...
You wait for me
Jersy!
My God! Jersy!
Cool, take me away!
These people are beasts!
Are you OK?
OK? But l really reach climax!
Give me face and
let me take him away
You can´t just come and go
or else Mr. Tetsuo will lose face
This has nothing to do with you
Cool, l always take you as buddy
But due to our rules,
l can´t be of help
What must l do to take him away?
Leave a hand
You must be killing me!
l wonder if l can win back his hand?
You´ll gamble with me?
l have no choice, right?
lf you lose,
you must leave both hands
No way!
My left hand is my beloved limb
And you mustn´t chop it
Why keep your left hand?
You´re not left-handed
l tell you...
since l was 13
My left hand has helped me wanking
And l still need it for wanking in future
This... chop it at once!
Mr. Tetsuo, what do you think?
l´ve been longing for
a game with you for 3 years
So why not invite Asian
celebrities here as witnesses
They can be judge of our game
l don´t mean this
l only want a game with you here
And no one shall reveal
the result, whoever of us win
OK, you´re expert
Let´s have a game
of sudden death
What do you want to play?
Flying Poker cards
OK, we´ll each draw 5 cards,
and see whose cards are bigger
l have no objection
No Ace, no 9, you can´t
get straight flush now
l have straight flush
But you´ve torn these 9s just then
lf l hadn´t pushed an 8 in it
l think you never believe there´s no 9
5, 6, 7, 8, 9
ls my straight flush bigger than yours?
Good, Cool has won!
You know why l like you,
as you´re mad at games
Untie him
l can take him away?
Yes
l really want to have
a serious game with you
Maybe later
Don´t go, l want to talk to you
You really go to peep
at my wife everyday?
What do you mean?
You love peeping?
lt´s OK, l have lots of tapes
You know, everyday after l bath her
l start playing her, up
and down, front and back...
As we´re buddies, enjoy
You´re not human!
She´s my wife,
you can´t change this fact
Tonight... I'll play
wax dripping with her
Ready to get my tapes
Let´s go, never mind the rope
You must try tonight, it´s funny
What did you talk to him?
About our co-operation
But he keeps beating the bush
Does he?
You needn´t say anymore
l will close this place and leave
Where are you going?
l don´t know
Now that they know l run this place
They´ll keep giving me trouble
You´d better go back to HK,
l don´t want you to get involved
l suggest that...
we should all return to HK!
And we´ll surely turn HK upside-down!
This life-style is not my cup of tea
Not your cup of tea?
lf not, why not switch to another?
Since you want to leave,
what about taking Karen with you?
Taking Karen with me?
Sure, you fear you´ll be arrested?
Take her out and fly with her
to a place where no one knows you
Then you can lead your own life
lt must be better than
leave her with that maniac
Doesn´t that hurt you?
Come on, he is right. OK, let´s go
Don´t consider, let´s take
Karen with us tomorrow!
Don´t shout, l won´t hurt you
Karen, don´t panic, l´m here
She behaves normally
Don´t worry, it´s going to be fine
Thanks
Look how romantic they are
And you, you´re a real stink!
A famous Japanese movie star
came for me and l ignored her
And you detest me?
Ghosts come for you, l say!
Can you let Karen have a rest?
She has been asleep for years
may be wakened
with our shouting
Go out please
l ask you not to shout
You go, you go and l´ll be quiet
What me go?
You bullshit all day!
Don´t push me!
Oh! My God!
Have l slept for a long time?
No
Karen...
l seem to have made a...
very long dream
l cannot find you in my dream
lt´s not a dream,
you were not dreaming...
You´ve wakened, really wakened
Karen...
Don´t leave me!
No, l never will
l won´t ever leave you...
l won´t ever leave you
l´ll stay with you forever
Honey...
Hold me!
Say... do you love me?
Of course l love you
Buy me a gold watch then
Doctor, are you here?
See if she´s nuts or something!
You´re bad!
No sex for one month!
l think you´d better
leave Japan at once
But Karen has no passport
Don´t worry, before l became a Boss
l learnt how to make a fake passport
l only need a genuine
passport as sample
then l can duplicate
a passport for Karen
Where to find a genuine one?
Don´t you have one?
What about me?
How can l go home?
Report loss to Consulate, and
you´ll get a new one in weeks
OK
l can stay and do more shopping
2,000 Yen here, we´ll share, take it
Put it away, it´s bad if you lose it
You take it all
Why? Why so mean?
Still got more?
No more
Give me at once!
Why must you be so practical?
What? 50,000 Yen is still very little!
Still got more?
No more!
l still have a roll of banknotes
lt´s not money, stop this!
Hey, remember this place?
You two danced casually here
and it has become a legend
The past life doesn´t suit me anymore
You must adapt to it again, anyway
Why?
Jersy, what are these people doing?
l am really someone in HK
As you´re my sworn brother...
l must make a welcome party for you
Greet Brother Cool!
Welcome Cool,
welcome to show up again!
Jersy, l have never said
l´ll show up again
Haven´t you?
Cool
Don´t let them down, OK?
But l´m not used to
this situation anymore
But l find it pretty good
As long as you like it
OK then!
Say no more, open champagne!
Cheers for Brother Cool!
Hey, how do you feel now
that you´re back in HK?
Everything is strange to me
You´ll adapt it slowly
The more you stick to rich, dirty life
and you´ll get used to it soon
l used to enjoy such a material life
but this time l come back...
l find everything is an illusion
Jersy, don´t ask me to the situation
like last night again
OK, make it every other night
Right, where´s Karen?
l´ve send a guard
to go shopping with her
and l also gave her
an ATM card for shopping
Cool
You´ve done a lot of shopping
Take this stuff upstairs for me
- Sure
- Thanks
Bo... Boss
Damn it! Why stammer?
No, but... sister Karen spent more
than $200,000 on shopping
More than $200,000... cash?
Why did you buy so much?
l´ve bought a watch
and some jewels
l don´t want you to lose face
if l go out with you
You don´t like...
as l´ve bought too much?
No, but we must forget our past life
Be discreet when spending in future
l go to fit them on
- Come on
- Good...
Sorry, l´ll pay you back the $200,000
lt´s OK, l´ll take it as sauna fee
Can you lend me an extra $100,000?
You need money that badly?
You want to go to Macau?
No, l don´t like gambling
l want to bet on horses
l want the video tapes and data
of horse racing for the last 2 years
lncluding the draws,
jockeys, dividends
field situations,
family trees of new horses
But l don´t want data
from newspapers
l need those professional ones
The most favourite thing in HK...
is that you can win money,
without contacting anyone
You can win in horse racing
by just sitting at home
There´s hundreds of
millions of dividends this time!
lf no jackpot,
it´s not worth betting
Now the dividend is right
What to bet?
lt´ll soon be closed!
Don´t hurry, let´s sit for a while
Hello, what´s the reading for
the grass track?
2.13, it´s sticky track then
Thanks
Bet on all those that
l haven´t marked on
There´re 6 horses for the first leg
and 7 horses for the second leg
and five for the third leg
So there´re 7000 bets in total
Each bet is $10, so it´s $70,000
lt´s done
Why so tired?
Sure, l haven´t slept
for 3 days already
You can finish in 30 minutes,
you´re Master Of Gambling
Horse racing is indeed statistics
The more effort you put,
the bigger chance to win
l never pay attention to
which horse will win
but l´ve been ruling out horses
that are going to lose
Horses l haven´t marked on must
have a bigger chance to win
You´re very professional
Occasional gambling relies on luck
but frequent gambling talks about skills
1, 2, 3, 10...
Don´t be nervous
l can´t help, it´s winning soon!
1, 2, 3, 10...
Rush...
We´ve won!
What about number 7?
That ass-hole had a fall!
But you still won Triple Tierce
What´s wrong with you?
You´ve won Triple Tierce,
you´re not shot
You aren´t excited at all?
l´ve studied for days, if l don´t win...
l´d better kill myself
l tell you, work with me and you´ll
make big money in horse racing
Just let me take all decisions
Only $40 million?
And l´m not the only winner?
There´re lots of competent guys, l say
Jersy, shall we share the $40 million?
But wouldn´t it be better...
if you teach me?
You can have my half share
What do you want me to teach you?
Teach me a bit of everything you know
What l want to learn
most is flying cards, why?
So smart!
Flying cards is simple indeed
Just concentrate
your force in a spot
First, you must estimate
how many spins it must swirl...
before it reaches the target
lt´s about 11 yards to
the target from here
This card is 2 by 4
and a half inches
l guess it´ll reach
the target with 31 spins
Try it
lt´s about 10 yards from the target
from here
This card is 4 and
a half inches long
lt means it´ll reach
the target with 25 spins
Don´t hurried with flying cards
You must practise a lot
before you make a success
Practise on, ask me
if you have any difficulties
But I have... lots of...
No way, it must be my nail
that lowered my force
l´ll surely make it this time
No way, l must be hungry...
and threw it too weakly
l´ll make it this time
No way, l must have anaemia
So l failed in it
l use internal energy,
l must make it this time
lf l fail again, l´d better die!
l won´t use fishing
line again this time!
But l definitely fail
without the fishing line
No, l must try other ways!
No way, l must be too tired
l must sleep now!
What dream did
l make just then?
l recall now, l saw him!
I saw... pig´s skin!
Stop looking on
What is it?
Come on, chat with me
Let me look at you
l´m happy
Why happy?
As you pamper me
l let you suffer too much in the past
so l must compensate you
You don´t fear
l´ll spend all your money?
l´ll make money
if you spend it all
Have you ever thought about...
winning big money again?
Then we can retire
How to win big money
again and then retire?
Tetsuo
But you´re always against
me competing with him
lt´s not the same now
His office takes up
all soccer betting in S.E. Asia
Europe Cup this year
will bring him $3 billion profit
Who told you that?
They did
l could always hear their conversation
lf you defeat him,
we can take over the office
And lots of people
will make money for you
lf so, l can never retire
He´ll still come for you,
though you avoid him
Anyway, l don´t want to have
relation with people of this field
Stop it, you will never understand this
Karen
l go out
You scare me to death
What´s wrong with Karen?
She looks upset
She wants me to challenge Tetsuo
She´s right with that!
And you need her to remind you,
you´re retarded
All l want is peaceful life
lf you don´t gamble, you mean
you´ll become a gigolo?
l´m just joking
Don´t you find that Karen...
Nothing
What is it?
Help!
Hello?
What to talk business with you
Cool, help!
Yeung Kwong, what do you want?
Want you to gamble with Tetsuo
Gamble with Tetsuo?
lf you agree...
you can have Karen after the game
Yeung Kwong, l agree!
OK, straight guy!
l´ll inform you
the location and time later
lt´s a deal
Hello!
You can´t avoid this time
Defeat Tetsuo and rescue Karen
This aircraft-carrier is
the iron base of Tetsuo...
for taking up bets of soccer
and horse racing of Asia?
Right
He bought it from Russia, modified it
and leaves it in highseas
so as to receive
satellite signals as well
Governments of all
Asian nations can´t deal with it
lf ever small squadron
wants to approach it
it´ll shoot a missile
and eliminate them
lt seems to be powerful
Right, or it won´t be
called iron base
We might buy such an aircraft-carrier
as toy if we make money in future
l´ve been waiting for
this day for ages
Me too
You two behave like
whores who long for men
Don´t bullshit, start now
Today is the Final of
European Cup Soccer
France Vs ltaly
The two heroes are meeting here
Audience are also interested in
our final battle as well
Result will be out before dawn
To prevent anyone cheating
we´ll record the whole game tonight
We also have the honour
of inviting 10 referees
So you really stress on the title
of Asian Number One
l´ve waited for 3 years
Today is the Final
of European Cup Soccer
and the time for us
to find out who the winner is
You won´t believe me,
l´ve guessed what he says
Therefore you want to bet on Poker
and soccer at the same time?
Right, France is giving half goal
l think France has better skills
but France will have a hard
match to give half goal to ltaly
l bet on ltaly, $50 million
OK
Hurry up, Big 2 or Showhand?
Baccarat
Make it a serious game,
let the bet decide who will win
$100 million chips for each of you,
you can bet however much you want
$100 million? You mean
the number of my sperm?
l don´t have so much
Silly boy
The name of Cool
is already worth a billion
No problem
No problem with me either
l´ve bet on Player, $10 million
OK, l bet on Banker
Blow...
As big as possible
8, not bad
Both sides 8, a draw
First round a draw?
Strange, isn´t it?
Silly boy, they mean to be
police for the first round only
You saw it?
We manage to remember all card
sequences of 16 sets when shuffling
Now we´ll fight with memory
For the first 10 rounds, the very first
round should be a draw
Then the winning sequence will be
Banker, Banker, then Player
then Player, Banker, Banker,
Banker, Banker, Banker
so... let´s bet $5,000
on Banker at once
At least $5 million for it!
So l always say if you bet from
time to time...
you can then enjoy retiring life
$20 million, on Banker
l bet on Banker too, $20 million
Mr. Tetsuo, please read the cards
Player 1, Banker 8, Banker wins
What´s the point of playing
when you all know the results?
Only the last round will
decide who´ll win finally
Because l fail to
see the last card clearly
Yeah!
ltaly wins by 1-0!
l´ve said France will have a hard
match if she´s to give half goal!
Boss, there´re intruders,
many of our men have died
Don´t disturb, it´s the last round!
Yes, Boss
Mr. Tetsuo, let´s have
another game later
Don´t let those people disturb us
You´ve lost by one point
lt seems this is going
to be the last round
l´ll bet on Banker
So sure?
l´ll believe in luck occasionally
OK, l´ll bet on Player then
Good, let´s decide
who´ll win with this hand
Serve
A black card
lt´s now the most critical moment
6 or 7, hit...
1, 2 or 3...
9!
lf the next card isn´t either 3 or 4...
No chance then
They´re intruding!
Sorry
Sorry for interfering with your
Poker game, you two idiot
Yeung Kwong!
How dare you betray me?
You´re much more stupid than him!
Being an able, smart guy...
l don´t want to work under you
You damned fool
You both want to
be Asian Number One?
l´m Asian Number One!
Yeung Kwong, where´s Karen?
Yeung Kwong, l want a duel with you!
Are you OK?
You still miss women at this moment?
You haven´t had women for ages?
Don´t ever think l´ll let
your woman go as you come
Cool...
He kidnapped Karen so as to
force me to gamble with you
l see
Your target must be the billions
of cash here
l tell you, you can never make it
Don´t worry, no one will blinkly
know even if all of you die
l´ll spread the news after
l´ve got all the money...
that you two idiots die in my hands
Get me all the cash
from the safe now!
l´m afraid my very last game...
can never finish
Don´t move, look at that side
Cool!
The soccer match is breathtaking,
l was going to kill you after the match
but l´m afraid of your flying cards
So what shall l do?
Therefore l suggest...
chopping it off
1-1 now!
Mighty? lt´s designed to neutralise
your flying cards attack
Cool!
You have no more hope
You´re not karen
When did you notice that?
Because l´ve rescued
your sister from Japan already
Since we returned to HK
l notice that you have
a totally different character
So l asked Banana to
check at the big house
and we learnt that
your sister was still there
Then l pretend to let
nature take it´s course
Promise to have a game with Tetsuo
and settle the old scores
between Yeung Kwong and me
Brother Kwong, we´ve got the money!
You leave now!
Let´s go
You leave now
l´m sorry...
to cheat you...
l´m sorry l´ve betrayed my sister
Cool...
What is the last card?
You´ve won
lt´s an Ace
Wait!
Wait...
l must die anyway...
so can you just give me a chance?
Just once!
Then I... will die with no regret
l´ve made it!
l´m the King Of
The World lnternational!
Cool
l´ll see which is faster,
your flying card or a missile
How many second you run 100 metres?
What? What catties of rice?
Let´s run!
Kill him!
Cool!
We´re real buddies, let´s do it together!
Accompany me, let´s do it together!
Big challenge!
Together, accompany me!
Together...
Take off!
Run faster! The propeller is stuck,
it´ll explode soon!
lt was generous of you
to burn all the money, thanks
lt was a big challenge for me
But sometimes for the sake of friends...
l´ll take money as shit
Frankly speaking,
your thank is very worthy
Hubby!
Honey!
l miss you so much!
Let me show you something
- No
- you better give me a kiss
- l miss you so much
- Take a look now
- No
- You´ll be cheered once you see it
No! Just look at me
Give me a kiss,
l´ve missed you so much
l beg you
Just a kiss?
Yes, just a kiss!
Karen
Nothing can separate us anymore
You bitch, you break
the capillaries on my lips
l´m not cheating you,
l only want one kiss
Very romantic!
Let´s leave
Jersy!
France finally won by 2-1 that evening
Therefore l always say...
nothing is impossible in this world
That night was the last time
l saw Cool and Karen
And they haven´t been seen since then
l wish them a happy ending
And l, Jersy, will definitely become
the most powerful Master Of Gambling
Come to challenge me if you dare
you can never pay back
though you become gigolo
Laughing?