Oh my---
What's with the mask?
I thought this was the only
way to be honest to you
- Sang-mi, I love you
- What?
- Have you been drinking?
- Just a little
Who do you think will win
if Hwang-bo raced a tortoise?
A tortoise will win
Then who do you think will win
if I raced the tortoise?
I will
I'll prove it to you right here
- Hey Sang-mi, count three for me
- What?
I'll show you
how much I love you
- One
Two--- Three---
We're going in
We should've done
marathon too
Stop!
Hey, that's a bomb
Don't drink that
Where's the PPX bag?
Hey Yamada sang
Any suspects
you're thinking of?
Do you have any?
- Well--- I'm thinking the director
- The director?
- Make some sense, will you??
- What?
He's been overly anxious lately
He's definitely up to something
Caught right on the scene---
You think you guys have time
to just sip coffee?
- Why just me?
- What?
He had coffee too, you know
I only go for one
- Sir!
- What now?
What is it?
What kind of an asshole
would call collect?
Tell him to pay himself
And, you---
Tell him that this is Murakami
Hello? Hello?
Brother, don’t hang up man
Please don’t hang up
Remember the green fish, bro?
Green fish!
When I was little,
I was catch that green fish---
Then I lost my slipper
Then you and other brothers
beat the crap out of me---
Hey bro, you remember that?
- You remember that?
- Excuse me/- Yes?
Sorry to interrupt while you' re
talking, but you got a coins---
Brother, please don’t hang up
Please don’t hang up brother
Hey bro, do you remember that?
Do you remember that or not?
You don’t?
Hey shithead,
you think life's that easy?
Sir, another call for you
I said not to bother
He keeps on insisting
that he's Murakami
Oh shit
Yes, I am the director
in charge
This is Murakami of the
honorable MMP
You should've said---
I would've picked up
Forget that, I want to speak to
an old friend of mine
Your Korean got better
What are you a tour guide
now or something?
Hey, gook
Just listen
We placed PPXs at major
public vicinities around Seoul
You know of PPX, right?
What do you want?
Just relax
The first one will be
at the new Worldcup stadium
It's going to detonate
in exactly 30 minutes
You're probably startled
Have you ever
been to Takeshima?
You mean Dok-do?
When I was in the navy, I used
to carefully observe Takeshima
You Koreans insist that
Takeshima's yours
But you people know
nothing about it
- Takeshima---
- Dok-do is
comprised of the
West island and the East island
The east island is
64, 698 square meters
And the east,
91,773 square meters
Longitude, 131 ° 52 min 22 sec,
Latitude, 37 ° 14 min 12 sec
It's only 90 miles apart
from the Ullung island
But it's almost 160 miles
from the nearest
Japanese island, Okki
- In history, Takeshima is---
- Takeshima is---
Historically, Dok-do has been
acquired into our territory---
BC 512, 13th year
of King Jijung's rule
Well---that's your story
The Japanese history has it that
in the 17th century---
If you look in the
Unju records,
And in the 1896 text written
by the Japanese
foreign ministry,
they acknowledge
Dok-do as Korean
I did some research of my own
So what?
I didn't say anything
I was just go to say that
that's the name of our mission
That's great genius
Couldn't get him, sir
Why the hell did you make
him hang up you fuck?
What are you here for?
Send forces to the stadium
Move!
What? You separated them
to save money?
And mixed water
in them too?
Okay!
It's possible that the remains
may explode, so keep searching
Hey, come here you two
I thought the guy would
be more daring than that
Only one trash bin in the
entire frigging stadium
Trash bin Trash bin Trash bin
Any leads, boys?
This is too strange
Are you fucking with us?
This time that was it
But wait for next time
Just be honest,
you lost the PPX, right?
That's PPX alright
Check the ingredients
Thought you had
me there for a second
Where's the next one at?
The Jang-chung Arena?
I'll be back Fangbo
I'll blow it all up
How would I know that
they were just water?
This is good
- Hey look at this
- What?
Put more water in you fuck
The soup's too salty
It's fine
- It's salty
- No it's not
- It is too
- It's not
It is too
Would you believe me if I
had said this is the Mia district?
I am standing in front of Mia's
apartment explosion scene
Early this morning at around
4 o'clock, there was a doubt-fire
that has turned the entire area
into one gigantic rubble
The whole area
has been effected
The police said that---
homeless teenagers were---
supposedly trying to cook
where an explosion took place
They will take the butane
seller into custody for interrogation
They boiled PPX in the pot?
- Hello?
- This is Murakami
You fuck! Why are you
harming innocent civilians?
We didn't do it
Well--- you guys are the
ones with PPX
Someone took it from us
What the fuck are
you talking about?
I'm serious
We just saw the news too
Are you listening?
I'm going berserk too
- What are you doing?
- Go Go Go
Hello?
Time out
Move!
We got five
How many do they have?
- Thirty, sir
- Shit---thirty?
We're go to get schooled
You know what, right?
- Yes
- Do not go one on one
We need to go zone
When he's covering him,
you shoot
What the hell is wrong with you?
You go when you're supposed to
You're not go to
get all three at once
- Make sure you cover them
- And you--- you just shut up
Whatever we're not
going down either
Why do you look all tired?
They got five
We got thirty and can't get
a single one of them
What's with you people?
We need more people
We don't have enough---
- Just listen to--- the rebound---
- Why can't you get that? Try
Just do as you would in practice
Are you guys with me?
Kill them all today
Come on--- just like in practice
Come on guys I'm with you
Head to head
Hey!
Are you boys ready to rock?
- Hey!
- Fighting!
- Go
Fire!
24 hours after
the exchange fire
- What time is it?
- It's the 24th hour, sir
Not 25th
No---
I meant what time is it?
They're good chasers
- I think I'm go to throw up
- Hey, which Arirang is that?
Isn't that 'Seopyunjae'?
I said which Arirang stupid
- This is scary shit
- You want to switch?
- Sir, I think I'm cramping up
- Me too
Keep stretching
Hey, Mr. which version
of Arirang is that?
Hey, Mr!
Which Arirang is it?
come on teach me
To hell with that
I'm going fucking insane
Isn't this a gunshot wound?
Yes
I need to report to the police
I did already
I was at the US Army protest
rally and somehow got shot our---
- I didn't see it coming at all
- What? The Army base?
They just shot me out of nowhere
- And couldn't avoid the shot
- How dare they---
Fucking head!
Let's go We need to take
care of the wound first
But uhhh---
By any chance---
Are you in the National
Collegiate Protesters' Union?
I sure am
I'm a NCPU member
Nice meeting you
I was the fourth year
member of the NCPU
I haven't felt such urging
patriotism in quite some time
If we break up, then we'll
come back to open it
What if we never break up?
- Will you leave it here?
- You don't like the idea?
Well--- I'll be all curious---
- about what's inside
- Oh yeah?
If you're that curious,
- Just break up with me
- What? Are you crazy?
I'm pissed
I even put in
a year's worth of
- salary for when we're old
- A year's worth?
Why would you do that?
What if somebody digs it up?
- Really?
- Don't worry
They will have developed a
time machine in the future
So we can come back
How awesome?
A forty year anniversary gift!
Honey---
Honey
I'm not wearing any underwear
Come get me bad boy!
What?
You naughty you---
Come get me
Stop right there honey
You beautiful little creature
Gotch'ya!
No No Off of me
Leave me alone---
Oh my---
Are you okay?
On the first day of his visit,
the emperor has ended his
day's chores and is now resting
at the Shilla hotel The cops
have placed SWAT teams
all around the hotel
Tomorrow morning, the emperor
will meet with President for
breakfast and in the afternoon
They plan on attending Korea &
Japan joint cultural ceremony
Chairman Kim Jong-il from the
North will also be there
What a bunch of crocker shit
Korea & Japan joint world cup?
I'll prepare a fucking joint
funeral ceremony
I thought you were gone,
but guess you're alive
- I tried my best
- Your best?
Guess you could say that
You must've tried
your best to miss
a guy that was practically
in your face
Hanako--- you've changed
What are you doing?
What's wrong? What?
Why would you drink
the last remaining PPX?
This is PPX?
You should've told me
I give up
I want to go
Where's your partner?
How would I know?
You should know fuckhead
I really don't know, sir
I didn't do it
It was him!
Did you see that?
It's him right there
Which dentist do
you guys go to?
Sergeant Yoo's dentist
He said I can get
50%discount
Oh yeah?
I got it done for free
- For free?
- Yes
I'm sorry
I just had to go
Don't worry
What are friends for?
And---
Why don't you go stay
in Hawaii when you're done?
I'll lend you the money
Hidden Cam-shot on
Fangbo and Sang-mi
Don't take this the wrong way
I didn't take this to watch
you fuck or anything
You've grown
Well---I was always a little
bit taller than you, wasn't I?
Do you have a death wish?
Regardless,
you should forget---
about this and forget Sang-mi
Understand?
You're losing it, aren't you?
It's me Fangbo from the
KP's class of 17
Fangbo Yoo
It's me Fangbo Yoo
I'm Fangbo Yoo
I'll make it simple
It's okay to make it
complicated
If you're go to be
so stubborn,
I'm go to go sell
this shit to porn dealers
What do you want, money?
How much do you want?
Is one good?
You're go to have to
give at least two
Two!
Okay!
You don't have
any copies of it, do you?
Who are we brother?
We're all mighty KP
Korea Police
Plus, I need to go visit
my dad at the cemetery
Anyway,
just go to Hawaii,
Okay?
Okay
Sir, You can't leave
until you pay
- He's going to see his father
- Okay
Sir,
I'm going to Hawaii now
Hawaii--- Hawaii
How fucking awe some is that?
That's enough dog--- enough
Hey Gabdu!
Gabdu!
Come on--- man
Come on--- man---
open your eyes Gabdu!
Suction
Perform vital check and
prepare for massage
- All set?
- Yes
- Did the heart stop?
- What?
Isn't this one of those electric
shock thingies for heart failure?
No, it's not
It looks similar---
but it's different
This is just a spray
What are you doing?
Off of me!
I'm going to a local hospital
You can't get this type
of treatment at local hospitals
Don't give me attitude,
young lady
How dare do you look
at me like that ugly bitch!
- What?
- I'm sorry, I forgot
Jesus! You can't forget
things like that
Fucking
- Hey!
- Yes/- Come over here
- Give me your ticket
- Yes
What about me then?
You only cause
trouble anyway
Just stay outside and wait
Everybody listen to me
We're almost there now
Stay focused
- You hear me?
- Yes, sir
Hey, hey
Where are you going?
You have to come this way
LPG should go over there,
and Helium this way
Don't get all mixed up
Come on man
Where are you going?
Help out a bit more,
Okay?
I'll spot a seat for you
Stop making that face
One Two One Two
Three Three Three
The Red Devils over there---
Please scotch over
to the front
Ladies and gentlemen,
President Kim Dae-jung,
chairman Kim Jong-il,
and the emperor of Japan
Let's welcome them with
a round of applause
What are you doing?
The ceremony has started
Hold on a second
This is the staff waiting room
Murakami!
This is so pathetic
Where's the PPX?
Go find it yourself
Shut up and just cough it up
This is Murakami!
Murakami!
Next is to wish a
successful 2002 Worldcup---
and celebrate peace
between the two countries
Once the torch is lit,
ladies and gentlemen
please give a
round of applause
On a count of three,
leaders of the three countries
will rise and light up
the torch
Let's all get together
One
- Two
Three
What is this?
We apologize for the mistake
Next will be the youth choir
What's wrong with my voice?
Sir, you may step down
Everybody freeze
- What is this?
- Don't worry! It's okay!
One Two Three
One Two ---
Everybody on their heads
Do you know what this is?
This is liquid gas bomb
On your heads
You've all heard of PPX,
right?
This is what blew up
the entire Mia district
You hear me?
I said get on your
head right now!
The guy in the front row,
what are you doing?
The one on the thirteenth
seat down over there!
On your head!
I'll kill you all if you leave!
Sang-mi!
Put that down
Don't come near me
Drop your weapon
and on your head
It's me--- look
Don't you have a head?
On your head now
- But listen--- it's me Fangbo
- On your head!
Do it right!
Yeah--- you do that boy
You look like a girl
You pansy ass mother fucker
You did well Very good
We're going to write our
own history now/- Captain!
- What?
- You too on your head!
What?
You too on your head!
What's wrong with you?
Are you crazy?
Yeah---I'm crazy
I think I'm on your side
Just shut the fuck
up and do it
What?
You want to all of a sudden
sort out negative feelings?
You think playing
soccer together
will change anything?
What are you trying to make
up for the past ninety years?
I'm Japanese myself!
But, you Japs---
Comfort women,
History textbook,
Dok-do---
Well---if you think about it,
there's nothing you did right
What the fuck are
you clapping for?
You talk shit about Japan
all the time
But what about Japan imation,
fetish prostitution, etc
You're the first
ones to accept their culture!
Regardless---
You should really
think about what you did
Drop your weapons!
Wait!
Hey!
If you're go to kill those
people, kill me first
I won't miss on the second one
Get out of my way now!
Okay
If your job comes before
your love, pull the trigger
How do you know
I loved you for real?
I have faith in our love
Okay! No regrets
I'm go to fire
- One sec
- Shut up
One
Two
Three
Sang-mi!
Chairman Kim
When do you think we'll
be able to meet up again?
Pretty soon
Okay
Shit
Chairman
Do you believe that the talks
we shared---
were truly honest?
Yes
Do you swear on
our friendship?
Sure
Dear god,
we have sworn in front
of you our friendship
So please bless
both countries
and help us find peace within
And bless our
ever-lasting friendship
Amen
Mr. President
President Kim!
Just---
wanted to call you
one last time
Don't smile
Brother!