Wake up!
Let's go!
Who's that?
You bastard!
Don't you ever come out again!
Fighting with your wife again?
I didn't come home last night!
Then you asked for it!
Do you think I want this?
My girlfriend threatened to kill herself
if I didn't stay!
It was a matter of life and death!
What was I supposed to do?
What's a married man like you
doing with a girlfriend?
We Italians are a people of love.
We can't live without it.
All Chinese want to do is work.
You wouldn't understand.
We do understand.
We're just a bit more selective.
We have to go to work.
What are you going to do?
I can't go out! My wife will kill me!
Then move aside and let us go.
She'll kill you both too!
We'll leave from the balcony.
You have fun hiding here!
What about the Spaniard downstairs?
Don't worry. Watch me!
Hey, I'll go first!
Hello...
Are you all right?
Don't you Chinese know how to
use the stairs?
The Italian couple
is fighting on the stairway!
Come on.
Why did you signal me to jump?
I signaled you NOT to jump!
You should've said so!
I was about to...
What did you say?
but you already jumped!
To go to Via Laietana
What road must I take?
Via Laietana?
- Where is Via Laietana?
- What's Wrong?
As you go straight,
at the first intersection, turn right
After you arrive at Mallorca...
- After that?
- You will be lost
You've just passed Bilbao
Then what must I do?
If you turn left from Bilbao,
you'll see a fountain
Make sure the fountain works
If the fountain works?
Then Via Laietana will be in the
front of the left side
If the fountain doesn't work
If the city hall is closed, that
means there is road construction
Then you must take
a different road
I understand what you are saying,
Thank You
Hello
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry
I didn't mean to do that on
purpose, officer
Let me help you out, officer
- I'm really sorry
- I'm sorry, officer
Don't make me see you
washing a car here again!
Get Lost! Do you not hear
what I'm saying?
- We won't do it again
- Yes
We won't do it again
Hello?
- Did you wash chimneys?
- No sir
Then why is your face so dirty?
Damn Chinese!
Private Investigator Matt?
Freeze!
Boss!
What on earth are you doing?
Nothing... I was just exercising...
Why didn't you get the light fixed?
The light is fine.
It's the power that's been cut.
When the electric company owes you,
they take forever to pay you back.
But they sure are efficient,
when you owe them!
What about me... no pay for three months
and I still come to work everyday!
What are you trying to say?
If it weren't for me,
you wouldn't have a job at all!
Without a job,
what right do you have to stay in Spain?
That's true.
But if I had some money, I could
have paid the electric bill for you.
Now you're talking!
Anybody come for me?
Just some guys from the phone company.
What business do they have with me?
None.
They just came to take the phone away.
That explains why it's so quiet here.
Oh, a bald guy named Alfonso
also came looking for you.
Did he come alone?
No, he was with two huge muscle men.
What did he want?
He said you promised to settle
a gambling debt of 100,000
pesetas yesterday.
Right... That was our secret code.
That means he has a new lead on a case.
He asked when you'd be back.
The next time he comes,
tell him I'm out of town on business.
That's another coded message meaning...
You better tell him the coded
message yourself.
Why?
He said he'd be back at noon.
Which is about now.
What? Why didn't you tell me earlier!
What's the big deal?
Is that another coded message?
Exactly. It's practically
a matter of life and death!
Meaning I have to
find a place to hide now!
As of this minute,
you are the Acting Chairman
of this agency.
You are in charge when I'm not around.
That is a promotion, isn't it?
Then what about a raise...?
It's hopeless!
Acting Chairman... is still a Chairman.
Better put on a tie.
Please have a seat.
Before you ask me to take your case,
please listen to
my principles of business.
Murder and arson, I do not do.
Burglary and theft, I do not do,
because I don't have the guts to do.
Now you may tell me
what I can do for you.
I'd like for you to find someone for me.
Finding a missing person? I've never...
You have not done that before?
I've never failed in
locating a person before!
I didn't know you were...
Chinese?
That's right, descendant of the Dragon!
I won't take up too much of your time.
I want you to help me find a woman.
Named Gloria and her children.
A boy and a girl?
No. There's actually only one child.
Then is it a boy or a girl?
That you'll have to
find out for yourself.
Here's some information on Gloria.
The information is incomplete,
and the picture was taken 22 years ago.
That's a tough assignment.
I'd do it myself if it were easy.
Should you decide to take my case.
You must abide by two conditions.
I have a condition too.
But let's hear yours first.
First,
this case must be kept confidential.
Second, you must find this child
for me within 14 days.
Here is some money for your expenses.
You'll get US$20,000 more if you deliver.
Now you can tell me your condition.
My condition is
I accept all your conditions.
That's perfect.
You may reach me at this number.
Trying to test me?
What are you doing?
My liquid preserver is better than
any lamination.
Then I'll wait for your good news.
Let's get to work.
Here, go get us some business!
- Hey, Chinese boy, a Coke please.
- Okay.
- What would you like?
- Coffee with cream.
Coffee with cream, coming right up.
- Something to eat?
- No.
Something to eat, Boss?
A cup of 22, and a box of 16.
Right away.
Would you like something to drink, Picasso?
- Coca Cola.
Here are the orders.
Okay.
Beautiful day... Beautiful business.
Beautiful rice!
That's a bit too much.
Nunchukas!
Here's yours.
And yours.
Delivery.
- Lady Boss, this is yours.
- Thank you.
Hey, what's going on?
Look at all the dust and fumes!
We can't eat here! Let's go.
Hey! Hey!
How am I going to do business like this?
We were incredible!
Hey, can you guys go elsewhere?
What's it to you?
You're ruining my business!
Why don't you go elsewhere yourself, kiddo!
What? What are you going to do about it?
Let's have a race right in this square.
The loser picks up the tab for tonight.
Sure!
Good! I'll be the referee.
Ready. Go!
Move if you know what's good for you!
Faster... Faster!
Hey, where are all our customers?
All scared away by the Hell's Angels.
I'll ask them to leave.
Save your breath. I've already tried.
Pack up and move the car.
Why?
We're going to play Robin Hood!
Faster...
My mother told me not to fight.
Did your mother tell you not to
mess around here?
Yes, but it slipped my mind.
I'm going home right now.
I won't fight you two. I'm leaving.
Let's get back to work.
- Morning.
May I see your pass?
- Goodbye.
When will your father
be out of the hospital?
You think he has hemorrhoids?
He's mentally ill.
God knows when he'll be out.
Oh no! A flat tire!
Don't worry. We have a spare.
Who said I was worried?
I just said "Oh no!"
Then you shouldn't have said that!
What should I say then?
You should say, "Ha! Ha! A flat tire!"
What normal person would say that?
Ha! Ha! A flat tire!
You're right!
Normal person would not say that!
Let's change the tire.
Do you have a magnet?
No. What do you need a magnet for?
Then I can tie a string around it.
Why would you want to tie a string
around a magnet?
So I can lower
the magnet into the gutter.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
Then why would you want to lower
a magnet into the gutter?
To get the nuts back.
What do you need the nuts for?
You mean the nuts for that?
You are smart.
How do we get the nuts out?
Unless we have a magnet.
There you go.
Then we're stuck.
I didn't know people with no brains
can survive in this world!
And you have brains?
Yes, a little rusty maybe,
but better than yours.
So what!
You can take one nut out of each
Of the three remaining tires.
Then you'll have a total of three nuts.
Use the three nuts on the loose tire
and drive slowly back to town.
That's a great idea!
Hey, you're so smart, why are you here?
I'm here because I'm crazy!
Not because I'm dumb!
Dumb and crazy are two completely
different things!
Do you understand, dumb pigs?
I better not waste
my time with you anymore.
I'm going to play on another beach.
Come on, let's take care of this.
- What's he doing?
- Who knows!
- Ask him.
- I don't want to.
Don't worry, then I'll ask him.
What are you doing, pal?
I'm a clock. I'm ticking.
- Oh... What time is it then?
- 2:30
No. It's 2:45.
Oh no, I'm running slow!
Hey, what's your father doing?
He's fishing.
Dad, I've brought Thomas to visit you.
Sh... You're scaring my fish away!
How are you, Mr. Chan? Are you bored?
The whole world is boring.
Have you found
a girlfriend for David yet?
There are not too many Chinese girls in Spain.
Spanish girls are just the same.
Love transcends nationality.
Hey, your father has a complete
change of heart.
I'm a little worried about him.
Oh, isn't that funny?
Mr. Chan, what is he doing?
He's telling himself a joke.
And that's how it ended.
Isn't that funny?
Why he's not laughing now?
He's heard that joke many times.
- He thinks he's Columbus!
- Really?
Well? How are you?
Fishing? Catch one for me too!
I know I'm crazy. But you too?
How can I catch a fish from a bucket?
You father is definitely getting better.
The alarm!
It's time for my date.
I don't mind if you guys tag along.
Your father is in such a rush.
Who's he meeting?
I don't know.
That's why love transcends nationality.
No wonder the doctor said
he was getting better.
- Where's your mother?
- She's making herself up.
She doesn't want you to wait long.
So she sent me to let you know.
I don't mind waiting at all.
Tell her to take her time.
I know what you're thinking.
I know what you think I'm thinking.
But I'm definitely
not thinking that at all.
I'm not thinking you're thinking that.
I know you're thinking that because
I'm thinking that myself.
Since we're both thinking about that,
that means we agree.
That's right. That means we both
should not be doing that.
She's gorgeous!
She belongs to my father.
Stop thinking...
I've stopped thinking.
Mr. Chan, we'll be on our way.
I'll come visit again next week, Dad.
Not yet.
You haven't met my girlfriend yet.
That's all right.
Here she comes.
Gloria. You look exquisite today!
I've missed you so.
I know what you're thinking.
I know what you're thinking too.
- We're thinking about the same thing.
- What are we waiting for then?
I've got to run. Goodbye, Mom.
Goodbye, Mr. Chan.
- Tell your father we're leaving too.
- Okay.
- Dad, we're leaving.
- That's right, Mr. Chan.
Wait, I want you to meet Gloria.
This is my son, David,
and this is his good friend.
- Hello!
Now run along and leave us alone.
Come on.
She's waiting for a taxi.
That's our chance.
You go over there and tell her
we'll give her a ride.
She can save on taxi fare.
What if she insists on taking a taxi?
She won't say that!
You're so confident,
why don't you talk to her.
I'll go get the car.
I'm giving you a chance to try it out.
You go and I'll get the car. Go!
- Hello
Miss... the taxi is here.
Goodbye.
She turned you down?
No. I didn't ask.
You are so useless.
The result might have been the same.
Of course not!
Without asking, you had a zero chance.
Had you asked,
you would have had a 50% chance.
Elegant yet warm, she may be a princess.
A princess with a crazy mother?
Anything's possible.
That's true. Come on.
Two thousand pesetas?
Even your mother is worth more than that!
Don't be nasty.
I'm sure we can work this out.
How about four thousand pesetas?
Okay.
Thomas, two coffees please.
Isn't it a little early?
It won't take him that long.
While you're there, remember to get them
to settle their account.
Thomas, how much do I owe you?
Jennifer. 1,250 pesetas.
Here's 1,300.
Keep the 50 pesetas for your tips.
Thank you.
Can I take a spring roll? Thank you.
Thought she was so generous.
That spring roll costs 70 pesetas!
Are you new?
Miss, what's your price?
15,000 pesetas.
Wow, how about 3,000?
Save the money for your retirement.
3,000.
- 2,000.
- Get lost.
- Hello
Hey, I saw the princess.
Are you kidding?
She wouldn't come to a place like this.
I thought I might be mistaken.
Why don't you go see for yourself?
15,000.
15,000 pesetas? That's $100 U.S. dollars.
That's fair. Let's go.
She's really going with him!
Let her be. It's her business.
Don't get so worked up!
Oh, you two are interested?
You've treated me to many spring rolls.
Now it's my turn to repay you.
Thanks, but no thanks!
She was so elegant.
Turned out she's just the same...
Not the same. She's more expensive.
She's probably just short on cash.
Hey, how much do you have?
- Why?
- Hand it over.
I've about 20,000. Even spending
the night doesn't cost this much!
What are you talking about?
I was just going to give her the money
and tell her to go home.
So she's got a night off.
Then what about tomorrow?
Pal, there are so many hookers
on this street.
They each have their sad stories.
How can we help them all?
We can't even afford to give them each
a free spring roll!
Get to work!
You took my wallet?
Hey, stop! Stop...
A thief...
Did you see a girl running pass here?
What kind of girl?
She's tall with long hair and
is wearing a red dress.
You should always watch your wallet
in places like this.
What's wrong with you?
I have a headache. I think it was
from the heat this afternoon.
So what do you want to do?
I want to pack up and go home.
Let's take care of this last order
and we'll go.
Thomas, have you seen
a girl this tall and skinny?
- This tall and this skinny?
- That's right.
There are many over there.
Be serious.
No.
- Now what?
- We'll keep looking.
So Princess is not only a hooker.
She's also a pickpocket.
Maybe the guy just left his wallet
elsewhere and blamed it on her.
Don't accuse anybody unless you see it
with your own two eyes.
We're home now.
You think I don't know that?
I wasn't talking to you.
- Miss.
- Hello.
You sneaky rat.
No wonder you weren't feeling well.
I was afraid you would be upset with me.
Glad you're not.
I'm sorry it was so uncomfortable.
Let's get out.
Miss, I'm afraid we can't give you
a ride home.
Did I say I want to go home?
Then why don't you come up
for a little while?
Are you trying to signal me
not to invite her up?
No. I grabbed the wrong hand.
Our apartment is right upstairs.
It is our pleasure. Welcome!
Thanks.
Looks like Valentino is home tonight.
Hey, have you seen Fatso lately?
Haven't seen it in awhile
- Did someone die?
- No, why?
You look like you just came
back from a funeral
Hey, Grasshopper. Long time no see!
It's you, Moby! Have a drink.
I can't get drunk today.
Have you seen Fatso?
I just got here myself.
Is it something important?
You're very clever.
It is something important.
I'm now the Acting Chairman
of Matt's Detective Agency.
But keep this to yourself.
Of course! Who do you take me for?
Your punishment is
to have another drink!
I really can't get drunk today. So long.
Hello, Moby, it's been a long while.
Have a drink.
- Just one.
- Okay.
I'll have another.
Have you seen Fatso?
No. What do you want him for?
Can I trust you guys?
This is not the first day we met.
Just keep your secret to yourself.
We're keeping enough secrets already.
All right. Listen closely.
Promise you
won't tell anyone about this.
I'm now the Acting Chairman
of Matt's Detective Agency.
I need Fatso for some very
important information.
That calls for celebration. Drink!
Thank you.
Cheers.
Moby's been promoted.
I really can't get drunk today.
I have to go find Fatso.
Congratulations, Moby!
Cheers... Cheers... Cheers!
Keep my little secret to yourselves.
Don't tell anyone!
Goodbye.
Darling? This is Moby.
A kiss? Sure.
No. How could I forget you?
I've been very busy.
I swear that's the truth.
All right. All right.
Stop faking it.
She probably has a face of a pig.
Tonight? I really can't make it tonight.
All right. Another kiss?
Okay, a kiss. Listen up.
Was that loud enough for you?
Just hold on.
It's your wife.
Come in.
I'll kill you for fooling around.
Come out right now! Let me shoot you.
Susanna, let's talk about this.
I've nothing to say. The bastard
even has lipstick on his underwear!
Honey, I'm innocent.
Those were ladies panties, not mine!
Then what are you doing in them?
It was an honest mistake.
I'm going to kill him!
- That's our door!
- Get out of my way!
We will if you point
that rifle the other way.
Let go!
Why are you grabbing me?
Wow, bouncy! You're upset because
you're afraid of losing him.
If you kill him,
then there's really nothing left.
That was probably just a one-nighter.
He's still yours.
If you kill him,
you won't be able to find another man.
I know I still love him very much.
Then go talk him out of our apartment.
Dino... Dino...
Why don't you answer me?
Do you know how much I love you?
Me too.
Do you still remember when we first met?
- Yes. It was love at first sight.
- Really?
You're my whole life.
I'll have nothing if I don't have you!
Dino...
You bastard!
I'm going to kill you...
think you can run away? You pig!
Sorry to have imposed on you.
That's all right.
I have no plans to leave tonight.
What?
You don't like that?
Sure I do, if she's not afraid of us.
- What's there to be afraid of?
- That's right...
What's there to be afraid of?
Of your sleepwalking!
Fatso?
Fatso, what happened?
Have you been robbed?
Good thing I was late.
You're too heavy to move.
Hey, what really happened?
That's all right.
It's none of my business anyway.
Now I have some questions for you
that you must answer.
When you were the major pimp
on Sunset Boulevard 18 years ago,
did you know a Gloria?
She might have been pregnant
or just had a baby at the time.
What?
The guys who beat you up just now
came for Gloria too?
- Did you tell them?
- I didn't...
That's good.
I didn't want to,
but they beat me up real bad.
So you do know Gloria's whereabouts.
Not now... before.
Man, can you speak a little clearer?
Where did Gloria use to live?
62 Thanksgiving Street.
You're not worried about her itchy fingers?
Oh, we can just hide our money.
What if she really tries to steal
and can't find any money?
Then she'll know we've taken precautions,
and her feelings will be hurt.
That's true.
Then let's just keep a few bills
in our wallets.
If she did steal,
it would be a bargain price
to pay to get to know her.
That's a great idea, Four Eyes!
- Did you give her the shirt?
- Yes.
She looks better in it than you.
- Are you two talking about me?
- Pretty.
I heard more than just one word.
Pretty, pretty, pretty...
Have you decided
where I'm going to sleep?
- In...
- The living room.
Thanks. My name is Sylvia.
My name is David.
And I'm Thomas.
Good night.
I'm not sleepy yet. You guys go ahead.
I want to watch a little TV.
- I'll turn the TV on for you!
- Thank you.
I'm going to bed.
You'll sleep much better with this pillow.
Thanks.
Can I get you a glass of water?
Sure. Thanks.
It gets cold here in the mornings.
Here's a blanket for you.
- Thank you so much.
- It's my pleasure.
Water?
Let me pour you a glass of milk instead.
That sounds good too.
Thank you.
Let's not waste time.
Which one of you
wants to go first tonight?
It's all the same to me.
We'll sleep in our own beds!
- Good morning.
Was everything all right last night?
It was fine.
That's good.
Hey, have you seen my car?
No.
Susanna, my car has been stolen.
My car's been stolen.
I'm going to the cops now.
Princess left so early?
See? My money is still
lying safely in my wallet.
I was just being prudent.
You must have faith in this world.
My money's all gone!
I told you so.
Listen to the voice of experience.
I knew she had her eye on our money.
Your money in the drawer was like
a 24-hour ATM machine to her.
Shoes, on the other hand,
are a much smarter idea.
Damn! She took all my money too!
That's at least fair.
I told you not to
let her spend the night!
This is the first time
I've heard that from you.
She has guts! That's the end
of all our hard earned money.
Now that's an incorrect accusation.
She didn't take everything.
If only I could see her again!
I feel the same way.
What would you do?
I'd ask if she needed more money.
What's the matter with you?
Don't you know how to drive?
Do you have a license?
I'm sorry, Sir. It's my fault.
I'll pay for the damages.
That goes without saying!
Look at the dent!
It won't be the same again!
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me just this once.
You're lucky you ran
into a nice guy like me.
But it's very dangerous
to drive like that.
My brother always told me
to give up driving.
And now, another accident!
My brother's name is Dino Martini.
This is his car.
You give him a call
and he'll have your car fixed.
But...
I'm running late.
I've got to go to work.
Call me some time. We'll have lunch.
- All right. All right.
- Thanks.
Back up...
Go.
Bye!
Who's there?
What do you want?
We want you to come with us.
To the police station?
You're not cops and
I don't even know you.
Where do you want to take me?
Some place fun. Now cooperate.
And what if I don't?
If you don't cooperate,
we'll force you to cooperate.
Let me go! Let me go!!
Let me...
Come on! Go after the girl!
Let's split up and search.
Split up and look!
It's those guys
When will you deliver the items?
You don't trust me or what?
Why did you give someone else the job?
Who?
That's what I'm supposed to ask!
They were some dangerous guys
I never paid someone else to do the work
- Then why...
- Get your hands off that problem
Just make sure they don't kidnap Sylvia
First tell me who they are
I have to know who I'm dealing with
- If you don't tell me, forget it
- Hold it right there
Sorry for giving you a hard time
But I have no choice
The only thing I could do is
raise the price I'm giving you
I'm assuming you need more
time to think
Yes, three seconds
One, two, three.
I'll do it
- All right, may God be with you
- Thank you
- Hello
I wonder why Moby wants to meet us
at the disco.
I'm sure he's up to no good again.
When we see him,
just say no to everything he asks.
Have a seat.
- Can't say no to that!
- That's true.
What would you gentlemen like to drink?
Three beers and a bottle of XO.
How's the meals on wheels business?
No good, worse than our waitering days.
How's the catering van working out
after the conversion?
No good. It's even worse
than before it was converted.
Is Mr. Chan feeling better now?
No good. It's worse than before
he went into the hospital.
Really? He was already going after
people with knives!
Don't listen to him.
He's doing much better now.
That's good. Our drinks are here.
Come on.
Let's drink to Mr. Chan's health.
No. We don't want to.
Can't say no to that! Cheers!
This "just say no"
business isn't working.
Let's try another trick.
I need you guys to help me out.
A girl ran into me this morning.
Oh, the dog of the store
around the corner just had four puppies!
What do the puppies have to do
with my car accident?
Then what does your car accident
have to do with us?
Please hear me out.
After the accident,
the girl gave me a card.
Said the car belonged to her brother.
That still has nothing to do with us.
But when I found this guy,
he said he didn't even have a sister.
Plus, his car was just stolen.
Then I gave him
a description of the girl.
He said it sounded like the girl
you brought home last night.
Even if it were true,
it still has nothing to do with us.
That's right.
Oh, the girl gave me some money
to give to the both of you.
She's really returning the money?
Not returning. Just giving.
What do you mean give? She stole this
money from our apartment last night!
So you were her victims too.
And you still say it has nothing
to do with you?
Whatever you say.
Just hand over the money.
Wait. This isn't the money.
She still has the money.
I think I better get some exercise.
Me too.
Can you tell me where this girl
usually hangs out?
Her home.
Any place she goes everyday?
The ladies room.
Don't mess around. Tell me the truth.
The truth? The truth is we don't know!
All right. Forget it.
Come on. Please tell me!
I thought you just said forget it.
Please give me at
least something to go on.
We've already said we don't know.
Fine. Forget I even asked you!
I'm sorry I ever met you two!
I thought we were friends.
We are fellow Chinese.
And you won't even help me
with a small favor!
It's not like I'm the Red Cross
asking you for your blood!
I can hear me fine.
Why you can't?
What?
Even the worst Spaniards are better
than you!
What did you say? I can't hear
you over the loud speakers! Louder!
I SAID, SPANIARDS ARE THE WORST...
Sorry. My fault.
Okay. You got me again.
Who do you think Sylvia is?
She's a Spaniard.
Nonsense. I meant why is she wanted
by so many people?
Because she's beautiful.
Retard!
She's no retard! She's very bright!
I meant you!
- Sylvia.
- David.
Long time no see. How are you?
Long? It's been less than 24 hours!
They want to force me to do something
against my will!
Friend, you should be nice to ladies.
What to kick me? Try it now!
What's going on?
Ask them!
The girl picked my wallet.
These two are her accomplices.
Stop right there!
She fooled us again! Never believe
anything she says ever again!
You better remind yourself.
I never trusted her from the beginning.
Just look at the two of us now!
No need to overreact!
It's you.
It's you!
I came to thank you.
If it weren't for you,
I'd have had to spend the night in jail.
Don't thank us.
If we had known
why they were chasing you,
we wouldn't have helped at all.
Tell her not to go yet.
- I thought you said...
- Call her back.
Don't go yet!
We want to ask you something.
Would you mind coming up to
our apartment for a little while?
I was afraid you'd never ask!
You said you have something to ask her.
I've decided it's best that
you ask instead.
- Me?
- Go!
I would like to ask...
if you'd like something to drink.
Red wine please.
That's okay. I'll get the drink.
Cut to the chase!
Remember you spent the other night here?
The next morning, we found out that...
My shirt was still here.
And the blanket was neatly folded.
Money! Gone!
But we were missing... missing... you.
That you'd left.
Fine. You can take a break.
I'll do the asking.
What David meant to ask was the other
night when you spent the night,
did you steal our money?
- Yes.
The people that were chasing you.
Did you steal from them too?
Yes.
Don't be so rude!
Rude? You ask then.
But why?
You're so pretty.
You could have easily... easily...
What he meant was
with a body like yours,
you could have done quite well
even as a hooker.
I detest people calling me a hooker!
I use my brain, not my body!
My body is not for sale!
Miss, I'm only the interpreter.
You should have slapped him instead.
But it's still not
a good thing to steal.
My mother went into the asylum
when I was 14 years old.
I've had to support myself since.
No one has even given me a chance.
All the men I've met,
no matter what they said,
the bottom line was the same.
They wanted my body.
That's true.
Those were his first thoughts too.
To these men,
stealing their money was like
teaching them a lesson.
Remember this lesson
when you see the next pretty girl.
I told you not to get involved.
I didn't mean the two of you.
After tonight,
I know you're good men.
I'll try to get the money back to you
as soon as possible.
No hurry.
I just wanted to understand why.
When you can,
go ahead and pay him back first.
I'm not like him. He was saving the
money to get married in Hong Kong.
That's not true.
The money was for emergencies.
That means he doesn't need it.
Pay me first then.
Any which way.
Just so long as the money is legal.
Thomas and I were just saying.
Your mother
and my father are good friends.
We can't just
let you carry on like this.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
But he was afraid you're already
too far gone.
If given a choice,
who would not choose a normal life?
What if you were given a choice?
Then I would try to start over again.
That's good enough. Four Eyes, didn't
you always say you needed an extra hand?
No. I never said that!
Oh yes! But...
He doesn't know if you can stick it out.
How would you know if you don't
give me a chance?
All right.
You're on probation for three months.