Executive Producer: Raymond Chow
Producer: Leonard KC Ho
Writer, director and leading actor:
Jackie Chan
MIRACLES
The Hansen factory is looking
for young apprentices.
There are 250 vacancies right now.
The pay is $8 a month and you
are guaranteed a year's bonus.
It's just two dollars to register.
- A job in Hong Kong?
- But $2 he said.
You must be prepared
to work hard and long hours.
$2 dollars, that's too much.
No need to push.
There are 250 positions.
If you feel this is for you,
it's only $2 to register.
They also need a bright lad
to work as a cashier.
- Pay is $12 a month, any takers?
- I will.
Come this way.
- What are you good at?
- Kung fu and acrobatics.
- But can you use an abacus?
- No problem.
- Guarantor?
- What?
- Have you got any money?
- Yes.
- It's $30. What's your name?
- Kuo Chen Wah from Canton.
- Do I have to pay now?
- That's the deal.
Pay cash, you're in.
Still want it?
I only have $25.
Pay the rest later.
Report for duty tomorrow at this address.
Jobs galore!
Hurry, they're going fast.
You're really lucky.
Line up over here!
Only $2 registry fee!
What are you doing here?
This isn't Hansen's cloth factory.
Who took your $2?
The address is right,
but the Hansen factory doesn't exist.
It's not easy to make a living
in Hong Kong.
Leave now, you've all been conned.
Leave, or I'll call the police.
Robbery! Robbery! Robbery!
- What do we do now?
- Call it a $2 lesson.
We were lucky.
I saw some guy pay the man $30.
- That was very bad luck.
- More money than sense.
Hong Kong!
It's all arranged.
- Be careful.
- Sure.
Boss, you look bad.
Uncle Hai, I can't find his medicine.
You forgot the boss's medicine?
One of you must have it.
Imbecile!
Pretending he's boss.
They forgot your medicine.
We'll postpone the meeting.
- We mustn't show any weakness.
- It's not that...
If Tiger's reasonable,
don't be too harsh.
You're too kind-hearted
for this business.
In our business, it's them or us.
That's why I have
absolute faith in Fei.
He's vicious and cold-hearted.
Sunglasses.
- Late, as usual.
- I'm not late.
You were early.
What's wrong, old man?
You're ill again?
Cut the small talk.
Why did you call me here today?
Fine.
Remember Yang - your partner, Mr White?
Sure I do, but he's dead.
Yeah, but he and I made a deal.
The Ritz would be split down the middle.
He may have said so, but I never did.
Come on, calm down. You came to talk.
I'm here because as Mr White,
I won't be forced into bargaining
with you pack of liars!
You're calling me a liar?
That isn't nice. Open fire!
- Are you all right, boss?
- Get him out of here.
- Would you like to buy a rose, sir?
- No.
Don't refuse me
this early in the morning.
No, thank you.
Buying a rose from me
will bring you good luck.
- Your first time in Hong Kong?
- Yes.
Take care.
I learnt my lesson yesterday.
I'm afraid you didn't.
Look at your suitcase.
As I said, take care, sir.
Hey, wait a minute.
I will buy a rose after all.
- Let's hope your luck will change.
- I hope you're right.
Thanks!
Be careful.
Get lost!
What now?
- Don't move!
- I'm just trying to help.
Thanks very much, young man.
Don't move!
Run for it!
- Boss, are you OK?
- How did we get into this mess?
Young man, could you help carry him?
- Who are you?
- We'll pay you $100.
$100?
Over there!
- Where do I take him?
- Anywhere. Move!
Run!
- Where now?
- Ouch! That hurts.
Put me down.
You're hurting my stomach.
- Put him down first!
- OK.
- Boss, are you OK?
- You...
My...
This way.
How is your stomach?
Boss, how are you?
Tell me who is going
to take your place?
Let him have it.
- Let him have it?
- What's happening?
- Are you sure?
- I want him...
Boss! Boss! Boss! Boss!
You all heard Mr White.
We must obey his wishes.
But we must get out of here.
Let's go, boss.
From now on, you're our boss.
Me?
Being our boss, you don't have to
worry where you live or how you live.
You still don't understand.
Look, you get to have elegant clothes.
You're always fighting,
it's a dangerous job.
- I might as well do it.
- What?!
Don't worry.
Just do as I tell you, you'll be OK.
Why did the boss name this jerk?
You were his right hand man.
If I'm not the right man for the job,
we'd soon know about it.
If you're not up to it,
then who is?
Let's wait and see what happens.
Boss, any spare change?
Here, now scram.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
Keep an eye on things.
We'll go in the back way.
What if nothing happens?
Then fix the car.
Young man, a rose for luck?
Get lost.
I'll buy a rose from her.
Hey, lady!
I'll buy a rose from you.
It's your lucky day, sir.
- There.
- That's very kind. I thank you, sir.
Let's go, boss.
- Why isn't Fei our new boss?
- You really want him up there?
Who else? You?
Fei's the only man,
otherwise it could be any one of us.
Why not you?
We've got him outnumbered.
He doesn't stand a chance.
If he's got the guts to fight,
he can show us.
I can't go through with this.
Don't force me.
We won't force you.
You can take the back stairway out.
- Thanks.
- But you must be careful.
Why should I be careful?
If you leave now,
we can't protect you.
If Tiger catches you,
they'll make mincemeat of you.
But I helped your boss, remember?
I couldn't figure out why you helped.
It's odd he chose you,
but I must obey his instructions.
I'm cursed whichever way I turn.
No problem. I'll look out for you.
Now you even look like the boss.
Here's your speech.
Let's go.
We'll test him.
Don't be afraid.
Brothers, at the request of Mr White,
I'm here to introduce your new boss,
Kuo Chen Wah.
Uhh... good day to you, friends.
I would like to...
Can't you talk without reading?
I don't know how to be your boss.
In my opinion you shouldn't rob banks,
or do bad things
like racketeering, killing,
or breaking the law in any...
Our new boss
has got a great sense of humour.
Words are fine, but show us
what you're really made of.
- Show us what he's made of.
- Go on.
- All right?
- OK.
- Look out for him.
Go on, then.
Over here, over here!
Don't be shy.
Come on!
Fatty, you be referee.
Settle down.
Move out of the way.
Ready? One, two, three...
Who burnt me?
Don't make excuses.
Well done, boss.
I tell you, somebody burnt me.
Arm wrestling doesn't prove anything.
Otherwise Tom would've been
boss long ago.
In this business,
you must be able to fight.
You fight him them.
You're on your own now.
We'll show him.
Is two against one too much for you?
Let me go!
Help him up.
Boss.
- The boss is the winner!
- Well done!
The boss is the winner.
"The King George"
The letter?
- And the paper?
- Here. Write sparingly.
If the boss finds out, he'll fire me.
I won't waste it.
Here's a rose for luck.
'I was at Mr Chow's party today.
'He was asking after you.
'When I got back to the hotel,
I received your letter.
'I am so happy that your school
friend, lan is so good to you.
'I am very happy for you,
I think he must be very handsome.
'If you're not too busy, I hope we
can meet in Shanghai later this year.
'We're going to a function
at the Indian Consulate tonight.
'No doubt it will be chicken curry.
'I'm sending you some more money
this month.
'You're getting older now,
so you'll be needing a bit more.
'The weather's getting cold,
take care you don't kick off your covers.
'The chauffeur has just arrived.
I've got to go.
'Sorry to write so little, Mum.'
So we're making a loss and breaking even?
Something must be wrong.
You don't know what Yang is like.
He tricked him in a game of chance.
He lost all his shares in the Ritz.
So I juggled the figures a bit.
Do we have to get involved
in shady deals?
Boss, I'm just following orders.
The brothers won't object if they're fed.
Can you make this restaurant
more profitable?
I won't run a casino.
A whorehouse, then?
Uncle? Sorry, but there's a Miss Yang
here to see you.
Come in. This is Uncle Hai.
Good day, I'm Luming Yang.
My father used to own half this place.
I believe he died in Shanghai
three months ago.
Yes.
That's why I've come to discuss
the business side of things with you.
This is Mr Kuo Chen Wah.
He's our new boss here.
My father gambled his share
of the restaurant away.
He asked me to find a way to repay you.
It's nothing. Forget it.
Wait.
He meant at your own convenience.
I've got some money here.
Can I give you that for now?
Your father owed us thousands.
I could work for you without pay.
As what?
I sang and danced
at a club in Shanghai.
- Why did you leave?
- The club closed.
It wasn't my fault.
I was very good.
One minute. I'll sing for you.
Hong Kong by night, never sleeps
The Pearl of the Orient that we are
Listen to the symphony of waves
and tides
- It's not much.
- I got it. Build her up.
- We'll open a nightclub.
- Yeah, we'll do that.
- Up there.
- One, two, three...
Be careful, be careful.
What's the total?
If I knew how to add,
I would have joined the Navy.
You're crazy!
It's someone for you.
Mr Jang.
Mister.
You're decorating?
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
Be careful!
Why are you taking so long?
If I knew how to write,
I would have joined the airforce.
Are you ready?
Now look at the camera.
Ready.
- Let's go in.
- Welcome!
- Put it there.
- Your reservations, sir?
- Tiger Lo needs no reservations.
- This way, Tiger.
So kind of you to come, Mr Tiger.
You've got a nice place here.
Let me introduce you to our new boss,
Kuo Chen Wah.
Kuo Chen Wah. You're not White, then.
I thought White was your father.
Miss Luming, hurry up.
To what do we owe
the pleasure of this visit?
Relax, this is a social visit.
I see you've spared no expense.
I'm ready to forget Yang's debts.
Give me half of the Ritz.
I think...
- Are you the boss here?
- No, he is.
Then shut up. Well?
Yang's debts are not our business.
You can see
we've spent a lot on the decor.
We don't need outside investment.
Ladies and gentlemen,
there's a great surprise in store tonight.
Luming Yang of Shanghai,
star of Broadway.
I'm usually short-tempered,
but tonight...
Make way, make way!
- Get the lights on.
- Nobody move.
Stay in your seats. Stop the music.
- Spotlights off.
- Turn on the house lights.
The Chief Inspector Ho
of Hong Kong here.
Identity cards, ready, please.
- Mr Ho, you are disrupting the show.
- Inspector to you.
Inspector, we have a proper license.
And we have a proper search warrant.
I don't carry a card.
What are you saying?
No cards? Why?
- So what?
- Imprisonment, that's what.
How are you, sir?
- How's Mr Laughton, your boss?
- He's well, thank you.
You may leave.
These are all good people.
Have you made the check?
Inspector Ho,
you are disturbing our guests.
I will come here whenever I please.
Today, tomorrow, the next day.
- Are you the licensee?
- No, not me, him.
I'm Kou Chen Wah, the manager.
So you're the new boss?
It's our opening night.
Excuse us for any shortcoming.
Looks like a boss.
I won't disturb them,
but I would like a word with you.
No problem.
Of course.
Now what?
Stop searching.
Let's go.
Come upstairs.
Inspector Ho, please, sit down.
I didn't come here to sit down,
I came here because I saw something.
Saw something?
Something that doesn't belong here.
You must be mistaken,
everything here is bought and paid for.
- I mean you.
- Me? I don't belong here?
Yes, all the people downstairs
make a living through theft,
deceit and other foul means.
Don't argue with me.
I reckon...
amongst all these people...
the only person
who hasn't committed a crime yet...
I want to save you
from this den of iniquity.
- I want to do you a good turn.
- A good turn?
Yes, from now on...
if you can inform me
of Yang and Tiger's activities,
then I will put them behind bars.
Then you and I...
will create the biggest story
to come out of Hong Kong in its history.
I must wipe them out.
I hope you aren't one of them.
But I have been thinking of a gradual...
Don't reply now.
Think it over and give me a call.
I don't usually trust people,
but in your case...
Boss, some tea for Inspector Ho.
No need,
we won't be bothering you any further.
- What was that...?
- Sorry, I forgot my hat.
Continue.
- What did he say?
- He told me to behave.
He wouldn't say that.
He must think you are the only
innocent person here.
Did he ask you to do the right thing?
- No.
- Of course he did.
He must have asked you to rat on us
and do Hong Kong a great service.
He must have said
he didn't trust anyone
and you shouldn't miss the boat.
So you know what he told me?
Not just me. Everyone knows.
Even the door man.
Back to base!
Sorry about the interruption.
Continue the music.
Let's give Luming a big hand.
Ask your boss to have a drink.
This is all water under the bridge.
We don't want to start a war.
Very few people
are as peace-loving as you.
If I was boss, I'd prefer peace too.
Kuo is too young
and Hai is too sneaky.
- Pass on the message.
- If that's all, I'll leave.
All debts are paid.
Here are the IOU's.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Tong's still out buying roses.
- What for? It's not a proposal.
Chen Wah.
What is it?
- Have you thought about the future?
- I have thought about it.
Everybody's waiting.
Wait till I come back.
Wait three years anyway.
Hey!
Three years!
Don't you know the Black Tiger gang
had 7 bosses in three years?
I can't find Madam Kao.
Can't you go without roses?
- That's not the point.
- Fine, get started. Get in.
I wish you good luck.
Thank you, miss.
- Isn't it beautiful?
- Lovely.
You people cover the back alley.
- Rush in when I throw the cup.
- OK.
Wait a minute.
Tidy up.
Kid, you do have it.
Sit down, please.
Quick, stay alert.
Don't nag me again.
Now you're here,
some good will come of this.
Sign here, and you go home safely.
With not a hair missing.
Half of the Ritz?
Whatever has happened
between us in the past,
sign here and we'll be brothers.
Understand?
Yes, but...
Are you qualified to sign?
If not, shut up.
- I'll sign.
- Now you are talking.
With one more clause...
we get half your income from
the casinos then - unconditionally.
Repeat what you said, young man?
Say that again.
Go on.
You take half the Ritz,
we're entitled to half your assets.
Don't move!
Fools! Ten Shantung men
can't beat two Cantonese?
Useless morons!
What are you doing with your guns?
Put the guns away, you idiots!
Young man, if you've got the balls,
come outside with me.
If you're going to hit me, kill me.
You old rotten egg!
Boss is in trouble.
You're good, young one.
- Pick him up.
- Move it.
Let's go.
Don't push. I'll go myself.
- Go, quick.
- Hurry up.
Give me half the Ritz
and I'll set them free.
Let's go.
Police.
Finished fighting? Seems we're late.
What did you say, Inspector Ho?
Mr Tiger, was there
fighting going on here?
I don't understand your dialect.
Speak Cantonese.
Cantonese?
It seems there was a fight here.
I'm sure you weren't involved.
A fight? I didn't see anything.
- Nothing?
- No.
You saw nothing.
Are you under duress?
We were having tea and a chat.
Well, our tea and chats are over.
See you some other day.
Any time.
Tell me he threatened you
and I'll have him arrested.
Inspector Ho, I don't understand.
You're refusing to cooperate,
next time I may be too late.
Now I understand. Goodbye.
That's it, then. Let's go.
They were fighting.
Do you believe he was having tea?
I'm not blind.
Mission over.
Dismissed.
The Inspector saved the day,
not the rose.
I won't go anywhere without a rose.
Superstition.
Uncle, do we need to repair the car?
Yes, you and the car.
An overhaul is expensive.
I suspect Fei is behind
the whole thing.
You suspect him?
He's an old-timer and knows the ropes well,
yet he failed miserably.
So you question Fei's loyalty?
In our business,
there's one thing we can't forget...
trust no-one.
I don't like it.
You don't have much choice.
- Do you want this?
- No.
- Where are you going?
- To the States.
Without consulting me?
You never gave me a chance to talk.
You only have time for fights
and business.
You take a holiday. It's OK.
I'm not coming back.
What? Why?
- I want to get married.
- I told you, it's impossible.
With whom?
With Mr Lu.
His parents in the States are dying
for him to get married.
You think nobody wants me.
Don't try to stop me.
You can't leave!
- Why can't I go?
- You can't. Listen to me.
- You are rotten!
- Help me, please.
It's none of my business. Carry on.
If you leave what will happen to us?
All you care about is business.
You never have time for me.
Who do you think I am?
The piggy bank?
I never treated you like that.
Hey, help me out here.
What can I do?
- How do we treat her?
- As the piggy bank, of course.
He said it. Don't deny it again.
He's lying. Don't believe him.
Right, I lied.
What lies should I tell now?
Lies? You fool!
Lady, you know well how I treat you.
How do you treat me?
You know.
I don't know. You usually mumble,
I don't know what you're saying.
You're driving me crazy.
Lady, lady...
Lady, are you really going
to drop everything and leave?
It's now or never. Should I wait
till you are riddled with holes?
Fiddlesticks!
Did I say something wrong?
I just heard wrong.
It's none of my business.
None of your business?
All you do is drink. She's leaving.
That is my business. Stop her.
Lady, please, give me two more years.
You think I'd trust you?!
- I really mean it.
- You really mean it?
Let go of me!
Lady, lady, please, stay.
You lied to me.
No, I didn't.
I paid you back money
which my father didn't even owe you!
I worked hard for you. What have you
got to say for yourself?
I told him not to cheat you.
I've never objected.
He said the same thing.
At first, I didn't know you well.
Later, I didn't know how to begin.
The money is intact.
I'll pay you back.
So you cheated because he said so.
I didn't know you then.
Now you know how to shift blame.
Shut up, you!
Forget it. I don't want the money.
I'm going.
- Lady, listen to me.
- Let go of me.
Listen to me.
Boss.
Mr Lu wants to know
when we are leaving.
None of your business.
No, I've come to report
the engine's dead.
Tell him to go away.
How can they leave?
Yeah, how can they leave,
do I have to push them?
Tell Mr Lu to leave.
Tell him to leave, OK.
You depend on others for decisions.
Only when they are right.
- Lady.
- Let me go.
Lady, you can't go!
Don't go.
Give me a reason to stay.
A reason? What reason?
We don't act on reason.
You drink too much.
Are you all right? I'm really sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Boss, Mr Lu insists
on seeing Luming first.
- What then?
- Gun him down.
Shoot him dead.
- Let me get up.
- Please don't leave.
You can't trap her like a thief.
Kiss her, then she'll stay.
- Kiss her?
- And you refuse to listen.
I do, I do.
He'll leave now.
I'll go and clean the car.
Don't touch me.
Lady, I am sorry.
Baggage in hand? Going on holiday?
I tried to send your letter,
but I was caught and sacked.
- Where's the letter?
- The manager took it.
- Mr Manager.
- Manager, she wants to see you.
Yes?
You have a Shanghai letter
addressed to Mrs Kao, it's mine.
Yours?
But you don't live here.
How come there's a letter for you?
I used your headed note paper.
- Kick her out.
- Mr Manager, Mr Manager...
I'm in dire need of the letter.
Please give it to me.
I was wrong to use your letterhead.
I won't do it again.
Please, give me my letter.
Stop it. Is there a letter for her?
There was but I returned it.
No, that letter was non-returnable.
He's taking it to the post.
- Madam!
- My letter, my letter!
Go back to work.
Nothing. Sorry for the disturbance.
Thank you.
- Leave now.
- Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You've fixed everything.
I'm going to have some tea downstairs.
Let's shake hands and be friends.
I don't know
if he will accept your offer.
I don't think he's a bad person.
You think you know best.
We have a proverb, even pigs can fly.
So where are you from?
Me?
The most honest of Cantonese people.
Remember, morning tea.
I'd better be going.
Cantonese, Shandong people,
they're all the same.
I'll say it once more for you.
Chicken George used to work on the docks.
I know. He has hundreds
of dockers working on the harbour.
He is very powerful.
When you see him,
don't be too humble.
I know, the dockers are always
delivering goods to Wan Chai.
What are you up to? More business?
You know the Black Dragons have
invited me to dinner, I have to go.
When he's talking to me,
can you not look at him, please?
Boss, I got it.
I bought the chrysanthemum.
- A chrysanthemum? Are you new?
- Chrysanths' are flowers too.
You fool, go out and clean the car.
A flower is a flower.
Hurry up. Time's short.
No flowers. They're waiting.
Don't be so superstitious.
Let's go.
No, no rose, no meeting.
I know you're looking at him.
I'm glad you have your own ideas.
Boss, we can't find Madam Kao.
- I was told she's sick at home.
- Sick?
Mr Wah, this way please.
Mr Wah.
This way.
OK, the flower's here. We must go.
I've come to buy a flower.
Are you all right?
Take your medicine.
- Has she got a temperature?
- No, she feels cold.
It's not the flu. This is no use.
Give the boss a flower.
He needs it for luck.
Have you ever thought of giving
others some luck? You're inhuman.
Get a doctor here fast.
Boss, doctors are useless.
She's heartbroken.
Tell me who did it and he's dead.
Tell me and I'll cut him to pieces.
Tell me, I'll see if I can help.
Who is this?
That's her daughter.
I don't believe it.
She's so beautiful.
Sorry, I didn't mean it.
Forget about it.
Stop crying.
- I know. Her daughter's dead.
- Shut up.
Go and clean the car.
Hey, it's time now, we must go.
How can we leave?
The dockers may be offended.
- Let me buy the flowers first.
- Then buy them...
Mr Kuo, this is for you -
to bring you and everyone luck.
I hope you are all lucky.
You should be glad
you have such a pretty daughter.
Where is she?
Any way we can help?
Her daughter is studying in Shanghai.
She's coming back to see her mother.
Wonderful.
Does she have money for the ticket?
I'll buy it for you.
She's coming with her boyfriend
and his father
to discuss details of their marriage.
Madam Kao never let her know
about the flowers.
She left to study at a young age.
She was told not to worry about money
because her mother
is well known in Hong Kong.
She said she lived at King's.
Now if the daughter knows the truth,
she'll be very disappointed...
and if the father and son know,
there would be no marriage.
Tell me what I can do.
Only you can help.
You are the only one.
You are obliged to help her
as her rose brought you good luck.
How can I help her?
Easy, send her to King's
and give her a makeover.
Easy to say. That takes money.
We've raised some money for her.
Here's it is.
Do you think it's enough?
It's OK. There's no need for that.
I'll do whatever you say.
I have to leave.
- No need to worry, you have me.
- I don't know how to thank you.
You sort it out.
- Why bother with this?
- It's easy. I'm glad to help.
- This way.
- Miss Yang, everything's set.
Take care of Madam Kao.
So beautiful.
- Bring the things in.
- Yes.
Miss Yang, is everything OK?
Say yes if anyone asks
if Madam Kao lives here.
But say you don't know
if they ask about her.
Madam, welcome to your new home.
Chen Wah, over here.
- Beautiful, isn't it?
- Very.
Money buys everything.
I really don't know how to thank you
for all this wonderful help.
- Mr Kuo loves to help people, right?
- Yes.
Miss Yang, all your people are here.
Come in.
Please.
Who are they?
This is the beautician, the tailor,
the hairdresser. All for you.
Afternoon tea is ready.
- Who's he?
- The butler.
The butler?
Mr Kuo, this way.
Madam Kao deserves a butler.
- Uncle, we're leaving.
- Thank you.
- You've everything under control?
- Absolutely.
- What?
- We need a husband.
- What husband?
- She said she had one.
- What should we do?
- Find her one.
Me, find her a husband?
Where will I get one of them?
Don't ask me.
Children mean a husband.
A husband?
Don't get me involved.
Miss, where will I find one?
Miss, I have the perfect candidate.
- Who?
- A friend of mine.
Is he suitable?
Never mind that, get him here fast.
Then you stay.
I'll play any part for money.
Follow me.
I'd sign anything to live here.
Mr Kuo, this is my friend, Mr Tong.
From now on, he's your boss.
Kuo Chen Wah, Mr Kuo.
Haven't we met before?
No.
Go over and greet Mr Kuo.
- Mr Kuo, how do you do?
- How do you do?
- I did meet you some time ago.
- Impossible.
Thank you. Gentlemen, Madam Kao.
She's your wife.
Don't be nervous. Relax.
Mr Kuo.
When are you going to introduce me?
Miss Yang,
this is the husband, Mr Tong.
You? Come here,
let's see you together. Not bad.
I just need clothes.
Have you finished yet?
- Luming, all done. Can I go?
- You may.
- We're leaving.
- Go home first.
You can't go just yet.
What? Is there anything else?
- We're meeting the ship tomorrow.
- I don't need to be there.
See this thing through.
- Right.
- OK, you can go now.
- Let's talk it over.
- Tea over there.
Why are you staring?
It's only Madam Kao.
I remember who he is.
I know who you are.
Let bygones be bygones.
I am the husband now.
- What is it now?
- Nothing.
What's the matter?
Nothing, I saved him once.
Let's have some tea.
The ship's docked, boss.
Hurry up.
We're all up front.
- What will Belle say?
- She will be delighted.
- I owe it all to you.
- It was nothing.
She's docking.
She's arrived.
Have you got it?
"Welcome, Mr Wong"
- Why is it so small?
- I was late back.
- Should have used a business card!
- Why are you late?
There's a bigger sign over there!
- There's someone else meeting Wong.
- If you can so can they.
Madam Kao is well known.
We can't let them meet her
or we'll be finished.
- What now?
- We mustn't let them meet.
- Tell them to leave.
He bumped into me!
Remember, he's my teacher's
old friend, so behave yourself.
I couldn't get rid of them.
It's Inspector Ho.
You sort it out.
- Inspector you must listen.
- What is it?
Do you want to know
what Tiger is up to?
- What?
- Not here.
- In the station.
- I've come to meet the ship.
My information will be useless later.
Then tell me now.
I told you, not here.
Whisper it in my ear, then.
Forget about it.
- All fixed?
- Yes, taken care of.
- You two, follow me.
- OK.
Robbery!
He touched me up.
Don't get involved.
Hold up the banner.
Nobody's molesting you.
Hey, what a coincidence!
- How's the kid?
- Fine. What brings you here?
I'm looking for a fight.
- Where is Ma's money?
- I sent it.
You have?
Stop fighting!
Hit him!
Hit him! Hit him!
Go over there and kill him.
It's none of our business.
Hold the banner. Higher.
- Is Chief Inspector Ho here?
- That's me.
So it's you. You piece of shit!
- Why are you two up to?
- We're meeting the ship.
Not any more. After him!
Don't let him get away!
- Can you see her?
- No.
Do you recognise her?
There are so many people.
- Do you recognise her?
- I only saw her photo. I don't know.
- Can you see her?
- No.
Can you see her?
Belle.
- Belle!
- Mum! Mum!
That's Belle, my daughter, up there.
I see my mother. She's down there.
OK, OK, let's go.
- Which one is she?
- I'm not sure.
My dear daughter, she's back.
- Where is she?
- I'm not sure.
- Which one is she?
- I don't know.
Can you see?
I heard Mr Wong is very rich.
Take plenty of photos.
- What's that about?
- I'm not sure.
- Boss, boss.
- Let him go. What's the matter?
Two reporters have come
to interview Wong.
Reporters?
- Tie them up.
- OK.
That's against the law.
- We're detectives.
- What are you doing here?
We're reporters.
We've come to interview Mr Wong.
- We'd like a word.
- But the passengers are coming.
- We're not asking.
- Come or take a voluntary holiday.
- Let's go!
- What are you doing?
Do I look all right?
You look fine.
Mum!
Belle!
Look, you did a good thing there.
This is just the beginning.
This is your stepfather.
- Introduce us to your friends.
- Right.
This is Mr Wong Hsin-chuan.
- Mr Wong, we've heard about you.
- This is my son.
How are you?
Thank you for looking after Belle.
It's she who looks after me.
It's too noisy here.
Let's go back to the hotel.
And this is?
- This is her cousin.
- Right, right.
- An Uncle on my mother's side.
- Uncle.
- This is my wife.
- Auntie.
Mummy, you never mentioned
this cousin before.
He was the black sheep in the family.
Marriage changed all that.
Mr Wong, Mr Wong,
let's go back to the hotel.
I'm meeting other friends here.
I've told everyone
to go to the hotel.
Let's go.
- Uncle?!
- Why weren't you introduced?
I'll start the car.
If you don't get a pay rise,
it could mean exploitation.
Exploitation makes you feel worthless
and that can lead to suicide.
Suicide means you're gone.
What do you think so far?
The missing reporters
are valuable employees.
I am your boss Laughton's old friend.
Stupid conjecture may lead
to your job disappearing!
I'm sorry, I just wanted to get
some background information on them.
Trying to put pressure on me.
I've a job to do.
Divide this.
- Miss Yang.