Very pretty
Everybody!
I'm sorry to you. It'll OK soon
Sorry... sorry
Granny, you can't light it up in this way
You've just got the oil,
but you haven't got a lampwick
I know that
But I've lost the lampwick.
I can do nothing about it
Buy a new one
It's reasonable...
Miss, excuse me
if it is the lamp of Buddha
where to buy a new lampwick for it?
Show your real image!
The Four Kings from the Nantian Gate
and Erland God
Zixia. Your sister Zixia and you
is the lampwick
inside the lamp of Buddha
You left Heaven without permission
You told the public that
the one who can pull your Magic Sword
out
is your best love
You're an immortal.
You can't love any ordinary man
If a devil pulls your sword out
we'll become the laughing-stocks
No matter who he is,
an immortal or a devil
the sword can only be pulled out
by me and my lover
I will stand by him forever
If I can't be with the one who I love
I won't be happy
even if I were Heaven Emperor
How dare you are
You're this stubborn
I'm gonna kill you
You're gonna vanish
That's fine.
I don't wanna be a lonely immortal
Look out!
No need to say anything
I'll kill whoever speaks it out
I've said it's not permitted to speak it out
I wanna tell you
Your beloved dog is doing that
with a bitch
How dare it is!
Ok, I'll kill it. Let's eat it
Ok...
We've decided to do so for a long time
Jing Jing
Jing Jing, where are they?
Immortals?
Devils
Thank you
Please go into the Spider Web Cave
Spider Web Cave?
Don't cheat me! It is the Waterfall Cave
Spider Web Cave, what a nice name
Just call it Spider Web Cave
I live at here
Hold it
Listen to me
all things here belong to me!
Including you!
Me?
Yes
just like a donkey,
let me make a mark on you
You're my guy now
Don't scare of anyone.
Just tell them you know me
I'm called Spider Web Immortal now
Spider Web Immortal?
500 years ago?
You haven’t turned back into
the Monkey King because
you haven't met the guy who'll give you
the 3 birthmarks
Open the door
Close the door
I can't believe it...
I don't wanna be the Monkey King
I have to save Jing Jing
Give me back the Box
Open the door
I have heard that she said "open the door"
How dare you are?
Let's go there through another way
Be careful
That way
Open the door
Who?
Is it necessary?
It's great!
We needn't scare of Qingxia
since we've got the box
Come out! Are you really this shy?
this Box is... It's me!
I've said that all things here are mine
What do you want?
Nothing...
I've heard that you wanna go
Can you bring me with you?
Are you also chased after by someone?
I'm going to save someone
Save whom?
Save my wife
It's Pak Jing Jing. You know her
I don't know her
I know that. But you'll know her soon
Because she'll be your disciple.
And this Box...
It's mine!
I know that
But in fact, I gave you this
Then, you gave me back at that time
So I come back and
give it back to you again now
Do you understand?
Yes, you're crazy Yes
And you have to bring me with you
Why need I do so good to you?
This is because you're my master
It's meaningless if you leave me here
Really?
Sit down
Ground
Give me your hand
I'll buy new clothes
for you later
Bark!
Wow!
Louder!
Wow...
Immortal...
Be quick, the moon has come out
Go!
Where to go?
Are you leaving?
If you aren't, give me the Box.
I'm leaving
What Box?
Listen to me
I won't wait until tomorrow
Be quick, shut up
Then your bitch sister will come here
Shit, how dare you tell the others that
I do bad to her
What?
I'm that bitch's sister
Don't listen to her nonsense words
Joker
Why didn't tell me to wake up last night?
What?
Where have you been? Stand still
Sit down
Chair
What about you?
Why are you looking at me in this way?
What did you see?
Did you see her?
Did you see my sister?
She's come
What did she tell you?
don't trust her, she's crazy!
Maybe she had a fierce fight with me
in our past lives
So Buddha
turned us into a lampwick
told us to practice more
Solve our disputes
But we couldn't do that
We are still fighting with each other
don't say that anymore
Let's go
Do you think that I'm crazy?
No. That's really my sister
Don't you believe me?
Come on, come on
Let's tie our hand up
You will know that tonight
I don't think the moon will come out
tonight
Really?
Bitch
You can't escape from me
What's your name?
My surname is Lin?
You're Lin Qingxia.
My brother talks about you usually
Your brother?
The guy who you beat up is called Joker
How about you?
I'm his twin brother Broker
Joker? Broker? You tell lies
You're so smart
My brother is called Qin Han.
I'm called Qin Xiang Lin
What are you doing?
I admire you
You admire me?
Not only admire, I don't want to lose you
So I tie myself with you.
Please accept my love
Let's go together
You have to pay something for my love
You hate your sister so much
I've lied to her that
I would kill you tonight
Then you have nothing to worry
So I have to take a thing as a sign
Do you have valuable thing such as...
jewels or Pandora's Box...
ok, but they are useless
Give her my Magic Sword tonight
She'll believe it
Fine
It's him
Bring me to the market
since it's not dark yet
What?
What's up?
My heart is pounding
What to do?
Follow me
Now Big Brother has turned back into
human face
and he's with Zixia Immortal
Did Zixia has a part in
the capture of Master?
We should keep it secret
My martial arts skills and IQ
is better than him
But there is Zixia Immortal now
She's better than me, I think
I'm here
She's better than me because
I've got a burden, it's you
Give me half of this pig head, thanks
I don't sell pig head.
Do you like pig penis?
What?
My lover is nearby
Did you see him?
No
because my Magic Sword is beeping
Where does the beeping sound
come from?
Do... do... do... right?
you made this, not the sword
I know you didn't hear that.
So I made it for you
I'm scared!
I'm really scared!
What?
It's fate. So don't be afraid
Come again?
My heart is pounding
My heart is beeping
What?
How should I tell him?
Just tell him
it is fate
If he doesn't like me, what to do?
If he has wife, what should I do?
It's fate. It's God's order.
He has to accept this
Really?
It's fate! He has to accept this
Yes! Yes...
He's come
It's me?
It's you. How do you know? It's you
I didn't know
how to tell you
You're so smart
But I have a wife
I know, but I can do nothing about it
This is fate. You have to accept this
You just need to leave your wife
And then follow me
That's great!
Fine?
That's fine
Let's start our affair
Ok, let's start
Kiss me first
Fine, come to me
Come!
Give me!
You deceive me
You don't wanna kiss me
You deceived me! You lied to me!
I'm serious. Give me the Box first
Should I show you my heart?
No, I do this
Wow! Your heart looks like a coconut
Miss, I'm ugly
But I'm a gentleman
Tell me honestly
does she love his wife?
I'll kill the one who're gonna block
my way
Granpa Buddha, look
Look!
He doesn't move
I know that
Let's go
Brother, what is this mean?
I know you've got good figure,
so I touch you
Yes, please go on
That's fine. Touch me again
Whose hand is it?
What are you talking about?
Take away
Devil
Have you finished?
Don't get angry, I just do that for fun
Take care of sister
She will give you back
Sister, I won't angry at you
We should regard you as Goddess and
worship you
It's dark. I will go to find sister
Good luck
It's really lucky
Qingxia
Where are you?
Come out
I've killed your sister
Monkey King
You bastard
You wanted to marry
the King Bull's sister
But you regarded the Longevity Monk
as a wedding gift
And you invited all devils to eat his flesh
Do you admit your guilt?
Bitch!
She's chased me for 3 whole days
I didn't beat you up
because you're a woman
Don't think I'm scared of you
Monkey King
Don't say that to Goddess
Shut up!
You scare me again!
Monkey King, Longevity Monk?
Do you know you've committed offences
You've grabbed Zixia Immortal's
Pandora's Box
You don't want to see me
Now, I can't escape
I'm gonna fight against you!
What's up?
Monkey King, you're so naughty
I've told you don't throw things
It's wrong to throw things
I haven't finished yet.
You've thrown away the stick
The Box is a treasure
You'll pollute the environment!
What to do if kids are hurt?
It's still bad
if you hurt plants
What are you doing?
Let go!
What do you want?
Tell me if you like it
I will give you that if you like it
Of course, I will give you if you like it
I won't give you if you don't like it
I'm pretty sure that I won't give you
if you don't like it
We're reasonable
I'll count to 3
Tell me if you want it!
Monkey King
You know him now
This guy is very annoying
Very disturbing
Just like a fly
Sorry, not a fly
but a swarm of flies
Fly into your ears
Help...
Help!
So I tear the fly's belly open.
Tear out its intestines
Put them around its neck, and then pull them
Then its tongue comes out
and I use my blade to cut!
The world's silent then
We all know this now
why I kill it
Really?
So many excuses
You don't want to get scriptures
I won't forgive you
because you're so cruel to your master
Sister
you're wrong
The Monkey King wanted to eat me
It's just a thought
Not a fact
You haven't got any evidence
He's not guilty!
Just wait, when he's eaten me up
you can prove him guilty
Longevity Monk, I know you're annoying
But I don't know you're this annoying
I gave you the Gold Ring to control
this monkey
But you don't use the ring
The size of that ring doesn't suit him
He can't wear it
It makes him very uneasy
He can't sleep at night. It disturbed me, too
Although it is just a monkey
you cannot do that do it
I'll be indicted animal abused
if the government knows it
That Gold Ring...
I met iron-smith last year
at the Chan's village
His skill is wonderful and the price is low
Really fair price
I think
you should buy a new one from him
Shut up!
It's a sin...
Now, I think you know my pain!
Answer me!
It's Ok!
I've told you not to throw things
Look!
Monkey devil, go to hell
You can't defeat me!
You're not Buddha
No more fighting...
Goddess
Please let the Monkey King go,
don't hurt him
No more fighting
I'm gonna kill him!
Goddess, stop!
It's normal to make mistakes
He's my disciple
I have to take the responsibility
Goddess, please let him go
If I won't kill him
I can't report to Heaven Emperor
I know that
Please tell Heaven Emperor that
I'm gonna sacrifice my life to him
What?
It is a master's responsibility
Goddess, please listen to me
I just wanna teach him...
in order to show my spirit
That's great...
Monkey King, I hope you'll learn
your master's spirit!
Namonitabhaya
Dreaming again?
It's big trouble.
I always have nightmares
Where is Qingxia?
Not here
Qingxia...
Everybody, how are you?
It's cold!
Have you worn more clothes
I've lost my way
I wanna find a place to stay at night
Go there to sleep
Thank you very much.
Wish you all long live
I saw him come here
Where is he now?
Why did you go to pee?
You have to take the blame
It won't hurt you
Is it illegal?
Old Black Mountain Devil?
Monkey King
You turn into human face again
Do you still recognize me?
You are the fly
Monkey King...
Impossible, I must be dreaming
It is still early to make dreams, but...
I dream of you
when I was travel through time and space
Do you miss me?
The Box is at your side?
Yes, it is. Do you want it?
Who?
What's up?
Soldier
My dad also wanna stay here
No problem
It's your dad!
Yes, dad, come out to say hello to all bros
Where does he come from?
From India
India? Where is it?
I need to carry on tomorrow. Sleep there
Thanks
It's really noisy
Annoying
Sleep inside
It is the problem of time difference
I have just slept in India.
Now you tell me to sleep again
You go to sleep
Where is the Pandora's Box?
Monkey King, can you behave yourself?
Look, just keep calm
What is he doing?
He's breathing in life
Pretend to sleep.
I hope that he won't breath in ours
Go to sleep!
Do you know me?
That Indian...
You like it, take it
My disciple is calling me, bye bye
Don't play with fire again
bye
Please don't follow us. I don't know you
It's great to see you
Where is the Box? The Box?
The King Bull?
Bro. catch the Longevity Monk
and give him to me
Miss, handkerchief
It's wedding day, why are you weeping?
I'm not weeping. My mouth is watering
It's a very happy day
What?
It's not only the wedding day of my sister
but also the day of my marriage
with my concubine
Concubine?
What does sister-in-law say about this?
That bitch
She's now at the Flame Mountain
She can do nothing about this even if
she knows it
Bull, how did you know
this new wife?
I passed the desert yesterday
I saw a pretty girl
She's dying
Master, what to do now?
Fine! No problem...
Really? We succeed now!
Zixia, what a nice name you've got
Let me introduce my sister and
my brother-in-law to you
Xiang Xiang, Bro
Come here, follow me
This my brother-in-law
This is my sister Xiang Xiang
Zixia!
How can you get marry here?
I can!
How about your wife?
My wife? Do you know her?
You've got a wife?
We're divorced
I haven't heard you say that before
Sister...
It's normal that a man has many wives.
Take it easy
Bro, do you think so?
Yes...
Zixia, be honest
I think I've fallen for you
after these two days
I wanna show my sincerity
Thus I'm gonna request you to marry me
in front of my bros
This Pandora's Box
is my gift to you
I hope you'll marry me
I object this marriage!
Why?
Let me speak...
What a good couple they are!
You're a devil,
you're not qualified to object
You have to pass Zixia's test first
If you can pass it
I won't object it anymore
What test?
She has sworn that
she would marry the guy
who could pull out
her Magic Sword
Listen to me
It's untrue
It's just a joke
What joke?
It's not important
who can pull out the sword
Stop nagging in my place!
I'm gonna kill the ones
who block my way
King, Iron Fan Princess has come
Why are you here?
At this time, the sword is close to me
0.01cm I think
But after 0.01 seconds
the owner of the sword will fall for me
This is because I've decided to tell lies
Although I have told many lies before
this is the best, I think
You're gonna kill me
if you step forward again
You should do that
I deserve to die
I have had my best love before
but I didn't treasure her
When I lose her
I fell regretful
It is the most painful matter in this world
Just cut my throat!
No hesitation
If God can give me
another chance
I will say 3 words to her
I love you
If you have to give a time limit to
this love
I hope it is 10 thousand year
But how will you tell your wife?
I have to tell her
So I must get the Box back
Tell her clearly and go back with you
I won't listen to the others opinions
I won't listen to the others
objections
I will take all those on my own
Don't lie to me!
But I hate myself
because I can't get back the Box
I
I'll help you
No! it's dangerous
You don't want
I want
I won't hide a woman
It's just rumor
I won't trust you anymore...
What are you doing here?
Who's he?
I'm asking you, who's he?
He
Bro, who's he? Tell me
He's my wife
Bro, it's too much of you
Bros
You marry your sister to him!
So his wife pointed a sword at him
You follow me,
I have something to ask you
You've got a wife
I've lost my feeling to her
Tell me what's going on
I've told you... Sister-in-law
Sister-in-law?
Sorry, Madam Bull
When you watched the moon with me
in the past
you called me Sweetie
Now you yet your new lover!
Call me Madam Bull?
Sweetie?
Do you think that I come here for
that ugly Bull?
I come here for you, heartless monkey
Bro, thank you
It's none of business
Sorry
wait for me here at midnight
I have something to tell you
If I were you
I'll die when my husband decides to get
a concubine
Really?
Yes! But I'll castrate you first
Follow me
Zixia, I...
I trust you
I'll get the Box today
Wait for me here at midnight
Bro...
Let me go to see my bros first
See you tonight
Damn monkey, it's midnight now.
Where is he?
Big Brother!
I've told you that
Big Brother won't do so to us
He'll come to save Master
Gout at night, wanna pee?
No need to praise me
I'm just better than you a little bit
Stop nagging, go to save Master
I can't take this anymore
I'm sure that Master is inside
Right...
He's very annoying.
I can't take this anymore
You go in, I stay back...
Go! You at the middle
This way... Master is here, go in
Master
Master, master
We come to bring you out
I won't go
Really? Why? No
There're full of obstacles in the way of
getting scriptures
This is because we're not united enough
so the devils can do bad to us
Ok, now it is the case
Staying in this prison or not is
just the same
The outside world
is just a larger prison to me
You go out first,
I have something to talk to Big Brother
Master
Piggy, you're naughty again
No, Master
I go out and protect you
Sandy, follow me. Yes
You stand aside
Blow up and blow up the ball
You've dropped your thing
Bro, keep it
Why should I keep it?
Because I'm stronger than you
Stronger than your shit!
Come in and have a sit
Honestly, I'm not your bro
I don't want to be your disciple
Master, be kind to me
Please let go of me, alright?
Do you know what "Dong, Dong..."is?
What "Dong, Dong, Dong"?
Only you...
can take me to get scriptures in the west
Only you... can kill the devils
Only you... can protect me
No need to eat by the monster
Only you are that strong
Only you...
don't blame the master so talkative
Wear the ring back
Don't scare the death
Don't scare the shit
Do your best, if you scare,
I'll be with you...
Namonitabhaya
I can't take this anymore!
Oh your shit! Stop it!
I've said I can't take this anymore
But you still sing
You disregard my feelings
I'll kill you if you sing again
Monkey King, you kill you again
Life and death are minor
You'll sing this song with me
when you know making sacrifices is
so meaningful
Namonitabhaya....
Zixia
Bro, why are you taking a woman
with you?
Master has gone
He said we had to wait for him
at the forest 300 miles away
Go there quickly, please
Hold it!
What?
Ambush at the front
I can see it, no need to listen
Stupid
Hold you
Xiang Xiang!
Why are you here?
Wow! Why is there so much blood
on your hand?
This is the blood
of the woman you're holding
Her blood?
Yes! It's hers
I stabbed her
when she's sleeping
If this woman is still alive
you won't come back to me
You have to let it be
It is fate
Bullshit!
If it is fate that you love Piggy
will you love him?
If this is God's order
I have to accept it
Great!
You don't have to wait for God's order
Wow! What are you going to do?
Go, go...
Changing Image Magic!
I will turn you into a rock
Let go of me!
Grab your breasts!
Zixia...!
Wake up
Big Bro, why are you embracing me?
Piggy?
Yes!
Where is Zixia?
Qin Xianglin...
Qingxia?
Wow! Please don't play joke!
I'm also hurt!
My chest muscles nearly touch
my stomach
Do you hate me?
No!
You hate me!
Fine! End now!
Stop! Give me some time
I just vomit. I'll vomit all things out soon
Fine! I trust you
Give you some time
Try to get used to it now
I'm used to it already
Fine, I'm OK
I wanna vomit!
You're so disgusting!
If you're not, he won't vomit
Please be good to me
I will marry him
I'll give him a warm family
Give birth to many kids
Xianglin
I will kill you!
Kill you
Bro, you're also hurt?
Turn me back!
Shut up!
Listen to me!
Change me back!
I also want to do so!
I've used my power once.
I need 49 days to recover
49 days! I...
Xianglin, face the reality!
Use your energy!
Use your energy! Stop playing!
Be quick!
Who is inside you?
I don't know where I am
Two voices?
Who are you?
I'm Piggy. Who are you?
I'm Zixia
Xianglin
Joker
Bro
Zixia
Ziaxia, you're still here
You bitch!
I find you at last
What are you doing?
Long time no see, and you become this
Where's the Pandora's Box?
I didn't take it
Kidding
Give me
Wait
What will you do to the Box?
Go with me!
Fat woman! Don't hang around with me
Xianglin will go away with you...
The King Bull
Don't dream
you ask him if you don't believe it
You said you love me
because you wanna take this and
go away with her?
Wait...
It's not true
Don't want you to throw it away
Great!
You should not do that
Look at you
Don't deny it!
I'll throw that away!
Bro...
What a man!
Shut up!
I love that!
You can't leave anymore
Bull, you're seriously hurt
Do you think that bitch hurt lesser?
Have a look!
You've deceived me so long
In fact, I'm not
Xianglin, who's that woman?
I won't listen to you!
Bastard! I'll leave you
You affairs are none of my business
You get yours! And I get mine!
Help Zixia, you have a part in the body
Beat it up, make it hurt! Then you can
do nothing about it even if you
Yes!
Wanna go?
Explain it clearly or you can't leave!
Don't hit him!
Bitch
Bitch, stand aside,
it's none of your business
Stop it!
I'm afraid that she'll hurt my body
I won't help you
Shut up!
I'll help her and beat you up
Have a try!
I'm a woman. Please don't hit her strongly.
I'll kill you
I won't give help.
I just wanna see your fight!
Go!
No
I'll take the Box for you
And you can explain to your wife
Wow, you're great! Perfect!
Really?
You're as perfect as possible
Wait!
You!
Bitch, don't hit my girl
I like to do it
Your man has gone
How cool he is!
I'm a lucky woman!
Ok, I can play jumping down
from the cliff
Go nearer
Monkey King
Don't jump!
I don't want to do so
You prefer jumping down to seeing me
Ok,
I'd better go back to the Flam Mountain
I won't do this case
if I know this before
I don't know stealing grapes will
make me suffer such punishment
If I know that, I won't be a robber
Yes, sure
Like me, being a soldier
you have no chance yet
unless immortal comes to save you
I won't be a soldier
Immortal has come
Immortal!
Jing Jing
Granpa Buddha
He steams buns
None of your business!
Jing Jing!
Don't flirt with me!
I flirt with you because I love you
Listen, if you want to be my wife
don't do bad anymore in the future
Sure!
Let's go
Drink tea
Thank you!
You're welcome
Why bring me back to this cave?
I didn't bring you back
It's you who brought us back
It may be because I miss Jing Jing
very much
Yes! When you fainted
you spoke out the name Jing Jing
98 times!
Jing Jing is my wife
and a name Zixia
You repeated 784 times
784 times
She must have owed you lots of money
I want Spider Web Cave Immortal to be
my master
She's changed Waterfall Cave into
Spider Web Cave
You tell me there's no such person!
We don't know
Son of a bitch, you're still here!
Why did you do that to me?
Jing Jing
Jing Jing, it's nice to see you
What?
You've got thinner
I'm not the Monkey King
But I don't how to tell you
because you won't believe in it
I will
Because that damn monkey won't be
so gentle to me
Who are you?
I'll be your husband 500 years later
500 years later
you will give up this affair because of me
What I did is totally
just for you
Jing Jing, I miss you
I miss you much and much
I miss you much and much and much
Don't you trust me?
No!
I can't blame you
Let me see what's going on
But I think I know you
Absolutely
Very and absolutely
Very and absolutely and extremely!
How will we meet 500 years later?
At a pitch-dark night
I'm Joker, you're Pak Jing Jing
Fantastic love
starts from a fire at the bridge
When I turn back,
you point at me with your finger
then my hand gets burning
you rush to me and hit me!
Hit and hit and hit!
No...
look at me...
yes, can you see it!
there are many
twists and turns
Suddenly, the King Bull comes to us
I fight with him with a bone
He grabbed me to the Spider Web Cave
It's right that time flies
The following is the main content
On the cliff, we reach the climax
At that time, I touch you
You touch me too
We make promise that we won't separate
But happiness is always a flash of time
We only have endless pain!
Why will you die?
So I use the Box to travel back
to the past
I discover that you kill yourself
At the last moment
I save your life!
But at the last time of time travel
the Box doesn't work properly.
I go back to 500 years ago
That is the story
What are you gonna do now?
I've found you, I needn't go back now
Let's get married!
I ... I just wake up
I have nothing to do
So I come here. I wanna be a disciple
You request marriage suddenly
I... haven't brushed my teeth!
I know you're suspecting...
If I can give you my heart
you'll know I'm not cheating you
it's very simple!
You look like a thing
Coconut?
A girl said that to me
Oh, coconut
are his words all true?
No need to think!
You search the bottom!
Coconut, thank you very much
Please tell you, am I his best love?
You've come back for a long time
You just wanna get the Pandora's Box
What do you mean?
I'm asking you when we will get marry
But you keep saying no
Will you marry me?
I do!
Is your sister crazy?
She keeps speaking nonsense all day long
She's not crazy.
She's something wrong with the brain
If she promises...
she has promised to marry him
7 days later
you have made up your mind?
I cheated him
I'm waiting for my man to pick me up!
You think that bastard will come to
pick you up?
Congratulations!
But even if he comes back
he can't get you back
from the King Bull
It is fate that he can pull out
my Magic Sword
He must be an unordinary man
I'm sure
I know he'll come back one day
appear in public
wearing golden armor
and stepping on colorful cloud,
come to marry me
You are crazy!
I'm not crazy! This is just my hope
Promise me! Little psycho
No!
Bro, things are always unpredictable
I can't think you'll get marry with
Miss Pak so soon
Yes, me too
We're happy for you!
Thank you!
You made dreams last night
You repeated the name Zixia 785 times
One time more than last night
6 days have passed.
You'll get marry tomorrow
He will come? I don't think so
Yesterday, I told a spider to tell you
Told you I missed you much
Do you know?
You don't know again
I am cheating you
That's fine!
Just like a moth
it flies to fire even it knows it'll get hurt
Moth is so silly!
Come out, grapes
I don't want to watch you
I just want to study
the interesting relationship among humans
Bro, you're a robber
Don't pretend to be a scholar
Even a robber has its own knowledge
Stop it, go to sleep
In your mind,
is Zixia an exclamation mark?
Or she's a full stop?
Is your mind full of question marks?
Zixia is just a girl who I know
I lied to her in the past
I'm just feeling a little bit regretful
I hate him
I'll get marry today. What do you want?
When you discover that
you've fallen in love with a man you hate
this affair is really hurting you
But how can I fall in love
with a person I hate?
Please give me a reason. Please!
We don't need any reason to love a person
Don't we?
Do we?
Let me study it for you
Why are you so serious? Need we?
Who?
Time's up
How many brothers and sisters
do you have?
Are you parents alive?
Speak up!
I just wanna make a new friend
when I'm going to die
How to save Master?
Being a devil is the same as
being a human
We should be kind
If we are kind
we are not devils, we are a hybrid
He understands?
do you understand?
No one will come to pick you up
Your letter
Thank you
Your conscience told me that
I'm not your best love
Your best love is another woman
When I saw the thing left by her
in your heart
I know that you came back not for me
but for her
This is God's order
It is also called fate
Jing Jing's gone
I know
I've read the letter
Granpa Buddha
What's going on with her?
Have you read this letter?
No
You read it
Good
Wanna go?
I know my sister Pak Jing Jing
has been here
Where is she now?
Speak up!
Does she owe you this much?
You don't let your sister go
Just tell me
I don't know
it is heard that you're kind
They are your friends?
No!
Do you know?
Kill me if you must kill someone
They don't know your sister
All of them are innocent
I agree!
I admire bold people very much
If you're one of them
I can fulfill your desire!
Wait!
I really think that
you aren't scared of death!
I'm gonna die. Please do me a favor
I've heard that if you cut fast and
accurately
the man got hurt won't die at once
when he's cut open
He can still see
Help me, do it as fast as you can
Tear out my heart
Let you see it clearly
What are you talking about?
A friend of mind
left something in my heart
I want to know what that is
It's strange
Humans and devils are born
by their mothers
Different person acts as a different mom
A devil's mom is a devil's mom
I can take this
What's your name of your mom?
Kowtow to Heaven and Earth
Let's marry
Wait!
Look!
Now, she is the younger sister and
she'll save her elder sister
The elder sister
will save the younger sister
What do you want?
We're married today. Let my sister go
I won't break my promise
I don't want to fight anymore
You go!
I just have one sister in my life
Sister
King Bull!
I won't let my sister marry you
Sister
What are you talking about?
I just have one sister in my whole life
Come on!
I'm right
Faster than me
you're so great
It's time
Changing image
Xiang Xiang?
I'm not your sister
Xiang Xiang, what are you doing?
Brother
Brother, my Changing Image Magic...
Xiang Xiang
Turn me into a dog
Who are you?
I'm Qingxia!
Sister...
I will kill you
Go to save Master!
Don't hit my sister!
Come to save us
Kill that girl!
No!
It's you!... Go away!
I'll kill the one who block my way
Goddess
I'm about to understand your words
I use my eyes to see
When I'm dying
I use my heart to see this world
and all things
I see it clearly
That girl...
left a drop of tear in my heart
I felt
her sorrow
Have you given up
all things in human world?
Yes
Life and death
is minor
Great, great
Congratulations
Bro, what's up?
Come on, have a sit
Have a sit
It's unlucky that 3 friends of mine were
get involved
It's none of their business!
But I don't understand
How can human hatred last 10 years,
50 years
and even 500 years?
What hatred is it?
So the Longevity Monk went to the west
and got scriptures
which clean our heart
Understand
I wanna stay. There are
many things waiting for me to do
You go to have your next lives
as soon as possible!
Good!
You're slashed because of me
I hope I can pay you back in my next life
Pay back more
I can do what I can do, grapes
Goodbye
We're leaving
I wanna warn you again
After wearing the Gold Ring
you're no longer a normal human
You can't touch human desires anymore
If you do so
the Gold Ring will get smaller and smaller
It's very uncomfortable
Ok!
Before wearing this Ring
what do you wanna say?
I had my best love
But I don't treasure her
When I lost her, I felt regretful
It is the most painful thing in this world
If God can give me
another chance
I will say "I love you" to her!
If there is a time limit
I hope... it is 10 thousand years
Kowtow
Kowtow to the forefather,
drink wedding wine
Now you're a member of the Bull Family
Colorful clouds...
Look like marshmallow
Really?
Be careful!
Thundering
It's raining, get the clothes
Damn monkey, you flirt with my life
Although we are friends
I'll indict you slander if you repeat again
Kill him
Sorry!
This sneeze may make you disappointed
Joker
Are you satisfied this time?
Master
It's the Monkey King
I just thought it's a piece of cloud
Master, I committed many offences
in the past
It's lucky that Goddess show a right road
to me
Now I'm gonna worship Buddha
whole-heartedly
I won't feel reluctant to give up
human desires
Master
I will take the responsibility
Great
You're now on the right road
Joker
Joker, you're here eventually
Miss!
I... know a friend called Joker
He ask me to tell Zixia Immortal
something
Is it you?
Joker
Stop!
I'm asking you, is it you?
Is it you?
Speak up
Yes
He said he had went back to the
starting point
And he hoped that
she would find her best love
as soon as possible
Don't kid me, Joker
Let me tell you again
I'm the Monkey... King
Don't make any mistake
I'm gonna kill you today
Change!
Beat you to death, damn monkey
Look out my fork
I like barbecued chicken wing!
Use my fork to make
barbecued chicken wing?
I nearly forget it
I'm a vegetarian
Give me back!
Is it funny! Tell me!
Tell me...
Why are you so quiet?
Help me
Sorry
I don't want you lose face in front of
your bros
Let me help you
Give back to you
Great! Look out
Super bugs
I'm scared, so many bugs
It's lucky that I have many little monkeys
Kill all the monkeys
Let him kill
Are you the Monkey King?
Will you go to the west to get scriptures?
bring me with you
Yes!
She can act as a whore
if she goes with me
That's great...
I can't take this anymore
Come here, hold me tight!
You can't take me anymore
I can
I can't take you anymore
You're so ugly, we're immortals
please no more sexual harassment
Why did you do that to me?
Are you angry?
I would get angry!
Cry if you want
I'll kill you all bastards
Magic Fan
Help me
So troublesome!
Master!
Monkey King, help me!
I can't believe that you do that to me
You two protect Master
I know
Zixia, no
What are you doing?
Will you come?
Why are you so concerned about me?
Let me die
I'm not concerned about out.
We'll treasure our lives
You are no immortals
Monkey King, you can't defeat me
What a wide ditch
It's coming!
Stop kidding
Put the whole city to the side of the sun
Whom can you save now?
Don't bother me, you go to hell
Wait!
Lie to me again?
Damn monkey,
how dare you stop my attack!
Go!
Go back!
Shit, burning
Stupid!
Bitch! What do you want?
you're stupid!
You're not human
Don't get mad
Do you understand what I've told you?
Do you know I'm not an immortal now?
I only understand one thing
Love means pain
Don't bullshit with me
You've mistaken me!
Where did you buy these gold rings?
Be careful!
Zixia
Master, look out!
My lover is a hero
One day he'll come with a cloud,
come to me and marry me
I've guessed the start
But I haven't guessed the ending
Master...
I want your life!
It's very hot! You'll be a roast pig
It'll explode
We have to get the help of Pandora's Box
Go
The sun is coming, hurry up
Bring Master go
Hurry up!
Qingxia
My sister is not here
I think I should go back
to be Buddha's lampwick again
Goodbye
Big Brother, you get up so early!
What's happened?
Big Brother, you've forgot it
I met a storm last night
You brought me here!
Go!
Master, where are we going now?
India
Why does Master speak in this way?
Master is a clear cut guy. Let's go
Master, walk slowly please
Bro, be careful!
Thanks!
It is said that this was the Waterfall Cave
500 years ago
It's the living place of the Monkey King
Since he's killed the King Bull
and saved the Longevity Monk
there are no devils in the world
After that, many people came here,
fooling around
That guy put on a pig head
and say that he's Piggy
Bro
There is only make-upon your face
Please be more professional
Look at your hair
There are two cakes on your head
You should pay more money to make
yourself up
What's up?
Your image is really disgusting
Don't angry at me,
I'm always an honest guy
I won't get angry
Cut me if you like
You son of bitch!
Do you think I daren't do so?
Thanks
This is really sage
Big Bro
Bro, let's go
Buddha Cave
Fine, thanks
Thanks...
Big Bro, what are you looking at?
Both girls who know Piggy
Who?
Beancurd Beauty
It is heard that
they sell beancurds
They have earned much money
for their husbands to attend
the civil service exam
The Highest Graduate
Mei!
Congratulations!
You husband has become
the Highest Graduates of the exam
Go to welcome him
Honey
Honey Honey
Go away, no one of your business
Honey, Ah
You work so hard making beancurds
You work so hard making beancurd
Honey
I know how to make beancurds, too
Go!
Blow the ball
I blow the ball up
Blow the ball up and up
Come here!
It's crowded!
Monkey King
Master
Have a look
Ok!
They've stood there for 3 days
They didn't
Look, devil
I think I shouldn't come
It's too late
Leave some memories, Ok?
I don't need memory
I want you
You can just get my body
instead of my spirit
I've got a lover already
We won't have good result
Let go of me
I'll let you go
But you have to kiss me
before you've left
Have a kiss...
Kiss...
I'm just a powerless warrior
If kiss you
my image will be ruined
You're lying
You daren't kiss me
Because you still love me
I'm telling you
If you reject me
you'll regret for your whole life
I won't kiss you even if I regret
It's fate
I will stay here for my whole life
I love you
What's up?
That guy looks strange
I know
He looks like a dog!