Have a chat each other.
Don't get into fight.
Hale, barbecue again?
Join me for barbecue.
No, I already had a date.
Do come with your friends.
The ribs are pretty good.
Maybe next time.
Hello... Who's calling?
He's not available at the moment.
Hale, gimme a call at once.
Laurie, come on. We back home.
You brought him together during the rides?
Yeah.
Let me carry him.
Thanks.
Two hundred and sixty-two.
No tickets. Less the rent and fuel,
I earn two hundred and sixty-two.
Pretty good. Let's go.
You're awake?
I'm hungry.
I cook for you
Here comes the meal.
It's hot. Be careful.
I got you a night-shift driver.
Go to bed.
What's your name?
Hale.
What should I call you?
Whatever you like.
How about Hale?
I'm old enough to be your dad,
still call me Hale?
Uncle Beard?
What if I don't have beard?
What'll you call me?
Lucky.
What? Lucky?
Lucky is a puppy's name.
Go to bed, good boy.
How about your mum?
No idea. Maybe she's on a trip.
Do you miss your daddy?
Yeah, I miss him so much.
Why does the TV work again?
Lucky got it repaired.
Who's Lucky?
That is Hale.
He also did the curtain, right?
Don't know.
The mirror isn't clear.
Do you get the right spectacles?
Sorry, I got the wrong pair.
Can he manage? I'm worried about him.
It's difficult to find such a reliable driver.
He hands you the minibus on time
and refill the fuel.
Ma'am...
Don't think I'm an idiot.
I raise four children
with the minibus service.
They all got a university degree.
It's boring to stay at home all the time.
So I just wanna kill time.
Hand over at 3 p.m.
He'll park the vehicle outside your home.
Thank you, Uncle Chiu.
OK. Bye.
I go to work now.
Hale, do me a favour to raise my son too.
Iced lemon tea. Got it.
You help her only. It isn't fair to me.
Hale dress up and got shaved.
You're gonna get her soon.
Still pretend to be cool?
Shut up.
Hale, let's place a bet for 3T together.
He has given up on gambling
for a long time.
Besides, he needs to saves money.
That's it.
The economy is halted.
Always got a free gift whatever you buy.
A widow with a son as a gift.
No need to pay for the napkins.
Yeah
What're you talking about?
Just kidding. What's wrong?
You wanna make troubles?
Hale...
You think you're still well-off?
Still got vehicles for lease?
That's not the case!
Look at you! What did you say?
Relax. Just minor business, right?
Don't fight over this.
Get on board...
Go. Set off!
The tyres have worn out.
Two seats left. Get on.
Come on!
You steal my passengers!
Another ride.
The tyres have worn out.
Have you called the tow service?
It's expensive.
Please help me change it.
Can't make it.
Why?
Trust me. Replace the tyres in the garage.
Please hurry up.
Watch out and go back to the pavement.
Ma'am, this doesn't work.
Take it to the garage.
Hello?
Hello. Has your vehicle been on tow?
Yeah, thanks.
Where're you?
At the terminal.
Can you pick Laurie up?
I can't make it on time.
Yeah, I'll go now.
Bye.
Sorry. Ladies and gentlemen,
please get on the next ride.
Sorry...
What's the matter?
Hale...
See you tomorrow.
See you.
Sir, you're...
Are you Miss Cheung?
I'm... a friend of his family.
I'll help take him home.
Laurie, who's he?
Lucky.
I'm a friend of his mom's.
But it used to be his dad
who took him home.
My dad died.
Are you crazy?
Sir...
Please tell his family.
They haven't paid the tuition fees
for two months.
Have you taken Laurie home?
Not yet. I want to take him out.
Don't you have to work?
I want to take a rest.
I'll bring him home later.
That's fine.
You bought my tuition fee?
Not 'bought' tuition fee.
I 'paid' your tuition fees.
Could you buy me an ice cream?
Sure.
What favour do you like?
Watch out.
Did uncle buy you all the gifts?
Where's Uncle Chiu?
I've thought about it.
It's better to drive it myself.
Why?
I can get more and save more
from driving by myself.
You made the soup?
What...
Did I forget to pay the tuition fee?
I've paid it for you.
I'll give it back to you.
Take your time.
By the way, I've fixed your sink.
Save your money, man.
It's OK.
I bought them for your kid only.
What? Are you OK?
OK.
Miss Lam, my mom send me
to collect the rent.
Don't worry. I'll pay you soon.
No way...
You've held it off month after month.
I fear no bad tenant!
Miss Lam,
you know the elders live on rent.
Don't worry, I'll pay you after two days.
OK. I'll wait till that day but no more.
I'll come next Monday.
Don't hold it off any more at that time.
Don't worry. The landlady is kind.
It's her daughter who's troublesome.
She fears that I can't pay the rent.
I work so hard.
How can I make no money?
If I hadn't blown the tyre today,
I would have made it.
Eight dollars for crossing the harbour.
Hop in!
Eight dollars only, get in.
Damn, stop!
Stop!
Open the door!
How dare you! Stop...
Damn it! I'll dig you up.
Where did the clunker 1314 come from?
It seemed to come from Eastern District.
Good. Anyway,
tell our men to get her tonight!
Got it!
You snatched the passengers
from their turfs?
I'll settle it for you.
Take the kid to school first.
What're you doing?
I'm calling the police.
Are you nuts? Can it help?
Do you know them?
I'll revenge if I do.
How do you revenge? Kill him?
Where did you go last night?
How dared you snatch the passengers
from their turfs?
They all have triad backgrounds!
They ruin my business.
I'm starving to death!
All professions have their own rules.
You must obey them.
I believe there's justice in the world.
See them with me!
I'm not tough like you.
Go by yourself. I won't go with you.
You only act by yourself!
Hey!
Bitch!
Which bastard wrecked my car?
Me! What can you do?
How dare you push me?
Is money the only way to go?
I wanna earn my bread and butter only.
Yeah!
I'll call the police to nail you. I swear it!
Don't push me any more. I warn you!
Kill me! If you dare!
Stay here if you have the guts!
Kill me!
Don't run away!
Shau Kei Wan. Hurry.
What's with you?
Don't do anything rash. OK?
Listen to me this time. Alright?
I'll settle it for you!
Listen...
Let me do the talking.
Don't do anything rash.
I'll try my best.
Uncle Seven.
Elvis, you're here.
Wanna play mah-jong?
Come on. Let's...
I'll take a rain-check.
Uncle Seven, I'd like to talk with you.
My granddaughter is holding
a birthday party tonight.
Talk to me tomorrow.
Sorry, Uncle Seven. Just for a while.
What's the matter?
You know, Man was killed in the crash.
His wife wanna take the route for him.
That's her?
Yes.
I have told you
not to queue up.
She can take the route once she pays.
I know. Uncle Seven.
But she's got no money.
So we wanna ask for your help.
No money... you two may help her out.
And she's really gutsy.
If she keeps buggering around,
you'll be in big trouble one day! Got it?
I must drive to the terminus.
Terminus?
Your man died, and I have to pay you?
Then, what if dad dies,
his son asks for help?
And what if an older bro dies?
Free for his younger bro?
Can I still make a living?
Absolutely not!
I must drive to the terminus.
Dad,
today’s your granddaughter's birthday.
Cut anything about death!
For your goodies.
Kiddo, you're so cute.
How old are you?
Five.
Five only?
Granddad!
Good gal.
Laurie Leung.
Charlene Cheung.
I'm celebrating my birthday today.
My auntie wanna drive to the terminus.
For what?
I don't know.
Play with me.
I love to.
Uncle Seven, they're friends.
They may become very close friends
one day.
Yes, it's man who sets the rules.
You can always change them.
My boy, a dozen grand only.
You can help them.
Spare her the charge, please.
Uncle Seven.
That's right.
You'll be rewarded for your good will.
Right? Auntie.
Auntie? How do you do?
OK, well...
I make an exception this time and not next.
All set. What got you into a fuss?
I've told you not to worry.
You're just lucky today.
To tell the truth, those guys...
are only bluffing. They're just wusses.
I am never scared.
Shush.
If they reject me,
I'll ask them to return Man's money to me.
Right, Laurie?
You're nuts! OK...
I'll go to the market and buy some food.
Let's celebrate tonight.
It's late now. Save it.
Where are you going?
Sir, any shrimps and crabs?
All sold out!
Then... any fish?
Can't you see fish?
I sell you all for 30 dollars.
I can't take all these. Too many for a meal.
Two sets are enough.
This fish... can you make it into a dish?
I can pan-fry it to make it a good dish.
The vegetable stall is closing.
Keep this for me.
Sorry, sir. I don't want it.
How much is the cabbage?
Five dollars for one catty.
You don't want it?
It is decaying. Dump it.
Can you give it to me
if I buy two more catty from you?
Take all home if you like.
Thank you.
I waste no food.
Don't you know you're in a mess?
It's alright if you can't handle it.
Stop push yourself.
It may be OK for a grown-up.
But how about the kid?
If the days go like this,
you are raising him like a dog.
Is it OK to feed him, water him like a dog?
I know you've been helping me a lot.
And I don't want to cause you
any more troubles.
I shouldn't ask for help all the time.
It doesn't matter.
But no one will sympathize
with you for good.
I know.
I don't want to be a laughing stock.
Didn't Man told you at the time of dying...
that I must be tough?
To be frank,
Man at his time of dying
didn't tell me he loved you.
He didn't tell you to be tough.
That's my own words.
Why did you lie to me?
You cheated me!
I told you that...
to help you, to make you feel better.
But I might be wrong.
I am very busy and cannot receive
your call at the moment.
Please leave your phone number.
I'll reply you soon.
Where's Laurie?
His mom is dining out with him
for his birthday.
I've thought about it.
If you think it's not easy,
I'll ask his mom to raise him.
No way.
I love you but I love Laurie even more.
It's hard to raise a child.
Then, why did you fight for his custody?
A woman can't marry
if she got a child with her.
That's it.
You can't dump even a dog like that.
Do you agree?
Yes.
You've done a very good job.
No one will blame you.
For me,
a wife is your solution to your troubles.
You're right.
Let me get one tomorrow.
Marry me!
Marry you?
Will you do?
I'll do if you say 'I do'.
No. You'll do if I say 'I do'.
Will you say 'I do'?
Scare me stiff.
What? What scares you?
You know what scares me.
I have a hard time raising my son.
You'll add to my burden.
No! You must marry me...
Come up with a solution later.
Go to bed early.
Susan...
I know.
I was not in Hong Kong. So...
Are you available?
I'd like to talk with you.
I'm married.
Why do you know my address?
His mom told you?
I can't help you...
I've brought him to dad and mom
after Man's death.
No... I saw them...
I've paid them some grand.
What're you up to?
Wanna bring him to me?
No... I can't help you!
At that time, I didn't want to have him.
It's Man who insisted on having him.
We've gone through all the procedure.
I know. But...
Who are you?
Take him back now, I beg you.
You want money?
Give me your account number. I'll pay you.
Give me some time if you want a big sum.
I'll try my best to discuss with my husband.
I... I've got no money...
Let's go.
I'm so sorry.
I split up with Man right after his birth.
I've seen him a few times only!
Don't worry.
I'll bring Laurie to see you when I'm free.
Sorry.
Do you mean that?
Then tell me how can you deal with it?
Any other way out?
So hungry. Get something to eat. Go.
Let's get something to eat.
Sorry, I wasted your time.
Any other relatives?
They live on pension.
His grandma got hurt
when she fell down last week.
For the Rent?
Or the instalments on the car?
Let me lend you some money.
No.
Which one do you like?
You may pick more.
Really?
Don't buy any more.
He'll get the clothes inside.
Let's buy two.
Laurie. Take one more.
I'm full.
You have fed him three.
He used to love this goody. One more.
You wanna choke him on ice cream?
Stop. He'll have loose bowels
with too many ice-creams.
He can ease himself in the toilet.
He loves ice cream.
One more. Good boy.
Enjoy it...
Orphanage
Can you bring him in for me?
I can't!
I can't. He'll hate me for good.
I'd rather put your dog down for you.
I can't.
Laurie, let's go.
Say goodbye to uncle.
Uncle Hale won't go with us?
Where do you want to bring me?
I'll be a good boy.
I'll listen to you.
Auntie can't keep you.
Don't give me up.
I don't know my way home.
But I've got no way out.
Laurie must be a good boy.
Beware of the bullies.
Take good care of yourself.
I'll be a good boy.
Don't desert me. Mom.
I beg you. Take me to Dad and Grandma.
Forgive me.
Uncle Hale wanna keep me?
Hale...
Hale!
Hey!
What should I do?
Can you really send him away?
You should sell your minibus before him.
Don't cry...
Let me keep him, OK?
I'll keep him!
Come on. It's OK.
Don't cry...
Let's go. Go.
What will the others think
when they see us?
OK. Let's go...
Alright...
Don't cry.
The kite's high in the sky!
It drops.
A fallen kite!
Check out your throne.
Come on. Belt up.
Be careful.
And this board.
You can pull it down...
to do homework, drawing...
so safe and comfy.
Isn't it great? What's more...
Laurie, you see.
Thank you!
I've got something for you, too.
Call her mom, not auntie any more.
Why?
Coz your auntie will be happy about it.
Got it?
My mom got it from the temple.
It's great.
And...
I made a pack of keys for you.
It helps you see Laurie.
Terrific.
By the way, I've got an idea.
Laurie and you go live with me.
And you no longer need to pay the rent.
Come to my home when you're free.
It's a nice place.
Let me think about it.
Yes, think it over.
Coz... if I move,
it's wise to live out
the prepayment of two months.
That's right. Think it over.
I'll go now. You gotta work.
Bye.
Thanks a lot.
You're welcome.
Bye. Papa!
Bye. Sit down.
This kid's brainy and honey mouthed.
What's up?
You pay the instalments on the car
for someone?
Who's bullshitting?
There aren't many car companies around.
It's typically human.
One tends to gossip about others
but not oneself.
I just wanna help the kiddo!
Yes. You're right. But...
Got it.
What did you get? I haven't finished yet.
I said I got it!
It's good to give a helping hand,
but bad to overdo it.
What are the scruples
about helping people?
I don't mean that. I mean...
an existential subject may not be
an empirical one
yet an empirical one may not be
a rational one, right?
You must have read
too many hentai comics.
So, you talk like a philosopher.
Watch out!
You coward.
Aren't you gutsy? What scares you?
Give it your hand.
Let it shake with you.
Come on, let it smell your hand
and know you're Laurie.
He'll have a very good sleep
coz he played so tired.
I go now.
Hale.
Let me go with you.
Good idea.
Laurie hasn't played so happily
for such a long time.
Me too.
Sorry.
Let's get something to drink.
Ma'am, six bottles of beer, please.
Thanks.
You like it? I like it.
Get more foodstuff.
Fine.
Who're you?
I'm... a friend of Holly.
What... what're you doing here?
I'm... fixing something for her.
It's fixed now.
Thank a lot.
Holly and I are colleagues.
You also drive a minibus?
Yes.
I've made it. I'm leaving now.
There're soft drinks in the fridge.
Bye.
Excuse me.
You're with her?
Yes.
How's she now?
Quite good... Nothing wrong with her.
Do you know... her story?
I know.
Not long ago... she's so emotional that...
she couldn't make any good judgment.
But she's quite good now.
She looks tough.
But deep down she's dependent.
And she's rash and headstrong.
So her mom and I are worried about her...
We feared that she'd be cheated.
Would you please look after her for us?
Don't worry. I would.
And...
Don't tell her I've been here...
though it makes no harm
to tell her about her mom.
I got it. I tell her nothing then.
Thank you.
Alright.
Hale, let's have buffet with Laurie tonight?
Tonight?
I have to work till eight or nine o'clock.
It's OK. Laurie and I will be waiting.
Hale, go.
I gotta go now.
I am very busy and cannot receive
your call at the moment.
Please leave your phone number.
I'll reply you soon.
Laurie.
What's up?
Let's call Uncle Hale.
Hello?
Uncle Hale, I'm going to bed now.
Good boy.
How's your mom?
He wants you.
He said he must call you.
That's OK.
Where did you go?
I've just taken a nap.
I thought you wanted to turn
a blind eye to me.
Featherbrain. Why would I do so?
Then, I'll come and see you later.
OK.
What do you want?
Beer?
Six bottles, please.
Thanks.
How are you feeling? Not feeling well?
I'm fine. Alright.
By the way, I asked the landlady
to stop renting out her flat.
She only returned me
half of the prepayment.
We'll live with you.
If you feel uneasy with us,
do tell me.
Don't be silly. How can it be?
As the saying goes:
Two going well may not live well.
You have been taking good care of us
these days.
No matter how the days goes,
I'll be grateful to you. Thank you.
I have something to say.
Turn off the tap. Come over and listen.
Hale, call me when you're back.
Hale, I'm going to board a plane
with our son.
Keep on gambling.
I tell you you're not a good man
or a good husband, a good father.
You don't need a home at all.
Why got married? Why had a son?
It's too late to mend.
Good boy, say goodbye to dad.
Dad! Why are you not with us?
What's wrong?
I haven't done with my words!
I begin to do housework only
after they left me.
Make a meal, sweep the floor...
Stop talking foul languages before the kids.
Save money, stop smoking, stop gambling...
I used to have four minibuses. But all lost.
I'm foolish enough.
I cheated myself.
I know well they wouldn't come back
yet I make a spin
in my minibus every day...
I daren't change my phone, move elsewhere
or change jobs.
I fear that they can't see me any more.
The truth is, if they do want me,
they'll see me.
I got real at last.
I should face reality, forget the past
and not stay put.
I can't spend my life in...
driving from east to west, then back to east.
Right?
Last time, I told Laurie
and you to live with me.
You didn't say 'yes'.
I thought it over whole night.
I listened to that message,
again and again...
I take Laurie and you to be them.
I thought I wanna prove myself...
that I can be a good dad
and a good husband.
Do you feel grateful to me
or really love me?
Do I take you to be her?
Or you take me to be him?
If we got another one in our hearts...
it means nothing even if we have sex.
Hale.
You're a very good man.
Sorry, the number you just dialled
is not in service.
Turn around, please.
Take away your hands.
Open your eyes.
Gorgeous!
You like it?
With this bouquet... Will you marry me?
You're serious?
Yes.
Let me ask you a question.
If you can answer it, I'll marry you.
OK.
What does our plate number mean?
Forever.
I do.
Man, I gotta forget you.
Dad.
Call him grandpa.
He's grandpa?
Yes.
But I've got a granddad already.
Call him. Good boy.
He's so young.
He's honey mouthed.
Isn't it tough?
I work to kill time.
My old buddy opened this shop.
I'll have dinner at home tonight.
Good.
I wanna move back home.
Of course.
With him.
Are you a good boy?
Me? I'm not.
Are you bad-tempered like your mom?
Yes, I'm very bad-tempered.
Will you bicker with me?
Yes, I'll.
Will you do anything rash?
And the more I tell you not to do,
the more you want?
Yes.
But are you wicked?
And don't let me play anything?
You may do whatever you want.
But you have to tell me beforehand.
Just tell me. OK?
Dad.
Put less salt into your soup.
Too salty.
Too salty? Really?
It's true. I never cheated you.
Laurie, go to pee pee. Quick.
Hale, call me back, please.
What? Sell or not?
Think it over.
Wait...
Let me make a call.
What?
Hello?
Hale?
I just wanted to call you.
What's the matter?
Tell me first.
You gotta tell me first.
I wanna sell the car and do another job.
Which one?
Whatever.
The sort of business...
once the client come in,
they'll be very happy.
Sell ice-cream or something.
Have you thought over it?
No, I haven't.
I can't waste my time thinking.
Do you wanna change your job?
Will you sell your car?
Where're you?
At a car company in Man Wui Street.
Man Wui Street? I'm there too.
Really?
Papa!
I just wanna tell you.
I sold my car and got the money.
Wait, stay put...
You said last time...
I'm a very good man. Right?
If a girl says something
like that to a guy...
She means...
She won't go out with that guy.
Then...
Do you love me?
I love... you... a little bit.
A little bit...
That's good enough.
Is it because I have been helping you
Or you found out that I'm divorced
and lonely, so you feel pity for me?
Of course not.
Let's try it.
I'll sell it!