Rise and shine!
Come down to earth
Come on
you lazy girl, get up!
Ah, Ah
wake up!
Hey!
you, drop it
No way!
No running, I told you.
Your asthma might relapse!
Holy cow!
Stop tormenting your sister.
Ouch!
This is some morning.
Here we go again!
Back on your computer again?
It's mine.
I won it in a raffle.
Right, and you
keep it all to yourself.
Perhaps I'll throw it out soon.
Mom, get me a piano.
A piano!
How about a tutu?
I need one for the ballet recital.
No way.
Keep the old one!
- No. I want a pretty new one!
- Be quiet!
Oh, my god!
I need to pee, dad.
Bye, darling.
Don't lose any more buttons!
Jadoo!
Better just to sell the shares
and take the hit.
Yes. Sell them this afternoon.
Sure.
This is Chulsoo Lee
at Core Securities.
Sure, I'll be right there.
This is the BN System schedule.
Some major players
and fund managers are on it secretly.
You should get to it.
Would manipulation be necessary?
No choice!
The juicy details will be out in a week.
Keep buying for the clients.
- Recommend it to some market makers!
- This is...
Head Office is watching this.
There'll be a big bonus.
You have four kids.
Aren't you going to send them to college?
Hi!
Hi, what are you doing here?
Having dinner with a school friend.
Is he your client?
You know him?
Who doesn't?
He's the big tuna!
Thanks to his rich father-in-law.
Then again, 90% of his assets
belong to his wife.
He's just fronting.
Really!
Where's MY father-in-law?
How's your wife?
She SHOULD be doing fine.
We got a divorce.
Last month.
After 20 years of marriage,
some irreconcilable differences!
Nothing but bickering.
How about you?
on every Wednesday night?
Well...
Time for the Wal-Mart
special of the day.
Fresh octopus on sale
for 4,000 won, half price!
I've got to run!
I got it first.
I picked it up first.
Right? It's mine.
She got it first.
Donkey face!
Hello!
Hi, how are you?
My goodness! Did you get hurt?
Are you alright?
Don't forget this octopus.
Come on.
Have a good day!
What did the general
manager say?
Four kids, how are you going to send
them to university?
Same old lines.
So, what did you say?
No more manipulation!
I'd rather be fired!
That's what I wanted to say,
but I couldn't.
Are you going to?
The market will get better.
Let's not be greedy.
Yes! We need principles,
at least minimal ones.
Unanimous!
Revolution completed!
To our lasting pledge!
Cool!
Dear God,
thanks for the Pentium III you provided.
I'm enjoying it. Be merciful and send me
a new computer to complete your love.
Amen.
Daddy!
Not tonight.
It's Wednesday!
- Honey!
- yes?
Did we pay the monthly assessment?
I don't see the receipt.
We switched to automatic debit
on that one, remember?
Right.
Hon, right there!
Yeah, there?
Do you like doing it with me?
My saggy breasts, stomach,
I've changed.
A little bit, and the belly.
Thanks!
Don't like it?
I like it!
Darling, you want to
make another baby?
Are you out of your mind?
Younghee Kim!
That'll be the right thing to do
for the Kim family with not many children.
Just one more, okay?
How about two more
for a volleyball team?
There's an idea.
Nonsense!
Stop it.
Not there.
I miss Besame Mucho.
The cafe in the country side?
Where we first met!
I doubt it's still there.
That was a long time ago.
It was!
BN System concludes a contract on
technology transfer with the S Tech, U.S..
Here's correspondent
Sungchul Kim
With the details.
With the deal completed
BN System
expects over
$10 million in royalties.
The company
also plans to attract
additional contracts with other int'l
industry leaders
on the technology transfer.
The deal is about to be
completed after their continued
efforts for the last six months.
Shares for BN System?
That'll be hard...
Mr. Kim, this is Chulsoo Lee.
What do we do?
We can ignore Mr. Jung's request...
Not on BN System.
No way.
Of course,
the price will go up further.
Sell them now.
Please listen to me!
This is confidential information.
Buy as much as you can.
Please don't be greedy!
What's wrong with you.
All the others except you
...recommend it strongly...
I've got to be going.
- What happened?
- What?
What happened
to your minimal principles?
I was drunk...
Don't take seriously.
What did you say?
What's all this?
A word of advice!
Shoot straight!
Just like computers,
Life should be upgraded.
How long are you going to stick
to your lousy sense of justice?
Chulsoo.
Let me, let me!
Please calm down.
This reflects your
performance this month.
You don't think you can stay?
Head Office recommended
someone to take over.
This'll be your last week.
I don't understand.
If you can't do it,
you should quit.
This is so unreasonable.
Head Office wanted this done
and you didn't join us.
I am so sorry.
Dad!
Daddy!
Come here,
my precious ones!
Not until after dinner.
What's the occasion?
It's not mom's birthday yet.
What do we have here?
It's from your friend...
Jinsuk?
He sent this?
We have no room for this.
Send it back.
No! The piano is mine!
Play some!
If you're good, we'll keep it.
Dad.
- Come on, darling!
- No.
Come on.
And turn...
Haeoh.
Click!
- When does the picture come out?
- I am not sure.
My little sweetie!
- Dig in, Jioh!
- Yes.
How come you
don't eat octopus?
She doesn't.
Because she's fussy.
Settle down, kids.
- Want some more rice?
- Fill it to the brim with rice!
Perhaps I should quit my job
and open a restaurant.
l mean with your cooking skills!
Don't even think it!
- What are you doing?
- Keeping household accounts.
We're loaded!
One more payment left on
your dead brother's debts.
After that, we'll keep saving
and move into a 3 bedroom
apartment in 2 years.
Thank god all the
payments are made.
At least, I've been bringing home
a fat paycheck.
- It didn't take too long.
- True.
What's this?
No name on it?
Give it back to me!
Some secret account of your own?
Give it back.
Give it back to me!
Hey, I want to see it.
Stop it!
Aah! Stop it!
You really like free stuff!
God is with me.
He answers my prayers.
God must be bored these days.
Could you be more attentive?
I AM!
- Did you call for Chinese noodles?
- Yeah.
Too much dust.
Wear this.
I think I have a problem.
I keep coughing.
You have your God!
Stop the nonsense and polish this.
Hey you!
You clean yours!
Don't call him "Hey". Show some respect.
He's your older brother.
Dear God
Let me get out of this hell.
I need rest
and peace of mind most.
Let my parents love only me.
and let me grow up soon
And marry Ricky Martin!
Amen.
Chinese food is here!
- Is this the
residence of Mr. Chulsoo Lee?
- Yes?
We're from the Court Office.
Were you a guarantor for Mr. Kang??
Yes.
Mr. Kang defaulted on a note for
700 million won and disappeared.
According to the Civil Law 527,
Article 611, your property
And possessions are seized
What's all this about?
Seizure?
Didn't you receive
the repayment notice?
From now on,
you're not to remove those
seizure stickers off of the subject items.
That's illegal and you will be
prosecuted accordingly.
In case you don't pay it all
back by the 12th of next month,
...this apartment will be auctioned off.
Can you repay the debt now?
- We'll proceed according to the law.
- You go away.
No. You've got the wrong house.
This must be a mistake.
This is the right house
madam.
No!
What are we going to do?
Don't worry.
I'll handle it.
You even got fired!
It'll take 30 years
to come up with that kind of money.
How will you get
the money in one
month?
You're insane.
You must be, doing all this!
You be nice to
your dad from now on.
Don't ask him for money or toys
I won't allow it.
Come and talk to me instead.
We already do.
I'll start working tomorrow.
You have to get ready
for school for yourself.
No more newspaper,
milk, and yogurt!
No more private lessons!
Really?
I don't have to take my lessons?
But I still want to go
to my ballet lessons.
- Listen to me!
- No, I'll keep going there.
You're so immature.
I got the leading role
in our ballet presentation.
It must have been hard
for you to bring this up.
I'd like to and should
lend you the money.
But I don't have any.
I'm not any better off. Sorry.
No, I am sorry.
You sound just the same.
How have you been?
That much money made
on real state?
Turn it down!
And? That's just great...
Turn it down! By the way
Can you lend me some money?
Bitch. Didn't I lend her money
For her sick child?
Hello!
Did you move?
What?
You want the police
to come after you?
My god, get in there!
Mom, she started it!
No more. Go to your room.
As you know,
I was never a good student.
And now, a lot of MBA holders
from the U.S. are working under me.
What good is it to become
the top of the class in school?
That's why I don't pressure
my kids to study.
They can just play
computer games.
And if they're good,
I'll support them fully.
Who knows? They might make
a hell of a lot money with it!
You silly!
Taeoh.
Yeah, what?
Do you by any chance have any...?
Have you heard about Dongho?
He's in deep shit now!
What happened?
Thanks to Jinsuk Kang.
He lost 100 million won lent to Jinsuk.
Jinsuk defaulted on 700 million won.
Not everyone is cut out for business.
Anyone here lend money to Jinsuk?
No way.
Sit down!
Good to know.
Long time no see!
Hey, Seungmin.
Come on here.
Sure.
Come here.
I hear you're raking in money.
How have you been?
Good to see you
here at the alumni meeting.
How's it going?
- Okay.
- Yeah...
I heard you moved to
another company. Is it nice?
I'll see how it goes.
How about you?
About to quit.
Been setting up my own business.
Your own business?
Online securities company
and I'm a bit short of money.
Seungmin, do you have any spare money?
About 50 million won.
- What's happened to you?
- What?
At least, you didn't lie before.
- What do you mean?
- I know you got fired yesterday.
This is crazy. My former coworker
will be your replacement.
Crazy. On top of everything else,
coming home like this!
Jioh, Jioh!
I've got pizza for you.
Youndoo, Jadoo wake up!
You stink!
Your beard, so rough!
You must be enjoying this.
Go brush your teeth and get to bed!
Yeah.
Ouch! Ouch!
Couldn't you just come home safe?
My hands are full with
four kids as they are!
Stupid to get hurt!
Delicious?
Yummy?
Yeah.
Good!
Stop it.
I already know how you feel.
I closed the savings account today.
27 million won. 100 million won to go.
Don't be so weak.
I know you are strong.
Kids.
No one can force us to leave.
No one is going to force us to leave.
Because I am Chulsoo Lee!
They can't fucking break me!
Honey.
Jioh, Haeoh I can still run.
I can still run
I can run.
I'm going to fucking run.
Fuck.
Honey!
Daddy!
I'm not with the company,
but I'd like to continue
to manage your shares.
I won't disappoint you.
Trust me.
Thanks but no thanks.
No investment
without reliable information.
I'm confident.
Trust me!
Information is the key factor.
I need juicy tips to trust you.
For example,
tips on BN System.
You've changed a lot.
Time has passed.
I was hesitant about coming here.
First time since high school.
What if you don't recognize me?
You look just the same.
Haven't changed one bit.
I read the article on your donations
to schools. A pleasant surprise.
And I remembered the old days.
Remember I was pursuing you
for three years?
Long letters to you were never
answered. Not even a glance at me.
I'm sorry about those days.
That's in the past.
- Are you married?
- Yeah,
- Kids?
- Four.
What does your husband do?
Used to work for a securities company.
He lost his job.
I have a favor to ask you.
I know this is too much to ask.
But I know you from school,
and maybe there's hope.
My husband cosigned for
someone who defaulted.
Our apartment is slipping away.
100 million won will save it.
Pardon me, sir.
Your appointment is at 3 at the
Hotel Shilla. Better get going
I know.
I'm sorry, we didn't even have
coffee together.
That's all right.
Leave your number
and I'll call you.
You hit me!
How dare you?
Shut up! You four kids
are ganging up on my son.
He did it first,
he did....
The son of a bitch said
we are beggars. Come on!
What, son of a bitch?
What's wrong with you?
We're not beggars!
My mom said so. That you beggars
will be thrown out of your house.
Didn't you, mom?
Who called us beggars?
Mom.
Stop crying.
I know this is too much to ask....
But can I see the plans?
That's not possible.
Please!
I'll pretend I never heard this.
I still respect you.
After paying my brother's debts,
I thought we'd be better off.
I am really sorry.
sorry...
What have we done to
deserve this?
No choice.
This is our reality.
We could rent a small room.
I'll check it up
with the real estate agent.
I won't move out of this house.
I earned it.
Our first child Eunoh died of asthma
in a small basement-level studio.
I was using the sewing machine,
dusting the place, while he was dying
of pneumonia.
Just to make a few more bucks.
My heart was torn when
we scattered his ashes into the river.
To me, this house means him.
I'll never lose any of
our children again.
I cancelled everything but the
insurance policy for their future.
Can you make
the payment tomorrow?
You're so immature.
Do you think mom will be happy
with a birthday gift now?
What do we do then?
Lottery tickets naturally.
Win two 50 million won prizes,
and we won't have to move.
That's not easy.
God never disappointed me.
Always answers my prayers.
That's true.
I don't like that.
How about a vote?
It's split one to one between us.
You decide Youndoo.
What do you think?
Move into a tiny basement apartment
with no room for your piano?
No!
Your choice!
Hands up!
Who told you to break
your piggybank?
And didn't even won 1,000 won.
Hello?
ls this Ms. Kim's house?
Yes.
A package for you.
Please sign here.
Pretty shoes.
Mom,
did daddy send all this?
It must be for mom's birthday.
Keep your hands up!
Come on!
How did you like the opera?
Well, it's been a while.
You used to like it.
Did I?
Madam Butterfly was a true story
included in an American magazine.
A play writer called David something
adapted it for stage and Puccini
made it into an opera.
I used to listen to it
a lot back in high school.
I've been forgetting about it.
I'd never thought I could
see you again. If you hadn't come
we would have never met again.
I'm glad you still look
pretty much the same.
It's nice to be rich.
You said you need money?
Thank you.
It might take a while
but I'll pay it back.
What's your account number?
I don't need money.
No, that's not right.
It's a big sum.
It's all right.
No, I can pay it back.
Don't.
I want something else instead.
You're still pretty.
Madam Butterfly was a geisha
selling her body.
In comparison,
this'll be the best transaction!
I am sorry.
I asked for too much.
You are insane.
This'll be the last time.
Get me the data.
- No.
- Please!
Listen, this is so not like you.
What's to be like me?
After ten years, they fired me
for being honest. My best friend
took away my house and ran away.
I have nothing to lose or fear.
My children are...
my last hope to keep.
I need the file.
This is the data you wanted.
2 billion won is to be used,
with 1 billion to be the expected profit.
I'd like 10% of it.
Those are not great terms
for me.
I could lose the capital
and you risk nothing.
I won't take a penny
if you don't get the expected profit..
Are you confident?
If I weren't,
I wouldn't have started this.
This is our monthly wine club
get-together.
I told them about you,
and they are anxious to see you.
You can just have a casual talk
with them. No pressure.
Yes, sir.
The shares on Whajin
Tech seem stagnant.
We've got the shares,
and necessary data.
No need to worry.
Are you wearing some perfume?
Nice!
My usual.
What fragrance do you like,
Mr. Lee?
You look better.
Have some more.
Hello!
Mr. Jang, this is Mr. Lee
I told you about.
Mr. Lee, this is our
corporate lawyer.
Hello, how are you?
I'm Chulsoo Lee.
Hi, nice to meet you.
Hello!
Hi!
Is Chairman Kim here?
He's waiting for you.
Come this way.
0, 1, 6
Hey, you're still up?
A lullaby? You said you
don't like it any more.
I see.
Rock a bye baby,
in the tree top,
when the wind blows,
the cradle will rock ....
You weren't around.
Where were you?
I was resting in the den.
Should have rested at home.
It was a party for couples.
Plus I got to talk with Mr. Lee.
Mrs. Lee,
somebody left this for you
He asked me to hand it to you.
Thank you.
What's the meaning of this?
They are the keys to my house.
Whenever you are ready.
I'm not that kind!
Don't do this again.
- Honey...
- Yeah?
Nothing.
One week left!
Don't worry.
I'll keep this house no matter what.
I already know!
But you're the only one to turn to.
Please, this'll be the last time.
Are you listening?
Are you still there?
Can you hear me?
It's me. Couldn't reach
you at work or your home.
Where are you now?
Call me once you get this message.
Please!
My husband told me
you're having a hard time at home.
Will get better thanks to you.
Thanks for the other day.
I didn't see anything.
Nobody else knows about it,
right?
No one's around here.
- Don't do this to me.
- It's all right.
Things are going well.
Do you want to stop?
Why didn't you tell me?
You are as honest as one
an ever be.
That's why you were fired.
Why would you not tell me?
If I did, would you
be able to resolve it?
We are husband and wife.
I quit it.
I'm not in it any more.
Stop it!
Why should I give you the share?
Who else would compensate me?
My husband hired you.
You caused all this.
All right. l'll take care of it.
Quiet down.
How will you handle it?
You were getting 10% from him.
I can give you 20%.
Are you joking?
Does it matter whose money
you use for the investment?
I'll advance you 100 million won.
Take me to your house.
I want to do it in your bed.
- You're insane.
- Correct.
I've got to be insane to make
such an offer to someone like you!
Eight and...
one, and two, and
three, and four...
What happened?
She's been watching us
from outside the windows for days.
I asked her in. Severely asthmatic.
I had no idea.
She seems stressed out.
She should stay here for a few days
till her breathing becomes stable.
Doctor, will she be all right?
What happened?
Where's Youndo?
She's hospitalized.
Where are you going?
To get the money. We can't just let
her slip away like our first son.
Did you have lunch?
I don't care about lunch now.
How could you eat
at a time like this?
If only you hadn't lost the house,
we wouldn't be in this mess.
Right, it's all my fault.
Yes, it's all your fault.
That's why I'm running around
like a dog for the money.
How soon can you make
100 million won that way!
We have not just one,
but four kids.
Even without the medication,
it's hard to make a living.
Do you realize how much it takes
to raise the kids?
Jioh's mom never
contributed a dollar.
That's enough.
The kids can hear us!
Where are your buddies?
Where are your school friends
when we're struggling like this?
You've done so much for them!
Okay, I'll be back with the money.
I'll do anything to get it!
Do whatever it takes!
This policy will mature this month.
Why not wait for it?
I know. I'd just like to
close the account.
Did you bring the fees
for the organ test?
The surgery will take 3 to 4 hours,
...and you'll be hospitalized
for 3 weeks
I want to be upfront about this.
A healthy person can survive
with only one kidney.
However, some complications
may occur after the surgery.
I'll call you
about the results tomorrow.
Hello!
The results are due today.
I've been waiting for two hours.
I still haven't heard from you.
Call me at the coffee house
when you get this message.
I'll be waiting.
Can we talk?
Is this because
he's not your real son?
Chulsoo!
He's no blood relation to you.
But, to me, he's like my own son.
Don't you remember
What my brother said when dying?
I've done my share.
Money, money, money.
He must have been driven
to the edge.
Right! That's what I thought, too.
His friends made fun
of him being poor.
He must have felt terrible!
Is this you, Jioh?
I know...
...yes...
I know
On the 12th, 12th. Yes,
I fully understand.
I'll pay it back even if
I have to rob your bank. Okay?
- Is it good?
- Yeah.
Who's that, mom?
Do you know him?
No, I don't know him.
Let's get in.
I'll come and see your new sofa.
- Sure, see you.
- See you.
Hello!
Have you been to the hospital?
Yes.
If you need money,
please tell me.
Good bye.
Be careful. Hello!
Do you know
Youndoo's hospitalized?
How come?
What's wrong with her?
Is this what you like?
It was a gift for my wife.
Now I smell of your wife.
How do you kiss your wife?
Remember Hyoungsuk?
He used to ask for money
for his rocket building project.
He's a professor at KAlST now.
Youngmin used to live
in your neighborhood.
He delivered all my letters to you,
did you know?
I'm going to go take a shower.
Jioh,
Let's play some baseball.
What's wrong?
I heard something from outside.
Ignore it.
Jioh, Jioh!
Let's play some baseball.
Nobody's out there.
I can't do this.
Let's just stop.
We've a long way to go.
Sorry.
You'd better get going.
Don't do this.
Please leave.
We've just begun.
Stop it!
After you had your way with me!
You caused the whole nonsense.
You almost stole
the documents you have.
What's the difference between
that and selling your body?
I am sorry.
Younghee!
Don't do this to me.
Let me go!
Please forgive me.
Mom, I've got to pee.
Mom, Mom!
It must be nice for you
to have a mother.
Yeah.
I used to have my mother around.
When I was young,
we were so poor.
No father, practically no food.
One day I was coming home
from school.
I saw my mother at the marketplace.
I was happy to see her
and almost said, "Hi, mom!"
But I had to hide instead.
She was shoplifting some octopus
at a grocery store.
On the dinner table
lay the octopus - nicely prepared.
I loved octopus but didn't
even touch it.
And not even a glance at my mother.
I was embarrassed...
And now I think I know...
How she felt as she was
stealing that octopus.
I am sorry.
I just had to leave.
My mom stole the
octopus to feed me
but I just couldn't do it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I can't keep the promise
to save the house.
I tried everything I could...
Indeed, everything I could do
Sorry.
Jadoo, can you give me a hand?
Dear God! Please ignore
my prayers from now on.
But just once this time,
please answer my prayer.
I promise I'll share prizes
...and clean the fish tank.
So please don't
let us have to move out!
I don't want to move.
It's me, Younghee.
I've got something to tell you.
Sorry about the last time.
I apologize.
Are you at home?
What time do you get out?
I'd like to see you.
It doesn't matter if it's late.
No, I have to see you.
I'll come over to your house.
I don't mind it very late.
Finish your work first.
Yes.
I can wait.
If you're not up to this,
you can go home.
It's your choice.
What time is it?
We don't have to move out.
Get up.
Let's go to the bank.
You get commission
based on the number of clients
visiting your site.
With the recession,
you don't make much money.
At least you can afford
to be honest here.
Thank you.
Jihoon Han at Neo M&A,
didn't he lend you the money?
Yes, my wife knows him
from high school.
You'll have to work
your ass off to pay it back.
I'll work hard and
pay it all back.
Is this Neo M&A?
Could I speak to your president?
Yeah,
I'd like to come visit him.
I'm Chulsoo Lee.
He knows Younghee Kim.
She's my wife.
Yes.
Daddy.
Quiet down!
You bought a new dress?
New shoes, too?
Didn't daddy get them
for your birthday?
She wore these shoes
to the opera.
One, Two, Three, Four
Did you order?
Would you like
your noodles cut up?
Yes, cut hers up fine,
but not mine, please.
What's the occasion?
Visiting me at work.
Just because.
It's been a while since we had
cold noodles together. Right?
- Darling?
- Yeah?
I...
It's very hard for me.
Do you want coffee instead?
You're the only one I can talk to.
I can't go on
with a straight face.
Don't speak.
I...
One more word,
I won't tolerate.
I slept with another
man for money.
I needed the money.
I knew it wasn't right
but I did it.
I'm sorry, darling.
Jihoon Han, I met him.
If you cared about the kids and me,
you should have kept the
secret to the grave.
No matter how much it hurts
You should have kept it to yourself.
Why did you have to tell me?
Shouldn't have...
until the last moment.
I meant to keep it in
my heart till I die. But I can't.
Every time I see the kids or you,
I get so scared.
Day by day
I try to pull myself together.
But I just can't go back
to the way I was. I can't.
I could have let it pass.
I was going to let it slide
and go on.
What now?
It'll be hell to face
each other from now on.
What do we do now?
- How's the presentation coming along?
- All right.
Could you ask someone else
to go on this business trip?
You're in charge of the project.
They are expecting you.
Something urgent?
No, I can't just leave
the kids alone for three days.
Isn't your wife at home?
I'm sick of this.
We've had it for a month.
I miss Mom's food.
Are you crazy?
- You didn't like it, so I tossed it.
- You!
- If you're done, go away.
- Pick it up. You pick it up.
- Pick it up.
- None of your business.
What's all this about?
You're not even our family.
Our dead uncle was your real father.
Don't you think I know?
Isn't this a picture of your family?
Without you, mom and dad
would have liked me better.
Go away.
Mom left us because of you!
Daddy.
Am I too heavy?
No.
Light as a feather.
I think this is our first piggyback.
Tonight I'll make it up to you.
I wanted to be strong.
And I never showed
my weak side to others.
Even when my brother died,
...and when your grandparents died,
I didn't cry.
But...
Just can't help crying now.
I really meant well.
And worked hard.
But I only hurt you and
couldn't protect mom.
How did this happen?
I'm too ashamed to face you.
I wonder what you think of me.
I'm scared.
Can you understand me?
The lamb got scared and ran away.
The lion became sad.
- No, sadder.
- Sadder.
Mom!
Dad!
Dad! Mom! Did you see
me dancing in the center?
He did.
He even took some pictures.
Dad, I didn't cough at all.
Right, mom?
Boy, she talks.
Didn't I look like a real fairy?
Of course, only prettier.
Really?
l am prettier?
No
you were the ugliest!
Can you take a picture of us?
Sure.
Smile.
Thanks. Would you like me
to take one of you?
If you would!
Okay, gather around.
Jioh!
Why are you standing over there,
silly?
Wow, big family!
Come on, smile.
Whiskey, cheese, kimchi ....
Here we go!
Smile, smile!
One, two, two and a half
Three.