I wonder if Deunan is okay...
Hitomi!
Don't tell me...
You exceeded your life-prolong procedure limit
for more than three days!
Hitomi!
We are still not sure who owns the Land Mates
that attacked Gaia Research Center.
This is the end of ESWAT report for this attack.
All Bioroid, please remain calm.
We are trying to restore the life-prolonging system.
Please do not panic and be patient!
Premier Athena, isn't it beyond ESWAT's authority
to block all surrounding of Tarutarus and Tartarus?
Under extreme circumstances,
this is the only option under martial law.
It is our responsibility to protect Gaia.
Not to protect the D-Tank?
It is to protect Gaia!
Totally disregarding us Olympus military?
I only chose the best option.
What do you mean? Are you insulting me?
Please, we have no time to argue!
Everyone, this terrorist attack is targeting
Bioriod's existence, an unforgiving tragedy in Olympus.
If this continues, Bioriod's fate
would be to perish from the surface of earth.
There is an only one way
to save them as well as protect Olympus.
It took a long time to make the decision.
We discussed with Gaia for a long time.
Gaia has made a decision.
Gaia wanted to make Bioriod alive.
Make Bioriod to have reproductive ability.
About the technology to restore
Bioriod's reproductive ability,
I heard that Dr. Gillian
who developed the technology erased all data.
That made the development impossible.
That's true, General Uranus.
If that technology's data was indeed erased,
it's impossible to develop it again.
However, the lost data,
which we called "Apple Seed", does exist.
Soon we will find the lost Apple Seed,
and restore Bioriod's reproductive ability,
allowing them to evolve to be the new human being,
and build a new Utopia.
Hitomi...
She's fine.
Only sleeping...
Are you sure she could be saved?
As long as we find the lost Apple Seed.
If not...
Her body will degenerate very quickly.
She'll die within 24 hours.
Not only Hitomi herself,
all Bioriod will have the same destiny.
Premier Athena Reyes. you are Deunan Knute, right?
Deunan
Do you know Dr. Gillian?
No.
We did research over twenty years.
But still couldn't match Dr. Gillian's researches.
But, if we get Dr. Gillian's Apple Seed,
the Bioriod reproductive ability can be restored.
We can become the new human being
regardless of D-Tank.
Gaia made the final decision.
Athena, we all depended on you now.
Deunan, we need your help.
This old disc is the only clue?
Is it real that the first generation Bioriod
was born in this research center we are headed?
Yes, according to my superior.
Why did Athena cover the secret
of this disc up until now?
Why did Dr. Gillian restrain
the reproductive ability of Bioriod?
Deunan, this a secretive and dangerous mission.
We need to concentrate to do our job.
Be able to save Hitomi. Won't that be enough?
Don't think too much.
Can I ask you a question?
During that terrorist attack, your last shot...
Ah, never mind.
Deunan, Redon, here.
No mistake about it, this is it.
Kudo, back off.
Dr. Gillian, there's no time to waste,
please escape now!
Athena, there's still some data left,
I have to erase every last little bit.
We'll try to defend the first attack, please be hurry.
Mommy
What is it? Did you wake up?
How come...
What is it, Deunan...
Mother
Deunan, listen carefully.
Mommy hid the most important research data
inside this pendant.
But bad guys wanted to use mommy's research
for bad things.
Therefore, mommy had to hide it.
Bad guys?
Yes.
Bad guys who want to take away Deunan's future.
So Deunan must make sure she protects this pendent.
Nmmm, Deunan will protect it.
Good girl.
Deunan, but if Athena says she wants this pendent,
give this pendent to Athena.
Only Athena is an exception.
I know. Only Athena is exception.
Deunan, protect the "Apple Seed".
Deunan, do you remember the thing we are looking for?
Do you remember?
Carl's pistol... is Apple Seed inside that pendent?
Dr. Gillian, please don't move.
Don't move!
I beg you, don't move!
Mommy, what is it, mommy!
Deunan, don't come here!
Don't shoot!
Mommy
Trouble. Olympus military. When did they...
How did they know this place?
Too many enemies! Seaside is already occupied!
Only way is go to the top.
To the roof!
Everybody stay calm!
Position: Room D at 5th floor.
Redon, you betrayed us!
I always hated Bioriod.
As for the traitor,
that guy is the first one!
Hades
Deunan, long time no see.
I regretted I couldn't kill Carl myself.
No surpises, you smell like Bioriod yourself.
And, even with this Cyborg body,
you two are still together.
Tell you the truth,
I was a little scared of seven elder's trick.
But, over trust your men is always your weakness,
Briareos.
Briareos, what's going on?
Let me tell you, Deunan.
The one behind the terrorist attack of Gaia,
is this Briareos.
You still remember my Land Mate got away from him?
Because of him, many Bioriod died.
Is that true?
Answer her, you dog!
Come on, give that pendent to me.
Deunan.
Hurry, go to the top!
Hurry!
Kudo!
Let's go!
Don't come any closer!
Stay away from me!
Deunan, give me the pendent now!
They want the pendent, not you.
This is what my mother protected with her life.
You know everything from the beginning, don't you?
Deunan.
Deunan, you finally start to know him.
The true identity of that monster.
Deunan Knute, I am general commander
of Olympus military, Senator Edward Uranus.
Carl Knute was my old friend, so was Dr. Gillian.
I've seen you a few times when you were a child.
We don't want to hurt you.
Just give the research data to us.
We prepare to overthrow the legislative institute,
destroy D-Tank and eliminate all Bioriod.
Turning the human society back into human's hand.
But the data in your hand will destroy our plan.
Could you please give it to us?
I refuse.
Deunan.
Olympus is not the Utopia in Carl
and Dr. Gillian's dream any more.
I learned my fighting skills from my father Carl.
But I don't understand why father trained me
to become a fighting machine.
Now, I finally know why.
General, my mother's last words are that I should not
give this to anyone else except Athena.
Bioriod are not trust worthy.
They will only continue to control human being.
Maybe they are not to be trusted.
However, one thing is clear.
Bioriod will not kill each other.
General, we don't have that much time.
Deunan, it's a pity.
Athena was protecting human society.
So were Carl and Dr. Gillian.
They tried to hide Apple Seed to protect human.
They wanted to prevent the rapid evolution of Bioriod.
Because Bioriod is a dangerous being.
No. Continue Dr. Gillian's research,
Athena is making Bioriod to evolve slowly,
step by step.
General...
Bioriod is always protecting human society.
The reason I help Hades on that terrorist attack,
is to help Athena to slow down
the evolution process of Bioriod.
And keep Deunan's lost memories lost.
Athena wanted to hide the secret until the last.
My mission is to give Apple Seed to seven elders.
That's how I get the job to protect Deunan.
If so, that pendent must be destroyed.
General, isn't it rather strange?
Seven elders doesn't only want the Apple Seed.
They want to use Apple Seed to destroy D-Tank.
Athena must have some reason behind her protection
of the D-Tank.
General, don't let D-Tank be destroyed!
Briareos
Don't be fooled by the machine's word.
This is revenge, Deunan.
Can you imagine the life I had
after I was dismissed from ESWAT?
This is the revenge to Carl for dismissing me!
I will kill all Bioriod with his DNA.
I will kill all Bioriod!
Hades
If you want to hate someone, hate your father, Deunan!
Sorry.
Don't speak any more.
Although it's the latest Cyborg cell,
I still feel pain when hit by bullets.
Please, don't speak anymore.
Always want to see you again.
When I was dying in the battlefield,
just wanted to see you one more time.
Then, I was saved by seven elders.
If I can protect you,
nothing else matters.
I know.
My body and soul became a monster like this.
You didn't change.
Still yourself.
But I cannot protect you any more
I won't let you die.
Deunan, human being...
Briareos
There won't be a single human sacrifice.
Seven elders promised that.
However they must be planing something under the table.
Therefore, go!
But, I cannot leave you here.
The future of this planet is in your hands.
I don't need a future without you.
Deunan, don't let your mother die in vain.
Enough. Don't speak any more.
Deunan.
Briareos
Briareos sent SOS signal when he was hit.
Hecatonchires is really something,
the special structure is all different.
Stil have time to restore the tissues.
We can still save him.
Please save him.
The fuel is enough for the trip.
Lade Mate's Ultravibrate Gravity System
is already in use now.
Flying is more stable.
The center of gravity has some offset,
but shouldn't have any problem for 60 degree rotation.
Deunan, we Bioriod,
still have a little feelings of love left.
Please save Hitomi.
Deunan Knute. Mission accomplished.
Good work.
Deunan.
Deunan, good work!
Finally we Bioriod reproductive ability.
Hitomi has the same life cycle as a human now.
This way, Hitomi is saved.
I am so happy.
No need to worry any more.
Deunan...
It's you guys who killed my mother, isn't it?
Did you have my mother killed?
Deunan please forgive us.
That really was an accident.
If Dr. Gillian were alive,
We would only have more options.
Why did mother hide Apple Seed?
We got our only hope from Dr. Gillian.
The final chance to allow human race to exist.
Coexistence of human and Bioriod is the only way.
But, human never give up fighting.
They are afraid and hate the superior race.
With vehemence.
Human race has no ability to rule this planet anymore,
they are a disgrace to Dr. Gillian's ideal.
According to Gaia's prediction, human race will
be destroyed with earth in three generations.
Deunan, it's time for us human race
to step out of the way.
Step out of the way?
We human must give the future of the earth to Bioriod.
Dr. Gillian's virus,
will finally have its destiny fullfilled.
Virus developed by my mother?
Yes, on the top of Tarutarus.
Sealed inside D-Tank.
This virus can destroy the reproductive ability
of human being.
No human being will be sacrificed.
We will peacefully end human's history.
This is the euthanasia of human race.
My mother objected that idea.
She disagreed with the rapid evolution of Bioriod.
That's why you killed her.
There used to be two options for Olympus.
Coexistence with Bioriod or evolution
to the new human race.
To make the correct and fair judgment,
Gaia was produced.
Dr. Gillian made great effort to produce Gaia.
Gaia worked in the way Dr. Gillian designed.
If Gaia has a different opinion,
it's impossible to release the virus.
Just then, human started then World War.
this planet was turned to a wasteland.
The Olympus which rules the world became like this.
General Uranus' hatred
towards Bioriod only added to Gaia's anger.
Then, Gaia made the final judgment.
Using Apple Seed to make Bioriod the new master race,
and erase human race from the history.
You used me.
You used me as the decoy to make Briareos obedient.
Our effort is only
to make Gaia to come to the conclusion.
Gaia is a hoax.
This is the fate of human, Deunan!
As soon as I press this button,
D-Tank on top of Tarutarus will explode.
Virus will spread all over the world.
Stop there, old men!
It's 984G, please act as soon as possible!
The button has no use now.
What are you doing, Athena?
Bioriod was created to prevent the destruction
of human race.
Did you forget that?
Bioriod was set to obey the orders of humans.
We are not Bioriod anymore.
Please call us the "New Human".
Athena, this is Gaia's decision!
It's the rage against Uranus's rebellion,
the punishment to human being's atrocity.
General Uranus gave up the rebellion just a moment ago.
He is seeking to coexist with us peacefully.
General Uranus did?
This event, Gaia would not have not known.
Deunan, Gaia no longer exists here.
Gaia doesn't exist anymore?
The vehemence of human race is decreasing.
Gaia should have reconsidered the judgment.
But these old men stopped Gaia,
working on their own will.
Athena you are pretty smart.
New human is really perfect.
By stopping Gaia,
your life-sustain system would be affected also.
That's right.
We are going to step out of history together with human race.
The multi-legged cannon?
All multi-legged cannons
are proceeding toward Olympus headquarter!
The multi-legged cannons
are waling toward the top of Tarutarus!
No one can stop them now.
All ESWAT Land Mates move out now!
Attack the cannons!
Stop them by all means!
The defense system of D-Tank will hold, right?
If hit by multi-legged cannon at zero distance,
it still will break.
The most powerful sword against the perfect shield,
It's a tragedy to worship power.
At this speed, they will reach Tarutarus in 15 minutes.
How about the evacuation of citizens?
We are trying our best.
That's the top priority.
Once the cannons enter no-man's zone,
attack them immediately!
No 7 cannon is the control center of all cannons.
Hitomi!
Hitomi...
I am sorry, grandpas.
If you send control abort signal
from the the control box inside No 7,
all cannons will stop.
But don't ever destroy it!
No 7 has to be stopped manually.
The password for control abort is hitomi.
Briareos
Deunan, we have a promise.
Deunan, time to go. Jump...
You won't make it.
Human race will only make the planet perish.
Deunan, human race cannot turn back any more.
Why not let the new human bear
the sin of the human race?
We will survive even it's not an utopia.
We will shape our own future using our own hands.
Deunan.
Not good, they have no weakness anywhere.
Multi-legged cannon is now 2000 meters from Tarutarus!
We cannot hurt them at all!
Jilas Captain, we are approaching No 7! Cover us!
No 7 is...
The one in the middle.
Concentrate your attack on the legs of No 6 and No 8!
How about the No 5 in front?
Don't worry about that one.
Concentrate all of your firepower on No 6 and No 8!
No 6 is stopped!
Good.
How about No 8?
That's the one. I will attract its fire.
Deunan you approach it from below.
Understood.
Briareos
Deunan
Multi-legged cannons has reached Tarutarus.
They started to climbing towards the top.
Deunan the time is up.
Multi-legged cannon No 3 is approaching the top.
There's no way to stop it.
How come...
Why...
Briareos
Deunan, let go of my hand...
No, I can't do such a thing.
Hurry, enter the password!
Mother...
They stopped.
All multi-legged cannons has stopped. D-Tank is safe.
Briareos
Deunan... Hitomi...
How about the grandpas?
Oh...
The the last letter of the access code...
It's entrusted... it's entrusted to us now.
Nothing has changed.
It must be the unchanging
that added to human race's sins.
Even so, I will continue to fight.
For our children,
for the true new human race...