In the year of King Tai, Ming Dynasty
The eunuches held the real power of
the development
They built up different departments
to reinforce their power
The whole country was under their control
East Chamber was the most powerful
and arrogant intelligent bureau
In order to get rid of those opposing power
They recruited many heartless
and cruel soldiers with high pay
To form a cold-blooded Black Arrow Troop
They were under severe training secretly
There was an arsenal under the East Chamber
It is responsible to design new
killing weapons
They used the prisoners for test
Let me go!
You shameless bastards!
God will punish you
Come out
I'm a government officer
you can't kill me
And you
Let's go
Plum Blossom Sun Shooting Arrow
Dogs Teeth Arrow
Phoenix Tail Arrow
The head Eunuch Tsao Siu Yan
After appointing himself
the head on the East Chamber
He controlled the Emperor
and the whole government
He tried every means to get rid
of those who went against him
What he wanted was a kingdom of himself
He set up a court and collected Information
from many different sources
Those who were against Tsao
Would be arrested and executed
with terrible punishment
Everybody was afraid
of the East Chamber
The whole country was covered
with frights and anxiety
You Excellency, he is the Military Secretary
Yang Yu-hin
What secret do we know about him?
On the 4th of April
he and the secreataries of 3 other department...
wanted to submit an impeachment against
the East Chamber
He pleaded the Emperor to close
Your Excellency
please give your judgement
Your Excellency, here is his impeachment
Secretary Yang
Damn
You've misunderstood us
We're faithful to the Emperor
Your frame to us would scare our Majesty
Aren't you afraid of death?
It's a royal order that eunuches
aren't allowed to involve in politics
So as to avoid you freaks
to mess up the country
Now you slaugher the officials
You're the one who should be dead
How dare you?
Execution
Yes
Yang, I don't think you know
the situation well
Give me the military power
Then I'll let you live
It's so ridiculous that
the government of Ming dynasty
is controlled by you dogs
No one can take over military power
without imperial permission
Stop dreaming
Officer
Give Officer Yang a permission as he wanted
Tsao, because of you bastard
Ming Dynasty is hopeless
He committed suicide
Although Yang was dead
I'm afraid his fellows
would go to his right hand Chow Wai-on
Protect Yang's children to the frontier
I'm sure Chow'd try hard to save them
Yes, sir
This is the Royal Order
The traitor Ex-Military Secretary
Yang Yu-hin
Is to be executed at noon
Tsao Siu Yan killed
the whole family of Yang
but the son and daughter
of Yang were interitionally left
In the Autumn of the same year
they were exited
Tsao orderd the Black Arrow Troop
to tail them secretly
What he wanted was to kill
Yang's right hand, Chow Wai-on
So as to terminate
the remained power of Yang
Kiddo, are you fine?
What the hell it is? Not even a tree
It's so hot
My holy God, I, Yau Mo-yin
swear in front of this sword
I must save Yang's children
All is ready, let's go
Go!
To get out of the boundary
we'd pass Tsi, Turk, Hai-ku 3 places
You divide into 3 teams
I will give order in the central
They can never escape from us!
Your Excellency, the troops are all ready
What shall we do now?
From here to the boundary,
we'd pass Tsi Turk, Hai-ku 3 places
There are steep atopes and cliffs!
I think, Tsao must hide his troop here
to trap us
There is a dried river bed at the West
Let's take risk, to give him a raid
OK, let's go this way
President
nothing happened in these 3 days
Chow has been the right hand of Yang
He could be the coach of 800,000
imperial soldiers
Because of Yang's recommendation
Thus, thinking of such relationship
Chow would come to save the kids
I am thirsty
Drink it
Uncle, can you give us
something to drink?
Get lost, get lost
Come over... open your hands
Thank you
No hurry, drink it slowly
Sister, drink it!
No, you drink it
The president really knows everything
Set them free, now
No, we can't defy government's order
If not, let's kill him
We come to save
But not to kill
If you want to kill
let's kill the dogs of the East Chamber
Set them free and leave with us
Otherwise, those bastards won't let you go
Stop puzzling
You've no choice, hurry up
Sister
Kiddo
Enemies
Protect the kids
They are small potatos only
our large hasn't shown up yet
Kiddo
Your Excellency, Chow finally comes
The twins Sword
Sister, I'm so scared
The Black Flag Arrow Troop?
Sister, where are you?
Just follow me
The arrows are like a storm.
Save the kids and leave at once
Shit! The soldiers are coming towards us
Stay where you are
Your Excellency,
it wasn't Chow who came
They seem to be rascals
Brother, we are safe!
Chow Wai-on is such a wise man
The people come for the children
are trobbers only
Let them go first
I want to make a deed set at them all!
This is the Dragon Gate
I've made a date in the Dragon Inn with Chow
We'll leave the frontier together
We're carrying the kids
and the soldiers are after us
I think
We'd go to the Dragon Gate
along the river bed
Just do what you said
Yang Kwan is a main road
Shang, take 500 soldiers
to guard this gate
Yes
There are many lanes to Yu Mun Kwan
Send the best soldiers to block all exits
Although the Dragon Gate is heavily armed
I think Chow'd take this risk
And leave from the Dragon Gate
with the rascals
Go there by taking the path
I'll follow with the Black Flag Troop
It's wise of you, Your Excellency
Let's go
Yes, sir
Spicy Meat Bun
Three-taels
why don't you send me the wine?
It's coming...
Damn weather, the wind made me so dirty
Good morning, sir
What? You don't want to serve me?
No, if it's not you guarding the border
We can't even do business here
Fetch me some wine
OK, I'll go right now
Sir, here comes the wine
See, your nickname suits you well
Exactly 3 taels of wine per cup.
Not a drop less
My grandpa gave me this name
Spicy Meat Bun
Come here
Where is your boss?
She is dealing some business upstairs
You want to leave the border
through my secret tunnel...
Or want to sleep with me?
Tiger, you can only choose one of them
Choose carefully
I've made it
Men are all sex-oriented
You want it whenever you want it
and leave whenever you finish it
Cut the crap
Just relax
Come on
I want the answer, tunnel or me?
I want both
It's too greedy of you
I've checked it. I'm not interested at all
The Willow Dart?
I'll get 100 taels by sending you
out of the frontier
But I'll get 400 taels by sending you to hell
I really don't know what to choose
Here is fresh meat for the buns
The boss's coming.
We're waiting for you to extinguish our fire
Eating mutton will make you have more fire
It'll make you hot. Bastard
Maybe you can help us with this?
Damn you
I don't eat mutton
I want to eat you
Go to hell
Why not eat me? I'm bigger in size
Damn you
Who is he?
You're always interested in men
How about me?
I always treat you as well as I can
Good looking
He is Chow, a wanted criminal.
He was a coach of the Imperial Army
He doesn't look like a coach
Yes, he doesn't
He's in big trouble with
the East Chamber
They want his head
East Chamber?
Yes
It's nothing
Mind your tongue
Tiger's head worths 500 taels?
Meaner, ask the chef, Duo
to keep the head of the lamb
You just care about lamp but not me
How dare you do this
in front of your fellows?
You'll give them a bad example
Why is there blood on your dress?
No. There is no blood
Look
Really?
You're having period?
Haven't you seen it before?
Ask your mother then
She passed away long long time ago
Go ask your sister then
Come over here,
I'll teach you a good lesson
Come over here...
Come if you have guts
Damn you
Welcome.
How many rooms do you want?
We want 3 of your best
Okay, take a rest first
Your period doesn't seem to be regular
Tell me earlier next time
Time to go back, we're just here
May I help you, sir?
Thanks, I'll do it myself
This way please, this is clean
With less wind and sand
What do you want to eat?
Give us some bread
Why not some wine?
OK, give us 3 catties
I'll get it now
Listen
This is my place, everything is mine
If you violate the rules
You can never
trade your pilfered goods here again
Damn you
I'll do it
The Dragon Mountain is famous for its rain
Why?
How can it rain in such a sunny day?
I think you're a stranger here
Where are you from?
We came from the south
To the north
How long will you stay?
We'll leave tomorrow
Spicy meat buns...
Beautiful
How sweet of you
We don't know where they are from
Watch out for them
One is soldier, one is wounded
The one in black should be their leader
- She's a woman
- A woman?
I can tell she is female because...
She didn't show interest in me
There is something wrong with the meat
Don't eat
What is it?
There is something wrong anyway
Not showing respect
Go
Let's go
Do you have any medicine?
No
It's getting dark. Light up the candles
Mistress, what meat is it?
Spicy Meat
What is spicy meat?
Haven't you heard of it?
The name of spicy meat appeared in a novel.
Mrs Suen sold it
Mrs Suen opened an inn which robbed
But mine is Dragon Inn
But you don't look like a jinx
Really? My name is Jade King
What a pity that it's hard for
a stone to turn to jade
In this world
There're many things unworthy of the name
and many people got empty brains
You're pretty
You too
But I'm sure I know you better
So you should let me know you better
I don't think it's a big deal actually
Why not ask some men here
that'd be fun
What! You think I'm afraid of men?
I've messed with more men than
you've seen
Just look at you, you're still a virgin
Aren't you?
Where is the hen hurrying to?
Let's see how you light up
a candle on the roof
Who are you? Why are you laughing?
May I know where the Dragon Inn is?
Here it is
Are you the boss?
Just call me Jade King
Jade! What a good name
Beautiful name
How about me?
Any room?
Handsome guy
Are you a businessman?
I want a room
How long will you stay?
Do I look like I've no money?
I'm just afraid that
you'll leave without saying goodbye
You know,
Dragon Mountain is famous for its rain
Even the most
vigorous animal scares of it
So we're the same people
we should keep in touch
Glad to make friends with you.
I may need your help some day
It depends on how smart you are
Miss Yau
He is here
This is my inn, please make yourself at home
Wearing foreign dress for
foreign customers tonight?
I've told you to wash that flag
See, I got mud all over me
This must be a woman
How do you know?
As you said
only women won't be interested in you
But he is different
His eyes didn't show interest on me
but his heart did
I don't think his heart
is interested in you
I can listen to your flute again
Go to work
Don't just play that song
Uncle Chow
Poor kids, you suffered a lot
He is Ho Fu
Thank you for your help
I really appreciate for all your kindness
Don't mention it
This is called Dog's teeth Arrow
It's produced by the East Chamber
I'd seen when I worked for the government
So you'd better pay much attention
to it in future
When can we get out of here?
As soon as possible
Chun, take the money
Hide up and meet your family later
Sir, I can't take this
This inn is so complicated
Pack up and leave here
as soon as possible
Mistress
I know you will come
You're really clever
I don't need you to flatter me
I just want to know about the weather here
Come inside
This room is nice and quiet
No room is nice
in a deserted place like this
What tea do you want to have?
Tuckanhoe or something else?
What kind of flower is this?
It's beautiful
You think it's white lotus?
It's turnip flower
White lotus can only be found
on Snow Mountain
Try the tea
When will you leave?
Tonight
I'm afraid you can't
Why?
Don't you know
the weather of the desert?
Please advise me
This's raining season
the weather is unpredictable
It'll rain cats and dogs even
the sun is on
This's the only hotel here
You can't reach the gate even
you can leave here
I think you know
whether it's sunny or rainy day
It depends on who that asks
The rain'll keep you here
just stay for a few more days
Though the weather is unpredictable
we can't stay forever
Seems we're connected in some ways
Please help us
You're leaving?
- I've two children with me
- They're hostages?
Mistress, please lead us the way
It depends on which way you want to take
The general of the border is my friend
I think I can help you with my reputation
But if you want to leave secretly...
Let me think...
I'm okay. Weapons are ruthless
We're friends now. And I'll repay you
Come again tonight
I have to leave tonight
You can't. I'll wait
Block the gate
Damn you. Fool
The latch is useless, move the table
Open the door...
Who is it? We just closed the door
Don't open it, let him die in the rain
Open up, quick
Stop knocking, bastard
If you knock again, I'll...
What's the matter?
Are you deaf?
Why didn't you open the door?
We're in trouble
3 branch heads from
the East Chamber have come
Damn you
My books are all wet!
Are you blind? Just close the door!
Go and shut the door
Boss
He is calling you
Can't you see I'm busy?
Any good room?
No, all full
Please ask them to move out
I just do whatever I like
Not tall enough
I don't do things I don't like
Take it back
You bitch
What did you say?
Money isn't my concern
Most important of all
I want a comfortable accommodation
I'm doing business too
I don't care about the money
You've messed up my place
So what to do then?
Count the loss
And I'll pay you by triple?
Good room? There is one, come on
It is raining cats and dogs
we can't leave now
We'll wait
Take the luggage in
We have limited rooms but numerous guests
How long will you stay?
The weather is unpredictable
See how long can this gold pay for?
You must be tired
Sir, please have some tea
Any strangers checked in these days?
Are you looking for someone?
We businessmen should be careful
and get rid of trouble
I just want to know
if there is any trouble around
Have some tea
If there is any, I won't open an inn here
Sorry
This is a very special tea
The taste is nothing special
But you have something special
on your mind
Don't you think Chow Wai On
will take this route?
Go and check
Meaner...
Boss
Why you acted before my order?
Shadows are found everywhere
But they're not our men
We haven't taken any action yet
Go and check carefully.
Watch out for the money box
Yes
What a troubled world it is
Thieves'd watch out for other thieves.
Damn it
What is he singing?
He is barbarian.
He is humming barbarian song
I'll dig your eyes out
So you can't see
I'll peel off your skin
so you can't wear
I'll chop your head off
so you can't live
Don't make any trouble
Somebody is on the roof
Forget it
We'll leave right after the rain stops
Who was killed by the thunder?
We are all here
Good job! Kill your tribe
Thank god
Where are Bill Chow and Shao Tong?
I'll go and find them
No! It'll alarm our enemies
The rain is so heavy, we can't leave
Neither can they
Right
Look at the sword under the lamp
after drunk...
When can we live in peace?
I don't want to wait anymore!
Just stay calm
Anxiety won't help
But waitng won't help either
Lower your voice
If the eunuches come
we'll be in danger
What'll we do
if we are trapped in this inn?
Ho, I didn't pay a penny less
There are rules that
we all should follow
Miss Yau, my buddies and I...
make money by risking our lives
To save this two kids...
we've missed many business opportunity
and money
Now the government knows who we are
Damn, we've given all
we have to be a good guy
Well, I'll pay your loss
It sounds reasonable
Make it clean
Sir, did you sleep well last night?
Bull shit
Have a seat
- Shun, clean the tables and chairs
- Yes
Give us some tea
Still didn't get any news
from Bill Chow and Shao Tong?
It's strange!
We can't even find their bodies
There must be something strange
Tony, give them some bread
We don't want bread this morning
Give us a roasted lamb
Roasted lamb
- Do you have roasted lamb in desert?
- Yes
They're fat lambs!
We just killed two last night
Give us one
You too? Ok, coming...
The fight last night was tiring enough
And now we've to work this morning
Go and get the weapons
You are good looking
From your forehead
There is florid
I can tell you're having good luck
Thank you.
Hope your fortune telling comes true
If you don't mind,
can I see your hands?
Sure
From your influence line
you were a government officer 2 years ago
What're you working now?
Anywhere! When there is rough road
I'd make it flat
When there is tree blocking the road
I'd remove it
That's why
your influence line isn't that smooth
I don't think I've the luck
to be gov't official, but I think you have
Why?
In such a desert
Ordinary citizens won't wear
officer's boots
Don't be nervous! You're an officer
So you should know
something happened in town
Which one are you talking about?
The Secretary
of the Military Dept. Yang was killed
His corpse was hanged and his
whole family was killed too
Pal, do you know who did it?
I don't know
Really?
The water is boiling
Sir... oh no...
Mister
Can you tell me is he a lady killer?
Yes! His eyes attract women
Really?
The ones who killed Yang
are some ruthless bastards
It's hot, let it cool down
Mistress
This is for the broken table.
Buy a new one
I don't think it's enough
Give us the food! We're starving!
Pal, you are a man
of righteousness and guts
May I know your name?
I'm a wanderer, name is meaningless to me
Let's cheers for this nameless world
OK! I'll drink this wine with you!
Cheers!
- Please
Here's the roasted lamb
Mistress, how about our lamb?
It'd be roasted one by one
But first come first serve
Make it half then
Dao
Cut the lamb in half
How? Straight or cross?
As you like, just make it half
I wonder what relationship Chow has
with this inn?
I think we'd better take action
as soon as possilble
Let's ambush them tonight
Bravo! The rain has stopped!
We may go now
Don't panic, they will discover it easily
The larget is so great
We are not clear about the outside world
We have 2 kids too.
We can't go as fast as they can
Once this inn is owned by thieves
there must be some secret tunnel
Let's search it tonight
It was dangerous!
Quickly I fixed up the mess
otherwise I'd have lost if there're a fight
No, some hocus is put!
Drink this
Tonight, why no we...
What shall we do tonight?
What?
You are all fools!
If we want to leave here
We must get rid of those bastards first
Ho Fu, Iron, you two'll attack
from both sides
Mo-yan will attack in the midle
Cha's room is at the corner
and has just one door
Okay, let me do it