Presented by IM Pictures
Produced by Popcorn Film
Producer
HAN Seong-gu
There once lived a mean
cuckoo guy named Young-Dal.
His wife died giving birth to
their daughter Il-mae.
Since then, it was my mother who
breast fed her and raised her.
From our birth on,
she was my destined partner
who stole half of my milk.
That's how
my first love began.
Crazy First Love
Teacher, can we stay closer?
You punks! Keep your distance!
You all are a bunch of animals
with too much testosterone.
Tes... what? What's that?
Joo, Young-dal must keep
his words with Sohn Tae-il!
My dear ladies!
You all know me, right?
Sophomore at Kang High School
Class 7, number 58
SOHN Tae-il!!
Promises are supposed to be kept.
Especially, words from a teacher
who is a role model!
How can he break his promise?
At this moment,
In the presence of Buddha, Jesus
and all other Gods in the world,
I accuse Mr. JOO Young-dal,
a teacher at Kang High,
of breaking his solemn promise!
10 years ago,
our teacher Mr. JOO promised me,
"Just wait till you have some
hairs on your balls!
When that happens, you can marry
my daughter Il-mae!"
Il-mae! My pubic hair started
growing when I was thirteen!
So, I ran to your dad
right away.
"Look! I have the pubic hair
Now, hand over Il-mae
like you promised!"
But, what did you say? Teacher?
"That's not it!
It's just hair attached to your body.
You wanna see my real ones?"
Fine. Let's just say it was just hair.
But now, tell me what
covers me down there.
You wanna call them a bunch
of black threads?
Teacher, do you wanna
check it out?
Show us! Show us!
Il-mae! Look!
Do they look like threads to you?
Testosterone is a type of
male hormone...
that can turn a normal kid like Tae-il
into a wild animal in a snap!
- Ready?
- Ready.
Let's go!
What the...?
- Boss!
- Kneel down!
Was it you that broke into
my territory and beat up
my boys in open daylight?
and beat up my boys?
What do you want?
I'm a righteous warrior!
You little shit.
You're from Kang High?
So am I. Is that why you're here?
Cut the bullshit.
Are you gonna take me in or not?
How's Mr. JOO?
Why the hell did you bring up
his name?
Stay still!
Teacher, what's happening to
our school?
I'm a gangster now, but
I graduated high school though.
Teach them a lesson!
Especially that curly hair!
48th year class
Byun, Kang-chul!
Yes, sir.
Get down!
What?
Because of little shits like you
these kids wanna be gangsters.
Listen! Urgent news!
- Tae-il from Kang High...
- What about him?
He went to the boss of the market
area and asked him to take him in.
- For real?
- But the boss told Il-mae's
dad on him
and now he's getting
his ass whipped.
Pants down!
On your stomach!
Do you guys hear my heart?
It's crying out in pain.
Ouch! Ouch!
If my heart hurts this much, then
how would your parents feel?
Right, Tae-il?
You haven't changed a bit, sir.
I'm so happy to see you again.
Your mother works so hard
selling fish at the marketplace to...
Feed me and to send me to school.
So what?
You little brat!
Are you giving me dirty look
during my admonition?
You wanna lose your eyes?
Sir, I apologize.
Even an animal like a crow
appreciates the love of its parents.
Then what bird are you, teacher?
You didn't keep your words.
What did you say?
You think I sold fish at the market
to make you a gang?
Il-mae! What did you eat to grow?
Milk.
What kind of milk? Cow milk?
No. Your breast milk.
After all I've done for you,
how could you seduce my son?
Ma'am, you got it wrong.
Il-mae didn't do anything.
She ruined my boy's life...
Go inside.
Teacher, why don't you just expel him
from school?
He's only causing more trouble
staying in school...
Look at me.
You can't even look at me.
Pretty embarrassing, huh?
Face is busted by a gang and
ass is whipped by my dad,
and your back is beaten
by your mother.
Let me see your back!
Why do you live like this?
I'm gonna show him...
how his unkept promise
brings me down.
You're crazy!
What am I supposed to do?
You rank in top 3,000 nationwide
but I'm not even in top 300,000.
And everyday, you get prettier
and I get uglier.
You're slipping away from me
and... Shit!
There's nothing I can do
What am I supposed to do with you?
Shut up! Stop whining!
...even when you're angry,
you look beautiful.
What?
When I think of your pretty face,
I can't control myself!
I can't sleep nor eat!
When I open a book,
the words turn into your face!
You're so goddamn pretty and my
body is boiling with hot blood.
What am I supposed to do?
I've never seen a student
as unruly as Sohn Tae-il.
And what's worse is that
our naive students worship him,
and it'll keep creating someone
just like him.
it's time to pull out our swords
and eliminate the bad wolf!
We agree with you, Mr. Principal.
Let's hear from his homeroom teacher.
Every teenager has a bit of wolf
within himself.
To achieve peace in our school,
we should take this chance
to emasculate them all!
Even the sheepish kids!
Testosterone!!
Teacher, you'll pick a husband
for Il-mae through open contest?
For real? Awesome!
Shit!
Teacher! Isn't she Tae-il's girl?
Since he entered high school,
suspended from school 3 times!
Disciplinary confinement 7 times!
Lewdness in public
Intoxication, unlawful entry
and attempted kidnapping
Plus, he's in the bottom
with an IQ of 148 and
preoccupied with joining a gangster.
If you were in my shoes, would
you give your daughter to him?
No way!
Teacher!
What are the requirements?
Requirements? It can be anyone
Just improve your scores
up to my daughter's.
The day you bring me
your report card,
you will marry my daughter.
Understood?
Yes, sir!
Yes? You got a question?
As a man to man! One on one!
Are you challenging me?
Why? You scared?
Where are you going?
You challenged me!
Here I come!
You little punk!
You're nothing!
You can't even swing one punch.
How dare you want my daughter?
- Teacher!
- I'm here.
- That's water.
I'd rather die with you
than lose her to someone.
You are unbelievable
You said you're gonna be a fisherman,
but can't even swim!
You're hopeless!
Teacher, what do I have to do?
Please tell me what I have to do.
to beat 300,000 kids in 2 years.
Please tell me!
Give it up!
I'll die if you ask me to die
Please tell me!
It won't happen to someone like you
Teacher, please tell me!
I said, it won't.
It's impossible! Impossible!
Ouch! What are you hitting me?
It stings!
Sleep only 3 hours a day.
Then, in 3 days, you will nosebleed.
If you nosebleed everyday
till you graduate,
Then my girl will be yours.
I guarantee!
Teacher, I'll nosebleed everyday.
Il-mae is mine.
You can't give her
to anybody else. Ok? Dad?
I got it.
Gees... You're so heavy.
You see the spot I'm on
Marked with white paint?
Yes, teacher!
This is the spot,
where you freshmen's proud 6 year
senior SOHN Tae-il fell down
bleeding from both nostrils with
college exam scores in his hand.
That's when I found out
a man can survive
way too much nosebleeding.
You all know the proud tradition
of our Kang High, right?
Yes, sir!
Say it!
One! We don't have
guidance department!
And?
One! We're the worst enemy
of the Red Cross!
That's how it happened!
When Tae-il made top 3,000,
and got early accepted to Seoul
National University,
our principal said to the
Department of Education,
"Our students study so hard and
nosebleed everyday,
they don't have any blood to
donate!
From now on, Kang High is the
worst enemy of the Red Cross!"
Goddamn persistent kid!
Worse than a leech!
Father in-law!
Let's set the wedding date...
dad?
First, go to college.
Welcome! Welcome!
This is Seoul National University!
My school!
I got into the law school,
like you told me to.
So, let me marry her now!
Il-mae's college expels students
who get married before graduating.
You're joking, right?
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Now I'm in a law school, he's gonna
ask me to pass the bar exam,
Then finish the judicial trainings
And after that,
who knows what excuse
he's gonna come up with.
SOHN Tae-il!! Stop right there!
Where are we going?
Let's do it! Let's make a baby!
Are you crazy?
What?
I can't betray my dad like that!
What about me, then?
Math workbook pg.216, #14-8!
What are all critical points,
if there are any, of a function
where k (t) equals to one divide by
the square root of "t" minus
squared positive one?
Answer!
its critical point is
(0, 1).
Buddha, the God of Mercy...
Name, SOHN Tae-il!
Il-mae!
Is he ok?
Exactly then, you know
what your father said to me?
"C'mon, Tae-il!
Just a bit more!"
What am I? His slave?
If I keep listening to your dad,
then I'm gonna die as a virgin!
Let's go in! What the...!
You kidnap my daughter
in open daylight?
You crazy punk!
We're gonna have a baby first.
Have what?
Dad! Tae-il!
Stop right there! You little shit.
You think you can run away?
Kneel down!
Release him.
We have laws in this country!
You think you can get away with
abduction and physical assault?
I've lived well without any laws.
You piece of shit didn't pass
the bar exam yet, so what the hell
do you know about the law?
This is your mother in law.
Give her a bow.
Mom! Look how bad he's treating
one and only son in law.
If she were alive,
she'd be in her early 40's
But I only remember her as
a high school girl who likes fast food.
You mean...
That's right.
We both were in high school
when she got pregnant.
I don't like you! No, I fear you!
You're just like how I used to be.
You don't know anything about her.
About her pain and suffering...
What you see is all you know.
Is that real love?
Bull shit!
You're just pleasing yourself.
Look at me!
I loved Il-mae's mom to death...
but she was gone at 18!
If you really love her, then you
have to know how to protect her!
Tae-il!
Yes, sir!
Il-mae isn't going anywhere.
I swear I'll keep her safe.
So, can she stay with me just
a little longer?
Can you please leave her with me
just a little longer?
Teacher...
I'll protect her!
Up until I graduate and
pass the bar exam,
I won't even touch her hair!
Thanks.
Kiss... I'll allow kissing.
Nonsense! If I kiss her, then
I'd wanna touch her boobs.
And if I touch her boobs, then I'll cross
the line that I must not cross.
Until the day you give Il-mae's hand
to me, I'll keep her intact, and virgin!
Tae-il!
What a lie!
She is a slut.
She slept with me a lot
when she's in high school.
She wasn't even a virgin
when we first had sex.
She already had abortions,
even five times!
And her tube got so damaged
that she can't even have a baby.
How do you know her so well?
How? She's my first love
and so am I to her.
Out my window, I can see
Il-mae's room well.
That's my room.
Well done, Tae-il.
I protect my girl, sir!
Il-mae, I had a really good time tonight.
I'm sorry about...
That's ok. Your friend Tae-il
always adds thrill to our date.
I don't see him.
Tae-il! You!!
Shit!
I'm gonna get wrinkled and die
as a virgin without kissing a man
Why don't you go for Tae-il?
Tae-il?
Do you really love me?
If you really love me,
if you can hear my heart,
then please look at me.
Stop that gibberish.
You really gonna be like this?
You're an animal with
too much testosterone!
Patience!
Other boys? I hooked up
Yonsei University boys
with girls from Sookmyung University.
Only Ewha girls here!
I'm the only one who stands up to pee.
So no need to worry, sir!
How do you manage to
prepare for the bar exam?
I brought everything with me.
I'm confident in memorizing
with my IQ, I gotta go, bye!
How do you say "Eat it while
it's warm" in local dialect?
Slurp it while it's hot.
Let's see, where is Il-mae's
cold medicine?
It's her shampoo, snacks.
Where is it? Oh, here it is.
Hello! It's time for my girl
to take her medicine!
Il-mae!
She went swimming with a boy
she met in the lobby.
I can't even leave her alone
for 2 seconds!
Don't you think it's way
too much sexy?
Not at all. I have to knock him.
out with one punch!
Il-mae! JOO Il-mae!
SOHN Tae-il! Let's see
who's gonna win this time!
Where is that bastard?
What... what are you doing?
Thanks, Tae-il.
For... for what?
For looking after me till now.
You don't have to do it anymore.
This is our last trip of
our college years.
I want to make a memorable moment
with you! Right now!
Here?
Tae-il.
Teacher, please forgive me!
Wake up!
Too much testosterone!
Cover up yourself well
before you come out.
Stop right there!
I can't move anyway.
Tae-il, if you walk out on me now
then it's over.
You might never see me again!
Do you hear me?
Calm down and come out!
After giving you your medication,
I've got a lot to study tonight!
You fool! What's so important
about that stupid promise?
I need you... right now...
There might not be next time...
Stupid...
- Are you telling the truth?
- Yes, sir!
You finally did it!
Everyone! Tae-il passed
the level 1 bar exam.
Sir, Il-mae is really mine, right?
Of course! She's all yours!
Where are you?
Are you with her?
My whereabouts is a top secret.
I'm preparing a present for her.
Ouch... Be careful, will you?
Alright. We're giving you a cool
finishing stitches.
We can't stitch it up like this.
Relax, will you?
Relax!
What's that sound?
Did you get into a fight?
Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine. Teacher,
Il-mae is mine, right?
Everyone, bow to our teacher!
We welcome you, sir.
Teacher!
Tae-il!
Why are you crying
on this happy day?
- Then why are you crying?
- Because I'm so proud of you!
How much did you nosebleed
this time?
Not too much. Only about a bucket
this big... 2 of it...
You did well.
C'mon. Get up.
So, where is your bride?
My bride?
Yes, your bride!
Of course!
My bride just got off work.
So my bride should be here soon.
Oh, I see...
you're already getting excited
just thinking about her, huh?
Teacher! Please, don't touch it.
Don't be shy.
She's here!
Hello?
Tae-il... What are you doing?
Tae-il!
Congratulations!
Tae-il passed
level 1 bar exam
Did you really?
JOO Il-mae! How lonely you've been,
spending so many nights,
all by yourself! Open it.
This is my heart. From now on,
I'll breathe if you tell me to breathe,
And I'll stop if you tell me to stop.
Stupid! You're so stupid!
Stupid! Stupid!
Teacher!
Dad!
- For Tae-il!
Always wait for your return...
your apartment!
I call you because I miss you!
And I hear your lovely voice...
Stop!
This is the happiest day in my life
since the birth of
my daughter Il-mae!
Since we're in full swing of
celebration,
let's have the engagement
ceremony for SOHN Tae-il
and JOO Il-mae right now!
Dad!
Yes?
I wanna get married!
Sure! I'm so proud of Tae-il,
my SOHN in law!
It's not Tae-il!
It's not him
He's not the one I want to marry!
Teacher, you're just joking
with me, right?
You're worried that
I'm gonna mess up the 2nd exam,
And that's why you're doing this.
Shut up!
Please tell me this isn't real.
Tell me Il-mae wasn't serious.
What did you tell me before?
"Sir, I protect my woman!"
Well... you did really well.
I trusted you with my daughter...
Teacher.
You're worthless!
Even if this is the end of the world,
you can't do this to him.
You know he lived his whole life
just for you.
You're killing him.
But, dad, I slept with that man.
Many many times!
What?
I'm not a virgin anymore.
That's why I can't go back to Tae-il.
You worthless shit.
We did our best.
Okay, let's make a contract.
Thank you. I'll convey your message
to our president.
They want to contract
the agreement.
Il-mae! Il-mae! Get off me!
Let's go!
What are you doing?
It all started when we came to Seoul.
So let's go back to Pusan!
- Tae-il!
- Come on!
Let's go back to Pusan!
What am I? A joke?
You think you can just show up
like this and
cause all this ruckus and I'd
go with you?
Il-mae, I love you! I really do!
You don't know what love is!
- Il-mae!
- Excuse me, sir!
- Get off me!
- Sir!
Il-mae, don't do this. Think about it
one more time.
Do you know how I raised you?
Why are you acting like this?
- Let's go, ok?
- Get off me!!
Tae-il! Tae-il!
If you don't go with me, then
I'm gonna kill myself right here!
I already gave you my heart.
I can't live without you!
Don't be stupid. I'm not going.
Il-mae! Il-mae!
Tae-il!
Teacher, the sky looks
awfully blue today!
Tae-il!
I can't believe she's doing this!
Now what's gonna happen to him?
What am I supposed to do now?
You awake? You know how long
you've been passed out?
3 days!
You really scared me this time.
I prepared some seafood porridge.
Kang-chul left his gang and
opened up a sushi restaurant.
He made this for you using
only the freshest ingredients!
Too hot, huh?
Should I cool it down for you?
Give me a cigarette!
What? You got a problem?
No. I heard in Japan a father and
daughter in law smoke together.
I say, where are the morals
and ethics in that?
I mean, it's about liberation.
Cultural liberation!
We need to adopt that thinking
too, right?
- So what are you gonna do?
- About what?
About Il-mae!
We'll get her back. We will.
How the hell are you gonna get her back
when her heart has changed?
First, we gotta find out
who that guy is
Il-mae!
English, French, Japanese and now,
Chinese, too?
Wow, I'd better study harder
to be your husband
Who beat you?
I don't know. A woman came
into the bathroom and...
Il-mae!
How about a hot cup of coffee?
I'll get it.
Nonsense. I'll get it. Wait here.
Relax!
Come on, spill it out!
I'm sorry! Please stop.
I have hemorrhoid.
You should listen to your buddy
if he tells you to stop.
No, you're worse. If you're
his friend, you should've stopped him.
- Look! Look over there!
- Hold on. I should punish...
We got the wrong guy.
Shit!
- Why didn't you tell me earlier!!
- You didn't listen!
Would you like to order?
In a minute. Calm down!
Really?
Bastard! What?
You must know your enemy to win!
What's there to know? He's a rich boy
with tons of money! Fuck.
Fuck? Watch your language!
What am I? Your friend?
LEE Seung-no! Age, 30!
According to my investigation,
he emigrated to US at the age of 12,
received masters in psychology, then
graduated Harvard Law School,
received MBA at Wharton and
returned to Korea in 1999.
Impressive! Level 1 bar exam is
nothing compared to him.
Are you on my side or his?
Of course I'm on your side.
In 1999, he established
Phoenix Software, which
exports various games to
international markets.
In 2001, he was awarded for his
excellence in his industry.
Any weaknesses?
Neuschwanstein, or sometimes
it's known as New Swan Castle.
King Ludwig ll, a fan of Wagner,
built this castle for his lover.
But sadly, they never lived
together, right?
I'm different.
I won't spend my life only building
a castle for someone I love
Il-mae, I love you!
Cuckoo! Cuckoo! Hey, look at that
cuckoo flying over there!
You only know one side of a coin.
2002 Sisa English pg. 482.
King Ludwig ll and Wagner were
gay lovers.
Eventually, Ludwig destroyed
the castle, missing him
Why don't you go look for
a young boy?
Tae-il! You!!!
Take a good look at these!
A dog collar... At the office...
In the car... this one is outdoor...
Do you see now?
He has so many women,
besides you!
He's about quantity. Not quality!
He's not a man. He's a dog!
A dog!
Let's go.
Maybe you're too shocked to
fully understand the situation here.
No. It's you who's not
getting the situation.
I knew he had other women,
but I didn't care. Because I liked him
and that's all it mattered.
I'm sorry about this.
Let's go somewhere else.
Are you crazy?
What are you doing with
this playboy?
I'd rather be with a playboy who
knows how to love me,
than a kid like you who doesn't
even know what love is.
Nice photoshop work.
Pervert.
Fine! You can call me pervert or
whatever you want!
But what about me?
I lived my whole life just for you!
What about me then?
Who are you?
Me? An international referee.
Ready?
Hello?
Teacher, I forgot to tell you
one thing about LEE Seung-no.
He's a master in judo,
aikido and fencing!
Tae-il! Are you ok?
Teacher... he's pretty damn strong!
Tae-il! Tae-il!
Il-mae, I shouldn't say this
as your dad, but...
I think purity of heart is
more important than that of body.
I believe Tae-il loves you for
who you are in your heart.
Can't you just give him
one more chance?
Dad, give me a kiss!
You crazy?
You can't do it, right?
Neither can I. Tae-il is like that.
He's my childhood buddy.
Like a brother.
I can't even kiss him.
Really?
It's too late, dad.
I just want to be his friend.
I'm worried.
He'd never give you up.
There's only one solution.
I should marry Seung-no quickly
Tae-il! Are you out of your mind?
Why are you burning your books?
The reason for my existence was
to marry Il-mae.
Not becoming a judge
or a district attorney.
Tae-il! Tae-il!
Oh my god!
Fire! Fire!
JOO Il-mae, come back to me!
I love you forever.
Come back to me, JOO Il-mae!
JOO Il-mae, come back to me!
JOO... Il-mae!!
"Prepare yourself for death, and
you'll live and prepare yourself
for life and you'll die!"
said General LEE.
Chinese textbook pg.118, line 4!
Love is like a marathon!
I must eat to win!
Merciless bastard!
You can't take her away from me!
Maybe today is the D-day.
They dined at a fancy restaurant
and danced at a jazz bar, right?
Then, he probably gave her
Neuschwanstein and said,
he won't be a fool who
only builds a castle...
then a kiss.
They didn't kiss.
That's not the point!
With a little bit of alcohol and
sweet words, he melts her heart
Then with a seal of love,
the game is over
She becomes his woman.
You really like polar bears that much?
JOO Il-mae!
Tae-il! You're impossible.
Please let her go. Please.
You could have anything in the world.
But she's all I have.
Please let her go. I beg of you.
Il-mae! I never even got a chance
to show you how much I love you.
Just give me one chance!
He looks just like a weasel
Tonight is not the first night
we're sleeping together.
We've done it countless times.
So, don't bother me anymore.
You bitch! Bother you?
I've been bothering you?
How about me?
You think I enjoyed packing
your lunch for 4 years?
And reserving your seat at the library?
Do you think doing your
laundry was fun?
Really?
It's nice to know
how you really felt.
Can I go now?
Get out of my sight!
You make me want to puke!
No, I'll go.
I'm so shamed I wasted my life
chasing after a slut like you!
What? I ask you to go to Seoul
to look after Tae-il and
investigate Il-mae's affairs.
And, now you
return and cry like a girl.
Il-mae went to the hospital.
So, I thought she's gonna see
a gynecologist.
Hospital?
She has the myelodysplastic
syndromes,
the same illness that
took away your wife.
Oh, lord.
Teacher, you're so light.
You got no meat on your legs.
You've gotten so thin.
You need to eat more.
I'm not light.
You've become stronger.
Tae-il.
Yes, teacher.
Are you really ok?
Of course. I'm fine.
It's not a big deal to me
The funny thing is, the date for the
2nd exam is the same date
as Il-mae's wedding date.
Good. There is no reason why
you should attend her wedding.
Go on and do well on your exam
and pass it with flying colors.
Don't worry about me.
I'll pass the exam... get married...
have kids...
then I will come back to see you.
I'll never forget...
all you've done for me.
Alright.
Who is it? Dad?
Dad, Dad!
Tae-il... Tae-il...
Tae-il! SOHN Tae-il!
JOO Il-mae!
Yes?
Eat well and live well!
Eat well and...
don't get sick, ok?
If you do get sick,
don't get too sick. Ok?
You too! Don't get into
any more troubles!
And don't be so stubborn, ok?
Stop worrying about me.
I'll be fine.
Goodbye.
Tae-il! Do you know why
I'm marrying him?
Because he has other women.
He'll easily fall in love again.
Even without me,
he'll continue to live
a happy life!
But, you can't do that.
You'll only think of me
and love me!
Just like my dad!
I can't let you become
like my dad.
Dad, I'm not a bad person,
am I?
Of course not.
Like a flower... like a star...
you're the loveliest girl in the world...
Dad, let's practice the wedding march.
We have to be careful
not to step on my dress.
Alright, alright.
Il-mae!!!
- Tilt your head a bit to the left.
- Turn it just a little.
My love, do you know
what I did today?
I went to the photo studio with
Il-mae and took pictures.
She braided her hair and
wore this really pretty dress.
And we took a picture together.
She was trying to do what
you and I couldn't do.
Do you know what she said to me
as she took her portrait?
She smiled and said,
"Dad, I've a very happy life.
So please don't cry
when you look at this picture."
And she smiled.
My lovely child... my sweet child...
Teacher, you're killing yourself.
Please don't do this.
The 45th Level 2
bar exam center
Begin.
It would be much appreciated
if you'd participated in blood drive.
What the hell are you saying?
Of course it's our duty as his students
to do as much as we can.
- What's going on?
- Get off me!! You bastards!
SOHN Tae-il! You bastard!
How can you take a test right now?
Tae-il, come out here! You know
what Il-mae did for you?
Get off me! She... Tae-il, she's...
Tae-il doesn't understand why.
He's just trying to forget her
because she told him to.
Come on! Step on the accelerator!
He has no clue that she's doing
this for his own sake
For the only person she ever loved...
she wants him to be happy
even when she's not here anymore.
My love, what am I supposed to do?
What can I do?
I now pronounce you to be
husband and wife.
Nonsense!
- Nullify this marriage!
- Nullify! Nullify!
What the hell do you think
you're doing?
Ladies and gentlemen, this girl
right here, is a horrible person!
This stupid girl...
She's suffering from the same illness
which took her mom away...
So I can live happily by myself...
So I can pass the exam and
live happily by myself!
Il-mae, did you really think
I'd be fine?
I already gave you my heart.
How am I supposed to
live without you?
And our teacher...
he's a horrible person, too.
As her father...
this is how he shows his love.
Tae-il, why are you doing this to her?
What can she do now?
That's exactly why
I cannot allow this marriage.
If you'd known your wife's gonna die,
would you've not loved her?
Answer me!
Il-mae!
I never regret loving your mother.
Your mother was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
Even now, everyday of my life is
filled of joy because your mom!
Please, forgive her.
And please release her.
Allow me to be at her side
till her last day.
- Please release her.
- Please! Release her!
This marriage is... nullified!
Tae-il! I'm sick.
And I'll get sicker.
I'm afraid I won't be able to
be with you much longer
You can't die. I won't let you.
Forget the law school! I'll study
and go to a medical school
I'm gonna find out a cure
for your illness
I pretended I was asleep
and he's already snoring. Little fool...
Our first kiss was a long awaited one...
Thinking about our first kiss
still makes my heart flutter...
I love you, Tae-il!
Teacher, I can't say that!
Tae-il.
I can't... I can't do that here.
Let go of her, will you?
Let go of her.
Never! I'll never let her go!
I'm gonna cure her illness and
we're gonna live happily together
till our deaths do us apart
teeth fall out.