Okay, ladies, gather up your possessions.
Get up, ladies, let's go.
All right, let's move it.
Move it this way.
Move it.
Move it, then.
Hey, can't rush, huh?
Come on, ladies. Let's go walk.
Come on.
Quiet down now, girls.
- He looks good.
- Gutierrez, Luna.
- Coming, baby.
- Take your property, ladies.
Washington, Tyra.
Yes. Yes, I'm coming.
Baldonado, Lucy.
- Jones, Arabella.
- Asshole.
Kirk. Claudia.
- Hold it, baby.
- Cortez, Consuela.
Mazzola, Elle.
- All right, ladies, let's go.
- Let's go, ladies.
It's show time.
All right, ladies, keep it moving.
Watch the steps, now.
Shut up.
Come on over here,
and get some real hard shit.
Do you like Puerto Ricans, baby?
Quiet, please!
$500 or 30 days. Three weeks to pay.
October 14. Calendar 21.
People v. Roosevelt Davis.
Docket number 8483, September 19.
Defendant is charged
with attempted grand larceny.
Does the defendant waive
the reading of the rights and charges?
We do.
For the People, Saul Kreiglitz.
For the defendant, Aaron Levinsky.
- What are you gonna give me on him?
- A misdemeanor.
He's an accomplice. Disorderly conduct?
Come on, he shows a prior.
Yeah, he shows a prior,
but he hasn't done any hard time.
Give him a break.
What are we supposed to do,
give him a medal?
- How much you talking about?
- We're talking $100.
$50.
$75. Best I can do.
Hey, hey, coming through here.
Excuse me. Coming through.
...twenty-five years.
She started to laugh and told me
to go to hell, and ordered me to leave.
- Rose?
- In a minute.
Gonzales, your lawyer has just entered
a plea of guilty on your behalf.
You understand, pleading guilty,
you waive your right...
There she is, Arthur.
Now, is that what you wish to do?
- Do you understand what I've said?
- Sit down, Rose.
- Is that what you wish to do?
- Yes, yes, it is.
By this plea of guilty,
you're giving up important rights...
...I wish to make you aware of.
- She looks terrible.
Remember, Clarence said
this would be the worst of it.
Yes.
Do you understand that by pleading guilty,
you're waiving your right...
...to confront and cross-examine
any witnesses against you?
And you are also giving up
your right to remain silent?
Be calm, Rose. Everything's under control.
We'll be out of here in no time.
Now, sir, did you take property
from premises...
...at 540 East 8th Street
without permission of authority?
Are you pleading guilty? Because you are...
Did you see who's here, at $250 an hour?
Clarence fucking Middleton.
Last I heard, it was $350.
- Who's the client?
- I don't know.
Say it aloud.
Guilty.
Did anybody make any threats or promises
in order to induce you to plead guilty?
Saul, do you have the Kirk folder?
I'll be taking that one.
Mr. Gonzales,
this is your third appearance...
Thank you.
...before this court since last year.
The sentence of this court is six months.
Do you understand what I've said so far?
What have you done?
Counsel. Notify your client
of his right to appeal.
Thank you, Mr. Torres. Next case.
Calendar 28. People v. Claudia Kirk.
Docket 6418.
The defendant is charged
with manslaughter in the first degree.
- The Morales case is next on the docket.
- All in good time, Mr. Levinsky.
- I have an appointment in Part 30.
- It'll wait. Sit down, please. Let's move it.
Take it easy.
- My name's wrong.
- We'll take care of it.
Counsel, state your appearances
for the record.
Francis Xavier MacMillan
for the prosecution.
Clarence Middleton for the defendant.
The defendant has been indicted
in the county of New York...
...for first-degree manslaughter.
We request...
May I say something?
...she be given psychiatric evaluation
to determine her capacity to stand trial.
In accordance with article 730 of the CPL...
...she was remanded to the New York
County Prison Hospital for examination.
Excuse me!
The psychiatrists' report finds
the defendant not competent to stand trial.
I have something to say!
They recommend that she be committed
to a mental facility and the People concur.
- Hands by your side.
- All right.
I can't hear. I have a right to hear.
Defendant will keep quiet
if she knows what's good for her.
- Clarence, have you read these reports?
- We have.
- Do you move to confirm?
- I do.
- Consult with your client.
- Larry, in view of the overriding fact...
- Could you please let me go?
- The fact is, she's impossible to talk to.
Clarence, please consult with your client.
Make it quick!
- Get your hands off me!
- Face forward.
Claudia...
Listen, they don't have my name right.
I don't want to be known as Kirk.
Do you understand?
My name is Draper. Claudia Draper.
Yes.
- D-R-A-P-E-R.
- Yes, we'll get that changed.
Good.
Now look, Claudia, I am trying to help you.
We all are.
What's going on here?
We're trying to do
what we feel is best for you.
Who is "we"?
We offered you
criminally negligent homicide.
You didn't want us to.
Hey.
Who are you?
What?
Well, Clarence Middleton.
Don't you remember me?
Who do you work for?
- I'm your lawyer, Claudia.
- Good. We're on the right track.
We have to claim
that you're incompetent to stand trial.
- Do you understand?
- No, I didn't give you permission to do that.
- I'm not incompetent.
- Of course you're not.
- I'm innocent.
- I know you are. But that's not the issue.
- What do you mean it's not the issue?
- The doctors agreed.
Your parents agree it's best if you're
in a hospital rather than in a prison.
I don't give a shit what they say!
Your parents love you.
It's all been arranged.
- You goddamn son of a bitch!
- Arthur, stop her!
I'm not incompetent.
I'm not incompetent, you are!
Get her off me! Get her off me!
- Move it now.
- Hit him again.
Quiet in the court!
You can't lock me up.
Let go of me! Get away from me!
Let me through. That's my daughter.
- Calm down.
- Don't hurt her.
Sir, restrain yourself.
Why are you trying to put me away?
Why are you trying to lock me up?
You are all in cahoots.
Put me down!
There's nothing wrong with me!
God! Keep going!
- No!
- Watch out!
Put me down. I need a lawyer!
- Quiet in the court!
- All right, everybody settle down.
Order in the court!
Order in the court.
It's over, folks. Sit down.
- God, Clarence, are you all right?
- I'm bleeding. My glasses...
Can we go on?
No, we can't go on. I've been attacked
in a courtroom, for Christ's sake.
I hereby request permission
to be released from this case.
- Can't you just move to confirm?
- No, sir! Get someone from Legal Aid.
I'm going to a doctor.
- Are you all right?
- I need a Legal Aid member.
Where's Torbick? Where's Morella?
Don't we have anybody
in the appointments list?
Levinsky.
Where are you going?
To get Morella. I have an appearance
in Part 30, Your Honor.
- Let me get Morella. He's on catch.
- But I caught you.
Your Honor, I respectfully submit
that my caseload is...
Mr. Levinsky, is your caseload too heavy
to accept any appointments in this court?
For the record, Mr. Middleton withdraws.
Mr. Levinsky is appointed counsel
for the defense.
It's 7:30. We have two psychiatric reports.
All it takes from you
is a motion to confirm.
- I haven't seen the reports.
- See them. Let's move it.
Let's get this one out of here.
- What's the original charge?
- Manslaughter.
The original charge is not the issue.
Psychiatrists' reports say she's unfit
to stand trial. Let's have your motion.
Didn't you say you were in a hurry,
Mr. Levinsky?
- I am in a hurry.
- Then let's have your motion.
I don't have all day.
I move to controvert.
For the record,
the defense moves to challenge.
You wanted a motion.
That's my motion.
What's your basis, Levinsky?
Well, as I observed,
the defendant seemed a bit reluctant.
I have to consult with my client.
Fine. Adjourn until Monday.
Monday? I haven't even met the woman.
Between now and Monday
I have no time to prepare a case.
Adjourn until Monday, Part 65. Next case.
Calendar 29, People v. Calvin Johnson.
Docket 6914, robbery in the first degree.
Aaron? Are you out of your mind?
- I don't have to take that shit from him.
- Of course you do, he's the judge.
Look, do yourself a favor.
Go back in and settle up.
- Did you see that girl work over Middleton?
- I wish she'd nailed MacMillan, too.
Pardon me, I'd like talk to you.
I'm Arthur Kirk, the girl's father.
I'd like to talk to you, too.
- Aaron? See you later?
- Yeah, yeah.
My wife, Rose.
- Mrs. Kirk.
- How do you do?
I'm still shaking.
I can't believe what happened.
- Sit down.
- Yeah, thank you.
Tell me, why did you stop the motion?
I'm not familiar with the case yet.
The case is about a very disturbed girl.
She needs to be hospitalized.
I haven't read the reports,
and I have to confer with the defendant.
- How can you confer? She's sick.
- I know how painful this is for you.
You're damn right. What about her pain?
- Arthur.
- You see, we're talking about my child.
She needs to be in a hospital,
not some kind of a prison cell.
And let me tell you.
- She is in no condition to stand trial.
- Darling, he didn't say he wouldn't do it.
Of course. You didn't say that, did you?
Please, forgive me.
- I guess I'm not handling this too well.
- That's perfectly understandable, sir.
- Will you be seeing her soon?
- I'll have to, yes.
- Will you tell her that I love her?
- Of course.
Please.
I want to give you my card.
If you need anything, anything at all,
just call my office.
Thank you.
- Mrs. Kirk?
- Good-bye.
Doctor Arantes to the conference room.
I'm here to see Claudia Draper.
Levinsky, Legal Aid.
May I inspect your bag, sir?
Your name tag, sir.
Dr. Simon, 817. Dr. Simon, Psychiatry, 817.
Come with me, sir.
- Good night, John.
- Good night, Dr. Morrison.
- Excuse me. Dr. Morrison?
- Yes?
My name is Aaron Levinsky.
I'm the new attorney for Claudia Draper.
I just read the report
that you did with Dr. Arantes about her.
- Is there going to be a hearing?
- I think so, yeah.
Yeah, you got a minute?
Not about Mrs. Draper.
It wouldn't be ethical. Sorry.
I'm just curious about a couple of things
you wrote here in this report.
You mention that you found her
flagrantly sexual...
...and had random visions
and was subject to paranoid...
I'm really sorry, Mr. Levinsky.
Doctor?
I just want to ask you one question.
Is she crazy?
Crazy is a word I dislike.
Dr. Hodges, telephone on line 3.
Do I think she should go to prison? No.
She's where she belongs, Mr. Levinsky.
Good night.
Shut up, Mary!
Watch out for Babby.
She might try something.
Dr. Morrison's left a prescription for her.
You can wait in here, sir.
Claudia...
...you feel more better.
You feel more calm, huh?
You are a woman of passion.
Passion is good in the bed, but not here.
Someone is waiting to see you.
What?
Someone is here to see you.
She's fine.
- Do you want some help, Dr. Arantes?
- No, no.
You just follow me.
Follow me, Claudia. Just follow me.
- Right this way, Mrs. Draper.
- Thank you, Manuel.
You must be Claudia.
And I hope you're Mr. Green from Chicago.
Just call me Allen. Sit down.
Thank you.
- Champagne?
- Yes, please.
I've never had to take a test before.
Not since high school.
Do you have certain questions
that you ask?
Things like that?
No.
I just go by the seat of my pants.
How am I doing?
I'm about to slide over my chair.
Hello, Mrs. Draper.
My name is Aaron Levinsky.
I'm an attorney sent by the court.
Mr. Middleton
doesn't represent you anymore.
Would you like to discuss your case?
I don't know if you can follow any of this...
...but do you understand
that I'm gonna go to court on your behalf?
And tonight I got to go home to Brooklyn
on the subway...
...and that scares the shit out of me.
I'm real tired. It's been a long day.
You're breaking my heart.
- Terrific. She can talk.
- Talk?
I can dance, juggle, card tricks.
What kind of a show
do I have to put on for you?
Did I say something wrong?
It seems I can't get a fair trial
unless I put on a good show for...
...who now?
Aaron Levinsky, Legal Aid.
- No, it's not like that.
- No?
Well, how do I get to stand trial?
You don't have...
How do I get to stand trial?
That's what I want to know!
That's okay. Close the door, please.
I'm her attorney.
- Says who?
- Says the court.
If you need me, I'll be right out here.
You think I'm gonna need him?
Well, haven't you heard?
I lash out and strike people at random.
I know. I was there.
- I think you broke his nose.
- So the day's not a total loss.
All right, what we've got here
is a 730 process.
This is a process
whereby the State is assuming that you...
- Are you married?
- Pardon me?
You got a missus?
She give good head?
You want to talk
about your situation here or what?
You've been indicted
for manslaughter first degree.
I know all that.
Tell me why you're here.
- The truth?
- No, the bullshit, Levinsky.
I love listening to bullshit,
especially when I'm drowning in it.
I know why you're here.
- You're here to see if I'm crazy, right?
- No.
No. No, you're here to see
just how crazy I am.
Well, two psychiatrists already say
that you are incompetent.
Morrison and Arantes? Frick and Frack?
Arantes can barely speak English,
and Morrison...
...he's a very weird guy.
You know, I flashed,
and he didn't even look.
How about you, Levinsky?
Are you weird, too?
I must be okay, I'm looking.
- Your mother says she loves you.
- Fuck my mother!
Why didn't you tell me you work for them?
I'm not working for them...
- Why didn't you tell me that?
- Hold it! Listen!
- I came here to do my job in good faith.
- You talked to my mother?
- Will you listen to me? You got a choice.
- What did she tell you?
You can either cooperate with me
and maybe it goes your way...
...or you can yell at me, I'll sign that
motion to commit, and that's it.
You creep lawyers are all alike.
As long as you get paid, you don't care
who goes where for how long.
I'm not taking money from you.
This one comes in here
and tells me if I don't kiss ass...
...he's gonna walk out on me? Walk.
And be held in contempt of court?
No, thank you.
It doesn't work that way.
I'm stuck with you.
Oh, man!
Oh, boy.
First, we have to get a shrink
to look at you and then you...
No more shrinks.
I'm giving you very good legal advice.
Thanks. What I said about lawyers
goes double for shrinks.
Mrs. Draper, there are two psychiatrists
who already say that you're crazy.
You got to have at least one psychiatrist
who says you're not crazy...
...or you don't have a case.
- Sure, I do. I'm my case.
I get up there, I say my piece,
I prove I'm competent!
Look, I don't know if you believe this,
but I'm a perfectly sane woman.
And I don't bother anyone
who doesn't bother me first. You get it?
I don't want any more quacks
running around in my head...
...talking about my toilet training.
There's only one thing that scares me.
A stupid client. And you terrify me.
- Have you ever testified in court?
- No.
- So you've never been cross-examined?
- How long have you been hooking?
- Three years.
- And you've never been busted?
- Never. Now tell me I'm incompetent.
Well, look.
Mrs. Draper, it doesn't look good
to beat up one of the city's top attorneys.
Well, it may not have looked good,
but it sure felt good.
What was I supposed to do,
sit there while my own lawyer says...
...I’m incompetent to stand trial?
Are you?
How competent do you have to be,
for Christ's sake?
Good point.
Let's say for now
that you're not entirely incompetent.
Yeah, let's say that.
Let's say for now
that the doctors here are all wrong.
- Yeah, let's say that, too.
- Then why is all this happening to you?
Mrs. Draper?
Do you want me to represent you
in this competency hearing?
- I don't know. Are you any good?
- You had good. Now you got me.
I could do worse.
Don't be so sure.
If we win at the hearing, you get a trial.
But if you lose the trial,
you can go to jail for 25 years.
I'll take the risk. Because if I don't,
I could end up wearing this bathrobe...
...until I collect social security.
MacMillan's gonna eat me alive.
- All right, let's start at the beginning.
- Fine.
- Give me some background details.
- All right.
Now, you talk to me
and pretend I'm sane, okay?
Okay.
And I'll do the same for you.
Okay?
Thank you.
Frank.
MacMillan.
Yeah, Aaron, what's up?
The Claudia Draper thing.
I'm gonna go ahead with it.
Well, good, good.
No, no. I'm gonna defend the girl
at a competency hearing.
The judge set it up for Monday.
Why are you doing that?
She's better off in a hospital than in prison.
Don't mess this up.
She wants to stand trial
on the manslaughter charge.
I think she's up to it.
- Oh, you do?
- Yeah, I do.
I'll need the police reports
and a court order to enter the apartment.
You're making a mistake. That girl is sick.
I have an aunt who's crazier than she is.
She's president of the PTA.
Arthur Kirk is very well-connected.
He doesn't want his daughter going through
a trial. We're doing her a favor.
The accused wants her day in court.
I still believe in that kind of stuff.
Don't get high and mighty with me.
Maybe you just don't have
a good enough case.
Maybe you're trying to avoid a trial.
I don't have a very good case? Really?
She almost cut off a john's head.
You want her back on the streets?
- Will your secretary pull the reports?
- She has more important things to do.
Really?
Then I'm gonna have to paper you
to death, Francis.
You'll have to hire another secretary
just to keep up with the work.
All right, kid.
But you're going up against me on this one.
Hey, what are you doing?
Carla is waiting for Fantasy Island.
Hey, fuck it.
Girlfriend, I want to watch my game show.
That's not your card.
That's my card, Marian. I had four.
One, two, three, four.
Hey.
I told you not to do that.
- These aren't the same cards I had before.
- I don't want to see your cards.
Come on, Suzanne.
How many, Suzanne?
- Three.
- No, five on that play.
No, no. Wait. Stand pat, Suzanne.
Stand pat?
Yeah, you see, because you got
a good hand, so you can stay.
Hey, hey, that's not fair. No, hey, look.
Suzanne, you were gonna win.
Look, you got a full house.
You got three jacks and two kings.
Claudia? Claudia, would you like
to come into my office now?
Would I like to?
Let me put it this way.
Come into my office, Claudia.
I see you're still taking notes.
I have a feeling I'll need them.
Need them for what, Claudia?
Some guys are trying to put me away.
When you say "some guys,"
who do you mean exactly?
You mean, men in general,
or do you have some specific men in mind?
- Claudia.
- What do you want?
- I want to talk to you.
- I don't want to talk to you.
Last time I talked to you,
you and Pancho Villa asked me...
...stupid questions
and called me incompetent.
- It would be better if you could trust me.
- Yeah? Why?
Because you have so many degrees
on your wall?
Do you think I'm one of the guys
trying to put you away?
They don't pay you to turn me loose.
Do you guys work on commission?
- Would you like a cup of coffee?
- Only if it has Thorazine in it.
- Sorry, only milk and sugar.
- Pass.
I heard you had quite a violent episode
in court yesterday.
Where does it say I have to be nice
to get a fair trial?
- You couldn't seem to control your anger.
- No, I couldn't.
And based on the circumstances,
how did you expect me to act? Dead?
- You're getting angry again.
- I've got a lot to be angry about.
We all have these feelings, Claudia,
but we learn to control them.
Well, don't you ever lose control, Herbie?
Don't you ever let yourself go?
You're a very frightened girl.
And under stress,
you could become dangerous to others.
Bullshit.
That's what I plan to say in court
on Monday.
You need treatment
in order to be able to control yourself.
I'm in control.
Because right now,
I'd like to wring your fucking neck...
...but I'm not going to.
Good. That's a step in the right direction.
I'd like to help you
put your life back in order.
But, Herbie, there is no order in life.
Now, maybe you need order.
Maybe that's why you're here...
...behind bars.
It makes you feel safe, doesn't it?
- Do you think this is productive?
- I know you.
You see,
I know you better than you know me.
Do you know why?
'Cause I've seen you with your pants down.
You drop your pants
and talk about your troubles.
How you couldn't make it on Park Avenue,
not even Columbus.
So you're stuck...
...in the crummiest joint in town.
Right, Herbie?
This is 555-1246.
But I'm much more than a number.
Talk to me.
This is Mr. K. Back at the Tower Hotel,
room 671.
I have a tip
on some telecommunications stock...
...you might find interesting.
Come on over and we'll talk.
Mrs. Draper, your VCR is ready.
Give me a call when you want it delivered.
Hi, Claudia, I'm a friend of Lee.
Do you remember Lee?
The big guy, dark hair, glasses.
He's with Allied.
Anyway, he suggested
I give you a ring and...
Damn it, I hate to talk to these things.
I feel like an idiot.
My name is Allen. I'm at 555-9970.
Could you call me? I'd really like that.
Lee says I'd really like that, too.
It's 555-9970.
Hey, Levinsky. Are you ready for this?
A doctor who makes sense.
We have been talking for hours.
- Really?
- Really.
- May I join you?
- Please.
Dr. Johnson, this is my attorney,
Aaron Levinsky.
- Mr. Levinsky.
- Pleasure to meet you.
We're discussing the nature of paranoia,
a subject of interest around here.
Yeah, to put it in a nutshell, Levinsky,
this lady says I do not need a hospital.
I need a nice walk down Fifth Avenue.
You're saying that you don't agree
with Dr. Morrison's diagnosis?
I won't deny that Claudia could benefit
from therapy...
...but it could be conducted
on an outpatient basis.
Twice a week to start with,
leading to a group therapy situation...
...once a week.
- Is this terrific? Just what we needed.
Wait. Wait a minute.
Are you willing to have a doctor
testify on your behalf?
Well, this doctor, yes.
Doctor...
...are you prepared to testify
at Claudia's hearing on Monday morning?
- Monday?
- Monday.
What's today?
- Friday.
- Friday. Oh, my, Friday.
My. The weekend?
- Monday, you say.
- Monday.
Let me check my calendar.
Monday's the day I...
One of my secretaries
will be in touch with you.
Monday. What in God's name
am I supposed to do Monday?
Cheer up, Levinsky.
Don't want people thinking you're crazy.
You're very cute.
She is a doctor, you know.
A chiropractor, sort of, I think.
- What's that? For me?
- Lf you like mustard.
- Food? Honest-to-God food?
- Pastrami.
Pastrami? You're okay, Levinsky.
God, she looked so normal.
Poisoned her husband.
Oh, delicious!
- We're on Monday, 10:00 a.m.
- Okay.
I marked some places here
I want you to study.
Here and here. All right?
This is so good.
Why do you look nervous?
- I'd like more time.
- Relax. You'll do fine.
And I brought you some clothing
to wear at the hearing.
- You bought me clothes, darling?
- Brought you. Brought you.
- From where?
- From your apartment.
Who said you could go to my apartment?
What did you take?
Some clothing.
A dress. You know, some shoes,
some nice things.
I want you to wear your own clothing
at the hearing.
Why didn't you ask me?
Because there was no time.
Claudia, I'm just trying to help you.
What gives you the right to invade me?
Invade you?
I don't want you to look like a nut in court.
When is the last time
you went through your wife's dresser?
you searched in her panty drawer?
- It's no big deal. Calm down.
- It is a big deal!
Has anyone ever gone through your things
without permission?
I'm sorry.
I decide who sees my underwear.
I think you better get dressed now.
- Hey, I'd love to see you in these.
- Next week, my sweet.
I don't want to go home tonight.
You should have told me earlier.
Let's take
a nice sexy bubble bath together.
I can't, sweetheart.
I have another appointment.
I'm really sorry.
What are you going to do now?
Fuck somebody else?
- Hello? Hello?
- Hi.
- Claudia? You okay?
- No, no. I'm coming. Just that...
Where's the bubble bath?
You got some bath salts
or that kind of thing?
That sounds great.
About a half-hour? All right. 'Bye.
Allen, come on. Turn off the water.
Please, be a good boy.
Don't give me that whore talk.
Look, we had a lot of fun...
...but the time's up and the party's over.
I'll tell you when the party is over.
I like to bathe girls.
I'm not a girl anymore.
And you're not a boy.
- I don't do baths. Please.
- You bitch!
You sound just like my wife.
"Don't do this. Don't do that."
Hey, stop it.
Stop it, you creep! I'm not your wife.
Calm down!
You goddamn cunt!
You're all alike! Whore!
No! Don't! No! No.
Don't!
Make sure there's always plenty of water
in the pitcher for the judge.
The defendant must be well-guarded
at all times.
You look wonderful.
You know what I use this dress for?
For the ones
who want to sit on Mommy's lap.
All rise, please.
- Good morning, Harry.
- Good morning, sir.
His Honor, Stanley Murdoch,
the Justice of the Court.
Will counsel please state
your appearances for the record?
Francis Xavier MacMillan
for the prosecution.
Does the missus pick out your ties?
Aaron Levinsky for the defense.
This hearing is set
to controvert the findings...
...of psychiatric examinations...
...in the matter of the People
of the State of New York...
...v. Claudia Faith Draper.
Is the defendant ready, Mr...
Levinsky, Your Honor.
Yes, Your Honor...
...let the record show that counsel
for the defense has recommended...
...independent psychiatric examination
and testimony...
...and the defendant has refused it.
- Covering your ass?
- You bet.
- So noted.
- I'll make a note of that, too.
Defense is ready.
- Prosecution is ready, Your Honor.
- Proceed, Mr. MacMillan.
Two psychiatrists found the defendant
incompetent to stand trial.
One is present to testify,
but since their findings are the same...
...I’d like a stipulation
for the absent witness.
- Objection! Both of them should be here.
- Overruled.
I call Dr. Herbert Morrison.
Give your full name and county of residence
for the record.
Dr. Herbert A. Morrison, New York.
Do you swear the testimony
you shall give in this special proceeding...
...shall be the truth, the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth?
I do.
Mr. MacMillan.
How long have you been a psychiatrist?
I've been a licensed psychiatrist
for 30 years.
Where do you practice?
I am currently Ward Unit Chief
of New York County Prison Hospital.
When did you examine the defendant,
Claudia Draper?
Eight days ago, when she was transferred
from the Women's House of Detention.
What did your examination consist of?
The examination consisted of questions
and answers in the usual psychiatric flow...
...in order to determine
the patient's mental condition.
How would you define
the mental condition of the defendant?
Initially, she was withdrawn...
...silent, almost catatonic.
Completely uncooperative.
When she finally did speak,
she was abusive, hostile...
...deeply distrustful...
...with a tendency
towards inappropriate humor.
You just didn't like my jokes, Herbie.
Mrs. Draper, you are to remain quiet.
She was convinced of a conspiracy
and unable to comprehend...
...I was a physician who was there to help.
Do you believe the defendant can
consult rationally with her counsel...
...and assist in her defense?
- No, I don't believe so.
Does this mean
she can't understand the charge?
In this patient's case...
...she's so convinced
that the district attorney...
...her parents, and I
are conspiring to put her away...
...that I don't see
how she could distinguish...
...between a criminal charge
and persecution.
I can tell the difference.
This is persecution.
Mr. Levinsky?
I'm sorry, Your Honor.
It won't happen again.
Continue.
Do you think the defendant
is dangerous to herself and to others?
Yes, I do.
- Define dangerous.
- That's for cross-examination.
Ask him to define dangerous.
When a patient is paranoid,
and I found this patient to be paranoid...
- Ask him to define paranoid.
- Will you be quiet?
...and has her history,
then I consider such a person dangerous.
Define dangerous.
Mr. Levinsky, if these proceedings...
...are too much of a burden
for the defendant...
...I would be happy to entertain
a request for an adjournment.
It won't be necessary, Your Honor.
I'm sorry.
We allow a good deal of leeway
in these circumstances, Mr. Levinsky.
We're not nearly as formal here
as in other courts...
...but I would remind you
that the rules of contempt apply.
Young lady?
Do you understand what I just said?
- I speak English. Of course, I understand.
- She understands perfectly, Your Honor.
Continue, Mr. MacMillan.
As a professional, would you like to see
the defendant receive treatment...
...before being brought to trial?
Absolutely. If she had appendicitis
or pneumonia...
...no court would expect her to go to trial.
They'd postpone until she recovered.
Do you believe, with a reasonable degree
of medical certainty...
...that Claudia Draper...
...as a result of mental disease or defect...
...lacks the capacity
to understand the charges against her...
...or to assist in her own defense?
In my professional opinion, the patient
can't understand the charges against her...
...nor can she assist in her own defense.
Thank you, no further questions,
Your Honor.
Mr. Levinsky?
Yes. Your Honor, if you don't mind,
I'm going to be going rather slowly.
I mind, Mr. Levinsky.
This is a hearing, not a trial.
Yes, sir.
Dr. Morrison...
...you describe the defendant
as abusive and hostile...
...and deeply distrustful.
- Tending toward inappropriate humor.
- Thank you, thank you.
Did you describe her
as abusive and hostile?
Yes, I did.
Abusive and hostile.
To whom, Doctor?
- To the world in general.
- Yes, well...
...the world wasn't in one room with her.
You were.
- And after I, Dr. Arantes.
- The man couldn't speak English.
- Mr. Levinsky, control your client.
- The man doesn't speak English.
I asked two questions,
you've interrupted twice. Shut up!
- I never understood a word.
- You never understand a word I say.
Young lady? Young lady.
You've been warned.
Dr. Arantes speaks with an accent,
but he's fully qualified.
After all, Dr. Freud had an accent.
Thank you for volunteering that.
Tell me...
...you described the defendant
as dangerous.
- Is that right?
- In my professional opinion.
Did you ever see
the defendant hurt herself...
...or anybody else?
No, not personally.
Ever hear her threaten to hurt herself
or anybody else?
No.
Did anybody at New York
County Prison Hospital...
...ever see Claudia Draper hurt herself...
...or anybody else,
or threaten to hurt herself...
...or anybody else?
Well, let me see.
- Take your time, Doctor.
- Thank you.
Yes.
Three days after her arrival, she blackened
the eye of one of our other patients.
She made a pass at me.
The patient had to go to the infirmary.
Your Honor, may I have a moment?
Please.
- Why didn't you tell me about this?
- I forgot.
- I have to prove you're not dangerous.
- She grabbed my tit, I socked her.
If you had tits, you'd do the same thing.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Levinsky?
Are you prepared
to pursue a line of questioning?
I...
- I certainly hope so, Your Honor.
- I hope so, too. Continue.
Dr. Morrison,
before your examination of Mrs. Draper...
...were you aware
of why she had been arrested?
Yes. First-degree manslaughter.
It was more like womanslaughter,
but I finished first.
That's enough, Mrs. Draper.
Mr. Levinsky, you continue.
This time, stay on track.
Dr. Morrison...
...knowing that she had been arrested
for manslaughter...
...were you in any way predisposed
to regard Mrs. Draper as dangerous?
I considered that for a while,
but I held it in abeyance...
...and let the examination provide me
with a proper psychiatric profile.
You've been a psychiatrist for many years.
That's correct.
You must have testified
at many competency hearings, right?
Hundreds.
Do you have a standard set of questions
that you ask these patients?
Yes, I do.
So I imagine
you've already asked Mrs. Draper...
...if she understood
the charges against her.
That's correct.
You asked her such questions as
what day of the week it was...
...and what her parents' names were.
- Yes, that's right.
Did she know the answers
to these questions?
She refused to answer.
How could I know if she knew the answers?
Let me ask the questions, okay?
I'm the attorney.
Thank you.
She could have known the answers.
Yes or no?
Yes, she could have known the answers.
You say she didn't answer you.
What did she do?
She laughed.
She laughed?
- What else did she do?
- She never stopped taking notes.
She was entirely belligerent in her attitude.
She wouldn't answer me.
You're really not used to patients
who don't answer, are you?
I'm used to all kinds. What concerns me is
their attitude and behavior.
Could it be that the attitude
and behavior of this patient...
...challenged you,
and got you a little bit hostile...
...and perhaps colored the findings
in this report?
I've been a psychiatrist for 30 years.
I know how to control my emotions.
I did not show the patient
what I was feeling at the time.
So you felt hostile, you just didn't show it.
- I didn't say that.
- Yes, you did.
- I didn't. Don't put words in my mouth.
- I'm not putting words in your mouth.
I don't like your attitude, Mr. Levinsky!
Getting a little hostile, Doctor?
You're very clever
with your courtroom tricks.
But what you're doing here
is depriving a sick girl of proper treatment.
I'm a doctor.
I want her to receive that treatment.
I don't care whether
you win this argument or not.
The girl has a history,
and you're ignoring it.
- A broken home, a broken marriage.
- Sounds like half of us.
- Disillusion.
- That's the other half.
Your Honor, could we eliminate
Mr. Levinsky's commentary...
...and let the doctor speak?
I agree. Go on, Doctor.
We're not talking about a defendant,
we're talking about a very troubled girl.
She's not a girl from the streets.
She's a bright, upper-class girl
who couldn't cope, broke down!
She's a girl with a history. Broke down!
She became a prostitute...
...and in a homicidal rage,
killed one of her customers.
I object. There's been no charge
of prostitution...
...and any charge of homicide
has to be tried.
We're talking about a breakdown.
When there's...
Are you gonna allow this?
My job's to put...
The witness is making a speech.
It's not a proper forum.
That can't be in a courtroom or prison.
It has to be in a hospital.
Your Honor, I object!
I would like everything about homicide
and prostitution stricken from the record.
Mr. Levinsky, I am aware of the law.
You're going to have to trust me
to separate the issues.
I'm going to allow it.
I have no more questions.
With Your Honor's permission,
I will save my redirect for later.
You may step down, Dr. Morrison.
Thank you.
I'd like to call Mrs. Arthur Kirk.
- I don't want her up there.
- We don't make out the invitation list.
I don't want to hear her!
Your Honor,
I'd like to request a short recess.
- I want to consult with my client.
- That's an excellent idea, Mr. Levinsky.
We'll stand in recess for a few minutes.
Please remain seated until the judge
leaves the courtroom.
Go talk to her. Tell her you love her.
Come with me.
Claudia?
Hello, darling. How are you?
You look thin.
Are they feeding you?
I can arrange to have food sent in.
Would you like that?
You look tired.
Are we making you tired?
You can say so, darling.
Say something, please.
Can we go in there?
We can talk to her later.
We'll talk later, Claudia.
We love you, darling.
What?
- We love you.
- Don't you know that?
"We love you"?
Yes!
"We love you." One more time.
"We... "
Come on.
We...
"Love... "
Love...
"You."
You.
Outstanding.
Let's go, Levinsky.
- My wife and l...
- I don't want to hear about your wife.
I'm sorry. Talk about your wife.
I was thinking about
how people withhold...
...in a family.
How many kids do you have?
Three. Two boys and a girl.
You going to get divorced?
We talk about it sometimes.
Then we go to the movies.
Why didn't you want her to testify?
I just don't want her to testify.
Why? You wouldn't let me
get an independent shrink.
Officer?
Harry?
You can take me to my seat now.
No gum, Claudia.
And how soon after the divorce
did you marry Mr. Kirk?
Eleven months. Nearly a year.
- Did your daughter get along with Mr. Kirk?
- Fine. It was love at first sight for both.
Can you tell us when you first noticed
any changes in her behavior?
As early as the sixth grade.
She was around 11.
She'd always been active in school,
in sports and clubs and that sort of thing.
She was always a very happy child.
Then all of a sudden she withdrew.
She seemed to live in a fantasy
most of the time.
You never knew how she would act,
is that it?
Never.
One day she'd talk a blue streak
of utter nonsense.
The next day, not a word. Later...
...in high school, we had some problems...
...with marijuana,
and staying out all night and...
...there was a period of promiscuity.
Once, she was 16...
...we found her
at the mirror in the bathroom.
She'd cut her hair an inch from her scalp.
When we approached her,
she brandished the scissors on us.
She turned the scissors on you
as if to attack you?
Objection.
The prosecution is leading the witness.
Sustained.
Did you get any professional counseling?
Arthur was against it.
He doesn't believe
in airing family problems.
And I agreed with him.
We assumed it was part of adolescence.
Brandishing scissors on her parents,
a part of adolescence?
Do you have any idea
what caused her behavior?
I don't know. I don't know.
I know that I made mistakes.
Every mother makes mistakes,
and I'm sure that I made them sometimes.
But not enough times for her
to carry on the way she did.
Not enough times for her to drink and lie...
...and cut school and not talk to me...
...and not kiss me, not touch me.
Not enough times for that!
I don't know.
When she was a little girl...
...she loved me so much.
She used to say, "I love you
to the moon and down again.
"And around the world and back again."
And I would answer, "I love you...
"...to the sun and down again.
"And around the stars and back again."
Do you remember, Claudia?
Just answer the questions, Mama.
Did she get in touch with you
when her marriage failed?
I found out from a friend.
So I called and said, "Is it true? "
And she said, "Yes, it's true."
There was a big silence. So I said:
"Stay with us until you feel better."
"No," she said. Just no.
I was frightened for her.
A divorced woman is a target.
She's easy prey to any polite man
who comes along.
Were you able to keep in touch after that?
I called. I called.
But she never answered my messages.
So instead of calling, I wrote.
These are the letters. I have them here.
You should see them. You see...
Your Honor, I never knew about this.
Your Honor, I hardly think this is proper.
Mrs. Kirk?
Is this your handwriting?
Answer me! Is this your handwriting?
Mrs. Kirk, please.
I have 31 letters in my hand!
And every one is marked
"Return to Sender"!
I'm sorry, Your Honor.
Poor Mama.
Mrs. Kirk?
- Are you all right?
- Mrs. Kirk?
You could take a moment if you like.
I'm all right. I'm sorry.
I know this is difficult for you.
If you just bear with me.
Your daughter has been
continuously withdrawing...
...from you in the past 20 years,
is that right?
Yes, that's true.
Does your daughter need psychiatric help?
Objection. Is Mrs. Kirk a medical expert?
Sustained.
Rephrase. As a parent, solely as a parent...
...would you like to see your daughter
receive psychiatric treatment?
Hey, I'm a grown-up.
What difference does she make?
- Miss Draper?
- It's my life, Stanley.
You're trying my patience.
Why do you listen to all this crap?
Why don't you listen to me?
Sit down.
You'll have a chance to testify later.
Mrs. Kirk.
I'm sorry.
What was the question?
"As a parent, solely,
would you like to see your daughter...
"...receive psychiatric treatment? "
She needs help.
It's a difficult thing for a mother
to say about her daughter.
Yes.
She needs help.
One last question, Mrs. Kirk.
Do you love your daughter?
Say it for the record, please.
Yes.
I love my daughter.
Thank you. I have no further questions.
- All true?
- Close enough. Let her go.
Mr. Levinsky. Do you have any questions?
Let her go, Levinsky.
Would you like to take a minute?
No, thank you.
You stated that you
and the defendant's father...
You testified that
when Claudia was in high school...
What?
You'll have to let me discredit the witness.
Maybe you are crazy.
I have no more questions, Your Honor.
Mrs. Kirk, you may step down.
I would like to call Mr. Arthur Kirk.
Do you solemnly swear that...
...your testimony shall be the truth,
the whole truth, and nothing but the truth?
- I do.
- Be seated.
Mr. MacMillan?
How old was the defendant
when you married her mother?
Claudia was 5.
At that time, was there anything about her
that would have led you to believe...
...that Claudia was troubled?
She was frightened. They were both
frightened when I first met them.
They'd been abandoned, you see,
by Claudia's natural father.
So you would describe her
as frightened, traumatized?
Objection. The prosecution is
putting words in his mouth.
Overruled. Continue, Mr. Kirk.
Yes, sir.
She was always on guard, distrustful.
I shouldn't say always.
There were periods when she was happy.
But they were short-lived.
Did you get along well?
We got along fine.
I was her champion.
What do you mean?
Well...
...I forbade Rose to spank her.
Children should never be spanked.
It breaks their spirit.
- You tried to be a good father to her?
- Yes, I tried.
When I was courting her mother,
she said to me:
"Art, what about Claudia Faith? "
I didn't say, "Send her off to school,
get rid of her, send her away."
No, sir, I said,
"Rose, if you love her, I love her."
When she woke up
in the middle of the night...
...crying because of bad dreams,
I was the one who went to her.
I didn't know much about children,
but I learned.
And later, when she got a little older...
...I even took her to the office with me.
Given your years with her...
...and the close relationship
that you shared...
...would you say that you
understood her pretty well?
Objection. Leading the witness.
Overruled.
I understood her pretty well, yes,
I think so.
She was a troubled, but lovely, child.
A joy to be with, in spite of everything.
Even though I don't have the opportunity
to see her now...
...I’m sure she's a very special woman.
Were you surprised
when her marriage collapsed?
No.
All that surprised me was
that the marriage lasted that long.
I didn't know Peter until after the marriage.
I didn't know him well.
- He's a remarkable young man.
- You hated him.
Mrs. Draper, don't start up again.
That didn't mean anything
when he swore to tell the truth?
- He hated Peter's guts.
- You'll have an opportunity to speak later.
Speaking as a loving and devoted parent...
...do you believe
your stepdaughter needs hospitalization?
Yes.
I'm sorry to say I do.
Honey?
Go away, Peter.
Don't do this to me again.
I don't want to hurt you.
I promise, I'll just hold you.
Claudia? I love you.
Come on, open the door.
Mr. Kirk, did you hate Peter?
No, no, not at all.
I may have had
the typical father's reaction.
No man was good enough for my daughter.
- I see.
- Forget him.
You tied my hands pretty good.
Let me walk around a little bit, okay?
Mr. Kirk, do you have any idea
why Claudia attacked...
...her former attorney, Clarence Middleton?
Obviously, she didn't like his advice.
What was that advice?
I recall he suggested a hospital would be
a better place for her than Ryker's Island.
- Really?
- He felt it was the best way.
I see. "The best way."
The best way.
When you and Mrs. Kirk
talked to Dr. Morrison...
...when you chatted with him...
...about the crime
Claudia had been charged with...
...did he also indicate to you that...
...he thought it was the best way?
Mr. Levinsky, a trial is a public event.
If she were your daughter,
would you want her laughed at?
Hammered to a pulp by the attorneys
and the press?
She's just a client to you.
Day after tomorrow, you're gone.
But she's not just a client to me.
I'm not going to see her humiliated
in front of the whole world, no, sir.
No, this is not a common criminal.
My child is ill. She's sick.
And I will do everything I possibly can
to see that she gets better.
And that doesn't mean letting her sit here
in a public courtroom and be destroyed.
When you and Mrs. Kirk
were first married...
Strike that.
You're wasting your time.
Mr. Kirk, it's very clear to me
that both you and your wife...
...were very warm, loving parents.
- Both of you loved Claudia...
- And we still do.
That's right.
That's why I don't understand why...
...Claudia could behave
the way you described.
She was abandoned.
Her father walked out on her.
She was frightened, unprotected.
You replaced him
with something substantial.
Isn't that correct?
With love, affection and security.
All of those.
- Lf that's the case, it doesn't make sense.
- No, it certainly does not.
Maybe you gave her too much.
Maybe you were too generous.
I'm not ashamed to say I was generous.
I'm a generous man.
Well, is it possible then that you,
you spoiled her?
Look, I loved her.
And when you love someone,
you give them things.
Christmas, birthdays, graduation.
When she was young, I gave her presents.
When she got older, I gave her
gift certificates, sometimes cash.
- Cash?
- Yes.
Sorry. My mother always told me
it was wrong to give children money.
I'm afraid I disagree with your mother.
I'm a businessman.
To me, running a home is like
running a business.
You want someone to do something,
you give them an incentive to do it.
For instance, if she, let's say,
straightened out her room...
...she got $1.
If she came home from school
with a good report, she got $10.
- Like a reward.
- Exactly.
Let them have money,
give them a responsibility.
Let them make their own choices.
Now what did Claudia choose?
Mr. Kirk, isn't it true
that what Claudia did...
...was withdraw from you and Mrs. Kirk?
And from her husband Peter,
and from everyone else in her life.
God knows what's left
for her to withdraw from.
Speak no evil.
The people in your life have no mouths.
What can they talk about?
- Come on, Claudia, help me out.
- Stop it.
Mr. Levinsky?
- Have you finished with the witness?
- Not quite yet, Your Honor.
You can bang that goddamn glass
all you want. I'm questioning this witness.
Boy, you must be a saint.
You really must be.
Only a saint could love
a frustrating woman like this.
- Do you really love a woman like this?
- I've always loved her.
How? How could you do that?
This is a woman even a father could hate,
one you could beat with a belt.
- Is this your idea of humor?
- This line of questioning is irrelevant.
- I'll allow it.
- Did you ever lose your temper?
- Sometimes, yes, I lost my temper.
- You did?
- I even spanked her.
- You did spank her!
I recall you told Mr. MacMillan
that you never spanked her.
Once or twice, if you call a smack
on the fanny a spank. Then I did.
And I probably did
a lot of other stupid things...
...but I was always there for her.
I helped her with her homework,
dressed her, bathed her.
I was the one
who gave her breakfast before school.
She never drove you crazy?
Come on, Mr. Kirk.
I know you're the perfect father,
but you never lost control?
Stop that.
- Didn't you ever want to beat her?
- Arthur would never hurt Claudia.
How would you know, Mama?
Mrs. Kirk, sit down, please.
Rose, sit down, darling, please.
Mr. Levinsky?
Mr. Levinsky.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, Your Honor.
Proceed.
Mr. Kirk...
...you said that among
the many fatherly duties...
...that you assumed
when Claudia entered your life was...
...bathing her.
Do you remember saying that?
- Please respond verbally.
- Yes, I did.
How long did you practice
this particular fatherly duty?
Objection, Your Honor!
Overruled. Answer the question, Mr. Kirk.
I don't remember.
Did it stop when she was 5?
Did it go on a year and stop
when she was 6?
What are you suggesting?
Did it stop in two years when she was 7?
I remind you you're under oath.
I don't know. Not long.
- She liked me to do it.
- Do what?
- To bathe her.
- To bathe her?
To bathe her.
It was nothing!
I object to your insinuations!
My daughter locked me out
of the bathroom when she was 4.
- How old was Claudia?
- Claudia, please.
How old was she? 10? 12?
How old were you?
How old was she?
Was she 13 when you stopped bathing her?
Was she 14?
- She was a child...
- How old?
- He's harassing the witness.
- I'd like to hear an answer.
- How old?
- I don't remember.
I was 16.
What else occurred in that bathroom
between you and your stepdaughter?
What occurred in her bedroom?
Stop it! Stop it!
It's not true, Rose, you know it's not true.
Did you make her your lover?
- I told you, it was nothing.
- How old was she, Mr. Kirk?
That's enough, Mr. Levinsky.
When did it begin?
You little bastard! Look what you've done.
Didn't you make
your stepdaughter your lover?
That's enough, Mr. Levinsky.
Tell them it's a mistake.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Calm yourself.
Claudia, believe me, it's not true.
Mr. Kirk, sit down!
- Claudia?
- No, Daddy.
- Claudia, please.
- You stop that!
Tell him it's not true.
Mr. Kirk, control yourself.
Mr. Kirk, you're out of order.
No, please. Don't let him touch me.
- She's not in her right mind.
- That's enough!
I love you, baby.
Tell Daddy what you want.
I'll give it to you. Please!
I'm pleading with you!
Don't let him touch me.
Don't let him hurt me anymore.
It's me.
Aaron.
Aaron?
I'm sorry.
I got so wrapped up
in being a goddamn lawyer.
Did we lose?
Not yet.
Maybe they're right.
Maybe I am crazy.
I didn't tell him to stop!
I didn't tell him to stop.
You were a little girl.
I wanted him to love me, that's all.
Claudia, that's what everybody wants.
Oh, I'm afraid.
I'm afraid, I can't go back.
I'll go crazy in there again.
Don't be afraid.
You're sane.
Do you hear me?
You got to go home on the subway.
What?
You're supposed to be with the missus.
No.
No, I'm supposed to be right here.
Get up.
- What?
- Get up. We have to talk.
I'm eating.
You finished.
- You got a problem?
- You drugged my client.
After what you put her through,
I had to give her some sedation.
- I want her lucid. Not drugged.
- She'll be fine tomorrow.
If she's a zombie tomorrow,
I'll sue your ass.
Don't threaten me,
you lawyer son of a bitch!
Bon appetit.
You don't have to do this today.
I'm okay.
Mr. Levinsky, are you ready to proceed?
Yes, I am.
I call the defendant, Claudia Faith Draper.
Mrs. Draper, you may testify
from your seat, if you like.
Why?
I thought you might be more comfortable.
I'd rather go on the stand.
I have no objection to your being
sworn in right there.
I'm not an invalid, I'm a witness, right?
Witnesses go in the box.
So, if you don't mind...
- As you like.
- Thank you.
I'm not gonna hurt you. Relax.
Left hand on the Bible, raise your right.
Do you swear the testimony you shall give
shall be the truth...
...the whole truth
and nothing but the truth?
- I certainly do.
- Please be seated.
Are you okay?
Mrs. Draper...
You understand
the charge made against you?
- The manslaughter charge, right?
- Yes.
Could you define it for me?
First-degree manslaughter
is a Class B felony...
...under...
...2.5 point something
of the Penal Law Code?
I forgot...
Have you been given any medication
in the last 24 hours?
- Tranquilizers, sedatives?
- Yes, I told him I didn't need them.
Objection, Your Honor.
If he wants medical testimony,
he can question Dr. Morrison.
Sustained.
Tell me your understanding
of the legal concept...
...of justifiable force?
That's when someone's beating
your brains out and...
...you can stop them any way you can.
Thank you.
Would you tell us your understanding...
...of the provisions of the 730 process?
Yeah.
If I lose today,
they can commit me for a year.
Sixty days before the year is up,
the hospital can ask to retain me.
If I lose again...
...I’m gone for another year.
From then on,
it's two-thirds of the maximum sentence...
...which comes out to be...
...sixteen or 17 years without a trial.
Your Honor...
Mr. MacMillan, you'll have ample time
to cross-exam. Let her finish.
Mrs. Draper...
...what does all that mean to you?
It means if they do it right,
they can lock me up...
...in a mental hospital forever.
- The witness is exaggerating.
- No, I'm not.
There's a book on the table,
called Criminal Law of New York.
Look it up.
The witness is extending
the practical limits of the statute.
I didn't write the book.
The Honorable Eugene R. Canudo...
...Judge, New York City Criminal Court,
he wrote it.
However it's executed, that is the statute,
as you should know.
Proceed, Mr. Levinsky.
Can you tell us the names of the doctors
who examined you?
Yes, I can.
Julio Arantes and Herbert Morrison.
Herbert A. Morrison.
And how long was
Dr. Arantes' examination?
Fifteen, maybe 20 minutes.
He barely speaks English.
Objection.
He doesn't.
His Spanish isn't so hot, either.
How long was Dr. Morrison's examination?
Fifty, fifty-five minutes.
He knows more English.
Tell me, do you accept the findings
of these examinations...
...given to you at the hospital?
I do not.
Do you believe you are mentally prepared
to go to trial?
Yes, I do.
Thank you.
I have no more questions.
Mr. MacMillan?
- Claudia, if you're tired...
- I'm not tired.
And I'd like you to call me Mrs. Draper.
Very well.
When I get tired I'll let you know.
Mrs. Draper...
Are you tired?
How long were you married?
Six weeks short of 10 years.
Was this a happy marriage?
It had its moments.
- Do you have children from this marriage?
- No.
Was that by choice?
Yes.
Whose choice?
We agreed.
You jointly agreed?
Yes. I told him if I got pregnant,
I'd leave him. So he agreed.
- And you didn't get pregnant?
- No, I did.
- You did get pregnant?
- Yes, I did.
We came home late from a party one night
and we were a little drunk.
I put too much jelly
on my diaphragm and...
Did your husband leave you
when you got pregnant?
No, I had an abortion.
Why?
I don't believe in childhood.
Did you love your husband?
I don't know.
Where did you move
when your marriage collapsed?
I guess I loved him.
What?
Where did you move?
501 East 66th Street.
- You lived there at the time of your arrest?
- Yeah.
- What is the rent at that address?
- $2,400 a month.
When you moved in,
what was your income?
Peter gave me $10,000 when I signed
the separation agreement.
Did you ask your parents for money?
No.
Could Mr. MacMillan tell us why he is
so fascinated with Mrs. Draper's finances?
Does he plan to sell her a car?
Where are you heading?
My next group of questions will show,
Your Honor, if you'll indulge me.
Proceed.
So you lived off the $10,000
your husband gave you?
No, I spent that on furniture
and kitchen stuff.
What did you live on?
- Gifts.
Gifts from whom?
- Friends.
- Men friends?
And what did these men friends give you?
Jewelry?
Sometimes.
Furs?
I got a fox boa once.
- Did they give you food?
- Food?
One guy used to bring caviar.
Is that what you mean?
Did you exchange your jewels and furs
for food at the market?
- Isn't that silly?
- Did you?
No.
- I assume you didn't live on caviar.
- Hardly.
Did you use those gifts to pay your rent?
Excuse me.
Is it legal to take cash gifts?
I beg your pardon?
I mean, if I say to you, "Stanley,
here's $500 just because I like you... "
...is that legal?
Yes, that's legal.
Thank you. A lot of the gifts were cash.
And these cash gifts were enough
to pay your expenses?
What did these men expect in exchange
for the cash gifts?
- Is counsel leading up to...
- Your Honor, I haven't used the word "fee."
I'll permit an answer.
What did these men friends expect
in return for these cash gifts?
Friendship.
"Friendship." What kind of friendship?
Objection! The question is vague
and misleading.
Overruled.
These men that gave you cash gifts,
did they expect you to talk to them?
- Did you listen to them?
- God, yes.
- And you did them favors?
- Your Honor.
You did them favors. What kind?
Objection on the same grounds.
What kind of favors did you do
in exchange for these gifts?
What does it matter how Mrs. Draper
makes her living?
What kind of favors?
Let's stop all the bullshit
and get to the point.
You want to know what I do for a living?
Ask me.
My time is very expensive, Mr. MacMillan.
Probably more than yours.
I get $500 an hour. How much do you get?
I get $400 for a straight lay,
$300 for a hand job and $500 for head.
If you wanna wear my panties,
that's another $100.
You take them home, Mr. MacMillan,
No whips, no ropes, no spikes.
I've got liquor and grass.
Anything else, you bring your own.
It works like this.
You call me up, we make a date.
I look you over. And if I like you...
...we make a deal.
And, darling, I am worth the trouble.
Take my word for it, if you want the best.
Do you want the best, Mr. MacMillan?
I am talking about
taking your body to heaven...
...and sending your mind south.
I'm talking about spoiling you so bad...
...you'll hate every other woman you touch.
I'm talking about my mouth
on your mouth...
...and my tongue...
...anywhere you want it.
I'm talking about indulging
your every fantasy...
...and then giving you those fantasies
one by one.
Just for you. All for you. Nobody but you.
Do you get all that, darling?
Would you like that, baby?
Do you get what I'm telling you?
Do you all get what I'm telling you?
Now, could he bust me for that?
Can he...
No, he can't bust you.
Good.
- That's very enlightening.
- I thought you'd like it.
How long did you perform these favors?
35 months, 24 days.
Why did you perform these favors?
For $100,000 a year, net.
Did you ever ask your parents for money?
No.
Do you believe they would have refused
to give it to you?
No, they would have given it to me.
But you preferred living a life
of exchanging favors for gifts.
It hurts less to sell yourself to strangers.
If you were in the same position today,
would you make the same choice?
She's not in the same position today.
I'd like an answer.
I might.
You would rather lead that life
than ask your parents for money?
Probably, yeah.
Mrs. Draper, would you describe
your behavior...
...in the courtroom the past days as...
...normal?
Would you consider
the circumstances normal?
It's my job to ask the questions,
your obligation is to answer.
Yesterday this hearing had to adjourn...
...because you were no longer able
to participate.
The truth is, I didn't have a nifty childhood.
Poor me. Life sucks.
Yesterday...
...you all had a good time
watching me and my stepfather squirm.
Okay, it's out. It's over.
It's a fact of life.
I'll handle it.
The point is,
it's not relevant to what's going on here.
You don't trust me, do you?
Are you crazy?
I'm sorry, that's your question.
Have I done anything to harm you?
I don't believe this.
You're trying to put me away.
You don't believe I'm simply doing my job?
Your job is to put me in a hospital.
Maybe I'm dumb,
but I take that personally!
But you believe Dr. Morrison
is acting out of a personal motive?
No.
I'm sure he believes what he believes.
He thinks whores are girls on 8th Avenue,
who stick needles in their arms.
Whores aren't nice white girls
from nice white homes.
He knows that as sure
as he knows his wife is home...
...cleaning the oven.
Isn't that right, Herbie?
But what if he's wrong?
What if his wife is out balling
the insurance salesman?
What if he doesn't know his ass
from his elbow?
What if he is just an asshole
with the power to lock me up?
What if that's all he is?
An asshole with power.
Your Honor, forgive me for interrupting.
I believe the pressure of this proceeding
is doing serious harm to the patient.
She should be sent back to the hospital.
With due respect, Dr. Morrison,
I have a witness testifying...
...and I'd like to hear it without interruption.
Please sit down.
For her sake, Your Honor, I insist...
I said, please, sit down.
Proceed, Mr. MacMillan.
Do you trust His Honor, the court?
More than I trust you.
Do you trust Mr. Levinsky?
As lawyers go, he's all right.
Do you trust your mother, Mrs. Kirk?
- My mother?
- Yes. Do you trust your mother?
No.
Is there anyone in this courtroom
you do trust?
Him.
You're pointing at Officer Harrison?
Officer Harrison is the only person
in this room you trust?
He can't hurt me. You can.
The judge can, Morrison can. She can.
I don't trust people who can hurt me,
not anymore.
You believe your mother
wants to hurt you?
- She doesn't want to, but...
- You don't believe she wants to help you?
Sure she does. You all want to "help" me.
Except for Harry. Harry doesn't give a shit.
You don't believe your mother loves you?
God, of course, she loves me.
She told you that. Didn't you hear her?
He wrote it down.
Now you stand up there asking,
"Do you love your daughter? "
And she says, "Yes, I love my daughter."
And you think
you've asked something real?
And she thinks she said something real?
You think because you toss
this word "love" around...
...like a Frisbee
we're all gonna get warm and runny?
No.
Sometimes people love you so much...
...their love is like a goddamn gun
that keeps firing straight into your head.
They love you so much
you go right into a hospital.
Right, Mama?
I didn't know.
No, you didn't want to know.
Mrs. Draper, I'm a little confused.
Do you love your mother?
Sure, I love her.
So what?
No further questions, Your Honor.
Mrs. Draper.
Mrs. Draper. You may step down.
Your Honor,
I would like to recall Dr. Herbert Morrison.
You were fine. You told the truth.
- I don't think anybody heard me.
- I heard you.
Doctor, I remind you,
you're still under oath.
In view of the defendant's testimony
and all that's happened...
...have you changed your opinion
as to her capacity?
Absolutely not.
Wait one goddamned minute.
Mrs. Draper?
Capacity? Why me? Why not him?
Did they examine him for his capacity?
Did they examine her?
I know a judge who jerks off under his robe.
Was he tested?
You are no longer on the stand.
Then put me back on the goddamn stand
until I convince you!
Don't whip me with your rules.
While you're playing
with your goddamn rules...
...the meter is running out on my life.
Let her go.
Thank you.
Look, I know...
I know I'm supposed to be a good little girl
for my mother and father.
An obedient wife to my husband.
Stick out my tongue for the doctor.
Lower my head for the judge.
I know all that.
I know what you expect me to do.
But I'm not just...
...a picture in your heads.
Do you understand?
I'm not just a daughter or a wife...
...or a hooker or a patient or a defendant.
Can't you get that?
You think...
...giving blow jobs for $500 is nuts.
Well, I know women who...
...marry men they despise
so they can drive a Mercedes...
...and spend summers in the Hamptons.
I know women who crawl through shit
for a fur coat.
I know women who peddle their daughters
to hang onto their husbands.
So don't judge my blow jobs.
They're sane.
I knew what I was doing
every goddamn minute.
And I'm responsible for it.
I lift my skirt, I'm responsible.
I go down on my knees, I am responsible.
Now, if I play this part
you all seem to want me to play...
...if I play sick, I won't be responsible.
"Poor, sick Claudia. She needs our help."
I won't play that part, do you hear me?
I won't give you that out.
I won't be another picture in your heads.
Claudia, the nut!
Do you get what I'm telling you?
He can sign a piece of paper
saying I'm nuts...
...but it's only a piece of paper.
You can't make me nuts that way,
no matter how many times you sign it.
No matter how much you say it,
you can't make me nuts!
Or you, Mama!
Get it straight, all of you.
I won't be nuts for you.
Did you get that?
Mr. MacMillan, you may proceed.
Dr. Morrison, do you still believe she lacks
the capacity to stand trial?
Yes, I do.
- No further questions.
- Mr. Levinsky?
I have no more questions.
You may step down, Doctor.
Do you rest, Mr. MacMillan?
The People rest.
Mr. Levinsky?
Thank you.
Your Honor...
...my client is a real pain in the ass.
Excuse me.
She is ill-mannered and irritating and she...
...disturbs the peace.
But we shouldn't confuse her behavior
with her capacity to stand trial.
The defense rests.
Mr. Levinsky.
I would consider adjourning this hearing
for 14 days...
...if the defendant would consent
to an independent psychiatric examination.
Absolutely not.
That's a mistake, Counsel.
But if that's the way she wants it...
I'm going to call a short recess
and collect my thoughts.
You'll have my decision in a few moments.
Please be seated.
Claudia.
I'm sorry I yelled at you, Mama.
I want you to win, sweetheart.
I want you to have whatever you want
for the rest of your life.
Mama?
I...
Can I touch you?
Forgive me. I'm so ashamed.
Oh, baby.
I still love you.
"To the moon and down again
and around the world and back again."
It's all right. Why don't you go sit down?
- Yes.
- It won't be long now.
Thank you, I will.
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
Now, some people might call this larceny.
I would call it bad manners.
Consider it your fee.
Would you like me to sign it?
What would you say?
Something that would get you
in big trouble if the missus found it.
The missus.
You're okay, Levinsky.
Even though you think
I'm a real pain in the ass.
The court is deeply concerned
that the defendant will not permit...
...an independent medical examination
on her behalf.
It's a critical flaw in her case.
Nor has her behavior in this courtroom
inspired the confidence of the Bench.
On the other hand...
...the court is not satisfied that
the opinions expressed by Dr. Morrison...
...are completely persuasive.
I do agree with him that Mrs. Draper
does need some kind of help.
But that is not my role here.
My role is to determine...
...whether the defendant
is competent to stand trial.
...and that depends on
two factors only. One:
Can she understand
the charge against her?
Two: Can she assist in her own defense?
From what I have witnessed in
this courtroom these past two days...
...the answer to both those questions...
...is yes.
I therefore find the defendant
competent to stand trial...
...release her on her own recognizance
to await trial on the felony charge...
...of manslaughter in the first degree...
...which trial shall take place
one month from today. Court dismissed.
Your Honor,
the defendant has been charged...
...with a particularly cold-blooded crime.
- The People request a high bail.
- You've heard my decision, Mr. MacMillan.
- Court dismissed.
- Thank you, Stanley!
- Congratulations.
- See you in court, Levinsky.
- You did okay by yourself today.
- I did, didn't I?
- Maybe I'll change professions.
- Where you going?
Out!
And I poured it on the flat.
And I poured it on the store.
And then I said,
"Hey, what are you gonna do?
"What are you gonna do? "
And may God make...
5@y3