I'm not available at the moment.
Please leave a message.
I'll get back to you as soon as possible.
Have you called the police yet?
It's not my fault.
Have you called the police?
It's not my fault...
Have you?
It's not my fault.
I have.
He rushed the traffic lights.
Hold on, bro.
The ambulance's coming.
Help!
How're you, bro?
Cell phone...
Here you are.
Battery?
I'll fix it for you.
What's the number? I'll dial it for you.
Kirk... What's wrong?
The driver of 1314 has an accident!
What should we do?
Where's Elvis? I don't know.
Call him now!
Man, I was so worry about you.
Where're you?
Man...
Man? Hello...
Who are you looking for, ma'am?
Man Liang.
What's your relationship to him?
Fiancee.
Wait a minute.
Is that her?
He had brain bleeding.
We tried our best but can't make it.
No... no.
I think you've made a mistake.
He just gave me a call.
I think you really must've made a mistake.
Sorry.
No... This can't be... it cannot be him.
He just called me.
It must be you guys who made a mistake...
Please check it again, will you?
Ma'am, please stay calm.
C'mon.
I'm calm. But you've made a mistake.
That guy is not him!
Why are you here, Hale?
How is it?
It's alright.
Let's go there.
Here.
Doctor... Who are you looking for?
The driver of 1314... we're friends.
No... impossible...
He's just given me a call.
Ma'am it's the destination.
Isn't the North Street your destination?
How do you know that?
I usually give you a ride.
You're so "ugly". Who would forget you?
I wanna listen to this song.
Can I get off later?
Sure.
I can give you the CD,
OK? Great.
Maybe it's not such a goof idea.
You can listen to the song whenever
you catch my ride anyway.
What's the matter?
You ran away from home?
It's dangerous for a girl
to wander around so late.
Tell me your address. I'll take you home.
Isn't it... more dangerous?
Though I look like a playboy,
I'm a good bloke.
Look at my face...
Wait a minute. I pick up my boss home.
Hello.
You're off? Yes.
Thanks.
What's wrong?
Wanna eat something?
Let's go.
Do you like kids? You may play with him.
Whose baby is this?
Stupid question.
This smart baby must be my son.
Spacious!
Definitely.
You wouldn't believe this...
An old lady who usually catch my ride.
She walks like my mum,
so I helped her to get on and off.
Later we became friends.
When she knew I wanna rent a flat,
she showed me this.
Guess the rent.
How much?
Just three thousand something.
So nice guys always get rewards.
It's near the stop.
It takes less time for you to travel.
But it costs a lot.
Money is not a problem,
as long as this is a nice place.
Where should we put our sofa?
This kind of difficult design work...
it's better to leave it for your decision.
Sofa in beige colour
and wall sky blue.
Colourful curtain. Like a rainbow.
It makes you happy when you look at it.
You own my minibus.
You keep my passbook.
After getting married,
you can't return them to me.
When will you tell your dad?
I don't want to get into a scrap with him.
What?
Well... I'll invite him to come
for a dinner later.
It's me who tell him
about our wedding, OK?
Talk about this later.
Or let's try... the new room.
There's not even a bed.
No problem. I've never tried new poses.
Laurie. Time to go to school. Get changed.
I'll take you to a restaurant for breakfast.
Get changed.
I'll take you to restaurant
for breakfast, okay?
Laurie, remember... work hard.
Put the books into the bag.
Listen to the teacher, OK?
You can't be late for school, Laurie.
Get changed.
Where's your bag?
I've told you... don't put the bag
in the wrong place.
Where're your slippers?
Wash up. Be quick!
Ma'am, your money.
Have hair cut or washed, ma'am?
It's moved?
It's the next shop.
Hello. Miss Lam.
Please sit.
I give you a bag, Miss Lam.
Thanks.
Hello?
It's mum.
I've told your dad that
You and Man will come back
for a dinner tonight.
Do come back.
He's only long-winded.
Hello... are you listening to me?
Man's dead.
What?
He died in a traffic accident.
Holly...
How are you? Are you OK?
Come on.
Don't stay in the street. Go back.
Jesus...
I can't cry.
It's ex gratia payment.
Thank you.
I gotta work. Take care.
I was just on the scene.
It was me who called you that night.
I hung up as I saw you
come to the hospital.
It's me.
What's your name?
Laurie.
Sir?
Just call me Hale. I go now.
Thanks Welcome.
Laurie.
What's that?
Laurie the good boy,
let's put it into the niche together.
Don't open it.
It's daddy.
Yeah, he's dead.
Dead?
What is 'dead'?
It's... going on a trip.
Are they all going on a trip?
Why don't they take us with them?
Don't ask this kind of question.
Holly, I don't think it's good for you
to take care of Laurie...
It's alright, dad. Please take care of mum.
You also take care of yourself, Holly.
Mum, don't worry. I'm fine.
Come in.
Come here, Laurie.
It's pretty good.
Honey, come have a look.
Grandma.
Good boy...
Your dad and sis come see you.
We've worked together
for a long time, Peter.
It's not about the problem of trust.
Ye know... there're a lot of deceivers.
If you aren't firm,
don't get me into the troubles.
Bankruptcy is possible!
Laurie's a good boy.
Congratulations.
When did you become a grandma?
OK. That's it.
What's up?
Tell Helen: don't send him the cheque.
Your friend's not reliable.
What are you going to do now?
Go back to your room, Laurie.
I'm talking to you!
Fine.
What?
I mean what will you do?
Calm down.
Are you gonna raise that kid?
Yeah.
You've made up your mind.
No need to care about you, right?
Any problem?
We may go then.
Stay calm. Let's discuss this issue.
Sit down...
There's no need to discuss any more.
Let's go, dad.
Sharon...
Holly, how can you go on like this?
Anything to be discussed? She's great.
No need to worry.
Or talk about Laurie's issue with his mum.
Ask her to take care of him.
Let's go. She doesn't want us to interfere.
I'll wait for you downstairs.
Wait a minute...
Honey...
Keys, mum.
Don't be like this.
I'll make some soup
or do the cleaning for you.
Keys.
NO WAY!
I got it repaired, Hale. Have a look.
The mirrors and walkie talkie
have been removed.
The worn tyres are also replaced.
You're truly a vampire.
This minibus's useless.
Excuse me. Who's Charles?
Yeah.
Miss Lam? Charles
I want to get this minibus repaired.
How much is it?
Get it repaired?
It's better to replace it.
Maybe the engine still works.
But this minibus isn't lucky.
Don't bullshit.
Go to work...
Charles
Can you make it the same as before?
Well... miscellaneous included...
a hundred and ten thousand or more.
So expensive?
No.
Isn't there insurance?
Yeah...
But you have to pay
thirty thousand something first.
And thirty thousand something
for loading next year.
Maybe no insurance company
will accept the application.
It doesn't make sense.
Charles, how about eighty thousand?
Eighty thousand? No way.
Eighty thousand. No more bargain.
No way.
Well I'll call a tow company to tow it away.
Alright...
This time it's me who bear the cost.
I'll give it a try
Thanks and I want it to look
just the same as before.
Master! Please adjust the clutch pedal
to a higher position.
I have to fully step on it
to shift the gear. Too slow.
You car-racing?
Let me have a check first.
Hurry up. Gotta work.
OK. It's alright.
What's the matter?
Forget to bring the tea leaves.
You go to restaurant first
and I'll take the tea leaves.
I got it repaired. It's like brand new.
Thanks, Charles.
Thank you.
Lease it out?
No, I'll drive it on my own.
Well...
You are in the gear...
And fasten the seatbelt.
Which horse should we bet on?
Have a drink.
Thanks.
Welcome.
Who's this?
A woman.
Stop!
Hale, you're in "good luck".
Loudmouth.
Sorry. I didn't hit it on purpose.
I know. It doesn't matter.
That night... thanks.
It was a petty matter.
You're looking for somebody?
Yeah, I want to see Elvis.
Elvis, can you do me a favour?
Sit down.
What's the matter?
I want a place for the route
from this terminus.
Are you kidding?
I have a minibus driving license.
But you've never driven minibus.
I can manage.
I know...
But somebody has taken Man's place.
Just an extra vehicle.
If I had say, I wouldn't be
the terminal co-ordinator.
Well I'll talk about this with the boss.
But you have to pay for the place. It's a rule.
Man's paid for it.
But the sum is by head count not vehicle.
It's around a hundred thousand something.
But I don't have so much money.
You can be a freelancer.
You can run any routes.
See it as paid training sessions.
Thanks.
Welcome.
You go?
I reverse to make way for you.
Go away or she might hit you.
What?
Two inches left...
Tell all the bros:
stay away from this woman.
Look. What's she doing?
Ma'am, you stole the minibus?
Got a driving license?
Need some guidance?
Come with me and I'll teach you how?
Come have a chat. C'mon.
Wait!
Have a chat!
Laurie, c'mon.
Eat them all. Don't waste them.
Enough? I give you more.
You're hurt?
Wear daddy's gloves.
Good boy. Now finish it.
Laurie, work hard.
And aunt will earn more money
and buy you more toys, OK?
I'm late.
Bitch. How come you overtake
in this way!
Ma'am, the sign's wrong.
Thanks.
Christ, late again!
Can you hurry up a little bit? I'm in a rush.
Look. The tram's faster than you.
Yeah, Please hurry up.
Got it.
How do you drive?
Sorry...
I don't have any change.
It doesn't matter.
Clearway! What?
Get off!
What's the matter, sir?
No stopping.
No stopping?
Clearway!
Here's a clearway?
7 a.m. to 12 a.m.!
Driving license.
Give me a chance, sir.
Driving license!
Still here? Forty-five minutes passed.
Poor.
Five hundred. Fuel, miscellaneous...
and a ticket.
Three hundred and twenty... My God.
Bastard! That bloke in suit...
What's the matter?
What're you doing, Laurie?
You break the pipe.
Get up. Quick.
Laurie, go to bed on your own.
Be a good boy.
I'm not available at the moment.
Please leave a message.
I'll get back to you as soon as possible.
Daddy, I'm going to bed.
When'll you be back?
I miss you so much.
And aunt's driving is really poor.
She drives very slowly.
Goodnight, daddy.
You look familiar, ma'am.
You used to run taxi service?
I seldom see such a young girl
running minibus service.
You like driving?
I want to hire a driver.
Want to work with me?
That's enough. Sit down.
So annoying!
I really want to hire a driver.
Be my driver...
Leave me alone!
Get off now!
This is too much!
You throw up on my bus?
Why are you so fierce?
Go!
Cross the harbour? Get on the bus.
Cross the harbour? Yeah.
Get on.
Hey...
You can't load passengers here!
I'm going now...
Sorry.
Please catch the next ride back.
Next ride back. Sorry.
Are you crazy?
If you'd been a man, I'd have hit you.
Go away!
Go!
I'm not available at the moment.
Please leave a message.
I'll get back to you as soon as possible.
Man...
I miss you.
Can you hear me?
Laurie...
Good boy. Help dad clean the vehicle.
Look at your grubby hands.
Give me your hands.
You'd said it's easy to run minibus service?
The passengers scolded me...
The cops gave me a ticket...
those gangs kicked me out...
And I received a fake note.
Why can't I take the passengers
at the terminal?
Tell me... what to do.
Well... Goodbye.
It's only the first day. Not used to it yet
I can manage.
It won't be late.
Wait for me at the terminal.
Take a rest. Tomorrow's another day.
I can manage.
That woman is really unbearable.
She has no ideas
about the signs and signals.
The taxi driver behind
blew horn to rush her.
She's nearly got lost.
She's so skinny and
still worked for two shifts.
She did?
Sure
Big Fool saw her last night.
Even us feel exhausted
after driving twelve hours.
How can she stand a job like this?
That's the point.
Do me a favour. Help her.
Crazy.
His fiancee's died just recently.
Women need comfort.
Don't say this, OK!
Her boyfriend's just died.
She needs to pay the minibus mortgage
and raise Man's son.
Isn't she the mother of the child?
No. Man was divorced.
This lady's pretty good.
Sorry. May I ask you a question?
You were on the scene
of Man's accident, right?
Did he tell you anything?
Not a word?
He seemed to tell me...
He said, "tell her to be stronger.
Don't be too sad."
Maybe he wanted me to tell you these.
Then he asked me
to pick up the cell phone.
He might want to call you.
But he didn't make it.
How was he at that time?
Was he very painful?
It was just a short while.
I don't think he suffered much.
Thanks.
Not at all.
Excuse me. Please make way for me.
I need to drive the vehicle away.
There's enough room.
I'll help you.
Thanks.
These roads are narrow. Give it back later.
Why do you start with second gear?
It's too slow to use bottom gear for start.
We normally use it on the slope...
or for our own vehicle.
Bottom gear start reduces
the vehicle depreciation.
If you're on the same row with an 'enemy',
waiting for the green light
to hunt for the passenger,
you have to use second gear.
Hunt for passengers...
No hunt, no passengers, right?
That's true.
Remember: wait for the amber light
but do rush when it's alight.
And don't brake hard.
Otherwise, the passengers get hurt easily.
And this makes the vehicle behind
brake hard too
or it may crash your vehicle.
Running minibus service isn't as easy
as I think.
Have you learnt how to run the service?
I... caught Man's ride before.
Well...
I show you once. Be careful.
As a beginner, you must learn the signs,
recognise the routes and
remember the clearways and loading zones.
This sign, no loading during
the periods of 8 a.m. to 10 a.m...
So many restrictions.
But rules and practice
are different.
Do remember this sign.
No stopping at any time.
No loading at any time in this zone.
Turn to another street
for loading and unloading.
But those old passengers
should know this.
Be hawk-eyed.
Unload passengers if needed.
No loading, then accelerate.
The faster the ride, the more the rides.
The more the rides, the more the earnings.
Watch out!
It's always for the giant to bully the tiny.
No need to fear those taxi drivers.
Just drive close to them.
Scare them and they must make way
for you.
Just give them a scare
but don't really crash into them.
Otherwise, you're wasting time.
Look...
Crazy!
That idiot calls a minibus in the red routes.
If you wanna load this passenger,
look the mirrors first
to make sure there're no cops.
No cops. It's safe.
Then go for it.
Hurry up, it's red route.
Take a seat...
Look out!
Are you OK?
Get off in the next mouth.
Please alight beyond the clearway.
Loading only in the clearway.
It ensures an earning.
Unloading may bring you a ticket.
Too risky.
Who pities you?
A passenger.
Hey... you've missed that!
Sorry. Only a bit farther.
Forget about the horn and
complaints.
Why do you run your service like this?
Passengers will understand
your difficulties.
They won't make any troubles for you.
Anyone get off ahead? Gotta paid first.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Any one get off before the red route?
No stopping there
And if there are cops stopping you,
pretend you're not seeing them.
Gamble on fleeing the chase.
If not, beg for a chance.
It's easy for a woman to make it.
Soft tone and sweet smile.
You'll surely make it.
But I failed every time.
Weep then.
Weeping is the best weapon of women.
The cops let you go if they pity you.
Thanks.
Your profit is three times more than mine.
I'm lucky this time.
I broke the record when
I started to run minibus service.
No passenger for whole-day rides.
Hello? Yeah.
I'll come over now.
My son has a fever.
I must pick him up now.
Then your turn.
No, you're faster. It's near the terminus.
OK. Thanks.
Are you OK, Laurie?
Why are you so late?
Take him to see the doctor.
Sorry.
Aunt.
Come here!
I gotta work.
I got something to tell you!
Can you take care of him for a moment?
Just tell me what you want...
once and for all.
I don't want you drop in so suddenly.
Are you crazy?
You really run a minibus service?
Can you stop it?
How can you go on like this?
Man's gone and the story's over.
You still keep his son?
That's enough. Don't say this, OK!
If Man had been alive,
we would've got married
and Laurie would've been my son.
I'll do my best. I'm not that kind
of person like you.
You can't live off on your own.
How can you keep the kid?
So what?
Leave him or
send him to an orphanage?
How about his relatives?
His grandparents only live off
social security. Besides, his grandma's sick.
How about his mum? Where's she?
To be pragmatic, Holly.
You're an adult.
Don't play this kind of romantic game!
Look at you.
You look pallid!
None of your business.
I don't bring any troubles for you, right?
Just as I don't think in the same way
like you do.
I don't need any luxury cars
nor clothing.
I'm still happy.
Is money the only thing on your mind?
Don't talk about me!
I earn money not just for myself.
Who supports dad after he retired?
You spend on the monthly installment,
rent and the kid.
Have you given a buck to the family?
You think of the kid.
Why don't you think of your parents?
You're selfish!
I tell you, don't ask mum for money.
That means she can only
give you the money?
I take the money for investment,
not spend it.
What 'spend it'?
What're you looking at?
She's so fierce.
You know it?
Yeah.
Then am I fierce?
Yes or no...
He really has a fever.
Need to visit the doctor now!
Who's he?
If you go on like this,
both the kid and you will die.
What's the matter?
OK. Just park it aside.
Alright.
Let me carry him.
It's alright. He's heavy. Let me carry him.
Thanks.
Good boy...
Good boy, take some medicine...
Listen to me, good boy...
Don't move or it spills out.
Meal's ready, Laurie."
Come.
Eat the soup. Thanks.
It's hot. Be careful.
Salty and sweet... is it OK?
How's the soup? Seems a bit salty.
No, it tastes good.
Your clothes got dirty.
Is that... I help you.
No, I can do it myself.
Eat it.
Go to bed yourself after dinner, okay?
Your sink pipe got blocked.
Yeah. I've cleared it many times
but still can't fix it.
Buy a drain cleaner.
What? Drink cleaner?
No, D.R.I.A.N. Drain cleaner.
I can help you clear it when I'm available.
Thank you.
I take you to the terminal.
No.
I live in the place nearby.
Take care of the child.
He goes to bed on his own. It's OK.
You leave him alone at home?
What's wrong?
Oh... I forget to make him some milk.
You may go first if you are in a hurry.
He isn't a baby any more.
Still use baby milk bottle?
Yeah, it's his late night refreshment.
I think...
it's difficult... for you to go on like this.
I know you have sentiment on the minibus.
But if you lease it out,
you can put more effort on Laurie.
No, I'm not familiar with any drivers.
What if they crash the vehicle
or go away with it?
Frankly speaking,
do you know how to calculate?
I guess you repay the mortgage
of the vehicle.
Even if it's your own vehicle.
Renting it out is a must.
Two shifts a day. A thousand.
Rent, fuel and tickets...
How much can you earn?
And also the license fee, insurance,
maintenance...
Brake system replacement
at 3-month interval
and tyres 4-month.
Everything needs money.
If you don't do the calculations,
how can you make a profit?
And also the tickets.
If you got more points incurred,
you're disqualified.
You can't count on running
a minibus service then.
With money, you can pay the rent,
tuition and food.
Your sis may be right.
Why are you all the same?
Why do you all...
do calculations on everything?
I believe I can manage.
I don't need your help.
Sorry,
I'm loudmouth.
I'm leaving now. Bye.
Boss, prosperous business?
See. Buy two more fishes.
You really sell the biz to me?
Yeah, I've told you.
So, you do? Keep your promise.
I do. No reason to deceive you, right?
It's more comfortable here.
It was like in the jail just now.
C'mon.
Have a chat each other.
Don't get into fight.
Hale, barbecue again?
Join me for barbecue.
No, I already had a date.
Do come with your friends.
The ribs are pretty good.
Maybe next time.
Hello... Who's calling?
He's not available at the moment.
Hale, gimme a call at once.
Laurie, come on. We back home.
You brought him together during the rides?
Yeah.
Let me carry him.
Thanks.
Two hundred and sixty-two.
No tickets. Less the rent and fuel,
I earn two hundred and sixty-two.
Pretty good. Let's go.
You're awake?
I'm hungry.
I cook for you
Here comes the meal.
It's hot. Be careful.
I got you a night-shift driver.
Go to bed.
What's your name?
Hale.
What should I call you?
Whatever you like.
How about Hale?
I'm old enough to be your dad,
still call me Hale?
Uncle Beard?
What if I don't have beard?
What'll you call me?
Lucky.
What? Lucky?
Lucky is a puppy's name.
Go to bed, good boy.
How about your mum?
No idea. Maybe she's on a trip.
Do you miss your daddy?
Yeah, I miss him so much.
Why does the TV work again?
Lucky got it repaired.
Who's Lucky?
That is Hale.
He also did the curtain, right?
Don't know.
The mirror isn't clear.
Do you get the right spectacles?
Sorry, I got the wrong pair.
Can he manage? I'm worried about him.
It's difficult to find such a reliable driver.
He hands you the minibus on time
and refill the fuel.
Ma'am...
Don't think I'm an idiot.
I raise four children
with the minibus service.
They all got a university degree.
It's boring to stay at home all the time.
So I just wanna kill time.
Hand over at 3 p.m.
He'll park the vehicle outside your home.
Thank you, Uncle Chiu.
OK. Bye.
I go to work now.
Hale, do me a favour to raise my son too.
Iced lemon tea. Got it.
You help her only. It isn't fair to me.
Hale dress up and got shaved.
You're gonna get her soon.
Still pretend to be cool?
Shut up.
Hale, let's place a bet for 3T together.
He has given up on gambling
for a long time.
Besides, he needs to saves money.
That's it.
The economy is halted.
Always got a free gift whatever you buy.
A widow with a son as a gift.
No need to pay for the napkins.
Yeah
What're you talking about?
Just kidding. What's wrong?
You wanna make troubles?
Hale...
You think you're still well-off?
Still got vehicles for lease?
That's not the case!
Look at you! What did you say?
Relax. Just minor business, right?
Don't fight over this.
Get on board...
Go. Set off!
The tyres have worn out.
Two seats left. Get on.
Come on!
You steal my passengers!
Another ride.
The tyres have worn out.
Have you called the tow service?
It's expensive.
Please help me change it.
Can't make it.
Why?
Trust me. Replace the tyres in the garage.
Please hurry up.
Watch out and go back to the pavement.
Ma'am, this doesn't work.
Take it to the garage.
Hello?
Hello. Has your vehicle been on tow?
Yeah, thanks.
Where're you?
At the terminal.
Can you pick Laurie up?
I can't make it on time.
Yeah, I'll go now.
Bye.
Sorry. Ladies and gentlemen,
please get on the next ride.
Sorry...
What's the matter?
Hale...
See you tomorrow.
See you.
Sir, you're...
Are you Miss Cheung?
I'm... a friend of his family.
I'll help take him home.
Laurie, who's he?
Lucky.
I'm a friend of his mom's.
But it used to be his dad
who took him home.
My dad died.
Are you crazy?
Sir...
Please tell his family.
They haven't paid the tuition fees
for two months.
Have you taken Laurie home?
Not yet. I want to take him out.
Don't you have to work?
I want to take a rest.
I'll bring him home later.
That's fine.
You bought my tuition fee?
Not 'bought' tuition fee.
I 'paid' your tuition fees.
Could you buy me an ice cream?
Sure.
What favour do you like?
Watch out.
Did uncle buy you all the gifts?
Where's Uncle Chiu?
I've thought about it.
It's better to drive it myself.
Why?
I can get more and save more
from driving by myself.
You made the soup?
What...
Did I forget to pay the tuition fee?
I've paid it for you.
I'll give it back to you.
Take your time.
By the way, I've fixed your sink.
Save your money, man.
It's OK.
I bought them for your kid only.
What? Are you OK?
OK.
Miss Lam, my mom send me
to collect the rent.
Don't worry. I'll pay you soon.
No way...
You've held it off month after month.
I fear no bad tenant!
Miss Lam,
you know the elders live on rent.
Don't worry, I'll pay you after two days.
OK. I'll wait till that day but no more.
I'll come next Monday.
Don't hold it off any more at that time.
Don't worry. The landlady is kind.
It's her daughter who's troublesome.
She fears that I can't pay the rent.
I work so hard.
How can I make no money?
If I hadn't blown the tyre today,
I would have made it.
Eight dollars for crossing the harbour.
Hop in!
Eight dollars only, get in.
Damn, stop!
Stop!
Open the door!
How dare you! Stop...
Damn it! I'll dig you up.
Where did the clunker 1314 come from?
It seemed to come from Eastern District.
Good. Anyway,
tell our men to get her tonight!
Got it!
You snatched the passengers
from their turfs?
I'll settle it for you.
Take the kid to school first.
What're you doing?
I'm calling the police.
Are you nuts? Can it help?
Do you know them?
I'll revenge if I do.
How do you revenge? Kill him?
Where did you go last night?
How dared you snatch the passengers
from their turfs?
They all have triad backgrounds!
They ruin my business.
I'm starving to death!
All professions have their own rules.
You must obey them.
I believe there's justice in the world.
See them with me!
I'm not tough like you.
Go by yourself. I won't go with you.
You only act by yourself!
Hey!
Bitch!
Which bastard wrecked my car?
Me! What can you do?
How dare you push me?
Is money the only way to go?
I wanna earn my bread and butter only.
Yeah!
I 'Il call the police to nail you. I swear it!
Don't push me any more. I warn you!
Kill me! If you dare!
Stay here if you have the guts!
Kill me!
Don't run away!
Shau Kei Wan. Hurry.
What's with you?
Don't do anything rash. OK?
Listen to me this time. Alright?
I'll settle it for you!
Listen...
Let me do the talking.
Don't do anything rash.
I'll try my best.
Uncle Seven.
Elvis, you're here.
Wanna play mahjong?
Come on. Let's...
I'll take a rain-check.
Uncle Seven, I'd like to talk with you.
My granddaughter is holding
a birthday party tonight.
Talk to me tomorrow.
Sorry, Uncle Seven. Just for a while.
What's the matter?
You know, Man was killed in the crash.
His wife wanna take the route for him.
That's her?
Yes.
I have told you
not to queue up.
She can take the route once she pays.
I know. Uncle Seven.
But she's got no money.
So we wanna ask for your help.
No money... you two may help her out.
And she's really gutsy.
If she keeps buggering around,
you'll be in big trouble one day! Got it?
I must drive to the terminus.
Terminus?
Your man died, and I have to pay you?
Then, what if dad dies,
his son asks for help?
And what if an older bro dies?
Free for his younger bro?
Can I still make a living?
Absolutely not!
I must drive to the terminus.
Dad,
today's your granddaughter's birthday.
Cut anything about death!
For your goodies.
Kiddo, you're so cute.
How old are you?
Five.
Five only?
Granddad!
Good gal.
Laurie Leung.
Charlene Cheung.
I'm celebrating my birthday today.
My auntie wanna drive to the terminus.
For what?
I don't know.
Play with me.
I love to.
Uncle Seven, they're friends.
They may become very close friends
one day.
Yes, it's man who sets the rules.
You can always change them.
My boy, a dozen grand only.
You can help them.
Spare her the charge, please.
Uncle Seven.
That's right.
You'll be rewarded for your good will.
Right? Auntie.
Auntie? How do you do?
OK, well...
I make an exception this time and not next.
All set. What got you into a fuss?
I've told you not to worry.
You're just lucky today.
To tell the truth, those guys...
are only bluffing. They're just wusses.
I am never scared.
Shush.
If they reject me,
I'll ask them to return Man's money to me.
Right, Laurie?
You're nuts! OK...
I'll go to the market and buy some food.
Let's celebrate tonight.
It's late now. Save it.
Where are you going?
Sir, any shrimps and crabs?
All sold out!
Then... any fish?
Can't you see fish?
I sell you all for 30 dollars.
I can't take all these. Too many for a meal.
Two sets are enough.
This fish... can you make it into a dish?
I can pan-fry it to make it a good dish.
The vegetable stall is closing.
Keep this for me.
Sorry, sir. I don't want it.
How much is the cabbage?
Five dollars for one catty.
You don't want it?
It is decaying. Dump it.
Can you give it to me
if I buy two more catty from you?
Take all home if you like.
Thank you.
I waste no food.
Don't you know you're in a mess?
It's alright if you can't handle it.
Stop push yourself.
It may be OK for a grown-up.
But how about the kid?
If the days go like this,
you are raising him like a dog.
Is it OK to feed him, water him like a dog?
I know you've been helping me a lot.
And I don't want to cause you
any more troubles.
I shouldn't ask for help all the time.
It doesn't matter.
But no one will sympathize
with you for good.
I know.
I don't want to be a laughing stock.
Didn't Man told you at the time of dying...
that I must be tough?
To be frank,
Man at his time of dying
didn't tell me he loved you.
He didn't tell you to be tough.
That's my own words.
Why did you lie to me?
You cheated me!
I told you that...
to help you, to make you feel better.
But I might be wrong.
I am very busy and cannot receive
your call at the moment.
Please leave your phone number.
I'll reply you soon.
Where's Laurie?
His mom is dining out with him
for his birthday.
I've thought about it.
If you think it's not easy,
I'll ask his mom to raise him.
No way.
I love you but I love Laurie even more.
It's hard to raise a child.
Then, why did you fight for his custody?
A woman can't marry
if she got a child with her.
That's it.
You can't dump even a dog like that.
Do you agree?
Yes.
You've done a very good job.
No one will blame you.
For me,
a wife is your solution to your troubles.
You're right.
Let me get one tomorrow.
Marry me!
Marry you?
Will you do?
I'll do if you say 'I do'.
No. You'll do if I say 'I do'.
Will you say 'I do'?
Scare me stiff.
What? What scares you?
You know what scares me.
I have a hard time raising my son.
You'll add to my burden.
No! You must marry me...
Come up with a solution later.
Go to bed early.
Susan...
I know.
I was not in Hong Kong. So...
Are you available?
I'd like to talk with you.
I'm married.
Why do you know my address?
His mom told you?
I can't help you...
I've brought him to dad and mom
after Man's death.
No... I saw them...
I've paid them some grand.
What're you up to?
Wanna bring him to me?
No... I can't help you!
At that time, I didn't want to have him.
It's Man who insisted on having him.
We've gone through all the procedure.
I know. But...
Who are you?
Take him back now, I beg you.
You want money?
Give me your account number. I'll pay you.
Give me some time if you want a big sum.
I'll try my best to discuss with my husband.
I... I've got no money...
Let's go.
I'm so sorry.
I split up with Man right after his birth.
I've seen him a few times only!
Don't worry.
I'll bring Laurie to see you when I'm free.
Sorry.
Do you mean that?
Then tell me how can you deal with it?
Any other way out?
So hungry. Get something to eat. Go.
Let's get something to eat.
Sorry, I wasted your time.
Any other relatives?
They live on pension.
His grandma got hurt
when she fell down last week.
For the Rent?
Or the instalments on the car?
Let me lend you some money.
No.
Which one do you like?
You may pick more.
Really?
Don't buy any more.
He'll get the clothes inside.
Let's buy two.
Laurie. Take one more.
I'm full.
You have fed him three.
He used to love this goody. One more.
You wanna choke him on ice cream?
Stop. He'll have loose bowels
with too many ice-creams.
He can ease himself in the toilet.
He loves ice cream.
One more. Good boy.
Enjoy it...
Orphanage
Can you bring him in for me?
I can't!
I can't. He'll hate me for good.
I'd rather put your dog down for you.
I can't.
Laurie, let's go.
Say goodbye to uncle.
Uncle Hale won't go with us?
Where do you want to bring me?
I'll be a good boy.
I'll listen to you.
Auntie can't keep you.
Don't give me up.
I don't know my way home.
But I've got no way out.
Laurie must be a good boy.
Beware of the bullies.
Take good care of yourself.
I'll be a good boy.
Don't desert me. Mom.
I beg you. Take me to Dad and Grandma.
Forgive me.
Uncle Hale wanna keep me?
Hale...
Hale!
Hey!
What should I do?
Can you really send him away?
You should sell your minibus before him.
Don't cry...
Let me keep him, OK?
I'll keep him!
Come on. It's OK.
Don't cry...
Let's go. Go.
What will the others think
when they see us?
OK. Let's go...
Alright...
Don't cry.
The kite's high in the sky!
It drops.
A fallen kite!
Check out your throne.
Come on. Belt up.
Be careful.
And this board.
You can pull it down...
to do homework, drawing...
so safe and comfy.
Isn't it great? What's more...
Laurie, you see.
Thank you!
I've got something for you, too.
Call her mom, not auntie any more.
Why?
Coz your auntie will be happy about it.
Got it?
My mom got it from the temple.
It's great.
And...
I made a pack of keys for you.
It helps you see Laurie.
Terrific.
By the way, I've got an idea.
Laurie and you go live with me.
And you no longer need to pay the rent.
Come to my home when you're free.
It's a nice place.
Let me think about it.
Yes, think it over.
Coz... if I move,
it's wise to live out
the prepayment of two months.
That's right. Think it over.
I'll go now. You gotta work.
Bye.
Thanks a lot.
You're welcome.
Bye. Papa!
Bye. Sit down.
This kid's brainy and honey mouthed.
What's up?
You pay the instalments on the car
for someone?
Who's bullshitting?
There aren't many car companies around.
It's typically human.
One tends to gossip about others
but not oneself.
I just wanna help the kiddo!
Yes. You're right. But...
Got it.
What did you get? I haven't finished yet.
I said I got it!
It's good to give a helping hand,
but bad to overdo it.
What are the scruples
about helping people?
I don't mean that. I mean...
an existential subject may not be
an empirical one
yet an empirical one may not be
a rational one, right?
You must have read
too many hentai comics.
So, you talk like a philosopher.
Watch out!
You coward.
Aren't you gutsy? What scares you?
Give it your hand.
Let it shake with you.
Come on, let it smell your hand
and know you're Laurie.
He'll have a very good sleep
coz he played so tired.
I go now.
Hale.
Let me go with you.
Good idea.
Laurie hasn't played so happily
for such a long time.
Me too.
Sorry.
Let's get something to drink.
Ma'am, six bottles of beer, please.
Thanks.
You like it? I like it.
Get more foodstuff.
Fine.
Who're you?
I'm... a friend of Holly.
What... what're you doing here?
I'm... fixing something for her.
It's fixed now.
Thank a lot.
Holly and I are colleagues.
You also drive a minibus?
Yes.
I've made it. I'm leaving now.
There're soft drinks in the fridge.
Bye.
Excuse me.
You're with her?
Yes.
How's she now?
Quite good... Nothing wrong with her.
Do you know... her story?
I know.
Not long ago... she's so emotional that...
she couldn't make any good judgment.
But she's quite good now.
She looks tough.
But deep down she's dependent.
And she's rash and headstrong.
So her mom and I are worried about her...
We feared that she'd be cheated.
Would you please look after her for us?
Don't worry. I would.
And...
Don't tell her I've been here...
though it makes no harm
to tell her about her mom.
I got it. I tell her nothing then.
Thank you.
Alright.
Hale, let's have buffet with Laurie tonight?
Tonight?
I have to work till eight or nine o'clock.
It's OK. Laurie and I will be waiting.
Hale, go.
I gotta go now.
I am very busy and cannot receive
your call at the moment.
Please leave your phone number.
I'll reply you soon.
Laurie.
What's up?
Let's call Uncle Hale.
Hello?
Uncle Hale, I'm going to bed now.
Good boy.
How's your mom?
He wants you.
He said he must call you.
That's OK.
Where did you go?
I've just taken a nap.
I thought you wanted to turn
a blind eye to me.
Featherbrain. Why would I do so?
Then, I'll come and see you later.
OK.
What do you want?
Beer?
Six bottles, please.
Thanks.
How are you feeling? Not feeling well?
I'm fine. Alright.
By the way, I asked the landlady
to stop renting out her flat.
She only returned me
half of the prepayment.
We'll live with you.
If you feel uneasy with us,
do tell me.
Don't be silly. How can it be?
As the saying goes:
Two going well may not live well.
You have been taking good care of us
these days.
No matter how the days goes,
I'll be grateful to you. Thank you.
I have something to say.
Turn off the tap. Come over and listen.
Hale, call me when you're back.
Hale, I'm going to board a plane
with our son.
Keep on gambling.
I tell you you're not a good man
or a good husband, a good father.
You don't need a home at all.
Why got married? Why had a son?
It's too late to mend.
Good boy, say goodbye to dad.
Dad! Why are you not with us?
What's wrong?
I haven't done with my words!
I begin to do housework only
after they left me.
Make a meal, sweep the floor...
Stop talking foul languages before the kids.
Save money, stop smoking, stop gambling...
I used to have four minibuses. But all lost.
I'm foolish enough.
I cheated myself.
I know well they wouldn't come back
yet I make a spin
in my minibus every day...
I daren't change my phone, move elsewhere
or change jobs.
I fear that they can't see me any more.
The truth is, if they do want me,
they'll see me.
I got real at last.
I should face reality, forget the past
and not stay put.
I can't spend my life in...
driving from east to west, then back to east.
Right?
Last time, I told Laurie
and you to live with me.
You didn't say 'yes'.
I thought it over whole night.
I listened to that message,
again and again...
I take Laurie and you to be them.
I thought I wanna prove myself...
that I can be a good dad
and a good husband.
Do you feel grateful to me
or really love me?
Do I take you to be her?
Or you take me to be him?
If we got another one in our hearts...
it means nothing even if we have sex.
Hale.
You're a very good man.
Sorry, the number you just dialled
is not in service.
Turn around, please.
Take away your hands.
Open your eyes.
Gorgeous!
You like it?
With this bouquet... Will you marry me?
You're serious?
Yes.
Let me ask you a question.
If you can answer it, I'll marry you.
OK.
What does our plate number mean?
Forever.
I do.
Man, I gotta forget you.
Dad.
Call him grandpa.
He's grandpa?
Yes.
But I've got a grandad already.
Call him. Good boy.
He's so young.
He's honey mouthed.
Isn't it tough?
I work to kill time.
My old buddy opened this shop.
I'll have dinner at home tonight.
Good.
I wanna move back home.
Of course.
With him.
Are you a good boy?
Me? I'm not.
Are you bad-tempered like your mom?
Yes, I'm very bad-tempered.
Will you bicker with me?
Yes, I'll.
Will you do anything rash?
And the more I tell you not to do,
the more you want?
Yes.
But are you wicked?
And don't let me play anything?
You may do whatever you want.
But you have to tell me beforehand.
Just tell me. OK?
Dad.
Put less salt into your soup.
Too salty.
Too salty? Really?
It's true. I never cheated you.
Laurie, go to pee pee. Quick.
Hale, call me back, please.
What? Sell or not?
Think it over.
Wait...
Let me make a call.
What?
Hello?
Hale?
I just wanted to call you.
What's the matter?
Tell me first.
You gotta tell me first.
I wanna sell the car and do another job.
Which one?
Whatever.
The sort of business...
once the client come in,
they'll be very happy.
Sell ice-cream or something.
Have you thought over it?
No, I haven't.
I can't waste my time thinking.
Do you wanna change your job?
Will you sell your car?
Where're you?
At a car company in Man Wui Street.
Man Wui Street? I'm there too.
Really?
Papa!
I just wanna tell you.
I sold my car and got the money.
Wait, stay put...
You said last time...
I'm a very good man. Right?
If a girl says something
like that to a guy...
She means...
She won't go out with that guy.
Then...
Do you love me?
I love... you... a little bit.
A little bit...
That's good enough.
Is it because I have been helping you
Or you found out that I'm divorced
and lonely, so you feel pity for me?
Of course not.
Let's try it.
I'll sell it!