Here you go,my friend.
Make sure you go
as close as you can,
Ill get you something extra
if you make it a good trip.
Im going to get you close,
my friend.
But not too close.
You know what I mean?
Are you ready?
- Ready!
1, 2, 3!
Are you scared?
This is great!
You see anything yet?
No... Not yet.
what was that?
I dont know.
- Hold on.
- whats happening?
Hold on.
Make it stop.
what happen to them?
I dont know.
- were gonna crash.
- No, we are not.
were gonna crash.
Im going to take this tools.
Let go the rope.
Let go the rope!
Move your hands.
Come on. Keep...
Let go!
Its gonna be okay.
Actually Charlie that doesnt hurt.
They wont really be fighting each other.
But these one here are Corythosaurus.
They really like fighting
with each other.
They use their teeth and their claws
to rip each others jaws out.
Alan, hes three.
Let`ss wait until he is five.
Right. Sorry, Charlie.
- Ellie.
- Yes.
Its Tom again.
He says he has to talk
to you about the last chapter.
Just tell him I am not gonna to
lose the Jack Corner Club.
Hey, look whos here?
This is Alan.
Nice to meet you, Alan.
Daddy.
This is Hylaeosaurus.
Thats the dinosaur man.
Dinosaur man?
Jack, say my name.
Is my name Alan?
He used to know me.
Here you go.
Thanks.
So you know Mark is going to
work with the State Department now.
what do you do, Mark?
Its international relation most.
Somethings like that.
Ill get her.
You guys...
You guys have a little chat.
Hes a great guy.
So what are you working on now?
Raptors mostly.
My favourite.
Do you remember the sounds
they made?
I try not.
Ellie,
all the theories are about
raptors intelligence,
what are they capable of?
we work even close.
Tell me.
we did plenty of scan
on the raptors skeleton.
we find out it looks like a very
sophisticated resonating chamber.
wait a second.
So we were right?
I mean they had even living vocalise.
Im convince they had the
key of social intelligence.
which explains why they work
together as a team.
And co-ordinate they attacks.
And they probably know
what is going on.
They could talk to each other.
To agree, we could never imagine.
Ellie, they were smart.
They were smarter than
dolphins or whales.
They were smarter than primates.
I just want to say Ill be ready
to help with anything.
Someday if you want to ask,
you can call me.
Anything. Anytime.
Sure.
Youre still the best.
I mean it.
The last in my breed.
So the basic study about the
interior chamber,
and most of these specimens.
They begin to determine
the exciting color relation
between the upper-pales
and the leerings.
This lead us theorise the raptors.
which are capable of
sophisticated vocalizations
which were had been
tremendous evolutionary advantange.
Raptors were fierce,
intelligent and
socially sophisticated.
They were able to hunt in numbers
and co-ordinate their efforts.
with the catadysmic advance
which overtook them
its entirely possible
that raptors or humans
whether to become a dominant
species on this planet.
I hope this has been interest.
It certainly excites us
as its intelligence.
There is much more to discover.
That is why we continue to
need and ask for your support.
Thank you.
Thank you very much,
Dr Grant.
Now,
does anyone have a question?
Fine.
Does anyone have a question that
is not related to Jurrasic Park?
All the incident in San Diego
which I did not witness.
Yes, sir.
Your theory on raptors is good.
But isnt it a conjecture kind of mood?
I mean once the UN in Costa Rica
and everyone decides
how to handle that second island,
scientists will just go in
and look for themselves.
Dinosaurs lived 65 million years ago.
what is left of them is
fossilise in the rocks.
And this in the rock,
that real scientists make
real discovery.
Now what John Hammand and
Ingen in the Jurassic Park
is created genetically engineered
theme park monsters.
Nothing more and nothing less.
Are you saying that you dont want
to get to Isla Sorna and study them
if you have the chance?
No force on earth or heaven.
Forget beyond that island.
So what we got here?
20 million gas operator
sending out in a minute.
Gunship, magazine, third routine
and both our clothes cope with
reducing muscles...
Here, Udesky.
Yes, sir.
we are going to get here.
The matter of fact is
you knock things down
as soon as you bought me
that thing.
well, thats right.
There are two of the best
man that I would find.
No, sir.
Ive not worked with them personally.
But believe me, sir.
These men come very
highly recommended.
Nothing to worry about, sir.
Its going to be walk in park.
Billy,
I dont think that
I`mm doing this right.
Lets try to do first.
You got to do this slowly.
Itll just take a little bit of time.
I can never tell whats rock
and what`ss bone.
Technically its all rock.
But calcium in the bones
replace during fossilisation.
You can feel the difference, see.
Rough... smooth...
Dr Grant!
Mr Brennan.
So how did it go?
Its not too late to change
your major, Billy!
worse,
we gonna have backup in four weeks.
I have to run some equipment.
I got to show you something.
You like computers, right
I like the abacus, Billy.
Meet the future of paleontology.
Its a rapid photo type.
I scanned them from
the raptor skeleton.
If the computer breaks down
a thousand of slices.
And this thing scoops it.
One layer at a time.
Its done.
I give you the resonating
chamber of velociraptor.
Listen to this.
This is brilliant, Billy.
All I have to say,
its just a little bit too late.
Grant, Paul Kirby.
Kirby Enteprise.
My card.
How are you doing, Billy.?
what can I do for you,
Mr Kirby?
well, the first thing,
Im a great admirer of yours.
And I have a proposition and
I would like to discuss with you.
would you have dinner with me
and my wife this evening?
Itll be our treat.
That will be great, but...
Im tired,
I have been travelling.
Maybe some other time.
Believe me.
This will be worth you a while.
we love to.
Terrific.
Thats the spirit. Good.
See you this evening then.
- Billy.
- How are you?
So what are you boys drinking?
- Ice peak cap.
- Two please.
we admire your work for years.
Really truly inspiring.
Amanda
and I just love the outdoors.
we have been on just every adventure
that can come up with.
The Neil and everything.
we even have two seats reserved
on the first commercial flight
to the moon.
And for the wedding anniversary
this year,
we like to do something
really special...
- Something...
- Once in a lifetime.
Ive charged an airplane
to fly us Isla Sorna.
And we like you to be our guide.
There you go, guys.
This is a very kind offer,
Mr Kirby.
Im a very very busy man.
I can recommend a couple
of guys who is highly qualified that...
No. No.
You are the best.
Youd seen these animals
in the flash.
There is even one comes close
to you.
You wont be able to fly
enough low
to see anything
that is really interesting.
Thats the interesting part.
Because
we have the permission to fly low.
How low?
Havent issue yet.
But I can fly lower than anybody else.
I can tell you.
From what I understand,
I understand...
This is what we want.
You see,
through my business dealing,
import and export.
Emerging market.
I have
a lot of friends in high level.
In that case,
Costa Rica we can go in.
Dr Grant,
you have no idea
how this important to us
that you come along.
This will be all the difference.
Mrs Kirby, I...
And of course we love to make
a contribution to your research here.
I can write all kind of numbers
on this check, Dr Grant.
Tell me.
whats this gonna take?
No way.
This one is lucky.
A couples years ago,
some parties in Island hand
gladding these cleaves in museum.
And its big up draught come in
and swipe me right across the sign.
wham!
well, it does sound like.
This strap saved my life.
I got hook on the rock
when I was falling.
Survivor are the most idiotic.
Alan,
thank you for bringing me along.
The bones will still be
there when you get back.
This is the great thing about
bones that they dont run away.
The truth is,
you got me into this.
Ive no intention of being
on my own with these people.
Dont get too excited, Billy.
Chances are once here think.
Good time to be nice.
Awake me when we get there.
So how do you know the Kirbys?
Through our church.
Ellie...
Ellie!
Here we go,
were almost there.
Youre approaching Isla Sorna.
Do you want to approach...
My God. Ive forgotten.
we did it, honey.
we are here.
If you see anything,
yell up.
I thought of keep it to myself.
Im sorry.
Everyone, if you could
look out the left of the plane.
You can see a whole curf
of Brachiosaurus.
In fact you could see the front of
the group alpha male grazing there.
Udesky, Nash.
How about the front?
You guys see anything?
Nothing yet,
Mr Kirby.
Mrs Kirby, look.
Out here youll see a group
of Triceratops...
Mr. Kirby, we have to land
in strip down ahead.
You want me to put it down?
No. No.
I told you on a circle
to see the whole island.
You have been set down.
we cant land here.
what are you talking about?
- Hold on, I can explain.
- You cannot land on this island.
Its gonna be fine.
Everybody sit down.
would you please sit down...
Tell me we didnt land.
I think they are looking for someone.
Dr Grant, are you alright?
Im sorry we have to be so...
who hit me?
That will be cooper.
what are they doing?
They are setting up a parameter.
Then we could play safe.
These guys are good.
Trust me. In this island,
there is no such thing as safe.
we must get back to that plane.
Could you ask your wife
stop making up that noise?
That is a very, very bad idea.
Amanda!
Ben!
Amanda, honey, Dr Grant says
that is a bad idea.
what?
He says its a bad idea!
whats about idea?
what was that?
Its a tyrannosaurus.
I dont think so.
It sounds bigger.
we have to leave.
we have to leave now!
whats going on?
where is the professional who
can handle this?
Its alright.
we`rre just circled the island.
Stop!
what is he doing?
Thats Cooper.
Stop...
No one can stop this plane.
Are you okay?
were okay up here.
Everyone just stay put.
Mayday! Mayday!
who has a satellite phone?
I do.
I got it right here.
Come and get it.
The radio is gone.
we havent landed yet.
Damn it.
"The number you call is busy".
what was that?
what is it?
what?
- what...
- Hold it!
Hang on, everyone.
Help me!
Mrs Kirby, come back!
Amanda!
Follow me!
In here!
I think we lost him.
Its okay. It`ss dead.
Nobody move a muscle.
No... No... No... Please dont. Stop.
Please.
Its time you do some explain,
Mr Kirby.
we called everyone.
we did verything we could.
No one would help us.
The Costa Rica goverment
said this is no fly zone.
The US embassy...
Thats our US embassy told
we should accept the fact.
Can you believe that?
You left a 12 year-old
go para-sailing alone?
No!
He wasnt alone.
He was with a friend.
Ben Hilderban.
Paul and I divorced over a year ago.
So why me?
He said we needed someone who
had been on island before?
Yes. But I did not tell
you to kidnap somebody.
I have never been on this island.
Sure you have.
You wrote that book.
That is Isla Nublar.
This is Isla Sorna.
You mean there are two islands
with dinosaurs?
You stay out of this.
So how long have he been missing?
- 8 weeks.
- Almost 8 weeks.
Billy, now go back to plane
and set a camp.
And we make for the coast.
Dr Grant,
we are not leaving
this island without our son.
You can go on and look for him.
Or you can stick with us
as long as you dont hold us up.
Either way,
you probably wont
get out of this island alive.
So? what do we do?
Go and search for your son.
Thats the direction they are going.
Thats the one. Excellent.
Oh, sorry. Sorry.
Its nothing you haven`tt seen before.
How much weight did you lose?
About 25 pounds!
Ive been swimming.
I hate to swim.
And I dont even know how to swim.
I learned.
- You look good.
- So are you.
How would you classify, Billy?
Its a super predator.
Suchominus.
I think bigger.
Baryonyx?
Not on that cell.
Spinosaurus stick up with this.
I dont remember that
on Ingen`ss list.
Because it wasnt on there,
unless it makes them wonder
what they are up to.
So, Mr Kirby, tell me.
when you climbed K2,
did you based camp at
25,000 or 30,000 feet?
30,000 feet.
we were pretty close to the top.
It is above 30,000 feet,
actually.
No. No.
Thats a common mistake.
Mr Kirby,
there is no such thing
as Kirby Enterprise, isnt?
Theres Kirby Painting Tile and Plus.
The Plus stands for bathroom fixtures.
were in the
west Case Shopping Centre...
I suppose we dont check
you out or anything...
Now, listen to me.
Ill pay you the money...
- This is good.
- No matter what.
we are in worst place on
the world, we are not being pay.
Alright, now wait.
Fellows, hold on.
Ill make this up to you.
If you ever do a bathroom
or a kitchen...
You are not really a mercenary,
are you?
I never said I was.
Thats true.
what are you?
Im like a booking agent.
Guys who got sick count on me.
Here. See we are now
in a hardware store.
Pay in title, yeah.
You never can tell about people,
do you?
You get the truth.
Eric!
Quiet.
would you stop that?
Dr Grant said this is a
very dangerous territory.
Look.
Maybe we should split up
or something, you know?
we could cover twice as much
of the island.
Dr Grant says that is a bad idea.
Dr Grant...
Dr Grant says this...
whats the good of hiring an expert
if we are not going to use his advice.
Yeah. Except Dr Grant
isnt looking for Eric.
He is looking for the coast.
Okay, fine.
Go ahead and scream.
And when cry sake plot comes
and attacks.
Dont come crying to me.
- Not that bad.
- what?
- Nothing.
- what did you say?
- Nevermind.
If we split up,
Im going along with you guys.
- Eric!
- Mrs Kirby.
Mrs Kirby!
Mrs Kirby,
the chance is our remote.
There are still in our resonance.
An adult.
Hey, guys.
Thats my camera.
The battery is dead.
I got an idea.
Let me have the camera.
I shot this in the morning
he disappeared.
He is alive.
I know hes alive.
we got to find him.
will we find one of those?
Maybe.
Only if cell is not doing.
Lets take it.
If we spot a plane,
it might be the good way to get attention.
I got it. Okay. Okay!
Mrs Kirby, please!
Okay, you are free.
Come back, Mrs Kirby.
Amanda, wait. Amanda.
Amanda?
Amanda... Amanda!
Amanda, stop...
Im sorry.
I`mm sorry about Ben.
Its not Ben,Paul.
It`ss Eric.
Hes out there all by himself.
I know, I know.
Our kid is out there all by himself.
Listen to me.
well find him. I promise.
Paul..
Dr Grant!
You should come and look at this!
Raptor.
we are going to find him.
Are you listening to me?
This kid got resources.
Remember last time
we tried to ground him?
wheres Billy?
what are you doing?
I was trying to go to the nest.
Dont do that again.
Im sorry.
If I lose you,
that means you are a damn tourist.
I bet they are in there,
dont you think?
I bet my bottom dollar.
what you think it is?
Thats ancient.
Four seasons.
Eric!
Paul,dont do that...
what the hell?
whos got some change?
Let me take some quarters.
I got a buck ten...
This is how you make dinosaurs.
No.
This is how you play God.
- That way!
- Look out.
Its locked.
- This way!
- Go! Go!
Hey! Over here!
Push! Push!
My God.
Its calling the other half.
Come on!
Its in a hurry.
Out from the trace.
Udesky.
Mr Kirby!
Billy!
Is Alan with you?
Oh my God...
Mr Udesky!
Hes dead.
Oh my God. No,hes not.
- No, hes not!
- No... wait!
Something is not right.
Amanda!
Hold on! Hold on!
They set a trap.
Yeah, they set a trap.
what do you say?
what do you looking for?
Thanks. Thanks a lot, Eric.
You know who I am?
Yeah, your parents are here.
They are looking for you.
- Together?
- Together.
Thats not good.
They dont take so well
to get together.
I think its big surprise
when people could do in it.
when I have to.
You are Alan Grant.
what are you doing here?
Your parents...
invited me along.
I read all of your books.
I like the portion more.
Before you are on the island.
You like dinosaurs back then.
well back then they hadnt try
to eat me then.
when I jumped in here,
they left a lot of stuff behind.
Any weapons?
No. I just use the gas...
And I appreciate that.
Be careful with that T-rexas.
Scare some of the small ones away,
but attacks the really big one
with defend.
This is T-rexas?
How do you get it?
You dont want to know.
Dessert?
Sure.
Eric,
I have to tell you lost for
eight weeks in this island.
Is that all has been?
You are alive.
Thats the important thing.
And thanks to you is one thing
we have in common.
Did you read Malcoms book?
Yeah.
So?
I dont know. I mean...
It was kind of preaching...
And too much chaos.
Everthing is chaos.
It seem like the guy
was hiding himself.
well thats two things
we have in common.
what is it?
Coelophysis.
Alan! Alan!
Alan!
No matter how this turns out
it wasnt your fault.
Eric is always a sorry little kid.
AIways.
And he threw someone like
Ben Hilderban into the mess...
- well...
- well what?
All Im saying it`ss not your fault.
No... If hed been with you,
he`lll be completely safe.
You drive 5 miles in
every speed limit, Paul.
And Id thrown three cars
in three years.
well, not three.
The Buek wasnt really total.
I just said I was,
cause I wanted get a "Yes, you do".
Im so sorry that you
have to be here.
Im not.
Theres a boat lie along side
the bank.
Looks in good shape.
Rescue boat?
No. Someone left behind.
Lets move.
Stick to the plan.
Head for the coast.
You are not going to look
for Dr Grant.
Heading the coast is Alans idea.
If hes alive,
there is where he`ss heading.
I agree.
what about Eric?
Eric is a smart kid.
He probably know he stands
a best chance by the coast.
He figures all the big dinosaurus
are in the centre of the island.
Right?
Sure.
You know what this is?
Thats a raptor claw.
I have one. A fossil.
Mine is new.
How much do you explore?
I stick pretty close
to the compound.
I think if anyone is looking for me...
Theres where they started.
we need to get to the coast.
That was a plan.
Are you sure?
The closer you get to the water,
the bigger the things get.
we have to find a way to the canyon
to find a river out to the coast.
After we find your parents.
And then what?
One step to the time.
Listen.
what?
Thats my dad satellite phone.
How do you know?
Kirby Painting Tile and Plus.
Dad!
- Eric!
Eric! This way!
Eric!
Mom! Dad!
I know it. Oh my God.
Oh, Im glad to see you.
Hey, you got my beg.
Yeah, lucky strap.
want me to carry it?
Need to find a gap here.
How did you know we were here?
The phone.
The stupid jingle from the store.
I heard it.
My phone?
Yeah, your satellite phone.
where is it?
I dont have it.
when did you use it last night?
On the plane.
I got a call on the place and...
what?
I loaned it to Nash.
He must have had it when he...
Run.
Alan,
you wanna give me the bag back.
Its okay, Billy. I got it.
Please give me the bag.
Its not safe.
Raptors eggs?
Did you steal raptors eggs?
Now it all make sense.
I swear if I know youre
gonna end up with them.
I took them on an impose.
I thought that the door
with the fortune are enough for the
things I obtain 10 more years.
But you have to believe me
this was a stupid decision.
But I did it with the best intentions.
with the best intentions...
Some other worst things imaginable
have been done with the best intentions.
Come on, Billy.
As far as I concern, you are
not better than the people
who built this place.
what are you doing?
Those things are after us
because of those.
Those things know we have the eggs.
I drop them into the river.
They will still be after us.
what if they catch us with them?
what if they catch us without them?
There is a boat at the bottom,
just down the river.
we try to make to
the coast, at least.
- Youre okay?
- Yeah.
Lets do this one
other time, shall we?
Okay, come on over.
One other time.
Okay, Eric. Im gonna
leave you just for a minute.
And then you are going to
be right behind me, okay?
Mom, Ive been alone in
the water truck for eight weeks.
I think I can manage the next
few minutes without you.
Right.
we are all together now.
Okay, Eric.
- Come on, honey
- You go.
Mom?
Oh my God.
what is it?
Its a bird cage.
For what?
Eric!
I cant stay without my kid.
This way!
Billy!
Billy, stop.
Billy, stop!
Stop, Billy!
Billy!
Eric, hold on!
Eric!
Jump!
Billy!
Look out now!
Eric!
There he is!
with the pteranodous.
Get him out of there.
Go! Go!
what about Billy?
Hang on, Billy!
Go away! Go away!
Come on!
Its playing the gasoline.
Now just got to get out
to the coast.
we got some sort of...
some sort of signal.
Build the fire or something.
Something that can see
from the air.
Dr. Grant?
Hey, Eric.
How are you doing?
Im sorry about Billy.
You know whats the last thing
I said to him was?
Its... he`s as bad as the people
who built this place.
It wasn't true.
Billy is just young... thats all.
I have a theory there
is two kind of boys.
Those who want to be astronomers.
And those who want
to be astronauts.
The astronomers,
the paying intelligence.
Get to study this amazing things
from a place with complete safety.
But he never got to go into space.
Exactly.
Its the difference between
imagining and seeing.
Be able to touch them.
And... thats all Billy wanted.
Dr Grant...
It is open, Dr Grant.
Billy was right.
Listen.
Find the phone before
it stops ringing.
Eric,stand there.
- Its here
- wait, it`ss here.
I got it.
Hello? Hello?
"Enjoy your meal in one of
our four star restaurant... "
Look out!
Turn off the power.
You got to choose for making one call.
what do you do?
Dont call the US embassy.
They wont do a damn thing.
Hey, guys.
Come here. Look at this!
what is this?
Something must have spook them.
Get the edge of calling, Mr Kirby.
Open the plot.
Hello?
Ellie!
Charlie!
Charlie,
take the phone to mommy now.
Its the dinosaur man.
Okay.
Charlie,
are you taking the phone to mom?
Charlie?
whos in the phone?
The dinosaur man.
He is?
Alan?
- wheres the phone?
- There.
Get the phone.
Ellie, listen to me!
Alan, are you on a cell phone?
I cant hear you.
The raptor chases me...
Hello?
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
Paul, you cant...
You cant leave me like this.
Im not going anywhere.
Dad!
Remember when we went fishing
a couple summers ago?
we putted the boat in the water
and the trailer sank.
The toll truck tried to pull us out
and they got drag in too.
The truck driver wanted to
knock my lights out.
I miss fishing.
Mr Kirby.
That lady you called.
who is she?
How do you know that
she can help us?
She is the person
I can always count on.
I owe her a lot.
I dont think
I have ever told her that.
You should.
You hear that?
The ocean.
Pick up your eggs.
Everybody get down.
She is challenging us.
She thinks she stole the eggs.
Get behind me.
Give me the eggs.
Do it, mom.
No... No... Call for help.
Thats a helicopter.
Dr Grant?
Dr Alan Grant?
No!
Thats a very bad idea!
You have to thank her now.
Shes in the NAVY.
God bless you, Ellie.
- Is this man with you?
- what?
we made it...
Yeah.
I rescue your hat.
Give me that.
Thats the important thing.
Dr Grant!
what the hell is that?
Dr Grant, look!
where do you think
they are going?
I dont know.
Maybe just looking
for a new nesting ground.
Its all in the world for them.
How dare them to nest in
Olakhoma?
Lets go home.
- THE END-