Miss Tracy, please look this way
Have a smile
Thank you
Hi! Tracy!
Tracy, cheer
Tracy! If you've time
we can do something together
No kidding, you're a hot producer,
how can you spare your time?
I'm always ready if it were you!
Really?
Kit, any new masterpieces?
I heard you have released a CD,
is it Jazz?
Kit!
Sometimes I really envy artist like you
You don't need to cater for the market,
and just do the Jazz,
but who will listen to you?
Can you write some pop music?
Actually, it's quite commercial
I've asked my P.A. to send you some CD,
you haven't listened, have you?
I don't need to, but I can tell
any way, if you are going to write again
let me listen to it first
If I don't even understand,
who will?
There're many things that
you don't understand
but it isn't bad
Maybe you're just too stupid
I gotta leave
Stay longer
Aren't you leaving?
Dinner time!
Bo, Backie, come over
It smells good, hurry up
Where is your dog-belt?
You keep losing your dog-belt,
it's expensive!
If you're caught, you're dead
That guy doesn't seem friendly
You guys have to watch out,
don't be cheated
People do eat dog meat in summer,
understand?
Go! Bye!
Man can't get rich without a fortune
Come for your fortune telling
You look obsessive, let me have a look
I've helped many people
Sit down, you don't need to pay
if I'm not accurate
What's your name?
Lam
Mr. Lam?
How old?
29, snake?
Dragon
Dragon? That's 30
30...
Let's have a general examination,
it costs $1000,
it'll summarize your 10 years' fortune,
or, palm-reading...
I'll charge you $300
I could tell you things happen...
in 3 to 5 years accurately
I think it will be something
about your career
Let's look at career
Career, I'll charge you $30
Sorry, I want to know...
about my emotional affairs
Emotional problem?
Yeah
Romance, I'll take $30
Do you know your birthday?
No
No?
No problem, I can find it out
When I stay in,
you've nothing to talk to me,
when I go out, you're not happy
What do you want?
I'm a singer, I can't just stay in
I must socialize with others
How many times have I told you...
not to use your money?
You won't listen!
$3-400,000 is not a small sum
You've lost this time! Aren't you happy?
I've told you...
not to wear these messy clothes,
dress properly,
or they won't respect you!
I've no money to buy new clothes
I've bought you clothes,
why don't you wear it?
I live here, but it doesn't mean
you're supporting me!
I lost my money,
not yours
Are you blaming me? I don't mean it
I don't want to talk to you
Where's my box?
What have you done?
I know you're in bad mood,
but it can't solve the problem
Have you ever thought it over?
Your work is not bad,
but how come no one wants it?
Just because
you've offended too many people
They just comment a few words
It's not big deal! Take it as a joke
You won't be hurt!
But does it hurt your pride?
We've different. I've my style and
my working attitude
Alright... I don't want to argue,
give my stuff back
You're going to have a romance
and get a fortune!
This woman is a good house-keeper and
good-looking, don't miss it!
Not correct?
Incorrect, no way!
Anyway, it's alright
Thanks
Where have...
you been lately?
I've been to Macau
Macau! Have a fortune? Sit...
Thanks
Pick a song
Alright
You're my support,
you must come more often
Thanks, Bill
Bill gives us $200
Min...
Uncle you're late,
Mom is going to scold you
Where's my stuff?
I've taken it out
Quick
What? Playing mahjong again?
No, just talk!
About what?
Brother, I've told you not to smoke
You're old enough,
how come you still can't
take care of yourself!
Hurry up!
Why are you so hurry?
I must hurry home to prepare dinner
You're the greatest!
How come our business is getting worse?
But lots of people here!
Lots of people? But it doesn't help
They just sit here, and we lose money
Don't drink anymore!
Don't worry,
I've got the Asthmatic drugs
God! You take wine as medicine
Aren't you going to die?
I wish I could die, it saves a lot
Now I understand why we're losing money
Because you shirk work
He plays his saxophone...
as if he's sucking his dummy
Don't blame me,
I just don't want to over shadow you
Can you?
Mom
Let's play something popular tomorrow
Popular?
The life is tough nowadays,
let's give them some fun
Yeah! Min is right
No one wants to hear "Send you to hell"
It's your wife
who dedicates this song to you,
she wishes you dead
Your uncle is always against me!
Ling, let's try something new tomorrow?
Alright, let's do it
Listen... it comes again
The guy upstairs!
Every night is the same
New comers?
Who knows?
Let's get a Chinese clarionet and
do the same to him
What's this song?
I've never heard it before
It's a song? Just bull shit
No bull shit, it's quite nice
Turtle? Let's have a sip
Min, drink it
It's better to drink hot soup
Uncle, does he play good?
He's composing a song
Really?
Not sure
Aren't you going to sleep?
Still early,
please close the door for me
Are you calling me?
How come you know my song?
Is it really your song?
How come there's no ending?
I've not finished yet...
how come you know it?
You're making a noise every night,
our neighbourhood know it too
Did I disturb you?
It's alright for me,
but you're disturbing my family
But you're also singing in the morning
and with drums
Early morning?
We start at almost 11:00 a.m.
You must go to sleep very late
In the morning... no... I
I sleep in the morning and work at night
How come you're stammering
I think
you should take some chinese herbs
The way that I talk to you,
make me feel tired
Give me your telephone number,
I'll call you
I have to work now
So late? Aren't you a car thief?
No, I play organ in a bar
Does such kind of job still exist?
I know! Isn't it the topless bar?
No, just common bar
Any food served?
Yeah
Anyway, we've just met,
talk to you later
What?
You look cool
but you don't look like a bad guy
See you downstairs
Delicious! Min, pay the bill
Me again?
I don't have small change
Every time it's like this
You don't look that tall?
What's your name?
Call me Kit
I'm Min, she's Ling,
this is what they call us
In fact I saw you before
You're always alone in the park
You always feed the dogs
You remembered?
You love swimming?
How come you're so dark?
Please be polite!
I tell the facts
Where should we go?
So late, are you scared?
No!
We're in the same field and
we're neighbours too
Even if you're off key,
we won't tease you
Go
Go and get a karaoke!
You pay?
I'll buy your place off
This store is famous
for their roasted snails
One more order
You can play it quite well
Just try to earn a living
Anyway, it's not easy
Just like spilling the pearls
before pigs
You've been in this field
for a long time, haven't you?
I used to be a musician,
playing session in the studio
You're a musician
No big deal!
They can make up
many different music without us
So we've nothing to do now
Therefore you're composing songs
We're having economic depression,
we'd save our expenses
So you've made a right move to live here
Don't worry,
you'll grow back. You can get over it
Roasted snail, half dozen
I've ordered roasted snail!
How come it's so fast?
Because somebody has ordered more,
don't you want it?
Alright, I'll give you another one
I'm giving you a favour,
don't you understand?
Anyway... thank you
You're hungry like a wolf!
He's crazy!
He likes joking
He'll give you the same old stuff,
maybe he'll add something else
Let's eat
Dare him!
How much did you earn for a month?
You're sick,
how can you ask this question
Why not?
The Chinese opera...
makes her become crazy
Are you both singing Chinese opera?
She's the leading, I sing whatever
You like music, don't you?
Yeah!
Pop, English song, whatever...
I do know a bit about yours,
but not an expert
Please play your piece to us
I've no saxophone here, next time
Alright
Aren't you going back?
Lend me some money for taxi
Where are you going so late?
She doesn't sleep
Taxi, coming or not?
It's late, let's go back
I go for an adventure, aren't you coming
Let's go
Beautiful
$40 for 30 pieces, how's that?
Let me see
Great
This colour is newly painted,
it will fade away after 2 days
Right?
Not this! Don't shake it!
I never know there's a place like this
You certainly don't know!
You're abnormal
I'm abnormal! Aren't you normal?
Go
There're still lots to see over there
You're home so late,
don't you scare of your mom?
No, my mom is so tolerant about me
Don't you have any work to do
in day time?
Play
Not exactly! The band is my mom's
We do our business over there at night
Ling is the leading,
and also my mom's fellow
Your opera must be great!
Just like yours, trying to earn a living
Anyway, we do sing
some classical Chinese Opera
We're famous in the villages
Don't you know
what's outdoor performance?
Yeah...
something like setting up the stage
Not setting up stage
but on the stage
How come you're stammering
I know, it must be too many over nights
You should have
some stewed ginger with crow
Stewed crow?
No! White feature chicken
You've infected me
Next time when I've my recording
You come to play saxophone for me
It'll be perfect
if there's more musical back up
What's you recording?
Cover version,
those $10 stuff in the night market
Chiang Chi Kwong used
to sing George Lam's part
Life is fair, he's a big hit
What about you?
Red bean cake
Give me a white one and
a coffee for him
What about you?
Any one who is hit!
Like Tracy, Sarah Chan Suk Wah
Tracy, really?
There's no big deal
to sing cover version
Why should I lie? I'll give you
my cassettes some other time
But the tape is not good, always jammed
It's getting dawn,
let's see the sun rise in the Peak
To the Peak?
I'll pay for the taxi and
it takes 30 min to walk down the peak
No! I'm tired
No taxi?
It's not far, let's walk
Walk back?
In the morning, the air is fresh
Here is a taxi
Let's go and have a breakfast
You haven't finished your red bean cake
If you aren't enough, take mine
Great
Why don't we...
Nothing
Good morning, it's late,
why don't you get up?
I'm just about to sleep,
how come you get up so early?
My phone broke down,
I just want to borrow yours
I've no phone
No phone? Not possible!
My Grand Ma in China
does have a telephone
Check it yourself
OK
I thought you want to pretend that
you're poor
You're really broke
You eat instant noodle everyday
No wonder,
your face is just like a noodle cake
Great
It won't work!
I haven't put on the bamboo slip yet
Make yourself at home
You still want to sleep, don't you?
Remember to close the door for me
Don't! Don't waste your time,
find some friends
I've no day time friends
Now you have
You've just arrived here,
let me show you around
Let me give you a treat
I don't like to owe you a favour
I'm sorry for last night,
I've made you buy us right snack
Could you do me a favour?
We're not close friend
You're not going to borrow money
from me, aren't you?
I go and get changed
It's big and beautiful
You're the son of a wealthy family,
aren't you?
But you're rebellious and
like to join the band
So your Pa kicked you out, am I right?
Come and help me
You sleep here, the mezzanine?
We also have one,
but it's full of my Mom's stuff
Help me
I'll ask my mom to clean out
the mezzanine for me to sleep
Put it in my bag, be careful
How do you know Tracy?
Girl friend
Ex...
Master
Hurry...
Go over there and have leg exercise
You're on performance so young?
Yeah!
I was on stage at eight,
I've worked for 12 years
You know how old I am now
What about your mom? Was she a singer?
Yeah! She's great!
Like me, she knows everything
But she wasn't hit
Why?
My uncle said she's hot temper
And offended many people
The one playing dulcimer is my uncle,
nick named "Cheung Po Tsai"
He is responsible
for our outdoor performance
Isn't he playing saxophone?
No!
Just like me, he knows everything
I forget,
I should not always speak high of myself
I know...
why you pulled a long face and
ran away that day
Come
Come here
Get in
Don't worry! Come in
I give you a cassette
You've a lot of tapes
Yeah, I've a big collection
You really did it?
Please give me your comments
Blacky, who is this?
Sarah Chan! Haven't you heard this!
Be careful, don't break my tape recorder
No, the tape jammed
Your tape is really shit
Look, what a tape...
Aunty, how are you? I'm looking for Min
Don't you even knock?
Get up, it's ten already
Where's your mom?
Are you looking for her?
No
Last night, I've mistaken her as you
There's no big deal
I feel that your mom doesn't like me
I don't think so
Let me ask her
Don't
Look at yourself
You think I'm nuts
My mom's gone out early in the morning
Don't bother her, you both are the same,
always pulling long face,
why were you looking for me?
The tape dropped down,
and they're all poor
Yeah
Even I sang not good
but you shouldn't drop them
Could you give me some face?
I don't mean it,
but just missed it unintentionally
Alright! I'll give you a new one
So soon
Won't you let me in?
How can you live in this sort of places?
The rent is cheap!
Why don't you move in with your brother?
Not convenient, my sister-in-law,
you know...
I forgot, you two are incompatible
You're incompatible to everybody too
I heard Tat say,
you refused to perform in the concert,
didn't you?
There's no need to fight against money!
Don't talk about money
all the time please
Am I?
I've known you for so long,
have I ever mentioned money with you?
Don't be so weird
Not everyone on earth is your enemy
What do you really want?
Do you want to stay here
for the rest of your life?
Come back, will you?
Don't you want me to beg you?
Kit! I think this tape won't...
Sorry, I'll come later
I'll close the door for you,
there're many people passing by
Who is she?
Just met. She's nice
You've just met and you know she's nice
Cheap
Tracy, why do you leave so early?
Could you give me your autograph?
I love your songs
This is for you
I'm busy
He's still angry, don't bother him
Hi!
Are you calling me?
Why don't you say hello?
I'm very observant
You hate woman, I dare not bother you
How do you know?
Can't you see?
All the female sparrows...
fly away from you
What about your dogs? Throw away?
Here comes the dog-catcher
They're really clever
And hide under the bridge
Are you jobless?
Traveling around?
Who said I'm jobless?
I'm going for the recording session
Cover-version?
They said the oldies will be popular,
early release makes big money
Can I visit?
Of course, come!
This way
I just saw you go that way
Am I? No, I'm going this way
No, you're going that way
This way
Alright, this way
Cheung Sha Wan
Take the MTR?
MTR? Let's walk
Walk, but it's far away!
No, it's not far away
Ga Lip So Cha Cha Cha
Ga Lip So Cha Cha Cha,
Thank you very much!
Just now Yau Ling has sung you...
"The Love Affair in a Distant Land"
Is it great?
This song was dedicated by Fat
from the Fat's Restaurant,
and Mr Cheung
from the Cheung's Restaurant
If anyone of you want to hear anything,
just tell me
Our band will be glad to perform it
We're now taking a break
Because our Masters need to go to toilet
And will be back soon
Thank you...
Uncle
You're late today
I've gone to studio! Where's mom?
You're lucky,
she's gone for a wedding banquet
Take a seat, I'll give you a treat today
Min! Sing us a song
Sure, you sit here
What do you want me to sing?
"Tang Bai Fu dates Qiu Xiang"
Tang Bai Fu? That's not good
What about a pop song?
Good
"Keep coming even you've lost"
Are you crazy?
I've blown it! Let's do something to it
Yeah. Let's have Yan Ling to sing us...
the "The Work Repairer"
Great!
Thanks
What do you expect from me?
I was in the studio the whole day
I'm tired
And you have to stay
with your Prince of the White Horse
No, it's the Prince of the Black Horse
What are you talking about?
Thank you very much
Good!
Please come next time
Thank you
Go this way
Why did they throw the money
on the floor?
It's a majestic act
It'll give face to our leading artiste
as well as to our customers
I really appreciate you guys...
to have the guts to sing in the public
Are you afraid?
Afraid of what? Even in the HK stadium,
it's not that crowded
but it's different
What different? Just for a living
But they eat shark fin soup and
we eat vermicelli
You sing well,
why don't you enter
a singing competition?
I can't, I just know how to imitate
But I feel that you have the potential
As a singer you should have
a pretty face and you aren't ugly
Really? But I'm not pretty enough
You are pretty!
You know how to flatter now
You must have eaten
the ginger soup with crow
I'm serious,
you shouldn't hide yourself
Do you want to spend
the rest of your life singing here?
Don't you think I'm like a beggar?
Don't be misunderstood,
I don't mean to look down upon you
Anyway...
there's no different for professions
Look at these people,
what kind of entertainment do they have?
They just like to hear some songs
If they've money
they will dedicate a song,
we won't force them
In case of typhoon,
they'll be very disappointed
At least, they don't play here
Yeah, but you should try
Maybe you'll have further development
In fact I've considered it,
but my mom doesn't approve it
Why?
I've to help her
We've to spend a lot to hire
a leading artist
If I could get a big hit,
it isn't bad
Let me get a chance to talk to your mom
Let's talk about you
Look at your long face,
watch the performance!
How come it is closed?
Blacky, what?
A new boss
No? It's the pay date
That's it
How come this guy is so heartless!
Let's go for him
Where do you go?
He'll be in deep shit if I find him
If you find him call me
Great
Do you need money?
Let me lend you some for emergency
Where are you going?
Borrow money! Do you think
I really want to borrow from you?
If you have an alternative,
then I'll save it
Wait for me
Your pals are great
Yeah! Their music is better than me
But poorer than me
Keung, you should be
in the nightclub, shouldn't you?
They've got a DJ
so they kicked away the band
And changed into a Disco
Tat is even worse, his shop
has been changed into a gigalo bar
Why didn't he stay behind as a gigalo?
I want to,
they told me a gigalo could earn
over $10,000 a night
However I'm just too weak
The world is different now,
man is more costly than a woman
The world is changing now,
the ball bottom is popular again
We're of the last decade already
Don't be too pessimistic,
your music is great
in fact you can write the lyrics and
maybe you'll become a big hit
They've tried lots of time but in vain
Is there anything wrong
with your lyrics and song?
Is it too artistic?
What's wrong with it?
I don't mean it's bad,
but it's not popular
There's many good songs in Chinese opera
but can't sing here
Interest and living are
two different things
You look young
but you seem to be a man of the world
Who are you?
Second leading of the Vocal Band Group
Nice to meet you
Have you ever been jobless?
No. Touch wood
Kid shouldn't interrupt
when adults are talking
Have your coke
I am in this field
much earlier than you guys
It must be...
you guys like to put on air
And not smooth enough
in handling human relationship
Or get fierce if people criticize you
Incorrigible
It's gone
Keung, come and have some wine
I don't want to talk anymore,
I don't want to irritate you
Don't you want to irritate me? Never
It's easy said than done
You must have connection
I see people's face
much more than you do
Let's try some other time
Are you upset about me?
No
If no... then tomorrow morning...
If you don't wake me up so early
Then I won't be angry, alright?
Look at you, you're sweat all over,
have a wipe!
No one here, it's impossible!
Should he be alright?
Kit! Are you alright?
Get up
Get up! It's 4:00 already
What's up?
Last time I've helped you,
it's my turn now
Let's talk about it later
Hurry... your uncle is very angry
I understand
Hurry up
Hurry up! The ferry will leave at 8:30
It's only 7:00, and you lie to me
If I didn't lie,
you wouldn't have waken up
Let's go
Grandpa, clam
That's mussel, stupid
Fight...
Alright
Be smart
Ling can fight pretty well
Last time, there came some bastards
She just kicked them away
Last time the leading...
of the next door took away her customers
and Ling just "pa pa pa..."
pounded her wig away
and made the uncle clap his hands
Don't you believe?
Don't you think I lie to you?
No
Just say it! I can take it
I just know people do have
their ways of living,
whatever you do,
you're betraying yourself
Yeah
But I think...
Ling has the potential,
she doesn't need to be like this
If I didn't see her sing
I'll think she is trying to...
Seduce people?
You're not the first one to say so
Let me tell you,
Ling starts singing long before
and she just wishes
to be the leading artiste,
and have the performance
in a formal theatre
But now the Lee theatre was gone,
and she says it's alright
Because there're still some cinemas
In fact, uncle has tried...
his best to help
However,
there's no opportunity
She has had a deep thought
before she agreed to sing here
in fact she's earned a lot,
but she's very mean
Last time,
she made you pay for the roasted snails
What's she doing with the money?
Buy some costumes, accessories...
and it takes a few hundred thousands
Don't you have to buy it yourself?
Of course! It's not TV shows,
there's no sponsorship
If I have the chance
I'll give your pals a lesson
Ling has never complaint before
She said if she works harder,
she can enjoy the fruit herself
If others get a fortune,
are they going to give you a share?
If you want to win the Mark-six,
you gotta go and buy it
Don't look down upon me,
I'm not big mouth
I've walked from the death,
don't you know?
You fought in Vietnam?
Similar
It's easy said than done
Maybe if I really face the problem
I may not know how to handle it
Anyway, I've got a friend like you,
you'll help me
I want you to do me a favour
We've just met,
are you going to borrow money from me?
You don't even has gas,
how will I dare to do it?
Indeed, I've a dream...
Wanna to build up your character?
How do you know
I don't have that quality?
Sorry
I mean I've sung so many cover-version
I'm not even acknowledged,
if I were dead, I'll regret
Come on. Don't be lazy, finish your song
Ask your pal to write the lyrics,
and send it to the record company
You can't just sit here
It doesn't help if you just sit here
As if you're helping me
Alright! I take you
to the record company for a try
Yeah, our group will be fantastic
If we work together,
we'll draw a big hit
Min! Min...
Fellow sisters...
Come
They're my fellow sisters, he's Kit
Sit...
Roast goose noodle
Is it good?
Delicious
Give you another one
What about you?
You eat...
We're just friends
Of course, aren't you enemy?
He refers me to the record company,
so I give him a treat
We can sing pretty well,
can we try too?
If I'm going to release a record,
you'll be my chorus
Come over here
Coming
Go over there
We've to leave
Stay longer
No, please take us ashore
Alright, ashore!
Where are you going?
Come here...
Just a minute...
Don't you want to have business?
Leaving? Forget it
Min, what's up?
What are you afraid of?
Do you feel ashamed just now?
You're afraid to be seen sitting with us
No
You are!
You don't respect
my fellow sisters and me
Do you feel ashamed to be with me?
I don't really mean this,
I just don't want to see her
Sorry! Don't be angry!
It's alright
Are you still angry?
No
That's good, I thought you're...
What?
Jealous
I'm
Can I?
Come with me
Where?
Let's tell her, you're my girl friend
Great
Next time, I want to dress better
Not necessary, you're very pretty today!
Let's go
No!
Why?
Next time
Why next time?
Where are you going?
I'm going home, good night
It's late, who is it?
Is it mom?
It's calling from the recording co.
They ask Min to go for a trial recording
I really thank you for your help
Let Min sing your master piece
But you see...
we have to do our business
if Min doesn't sing here
it'll affect our income
And Min is not free
This time...
I must make it clear
I think you know what I mean
Feel free to come again
Don't go
Why? I've come
Your mom doesn't want you to come
Don't bother about her!
She doesn't mean it
I don't think so,
what if you run into her downstairs?
Kit, don't drag on
Once it's decided,
there's no need to worry
Maybe we'll make it
Are you afraid I'll become another Tracy
Sorry, I'm too strong, don't get upset
I'm not upset,
I just afraid your mom won't like it
Let's go
Kit! You're great
All your girl friends
can sing pretty good
I think you better be the manager and
get your commission
See which songs you know
Aren't we going to sing Kit's?
His song is not ready yet
We've got all these MMO
It would be better you pick one you know
and we book the studio
And have your trial recording
The contract is ready, have a look
Thank you
Where are you going?
I've forgotten, I've an appointment
What's up?
Kit, she said
she doesn't want the recording!
But the studio is ready
Why don't you try?
Fatty, call me after you've finished...
with Kit's song, OK?
Let's go
Kit
Director
Quiet, it's the deputy not the director
It's the same!
Any candy!
These are for the kids
I'm
Is he Kit?
How are you?
Buy me a red bean ice
Come on
How's he?
Tall and masculine
Min
Nurse-in-chief
Are you coming to visit us?
Why are you still so slim?
She only eats snacks,
of course not enough nutrition
Maybe Anaemia
Measure her blood pressure,
and get some blood sample
No! I'm alright
Go... Be quick
I'll wait for you in the canteen
Let's go to the canteen
When she was nine
Normally if a child gets bone cancer,
the chance to recover is very small
I don't believe at the beginning
Maybe it's a miracle,
her illness is under control
I still remembered
when she passed her
1st 5 years' observation period
We held a party for her
She was very lovely
She knew how to sing and dance
And she's not afraid of injection
and taking pills
The medicine is very strong,
not everybody can take it
What about her situation now?
Don't worry,
the 2nd observation period is over
She's recovered
Her will power is very important,
she's strong and optimistic
I've faith in her
But, it's strange
Why did she want me to talk to you?
She's dexterous
Be quick, it's coming
Kit, I've something to talk to you
But you don't need to come so high here
Maybe it's your pride that stop you...
from telling me your problems
For example your career problem
And your relation with Tracy
In fact, there's no big deal
I really want to...
share with you,
and tell you my history
Then you'll know how unlucky I was
God is really fair to you
But I feel that life is more important
So to me,
there's nothing that can't be solved
How can you be so optimistic
I was born to be like this
Maybe it's my experience?
But I remembered what my uncle told me
Not everybody are lucky enough to get...
what they want
Of course
it's good to have a house and a car
Are you going to cry if we got nothing?
So, we should be satisfied with
what we have
We're friends before,
but now it's different
You can't hide everything
Or sooner or later
we've going to quarrel about this
I guess that's the reason...
why Tracy broke up with you
Maybe...
my temper is too bad
Tracy is good to me,
but I treat her badly
Man is always like this
They treat their friends
better than his wife,
and express their temper to his family
How come you know everything...
just like an old woman
I can't help it, because
I have a whole family of old guys
So you have to speak out
Are you going to tell me or Tracy?
Of course you
I've to tell you something,
but you can't laugh at me
I've never been on a plane before
So what?
I've been on the train
and roller-coaster...
Just a couple of times
How come you don't even laugh?
You said I was not allowed
Come on
I'll do it once...
and you follow me, alright?
Start! One, two, three
Stop
Not enough
Again, one, two, three
Aunty, I know you realise
Min and I are going out together
I also know you don't really like me
But if you don't approve,
I'm afraid
it'll affect your relationship
I don't really want to see...
poor relationship between you and Min
But I feel that I must be frank to you
I really like her
She had cancer
I know
Aunty, I hope you won't mind
I don't feel alright about the way
you handle this
I can understand
why you don't want us to be together
Just because you don't understand me
But I think you shouldn't stop...
Min going for a trail recording...
...For your business,
Min wishes to be a singer
She's a chance now,
why don't you let her try?
This is only an excuse
As a mother who doesn't want her
to have a better life?
I don't want her to sing
on the street for good
You've your point,
because I really don't understand you
So how can I trust you?
Min wasn't healthy,
and she's suffered a lot
I don't want her...
to be hurt,
in fact, I shouldn't bother so much
Because I can't control everything
As long as she likes it,
it's alright for me
So you ask me out,
and from what you have said
I feel that you really like her
I'm glad
You can go out with her
Happy Birthday to you...
Happy Birthday to mom
Make a wish!
Best wishes to all of you
Blow the candles out
How old are you?
Anyway I'm younger than you guys
21. Just 21
How come you've invited
so many Filipinos?
Yeah!
They used to be my mom's musicians
They were the guys in the photo
We're old
Uncle Hung, help yourself
I've told you not to drink so much!
Have a sip!
You have helped me...
to beat those guys
I've Asthma, they want to abuse me
If it were before, they wouldn't
have been qualified to be my rival
I know
Min said
you're not going smooth these days
Yeah!
Afraid of what?
Youngsters have more chances
Everybody got many chances in their life
But it matters
if they know how to grasp it
What about you?
Me?
I was too lazy
When I was in the band, I was hot
However I've spent my life chasing women
But now I don't even have a wife
But I will only blame my bad luck
I never doubt my ability
Remember, never question yourself
You're out so early?
No, I'm at home
You've your telephone?
Yeah! Go outside
Alright
A powerful mobile phone
That's wonderful,
I don't need to raise my head up again
What's your no? I'll call you
How come you're so impatient?
I'll treat you tonight
You've got a job?
Yeah! I'll play in Jacky's concert
I've got the deposit
That's great!
Remember to take me to the back stage,
I like him
See you downstairs at 8:00 p.m.
Alright! You wears your suit,
I wear my make-up
Don't laugh at me,
I've got only 2 dresses
Do I look weird?
You've shaved!
Very cute!
That's for you
You make me almost faint
Crabs
Eat
Let's go some places else!
Why? You want to come here
Look at this girl
It's Min
Min?
Min is wearing dress?
When she falls in love,
she'll wear dress
And lipstick too
If you go on, I'll not come again
She's angry
Excuse me everybody
I just wish to enjoy...
a romantic dinner quietly
with my girl friend
I hope you won't disturb us
Romantic...
Let's be romantic
Isn't it cute?
Yeah
Don't you like it?
How much?
$50
No!
My mom told me not to take other's ring
Don't you regret?
Let's go
I'll buy it myself
You said you don't want it
Kit...
Min, what's up?
The pain!
Calm!
Min...
What's happening?
Call the ambulance
Fetch the medicine
Deputy Director, here you are!
I know it must be my bed
That makes my body sore
I'm alright! Can I go home?
Say
From the X-ray,
it's found in your pelvis
Injection will begin tonight
I know you don't like to stay in ward,
I've arranged a private room for you
You may ask your mom to accompany you
Or ask Kit to come, alright?
Are you kidding?
What's that?
You said I'll recover
But how come you take your words back?
Min
Shut up!
How can you do this?
You deny your words
It's alright...
I'm alright
Get out
Min, don't do this
I can't stay here
Min, what are you doing?
I don't want any injection!
I can't take it
I don't want to lose my hair
Min...
Get lost!
Don't do this!
The doctor is coming to see you
Go away!
Can't you hear? Go away...
Don't worship him! He can't help you!
Go to the hospital
You can't say so. God will help her
Granny, excuse me
Please come with me to the hospital,
leave me alone
You know,
faith is more important than creed
Don't you remember
how you used to encourage me?
Kit, I know my business
Let's break up
Why?
Don't you think
it'll make me feel better?
You hurt me, don't you know?
Let me do it please! It may help
Go with me
Don't force me
Hurry up
Leave me alone
Where are you taking her?
I know you can stand up!
How is she?
Keung and Tat do have a share,
it's our idea
Take this to her family
I want to see her
I come to see you, don't you mind?
I'm more than happy
Please come in
This is for you
It's beautiful, thank you
Kit's music is very good,
our company has bought his piece
And I'll be singing this song,
will you be upset about this?
No! You're more suitable
In fact I can't,
I only know how to imitate
This is a wig! Isn't it ugly?
You're very slim
I can't help it
If I know you're coming,
I'll wear some make-up
You're pretty
But Kit is getting haggard
I ask him to go home,
but he doesn't listen
Kit is good to you
Are you still thinking about him?
No
I heard his friend say
He become more cheerful after he met you
and his laughter is louder than before
Can you tell me
how can you make him laugh?
Just cheer him up
I've tried,
but it didn't work
Maybe he was in bad mood
And you both are hot tempered
Then you've to teach me
Let me try this on the next guy
When he meets disappointment,
you should encourage him,
when he is in bad mood, cheer him up
When he's down, talk to him
But never leave him
Then he'll be alright
In fact, it's just theory
I know Kit still loves you
He always thinks about you
He won't take the initiative to call you
When the time comes, you go and find him
Don't talk like this
I wish he's happy
You'll recover, you'll be alright
It fits!
Look, you don't even need to alter it
I want to go out again
Haven't you said you've quitted!
Everybody knows about Min,
I guess no one will laugh at me
I still have some money
Don't!
What's happened to you?
I used to be a bit mean
But now...
That's why I have money to lend you now
How long can you help me?
This house is going to be demolished,
am I going to send these old guys
to the park?
We gotta find a house for them
Ling, this instrument is taking over you
It's an antique, still in good condition
What a pity!
It doesn't really matter
I know you'll write a better one for me
Sure
I've something for you
I've many deficiancy,
when I love somebody
I don't know how to put it in words
And when I want to thank somebody,
I don't know how to express it
But I really thank you so much
You've changed me
You propose to me just
because you feel grateful, don't you?
No, of course not
I'm serious
Kit! I couldn't be a wife
I may not be able to walk
I'll carry you
But I can't do the house work
I can do it
Maybe I'll die
No! We won't die so soon
We'll live at least up to 70 years old
If you start to worry,
you'll become old and ugly
We take away 2 years, then 68
We'll stay together forever, alright?
If I really...
I won't let you sit in the park alone
You may only cry for a short time
Woman like to be spoiled
Sometimes you may have to compromise,
but it won't harm you
Tracy still loves you
Min
You don't need to worry about my future
When you're with me,
I've changed a lot
There's only one thing on earth
that will hurt me
If you don't marry me
I'll be hurt forever
Will you marry me?
Yes
The nurse-in-chief said
you stop any pills
Yeah
Why don't you have injection?
Those are poison
Her leucocyte level
is getting lower and lower
I'm afraid she can't stand it
Can you think of any solution?
I know she tries to stand the pain
But don't tell me you've given up
I've not given up
Nine out of ten kids...
of my own were dead
If it weren't her
who has given me some hope
I would have quitted this job
How can I... give her up?
But how's her condition?
I know she's trying to stand the pain
I hope...
she can get over it
Don't... don't
If she sees you like this,
she'll feel very uncomfortable
Cheer up
Why do you get up?
If you want anything,
just tell me to do it
I'm hungry
Hungry, don't you want some milk?
I want to eat red bean cake
Now?
It's alright
Don't worry, it's just 10 o'clock,
I may get it
I'll go to check, you take a rest
Wait for me
Buddy
What's the matter?
Are they all closed?
Which one?
Is there any red bean cake?
They've closed already
Red bean cake, thank you
What color?
Coffee
And one more white one