David, are you in bed yet?
Um... Yeah, l am.
OK. Good night. l love you.
l love you too.
More news here
at your all-memories station
for St Petersburg and Tampa
at the top of the hour.
Now, l'd like to send out congratulations
to Thelma Miller of Orient Park.
She was our eighth caller yesterday,
and collected $225
on our big Money Memories Jackpot.
Today it could be you!
Oh, my. Look at this.
Here you go, Alma. Your little cart.
- What a mess.
- Load this for me, could you?
- Ex-Lax. You got my Ex-Lax?
- Heating pad. My heating pad.
There, Bernie. l hope you feel better.
- Don't use that stuff. Use prunes.
- l use both.
- That's everything.
- Rose, l think these must belong to you.
Oh, thank you. l'm Rose Lefkowitz.
l don't believe we've met.
- This is Ben, Rose.
- How do you do?
She remembers who l am, she remembers
who she is, so we're doing OK. Come on.
That's it.
Poor Rose. She's really slipping.
Here we go.
* And swing 'em to the left,
then you swing 'em to the right
* Then you do the twist with all of your might
* Truck on down, let's go to town
* And that's what we call dancin'!
- Let me hear it!
- * And that's what we call dancin'!
Hit it! Oh, that's much better.
Come on, ladies. Pick 'em up.
Oh. Very good. Girls, that's wonderful.
l saw this, but l fell asleep,
so l don't know how...
* Shake your little shoulders
and get on down
* Do the Suzy-Q that's good for you
* And that's what we call dancin'!
- Let me hear it!
- * That's what we call dancin'!
Hey, Art! Art!
Come on over here.
l could use some real men here.
lf we see any, we'll send them over.
Hit it.
Here we go.
* And swing 'em to the left...
- You gonna do anything about that one?
- Already have.
You put it to her?
You're disgusting.
So then you haven't, huh?
- What?
- l say, so then you haven't.
- There you go, Pops.
- Ben!
- l said one!
- Walk on the wild side.
- You boys still trespassing over there?
- Yup.
Hey, they're not even melted yet! Wow!
OK, let's get a board under him. Let's get a
pulse, let's get a blood pressure. l'll get a line.
- 80 over 50.
- Keep pumping.
- Ready!
- Clear!
ls there a pulse or a blood pressure?
Once more. Now! ls there a pulse?
- No pulse.
- Blood pressure?
- No blood pressure.
- Let's call it.
Well, what's the word?
What's the word on what?
The doctor. You went
to the doctor. What did he say?
lt's a breeze. Everything's fine.
Hey, wait a minute. Wait right there.
This is me you're talking to.
Now, you went to the goddamn doctor.
Now, what did he say?
Doctors don't know everything.
Well, there is the one school of thought
that says they don't know nothin'.
Well, gentlemen, mission accomplished.
- Hope the water isn't too cold.
- You want it heated too?
What about a lifeguard?
Well, the marines have landed.
Navy's in.
- Boy, that's cold.
- You're right.
Ah, fellas, this is the life.
That'll make your old ball-sack shrivel up.
Well, all in all, that was a pretty
damn crappy day at sea, wasn't it, boys?
- You stink.
- Me? Come on, man.
- lt's the great unknown out there.
- Here. Here's half your money.
Half? What's this ''half'?
Bonner, you got my goddamn money now?
l got it right here.
l'll be with you in a second, OK?
Cos if you ain't got it now,
you're not tyin' up here.
Look. l don't wanna get rough with you,
you know? But l'm not takin' half.
- Fine. Give it.
- Get your hands off!
Just get your ass off my boat, man.
Get your ass off my boat. You believe this?
And take your embarrassing
beach towel with you.
Can you believe these tourists?
The guy throws up on the deck, he doesn't
catch one fish, gives me half my money.
- l need a brew. Want something cold?
- Untie the boat line.
No, wait! Don't untie the boat line.
Here you go, you bloodsucker.
l have nothing to live on. Nothing. Zip.
Oh, Kirk, come on. You're not actually
gonna take all my money, are you?
- You're gonna leave me $5, aren't you, Kirk?
- Not on your life.
Shit! Come on, Kirk.
That money'll bring you no pleasure.
- Could l have a word?
- l promise you!
- You just try and sleep tonight.
- l'll sleep like a baby.
Oh, shit!
We'd like to rent your boat.
- You what?
- We'd like to rent your boat.
We'd like to rent your boat. For 27 days.
lf that wouldn't be too long for you.
No. Yeah!
Yeah? 27?
That's my lucky number.
Holy sh... smokes!
Hi. Jack Bonner. How you doin'?
- Hi, Jack. l'm Walter.
- Hi, Walter. Well, come on.
Take a look around. Boat sleeps eight,
so you should be pretty comfortable.
lf you've got a latitude and a longitude,
l can get you there.
- lf you don't, l can still get you there.
- We know a great dive spot. We have a map.
Great. Great.
Uh... Guess we can talk price later.
Oh, that door basically
slides back and forth. lt may need some oil.
l haven't dusted in a while. But l'm gonna do
a whole cleanup, the whole sanitation thing.
lf you look at anything closely enough,
you're bound to find flaws.
l'm an experienced scuba diver
and tour guide, deep-sea fisherman...
Who will actually eat tonight! Yes!
ln the kitchen! You're in the kitchen.
And my mother went out on the porch,
and she was screaming...
- Give it a rest, Rose.
- ''You stop teasing your sister!''
- Hiya, Grandpa!
- Here's the little fella.
- Come right to the courts, do ya?
- lt's Thursday.
He knows our schedule.
- Hi!
- Here's David.
He's always here.
Does this kid have a home or what?
Bernie! His parents are divorced,
his mother works...
l'm an orphan.
Do l go around askin' for breaks?
We're goin' swimming later.
We have room left for one little boy.
And we might even have
a swimming suit for you.
- l got mine on.
- Oh, the navy could use men like you.
The property's been tied up
in an estate now for over three years.
And, of course, they really want to sell.
They're not interested in a long-term lease.
We'd just like the place for 26 days.
And we'll take it in as-is condition.
We're cousins.
We like to vacation together, informally.
As long as there's a swimming pool,
we have everything we need.
Uh, $7500 a month,
plus the pool man and utilities.
We won't be needing the pool man.
l prefer to do that myself. They use
so much chlorine. My eyes are very sensitive.
- Oh, but they're lovely.
- Thank you.
Clubhouse is closed, boys.
Well, maybe they'd give us
permission to use the pool.
- We could offer to pay something.
- Wouldn't be fun if we had permission.
Jack, this is the chart l was telling you about.
l estimate our position
is right about here. This point.
- l wanna get down right along this fault line.
- ls this land? What is this?
This is actually
an underwater-configuration map.
- A heat-sensitive map.
- l've seen these.
- Yeah, it's a brand-new development.
- The Japanese have this.
That's right, Jack. The Japanese developed it.
So the point is to head
directly south, right along this line,
until we get right here
on the edge of this fault line.
- You can figure that out?
- Yeah. Actually, l've been around here.
- Why don't you keep this?
- OK. Go get some sodas and sandwiches.
- Thanks, Jack.
- OK.
All right, let's start with line three.
- T-O-Z.
- And the next line.
L-P-E-O.
Try the next line.
K-O-C...
K-O-C-F-E.
Uh, sir, do you have another pair of glasses?
l don't need any other glasses, young man.
These are my glasses. l can read that fine.
Now you just run the pointer, all right?
Next line.
- ls there anything on that line you can read?
- No.
But, young man, remember,
road signs aren't made that small.
l can read road signs.
OK.
l don't think it's fair. l've driven everything
on wheels all my life and never had a mishap.
Shit. How's your girlfriend?
She's not my girlfriend.
She just followed me home that one day.
l don't like her at all.
You don't, huh?
- Hi, Dad.
- Hi, honey.
Hi, Mom.
- Wanna go out to dinner?
- Yeah!
No ltalian food. Makes me fart.
OK. l'll go get Mom.
You know, you're gonna have to make
a friend your own age one of these days.
l don't like the kids my age.
l like to hang around you guys.
Sure you like it here.
There's no pressure, and we baby ya.
- More things bother me than other guys.
- Oh, they do, do they?
Trouble with you is, you think too much,
and that's when a guy gets scared.
You know, Grandpa, you're right.
l do get scared a lot.
Nobody likes bein' scared.
Watch out. Those dolphins look pretty horny.
- This is pretty big.
- Yeah, pretty big.
- You need a hand?
- No. No, thanks, Jack. We're doing fine.
Excuse me.
- What the hell is that?
- Who cares?
You know, l bet they're dope peddlers.
l bet they made a pick-up out at sea.
- lt's possible.
- Should we tell somebody?
Huh! No!
By golly, if our new neighbours do that,
l don't feel bad about sneakin' in
their swimming pool while they're gone.
- You think it's safe?
- What are they gonna do, arrest us?
- Look at us. We're three harmless old men.
- Who knows what kind of people they are?
You know, l can't remember
the last time l really took a risk.
Ben's right. l'm in.
What the hell?
Look at that.
The water's really warm.
What the hell are those?
Listen to that!
They make me nervous.
lf Ben Luckett decides to jump off the Empire
State Building, do you have to do it too?
l have my pride.
- l feel great.
- Me too.
You wouldn't bullshit me?
My God, l'm telling the truth!
Why shouldn't he feel good?
l feel tremendous!
l'm ready to take on the world!
* l'm in the mood for love
* Simply because you're near me
You get a load of this guy? He'll be
chasin' them dolls till his dick rots off.
l'm too old for that kind of thing.
- Ah, hey, age isn't everything.
- No, no.
- Anyway, it's all up here.
- Oh, sure. Sure.
lt's not all up there, pal.
Some of it's down here.
Which, by the way, is hard as a rock.
- You too? You got a boner too?
- Blue steel. Cat couldn't scratch it.
l thought l was the only one.
* We're in the mood for love
* Simply because we've got one
You tired?
Aren't you?
l'm wide awake.
- What's wrong?
- Not a thing.
Art! lt's so late.
Are you all right?
* Some enchanted evening
* You may see a stranger
* Across a crowded room
- Want a piece of candy, little girl?
- Ben!
Ben!
Pung.
Three. Ghost Dragon.
Why is everybody so quiet today?
You're all off in another world, or something.
l was just thinking to myself.
Me too. l was just thinking.
l feel so nice today, l can't tell you.
Joe?
Let's go!
- Morning!
- Morning.
Excuse me.
- Do you think there's cocaine in that pool?
- Might be.
- What if we OD?
- Well, we'll keep an eye on each other.
l'll watch him, you watch him, you watch me.
Perfect.
Hey.
Hi. Looks like you got
these things pretty well covered.
Looks airtight.
Jack, l can't tell you what's inside there.
You know, l'm the captain.
Technically speaking,
l have to know what's in there.
Yeah, but what we're doing
is supposed to be a secret.
Kitty, l took a maritime oath.
A maritime oath! lt forbids me
to even reveal your names to anybody.
All right, l'll tell you. But you can't let
the others know that l told you anything.
They'd have to torture me.
Not a lot of torture, you know, but some.
Nerita peleronta.
- Ner... what?
- Nerita peleronta.
- What is that?
- They're giant snail shells.
They're extremely rare. We're taking them
to the Museum of lchthyology in Orlando.
Oh, really?
Yeah, l've been planning to go there.
l hear it's a great place. A lot of fish.
Oh, God. Oh, God,
l think it's broken. Goddamn it!
- Let me help you.
- Some ice. Get something cold on it.
- Let me look.
- Do not touch it.
- l can help you.
- No, no, no, no!
That feels nice.
That's amazing.
- Kitty, you married?
- No.
- lnvolved?
Come on.
Those guys are so good-lookin'.
Not Walter, maybe, but... You don't have
anything goin' with one of the young guys?
l'm not involved with anyone.
OK.
You know, we could go out
and do something, sometime.
- l don't know if that's such a good idea.
- Why?
- l'm not like the other women you've known.
- That's good news.
You're makin' me very curious about you.
Well, what if l trusted you
with something very private?
Oh, l can keep a secret. l wouldn't
tell anybody. Not even our kids.
Look, l don't know what you're thinkin'.
But if you're thinkin' that
l'm just out to nail you, that's not it at all.
l'd just like to get to know you,
as a human being.
OK. l'll see you in the morning, all right?
What?
Yeah, l got some things to do too.
They didn't give you any other
medication at all over at the home, huh?
Not a thing, Doc.
Well, Joe, l gotta tell you, l have never seen
anything like this before in my life! lt's a...
Well, it's a miracle! lt's a complete remission.
l just love to see you eat your words, Doc.
- Want to arm wrestle?
- No!
How about that?!
- Alma's not gonna believe this.
- You've got 'em? Ah!
Come on. Let's go, shall we?
l'm gonna go ahead and assume goodwill.
l'm gonna assume mental illness.
Oh, Bernie. l didn't expect it.
lt's such a surprise!
- l don't know how to do it. l didn't buy it.
- lt's just beautiful.
Thank you very much, ladies and gentlemen.
We start our second session of dancing now.
Our first tune is a special
arrangement of ''Dancing in the Dark''.
Let's waste no time.
- Why don't we dance?
- What? Oh, sure!
Oh, Bernie, Bernie, Bernie,
what am l going to do with you?
l don't know what l'm going to do with you.
- Well, you're not gonna dance with me.
- That's for sure. That's for sure.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- You're a wonderful dancer.
- l think so!
l'm very happy, Bess.
Everything's happening so fast.
- Are you talking about last night?
- No, no. Last night was fine.
Fine?
More than fine! Terrific!
l was talking in general.
Well, in general,
l think we're having a great time!
Yes, we are.
Will you still love me
when l can't keep up with you?
Of course. l love you now,
and you can't keep up with me.
You are a pain in the ass!
''There's gonna be a problem
in the fuel-injection system if...''
What does this do?
Reduced to a goddamn
Peeping Tom now, Bonner?
lt's embarrassing.
Holy shit!
Look...
What's the problem, Jack?
She's not normal.
There's something very abnormal about her.
Come on, come on, come on...
Son of a bitch.
Come on. Start! Go! Come on!
l've had all kinds of people on this boat.
All kinds! From all races! Come on...
All nationalities! All creeds!
Oh, my God, l can't believe it! lt won't start!
Oh, my God.
lt's... lt's hard to know who to trust.
lsn't it, Jack?
Oh! Oh, my God! Oh, God!
l'm in the water, far from shore.
lt's at night.
They got my boat. Shit.
Oh, my God!
Good to see you again, Jack.
Let me give you a hand.
l don't want your hand. Get back! Get back!
You get back!
Oh, no. Just put the towel down.
Just put it down and back away, please.
l'm sure you're bothered
by what you saw, but relax...
- l don't wanna relax!
- Why not let us explain?
Cos l don't wanna know anything.
And if you try to eat my face off,
or take over my body,
you're gonna be very sorry, mister.
You're gonna be very sorry!
Face-eating, Jack?
l've never heard of that.
ls that some sort of delicacy?
No. Forget l ever mentioned it.
- Are you sure l shouldn't try it, Jack?
- l'm positive.
Walter, Jack is our friend. Right, Jack?
Friend... Friend! That's right.
Friend. 100%. I'm your friend.
That's all l ever wanted to be. Your friend.
- But we do owe you an explanation.
- No, you don't owe me anything.
You don't...
Not even for the boat, honestly. lt's free.
Jack. Of course we're gonna
pay you for the boat. We're honest.
Well, of course you're honest!
Did l ever accuse you of being dishonest?
l accused you of being from another planet.
But an honest planet.
Jack. Jack, sit down.
- l don't wanna sit down.
- Jack, sit!
Now, Jack,
l want you to listen to me very carefully.
We're Antareans.
We come from a planet called Antarea.
Yeah, that's what l pretty much figured.
100 centuries ago, we had an outpost
here on Earth, before the first upheaval.
- Well, l think l'm better off not knowing.
- Shh.
We were able to evacuate everyone
except for my ground crew.
- Ground crew?
- And now we've come back for them.
Boy. l thought l'd been around. Nothing
like this has ever happened to me before.
Now, Jack, you could turn us in.
Or you could do something else
to make things difficult for us.
But believe me, Jack,
we will still get our friends back.
And the only thing that would happen is that
we'd end up renting someone else's boat.
You know, l got left behind once.
lt was in Coney lsland. l was nine.
lt was pretty heavy for a nine-year-old.
My parents finally came back for me.
Of course. And now we've come back.
- So you're comin' back for your friends?
- Exactly.
Jack, this is the most
important thing we've ever done.
You're not gonna hurt me, are you, Walt?
All we need to do
is to get our friends and leave.
And go... pfft?
- Yes. Pfft.
- Right. Pfft, pfft, pfft, pfft.
- None of this is bad for America, l guess?
- Of course not.
Well, damn it, l'm in.
This... This is incredible.
Right. Now, nothing's gonna fall off, is it?
No.
- Come on, Mr Lefkowitz.
- You'll love it.
- You'll be a new man, Bernie, believe me.
- Remember, l said l'd look.
- l'm not promising l'll get wet.
- Fine. Just look.
By the way, right here
is where a crime is being committed.
Not by me, because l'm being carried.
Don't you worry, Bernie.
We'll take the fall for you.
Fall? That's another thing.
l fall, l break my hip, l can't sue anybody.
- lt's nice and warm, Bernie.
- They're rocks.
What are rocks doing in a pool?
ln an ocean, fine.
There l expect to see plenty of rocks.
But in a pool? No.
Hah! Cowardly cowardly custard!
Can't cut the mustard!
Come on, Bernie!
And it's Joe... Joe taking the lead...
Come on! Come on, navy! Come on!
Come on, you worn-out old pusses!
Dig, dig, dig, dig, dig!
l'll see you tomorrow.
Hey, fellas? Fellas, fellas, hey!
Somebody's comin'. Let's get out!
Let's get out of here.
Come on! Let's go. Come on!
- Come on. Get a move on.
- Come on. ln here.
- Out of the way!
- Let's move!
- Jesus!
Come on, open the fuckin' door.
Let's go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
l begged you not to go.
You've got to do something.
There are things from outer space next door.
You gents keep suckin' on that oxygen.
They'll probably go back to their own planet.
- Get the police, you idiots.
- Hey, look.
l'm not callin' no cops because a couple of
geezers saw some people from outer space.
lf my husband said he saw people from
outer space, they were from outer space!
- Get the goddamn police!
- OK.
Call the police. Whoo!
They must have concocted
this crazy story to cover themselves.
Spacemen, you say? That's wonderful! Well,
we'll all be that old someday. lf we're lucky.
Yeah. Well, we're gonna shoot on over to the
home and straighten this whole thing out.
l wouldn't be too hard on 'em. Just tell 'em,
as long as they're willing to respect our
privacy in future, we won't press charges.
- We'll keep 'em on their side of the fence.
- Thank you.
My pleasure. Bye-bye.
Well, l guess we shouldn't be greedy about it.
We're better off than before we found it.
Bess said we should
take it to The National Enquirer.
They pay money for this kind of story.
l wish l had the guts to go in.
Yeah. Boy, l wish
l never even knew about this place.
Oh. What time is it?
Just after four.
l'm gonna go talk to him.
Goddamn, it's ridiculous.
Hey, Walter.
Well, l'm not surprised you're here.
There's something in that pool
a friend of ours just has to have.
Matter of fact,
there's a few of us could use a little of it.
We don't care who you are, where you've
been, what you're doin', what you're up to.
Sure need that pool.
Look, Ben, l know you're
just trying to help your people.
Well, l'm trying to help mine.
No, see, my friend Joe Finley, he's got cancer.
l'm trying to save his life.
l'm trying to save 20 lives.
And l'm running out of time.
No son of a bitch
has to know we're in that pool.
We'll just be a few old farts paddlin'
around in that pool. Who's gonna know?
Every ten or eleven thousand years or so,
l make a terrible mistake.
The last one was when l picked what
you call Atlantis as our base here on Earth.
Everyone else said use the North Pole.
l said ''No, too cold.''
Sinking never occurred to me.
You're gonna let us use the pool, aren't you?
You won't touch those cocoons?
No. No, l swear.
Use the pool.
Thank you. Thank you!
- l, for one, don't believe this alien crap at all.
- You don't believe your husband?
- No.
- l believe Joe. l believe him and l'm scared.
- l don't believe it and l'm still scared.
- l guess l'm just less gullible.
Mary, you have your nerve!
l have more horse sense than you ever had.
Ladies, ladies. Let's just go
and see for ourselves. Come on.
All right. Let's meet the aliens!
l hate to go visiting without
a plate of cookies or a box of candy.
- We're going home.
- Will you cut it out, Bernie?
- We have permission, don't we?
- Those people aren't people.
- l'm not gonna have anything to do with 'em.
- Oh, pipe down.
You're playin' with fire over there.
l'm a citizen. l believe in this country.
l'm thinkin' of blowin' a whistle
on the whole deal. Come on, Rose.
- Stop right there.
- Oh, what. What?
- Stop thinkin' about yourself. This is for Joe.
- Joe?
ls Joe above the law? Are any of us?
- ln 1948, Dutch Schultz walked into my store.
- Bernie. Bernie, shut up!
- Let me tell you about what Dutch said.
- Bernie. Bernie!
lf you don't wanna do this for Rose, if you
don't wanna do it for yourself, that's fine.
- But if you screw it up for us...
- Don't threaten me, Joe.
Bernie, please.
Let her come with us. Just this once.
No, no. Never. Rose and l
will never set foot over there again.
Nature dealt us a hand of cards.
We play them.
Now, at the end of the game, suddenly
you're lookin' to reshuffle the deck? Huh?
Oh, come on, Rose. Come on, let's go.
Anybody have second thoughts?
- Not me.
- l'm a citizen too.
l was in the navy.
l don't see anything wrong with it.
Then you drive. l got no licence.
* How would you like
to spend the weekend in Havana?
Are your extraterrestrials
gonna make a personal appearance?
Hey, Pills! Come on in!
Hi, Pillsbury. How you doin', pal?
You'll like Pillsbury. He's a fine fella.
Adios, Pillsbury!
All right. Let's start here.
P-E-Z-O-L-C-F-T-D.
Sir, what line are you reading?
The bottom one.
We're in a little bit of a hurry, OK?
Look, look! We've gotta go into the club.
Hello, Grandpa.
Hey, look at the old fogies.
Off the floor, Grandpa.
..requiring weekend
transportation to St Petersburg,
contact miss Lerner
in her office by one o'clock today.
Hi, Pops.
Hey. Hey!
l wanna talk to you two.
The word on the corridor is that you dudes
are onto some kind of rejuvenation.
Rejuve-what?
- You know what l'm talkin' about.
- No, we don't.
- l wish we could help you.
- Your wife been climbin' trees a long time?
- She climbs one every once in a while.
- Once in a great while.
That's right.
You know, whenever
l'm around you, l feel really good.
Really good. Do l do that to you?
lt happens.
Do you ever wanna do anything about it?
Well, not the way you think about it.
l mean, l can't.
Oh. Right.
Right.
Well, how does an Antarean...
express affection?
- We share ourselves.
- All right!
Do you wanna try it?
lt's very fulfilling.
Don't touch me.
Don't touch you? What's the big deal?
All right. l'm gonna tell you the truth.
You're not my first Antarean.
- l'm not naming names, but...
- Jack, go to the other side of the pool.
Well, l hope you're not gonna take your skin
off, because l really like skin on a woman.
lf this is foreplay, l'm a dead man.
- Three strikes!
- They set the pins up, l knock 'em down.
Hey, you know something?
You had marvellous balls.
l've bowled with a lot of women.
You have potential.
You seem like you're havin'
a grand time. l know l am.
Joe, you'll never bowl another
game like that as long as you live.
- Don't count on it. l may turn professional.
- Sure!
What's next? What's next? Let's have a party.
A party. l'm for that.
* You bring the hot dog,
and l'll bring the bun!
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
- What?
Look at you goddamn people.
l mean, l think this is a serious mistake.
What? A mistake about what?
Well, you know, l promised Walter
we'd keep it secret, and look at this.
Oh, yeah.
Let's not have too much fun, everybody.
Remember, we're old, old, old...
Not for me. l'm gonna enjoy everything.
- Where to next, Ben?
- Home.
- Ah, come on. Live a little.
- Joe, Joe, Joe. Everybody. Let's go home.
- But l'm not ready to go home yet.
- Come on. Come on, let's go.
- What's happening, suddenly?
- Well, l'll go with you, Joe.
No, you go on home.
l may have a drink or two.
Will you keep that for me?
So, good night, you worriers.
Boy, talk about wet blankets.
Hey. l'll be fine.
- l still can't believe l did that.
- l always liked chocolate.
l'll try not to dump anything on you tonight.
l can't promise, but l'll try.
Alma...
- lt's the pool.
- lt's not the pool. lt's not the water.
lt's not the first time.
- Alma, you're overreacting.
- l knew. l always knew.
l just pretended to be stupid, and l guess
l really was. But you're the stupid one.
- Things have been so good between us.
- Nothing's changed...
Go home, Joe. Don't make yourself look
any more ridiculous than you already are.
l'm happy you're going to live, Joe.
But l've got to live too.
Joe. Joe, try to relax.
Hey, are you up for a swim, maybe?
Well, sure.
Pool! Pool!
Can't you think about anything else?
- lf you and Rose came, you'd feel differently.
- We don't want to. We like the way we feel.
She needs it, Bernie.
- We should discuss this later.
- There is nothing to discuss!
You're a hard-head.
You're the most frightened man l ever knew.
- Christ, l don't have to listen to you.
- lf you sit at this table you damn well do!
You think you're in such great shape, Finley.
Your marriage is what's terminally ill now.
- You really are an old bastard.
- Old is right. l don't wanna be young again.
You're a mess because of the fountain of
youth, however healthy you think you are!
- Sit down, stupid.
- We don't want any part of that pool!
You can keep the goddamn fountain of youth!
No wonder your wife has no use for you.
- l'm gonna kill that son of a bitch.
- Joe! Joe!
Joe! Joe, Joe, Joe! Joe!
lt's next door, isn't it?
lt's in that pool over there, right?
- Get that pool!
- Get out of the way!
What is...
Oh, my God! What do we do? Ben...
- Please, get out of the pool.
- Come on. Everybody out!
Come on. Get out of there.
Come on, out of the water! Get out!
You're trespassing!
Stop!
Everybody out!
You have no right to be here.
You are trespassing here.
Put down the cocoon.
l said, put down the cocoon!
Put it down. Put it down.
l'm calling the police.
Get out, all of you. Get out!
All this time to energise the pool,
and now the life force
is completely drained from the water.
l'm not gonna be able to bring them back.
When Max saw me in that sweater with
the mouton collar and the ivory buttons,
he said ''Rose, where the hell
did you get that sweater?''
l stayed mum.
Because l knew you stole it.
But you stole it for me.
Max never stole anything for me.
And he never made anything
as beautiful as that mouton collar.
Max couldn't do anything with his hands.
Except when they were all over me.
But you wouldn't even
kiss my cheek without asking.
Dumping Max was
the smartest move l ever made.
Oh, Bernie...
Time for your medicine. l'll get it.
Here you are.
Rose.
Rose? Are you asleep?
Rose?
Rose!
Rose...
Rose.
l'm so sorry.
Can you help me?
l have to do something for her.
She... she...
The pool doesn't work any more. lt's too late.
l'll give you everything l've got.
l'm sorry, Bernie.
l wish l could help you. lt's just too late.
Rosie?
Oh, Rosie...
- Hello, Ben.
- Walter.
l thought maybe you guys had got out of
here already, after what happened today.
l came by to tell you l'm sorry, Walter. l...
l know we let you down and l'm really sorry.
l had never experienced the pain and...
the grief associated with death before.
l... never had anyone close to me who died.
Walter, these things out here.
Can you take them back
with you on that spaceship?
No. They would never survive the flight.
Well, can you put 'em back in the ocean?
Two are gone now.
Two of my friends are gone.
We don't have time to get them all back in the
ocean. We must leave this place tomorrow.
What if we do it tonight? We'll help you.
- Bring that one around here, OK?
- Let me give you a hand with that.
There are a lot more.
Take this one outside and come back.
- OK. Got it?
- l can't do this alone.
- Hey, could somebody give me a hand?
- Set it over there.
- OK?
- Come on, let's go. Let's get a hold of it.
Our base was sinking. The time to prepare
a passage for all of us was gone.
These 20 chose to stay behind
so the rest of us could leave safely.
They survived here in the ocean
for 10,000 years. They can survive again.
- OK?
- Yes.
- How you guys doin'?
- OK.
- You OK?
- l'm fine. l've been diving before.
Oh, yeah?
l want you all to consider very carefully
what l'm about to suggest to you.
You and your friends
seem to want what we've got.
Well, we have room for you.
We have room for you
and about 30 more of your friends.
You would be students, of course, but...
But you'd also be teachers.
And the new civilisations
that we'll be travelling to
will be unlike
anything you've ever known.
But l promise you,
you will all lead productive lives.
- For ever?
- We don't know what ''for ever'' means.
l got a couple of things l...
- Not a good cast.
- ..l need to talk about with you.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
l guess me and your grandma
are goin' away, David.
- Where to?
- Well, that's not important.
What's important is that...
when we get where we're goin'...
we'll never be sick,
we won't get any older and we won't ever die.
- You're joking me, right?
- No.
No.
Would l be able to visit you and Grandma?
And we wouldn't be able
to visit you either, and that kinda bothers me.
l'd never see you again?
No.
When would you go, if you did?
Soon, my boy. Soon.
- And do you know where?
- Where?
Look up.
Outer space, my lad. Outer space.
Who's gonna take you to outer space?
lt don't matter.
You wouldn't believe me if l told you.
And l can't tell your mother, because she'd
then know her old man had snapped his cap.
l wonder if they'll have fishin' holes there?
There's some things they won't have. They
won't have grandsons and they won't have...
baseball games, and they won't have hot
dogs, and they won't have that kind of stuff.
l'm gonna miss 'em.
All right, cast it out there.
l wish we'd get a bite.
l'd like to catch one more great big fish.
You know how much we love you, don't you?
Of course l do.
l just don't want you to forget how much
we care, no matter what we say or do.
Of course.
- Bye, Grandpa.
- Goodbye, little man.
Smile.
Bye, Dad. Bye, Mom.
Stop by next week sometime, OK?
Be a good boy. Mind your mom.
You havin' second thoughts?
Yes.
- So you think we're cheatin' nature?
- Yes.
Well, l'll tell you something.
The way nature's been treatin' us,
l don't mind cheatin' her a little.
- You'll be closing your account, Mr Selwyn?
- Yes, l will.
- All in $100 bills?
- Mm-hm.
Here you go.
This is for you.
Sir!
Here. Have fun!
Have fun, my friends, have fun!
Here, divide it up, girls! Divide it up!
There you are, there you are!
* Racing with the moon! Hey, enjoy, enjoy!
* Sailing to the midnight sun...
He can come in for a minute.
Hi.
They say if we go with them,
we'll live for ever.
Well, that's good. lt's probably going
to take you an eternity to forgive me.
l'm sorry, Alma.
l guess l've been ridiculous. l am sorry.
l love you.
You're my whole life.
l want to go.
But if it's a choice of
only six more months here with you,
or living for ever all by myself, well,
l'll take the six more months here with you.
l don't wanna live for ever
if you're not gonna be with me.
- So you definitely trust them?
- We trust 'em.
Men should be explorers,
no matter how old they are.
l don't know about anybody else,
but l'm going.
Why the hell not? We're in.
Are you nervous?
Me? No.
You're sure you want to do this?
Once l make a decision,
Arthur, l never turn back.
This is a big one.
l know.
Yeah, it's gonna be 72 and clear tonight.
A great night to see that total lunar eclipse.
Check it out.
But don't get weird on me, people.
Let's go. Let's go.
Quick. Get me a glass of water.
Look out.
- Don't do that!
- What is the meaning of this?
David? You staying up for the eclipse?
You don't seem too enthusiastic.
Did you and Grandpa have a fight today?
No.
What did he say to you?
David, l'm very worried about Grandpa
and Grandma. What did he say to you?
l can't tell you.
They're my parents, David.
You've got to tell me what he said to you.
He made me promise.
Mom? Dad?
Hey, Bernie! Come on!
You're coming with us, Bernie!
No. l came to say goodbye.
l just wanted to tell you,
l hope you find what you're looking for.
Rose is gone, Bernie.
Why stay?
This is my home.
This is where l belong.
Come on, go with us.
Goodbye, Bernie.
- Goodbye, Bernie.
- Bye.
We'll miss you.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on. Go.
Only when l need it, right?
Only when l need it.
Jesus...
- l know something is wrong.
- They're probably out dancin'.
Those folks love to dance.
Could we talk to one of their friends?
We'll go see Pops. Will that satisfy ya?
Pops.
Pops?
Got a little game of 20 questions for ya.
Pops!
Oh, shit!
Hello?
l don't know what's goin' on here.
- We'd better take a look down below.
- What?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Make sure you get the feed line,
cos it's gotta be... You got it. Good.
The injector.
Yeah, we gotta make the injector...
You got that, too? Good. Um...
Go house to house. Check the bus stations
and the airports. This is a serious situation.
The owner of the facility is on his way.
He's not happy at all.
Why don't we start by taking
a good look around the grounds first?
- OK, gentlemen?
- OK. Right this way.
Better advise your commander.
Don't worry, miss.
We'll help you find your father and mother.
- lt's right over here.
- We're in deep shit, you know that?
David! David!
Back this way!
Hey, hey. Whoa!
ln case you're wondering, Silly Putty.
Cast off those lines.
Grandpa! Wait for me!
l want to go too!
- Grandpa!
- What are you doing here? Are you all right?
- Yeah.
- My gosh.
- David! David!
- A boatjust left from the dock next door.
- Old people. A kid. Some in wheelchairs.
- Mom! Dad!
- David!
- We'd better move. l don't like the looks of it.
You can't go.
Only your grandmother
and me from this outfit.
Captain, this is Air 21.
l think l got 'em below me.
- Want me to swoop 'em? Over.
- Roger, Air 21. You are cleared.
This is the Coast Guard helicopter.
Heave to. Prepare to be boarded.
Manta lll, be prepared for Coast Guard boats
to come alongside and board your vessel.
Manta lll, this is not a request, this is an order.
You are endangering the lives
of your passengers. Cut your engines.
We are coming alongside
to board your vessel.
Jack. Don't let them board us.
Nobody's gonna board this boat.
You just get your friends here.
Engines! Cut your engines!
Captain, this is Lieutenant Spark
of the St Petersburg Police.
You have senior citizens aboard
who are in no condition to be out here.
You have a minor aboard
without authority from his mother.
We want to question you.
Please cut your engines now.
We are coming alongside to board
your vessel. Stand by to be boarded.
David's mother wants him
to come into the police boat with her.
David, come on! Please!
Mom and Dad, where are you going?!
David! You come back here!
- David!
- Swing it around!
Cut your engines! Cut your engines!
Man overboard! Man overboard, gentlemen.
- You all right?
- l'm OK.
l'm not scared! Get going!
Let's go.
Oh, David.
Roger.
Maintaining visual of the Manta.
These people must be nuts.
We're gonna have to pursue and intercept.
We just went into fog, rollin' out.
Recheck speed selectors,
full forward. Wheels up.
- Where the hell did this come from?
- l don't know.
l can't see a damn thing.
l never seen it roll in so fast.
My God.
- We got no reading on radar. Over.
- 1-4-X-3, we copy. Zero visibility.
- We're gonna run into each other. Go ahead.
- Roger. Let's shut 'em down. Over.
This should more than cover
the cost of the boat.
- l...
- l want to thank you for being a fine guide.
- And a good friend.
- All right.
Uh... Now, you drive careful, Walter.
See you, Walter.
Well, l guess your ride's here, huh?
Look, Kitty, next time you're in town,
l want you to look me up, OK?
Don't worry, Jack.
You'll know when l'm around.
You don't know how close
l came to buying a ticket.
- You'd better go.
- OK. l'm gonna miss you, Kitty. l really am.
''May the Force be with you!''
There can never be
an accounting, in human terms,
for the tragedy at sea which has taken
the lives of these men and women
in what should have been the beautiful
and peaceful sunset of their lives.
Do not fear.
Your loved ones are in safe keeping.
They have moved on
to a higher expression of life.
Not life as we know it,
but in the spirit everlasting.
Our loved ones are in good hands,
for now and for evermore.
Join with me now
in a moment of silent prayer.
Visiontext Subtitles: Yasmeen Khan
ENGLlSH