Take this and go home
Stay out of the rain
Dummy
Do you want to get electrocuted?
You're crazy
I don't want to split up like this
Let's talk just for a moment
Nothing can change
There's no use in talking
Let go of me!
Here's your letter
I don't want it anymore
Why?
There's no response and because of my conscience
I'll write it myself from now on
And tell her the truth
It's a golden opportunity
I heard she's very sick from the rain
So she's in the hospital
She's very sick?
Because of the rain?
Yeah
I'm going to see her
If I visit her when she's sick then I can score
I'll confess to her that I didn't write the letters
I won't tell her it was you
Actually
I'm not the type to like one girl
but I really like her
Oh Joon-ha!
He's calling you
Yes?
Twenty four, twenty seven
Thirty, thirty two...
I have to eat all this?
Look at this
Mawworms, intestinal worms
hookworms, roundworms...
You have everything
What the hell did you eat?
Because of you our class has the most parasites
But sir it wasn't my manure
Then whose was it?
You're the only one who'd have
this many parasites, Eat it now!
YOON Tae-soo
Eat three
But it's the same manure
Yeah, but some spots have more parasites and some don't
How'd you know I was here?
Why are you covering your face?
Stop it, I haven't washed my face, and it's dirty
But you're still pretty
- How'd you know I was here?
- I heard from Tae-soo
Why are you laughing?
I heard you ate 32 worm-killing pills
Tae-soo, that bastard has a big mouth
Did he say anything else?
After being silent for a while that's all he said and left
- Really?
- Yeah
He's so odd
- Are you very sick?
- Yeah
I'm sorry
I must be really stupid
Besides liking you
I'm not good at anything else
No, there's a lot you're good at
Like getting drenched and eating worm pills
Don't laugh
This is serious
I have to tell Tae-soo about us
Then we can clear our conscience
See you later
Is this her room?
My poor daughter-in-law!
How'd you get so drenched?
No, lie down
A cold can't be taken lightly
You can catch pneumonia
So, are you eating well?
You should eat well to recover
I'm sorry
This must be the wrong room
Wrong room
Clench your fists
Raise them like this
Now hit me
Why should I hit you?
Hurry and hit me!
I don't like hitting people or getting hit
My dad hit me too many times
I like Joo-hee
Actually, she gave me this necklace last summer
Are you okay?
Damn it
I've fallen again
Don't worry
And don't let my dad see that necklace
He'll get furious
That necklace was a gift from my dad
To Joo-hee
Oh Joon-ha!
It's your letter!
Later on, we went on school break
And I thought I couldn't see her again
I miss you
I miss you so much I'll die
And I'm curious how much our river has changed
Say hi to our haunted house
the shed, and our row boat
Say that I miss them and that I'm doing okay
Yesterday, Tae-soo came to me with your Uncle's address
He also confessed a shocking thing to me
That you were the one who wrote the letters to me
How could you hide that from me?
Anyway, it's okay
I almost threw away those letters
but now I can read them again and think of you
Tae-soo also made a suggestion
That you put Tae-soo's name on the letters you send me
Then my parents will think
that I'm exchanging letters with him
Look outside the window
If the branches swing gently in the wind
then the one you love is loving you, too
Right now it's snowing outside
When it first snows
they say you should stroll with your beloved
But I'm just writing a letter
Joon-ha, I miss you so much
I'm going to get permission to go to Grandpa's house
If I do
I'll send you a telegraph
Open your ears
If you hear your heartbeat
then the person you love is loving you, too
Close your eyes
If there's a smile on your lips
then the person you love is loving you, too
I want to send a telegraph
Then please sign up here
Okay
But fate must not be on my side
One of my letters
was returned back to Tae-soo's home
Joo-hee is in love with Joon-ha
I'm not in love with Joo-hee
Both of them really love each other
So that's why I gave up
Two people in love should be together
It's okay with me
No, I love her, too
I won't give up
Are you mocking me?
You always want things your way!
So your parents mean nothing to you?
Do you know who she is?
She's a congressman's daughter!
Know what that means, you punk?
You deserve to die
You can't even hold on to a girl
It was the end of a winter break?
I had hoped so much for
Know what this is?
A belt?
No, it's a whip
This bastard hits me
My dad doesn't want it to
but it keeps wanting to hit me
That's why I caught it
How should I punish it?
The death penalty
That's exactly what I thought
Kill it slowly and painfully?
Or starve it slowly to death?
Or give it sleeping pills?
Strangle it to death
Good idea
Joon-ha
Take good care of Joo-hee
Tae-soo!
Somebody help!
A person's dying!
Tae-soo, you bastard!
Tae-soo, hold on! Hold on!
Someone help me!
Somebody's dying!
Tae-soo! Tae-soo!
I told you to kill the belt
not yourself
Tae-soo, wake up!
Open your eyes!
Don't die. Don't die
Don't die, you bastard!
Breathe! Breathe!
Breathe, you bastard!
Go inside
If you're with him
he'll wake up faster
Hurry
Wait here for me
Hurry and get well
Ji-hae, know what this is?
An umbrella?
A very special umbrella
They're all the same
It's special because Sang-min gave it to me
He must know that I like him
Thought he wouldn't
when you stare at him everyday?
Go give this to Sang-min
No, you give it to him
I'm not going there
Why not?
Did you and Soo-gyung fight?
Remember when it suddenly rained that day?
Sang-min was drinking coffee here
He was looking out of the window
then suddenly turned to me and said
"Did you bring an umbrella?"
And then I said
"I was worried I didn't"
He placed his umbrella here
and said
"You can have it"
He said he was okay to get wet
And then he ran off in the rain
Did you bring an umbrella?
You can have it.
It's raining a lot outside
Sang-min might be getting soaked without an umbrella
This is a really special umbrella
I'll give it back to him
Did you bring an umbrella?
Of course, I did
Really?
But still, take mine
Is she crazy?
You have an umbrella
but why are you so soaked?
It's not mine
I came to return it to you
You left it at the store
I'm not the only one
who gets wet even with an umbrella, am I?
Don't go
You already know...
my feelings
Now, you know it all
Yeah
when I saw you run without an umbrella
I left my umbrella behind
Even on the day of the play
I wanted to give you a present
so I bought Soo-gyung's, too
And if fate was on my side
I thought you'd pick the gift with the card in it
I thought we'd grow distant
if I confessed my feelings
I wanted to say that I liked you,
but I couldn't
I'll come see the play
Look
I cut my wrists
I saw it all
Both of you whispering love
Do you really love her?
Is it really so?
I'm working out my feelings
My eyes were looking straight
but my heart was confused
Can I trust those words?
Can I think of it as a promise?
Yes
There's only one that I love
That one is me, right?
Yes, I love you
I swear that I love you
I love you, too
Sang-min
I love you so much
Sang-min!
What the hell are you doing?
I didn't even finish my lines
and then you call out my name?
You can't just change your lines like that
You ruined everything!
Sang-min, I wasn't acting
it was my true feelings
I love you
Love is more important than a play
After the play Sang-min and I went on a date
We decided to go to the river
where my mother's memories lay
Joo-hee?
No, I'm her daughter
My name is Ji-hae
Is that so?
I must've made a mistake
But you look so much like your mom
I delivered a lot of your mom's letters
Thank you, sir
I know well what happened to my parents afterwards
Students and citizens!
This is illegal demonstrations!
Eliminate corruption and establish a new state!
A new state!
Down with dictatorship and the military regime!
Down with the regime!
Down with dictatorship!
If you wipe on toothpaste
your eyes will hurt less
- Joo-hee?
- Tae-soo?
Put on toothpaste
It's been a long time
It has
Have you heard from Joon-ha?
Joon-ha!
Joon-ha
come back alive!
Joon-ah!
You have to come back alive!
Joon-ha!
Joon-ha
answer me!
Joon-ha!
Joon-ha...
come back alive!
Joon-ha
Joon-ha!
Joo-hee!
- Joon-ha!
- Joo-hee!
Tae-soo!
Joon-ha!
You have to come back alive!
Joon-ha
come back alive!
You have to come back alive!
Got it?
Medic! Medic!
Hold on! Hold on!
Breathe! Breathe!
Stop it!
He's dead! Retreat!
Get moving, you bastard!
Joon-ha, you bastard!
Where are you going?
Come back!
Corporal OH!
You haven't changed at all
Just like in the past
you're still pretty
I've aged a lot
- You had it hard, huh?
- Not really
How's Tae-soo doing?
I guess he's doing alright
Why didn't you get married?
Well, I did
I heard
I had so much to tell you
But now that we've met
I can't remember
It's a piano doll
We have one at my home, too
When I look at it
it reminds me of you playing the piano
It looks so much like you back then
Doesn't it?
We were so innocent back then
But the past has gone now
I think our feelings took the best of us
We cried and laughed at the smallest things
How do I look right now?
You look healthy
But I'd like to see you look happier
I'm crying right now
Can't you see my tears?
Why did you hide that you couldn't see?
It's late
Sorry, I have an appointment
I have to go
I'm sorry
It was almost perfect
I could've succeeded
I even came here last night to practice
You almost fooled me
You did a good job
I nearly believed you
Also...
I risked my life to return this necklace to you
Please don't
This necklace is yours
Afterwards, mom and dad got married
And I was born three years later
Then a few years later...
Mrs. Sung Joo-hee?
Joon-ha's last wish
was for you to spread his dust in this river
Actually
Joon-ha
got married right after you did
Poor guy had a son, too
And Joon-ha
wanted you to have this
Mommy, it's a rainbow
I still remember clearly the rainbow I saw that day
Until I finished telling this story
Open your hands