Out of office,
leave your message.
Hi, Bob,
it's Eden Moore calling you.
I was just wondering
what happened the other day.
You just rushed outta here...
Mmpf...
E... Eden, Eden!
- Hey.
- Hi.
What happened to you?
Listen, I'm... I'm...
I'm so so sorry...
for disappearing
on you like that, uh...
You know what, uh...
an alarm went off...
and the security
had everything blocked, so...
I was...
I was stuck for there for hours.
- Uhum.
- No, no, really.
I mean, I've been desperate
to call you, I...
I've been meaning to call you.
Alright, well...
I'll let you make it up to me.
Take me to lunch.
What?
Yeah, you can come in with
a better story by then.
Y... Y... You wanna go to
the cafeteria?
No, I thought we could eat out.
Eat out?
Yeah.
You don't want to?
No, no, no...
I'd love to!
Okay, great.
Uh... how about
café 'Dos Mundos', you know?
Yes...
Of course, uh... wow!
Café Dos Mundos.
Is that a problem?
No, no problem at all.
Okay, great.
I'll see you tomorrow at noon.
Alright, see you then.
- Bye.
Welcome to TransWorld.
Today it's 21 degrees,
a beautiful and sunny day in TransCity.
TransWorld wishes you a very lovely day.
TransOil, energy for a better life.
We're building your future.
- Hey.
- Hi.
How are you?
Good.
I'm so sorry I'm late.
Oh, don't worry about it,
I just got here.
Oh, you did? Oh, good.
So, how come I've never seen you
around TransWorld before?
Well, I mean it's a...
it's a pretty big company.
I don't know, maybe that's why.
Do you live nearby?
Me? No, no, uh...
I... I have a really long commute.
You know, I'm sorry...
Y... You really don't remember me?
I mean, if you... if you look at me,
like... I mean, really...
really look at me...
You don't remember me at all?
Come on, Eden...
Eden, we know each other.
- What?
- No, no, wait...
We really know each other,
I mean...
Why are you doing this to me?
What?
No, Eden...
Eden, please...
Damn...
Eden, wait!
Wait, wait, wait...
Come on, sorry...
Please, please, don't...
It's just a misunderstanding.
I just meant that we met before.
You know, it was at the elevator...
at work...
You dropped your papers and
I helped you pick 'em up.
- You don't remember that?
- No, I don't.
Yeah, why...
why would you, I guess.
Look, I... I'm sorry...
I'm confused, a little nervous,
that's all.
You know, I didn't mean
to come at you like that.
I'm really sorry.
Can you forgive me?
Look...
I should get back to work,
I think.
Come on,
just stay for one drink.
You can't stay for one drink?
We don't even have to eat.
You know, uh...
I'm not even hungry.
U... Unless, of course, you're hungry...
in which case I'm... I'm...
I'm starving.
Yeah, I mean, I'll eat
the whole menu... tw... twice!...
...if... if... if you sit down
and have one drink.
- I'm starving, actually.
- Yeah? Great.
Wanna sit down?
Isn't this upside down?
I will teach you how to
drink that stuff, really.
So...
- How am I supposed to do it?
- You have to...
- ...and you hold it like this...
- Okay.
Tilt it down.
What?
- How could I know?
- For a year?
- Exactly.
- Let's do it again.
- A year.
- These are good.
- Yeah.
- They're good.
- Yeah, take it easy.
Alright. Strong...
Hey, you know,
I wanna show you something.
Sure.
Uhm... it's a personal project
of mine, but...
I wanna do it at a much larger scale...
but I find your invention
could come in handy.
Wow, that's...
That's amazing, really.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
It's amazing, I mean...
I'd love to help.
Yeah.
That's the...
Sage Mountains, right?
Yeah.
I, uh...
I grew up there.
We still have our old house there.
Yeah, I know. We used to
go out there all the time.
You know, we still, uh...
come and pick the pomegranates.
Yeah, me too.
- They're the best!
- They're the best.
You're okay?
Uh? Yeah.
No, I'm good.
- I'm fine, no, really.
- Mmh.
It's getting, a little warm
in here, don't you think?
Let's get outta here.
- You wanna go?
- Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
We get the check?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
So there's this great orchestra
from down below.
Uh, ...they play here
Friday nights.
They're incredible,
you have to hear it.
Wow, that sounds great.
Okay, so see Friday maybe?
- Yeah, su... sure.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Thanks for lunch.
- Alright, take care.
Thanks.
Eden.
Eden it's me.
Our demonstrator will
apply the full product live.
We'll be selling five separate creams
...of increasing strengths
...according to the concentration
of the active ingredient,
...five being the most potent.
The goal is to tailor the lift
...to the condition of
various facial regions.
And as you see,
a range of strengths
...allows the consumer to apply
what's needed where needed.
For a general purpose product
I think the level two
...provide visible
all-round improvement
...without adverse effects.
Number five, being strongest,
can work miracles.
And speaking of miracles,
...now we're also developing a product
for the breasts and the buttocks.
Oh, I think it's ready!
Bravo! Bravo!
- Any questions before we continue?
- Yes.
Couldn't we market a cheaper
version for down below...
...with only one product?
Oh, yes, we could...
...at the very
lightest concentration.
The product doesn't hold up well
at very high doses.
Uhm, let's see what happens
with excessive application.
She had a product applied
about ten minutes ago, so...
I have a question to the demonstrator.
Mr. Boruchowitz, right?
Uhm...
I'm sorry, you must have
me confused with somebody else.
My name's Adam.
Adam Kirk.
Excuse me,
I'm looking for Eden Moore.
Have you seen her?
Yeah, she just left.
No, no!
Damn it!
Hey, stop!
Security please...
TransWorld.
For a better, brighter tomorrow.
That's him!
Gravity.
A revolution about to begin.
New from TransCosmetics.
Uplift yourself today!
Hey!
What are you doing here?
I'm looking for my dog.
What's your name?
I can't talk to you.
Why not?
You're from down below.
I'm Adam.
You son of a gun!
I knew you're up to something.
Bob, can I come in?
'Course, that's what I'm here for.
Come on, come on.
Right, right, well,...
I made it maximum weight
...to the exterior layer
to cover the heating problem.
Now, my friend,
try this for size.
If it fits, you are through
with overheating.
This is nice...
Whoa, wow, this is nice.
Oh, boy, oh, boy.
TransWorld are gonna curse the day
they fired me.
You got it?
That's a pretty good fit.
Good, good, right.
Well, I will get back
to the outer layer...
The icing on the cake!
I don't get it.
It's impossible to change
gravity status.
Are you sure?
Yeah, absolutely.
Look, all we have to do...
...is carefully...
...mix the two opposing solutions...
...and wait a second to
stabilize gravity...
...and then...
Voilà!
No...
God!
That is better than
a good idea, my friend.
That is...
...revolutionary!
But don't they have the formula now?
No.
No, I gave 'em everything
but the main ingredient.
Ah, hooo!
I would give good money...
...just to see the look on
Lagavullan's face right now!
So, are you telling me
we don't have the formula?
We...
Well, we tried to
recreate it several times.
But the thing is,
we're missing an ingredient, uh...
Pink powder.
We found traces in his office.
Without it there is no cream.
That's unacceptable!
You can't figure out without him?
No.
You remember?
I'm starting to.
Border Police!
Everybody up against the wall!
Now, this way, please.
Damn it!
Listen, I gotta go.
No!
- Identification!
- I'll find you!
Hey, you!
Hey!
Come back here!
Hey, stop!
Stop!
Breaking news coming in live.
Border Police have launched a
massive manhunt for a fugitive
...who just escaped from
the café Dos Mundos.
All national law enforcement
agencies have been alerted
...and we'll keep you updated
as the story develops.
Come on, let's go.
Wait, wait, wait...
What?
I... I... I just thought
I heard something.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Go, go, go, go!
Hey, you! Stop!
Eden, come on!
Come on, come on, come on!
Go, go, go!
Eden, the waist!
- Take on my waist!
- Okay!
Come on!
Eden, take this arm!
Hold on!
Hold on, hold on!
Eden, hold on!
Hold on!
I'm holding you!
Don't let go!
Hold on, hold on!
- Let go off me, please.
- No!
No!
I'm so sorry.
- I'm so sorry.
- No!
The guy fell.
No, no, wait!
Don't do this to me! Ugh!
No, no!
- Oh, please, no!
- Get in the car!
Ahh, no!
Don't do this to me!
Here's the deal...
You give us the complete
anti-aging cream formula
...and if you attempt to
contact Ms. Moore
...charges against her
will be reinstated.
Do I make myself clear,
Mr. Kirk?
So that's it.
They won.
And I lost.
- I just lost everything.
They took aunt Becky
and they took Eden from me.
Oh, it's hard to accept that I will
never see Eden again.
I was naive to think that
I can change the world.
You know, up there,
...they always win.
And down here...
Well, we always lose.
So I guess I just
go back to my life...
...to my world.
But I will never...
...ever...
...forget her.
Gently does it...
Victory!
So, is it true
everyone's rich up top?
Don't you know,
it's total paradise up there!
Paradise?
Well, guys, I...
I don't think so, you know.
Th... they might be
rich, sure, but...
...it's definitely not paradise.
Hey let me look at that, huh?
What do you think, we should,
uh, think we should make this fly?
Yeah.
Oh yeah, we'll give it a boost?
Alright, hold on a bit.
Alright, now try.
Go on, throw it.
Hey, Eden, it's Paula.
Are you still sick?
You haven't shown up
for four days.
Did you get those strange
flowers we sent over?
I think they come from floor zero.
Let me know, okay?
I hope you're alright.
Bye.
Bob?
Boruchowitz?
Yeah?
I'm Eden.
Moore.
I need your help.
Yeah! Fantastic!
Bob... Bob!
What?
You think you're the only one
who can go upside down?
You won't get rid of me!
Easy as that, old buddy!
How did you make this?
I mean, how...
how did you do it?
Hey, hey, hey...
Check this out!
Did you make a vest or what?
I can't believe it!
Oh, oh!
Put me down, sweetie!
You're not even wearing a vest!
- No, no...
- Where's the weights?
No, no, no... We're 90%
water, right?
So I combine
upper and lower inversion...
with a hyper... infusion, yeah?
Now, you know this better than I do.
But, but the breakthrough, man,...
the... the breakthrough, ahh...
Ahh, man, I'm jabbering...
The pro...
The problem is, right,...
The effect only lasts an hour,
right? I'll improve it.
Oh... you, you my friend...
Hey, you...
you have a rendezvous.
What's this?
"CAFE DOS MUNDOS"
You better not go dressed like that.
Hey, did you tell him?
Hey, another thing...!
The cream...
Well, thanks to your stamps
...I bought the patent
under the name 'Albert & Co.'
...before...
TransWorld.
Nice! Nice!
Adam!
Eden!
I can't believe it!
How did you get down here?
Bob found a way
to bring me down.
I can't believe it.
I... I... I don't know
what happened to you?
Are you okay?
I'm pregnant.
We're having twins.
I can't believe it!
How long can you
stay down here for?
Forever, maybe.
Bob said
it's because I'm pregnant.
He said you'd understand
...how this makes me different.
I love you.
We didn't realize yet the
repercussions of what we had done.
Our love would forever
alter the course of history.
But that's another story...