Your father must be teaching
you more than just sashimi
This kind of energy
doesn´t suit you anyway
Luckily,
your teacher likes sushi
Tell your father,
he doesn´t have to
come to school anymore
This teacher will share
your pain to the end
So this is what they mean by
tattered vital links
Whoever did this
had amazing technique
here´s no way
I can treat this
It was better when
there was no one to treat
Hey you!
You´re just muddying
the lake, catching no fish
The fish has transformed into a
dragon, ascended to the heavens
Expulsion is no fun
If you trash them because they´re
garbage, what will the world be like?
Expulsion,
Expulsion´s no fun?
That´s what incompetent
teachers with
nothing to teach
like to do
An "End-of-life certificate"?
Isn´t it hot?
Do you think they´re okay?
Don´t worry Surely they
won´t kill each other
Let´s get down to it
If I were at school,
I´d have blocked your vital
links before anyone else
Don´t worry!
It´s not your concern anymore
If you finish,
I just go
Kyung´- soo!
Your tattered links become
more and more painful
If that´s my destiny,
I´ll deal with it
Then let´s see how well
you deal with it
Leave me alone
If you don´t like it,
defeat me
Strength
It´s knowing how to gather the
energy around you, make it yours
Awakening, It is the wisdom
to merge you and your opponent
Get out of me!
Honor
Honor is---giving yourself up
Honor No opponent, no self
your vital links doesn´t
mean strengthened spiritual energy
From now on, it´s up to you
Don´t drag me into your fight
Kyung´- soo
Stop running away
Just you defy your destiny
doesn´t mean it´ll pass you by
From now on, you´re the best
Man!
Are we maids or students?
Why do they make us
clean all the time?
Hey!
I´m sorry
I don´t want to get
involved in your fight
It´s five now
but later it´ll be ten
This fight is meaningless
You have nothing to
worry about
You can run away again
"Boys, Girls"
Chae´- yi!
What are you doing?
Set your heart free,
like the flowing water
KIM Kyung´- soo,
you got a damn good friend
Yin´- Yang Conflux
Become water and flow
Yin´- Yang Repel
Thunder and lightning strike
Water and lightening are one
in nature
Oh, I´m thirsty
Tell me again
Did you see them?
Someone locked
Kyung´- soo
and Chae´- yi in the shower
If it´s a lie,
I´ll kill you myself
This would make a good
training hall for the teachers
I don´t like it
I guess these boys are men too
Their male stench is everywhere
Get up
It´s a complete pig sty
What´s this smell?
- did someone pee in here?
- Enough!
This is not a place for teachers
The Vice Principal has banned
all extra´- curricular activities
Vice Principal?
Then there must be
a mistake
He can´t do this to me
I´m JANG Ryang
Ryang or Jang,
I don´t care
School´s no place
for this nonsense
It seems
excessive to ban
their club activities
Is it true you´re getting rid of
the weightlifting team?
What is this?
I´m sorry
Of course, I knew it
The new teachers are
going overboard
I thought they were under
you so I stayed back
But no more
How the hell do you
manage things
that you let a student
come in here?
See?
This is all because of
incompetent teachers like you
- do you understand?
- Vice Principal
it´s me, JANG Ryang
JANG Ryang
Right
I know your name
If you have difficulties
at school,
you should see the Dean
Why are you coming to me?
From now on,
you´re Student Dean,
Mr. MA, Reason with
this student
Dal´- chun may be dumb
but he´s strong
Get out
Silence!
You have all suffered
I, JANG Ryang,
with generosity as wide as
a lake, have tolerated it till now
I´m pushing morals
aside and flexing my muscles
Today, I´ll lift 10,000 pounds
of iron as I´ve practiced
Ryang,
I have to go home soon
That was cool, huh?
I was gonna let it go
this once,
but no way
This is far enough
I´m Ryang,
JANG Ryang!
Ah, that felt really good
So you can completely empty
someone´s head in a flash?
Is it really possible?
That´s the frightening power
of wave energy
Go crazy in an instant,
then blank like a piece of paper
In an instant, clean---
Nice! Nice!
I want to test it at once
How timely, an animal
is caught in our trap
Do you recognize me, sir?
It´s Ryang, JANG Ryang
This is all Hak´- rim´s fault
If he wasn´t such a show´- off---
I´m sorry I´m really sorry, sir
To strengthen your character,
we´ve prepared
a fun class today
If your name´s
on the bulletin board,
report to the auditorium
Kyung´- soo!
Don´t be late
Listen,
do you hear the sound
of Volcano High being reborn?
JANG Oh´- ja,
I bet you don´t know why your
master left you an empty box
Right!
A big talker like you
wouldn´t know
What is education anyway?
You´re still as tacky as ever
I´ll slowly empty
your belly too
Last night, someone tried
to steal the Secret Manuscript
He conspired with Hak´- rim
against the principal
Luckily, he was
caught at the scene
The Manuscript shouldn´t
be hidden anymore
So I made a big
decision today
My dear---
Volcano students
Finally,
you will see the Manuscript
Now watch carefully
See what happens to the
student who lusts after it
That´s right, empty your mind!
All of it!
Empty your head and get ready
to receive new education!
Empty the idle thoughts,
rebellion, and silly desires!
Empty, empty, your mind!
This is the great teaching
of the Secret Manuscript!
Now the new history
of education
begins under
the name of Volcano High!
New, new, new---
The unprecedented technique
of the Secret Manuscript
will clear people´s heads of
worthless thoughts and garbage
Now you will begin again
Be reborn
Please stop now
I can´t hold back any longer
Impatient
Still, it´s not your turn yet
Now you know your turn
without being called
- Is this strengthening our
character?/- Sure!
It´s the class
you need most
Stop right there
Ryang needs to
go to the nurse
Someone fixed you up,
what a worthless thing to do
Ryang needs to
go to the nurse
Come and get
permission first
It´s because of brats like you
that there is chaos
Idiot, wake up
Stop it
This is my problem
Don´t act like a big shot
I´m Ryang, JANG Ryang!
I repay my own debts
It´s most rewarding
teaching someone like you
Trash
Your arrogant attitudes
are all same
Let´s end it here
Better than to live like trash
I won´t run away any more
Your life is over now
Mr. MA! Mr. MA!
You shouldn´t toy with
words like "death"
Stay away! Mr. MA!
Stay away! Stay away!
Stay away! Stay away---
Like one sun in the sky,
two cannot be most
revered at Volcano High
Let´s have a true fight today
I thought we ended
that discussion
Endurance Determination
I, JANG Ryang,
am not dead yet
I´m busy
Let´s get to the point
Mr. Vice Principal---
As time passed, I couldn´t help
my curiosity about the box
Then one day---
Hey! Listen!
I´m not done yet
Everyone knows it was
empty from the beginning
Oh - it´s a fake
You brats This is the real thing
The Secret Manuscript II
Vandalism Assault of male students
Assault of the Student Dean---
What classroom is
KIM Kyung- soo in?
Why write letters
you´ll never send?
Love is not about showing
It´s about feeling
Just 200 more to
get to a thousand letters