Presented by JR PICTURES
Ik-soo Express
Jeon Gwang-ryul
Jeong Woong-in
Kim Rae-won
Soh Yu-jin
Ye Ji-won
Ju Hyun
Son of a bitch!
Motherfucker!
Directed by Lee Yeon-woo
Chop him up
and feed him to the pigs.
How will you pull it off?
I've got an idea.
What if you get busted?
I'm counting on you, Tae-ho.
If you screw up...
Got it?
His name is Park Tae-ho.
A right-hand man of Gang Yong-gu,
one of Kunsa's drug distributors.
He's moving abroad soon.
He never runs the light.
He participates
in all the civil defense drills.
He never misses
the residents meetings.
Who are you?
I'm D.A. Choi Doo-chil.
Put me on the case.
At 03:30 in April 28th, 1980
A drug cartel called 'Dinosaurs'
was exposed to the world.
So was Gang Yong-gu.
An officer got killed on the job.
He was my father.
He made me an orphan,
and he's got to pay for it.
Give me the case
and I'll bring his ass down.
You sure?
It's my dad's memorial day today,
and he's going down.
We've got to bust him
before he gets on the plane.
Move out!
The operation name is 2424!
Give me some ideas.
I heard the mafia puts them
in the asshole.
Yeah, I heard that, too.
They carry grenades in the asshole
for an unexpected war.
- Wow, grenades!
- They take them out, and...
Put it in your asshole.
Go ahead.
You're joking, aren't you?
Come on, put it in your asshole!
- Hold him down!
- Okay.
No!
Watch it!
Jerk it in!
Don't squeeze it!
You should feel honored, man.
It's a lot smaller than a grenade.
I guess they've got bigger assholes.
They ain't the Mob for nothing.
What about eating it?
Hide them in the stomach?
That's good!
- Anybody can do that.
- Right!
You eat it.
What?
Try this one first.
- Come on!
- Hold his neck.
Hide them
in the jar of pepper paste?
I've never thought of that!
And your head is a lot bigger, huh?
- What time are movers coming?
- Should be here in no time.
I should get ready then.
- Tae-ho.
- Yes?
- Can I have some tea?
- Sure.
Come on.
Not you.
It tastes better when you make it.
Tae-ho.
We're really moving
abroad together?
Of course!
I'm a man of my words, girl.
No kidding!
I've already reserved plane tickets.
What do you want to do there?
Let's have a baby first.
You're my prince charming, Tae-ho.
- You're like a sex machine.
- Yeah, baby!
Good evening, boss.
Who's that bitch?
She's hot.
Is she yours?
No, I've never seen her before.
I can tell by looking into her eyes.
She's a horny girl.
That's right!
I called her in for you, boss.
You did?
You always look after me.
That's why I like you.
Pour me a shot.
Tae-ho!
Do I know you?
How did you know my name?
She must be high or something.
I'll leave you two alone, sir.
Okay.
Your skin is as soft as silk.
- Oh, you're here.
- Hi.
You've got a lot of stuff.
Our first motto, we carry the
hearts of our customers.
We do!
Another motto, we protect boxes
like we do our bodies.
We surely do!
And our last motto, we carry
dreams and hopes of our customers.
- We do!
- Let's get started.
This is it, boys.
Let's go!
Are you the one I talked to?
Oh, I am...
Let me carry that for you.
What a great place!
That was just an assessor.
This is our manager.
I'll make sure nothing goes wrong.
- Hurry, please.
- Sure.
- One more thing.
- Yes?
Uninstalling air-conditioner is free,
right?
Yes, of course!
- You know how to do it?
- Well...
Cut the chitchat, will you?
I think it would be wise of you to
call an expert for that.
Why don't you do it yourself?
I'll double your pay.
Yes, sir.
It's over there.
It hurts like hell, man.
I almost threw up.
He's fucking out of his mind.
We always separate paintings
from the frames.
Mom? Yeah, I'm kind of busy.
Yeah, I did. How about you?
Fuck!
Dectec... Dokgo!
Give me a hand here.
I'm doing this for the country.
So, help me out.
What are you doing?
Principle 1 of movers,
Never take what's not yours!
You think it's funny?
Don't forget you're on probation.
You don't want to mess up.
- I'll buy you some later.
- Okay.
Come on, back to work.
What have you found?
Nothing.
What are you doing?
Got a pair of socks to spare?
Is this the last one?
What's this?
We've got a ladder truck coming.
Have them move their cars.
- They want you to move the car.
- Tell them to wait.
- Why should I?
- I'm trying to study here!
What's the problem?
What are you doing down there?
What?
Don't you have a job to do?
What? I can't hear you!
Did you hear what he said?
Are we moving anytime today?
We've got a parking problem here.
I see.
Boys, help them move the cars.
Let's go.
Who is it?
- Move the car, please.
- I can't now.
- Come on, move it.
- No way!
Why the hell not?
Hey, get over here.
She says she won't move the car.
What a bitch!
Honey, move the car now!
I'm a Sunday driver.
Can you do it for me?
You bet.
Park Tae-ho is on the phone.
Trace the call.
Don't worry about a thing, boss.
I'll be over within the hour.
- Let me tell you...
- Hello?
What's up with the phone?
I told the phone company
to disconnect it.
We've got nothing so far.
Okay, sir.
He didn't stay on the phone
for more than 10 seconds.
We can't afford to let him walk!
10 minutes of a chicken torture
will make him talk.
Put electric wires on his ears,
fingers, toes, and his dick.
Give him a little electric shock,
and he'll talk.
No way.
We've got nothing on him.
We can't find anything here.
Let's finish up here and move
to the 2nd post.
- You don't trust my instincts?
- No.
We're running out of time.
Okay, let's hurry packing up
and move to the 2nd post.
God!
Aren't they from Hanjin Express?
What the...!
Hey, Hanjin!
You threw milk earlier, didn't you?
Move the truck, fuckface.
Never seen him before.
What milk?
Who the fuck are you?
Can't you see?
We're movers like yourself!
What is this?
And watch your mouth!
Beat it, kids.
Or what?
Should I arrest them?
We don't have time for this.
Move the boxes.
What are you, clowns?
You don't listen, do you?
Some beatings will make you
get out of here?
My name is Han Ik-soo.
Don't mess with me.
Tell your manager!
- Did you just hit me?
- Are you out of your minds?!
You want it, too?
Move your truck.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Who the fuck are you?
We were working our asses off,
and they started beating us.
What'd to do to them?
Sons of bitches!
What a bunch of losers!
You're dead meat, fuckers.
- Let's rock and roll!
- Yeah!
I'm in a great mood today.
So, don't make me hurt you boys.
Fuck!
Let's go.
Are you okay?
He's bluffing, you know.
He's nothing but a suit.
No match for you.
It's our 1st day in the business.
Don't mind them.
Fuckers!
- Excuse me.
- Huh?
Get me a carton of cigarettes.
Huh?
Don't tell me you don't know
what cigarettes are.
- It's okay. Keep the change.
- Okay.
What's up with his eyebrow?
You wait here,
I have something to do
Jars are made by the most famous
potter in Korea.
If you buy our soybean paste,
you get the jar for free.
Who are you?
It's so upsetting!
What?
I leave the company, and they
hire a beautiful girl like you?
Give it here.
These expensive goods require
a special packaging...
I see.
Hold on.
You don't only box up things,
but also the customers' hearts.
Honey, isn't that our truck?
What are they doing?
Stop the car.
Don't you have a job to do?
God!
- No place to park the truck.
- What?
They give out jars for free.
That old man...
He died in our neighborhood
last week.
Hey, you're here.
Why aren't you working?
They haven't moved out yet.
Go ahead. We'll be right up.
Ik-soo Express, hello?
Where the hell are you?
We're waiting for the ladder truck.
What?
Hello?
Yes?
You... Gwang-ja?
Young-joo?
Young-joo!
- It's been 10 years.
- Right.
You got your nose job done?
I didn't recognize you at first.
- You're married.
- How did you know?
Your ass is kind of saggy.
Raising kids fucked up my body.
You look so great.
I'm moving abroad today.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Good for you!
Your dream has come true!
Where? USA?
Australia?
Brazil.
Brazil?
Isn't it too hot there?
A little bit, I hear.
Yu-mi!
Your husband?
- I'll talk to you later.
- Okay.
I hear you're moving to Brazil.
Take a good care of her.
What?
Is that your real name, Gwang-ja?
Who the hell is that?
Excuse me.
Give me a buzz.
Here's your change.
Who is it?
Cigarettes.
I got your cigarettes.
Here you go.
He only smokes Salem.
Can't you smoke these?
These are too strong for him.
And smell yucky.
Salem...!
Dig it?
Go trade them in for Salem.
Okay. I'll get you Salem.
dad!
I can't believe I'm moving into
the apartment you lived in!
Tell me about it.
- Send me a postcard.
- You bet.
Take care, girl.
- Where's your husband?
- At the airport.
Bye.
Be well!
Wait! Wait!
What a fool.
Are we moving anytime today?
They're already gone!
We're right on it, Ma'am!
You guys go ahead.
It's you again!
Is this a karma or what?
We keep running into each other.
- Leaving now?
- Right.
How sad!
Hey, hang on a second.
Give me a call!
Criminal psychology comes in handy
in understanding criminals.
I didn't just run an errand
for nothing.
I found out that Park Tae-ho
only smokes Salem.
...which is a great discovery.
- Let us use your ladder truck.
- Get up now!
- We've got no business with you.
- We need a ladder truck!
What a nutcase!
- Nutcase?
- Out of the way!
Hell no!
I'm not fucking moving!
Let me give you some advice
as your superior.
Stay away from that asshole.
Why?
He's a criminal type.
You don't think you are?
This is why you're so green.
Didn't you see what he did?
Nobody does this any more.
Funny, huh?
What happened?
What?
Your eyebrow.
This is just...
You look like a criminal.
You have a crunch on me?
He only smokes Salem!
Wagon 1, where are you?
Shut the fuck up!
Okay, here we go.
This is our game plan.
They'll turn left at the intersection.
Our agent will change the light
after they turn left.
Where is he?
Wagon 5, where the hell are you?
Fuck!
Come on!
Why aren't you going?
What are you, sightseeing?
Roll it down!
Open it!
Wagon 5!
What's going on here?
Follow his car. Stay close.
Just as we planned!
Get the forensic guys ready.
Stop!
Let's get started.
Hello?
Moving in today?
Hi, there.
May I help you?
I'm from Seoul Newspaper.
Welcome to this town
I've brought some trash bags
to help you clean the place.
Let me help you with the trash.
It's so beautiful house!
This pepper paste has gone bad.
- Pepper paste?
- Let me throw this out.
Hi, I'm from daehan Newspaper.
I've brought a broom and dustpan
to help clean the place.
Hello?
I'm from Donghae Newspaper.
What's wrong with you people?
I got here first, so get out!
Nonsense!
Our paper is better than yours.
Is this the attitude of journalists?
Journalists my ass!
Stop the nonsense,
and get your hand off me!
Jesus Christ!
- Look who's here!
- Wait, wait!
Get over here!
I told you I didn't want
your paper, didn't I?
You haven't paid the bill, sir.
Doo-chill, what did he take
from the den?
From the den...
Shotgun and
a Japanese sword, sir.
From the master bedroom?
Some personal belongings
of Cho Gwang-ja.
Right.
What about the living room?
Living room?
What the hell were you doing?
You don't know shit!
I think that jar...
What about it?
- This big and...
- Shut up!
Once he gets on the plane,
that's it!
Call the airport security
to hold him up.
- What took you so long?
- Sorry, boss.
- Did you bring it?
- Sure.
Let me see.
What is this?
Get down!
You hear this?
Tae-ho...
Remember what I said I'd do
if you mess up?
You'll be seeing the pig farm.
What is this?
Nothing but soybean paste?
That's right, sir...
It's 100% % Korean soybean paste.
Shit!
Thought it was too easy.
Park Tae-ho fucked us up.
Gang Yong-gu,
Park Tae-ho...
You guys are fucked.
Do you have any idea
how badly I waited
for this moment?
Worthless scumbags!
The ghost of my late father
will see the arrest
warrant for you.
You wanted to
smoke, didn't you?
Smoke them all!
You think it's funny?
Let go!
- Let's go.
- Off of me!
You'll never see the sunlight again!
What happened to his eyebrow?
What do you think You're doing?
We've got nothing on them.
Sorry, sir.
Sir!
Put electric wires on
their armpits, fingers,
toes, and dicks
They'll start talking.
What the hell's
wrong with you?
I should've seen this coming
when you mentioned the jar.
How did you even
become a D.A.?
You sure about that?
Nothing but soybean paste?
See it for yourself!
Why did they run
with this then?
We've been playing into
the hands of Park Tae-ho.
Let them go and
put men on them.
And you're off the case.
Sir!
You're no good on the field.
Get it out of here.
It smells!
You messed with
the wrong guy.
Do you know who I am?
No way!
You can't run from me!
I don't want much from you.
Let me hear you say you're sorry.
Apologize!
Apologize for what?
Who the fuck are you?!
hey! Fake eyebrow!
Kings have knights.
Generals have soldiers.
And singers have fans.
Then, whom do I have?
I have you!
You knew it, didn't you?
You were so brilliant.
You knew they were on us.
That's why you used
the jar as a decoy.
Of course!
Where are diamonds then?
Go to Incheon port, boss.
We're taking a boat?
I've never seen anyone smarter!
Okay, I'll meet you there.
Bring the stuff.
What about me?
What?
You're not taking me?
Of course not.
We never meant to take you.
She's completely lost, man.
I've lived for this moment.
No way I'm off the case.
Your eyebrow is running.
- Thanks for earlier.
- Huh?
That crazy bastard.
Oh, that four-eyed freak.
How do I open it?
Use this.
Now I know how you
feel about me.
What are you talking about?
I was just...
I know it's hard but
don't let your personal
feelings get in the way.
You're so unbelievable.
- Are you always like this?
- Enough.
We'll talk later.
Sir!
By the way,
do you like eclairs?
What?!
You knew all along, didn't you?
He meant to ditch me,
didn't he?
Tell me, jerk!
Keep it down.
Dirty bastards!
Gwang-ja... where's the jar?
You intercepted it, didn't you?
You worthless junkie!
Back to the apartment.
- Got all the stuff up?
- Right.
You want some eclairs?
Right now?
- You had lunch earlier.
- I'm still hungry.
How's it going?
Who's this?
It's the same asshole!
Stop it!
How many jobs do
you have, man?
Obstruction of justice is
a serious criminal offense.
Is he nuts or what?
Pay up and leave.
There's nothing you do right.
Not only are you a bad mover,
but also a terrible baker!
It's all burnt!
I'll give you a different one.
I'm sure I'm a lot older.
So, show some respect.
Is that right?
How old are you?
I've had it with you people.
Get out of here!
You're asking for it, man.
Do you have any
idea who I am?
Of course we do.
A peddler without eyebrow!
Look.
Now beat it.
Sorry. We didn't know.
Did you expect this?
You thought we would fall
for a fake badge?
He's stupider than I thought.
Get out of here
before I take you downtown.
He never listens, does he?
Let's rock and roll!
Stop it!
We've got bad news for you.
The master of pottery...
who was helping us...
passed away a moment ago
at the age of 95.
We've got only 100 jars left.
Get the last famous work of...
Isn't that Doo-chil?
What's he doing out here?
He's really good at poking
his nose where
it doesn't belong!
Dokgo, where are you?
- At the scene, sir.
- Get your ass over here!
- Master bedroom?
- Done!
- Other bedrooms?
- Kitchen?
- All done!
Very good!
You guys did a great job.
- Where's the lady?
- At the janitor's office.
We have to get this signed.
Had it not been for
those bastards, we
could've finished it earlier.
What the...!
What are they doing?
- Eclairs, please.
- Sure.
Dokgo, my hunch was right.
They're back.
I know.
How did you know?
Go back to the office.
The director is here.
I don't care.
I'm not going anywhere!
You take a walk.
It's getting too dangerous.
You're too young to die.
Noodles aren't good for you!
I won't give up
until you apologize!
I guess you're a man, too.
You want to do it?
Dream on, moron!
Don't even think about it.
- Let's call the cops.
- We should.
I can't believe this!
One, two, one, two...
On the spot!
- Attention! Salute!
- Taekwon!
Okay.
You're moving in, right?
Right.
I run a Taekwondo gym
across the street.
Send your kids to me.
The first month is free.
And Jazz dance, ballet...
Get out!
Sure.
Move out!
Who are you?
Want milk delivered?
Did it hurt?
Sorry. I wasn't myself.
Don't get me wrong.
I gave up on you for your safety.
Otherwise, I wouldn't
have done that.
As a matter of fact,
I've been waiting for today.
You trust me, don't you?
You think I'd be his pawn
for the rest of my life?
I don't like Brazil.
I don't know a word
of Portuguese.
If you take me back, we can...
What is it?
What was that for?!
Where is it?
I don't know
anything about a jar.
Get out.
Out!
Where did you hide it?
Where is it?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Gwang-ja...!
We picked a wrong
day to move.
Think of it as
a blessing in disguise.
When will you guys be done?
Give us 30 more minutes.
Shake a leg, boys!
Let's go get something to eat.
Too upset to eat!
We'll be back soon.
What's he doing here?
Lock the door!
Sir, from my experience...
What do you think you're doing?
Close it!
Judging from my experience...
- What experience?
- It must be inside the apartment.
But you've checked all the boxes.
And look at yourself!
Go back to the office.
Judging from my experience...
What experience?
This is your first field operation!
The evidence must be hidden
either in the wall or ceiling.
- What do you want from me?
- Put me back on the case.
No way!
I'm going in!
What the...
Go after him.
Tae-ho, isn't he that D.A.?
You want me to do him?
No, don't mind him.
Nothing can break our spirit.
Cheer up, guys.
Let's get back to work.
What are you doing here?
I'm a D.A. on a case.
Keep them out here.
Out of my way.
Get out!
I guess he's the real D.A.
- Don't go in!
- They're destroying everything!
What do you think
you're doing?
Who told you to come in?
Get out!
Get out of my sight
before I have you all arrested!
What did we do wrong?
Obstruction of justice,
blackmailing...
and assault!
You ruined my eyebrow.
You've trashed the place!
The damage will be paid for.
- The damage?!
- Out of my way.
damage my ass!
- God, you hit me again!
- Get up!
Knock it off!
Stop!!
So glad that you're here.
Arrest them!
What are you doing?
Cuff them!
Sir, that's enough.
Park Tae-ho was at #1001.
There's nothing here.
Nothing?
I see.
The damage will be paid for.
No matter how important it is,
you can't do this.
They moved here with dreams.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to say.
No words will fix it,
but I know it's not your fault.
I've got to go in to wrap it up.
Okay.
Wait!
Huh?
- Ik-soo, right?
- Right.
My name is Dokgo Jin.
- The cops are on our tail.
- What?!
- We can't take the boat.
- Then what?
'Jeju Island'
Why don't you go to Jeju Island?
Jeju?
And cruise over to Japan?
That's an idea.
Japan is better than Brazil.
Hello? What did you say?
- Can't you hear me? Hello?
- I'm losing you, boss.
Gosh, look at these!
Leave them on.
Everybody out!
Apt # 1205!
Gwang-ja, the sun will rise
tomorrow, too.
Park Tae-ho...
Will there be
tomorrow for you?
Push it again.
- Who's holding it!
- No fucking manners!
I hate stairs!
I won't let either cops or
gangsters get in our way.
They have no right to ruin
the lives of our customers!
I don't mind going back to prison.
What do you say?
What did you say?
How can you say that?
They messed with
the wrong girl.
Let's rock and roll.
Fuck!
motherfucker!
Buy the chest!
- Come on!
- My legs are shaky.
Who the fuck are you?
We're going to Apt # 1205.
- Hi there.
- You're already here?
Your friends look
very familiar.
Do I know you?
Hey, it's me from high school.
My nickname was 'Tin Can'
Tin Can?
Congratulations on
your marriage!
Where does your father-in-law
keep the jar of pepper paste?
- The jar of pepper paste?
- You fucking asshole!
You hired goons to take
the chest from us so
you can save money?!
Is your fiance
really a teacher?
Okay, sir.
Park Tae-ho has
retrieved the stuff.
- Where is he?
- 12th floor.
Let's go!
Park Tae-ho!
- They're here!
- Get them!
Hurry!
Come on, this way!
Dokgo, where are you?
We've lost Park Tae-ho!
We're fucked!
Where's Ik-soo?
Freeze!
- I'm an agent on the case.
- And I'm a mover.
Park Tae-ho!
Like father, like son!
I knew you'd nail him!
Get him out of here!
- I don't get it.
- What?
You should've
been a detective.
Aren't you cold?
- I'm okay.
- You're bleeding.
Come on, let me see.
Apologize!
I'm sorry.
You have my apology.
So sorry!
Father!
Refreshment, ma'am?
Juice, please.
How long does it take to Brazil?
27 hours with
a stopover in LA.
Ready?
Come on, over here.
Come here, guys.
Don't take it yet.
Let me hold you.
Everybody, squeeze in.
Here we go.
One, two, three... Cheese!
I don't just carry boxes,
but the hopes of our customers.
And we've added a new
member to our family.
Ik-soo Express