(WIND BLOWING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(NEWS REPORT PLAYING ON TV)
(GIRL GIGGLING)
No, no, no.
Don't food
the dog, darllng.
(GIRL GIGGLING)
(SIGHS)
CURTIS: Thanks, babe.
You slept late.
Yeah, I need to go.
What you got
golng today?
I've got to
ﬂnlah up some cultalna
for Saturday,
and Nat and Cam
are oomlng over.
Wlth the klda?
Yeah.
Cammie said she just needed
to get out ofthe house.
Tell Nat to take
It easy on her.
Cam can hold her own.
We need to
send In the deposlt
for the beach oondo.
I love you.
Just wrlte the check,
babe, okay?
Okay. Bye.
(CHUCKLING)
Mmm-mmm.
No more food.
You, eat.
(WHIRRING)
(WHIRRING STOPS)
CURTIS: Yeah, let's keep
going with that bit.
It'll go
another 10 feet.
We won't get
the gravel pack
down today.
Why not?
Clouds.
We're gonna
have to call It.
Happy hour starts
at 5:00, Dewart.
Not If It's raining.
Ready?
Oh, yeah.
(DRILLING RIG WHIRRING)
(SEWING MACHINE WHIRRING)
NAT: They werejust
drinking and laughing.
And, oh, my God,
It was like I was
being In a museum
and I saw the progress
from apes to men.
(BABY CRYING)
(LAUGHS)
I saw It.
I saw the future.
(LAUGHING)
Dewart, that was him,
that was going to
be him In 20 years.
(ALL CHUCKLING)
Let me tell you,
you laugh.
You laugh. But this
little one In your arms
is gonna be shuffling
in a barjust like them.
Yep.
Don't listen
to her.
Hannahl
What?
You guys okay?
KID: Yeah.
No. Don't touch.
You understand?
Okay. Come here.
Go play.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Hey, DJ.
Bring the girls lnslde.
(RIG WHIRRING)
(RAIN PATTERING)
What?
It's not my fault.
I told you.
Yeah, all right.
All right,
I'm calling It.
Shut It down.
Bye. surl-
Thank you for coming.
I'll call you about
the Lions Club supper.
Okay. Love you.
Bye, Sam.
Bye, Cami
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Can you sign
S-T-O-R-M?
Storm.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
I gotta get home.
(OPENS CAN)
(DOG BARKING)
(SIGHS)
Nat and me been looking
into athreesome.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
We've been chatting
with this girl onllne
from Canton.
Yeah. Blg old girl.
(LAUGHING)
What's blg?
She's about 250, 215.
(CURTIS LAUGHING)
She can't be no taller
than ﬁve foot.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Oh, shit, man.
I don't see me
and Sam gettlng Into
something like that.
No. I don't
guess you would.
You got a good life,
Curtls.
I'm serious.
I think that's
the best compllment
you can give a man,
take a look at his life
and say, "That's good.
'That guy's doing
something rlght.'
Well, It ain't
always so easy.
Hell, I know that.
Ah, shit. I gotta go.
(CLOSING GLOVE BOX)
lfallana?
Good night.
(noon CLOSES)
(STARTS ENGINE)
(SNORING SOFTLY)
Hey, baby.
She do
all right today?
She's still not playing
with the others, though.
Nmm.
She can't connect.
Honey, you gotta
clean up that trash plle
In the back.
She ﬂshed out a board
that had nails on It.
I'll get to It
this weekend.
I still
take off my boots,
so I won't
wake her up.
I still whlsper.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(DOG BARKING)
(WIND HOWLING)
(STORM INTENSIFIES)
(GROWLING)
(SCREANING)
(SCREANS)
(PANTING)
Curtls?
What?
Did you hear me?
You got to be home,
showered,
ready to walk out the door
by 6:00 tonlght.
What's wrong?
Nothing. Ijust want her
to eat her breakfast
and stop playing
with the damn dog.
She's fine down there.
She had toast already.
All right.
SANANTHA: What?
Hannah.
Come here. Hannah.
Curtls?
(LOUDLY) What?
You didn't eat anything.
It's okay.
(HINGES SQUEAKING)
(noon CLOSES)
JIM: I didn't say
you had control over
the weather, Russell.
What I did say was
that the top shelf
has got to be cleared
by the 15th.
That's non-negotiable.
Um, Curtls?
Curtls? Where we at
on that East 82nd slte?
Yesterday
slowed us down.
We couldn't
get the second
pllot hole drilled.
It rained for
two hours yesterday.
Two hours,
and our entire schedule
went In the toilet?
We lose the permit
If you're not out
of there, end of day.
Yes, sir.
End of day, Curtls.
All right.
Valerle tells me
that the father-son
pancake cook-off...
Hey, I gotta make a stop
before we head out there.
Thlnk we got time?
Yeah, there's tlme.
(CURTIS GRUNTING)
Shlt.
(WHIRRING)
(METAL SCREECHING)
(DRILLING STOPS)
Son of a bitch.
DEWART:
We strlpped that bit.
Yeah.
Well, brlng It up.
We gotta reset It.
(STARTS RIG ENGINE)
Curtlsl
(CHAINS RATTLING)
You ever see
blrds ﬂy like that?
What?
(RIG ENGINE WHIRRING)
(CAR ENGINE WHIRRING)
(INAUDIBLE)
Damn It.
(TURNS OFF ENGINE)
Come on, we gotta go.
CURTIS: Oh, Jesus.
Honey, loan
really use a shower.
(KEYS JINGLING)
(CAR STARTS)
TEACHER: So ifyou continue
with the basic vocabulary,
this will allow you
to communicate with
your children better.
Between the ages
of four and seven,
the focus ls more
on the sign.
And then later,
we'll begln
adding the alphabet
as more of
a support system.
Now, In ASL,
the male sign is signed
at the forehead area.
For example, 'father,'
ls signed up here
like this.
Father. Very good.
You're not sorry.
I am sorry.
Well, you stlnk.
You smell really bad.
I think I smell good.
Do I smell good?
(LAUGHS)
(INAUDIBLE)
See? Maybe I should
marry her Instead.
Stop.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(WIND WHISTLING)
Oh, man.
You okay?
ShltI
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
(CRASHES)
(HIGH-PITCHED WHINING)
(MUFFLED) You okay?
(MUFFLED) You're okay.
(WHISPERING) It's okay.
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(FOOTSTEPS ON CAR ROOF)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(ExcLAINS)
NoI
(HANNAH SCREANS)
(GROWLING)
(STRUGGLING)
(HANNAH SCREANING)
Hannahl
(SCREANING)
(SCREAMING) Hannah!
(GASPING)
Here, honey.
Put on your shoes.
Good, you're up.
CURTIS: Yeah.
Honey, you're soaked.
I've felt better.
I guess we can stay
home If we need to.
Where you going?
It's Saturday.
I was going to take
Hannah to my booth.
Oh, yeah.
You look really sick,
honey.
I'm all right.
It's Just a cold
or something.
Let me get you
some Advll.
No. Don't worry about it.
Just go. I'll be fine.
You sure?
Nmm-hmm.
Better already.
Okay. I got my phone
ifyou need anything.
Don't forget,
Sunday lunch ls
here tomorrow.
If you're sick,
we should cancel.
I'll be all right.
Okay, we'll talk later.
Come on. Let's go.
You sure?
Honey, please.
WOMAN: How much you asking
forthis pillow?
Thls plllow Is 315.
That's more than
I want to spend.
This is all hand stitched.
It takes a really long time.
That's why
I charge that.
I'll give you $1 for It.
I can't go that low.
Well, that's my offer.
How about 10?
I'll give you 38,
but It's In change.
That's ﬁne.
Lucky for you she likes
to count change.
Come on.
Get In. Good boy.
I'm sorry about this,
buddy.
Wejust gotta
work It like this
for awhile, okay?
(SIGHS)
(CLANKING)
(CLICKING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Whlle rescue workers
made several attempts
to reach the family,
Walter Jacobs' wife
and brother-in-law died.
SAMANTHA: That's what
I don't understand.
If he didn't do anything,
why did you put him out back?
(CURTIS MUMBLES)
What?
Did you hear me?
I said If he
didn't do anything,
why did you have
to put him outside?
Ijust wanted him to
be outside for a while.
He's your dog.
He's always been
an Inside dog.
He's my dog,
that's why he's outslde.
Look,
right now with
Hannah and everything,
I Just think
It'd be better.
Hannah loves Red.
NEWS ANCHOR: ...the gas cloud
spread across their
six-acre property.
The only way off their land
was across the train tracks,
whlch were
blocked by wreckage.
JACOBS: l trled
ualng some wet raga
and some towels
to breathe through,
but that just seemed
to make It worse.
Whlle reecue workers
made several attempts
to reach the famlly,
Walter Jacobs' wlfe
and brother-ln-law dled
In the home.
Jacobs aurvlved
deeplte endurlng ff hours
of exposure to
the gas cloud...
You hearing this?
It's awful.
Eleven hours.
No way out.
(REPORT CONTINUES)
(RAIN PATTERING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(CURTIS GASPS)
(THUNDER CRASHES)
Heyl
(THUNDER CRASHING VIOLENTLY)
Hey! Hey!
(RATTLING)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
(PANTING)
(OBJECTS SHAKING)
(COMMOTION INTENSIFIES)
(COMMOTION CEASES)
(MUTED HIGH-PITCHED
TONES RINGING)
(MUFFLED STRAINING)
(WHOOSHING)
(GASPING)
(PANTING)
(FLUSHING)
Babe?
Yeah?
You got the number
for Dr. Shannan?
You're still
not feeling good?
Yeah, we got
the number?
Yeah, baby,
but he'll be closed today.
nght. Yeah,
I'll sell tomorrow.
Honey, If you're
not feeling good,
we got to take you...
No. Stopl
Okay.
Do you want me to
cancel lunch today?
Shlt.
What Is that?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Ijust...
I got a sore throat.
I'm sorry
I'm taking It out on you.
I was gonna
leave Hannah with you
so I could go to church,
but I'm not gonna
with you like this.
It's ﬁne.
I'll be ﬁne.
No. She needs breakfast.
I got It.
I'm sorry
that you feel bad,
but you need to
drop the attitude.
Come on. Just go.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry.
Just go.
Hannah's in the den.
We have cereal for her.
(WASHING MACHINE WHIRRING)
We're going out.
Okay?
It's okay. It's okay.
You stay put, okay?
(SIGHS)
Let's Just start.
Let's all Joln hands
for the blessing.
(CAR PULLS UP)
Where the hell
have you been?
I know. I'm sorry.
I had to run an errand.
You're really late.
I know.
You didn't even
bring your cell phone.
(SIGHS)
MELVIN: Mlssed you
at church this morning,
Curtls.
He knows what to do
If he wants me
to stop asking.
Was it a good service?
It was.
It was good work.
I'm thinking about cleaning up
that storm shelter out back.
(SNORING)
(noon OPENS)
(GRUNTS)
Curtls?
Curtls,
how you doing, bud?
Hey, Doc.
Hovfs my girl?
She's good.
That's good to hear.
Tllt your head back
for me.
I don't have a cold.
Oh. Did she get
that down wrong?
No, Ijust
told her that.
Oh.
So what's the problem?
I've been having...
I've been having
some trouble sleeping.
I was hoping
you could give me
something for It.
Mmm. How long's
this been going on?
About four nights now.
You're not sleeping at all?
Well, some,
but real restless.
Well, lthinkfour nights
is a little too soon to tell.
My advice would be to
not eat or drink anything
after 0:00 at night.
Cut back on
any alcoholic drinks,
tobacco, saffelne.
Get some daily exercise.
Well, I think...
lthink I might need
to try some medication.
Why do you say that?
The reason I've been
having trouble sleeping
ls these dreams
I've been having.
I didn't think
It was anything at ﬁrst,
but then
the other day I woke up
and the bed was wet.
You urlnated
In your bed?
Yeah.
Couple days before that,
I had a dream that
my dog attacked me
and It took all day
for the pain
in my arm to go away.
You been out to see
your mother lately?
It's been about a month.
Okay.
(TEARS PAPER)
Okay. This is a prescription
for a pretty mild sedative.
It's non-habit forming,
but I'm only
giving you enough
for a few days anyway.
Take It
and see If It helps.
In the meantime,
this Is the number of
a good friend of mine
In Columbus.
He's a psychiatrist.
It's a drive,
but he's the best I know.
Okay.
I'll give him a sail
and let him know
you'll be down
to see him.
All right.
Hey, Dewart.
What you say, Curtis?
Not much.
They want us
to get a pilot hole
drilled by lunch.
I ﬁgure
worse comes to worse,
we can eat on the rig.
Yeah, we'll get It done.
Weekend all right?
Yeah. Same old shit.
INSURANCE AGENT: No.
No, I need the name
of the specialist
whose dlagnosls
you'll accept.
(SCOFFS)
No. Look it, I've told
you this twice. Please.
Just get me the name
and/or the approval code.
Okay.
All right.
And the phone? All right.
Great. Well, thank you
very much. Mmm-hmm.
All right, this is the name
and the phone number
ofthe specialist
who the Insurance
company approves of.
Just sail and
make an appointment.
Now If this doctor
signs off,
you should have
the Implant procedure
fully covered.
I'm sorry
It took so long.
Can I give you a hug?
(BOTH LAUGH)
It's ﬁne. It's ﬁne.
You know,
your husband's
company actually
has very good Insurance
when It kicks In.
Not a lot ofjobs offer
policies half as good.
You're very lucky.
(LAUGHS)
Oh. That's okay. We have
your insurance on file.
That'll be $41.64.
What's the co-pay?
That Is your co-pay.
(SIGHS)
Hey.
(CHUCKLES)
I love you.
I love you too.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
(LAUGHS)
Green?
How about a red?
(HANNAH LAUGHING)
(KISSING)
(LAUGHING)
It was like talking to
a sane person for once.
She made one phone sail.
That's It.
I've been trying
that 000 number
for weeks. You.
(HANNAH YELLS
IN EXCITEMENT)
It's great.
Hey, Hannah.
Are you excited? Huh?
We're gonna
get you some help.
How do you say,
slgn, 'exclted'?
Like this.
Excited? Yeah?
(GIGGLES)
All right.
What've we got here?
I got to do you.
(LAUGHS)
SAMANTHA: Oh, honey,
look at this one.
It's a 2-1, and It sits
directly on the beach.
Wouldn't that be great?
We wouldn't have to worry
about Hannah
crosslng trafﬂc.
What's the rent?
$000 a week.
(CHUCKLES)
That sounds real nice.
(SNIFFLING)
You sleep well?
Yeah. I did.
You look like
you're feeling better.
DEWART: You want me
to come up there
and do It for you?
Jesus.
CURTIS: Hey, how much food
you think you'd need
to live on for a week?
What do you mean?
I mean to stay alive.
What do you think
you'd need?
Not a lot.
Yeah? You think?
I don't know.
You hear about
people living for days
all the time
off bark
and melted snow.
I've never heard
of that.
Shit, I don't know.
You asked the question.
It's on there.
It's on. Come on.
(THUNDER CRASHES VIOLENTLY)
Damn It.
What?
It sounds like thunder.
DEWART: What sounds
like thunder?
What's the matter
with you, Curtis?
(THUNDER CRASHES)
Curtis?
(WHEEZING)
Where you going?
Curtis, where you going?
(RETcHING)
(WHEEZING)
(GASPING FOR BREATH)
(PANTING)
(SNIFFS)
Curtis.
Hey, Mom. (SNIFFS)
(cLEARS THROAT)
Come In.
Sure.
(CLEARING THROAT) Um...
I'm gonna
get some water.
You want some?
(SOFTLY)
Isn't she lovely?
Mom?
Yes?
I need to
ask you something.
Do you rememberwhat year
we brought you up here?
To the ﬁrst place.
It was '00.
Yes. Because Kyle was
going to be a senior.
I was 10.
Yes.
Can you remember what happened
before you got diagnosed?
What do you mean?
I Just want to know
how It all started.
Before you had to leave.
Oh, I don't know.
I remember It was
a real stressful tlme.
Your father
was gone a lot,
and I couldn't
handle things on my own.
Did you ever have any
dreams?
lee, bad dreams?
No. Nothing like that.
There was always...
There was always a panic
that took hold of me.
(WHISPERING) I thought
people were watching me
and listening to me.
It's all right.
It's ﬁne.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah. I'm ﬁne.
May l have the number
for Dr. George Shannan?
Thanks.
Hi, is Dr. Shannan there?
May I speak with him?
This is Curtis LaForche.
Hey, Doc.
Yeah, sorry...
Sorry to sell you at home.
I just... I don't think
I can make it to Columbus
to see
that psychiatrist.
Yeah, It's Just too far.
Is there somewhere local
you could send me?
Hey.
Oh, hey.
Sorry I woke you up.
It's okay.
Where you been?
I went to see Mom.
Is she okay?
Yeah. I Just wanted
to check up on her.
You should've told me,
we would have gone with you.
No, that's okay.
Come to bed.
lwlll In a bit.
Well, you've kept up
with the payments
on the house.
We've been good
about that.
I gotta tell you, Curtis,
banks aren't loaning money
the waythey used to.
We've got you
a loan today,
but the Interest rates
are variable.
We have to tie It
to your house.
That's ﬁne.
Curtis,
I've known you
a long time.
Financed your house
foryou, two vehicles.
I'm telling you,
this Is a risky loan
you're taking.
I need the money, John.
Okay.
(WHIRRING)
(TURNS OFF RIG ENGINE)
Hey.
Sorry I left you
yesterday.
Jlm same by.
I covered for you.
Thanks.
I need your help
with the depth charts.
(SIGHS)
Fucklng Nat put me
In charge
of frying oysters for
that Lions Club supper.
You need
another burner?
Yeah,
If you still got yours,
I could use It.
Hey, you think
you could help me
with something?
What do you need?
I'm gonna build out
the tornado shelter
In my backyard.
I could use some help.
The hell you wanna
do that for?
Just needs to be done.
What do you need?
I ﬁgure I'll do It
on a Saturday,
borrow some
equipment from work.
You sure about that?
Yeah, I Just
need a backhoe,
a hauler.
I'll rent the rest.
Yeah. Whatever.
I'll help.
Thanks.
You all right, man?
What do you mean?
I Just don't
wanna see you fuck up.
I'm not.
WOMAN: Come In.
Have a seat.
I'm Kendra.
Curtis.
Okay.
I'm gonna start
by asking you
some questions.
Okay. I already answered
all the questions
on the form.
Yeah, I know.
I looked at them,
but I need to get
a proﬁle started on you.
nght. Well...
Out of the ﬁve
possible symptoms
needed to be diagnosed
with schizophrenia,
delusions, hallucinations,
disorganized speech,
disorganized behavior
and the negative symptoms,
I've had two.
So, Itookthis quiz
in the back ofthe book.
I scored a ﬁve
out of a possible 20.
Schizophrenia starts
at 12. So...
They say it might be
a brief psychotic disorder.
Yeah. Whatever it is,
I need to know what to do
or what to get on
Look. I'm a counselor.
Certlﬂed,
but I'm not a psychiatrist.
I ean't prescribe
anything to you.
I ean talk to you,
lean recommend where
to send you,
but that's It.
Now, that said,
If you want to talk,
I'll llsten.
For a lot of people,
that's a good start.
Now you said here
that your mother
was diagnosed
wlth paranoid schizophrenia
In her 30s.
And you're at 35.
You wanna talk
about that?
Yeah, I don't know
my mother's symptoms.
lwasjust 10.
My brotherwas 17. And...
I don't know. She Just
left me In the ear
in the parking lot
at the grocery store one day.
And she didn't come back.
And then they
found her a week later
eatlng trash
out of a dumpster
in Northern Kentucky.
My dad had to put her
In the State Hospital
In Columbus.
And she's been in
assisted living ever since.
Yep.
My dad raised me.
He died last April.
So tell me
about these dreams.
SAMANTHA: I don't know
what our schedule will be,
but...
That's all right.
But I really do think
you should continue
with the sign language.
And any additional therapies
that kids need for
the cochlear implant.
SAMANTHA: Absolutely.
Okay.
Good night.