Produced by Fuji Television Network
Kadokawa Shoten Publishing & Toho
Official Film for Italy
in Japan 2001 Foundation
Original Story by
Kaori Ekuni & Hitonari Tsuji
Will you go there with me someday?
When?
Let's say...
...ten years from now.
Will you promise to do that, Junsei?
I will.
I promise.
Twixt Calm & Passion
Spring 1994
The record rainfalls in 1966
quickly flooded the Arno River
and all the historic areas of Florence.
Damaging numerous,
irreplaceable works of art.
Paintings, sculpture, furniture,
textiles, books,
and precious art stored
in galleries and storerooms.
To save them,
we developed and mastered
new restoration techniques.
The entire city turned into a
restoration studio.
It was a revolution in the craft
of fine art restoration.
That pride and spirit have been
passed on down to us.
Florence remains the most
important center of
fine art restoration in the
entire world.
Our mission,
to resurrect historical pieces.
Our experts devote themselves
to their work.
Often spending an incredible
amount of time on one piece.
Let's take a look at it.
It's been a while.
Completed.
Wonderful.
Let me introduce my disciple Massimo.
You did a good job.
This one was greatly damaged.
He is an expert in water painting.
He colored it with complete skill.
It was damaged by dampness.
It took five years to finish it up.
I went to Italy to study art restoration.
I was twenty-three years old.
I'll use this gesso.
Okay.
I went to one of the leading
studios in Florence.
For three years
I studied as a trainee.
Some of the world's leading
experts worked there.
Our teacher, Giovanna, was one.
She was an expert on
oil painting restoration.
I managed to pass a few of
the qualification exams.
Mostly due to Giovanna's teaching.
You added gesso?
Yes, I added it all.
Occasionally, Giovanna
used me as a model for her work.
That first time,
I was quite flustered.
All?
Take it all off?
All of it?
Every stitch?
Completely nude?
I asked her three times, to make sure.
Everything... even my underwear.
The fourth time, I acquiesced.
Don't move.
Giovanna seemed to always
work on her drawings in silence.
I kept quiet and soaked up
the atmosphere of
serene time and space.
To me,
Giovanna was like a mother.
My mother died when I was young.
Her studio was always warm.
Giovanna's favorite perfume
exuded the gentle fragrance
of the iris.
You're in a church.
Aoi.
- Take it away.
- Not yet.
I want veal in tomato
sauce and pasta.
Tell him no beans
in the pasta.
No white beans, please.
Just translate.
Everything's fine, thanks.
You're always angry.
Who's Aoi?
You called her name in bed last night.
I apologized, didn't I?
My name is Memi.
Who the hell is she?
Why ask?
It's nothing to do with you.
I'm sorry.
Look, I apologize.
Waiter!
More wine here!
Memi is studying at a
language school here.
Her roommate also attends
the same school.
Those two facts
are all I know about her.
In my heart...
...there's a woman...
...one I can never forget.
Spring 1997
Aoi.
That's her name.
As for me,
for all these years,
I could never...
...forget her.
You majored in Japanese literature
in Japan, didn't you?
Right.
So this is not your field.
Morning.
How did you win Giovanna's favor?
What's that mean?
You should know.
Did you bed her?
Bed? A bed of sushi?
I like it raw.
I heard that she is thinking about
getting Junsei to work on
the Cigoli painting.
What?
That's great.
Congratulations.
What's up?
Junsei's in charge of Cigoli.
It was painted in 1610.
The owner is a private collector.
You want me
to work on it by myself?
You don't feel up to it?
It's not that...
I do.
I'd really like to do it.
What do you think?
It's good work.
Want me to get you something?
No, thanks.
I'll be back soon.
Alright.
Thank you.
Do a good job.
First, I worked on the surface.
I felt as if my soul,
and the artist's, became as one.
Almost a sacred feeling as if
my soul was being cleansed.
You know Lodovico Cigoli, don't you?
Back in Tokyo
I showed you a print of his.
I'll finish it soon.
It's been three years.
How have you been?
Hey, Takashi.
What's wrong with you?
This girl called Kana is exquisite.
I quite fancy her.
She told me to "take care"
when I left Japan.
It's just crap talk.
What's with you?
Well, yesterday in Milan...
...I met Aoi.
Here.
This is where she works.
It's a jewelry shop.
She's been there three years.
You knew all along?
Don't be snotty.
No, give it back.
Forget I said it.
Don't do that.
Leave it there.
I should never have even
considered telling you.
She gave it to me
just as I was leaving.
She never said to give it to you.
But after all,
I was there when you split up.
I can't forgive you.
I want you out.
Now, I said!
Looking for a present?
Not really.
Actually, yes.
A birthday present.
I see.
When is it?
May 25th.
Too late, that was last week.
Is it a present for your girlfriend?
Let me choose something for you.
How about this?
The color is very appealing.
I was wondering if she is...
"Marvin Lai
Milan Branch Director"
Please.
It's from the Piedmont region.
It's been a while.
I asked at the jewelers.
He's recent,
she's totally besotted.
I'll take them.
Wait here please.
Sorry, but I'll get going.
Did you invite me
to see the painting
or to show off your new boyfriend?
Anyway, it was a mistake to come.
From what Takashi said,
I thought you still felt hurt.
How come?
I'm just fine.
The past is all forgotten.
I'm happy now.
Junsei.
Where have you been?
The police came looking for you.
The police?
You can't enter.
Are you Junsei Agata?
How did this happen?
No...
It wasn't me.
You must make a statement.
But it wasn't me!
No.
I didn't do it.
Let me go.
Who the hell was it?
Which one of you did this?
I'll take you back soon.
You know my roommate?
She's found a new boyfriend.
An Italian guy,
he works at a gym.
They fuck every night,
he has to smother her cries.
You don't need me, do you?
It's obviously someone
with a grudge against Junsei.
A grudge?
Think about it.
It wasn't a robbery, nothing's missing.
Junsei's Cigoli is the only damage.
Then someone must really hate you.
Takanashi, you found it.
Using my surname?
Mind your manners.
You framed me up.
Did I now?
You were out partying,
you screwed up!
The mass media jumped
all over the story.
The studio lost its good reputation.
The police had no suspects.
Since it wouldn't be solved anytime soon,
the police closed us down
until further notice.
I don't care if we never find out.
That way there's no one to resent.
Yes, but still...
This city just seems to
get more and more rundown.
No matter how hard we work,
we can't keep up.
The people of Florence all
live in the past.
The only work here is
in restoration and tourism.
Don't let hate destroy you.
You have a future.
Some future.
Giovanna decided to take a sabbatical.
A rare chance to take a
long holiday, she said.
Then she smiled.
I lost my job.
Unlike my colleagues,
I didn't want to go to another studio.
I couldn't see a future for me
in this town.
Take care!
I gave my bike to Memi's friend.
I moved out of my apartment.
I went back to Japan.
Spring 1998
Junsei, I'm coming in.
I took Kana to Hakone.
She's a good girl.
Hi...
Is this that Aoi?
Yes, that's her.
Who are you?
If you're going to be
taking it easy,
why not try a tempera?
I don't have the talent.
Yes, you have.
You just want me to do
what my father didn't.
Does he ever visit, grandpa?
Sometimes he does.
For more money?
Nothing's changed.
Is the studio closing
the only reason you came back?
Is that what made you
run away from Italy?
I'm happy now.
The past is all forgotten.
A letter for you, Aoi.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
He's stable.
Do you have Uncle's
number in Kashiwazaki?
I called Auntie,
but we'd better let Uncle know.
No, I haven't called Dad yet.
No point calling him.
Too early for the inheritance.
He's out of danger.
That's good news.
You, too.
You're looking well.
I'm relieved.
Come on, Asami.
Your son is really cute.
He takes after me.
Why can't I cook for you?
Mind your own business.
Stop hanging around.
You should talk!
I quit school and left Italy
just for you.
Who asked you?
Don't blame me for everything.
So you don't care what I do?
Get pregnant and have an abortion?
I'm not like Aoi.
Who told you?
She aborted your baby.
That friend of yours.
He told me.
She's a good girl.
She's trying to understand your past,
that's why I told her.
You shouldn't have blabbed.
I didn't tell her everything.
I didn't tell her about your dad,
or the details of you and Aoi.
Nor how you and Aoi
spoke with your minds.
That's silly.
But you two were so close.
A good lesson for me.
Too much love can
sometimes spoil it.
You never end up with
your true love.
So Aoi is...
...she's happy in Milan, isn't she?
See you.
Thanks for the meal.
Memi, isn't it?
Say hello for me.
Is Kana your second choice?
No, she's top of my list.
Sorry about that.
Goodbye.
Hey, Takashi.
What was that about my dad?
About him offering cash.
What cash?
To Aoi.
Didn't you know?
You're a sensible girl.
I'm relieved.
How come?
Why didn't you tell me?
It's my problem, not yours.
I can't forgive you.
I can never forgive you.
I want you out.
Now I said!
Get out now!
An induced miscarriage.
The baby wouldn't have
survived, anyway.
You?
Hi there.
Hello.
We just dropped by.
You must be Kana.
I'm Aihara, general affairs.
Why don't you go in?
I'll have the new will
delivered to you here.
Fine.
Thank you for coming.
Asami, you too.
Thank you.
Are you satisfied now?
Remember your friend,
Mr Tazaki?
His paintings soared in value
soon after he died.
I bet his family is clawing over
the inheritance right now.
This way we're spared
any ugly disputes.
As for impregnating young females,
it's all taken care of.
See you later.
Hey, Junsei.
What did you say to Aoi?
She's not that kind of girl.
You insulted her!
Apologize!
Apologize.
Say you're sorry.
That's enough.
You apologize.
Stop that!
Apologize.
Spring 1999
Dear Aoi...
Forgive me for writing
out of the blue.
This will probably be the first
and the last long letter
I write you.
I'm at the apartment in Tokyo.
I ran away from Florence.
Yes, I ran away.
I came back to Japan.
I went to Shimokitazawa today.
The place where I first met you.
Spring 1990
Hey chief.
Ten yen?
It's only ten yen?
This would cause a riot in Asia.
Hey.
Is that any good?
That's really great.
- I've never heard it.
- Me, neither.
That's how we met.
In that shop, in that town.
Just a quick passing,
no words exchanged.
Why do I remember it so vividly?
It's yours.
When I saw you the next time,
you looked a little wary.
But I was a regular visitor
to the museum.
I already knew they'd hired
a new receptionist.
She was part-time.
She went to my alma mater,
but a different discipline.
One more thing.
I found out that she was
always alone.
And I knew it.
The kind who doesn't mind
being by herself.
I thought you were a very
strong person.
But the reality
was quite different.
You were lonely,
craving for company.
At the same time,
so stubborn and unyielding.
What could I do?