Her name is Kyungjin
Yeo Kyungjin... I feel strange
just saying her name
She has something special
that no one else can touch
It's the dream of any man
to go traveling with a woman he loves
I wished for that too,
and we did go on a trip
However, my fate...
no, first let me tell you how we met
Thiefll Thiefll
Thief!! Snatcher, Stop
My purse! Somebody catch him!
Get him! Please help me!
Excuse me!
Hey, stop!
You!
It's not me, it's him!
Why are you chasing me? It's not me
It's not me. I'm a brave citizen!
He's getting away!
He's getting away! Over there!
That's what they all say
What are you doing?
My eyes! My eyes!
Help me! I'm dying here
I can't open my eyes
My eyes! Get this off of my eyes
Anything you say may be used
against you in a court of law
You have the right to remain silent,
but if you do, you're a dead man
My neck!
"You have the right to consult a lawyer
If you're broke,"
The government will get you one
But I doubt it'll help you any
Sir, a criminal caught red-handed!
Aren't you off duty today?
Sir, a cop's a cop even
if she's off duty
Ma'am! He's the thief, right?
I caught him
Ma'am, you remember me? I'm innocent!
You were robbed at a shoe repair shop,
and I ran after the thief
Hey, shut up
Are you sure this time?
Why don't you trust me, sir?
Well...
Gimme your ID
In my back pocket
Give me a break
Occupation? Physics teacher
At Sunik Women's High
I start next Monday
Cut the crap! Or you might
get in real trouble
I can describe the thief
He was wearing a blue shirt
and black pants
He had curly hair,
and an earring on one side
His eyes were narrow, and there were
a few whiskers on his chin
He had a long nose, with white skin...
And his shoes were...
suede with gold decoration
You remember in great detail, huh?
Betray your partner,
then you can go free?
I can draw a picture of him
Shut up! You could be his accomplice
He doesn't seem like an accomplice...
Exactly! It wasn't me
I'm innocent. Really! Truly!
Hey! Come over here
Smile
He looks the same!
Well...
What? I don't look like him at all
Get your ass over there and shut up!
Don't you smell a criminal, sir?
I don't smell like a criminal!
He's got sharp ears, too
Can you draw a picture of him?
These handcuffs... I'll undo them
I've never lied once in my entire life!
So you can draw, huh?
All done
Me next! No way."
No. It's not what you think
My instincts are always right
You're under arrest
Say cheese! One, two...
You caught him?
Yes, and he works solo
Well then, I'm outta here
Hey!
You're just going to leave?
Can't you at least say sorry?
"Sorry" is not in my dictionary
If you want to hear it,
change your name to "Sorry."
Then I'll call you "Sorry."
You're so pretty
You're doing volunteer
patrol in red light districts? Yes
You're late
Everyone's gone off in pairs
Then should I go alone? No
Wait. Your partner should arrive soon
Let go of me
Shut up! This isn't legal!
Can a cop treat a citizen like this?
Sure, why not?
Hey, it's you again!
Did you get robbed?
Please believe me! Please!
You bastard, come on here and sit down
Lots of delinquents at your school?
I don't know, I'm still new
Kids who sniff glue?
I don't know yet
Hey, let's eat something
Welcome
These days kids do Ecstasy
Lots of school violence
and cyber crime, too
But the worst are school gangs
who steal from weaker kids
Need to give those bastards
a taste of real life
There's an old saying...
"Only the wicked see the wicked"
What did you say? Nothing
You pay!
Do you have change for this?
I'll eat more then
A bitch in uniform!
Do they run a beauty pageant
to select cops?
Don't do that, you idiot
She's cute. Yeah, right
Better than your girl
Your standards are too low
You wanna die?
Hey you, get over here!
Oh Come on
She lost her mind
What the...?
Gimme a break
You're in the wrong place today, Sister!
Did you throw that?
You're in high school, right?
Pick it up!
How much is the fine? I'll pay
Have you lost your manners?
Pick it up!
What if I won't? Pick it up
Hey Sister, what's the matter?
Are you having your period?
Leave us alone, huh?
Pick it up
Follow me, you bitch!
Take it easy
Don't get mixed up with these kids
Notify their school,
and they'll take care of it
Come on you... Shit!
Let me go
You're hopeless. Get off of me!
Shit,
You bitch!
You bitch, you'll regret this
Hurry and pick it up!
Shit! Dad!
Adrug dealer. Drug?
If we follow him
The guy on the left must be the dealer
Let's tail him
We might be able to get the whole gang
No way. We should be looking for kids,
not drug dealers
Those drugs will all end up
in kids' hands, get it?
Let's just call the station and go
That's the DEA's job
Then it'll be too late
You go, I'm going home
Let me go! Uncuff me
Come on
Let me go. I'm not a criminal
Let me go please!
The more you wiggle
the tighter it gets
Gimme the key. I don't have it
Of course you have it!
Where are you touching?
Let's go
Get down
What do you think I am?
Get down!
Come on up!
Go over first and get down
What am I? A ladder or something?
Am I stairs?
I'm a teacher! A teacher!
And this isn't even your district
Don't piss on the street
One. Two. Three!
Who called the police? Son of a...
We didn't!
Drop the gun! Drop the gun!
Drop the gun you bastards
Don't point the gun at us!
You're dead!
We need to get the leader!
Let's get out of here
Freeze!
Who the hell are you?
Let me go. I'm an undercover cop
What's an undercover cop?
I don't know. An agent who does
secret investigation
Nice work
Who the hell are you?
You ruined everything!
I could've nailed them all
You ruined it!
Let me go!
You destroyed my masterpiece
Let's go
Do you know how great my plan was?
You threw mud on a Picasso!
Come on up, hurry
Give me the key
It's gone. I must've dropped it
while we were running
Let me see. Don't touch
It hurts
Hold my hand. It won't hurt as much
Everyone had to rush out for backup
We don't have any extras
They took all the handcuffs we had
Oh, and did you...
beat up some kids on the street?
Yeah, why?
His father is a big shot in our district
He's in a rage!
He's coming here. You'd better hide
Why? I didn't do anything wrong
He's the godfather of the nightclubs
He's almost like a gangster
Hurry and go
Nice introduction, Sheriff
So you're the bitch who beat up my son
So what? Wait, sir!
You stay out of this
Sir, let's talk first
Get out! Hey, bitch
How dare you hit my son?
You want to die? Are you staring at me?
I don't care if you're a cop
Go ahead, bitch!
Take it easy, sir
Let's talk it over
Who the hell are you?
Hey bitch. What did my son do?
Cops shouldn't hit people
He was smoking on the street and
acting rude so I taught him a lesson
If his Dad doesn't care,
I don't care if he smokes
who are you to hit him, bitch?
Stop calling me bitch,
you son-of-a-bitch thug!
What? You're asking for death
Calm down, Officer Yeo
I'll take care of this, sir
She needs to be fired
She's a waste of taxpayer money
Hey you, watch out
when you walk home at night
Hey, boys. Remember her
Don't forget her face!
Yes sir!
How about you and
I just step outside
What the hell?
Do you think I have time for this?
You bitch
Why, are you scared?
You ill-mannered bitch!
You asshole!
I can't take this shit anymore!
So you can yell, huh?
Stop staring at me, punk
You son of a bitch
You're a big guy, huh?
That doesn't mean
you can hit a police officer!
Who the hell is this?
Me? You wanna know about me?
Shit!
Murder, arson, rape... I'm a three-peat
offender! You wanna die too?
What's the difference
between three murders or four?
Do you wanna die? On your knees, now!
On your knees! On your knees!"
What are you doing?
Can you do this in a police station?
You're one to talk
On your knees, bastard!
What are you guys doing?
On your knees!
Rich bastards get away with everything!
I'm sick of this world! On your knees!
Repeat after me. I'm sorry, officers
I'm sorry, officers
Louder, assholes!
I won't do this again
And you! Teach your son
some manners, okay?
Teach your son some manners, okay?
Not that, asshole!
Now, beat it while I count to three
Whoever's left is gonna die!
One... Two three! Who's left?
Sorry, sir
I've done a bit of acting
Put this on
Can't you wash your foot
after I wash my face?
Until this process is finished...
Did anyone lose this lunch box?
No one?
Then it must be the teacher's
Take this
Ladies. I need to say
something as a police officer
lam officer Yeo
Students need to study. Right?
Yes
So don't go around
beating up weaker kids,
You with the lunchbox!
drinking booze or smoking...
How dare you eat when I'm talking!
You!
And if you hang around
red light districts,
I'm gonna whip your butt, got it?
As for your teacher Mr. Go
He's my boyfriend, so don't you
dare try making eyes at him
Go now
We slept together too
Go, please!
A relationship like this...
This is great!
Which of you is Chundeuk?
Be honest
You need a servant,
not a boyfriend, right?
A boyfriend should help
his girlfriend, shouldn't he?
Which floor are you on?
The top floor
Put these over there. Okay
You're a twin?
Nah, that's a composite photo
You're a twin, right?
Guess which one's me
On the right
No, the left
You're really a twin
Who's older? On the right
I don't play the black keys
Why not? Just because
What's your sister like?
Is she like you?
Then hook me up with her
Just joking
She's dead
We were so similar,
no one could tell us apart
Mom put us in different schools
so people wouldn't be confused
She was like the black keys,
and I was like the white ones
She was really playful,
and she liked to switch roles with me
Yeo Kyunjin
Yeo Minjin
She got me to take exams for her, and
made me do things she didn't like doing
I used to hate her for that
Six kings have been born in this land,
so the heaven helped...
This sentence indicates
that our country...
And then one day...
It was the date for graduation photos
I had a piano competition,
And while she was going
to school in my place,
she was hit by a car
I should've died instead of her
So neither of us has a graduation photo
She wanted to become a cop
Do you still play the piano?
Sometimes...
but I play without the black keys
How about you?
Me? The only memory
I have from high-school
is when I had to go on a trip
with both arms in casts
Here, say cheese! One Two Three!
That's funny. Yeah, it was
Let's start
OK!
Myungwoo!
Myungwoo's a fool!
Am I late? Just an hour
Is it that late?
I bought you a present
Really? Me too
It's a book that your
student Chundeuk wrote
You should use his full name
to show respect. He's over 90
You have a student who's that old?
Here
Thanks
District 230. This is line 2
We see the suspect...
chasing him now
Faster!
Run! Quick! Hurry!
Let me go! Let me go!
One kidnapper is caught,
two are heading for
district 103 with the hostage
Block nearby roads
Freeze, or we'll shoot!
Request backup! Be careful
Pick her up
Can we leave him like this?
Just go
Suspect heading for District 103
I repeat
Yeah. I'm running my ass off,
No I'm not
and you're lying in bed?
Officer Yeo in district 103
Wait, Line 2
Two kidnappers ran behind Taeyang
Requesting backup
I'll call you back later!
Officer Yeo is still chasing alone
Can you run 100 meters in 11 seconds?
What? That's how fast this girl is?
I can only do 15 seconds
Stop. Let's stop here
Get her on her knees
On your knees
What do we do with her?
What should we do?
You decide Let's kill her
Kill her?
Yes. The bitch saw my face
But... even if... How could we?
You kill her. You do it
No, I can't! You do it
It's your specialty!
My specialty is welding
Grab her, Grab her!
Where? Shoulders
One shot in her head and she's gone!
Should I stab her on the left or right?
No!
Did you kill her?
What the hell?
Let's get him first
What are you doing here, Sir?
No!
You can't kill her
Why not, man?
Come closer! Can't reach!
Come a little closer. Come on
Okay
Come on! Just a little bit more
Damn, nothing's going right today!
I'll see you in prison, I'll go first
I'll shoot. Freeze!
Kyungjin!
Quiet! Kyungjin! Kyungjin!!
Got you!
Come on! You!
Hiding in here, huh?
What are you doing here?
Can I help you? Is Mr. Go here?
He left already
You didn't you see him on your way in?
No, I didn't...
Bastard
Where'd you get this piece ofjunk?
What do you mean, junk?
She's a beauty!
You bought it? Of course
I'm going off on a road trip
all over the country!
No pavements!
Yeah? I'll go too
I'll take a vacation
Don't you need to stay here
and catch bad guys?
Bad guys are everywhere
Try this. It feels like flying
I must've been the wind
in my previous life
I want to be free as the wind
When I'm not around,
if you feel the wind blowing,
then that will be me
Then is this wind you?
It's my friends
If I die,
I want to become the wind again
Mmm, the fire smells great
Isn't it nice? It is
You know why people join their pinkies
when making a promise?
No, why?
Once upon a time, in a huge,
vast country,
there was a princess who was very,
very beautiful
Mirror, mirror on the wall,
who's the prettiest of them all?
Of course that would be you,
my lady
Really? Do you think so? If you're lying,
I'll break you into pieces!
I never lie, my lady
You are the most beautiful
You're so pretty
Because the princess was
so pretty and wise,
princes came from all over
the world to seek her hand
Finally, five princes were
left in the final round
In order to choose the best match
for her, she gave them a test
She hid her right hand
and unfolded one finger
The five princes had
to guess which one it was
So that sign came to
represent a vow of marriage
The prince and princess
couldn't have been happier
But then the Crusades began,
and the prince had to go to war
The prince promised to come back alive,
crossing his pinky with hers
But ten years passed,
and the prince didn't return
She didn't even know
if he was still alive
But since the princess
was still so pretty,
many people came to ask her
to re-marry
She kept saying no,
believing that he'd return,
but she couldn't turn
them down any longer
So she decided to marry a man
who joined pinkies with her
One day,
a filthy beggar came to the palace
Everyone tried to get rid of him,
but the princess called him in,
saying everyone deserves a chance
That beggar was her lost prince
The truth was, the prince
had been killed on his way home
The soul of the dead must
depart after 49 days
That day was the 49th day
In order to keep his promise,
the prince returned as a ghost
Finally the princess found
the body of the prince
Now you know the meaning
ofjoined pinkies, right?
Yes. Can I ask you a question?
If I die, will you die
for me like the princess?
Are you crazy? Why should I?
Stop putting wood on the fire!
The room is boiling
Are you trying to burn me
to death?
Does it hurt?
What happened to your lips?
Forget about kissing her tonight
Aren't you sorry for this?
Like I told you before,
if you wanna hear me say that,
change your name to "Sorry"
My name is "Sorry." Call me now
Your name is Myungwoo
I changed my name. Say my name.
I can't approve it
Why not? I changed it
Stop fighting and eat!
You're hurting my ears
Myungwoo! Myungwoo!
Myungwoo! Wake up!