"Honesty and Justice for all"
Court in session!
They look innocent, but in reality
they may be that vicious Iron Monkey!
Confess now!
- Who stole the seal?
- Hand it over!
Don't act so innocent in front of me.
Your Excellency, I think...
I'm a kind-hearted official.
I love my citizens.
But you can't be soft
with these guys!
He sounds familiar to me.
You always say that.
It proves you come from the same class.
You won't confess?
Then I must teach you a lesson.
Very wise. Give them a warning.
Fox!
I know it's you.
Give Governor Cheng 30 lashes!
Sir, it's an order. I can't help it.
Go ahead!
Enough! Enough!
I have an idea, sir, please...
Tell me, then.
Get lost!
Your Excellency,
I hope these documents are sufficient.
You're smart to come up with
this idea in such a short time.
Come here, come on.
Again, Your Excellency?
Sir...
It's a shame to see a smart guy
like you wasting away in this place.
Thank you, sir.
I'll deploy you to another province.
- Choose for yourself.
- Choose myself?
I'll choose a wealthy place.
I'm going to be rich!
It's worth being hit.
You return first
and organise my trip.
Yes, sir.
- Governor Cheng.
- Yes, sir.
Open the stores and donate the food
to the public. This will look good.
I'll report to the Emperor.
Thank you, sir.
Go on, open the stores
and hand out the food.
Hurry up.
Put the food on the cart.
Quickly, we must deliver it.
Next month, I'll be moving to Canton.
Would you give me some advice, sir?
As an officer you've observed four
righteous rules and four witty rules.
The four righteous rules are
to repay for merits,
to flatter, to liase and to ally.
Anyone who is skilled in applying
these rules will be prosperous.
And the four witty rules?
To create discord, to reprobate,
to frame and to set others up.
How wise you are.
You have my greatest respect.
You've already learnt how to flatter.
I didn't mean to.
Just remember
politics is like a dream.
Don't take it too seriously
and you'll be fine.
Then you'll live long and prosper.
Prepare the sedan chair
for His Excellency.
Chiretta, good for blood.
Ginseng for respiration.
Crocodile to cure catarrh.
Lizard to treat poisoning.
Tin-tsi... tin-tsi...
You fool! Don't hit me, Dad!
Dad.
Stick out your tongue.
Come on, stick out your tongue.
A slight fever.
Dr Yang isn't here.
I'll give you some medicine.
If the fever doesn't subside,
come and see Dr Yang.
Thank you, Miss Ho.
I've borrowed the pills
to raise money for my trip.
I must save my dad.
I'll repay you in the future.
Thank you.
Thank you for watching.
Ladies and gentlemen,
my father and I were separated
and I need money to get home.
I've no choice but to sell
our secret family life-saving pill.
30 cents each.
Little master, you helped us before,
now we'll help you.
Get lost!
Your dad hurt us before, kid.
Now it's our turn to hurt you.
Honest people don't do
sneaky things.
- I'm Wong Fei-hung. And you?
- Chiu Tin Pa.
Run Wong Fei-hung!
After him!
Make way!
You piece of shit!
Bullying a small boy.
You have no future.
Your mother would rather
have a bun than you.
- Nice moves. Well done!
- Thank you.
Watch out, hot water!
Watch out yourself!
You ruined my stuff.
You little bastard!
Turn around.
Give me that.
Boss, I'll pay for the damages.
- Enough?
- More than enough.
Too much.
How come my kung fu is so good?
Wong Fei-hung, you are great...
Do you take students?
I'm not qualified to teach you.
Put me down.
Shut up!
Who is Wong Fei-hung?
That's me.
That's him.
A dragon? A worm, more like!
Call someone bigger than you.
I'm this big. If you want me
to be bigger, wait a few years.
Challenge me?
I specialise in taming small kids.
You're so powerful.
If I catch you, you will suffer.
Come and get me. You can't keep up.
Let's go for a run.
You're like a lump of wood.
Can't you keep up?
If I can't beat you, I'll retire.
I beat you. Retire.
He's really retired so quickly?
That was easy.
- Little worm.
- Crazy nut, another nasty show?
I've got thick skin.
- Stop talking to him.
- Shut up! He was lucky. Get lost.
Who hit me?
A stone.
Fei-hung, get up.
Come on.
Why did you sneak away?
I'm sorry, Auntie.
I wanted to find my dad.
I'll think of a way. Let's go.
"The Emperor's Royal Officers"
Welcome, Your Excellency.
Summon the Governor.
Summon the Governor!
Summon me?
Is the investigator back again?
Where does this monk come from?
You dare sit in my chair?
Take him away and close down the temple.
Why don't you come to greet
the investigator?
You're the investigator?!
Another one.
This time I've got to see
your royal seal.
My rule is to kill
before investigating.
Is that another note
from Iron Monkey?
We've no money left.
He is the real one.
Your Excellency.
So you'll serve me now?
Yes, sir! Wash all the dishes
and prepare a banquet.
Yes, sir.
His Excellency would like
some chicken and shark fin.
Of course, of course.
The rod is blind,
it sweeps away all injustice.
Strong force
that switches north and south.
Fei-hung, your turn.
Seek the way.
Fisherman's Paddle!
Double Flight from the Sea!
Old Branches on the Ground!
Open Both Up and Down!
Rod that Calms the Central!
- Is he your first apprentice?
- You are the first.
He is your junior.
His dad will fight with you
sooner or later.
I really hope he doesn't come.
If you lose...
That's why I'm teaching him
how to use the rod.
At least I get a follower.
Come on, Fei-hung.
Dad!
They should meet each other.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
Still in one piece.
Dad, don't worry.
A man should be dignified.
Fei-hung hasn't made you lose face.
Good. I'm glad you've grown up.
My worries are over.
Thank you for saving my son Fei-hung.
My pleasure.
Please...
Help yourselves.
I heard there were some refugees
coming into town.
Iron Monkey will be around then.
Fei-hung, take this.
Fei-hung! No.
You can't eat roast duck, you're ill.
Let go.
From my diagnosis
he shouldn't eat so much.
You have it, Dr Yang.
You don't need a special diet
with my medicines.
It's better to be safe than sorry.
The Po Chi Lam Clinic prescription
is quite effective.
Fei-hung is still young, his stomach
is too weak to take such greasy food.
Brother Wong, you'd not put it
this way. But there is a basic law.
Since he's just recovered, he has no
appetite. This will give him one.
It doesn't matter what he eats,
as long as he does.
Not at all.
You'll never finish your meal
if you keep arguing.
I'm sorry.
"The Government House of Chekiang"
It's nice to be so relaxed about things.
You still have your women...
I'd love to be a monk like you.
What a waste of my talent.
Goodbye sweet ladies.
The dream has faded.
I must get some money
to buy an officer's post.
My last prayers, I can't believe
I have to bury you here.
Bless me
that I won't be tortured in future.
After I've buried you,
I'll have to sell myself.
Protect my future descendants from
such suffering as I've experienced.
You don't have to sell yourself.
Take this money
and bury your husband.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
Dead monkey, I'll bury you!
It's a trap.
Right.
A rich city merchant hired us.
You'd better surrender,
Iron Monkey, or else.
You impostors!
I'll remove your mask.
You bastards.
You're even worse
than those greedy officers.
The Virgin's Sword Stance.
How can you call yourself a virgin?
You're so ugly,
you look more like a pig!
Lo Han's Double-Edged Sword!
You don't know one side
of the sword from the other!
Take your hands off!
Why don't you leave?
You call yourselves martial artists?
You have to beat me too
before you leave.
Shaolin King Kong Palm.
Your kung fu is good.
You even recognise my Shaolin King Kong Palm.
It's nothing special.
Then try my Nothing Special move.
You can't escape from me.
Iron Monkey?
Shaolin Palm?
The Flying Monk?
Right,
I'm the master of the Flying Monk.
Monk, you rebelled against Shaolin.
It was you who burnt
the Shaolin Temple.
There are no rules. Human beings
die for fortune. Birds die for feed!
Preach to your dead colleagues.
How dare you challenge me.
- Tell me your name.
- Wong Kei-ying.
Wong Kei-ying, your kung fu
is like nothing I've seen before.
You're right.
No Shadow Kick, the Wong family move.
King Kong Palm!
You don't know when to give up.
I might as well finish you off!
Wind and Thunder King Kong Palm!
Lo Han Palm!
Once you've felt my King Kong Palm,
you've no chance of survival.
Are you OK?
Where are you hurt?
Get the needles for me.
I was hit by the King Kong Palm.
Release the poisoned blood first,
then give me the antidote.
Release the blood.
Take down the list of medicines now.
One centipede.
The tail of a scorpion.
The gall of a bear.
One viper.
One lizard...
Big brother, wake up!
Any other medicines?
Wake up.
Dr Yang!
Dad, are you OK?
Fei-hung, dad is hurt,
get Dr Yang now.
Who is he?
Iron Monkey?!
Dad!
- What are you doing, Fei-hung?
- Stop, Dad, he isn't Iron Monkey.
How dare you contradict your father.
Master Wong.
Is Dr Yang Iron Monkey?
Dad!
I just want to inspect
Dr Yang's wound.
Silly boy!
Miss Orchid, please get up.
King Kong Palm?!
Fight poison with poison.
It's a valuable treatment.
What an excellent doctor he is.
- Fei-hung, get a pen and ink ready.
- Yes, Dad.
There are no norms and no rules
You are trapped in a corner
There is nowhere to run
- Gold can't change
- Sad for blood
Release the blood
and revitalise the soul
A curse that would put you to death
- Emergency aid
- One chance for life
The only way out is death
Hurry up! Cure him.
Dad!
Iron Monkey and Wong Kei-ying
are both hurt.
Check all the clinics.
Arrest all those who are hurt!
Yes, sir!
Such medicines can cure
all sorts of illnesses.
Po Chi Lam Clinic
is really prestigious.
To cure poison
with poisonous insects.
The impact of your clinic on medicine
in the future will be enormous.
However, will you take me to court?
I can't right now,
but you will be arrested one day.
Take my advice and mend your ways.
My father was a righteous officer
when Wei Zhou was deposed.
His colleagues were greedy
and stole food.
My father was killed because of them.
How can the officers save others
when they can't even save themselves?
You can even buy an officer's post.
If there were fewer greedy officers
in the world,
we wouldn't need Iron Monkey.
- Who is it?
- Master Fox.
- Where is Dr Yang?
- He is out.
- Where is Wong Fei-hung?
- He's with Dr Yang.
Damn it!
The investigator wants them arrested.
Why?
Tell them to leave immediately.
Master Wong...
I heard.
I can't imagine
they're going to arrest me.
Dad, let's leave now.
Fei-hung, you can't follow me,
it's very dangerous.
Go back to Fushan by yourself.
If I don't return...
you take care of yourself.
Yes, Dad.
Fei-hung,
a man should be as strong as steel.
I understand.
A man should shed blood, not tears.
- Do you understand?
- Don't worry, Dad.
Dr Yang, please look after my dad.
If anything happens,
please let me know.
Of course.
Dad, don't worry about me.
Fei-hung,
have you forgotten my words already?
Don't cry!
Repeat what I said before.
A man should be as strong as steel.
A man should shed blood, not tears.
Master Wong,
I'll show you the back way out.
- We'll find a safe hiding place.
- Fine.
Dad.
Don't worry,
I'll take care of Fei-hung.
Fei-hung, go inside. I'll answer it.
- Open the door!
Open up!
A girl! A pretty girl.
What do you want? Aren't you monks
ashamed of yourselves?
A monk still needs pretty girls.
Let's enjoy ourselves.
Do you want our lives to be empty?
The Tum Ma move?!
She knows kung fu.
There's something strange about this clinic.
Stranger than you?
I'll show you!
Ether powder.
We got her.
Look at that face.
She's so attractive.
Let's listen to her screams.
We'll do our best to entertain you.
I guarantee a pleasant surprise.
We'll help ourselves.
See how nervous she is.
She must be very anxious.
Relax, this won't take long.
Go to hell you bastard monks!
Monks aren't monks,
officers aren't officers. Bullshit!
You little bastard,
do you want to die?
Auntie, leave now!
Do you want to go in?
Carry the Bow and Shoot the Moon!
Monkey's Rod!
Double Flight from the Sea!
Fisherman's Paddle!
What are you reciting?
Too many stances.
Don't let his stances put you off.
Rod that Sweeps Away all Injustice!
Very powerful.
Strong Force
that Switches North and South!
Don't let him recite. No more!
Over the Top...
Under the Earth!
Stop for a minute.
I don't think so.
Let's see you dance.
Left, right, left, right,
left, right. Halt!
Golden Snake Goes Into the Hole,
Golden Snake Comes Out of the Hole!
Back to the start.
Old witch!
Are you trying to scare the ghosts?
Then you can be a ghost.
No Shadow Kick!
Iron Monkey is Buddha.
The gold which he gave us
can't be spent frivolously.
If we spend it all
there won't be any more.
Dr Yang, Master Wong,
dinner is ready. Let's eat.
Thank you.
There are only two bowls.
What about you?
We have a big abalone.
Don't lie to us.
We'll have the big abalone,
you take the rice.
Well, we'll share
these bowls of rice.
We've already eaten. Here.
I don't even like rice.
- We've eaten. Here.
- I don't like rice.
Miss Ho is here.
Big brother, Fei-hung's been arrested
by the soldiers.
What?
What's wrong with you?
Orchid, Orchid!
It must be the monks. Orchid!
She seems to be suffering
from ether poisoning. Orchid!
Wake her up first.
Wong Fei-hung,
tell us where your father is.
Your dad is here.
Greet him now. Damn baldy!
Tough guy, I'll teach you
a lesson you won't forget.
Wait! If we kill him,
we'll never find Wong Kei-ying.
You're a traitor!
How dare you beat me,
the head of security!
Master Fox!
Look out!
Hin Hung, let Wong Fei-hung go.
You're not the Iron Monkey I met.
Iron Monkey is Iron Monkey.
Hin Hung, prepare to meet your death!
Iron Monkey is here.
Catch Fei-hung!
The Flying Sleeves!
Come here!
Wong Kei-ying or Iron Monkey,
you still have to die!
Kill them both!
Go to hell!
See the Dart!
- You can't save him now.
- Have pity.
You've come to help.
You must all be in the same gang!
Call yourself a kung fu master?
You're useless!
Don't block my way.
Be gone!
Take Fei-hung away.
Your Excellency! Your Excellency!
Take him away.
Flying Sleeves?
What happened to Shaolin Palm?
You didn't die from my palm?
You're tough, huh?
You are an investigator
yet you yourself are underhand.
You are a disgrace
to your profession!
Let's fight, then!
Hurry up!
Stay where you are!
I'll be a laughing stock
if I let you bastards escape!
Old traitor, let's see how many
stances you can resist.
You joined forces with Iron Monkey
and brought shame on our school.
You have no right
to call me a traitor.
Stop pretending to be so righteous.
If it weren't for bastards like you,
there wouldn't be
a need for Iron Monkey!
Flying Sleeves!
Come here!
The Fifth Brother's Rod!
Old traitor!
Come on.
Shaolin King Kong Palm!
- No Shadow Kick!
- Flying Leg!
I'm coming! Damn you, baldy!
Fei-hung, don't!
It's too dangerous.
Up the poles.
Hey! It's burning. Get down.
The fire is burning the poles.
Dad! Iron Monkey! Run!
Hin Hung, I can't defeat you on
the ground, but your balance is bad.
- I'll beat you on the poles.
- Well, come on then.
Let me take your place.
Watch out!
Off the poles.
Not good enough.
Attack the lower part. I'll go first.
No Shadow Kick!
Hit him!
King Kong Falls!
You're no better.
Shaolin King Kong Palm!
Iron Monkey, catch!
Monkey Hangs on the Dried Tree!
Push him down! The monk is losing.
Not so easy!
A Thousand Hand Move!
Kick him off!
Hit him!
Fall down!
It's hooked.
When the wooden poles burn,
we'll have to fight in the fire.
Down, dog!
Stay where you are.
A return for you, monk!
I'll sweep away all the poles.
Iron Monkey, over here!
There's only one pole left,
you're going to fall!
It's going!
Stand at the two ends.
You can't stand properly.
Don't worry about us.
The pole under your feet
won't last much longer.
You'll be buried in this sea of fire.
Kick the pole and push me across.
- The door is open.
- One pole to the sky.
Monk, we tricked you.
One pole to the sea!
You are totally wicked.
Down to the fire!
- Hurry up! Throw the rod here.
- OK!
Catch!
Dad.
I'm fine.
I thought
I was never going to see you again.
Why doesn't anybody care about me?
Don't just stand there, leave now.
Go!
"Train Station"
Master Wong, who knows
when we'll meet again?
Dr Yang, Miss Ho, why don't you come
to Fushan to visit us?
Auntie, you must come.
Master Wong, I'm sorry I'm late.
Ah, you've come to see us off
though you're so busy.
Don't mention it.
I'm busy catching Iron Monkey.
Another new officer is coming.
I hope he is a good one.
Well, we must say goodbye.
Fei-hung, let's go.
Take care.
DVD Subtitles
by European Captioning Institute