Follow.
But you should show us the money.
Where is the change?
Change?
Hey, over there...
I'll go and take the money, sit here.
Honey, give me few millions.
We have separate account, you know?
But you have 30 million cash
put inside the house.
I have forgot where it is.
You will remember, you're smart.
What should I do?
Get rid of this.
You mean it?
You should trust me.
Nine circles.
- Bingo!
- Me too.
Me too.
Damn you!
Where is Officer Lai?
He is having fun inside the CID room.
You bastard!
I want to discuss something
important with you.
Can't you see I am busy at beating others?
I want you to give me
2 million for gambling.
Are you kidding?
How dare you counter attack?
You should give me 2 million.
How can I get 2 million for you?
Taior comes for gambling,
if I've no money,
our secret will be disclosed.
Then we will be in deep shit! Hurry up.
Hands off me.
If only you promised me.
Where have you gone?
I am sorry, I went to get some money.
The money is not well kept.
I put it inside the maid's room
which is in Yuen Long.
Cut the crap, we are waiting for you.
The cards please.
Deal now.
A pair of 8, it's your turn to call.
I want to show...
Hold it, just to tempt them.
Nothing special, just $200,000.
$200,000?
I want to raise it to a million.
I will follow you!
3 eights.
No hesitation, just show hand.
How about the newspaper?
Show it too.
3 eights?
Shit, it's not much!
Follow!
I quit.
I have 3 Aces.
I don't believe that you've got 4 eights.
Don't be that nervous.
Don't cry, pal!
4 eights.
Why? I have had an eight!
You mean the game before you left?
Sure it is.
But we have played many rounds after that.
Why don't you tell me?
You didn't ask!
I...
You are back? Win or lose?
You can tell from my head.
A great loser.
You said you are the King of Gambling.
I didn't mention it.
I have mentioned it.
What'll we do now?
Give me 1 more million to gamble again.
I will show them my real power.
You want 1 million more?
What I gave you was the money
from the bailing account.
Now, we are asked to return the money.
If you don't give us back the money.
You should be in fugitive!
Please lend me money for the tickets.
You...
- Give us one million more.
- You idiot!
Or we'll be in deep shit!
What would you do if you lose that again?
Anyway, let's take risk.
Why do you beat me?
I am making a living only.
Whom are you hitting?
A racketeer.
Why don't you respect
such decent professionals?
He cheated $2.
Who is cheated by him?
It's me.
How can you cheat a beggar?
Beat him to death!
What? The greatest enemy of
the Saint of Gambling: Master Hung!
Hello, how are you?
I am in deep shit! I lost much money.
Pal, ask them not to beat me.
I will teach you how to cheat
on the gambling table.
But, show me something first.
Kidding! Where has he gone?
We have finished 16 rounds,
he hasn't returned!
He is back!
Hey, my dear audience...
He looks smart!
He looks familiar.
Who are you acting?
Guess.
I know!
The Saint of Gambling.
Wrong.
I am acting as David Copperfield.
Deal.
I have 3 Kings.
I have 3 Aces.
Straight flush.
A bigger one.
4 Aces.
5 Aces?!
What Master Hung taught you are powerful.
Win as much as you can.
I'd make use of this chance
to find out the truth of Wong's death.
One million.
I will follow
It's your turn, a pair of Aces.
You are silly,
it'd be the turn of straight flush.
Show hand.
I don't think you're David Copperfield,
I will follow.
I have 50 cents left.
5 million as credit, OK.
Forget the money,
I want you to answer me a question.
Then I will forget the money.
What question?
Have you ever thought of killing me?
Answer me.
- I...
- Answer me.
I want to quit!
Your question is nonsense.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
Just take the money.
Have you found the truth of the case?
The truth is...
I had a four only, but the idiot quitted.
Boss, are you alright?
Are you hurt?
Give me back the money.
Just return the loan.
We needn't give you a share
of the money we won!
But you should give interest.
OK, just follow the bank's rule.
Cheap interest rate, 2.75%.
$2 million is divided by 365.
Just $25 is charged, keep the change.
Take one more.
You'd have done that earlier.
Any progress?
I have found that Judy Tong
was suspicious.
I think she is having a secret.
And that Taior Lam...
Don't look only at the surface.
When I was trained in Scotland,
I have studied all
the extraordinary precedents.
Including the murdering case
of the Eastern Express.
The murdering case of River Nile.
The murdering case from Fatal Attraction.
And the hidden corpse under the stove.
I have found out a principle.
What is it?
The most suspicious criminal
is not the real murderer.
Shit!
I agree! It always
happens in movies.
You can put it
in that way,
the murderer may or may
not know the victim.
He or she has the inclination
of violence acting.
Maybe a money digger,
or is greedy for money.
As what you have said,
the murderer may be you.
Man, arrest him.
Yes sir.
Are you crazy?
Sorry sir.
It's just theory.
By the way,
you can't get any clue
from Judy Tong's home.
See whether there're any conflicts
between Wong & Taior in office.
May be they have had quarrel
in business which made him kill.
You said the most suspicious
one isn't the murderer.
It's bull shit,
why don't you go and check now?
Let me finish the most
important thing first, OK?
Love you 360 years.
Damn it, you just forget about me!
Thank you!
Bitch and bastard.
I wanna kill!
Knife?
Shit!
The door!
Taking a seat.
Thank you for your flowers.
The one who wears the patterned socks.
I have boyfriend, you know that.
Although he is poor and selfish...
He is mean and old fashioned.
She doesn't mean it.
But he is my boyfriend.
I can't accept you.
Don't...
Don't!
I will kill you bastard!
It's you!
It's you?
Actually, I mean...
I want to kill you!
Stop it!
What are you holding the knife for?
Drop it first.
Hold it, listen to me first.
I have tailed you for a long time.
You come to look for this bitch!
Me?
Why are you still asking?
How dare you seduce my wife?
I am asking you!
Whom do you love?
It's just for fun.
Just for fun.
You are played by others.
You are bitch, and you are bitch too!
You bring me bad luck!
You want money, isn't it?
OK, it's just money!
Come on...
Hey, money!
What? You are paid,
why don't you leave now?
You two...
OK, I am leaving!
Ah Man...
This is your home,
where are you going to?
Yes, this is my home!
You two, leave here at once.
Leave!
Man, don't get angry, listen to me.
Wait for me downstairs.
I will give this bitch a good lesson.
Go, what do you want?
I won't give it a damn.
I warn you seriously!
Never see my wife again.
Or I will beat you! Got it?
She has gone, why do you keep on acting?
Don't you feel it funny?
We should act!
Don't you think my acting was good?
Poor!
Kidding? I got a prize in drama acting!
But you acted poorly.
How could you be
courted by that woman?
She is nice and she always
buys flowers from me.
So I date with her when I'm free.
I can't tell she is a lesbian!
I can't tell it's her!
She is waiting for you.
Why don't you go now?
Go!
I will accompany you
all day after this case, OK?
I have bought you something.
What is it?
Patterned socks.
Burn it.
Mr. Wong, good morning.
Good morning.
Mr. Wong, good morning,
Mrs. Wong is not around.
I know.
There is an electricity cut inside.
Never mind, I just want to
fetch a cup of water.
This is sent in this morning.
What's the matter?
Nothing, get out now.
There must be some problem with you.
Nothing to do with you!
Get lost.
Pay attention.
Don't light up with the lighter.
What does it mean?
It's brandy.
Boss.
Hello? Taior?
How is it?
How did you get my picture?
By camera.
I have waited for this chance for ages.
But I can't imagine
you have courted this one.
I think the gossip magazines
are interested in such pictures.
You bastard!
I don't mind.
What I want is money.
If you want the pictures back,
come to my office at 7 p.m.
What do you want?
Fire station, please.
What's the matter?
Here is Fire Station.
Who is it?
Are there any raincoats for sale?
Go to buy it in department store, damn you!
Who are you scolding? Who are you?
You are so impolite!
Don't cut the line, hello...
Taior, you are going too far!
You will regret if you don't come.
Don't bother me from doing exercise,
see you at 7.
Mr. Wong, what are you doing?
Drinking, I have told you.
You stepped on my food,
pay it to me.
Miss, who are you looking for?
I have a date with Mr. Lam.
Follow me please.
Please come in.
Please.
I am so happy to see you.
Give me the file of the 1st 6 months,
I won't listen to any call.
Yes.
Take a seat.
Cut the crap,
how much do you want for the pictures?
Don't misunderstand it.
I am not that rich!
But I won't be interested
in 10 or more billions.
Don't you think I want to blackmail you?
Give me a price.
It's not good to talk money
among good friends.
But I do want to give you money.
I have checked that your existing
husband is a fake one.
I can kill him for you, but you don't
have to take any responsibility.
And, I will give you 3 billion
for the land in Wanchai.
You bastard!
The land costs over 20 billions.
That's why I won't be interested
in only 10 billions.
I want 20 billions.
Damn you!
Don't scold me with foul language.
Which will damage your image...
as a pretty lesbian.
Bastard!
- You!
- What?
Let's sign the contract 3 days later.
Or, I will send you pictures
to Portland Street.
And to the gossip magazines.
What are you looking?
Stealing?
No, there is a naked beauty.
I won't trust you.
Come and take a look.
I am afraid you'd attack me
if I go near you.
Even you don't go,
I can attack you too.
What's the matter?
I was attacked by a man
who is wearing a business suit.
Go and chase after him.
Have you seen a man wearing
a business suit?
This way.
Thief!
What kind of noise is it?
I don't think so.
I will break his neck if I see him again.
Go that way, I will watch over here.
Wol...
Wolf! Help!
This way.
I changed my job,
but why do you still bother me?
Arrest him!
Go, you bitch!
Give me back my teeth.
It's you! It's fashionable.
What is it?
Guess who wants to kill me?
Who is it?
Give me some hints.
It's her?
How dare you!
You could be run over!
How dare you give me RMB notes?
Don't you think I am blind?
I will throw you to death!
Are you back?
Where have you been?
I am asking you!
I have been playing mahjong all night.
Where have I been?
Are you playing mahjong all night?
We played 16 rounds.
What's wrong with your husband?
There is something wrong with him.
You looked so weird, where have you been?
What is this?
It's blood!
Did you kill?
What's wrong with you?
I am making fun with you only.
The day after tomorrow will be
the 7th anniversary of us.
I want to hold a party to celebrate it.
Do you agree?
Don't be angry.
Let me give you a kiss.
You scared me.
Officer Lai, help yourself.
Do you know Lam was killed?
I do.
I am going to die, do you know that?
Yes, I do.
If you can't get the murderer,
you'll die too.
I am quite confident
to point out the murderer.
Who is it?
Don't be anxious,
my 7th sense tells me that...
there will be a result tonight.
The real murderer will show up tonight.
- Don't move.
- Put your hands on you head.
It's you!
Mr. Wong, I have something to talk to you.
I know what to do...
I am sorry, please go over there.
Thank you for your co-operation.
Please go over there.
You may talk now.
In fact, I want you to leave alone.
You should tell me earlier,
it cut my pride, you know?
Mr. Wong, take care of Judy.
What's wrong with her?
It's none of her business,
nothing to do with her.
Tell me clearly.
I can't help telling you now.
In fact she...
Be frank, tell me!
Right, be frank and speak up.
I love this music.
Dance with me, come on.
Mr. Wong.
We hold party every year,
but this is the happiest one.
How do you feel?
Your feeling is most important.
It seems that you are not very happy.
What do you think?
There must be some reasons
for one to do something.
But I think, anybody do anything...
There must be karma.
What's the reason of killing somebody?
Tell me, Judy!
Why don't you talk?
I am thinking that,
if you were Million Wong...
that would be very good.
You know I am fake?
I knew it on the first day I met you.
You haven't answered my question.
Don't make me dislike you.
Million and I were not living
happily in these years.
In these days,
you recalled the sweet memory of ours.
We were poor in those days.
But, our love was true.
When he got rich,
he loved fooling around.
And I...
I changed emotionally.
I hate being woman.
I want to be man.
To be a man whom can compete
with him for woman.
But when you came here,
you made me feel like woman again.
I don't want to know who you are.
I just want tonight...
can you play your
role whole-heartly tonight?
Hubby.
I want you to accompany me tonight.
Will you promise me?
I want some make up.
You haven't finished.
Who are you suspecting to be the murderer?
I suspect it's Judy.
How come?
I was in the scene when Taior was killed.
I tailed Judy to the scene.
Although I didn't see her kill,
there wasn't anybody around.
Why don't you tell me earlier?
Go ahead.
I don't know why!
Are you kidding?
Hold it, listen to me first.
Even Judy did kill Taior,
I am sure she had her reason.
What reason?
She was the murderer!
But you are a cop.
Don't treat her as your wife.
Mr. Wong, long time no see.
Good morning...
I won't bother you, see you.
Tell me the rest that you know.
I think the murderer will kill again.
What?
To kill those who know the secret.
Luckily I don't know any secret.
You know it now.
I know it too.
There is another one who know this...
Miss Ching!
Why don't you inform her now?
I will arrest her by all means.
Go now.
It's me.
You scared me.
Don't do that.
This is the most wonderful idea.
I have had masked.
The real murderer would be fainted
once he looks at me.
I will arrest him right away.
Let me put on the mask.
Hello!
- What's wrong with this?
- You scared everyone!
They have seen the newspaper
about the death of Taior, you idiot!
What'll we do now?
Go up to Judy's room and watch.
You will get something! I am sure.
You mean reward?
Where is my gun?
To do such dangerous thing,
you asked me to return your gun?
Don't you think I am idiot?
We should take revenge for Brother Taior.
He was killed by the Million Wong
and his wife obviously.
You should be careful!
Don't worry.
Please.
You have another boyfriend.
Don't come to me again.
It's a misunderstanding.
Maybe, this is a modern dance.
Let's follow them.
Miss, may I?
Come here.
Miss Ching, it's very dangerous.
You are the wolf!
I changed many jobs because of you.
And I can't escape from you in this party!
This is fate!
OK, come and rape me.
It's a misunderstanding.
Come on... Just once,
never bother me again.
Come and rape me.
Damn it!
The victim died so horribly!
Isn't it a heart attack?
What?
A person was shot dead by an arrow.
That's him.
Don't move, the cops are coming.
I watched Judy Tong upstairs.
She hasn't left her room.
We are trapped.
I don't want to be controlled.
I want to go my own way.
Judy, there won't be any good to you.
Don't bother me.
Judy
Leave now, I don't want to see you.
It's you!
I have picked the killing weapon
and I want to hand it to you.
You should not hit so heavily!
Don't move!
Judy!
Don't get mad.
I know you are the murderer.
Yes, I did all the cases.
Take back the gun.
Good job, you must be promoted.
How?
What do you think?
Let's calculate the salary first.
OK, just go ahead.
Go!
Give way please.
I am leaving, hubby.
What are you doing?
Do you know what had happened?
What happened?
The murderer is arrested.
I see, who is the murderer?
The murderer is...
Judy.
Before taking her away,
you showed great affection to each other.
She kissed your left armpit.
I know it, my cousin told me that.
It's totally wrong.
Totally wrong!
How dare you deny?
I won't!
But, she didn't kiss my left armpit.
Where did she kiss?
Ah Man, trust me, I love you only.
I am willing to take
any punishment you offered.
Come on, punish me.
Come on...
I won't punish you.
Well, then I will punish you.
You are bad.
You hit me?
Come on.
Where did you get this?
You said you are willing
to be punished by me.
Isn't it alright?
Are you scared?
I am really scared.
Are you willing to be kissed by others?
Dare you?
Loose me first.
What are you doing?
Bathing.
Let's not waste any time.
Honey, come on over.
It's jammed.
Punish me.
Come on! Baby! Come on...
It's you!
You are nosy!
Ah Man! Ah Man.
You dragged Judy down.
What? Repeat once more.
I want to take revenge for Judy.
I can't hear clearly, repeat once more.
Can you repeat again?
I can't hear clearly.
Are you fooling me?
Do you want peeping?
Watch out!
How dare you!
I wanna kill you!
Damn it, how dare you stab me like this?
Do you mean it?
It's not stabbing, I am going to open you!
What are you staring?
I want to kill you!
Please don't!
None of my business.
I know!
You are over, it's my turn now.
Not exactly!
Thank you.
Don't you think I am useless.
I am cramping.
These are the dirty pictures of
Judy and Ching.
Ching is not only a lesbian.
She is insane too.
She has an inclination of violence acting.
She wants to kill those who loves Judy
and those who harms Judy.
So she killed Million Wong first.
Then she killed Taior Lam.
Judy confessed the situation of that night.
You can't fall for that fake Million Wong.
I don't want to be controlled.
I want to go my own way.
About this fake Million Wong.
We can have bright future
if only he is killed.
You are crazy.
Am I? It's you who has changed.
Wong hit you.
I took revenge for you. So I killed him.
It's you who killed Million?
So what? I killed Taior too.
I knew it.
He took our dirty pictures
to blackmail you.
Such rubbish.
Only a dead one would do no harm to us.
You did everything.
Why?
For you only.
I am now going to kill him.
I won't let you do so.
Are you falling for that man?
Get lost.
No, no...
That's why she wanted to kill me.
Ching wanted to kill me with the arrow.
Why Judy wanted to protect Ching?
She has deep affection with her.
So she took all responsibilities herself.
She is...
What? None of your business, you know?
Yes.
That's right.
You have done a great job.
You are assigned to another case,
to be undercover again.
Are you kidding?
This is an order!
Is this an order?
You...
Be polite, call me Sir.
ICAC admitted that it was a mistake
to charge against me.
I resume duty now.
Isn't it true?
Sure.
No big deal.
You may have the same rank as mine.
You are wrong, the head said that you
always bully your subordinates.
You are suspended now.
So, before 1997,
You will be bullied by us.
How dare you?
So what?
Stop it please, stop.
What are you doing? Hands off please.
Just leave them alone.
Chow Sing-Sing, someone is looking for you.
Big Mouth.
It's you, Big Nose.
Are you fine?
What?
We are having a party tonight.
I have bought many girls with us.
What are you waiting for?
Bring some boys to join us.
Right, hurry up.
Fine, make it next time.
Enjoy yourself.
Fine!
Wait for me!