CHO In-sung
SIN Min-a
PARK Jung-ah
Kang Lea-yen
KIM Soo-ro
Director K.C. Park
Good night, Miss Lee
- Good day
- Thank you
- Are you closed?
- Yes
Is it raining?
- Are you here for a cut?
- Yes
So sorry.
Come back tomorrow?
Wait. Wait a sec
Give me a reason why you need
your hair cut today and I'll do it
A reason?
Yes, Mr. Ji-suk Kang!
Um, how do you know my name?
Don't you know me?
Well
Shall we play a game?
Remember who I am before I'm done
and the haircut's on me
But if you can't remember,
then you pay me double
Are you always like this?
It's a game.
What, no questions?
- Okay, you're done
- Thank you
Don't you want a hint?
A beautiful woman knows my name
Aren't you even curious?
No
I think I've won
Dong-beak Junior High,
ninth grade, Hee-jin Park
Wrong!
Not Hee-jin Park.
It's Hee-jin Lee!
Madeleine
Guess who I met today
Quiet, I'll lose count
Our class president in 9th grade
He looks like a total goodie.
But with some work here and there
he'll be decent boyfriend material
- Looking to get dumped again?
- What!
Joon-ho Kim
Hee-jin Lee
What do you mean, dumped?
I dumped him
Oh, yeah?
It might start raining again
so get out your raincoats
Ji-suk, good work!
Gyu-hee!
You missed 36-13 yesterday!
Don't forget it today!
Man-ho! Good morning
Hey, Mr. Writer
- Good weekend?
- Yeah
Should we get our coffee?
Hmm, sounds good
What'd you make in class today?
For our teatime pleasure today
Sweet rolls!
Looks good, Man-ho
Thanks
This is really good
How many stars today?
Out of five stars four and a half
Ji-suk Kang!
- Hee-jin!
- That's right, dude
- Where are you headed?
- School
Huh? You haven't re-enrolled yet
I'm going to the library
No girlfriend, huh?
Why else would you go there
on such a beautiful spring day?
Still, there are a lot of
single girls there
Hey! Give me your cell phone
Whoa, what an antique!
Can you even send text messages?
No numbers saved?
I don't use it much
Well, what an honor,
I'm number one
I'll show you how to do it
- You press this
- Miss Lee
And then save
Hey, she's calling you
Yep, well, see you next time!
Hello?
- Hello?
Hee-jin, it's me. I got us
a blind date off the internet
Again? Did you get fired? You work
at an internet cafe now, don't you?
Hey, don't be mean. Get dressed up
after work and wait for me
- Oh! No!
- Love you!
Hey!
Um, excuse me Uh
Do you have something to say?
No
'Please dine with me tonight.
Woo-jin Choi'
Damn, what a bust!
Cheer up
Did you think you'd meet
Prince Charming on a blind date?
I was crazy to go with you.
Plain crazy!
Treating me like that,
they suck! Ugh!
You know,
they so weren't my type
Shit!
Hey, in your mood,
you'd kill at Fortress
Let's go play a game
Do you know what time it is?
Tomorrow's my day off
Let's go, let's play
Do you think I'm off, too?
No, I'm going home to sleep
Come on
You lonely?
Want me to set you up?
Hey, set me up with someone
You have your little honey
Nah, she thinks
keeping her virginity is
God's will or something
Know why her name's Yae-eun?
'Yae' is from 'yae-soo' (Jesus)
'Eun' is from 'eun-hae' (blessing)
Get it? Jesus' blessing.
So what chance do I have?
And I've invested too much
to dump her now
I think I need a sex partner
Bastard
Hey! Ji-suk!
What are you doing here?
As you can see
You are weird
Wow!
This is for the coffee!
This is the best coffee
vending machine around here
Wow, it's really good
I'm so strange. I just can't pass up
coffee from a vending machine
Standing in the street,
drinking coffee like this
I feel so elegant, I love it
Watcha doing later?
I'll probably be at the library
The library again!
I'm off today
Let's go somewhere and play
Where?
Where ever. You decide
Hey, Ji-suk!
Hey, you're here
You love me, don't you?
You must love me
to wait 40 minutes
Then you must hate me
to be 40 minutes late
No, I'm usually an hour late
for the first date
I'm actually 20 minutes early
Let's go
This is where
you chose for our date?
Why not? It's nice
With lots of vending
machines around
Ooh, f-e-e-I that sun!
I love the sky!
It's never boring
When I don't want to see it,
I don't have to
And when I want to,
I can see it from anywhere
You really do love me, don't you?
You smile at whatever I say!
Mr. Author!
Did you read all these?
I'm working on it
You're so weird
Why do you want to
write books?
No one reads books nowadays.
None of my friends read books!
That's an error from
over-generalizing
Over-general what?
Just because your friends
don't read
doesn't mean
the whole world doesn't
Right, you're so smart
I don't know much about
over-whatever
but I know too well how to scrimp
to make ends meet
You haven't tasted the bitterness
of society yet but
Give me one of
your thickest books
Very good! Me likes it
I'll lend it to you.
Give it a try
See! It's the perfect pillow!
That book is sort of
a milestone for me
After ending army duty
I vowed not to cut my hair
till I read 100 books
Then when you came to the salon?
That's the 100th book
Wow, we have something in common
My goal's to fill up my phone
with 100 boy names
- Let's go!
- Where to?
To commemorate our date!
Another year, another birthday
let's all congratulate Ji-suk
All together now, happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday!
Congratulations!
Hey, is this a dinner show?
Fun, huh?
Yeah, lots
So what if
it's not your birthday
Think of it
as congrats on our date
Do you know how many papers
I need to deliver to pay for all this?
Is this the bitterness of society?
Ji-suk when you write, do you
calculate how much each word costs?
10 cents, 20 cents, 30 cents
Eat up
So you got
what you dreamed of
Hair designer.
Wasn't that your dream from 9th grade?
Huh! You remember that?
I don't think any of
our classmates could forget
Will you look at this?
Are you wearing mousse to school?
Hee-jin Lee!
If you're like this now,
how are you going to turn out later?
Do you want to end up
a bar hostess?
I'm going to be
a hair designer
A hair designer?
Ji-suk!
Do you think her hair's pretty?
Um it's pretty
What did you say?
Is that pretty to you?
Ji-suk!
You're the class president!
No wonder this class is in the dumps!
Did you start right
after high school?
Nope, since 11th grade
Wow, you're quick at everything
It's cause I'm simple.
I do it cause I like it. Simple!
Why did you get a job
delivering papers of all jobs?
I do it cause I like it, too
Delivering papers at dawn
it's like taking a walk
in an empty city
Hee-jin!
I wanted to take a walk
at dawn too
33-90, that's the house number,
R-alley, R-swing is
- Past the right alley
- Oh, past the alley, swing right?
Yep
So L-swing, R-1 means
swing left, first house on the right?
Wow, you catch on fast
It's easy
Let's start!
Let's go!
Okay, here you go
- Hey, Mr. Writer!
- Good morning
- Are you quitting your route?
- Huh?
Oh, no, she's my friend
- Hello!
- Hello. How do you do?
She's pretty
No wonder I wanted to pack
some extra today
What's today's menu?
Today, it's um
Let's have some milk
- Thank you
- Do you have strawberry milk?
Strawberry? Um yes
- Here you go
- Thank you
Ah madeleines!
Today's madeleines
Ah so these are madeleines?
Have you had
madeleines before?
No
In Remembrance of
Things Past
the book starts with the character
recalling a childhood memory
The thing sparking his memory
is the madeleine
Why?
He eats a madeleine
by chance
and remembers
the taste which triggers
other forgotten
childhood memories
Here
Mmm, it's good!
Five stars
So do you remember anything?
This is my first time
Maybe, in 10 years
I'll eat a madeleine by chance
and I'll remember today
Ji-suk Kang!
What?
Shall I make today
unforgettable for all time?
How?
Let's date!
What?
Let's have a romance!
We don't know
each other very well
Did I say for us
to get hitched?
We date,
to we get to know each other!
Why? Don't you like me?
- It's not that
- Then what?
Give me some time
to think about it!
Fine!
I'll give you
till we get home!
Go on in
How about it?
What do you say?
About our romance
Um, well It's um
It may be easy
for you to decide
- But this is very hard for me
- Stop!
If it's too much for you
then let's just go out
for a month
What?
An arranged romance
for just a month
Watcha think? Fun, huh?
The conditions are
we have to be 100% honest!
We can't say let's break up
until the month is up
After a month,
we part ways grandly!
You do whatever you want,
don't you?
But poor you
After a month,
you'll be in love with me
Then what happens?
Then? Well, say that
you love me
I shall consider it then
Hey, is it supposed to
sting so much?
My scalp feels like
it's on fire
Wussy you know what we call hair
that's never been permed or colored?
What?
Virgin hair
Ji-suk, the first time's
always a little painful
How come a guy like you,
who can't make a decision
said 'yes' to our month romance?
here are some moments
I want to share with you
Really?
What kind of moments
do you want to share with me?
Well, you see, it's
So what you want to share with me,
it's to go biking in the rain?
Isn't it romantic?
Please don't write a love story
I'm writing one right now
Well, take this scene out
Ji-suk, why do like
getting wet in the rain?
In the rain, I feel like
I'm getting cleansed
You do know
that it's acid rain
That's why
we're wearing raincoats
Ji-suk, you wanna
go to my place?
Hey! This is really good
My mom likes tea
more than sex
I've inherited
her talent with tea
I think I'm going to like tea
more than s-sex
from now on
Liar
It's really good
Not that
Have you even had sex?
No, right?
Hey, at my age,
of course I have
Really? With who?
Well, um
Ji-suk Kang,
you're so cute
The moments we shared today,
I was really happy!
Even when I'm older,
a grandma
every time I drink this tea,
I think I'll remember today
This way, my memory
will be more vivid
- They'll break!
- No, they won't!
Don't talk when
I'm doing the dishes
I can't concentrate on,
so I might break them
You know, you're pretty good
with dishes
Yeah? Well, of course. I've lived
alone for years. Dishes are a given
Yeah? You can do
laundry as well?
- Laundry?
- I have lots of laundry
laundry? I can't do it well
- Are you good with dishes?
- Of course
Hey! Don't you feel like
this is a waste of time?
Nope! Doesn't it just
clear your head?
Play another game!
Any questions,
just ask me, the master
Hi! It's Sung-hae, remember me?
We were in the same class, 9th grade
Wanna catch up? Come to Blue Moon,
Sat. At 7. You can catch me there
What I wish for is
your blue ocean
The universe inside those pearls
I cannot see anymore
I lose sleep, I'm so tired
The energy inside me
Fading, fading
As I wait quietly
Finally, blue eyes
I lose sleep, I'm so tired
The energy inside me
Fading, fading
I lose sleep, I'm so tired.
The energy inside me
Fading, fading
I lose sleep, I'm so tired
The energy inside me
Fading, fading
Hee-jin Lee,
what are you doing?
Aren't you meeting
Ji-suk today?
Shhh, mommy's reading
Be quiet, please
- You major in film?
- Uh-huh
Bye. See you tomorrow
- See ya!
- Uh-huh
A film major and
lead vocals in a band
Wow that's a busy life
There were 3 things
I always wanted to do in college
Love, travel, and the leader
of a rock-n-roll band!
Then you've done all three?
Of course!
Oh, there's a class
reunion this Sat
Reunion?
Just some classmates living in Seoul.
You want to come?
Do you have a girlfriend?
Uh, uh, no
Hello?
It's me
Oh, Hee-jin
Yeah. Ji-suk, I read 100 pages
of Moon Palace today
Oh Really?
At this rate, I'll finish it before
our month is up, don't you think?
Probably
Probably?
How come you're
so wishy-washy, huh?
One time, Jong-chul, man,
he was at my house to watch porn
Suddenly, my mom walked in
Wow, we were screwed,
you know!
We tried to get the tape out
but it was stuck
So then what happened?
We took the whole player out
Told his mom, we had to copy
an English tape or something
Hey! You're really a hair designer?
Not a washer?
If I were still a washer,
I'd die!
That's impressive!
You're the only one still doing what
we dreamed of doing in school
Oh, my!
I must be the last one
- Hey, Mi-hee!
- It's so good to see you, girl!
I'm so heavy
it's hard to get around
What's a mommy doing here?
Min-chul, you be quiet!
But what's this?
Oh, it's Sung-hae's birthday today!
Whoa, Sung-hae's birthday?
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday, dear Sung-hae!
I dedicate this song
to my friends
who remembered my birthday
You're still in my heart
When it rains,
the rain covers, hides me
The times we spent
together pass
You go one without
remembering me
Oh, time passes,
without a word from you
Even when forever comes,
you still don't know me
Yeah. So what if it's Pusan
or that it's between other acts?
We can't be too picky
Anyway, Pusan's my hometown
Alright, so we're taking the gig
I'll call you later. Bye
Uh-huh
- Sung-hae!
- Huh?
- Happy birthday
- Thanks
Come by the salon sometime
I'll cut your hair real nice
for your present
- Really?
- Of course
Come to our gatherings
from now on
Bring your boyfriend too.
Okay?
Okay
Oh, yeah. You came with Ji-suk, right?
He told you about tonight?
Yeah
- So is it true he doesn't have a girlfriend?
- What?
Hey, how would I know?
Why?
Did he say he didn't?
Well, that's what he said.
But I think he has one
Hey, I really can't dance!
Whatever, it's easy,
just move
Yeah, stop being such
a goodie goodie
Go on! Get up!
Hey, sit, sit, here!
Don't they look
peachy together?
Actually, Sung-hae liked
Ji-suk back in junior high
That girl,
she's so cool now
But she was too shy to
tell him back then
Sung-hae has really blossomed
She used to
be a real geek
I always thought
she was pretty
Did you like her back then?
Hey, everyone thought I was
a goodie goodie, remember?
A goodie goodie is also a guy
We promised to
be 100% honest
Uh-huh
I may not be able to forgive ugliness
but I can forgive a past
It's okay, tell me
Um, when Sung-hae had her appendix
taken out and missed school
being the class president,
I did lend her my notes
Ji-suk, what are you reading?
Wanna borrow it?
When you're done
I'd really appreciate your notes!
That was my first kiss
I wasn't sure
Nope, I was even gonna
let it go
But honestly,
I'm really bummed out
Because Sung-hae
was my first love?
It just hit me
I'm a woman who
can't help myself
And you have no clue
about women
Are you mad?
You know, life's a bitch
See you
100% honesty, right?