Presented by IM Pictures
Produced by Shin Cine
In association with MVP Venture Capital
and Cinema Service
Jeun Jee-hyun Cha Tae-hyun
MY SASSY GIRL
Exactly two years ago today,
she and I buried a time capsule here.
We promised to meet here two years later,
but she hasn't come yet.
I'm going to wait.
Here we go.
Please don't move.
One, two...
Wait a minute.
Hello? Oh, auntie.
Sorry, I'm on my way.
I'm really sorry. Yes, I'm coming.
I'm having my photo taken. Bye.
Are you ready?
Here we go.
One, two...
My parents wanted a daughter,
so they raised me like one.
So I thought I was a girl until I was seven.
I had to go to the women's public bath, too.
The older I got,
I thought my penis would get smaller and disappear.
But it was the opposite.
First Half
He hasn't changed at all.
No, I'm a real man now.
Hey, asshole.
Think clerical work in the army makes you a man?
You irritate me!
Give me a break, asshole.
My job was tougher than you could imagine.
Hey!
I worked near the DMZ.
Who are you kidding?
Hold it. Anyway, welcome back home.
She's just my type.
When l see my type, I can't help it.
I need to hit on her.
Who's interrupting me?
Hello? Who is this?
- Your mother, you bastard.
- Oh, mom...
Why aren't you at your aunt's house?
I'm leaving soon.
Keep quiet! It's my mom!
Talk over there!
Make sure you pay a visit.
It's been over a year since you saw her.
That long?
You know she feels lonely
after losing her son last year.
She says you resemble him.
She'll be so glad to see you.
Still there?
We don't look alike.
Plus,
I hate when she rubs my face and kisses me.
Uncle does, too.
She'll introduce you to a girl. Hey!
I know the type she likes.
Tell her no thanks.
I want to meet a girl
like the ones in romantic comic books.
But on that day...
She's my type, but I don't Iike her.
Why?
Drunk girls disgust me.
Hey, get up!
Offer your seat to the elderly!
Ugh!
Go!
Hey.
Don't wear pink.
Honey!
She call him honey!
I'm not...
What are you doing!
You handle this!
I'm not...
Think I'm stupid?
Come here!
Are you laughing?
Why didn't you look after her?
Hurry and do something!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry. Let me help with cleaning expenses.
Forget it. Just take care of her.
Nothing's there when you need it.
Where did all those motels go?
I hate being with a drunk girl.
Carrying her on my back is worse.
Wow, your honey's wasted.
No, it's not my fault.
Of course, it is. I know everything.
You see, we're engaged.
Western or Korean style?
Give me any room.
Room 405.
None on the first floor?
Fourth floor!
You forgot to check in.
It's 40,000 won, kid.
What? 40,000 won?
Why? Find another place then.
Count it.
624... 770
Shindang-dong, Joong-gu... Seoul...
Hey, why do you keep reading this?
016... 228... 53...
Oh, please...
A thousand won Ieft!
Hello?
This phone's owner?
She's sleeping beside me.
What? Here?
The Uk-su motel near Bupyung station.
Better wash and leave fast.
Aha!
Hands in the air!
What are you doing?
Aaggh!
No, I'm not, sir!
I toId you. I'm an innocent victim.
Talk about it later and get in there.
Oh, damn! l'm gonna die mad!
Come over here. Come on!
Please forgive me just this once.
Please forgive me. I can't get in there...
How are you?
PIease, please save my life!
Hi? How are you?
Please just for once! Please...
See you!
What's your name?
Answer now! Boss told you!
Gyeon-woo, I'm Gyeon-woo.
What brought you here?
I'm innocent.
I'm telling the truth, sir!
So you're an innocent and we're fucking guilty, huh?
No, l don't mean that!
That's exactly what you said, Motherfucker!
I'm gonna put it right. I'm sorry.
You raped a girl, huh?
Nope! No!
Come on! Shoot now, you little creep!
You wanna cut your finger or talk now? Huh?
Be quick, He told you, you little bastard!
You turn against him, or what?
All of you.
Eat one a piece, okay?
Yes, boss.
What are you looking at? Look away.
Gyeon-woo! You're out!
Take care you guys!
Bye!
And remember to keep in touch!
Uh... Oh, yeah.
Don't just pass by us next time, all right?
Of course. See you.
Hey! You come over here.
Didn't I say eat one a piece!
I'm home.
Did you go to Bupyung?
Yes, I did.
Come here!
Where did you sleep?
Your aunt said you didn't come!
And you're telling me a lie!
What happened to your sweater?
l'm such a poor guy.
All this because of a drunk girl.
I wanna die.
You asked if I went to Bupyung!
I did, but not to see auntie!
What?
Bastard! Wait till he comes back.
Know me now, right? I'm a typical student.
An engineering major. Study?
I'm smart, but I never study.
My parents can prove that.
You're smart like me, but studying is your problem.
Since you inherited your brain from me,
you'll get good grades if you study harder, idiot.
Up four points in three years.
Call this a report card?
Since you inherited your brain from your mom,
you'll get good grades if you study harder.
If you raise kids, never tell them they're smart.
They'll never study.
My goals?
Haven't thought about it yet.
You know now?
You got it.
I'm a hopeless student.
Hello?
Who are you, asshole?
What? Who's calling?
Why were you naked in a motel with me?
What?
Come out!
To Bupyung station now!
Uh...
How could she do this?
I went to jail and got beaten with a vacuum for her.
Excuse me.
Is it you?
Yes?
Follow me.
Get over here.
What do you wanna eat?
Cherry jubilee...
Mango Tango or Shooting Stars...
Jamonka Almonds good, too.
I'll just have a Love Me.
Hey, wanna die?
Drink coffee.
Two coffees.
You pay for it.
Tell me.
What happened last night?
Well, it's...
You were drunk, so...
Don't stumble, and speak clearly!
You see.
You were drunk and staggering at the subway station.
I saved you from the train.
I thought maybe this girl was a snake.
Pretending to be drunk and vomiting
to use the guy in a state of confusion.
So I called you honey?
That's right.
I kind of remember that.
You showered to wash off vomit and sweat,
and the police came?
That's right.
Would you believe that, too?
To a girl like this,
you need to show her who's the boss.
So I did that, right?
Yes, you did.
- Sorry, it's late.
- Yeah...
When she's not drunk, she's just my type.
You look prettier and livelier than yesterday.
Are you mocking me?
No, I'm not.
Then are you hitting on me?
I don't wanna date you.
We're not destined for each other.
Throw the trash away.
Damn it.
I think she's a heavy drinker.
You order.
Kimchi soup and Soju, please.
Eat Golbangee.
Then you should order.
Stop pouting!
Golbangee, please.
Let's go somewhere fun later.
I know what that means.
- A motel? Are you rich?
- Of course.
How much will you give us?
We'll see, so don't worry.
You kids are prostituting, huh?
Why'd you order Golbangee? Eat something else!
What's it to you? Mind your own business.
We're just having a drink with some friends.
What's wrong?
You take friends to a motel?
How old are you kids?
Old enough to drink. Mind your own business.
Think I'm doing this 'cause you're drinking?
Show me your ID. You, too.
What's with you?
Show it, now.
This sucks.
She's a vicious chick. No matter how pretty she is,
I'm too embarrassed to be with her.
Who are you to butt in other people's business?
- Don't you have a daughter?
- I don't. Bear me one.
Who the hell do you think you are?
- How dare you?
- Come on, let's fight!
Come on! I'll show you.
Don't live like that!
Catch up with the girls.
Have a drink and calm down.
Shit!
Ah!
Seeing a girl cry makes me sad for some reason.
She's more attractive the closer I look at her.
Did you blow your nose on this?
No.
Please stop crying.
Also...
The handkerchief is mine.
To be honest,
I broke up with my boyfriend yesterday.
Excuse me.
Wake up.
Come on, wake up.
Your fiances wasted again?
What now?
Sign you in like before, right?
Yes.
But mister, have any medicine for alcohol?
No, you buy it.
Where did you go, honey?
- What! What is it?
- Uh!
I saw her lips.
Her white neck.
And...
I saw her breast, too.
While watching her sleep like a baby,
it may be forward, but this occurred to me.
I want to heal her sorrow.
Give me some water.
Hey.
Why am I here?
You see.
I'm sorry,
but I saw your ID, and you're twenty-four.
If you talk down on me again...
So what are you gonna do? Just that...
Nothing.
Give me the towel.
Yes. You see, I'm a year older.
- Then talk like friends.
- Yeah?
Toothbrush.
Toothpaste?
In the bathroom.
Our relationship is so peculiar.
We met only three days ago,
and slept twice in a motel.
That's how our relationship began.
Lee Hyung-chuI.
Here.
Jeun Mi-young.
Kang Man-gyu.
Yep.
Gyeon-woo.
Is he absent?
No, no!
I'm here!
Then answer right away.
Phew! Gonna be sucks!
Lee Jeung-min.
Here.
Gu SeoI-soo.
(In a dialect) Yes, I'm here.
Professor. How about a break?
You're right. Let's take a break.
Let's go.
Go where? Class isn't over yet.
Don't be a coward. He called roll, right?
Let's go.
I can't. I can't miss this class.
Kill me instead.
All right.
Who is she? She's pretty.
Pretty? Doesn't matter.
A girl needs to act pretty.
- But she's still pretty.
- Nice body, too.
Who's Gyeon-woo?
It's me, sir.
I won't mark you absent so you can leave.
Pardon me?
I said leave.
Why?
Wasn't that girl your girlfriend?
So go see her.
Thank you, sir.
Oh, Gyeon-woo.
If you can, raise it with her.
It worked.
What did you tell him?
That I'm getting an abortion, and you're the father.
What?
No, no! Professor, it's not true!
She wanted to be a scriptwriter,
so she kept writing stories.
She called them synopsis.
To get me into the mood,
she took me to the park to read them.
Reading her synopsis was stressful.
If I miss anything, I'm dead.
Wanna die? Finish reading it.
I will.
Mister! How could you throw the butt here?
Pick it up!
And why did you wear that color?
Then what about you?
Don't wear the same color as mine!
The heroine is tough, like the 'Terminator'.
The year is 2137.
Villains kidnap her lover and travels to the present.
I don't know why.
To save her lover,
she travels in a time machine to the present.
They have to kiss in the end.
This isn't a melodrama. It's an action movie.
You don't know movies.
Koreans like melodramas.
Why?
Know what novel touched us when we were teenagers?
Shower by Hwang Sun-won.
It shaped our people's sensibility in their teens.
Koreans like sad movies all because of 'Shower'.
Shower? What's sad about it?
It's sad when she asked
to be buried in the clothes reminiscent of her love.
I couldn't sleep for one week.
The ending sucks.
Gotta change it.
How?
It's sad.
Her family couldn't afford to pay for her medicine.
Their family line is broken up now.
But you know,
she must have been an extraordinary girl.
Why?
This was her last request:
"When I die, please bury me with my loving friend."
What?
To bury him alive, even.
Oh, my gosh.
- What's the matter?
- What's wrong?
No way!
This is wrong! This is wrong!
This is wrong!
Please. Don't!
Bury him!
They bury him alive. Isn't it sad?
I must be hurt still.
I think I'll never get over him.
How deep could it be?
I don't know.
Gyeon-woo, go in the water.
I wanna know how deep it is.
Come on.
Help me! Help me!
Wow, it's deep.
I can't swim!
Yes, it's deep...
My mind was getting blurry.
At that moment...
Heard you got a girlfriend.
Introduce me.
- Really?
- I'm serious.
Is she pretty?
Have you kissed her?
Girlfriend?
Gonna introduce me or not?
She really pretty?
What are you looking at?
See that girl over there?
She's my girlfriend from today. Got it?
Hey...
Excuse me...
Hey, baby.
- Are you free?
- Hey?
What?
Baby?
Hey! Come here.
Hmm!
How could a coincidence like this happen?
"Reportedly say
there is an accident of runaway soldier..."
Hello?
You call a wrong number or the dial is not in service.
Please, call again.
Let's drink. Drink till we die.
- 1 HOUR AGO -
It's me. Where are you?
What are you doing? Meeting your friends?
Can't I join us, can I?
Why not? I wanna see your friends!
Hey! Hey! Now, you're dead.
Excuse me...
You've just forgotten your things.
Oh my gosh! It's kind of you, thanks.
Do you want me to hold it for you?
- Oh no. That's all right.
- All right then.
I'll help you, ma'am.
- Oh, thank you.
- No problem.
Watch your step!
Hey, money!
Ooh! Damn it!
Since I'm drunk,
I decided to take revenge on her.
If I'm out cold at Bupyung station,
then she'll have to carry me on her back.
This stop is Bupyung station...
Hey, kid. Wake up. Wake up.
Where am I?
I'm at Inchon station. Be here in 30 minutes.
Wake up. Get up, idiot.
Go away, buttbrain.
Talking back?
- Get up, bastard!
- What the...
How're you?
Hi!
How are you?
Oh, how is it going?
What?
"Go away, buttbrain"?
You got a bad mouth.
I'll set you straight the gangster's way.
On your head.
Get up.
Sit down. Get up. Sit down. Roll right. Roll left.
Do it right. Keep going!
What's going on there? Stop fooling around.
Hey! You low-life thieves.
- What officer?
- Keep quiet.
Low-life thieves?
Damn it.
- Hey. Want some of this?
- No thanks.
Try it. It's delicious.
- No.
- Hey, boy.
Pay attention to your elders.
Eat it, buttbrain.
I told you no. How many times did I tell you?
Am I your toy? Leave me alone you petty thieves!
Stop toying with me, you jerks! It's humiliating!
Oh, shit!
Good morning.
- Keep quiet!
- Thank you. Thank you.
You bastard!
Do that again, and you're dead.
What?
"Are you free, baby?"
Your English is good, too.
Better behave!
Wanna die?
Taste good?
It's so delicious.
You're very happy to see me, aren't you?
Be good to me...
and you'll always be with good luck.
If I sleep out,
mom beats me with whatever's in her hand.
If she's sweeping, it's a broom stick
If she's cleaning, it's a vacuum.
When I'm lucky, it's a cucumber or eggplant.
So I have to come at the right time.
You studying now?
Yes, I'm.
I'm looking over something on the internet.
- Go to bed now.
- You too, dad.
- All right, good night!
- Good night.
Ok then, I'm gonna have a sleep too.
You're not looking at dirty pictures, right?
Of course not, dad. You don't trust me?
No, I do. Time for bed.
- Go to sleep.
- Good night, dad.
Uh?
Hi, Gyeon-woo. My birthday's in two days.
You're dead if you forget. Got it?
Since I like you so much, better make me smile like this.
* *
¦¬¦¬¦¬¦¬¦¬¦¬¦¬
Got it?
I got it.
Phew!
Her birthday.
If I prepare nothing, she may murder me.
I have a good idea.
Before going to the service, I worked in a theme park.
So this is my plan.
At midnight, I'll be alone with her in the park.
It'll be completely dark all around us.
One by one, the lights to the merry-go-round flick on.
I raise my arms up there, and her birthday song starts.
Then all the lights turn on and it moves.
There's fireworks, too. Isn't it fantastic?
She'll be thrilled.
I gave 200,000 won to my friends working there.
- Jump over here?
- Yeah. We have to.
I always wanted to come here at night.
It's my birthday, not yours.
Please, let's just try.
I'll go up first and help you.
Eh? There's a step here.
Take my hand.
Oh, shit!
Shit!
Gyeon-woo.
Hey!
Answer me. I'm Ieaving. I'm leaving.
Answer me! Gyeon-woo! You're dead.
Wait till I catch you.
Why didn't you answer?
Wanna die?
Come with me!
Hurry and get in.
Shut up!
Go in fast. Move it. Sit here.
If you're loud, I'll kill you. Got it?
Yes.
- Answer quietly!
- Yes.
Is that a real gun?
- Wanna see?
- Forget it.
How are you two related?
We're just friends.
Really?
You mean she could be my pussy?
What?
Your pussy?
I'm not a cat or anything! Go ahead and apolize!
Alright. I'll do it. I'm sorry.
Anyway, friends come here late at night?
Why are you here?
We just wanted to come here at night.
- Tell me the truth, idiot.
- Nothing special.
Bullshit.
What makes you trust a guy like him?
I trusted myself.
I had a girlfriend, too.
She visited me every week for one year.
I was so happy.
But that bitch fell in love with the guard house sergeant.
I found out the fact after he was discharged.
Damn it.
While I'm in the service,
even my dog ran away with some mutt, too.
My Yorkshire terrier.Bitch.
Fuck. I came out to kill both bitches. Fuck.
I have the worst luck in this world.
Damn it.
Know what special day is it today?
Huh, damn it? This sucks!
Hey, what are the odds
to meet a runaway soldier in a park?
Don't know.
Heard your head blows up if you shoot in the mouth.
Yeah, the hole in your head is this big.
That's serious. A teeny bullet does that?
Yeah, the bullet tears the...
Hey! What are you two doing?
Stop joking around.
Damn it. Damn it!
Even you bastards ignore me.
- That's why don't be foolish.
- Why am I foolish?
Even if you do this, she won't come back.
I know. l know, too.
But if I die, she'll be heartbroken.
She'll never be the same.
You're wrong.
The pain goes away sooner than you think.
You went through something like this?
Yeah. It happens that way.
Damn it. If I'm caught, I'll go to the can.
I'll always think of her there.
What does 'can' mean?
It means prison.
- Don't interrupt.
- Sorry.
Anyway,
you're responsible for your actions now.
Excuse me, sir.
How about letting her go?
If I say no?
Then...
...let me go, instead.
Come to think of it,
your eyebrows remind me of that sergeant.
You act like him, too.
You can go.
And you...
We die together. Got it?
Pardon?
Hey, lady. Forget about this bastard,
and look for a nice guy. Got it?
- Go!
- Let's go together.
All three of us.
Will you leave if I kill him?
Gyeon-woo. Don't worry too much.
This soldier isn't a bad guy.
You'll come out safely.
You're leaving me alone?
There's no other way.
I was afraid to die alone,
but I'm glad we're in it together.
Oh, right.
Over there,
there's an exit near the merry-go-round.
Nobody knows about it.
I used to work here.
Really?
You're not tricking me, right?
I'm a man, too. Why would I?
Walk in front of me.
See?
I told you so.
This way!
Shit!
What's going on? It's Gyeon-woo.
Screw you! Don't come closer!
I'll kill him! I'll really kill him!
Tell that bitch to come! So she can see me die!
I'll give you an hour!
If not, I'll kill him, and myself, too!
- Got it?
- Hurry up!
Sniper 2!
The hostage is in danger, but we can still fire.
Don't! Wait! Don't shoot!
Hey, soldier! I mean sir!
Your girlfriend changed her mind, right?
Did you really love her?
Ask yourself.
I think you didn't.
If you really love her,
you should let her go.
If not, then it's not love.
What's wrong with someone
you don't love getting married?
Stop this,
and go back to base as a real man.
A person like you should learn more about love.
If we want to learn,
then we should keep living.
Damn it.
She's the nicest girl I've met.
Hey! Don't Iet her go. Got it?
If you do, I'll take her.
- Can I go?
- Go. Screw it.
Shit! Don't know.
Thank you. Today's my birthday.
I'll live on until I learn what love is.
What?
"We're just friends"?
No, I said that to save you.
"Let me go, instead"?
Wanted to save yourself, huh?
He wouldn't have let you go.
Stop lying! Stop lying! Stop lying!
Have a nice life alone.
I screwed up her birthday,
but I feel good anyway.
'Cause I'm proud to be with her,
and things turned out as planned.
I hope you beIieve in me.
You can't?
Wait...
Second Half
I remember.
She always came with him until last year.
Was it last spring or winter?
One day,
she came alone with flowers to ask a favor.
To not let anyone sit in his seat that day.
What's up?
Oh, hi.
You're early.
I was in the neighborhood.
Miss me?
Of course!
She always tried hard to look cheery.
I like her that way.
- What would you like?
Coke, please.
Wanna die? Drink coffee.
Two coffees, please.
He he he
I know her.
She pretends to be happy,
but she's full of sorrow inside.
What are you doing?
What are you smiling at?
No. It's nothing.
Looks fun, huh?
- Another one?
- Why? Don't wanna read it?
She may get disappointed,
but I should be honest for her sake.
Looks fun. I'll read it.