Don't beg me, I won't come back.
I don't come to beg you.
What did you come for?
In fact, our situations are the same.
I was taken as Tiger's maid at 12.
I have been his concubine since I was 16.
I am the same as you.
I have had no romance before marriage.
How come? You are happy at least,
you are willing to marry him.
I am forced to do so.
These 20 years, I think I am happy.
I married a rich husband,
and have a good daughter.
After seeing your brother on stage.
I realize that I am cheating myself.
Actually, I need...
What do you need?
Love!
What! You are fond of my brother?
I know he is alive.
If you see you brother again.
Please give this letter to him.
Aren't you afraid of Tiger Lui?
For love, I fear nothing.
Mom, you are great!
You've won a girl's heart.
Actually, my brother is...
I know you are better than your brother.
Oh, it's you!
What do you want?
Nothing, I just want you to know that,
l, Tiger Lui is a man
of virtuous persuasion.
I don't want to make you
to be my son-in-law by force.
We should explore each other's merits.
Maybe, we shall find
we have many common interests.
Common interests?
- Right!
- Really?
I won't be angry.
Virtuous persuasion.
Why is it so noisy?
I want to be a man
of virtuous persuasion.
"I practise singing early in the morning"
"Beat the drum"
"Singing can help me to win a wife"
"It's great"
"Where's your mother?"
"The wrong thing she did
is to give birth to you"
"Beat the drum and be healthy"
"I am going to destroy this family"
"Your mother is not mine"
"Beat the drum"
"Singing can help me to win a wife"
"It's great"
"Your mother better not have you"
"Beat the drum and be healthy"
"I am going to destroy this house"
Your mom is not my mom.
My mom is not my mom.
You've gained weight.
I always eat, that's why I get fat.
Have you lost your virginity?
No!
That's better.
Do you want to escape?
I don't know you situation.
If I escape,
You might get into trouble.
Anyway, I am tailed by so many people.
I can't escape.
What a good boy.
I have checked the way of escape
when I entered.
I will save you tonight.
Then, we will burn our house.
They will think that
both of us are dead, right?
Then we will go to town for your dad.
Let's cheat them
for the rest for their live.
We'll never come back.
No one will know anything.
What?
Mom, you look so wicked.
Someone wants me
to send you this letter.
Who is it?
Your girlfriend.
Siu Wan,
I will meet an important guest tonight
with the governor.
I will be home late,
you'd better go to bed first.
Mom, dogs!
Nothing to be afraid of!
Did you offend the bitch?
Don't chase me!
It's horrible to be chased by the dogs!
Mom, run!
It's shit to be...
chased by the dogs!
This way!
Who is it? How dare you break into
the Lui's mansion?
Bite him!
Madam!
Stop!
Tai Yuk, it's you.
That's right! It's me.
Ask your fellow to leave me alone.
So they can't hear our talk.
Fine.
1, 2, 3, 4, go back.
Hurry up!
- Tai Yuk!
- Don't come over.
I am afraid I can't accept you love.
Since I received your letter,
I have been suffering thinking of you.
I can't stand it any longer.
So I come to see you now.
"The beauty put up the curtain."
"She sits with furrowed brows."
"One sees only the stain of tears."
"Who is it that she hates?"
Madam, this poem is
specially written for you.
He knows how to write a poem!
There is noise.
Madam, I have to go now.
See you later.
Tai Yuk!
Madam, what's the matter?
Nothing, why are you here?
Who asked you to come here?
It's wise to leave now.
It's you? It's me!
You?!
It's you!
Miss Chan,
have you also been
kidnapped by Tiger Lui?
Yes, how about you?
Me too!
I tried to find you
in the Playfield afterwards.
Me too! I waited for a long time.
You didn't come, so I left.
You mean you were waiting for me?
She waited for me!
Do you want this gold medal?
You always take this along with you?
I heard noise over there.
- Did you find anyone?
- Nothing!
I am afraid, I have to go.
Watch out, there are dogs.
If I leave like this,
I can never seen Miss Chan again.
Fong Sai Yuk is here, come and get him.
Fong Sai Yuk is here, come!
The purpose of my visit,
is to destroy the rebels
of the Red Flower Society.
I have got a clue that,
they'll appear in this town.
I hope, once you get any information
about the rebels,
come and inform me right away.
Yes, Sir!
Don't worry, I will try me best.
My heart is devoted to the Court.
Please take note of my efforts.
Help me!
What?
My husband returned from town yesterday.
He did not see his son
and got angry with me.
He punished me. Look, he beat me up.
He burnt my hand.
Alas! Poor me!
None of my business!
I just want you...
to let Sai Yuk meet his dad,
just one day will do, one day only.
If Mr. Fong really misses his son,
he may come and visit him.
Or, come and live here...
for as long as you like.
You are too cruel.
Well, I will kill myself in front of you.
Where is the wall?
Don't do that!
Master, just let Sai Yuk
come back for one day.
I don't believe she will
bump her head against the wall.
Let her try.
I'm sure she won't.
Okay, I will die in front of you.
Tai Yuk...
Tai Yuk...?
- Tai Yuk, mom is going to die.
- Don't...
- Master,
you are man of virtuous persuasion,
aren't you?
Don't!
A man of virtuous persuasion, right!
Take him home now,
bring him back tomorrow.
Thank you.
Master is here.
Mom, is dad back?
It is a lie.
Pack up,
we are going to look for your dad.
Okay!
He is back!
He has a dark face!
Freeze!
Why don't tell me about the wedding?
How can you be his mom?
I left for a few days,
and you lostom son.
How can I face our ancestors?
I...
Shut up!
It's none of his business.
I should be blamed.
Any way, I am no good as a wife.
I don't know how to teach my son.
I can't face you ancestors.
Let me die.
- Let me die...
- Mom.
Don't stop me, just where's the wall.
Don't!
Mom, it's your second time today.
Well, I have to do something first.
I will go see Tiger Lui tomorrow.
I am going to die.
Do you want to leave like this?
Why don't you save me?
You're heartless.
This is for you.
A razor!
It's for me!
It's for me to shave my legs.
Mom, it's raining.
Let's get an umbrella for your dad.
Yes!
Why is it raining so heavily?
Be careful!
Get an umbrella.
Mom, the rain has stopped.
Someone inside.
What?
Fine, don't cry!
Bastard!
Mom, don't get angry.
I don't want to live anymore.
Don't be silly.
You are pregnant.
They even have a child!
Don't worry.
I am responsible.
I will take care of him.
We are responsible too.
Bitch! So many men too.
All are involved.
Why should dad take
the responsibility alone?
If Fourth Brother
wasn't trying to save me.
Lok Ping wouldn't have lost her husband.
And I couldn't bring this list out.
Oh, dad is not having a mistress!
I am almost scared to death.
Mom, don't cry!
Who is it? Come out!
Don't go!
What kind of noise is it?
Firecracker!
- Firecracker?
- Yes!
See, you hands are trembling.
You don't seem to practise kung-fu.
Why did you join the rebels?
We work for different bosses.
To you, Chien Lung is good emperor,
to us, he isn't.
If only you hand me the list,
you will enjoy a prosperous life forever.
For my wealth,
I'd be giving up thousands of lives.
Even I am willing to do so,
my brothers won't let me do it.
Even if they are willing,
my family won't forgive me.
Of course we will forgive you.
Where is he?
Attack!
Dad!
To my mind, my dad is kind-hearted man.
So, I want to beat you.
Let's go!
How dare you bully my husband?
Go to hell!
Mom!
Watch mine.
Dad, where is the list?
Here it is!
No-Shadow Hands.
What are you doing?
Sai Yuk, save Lok Ping.
You mom can handle it.
Be careful!
Miss Lok, how are you?
Little hero,
help your dad to protect the list.
Don't worry, I won't let you down.
Good-bye!
Take care of yourself.
Son, we are leaving, take care of here.
Don't worry!
How dare you join a secret society!
It hurts!
Come on!
It doesn't hurt!
No?!
No, not painful indeed?
My dad used to hit me like this.
I tell you,
I used to hit my dog like this.
Bastard, an inch longer,
an inch stronger.
So, mine is short but powerful!
Where can you do?
See you!
Dad!
Sai Yuk, are you tailed?
Don't worry,
I haven't been
practising kung-fu in vain.
Where is mom?
Must have quarreled.
Mom, are you alright?
He has never treated me
that nicely before.
He recited 10 poems for me.
10 poems, great!
Leave me alone, stop bothering me.
Too smart!
How romantic!
Sai Yuk!
Dad has chosen his path,
so you and mom would have
a hard life from now on.
If I am having a good life alone.
How about the others?
Even I wish to do so,
others would object!
Even others are willing to do so,
how is my feeling then?
But if others...
and I agree, so what?
No matter what,
your choice is correct.
I will go with you all the way.
I don't know what you are talking about,
But l, too, will go along.
Since you have made up your mind.
Let's go to find Lui tomorrow.
It's dangerous!
The most dangerous place is safest place.
I understand!
What? You want to move to my home?
Right, actually I don't want to do so,
but my wife said,
you are a man of virtue.
Even my naughty son admires you so much.
I want to see for myself.
So I agreed to come...
and live here for a while.
To see how righteous are you.
I am a man of righteousness.
So help yourself.
I will let you stay
until you admit I am righteous.
Miss.
Meet your Father and Mother-in-law.
Go!
Honey, I miss you.
But I am not... She is your wife.
- It's you!
You are thin.
You are thin too.
Your son is really romantic.
It may be inherited.
Come on.
What's the matter?
This Mirror is our family treasure.
It's a present to you.
Thank you mom.
Since all of us are here.
Why not take this opportunity,
to celebrate their wedding tomorrow.
I am sorry...
It doesn't matter.
I am a man of righteousness.
Go ahead, until you think it's enough.
I don't have any friends in Canton.
Why not ask your relatives...
to join the wedding party?
Can you ask Tai Yuk to come along too?
It doesn't matter,
I am a man of righteousness.
I don't mind that!
Great!
It doesn't matter.
Let's rest now.
There will be many guests
coming to our party.
Let's take a good rest
to meet our guests tomorrow.
To be a righteous man.
Why don't your relatives or friends come?
Well, we do have a big family.
But they are all over the country
doing business.
I can't inform them about the party
in such a short time.
But you do have friends here?
Say, friends in the market!
Well, my dear father-in-law.
We grow the vegetables ourselves,
we needn't go to the market.
How about rice?
We grow our rice too.
How about your clients?
Aren't they your friends?
No, they aren't our friends.
If not,
I won't sell them bad cloth.
Or I charge them
with unreasonable prices.
Selling cloth is more or less
similar to running a brothel.
If a client wants to buy,
we are willing to sell.
It won't do to become affectionate.
So, we don't have friends.
Am I right?
Perfect!
Master, the Governor.
Finally, a guest! Show him in.
Don't panic, just the Governor.
The Governor!
- Brother Lui.
- Your Excellency!
His Honour, the Governor of Kau Mun.
Your Honour.
- This way please.
- Welcome...
Let's meet our guest together.
Come!
Your Honour, this way please.
Welcome...
Your Honour, my son-in-law,
and his family.
Take a seat, please.
This way please.
Good-bye!
Take a seat!
Your Honour!
Why are you sitting there?
Come and sit with us.
No, I think it's too crowded.
We'd better sit here.
Bull shit, join us.
Come on...
I dropped my money.
Where is it, let me help you.
Mister Fong, don't sit alone.
Come over...
Where is the money?
I can't find it.
When did you come?
I have just come over.
What is your son-in-law doing?
What are you doing? Get up!
The meat you love is coming.
Get up!
Mom,
towards you right.
Is he your son-in-law?
Mr. Lui,
didn't you tell His Honour
you are related?
Fong Sai Yuk is my son-in-law.
So, you are the one in-charged here?
Sure, I am the one in-charged here.
Give me the list!
Husband! Be careful!
Siu Wan!
Mom!
Ting Ting!
Where is the name list?
I am going to kill you.
Mom!
Let's fight!
Go!
Siu Wan...
Master, be careful!
- Go!
- Yes!
Take it back!
Burn the house.
Damn it. You son of a bitch!
I marry my daughter to you,
but you get my whole family into trouble.
Mr. Lui, it's not the fault
of young master.
Cut the crap, or I will kill you.
Let him go, or else...
You want to fight?
What do you want?
Young master, forget it.
Dad, mom's hurt bad.
Damn!
Siu Wan!
- Ting Ting!
- Mom!
Where is your dad?
Siu Wan, are you alright?
Hurry up...
Do you need a doctor?
I know what to do.
Leave me alone.
Don't touch her!
No! She is seriously hurt!
Siu Wan. Let's go!
Be careful!
Do you want me...
to take you to the doctor?
Save the crocodile tears.
Let's go our separate way from now on.
Dad, don't do that.
You are a stranger around here.
Are you leaving?
If not, you're no longer my daughter.
Ting Ting!
Go!
Go! Go now!
Sai Yuk, I feel so lost.
Mom, don't worry!
While the list is with us.
They won't do anything to dad.
I am going to town.
Be careful!
Sing!
Who is it?
Sai Yuk.
open the door now.
Come in!
I have seen the notice...
that my dad would be executed tomorrow.
Many people were caught because of us.
I come to see whether you are okay.
I am fine...
What's wrong?
Sai Yuk, I am sorry.
Sing, what'd happened?
Some officer took Bo and me
for questioning.
I said...
I didn't know you.
Where is Tai Bo?
He said I was a crowed.
He refused saying that
he didn't know you.
So he was beaten up.
The officers are tired,
they wanted Bo to kau-tow
before releasing him.
Bo refused.
Where is he now?
He was beaten to death.
And his corpse is
hanging at the East Gate.
Sai Yuk, forgive me.
I am scared.
I won't blame you.
I lost a friend,
I don't want to lose you.
Who is it?
What are you doing?
I came to collect his corpse.
Who are you? How dare you?
Fong Sai Yuk.
Fong Sai Yuk?
How dare you come here?
My friend is not afraid of death.
How can I be a coward?
I have come for his corpse.
- Attack.
- Yes!
Bo, let's fight together.
Kau-tau 3 times to my friend.
Please forgive us.
Bo, let's go.
Let us go!
Bo, you are my best friend.
Hope we'd be buddies in our next lives.
Young master, don't be so sad.
Macu, dad will be executed tomorrow.
What?
I must to save dad alone.
You take mom and leave early
tomorrow morning.
How can you go alone?
It's too dangerous.
Enough!
I have made up my mind.
Never let mom know this.
Macu...
Don't cry.
Let's go back,
mom is waiting for us.
Do you have any information
about your dad?
He'll be fine, don't worry.
Dad was rescued by Chan,
the Head of the Read Flower Society.
Really?
I won't cheat you.
Why didn't he come back?
Mr. Chan said,
it's not wise to stay together.
He'll meet you and Macu
at Puishi Beach tomorrow morning.
Isn't there a branch of
the Red Flower Society at Puishi Beach?
You dumb-bell, answer mom now.
Right, I went with Old Master a year ago.
What about you?
Mr. Chan asked me to take
this name list to Long Fu Hill.
And hand it to a Mister Chiu.
Are there any Mister Chiu
in Long Fu Hill?
Speak up...
Right, a year ago,
I met him once with Old Master.
We dined together.
He is a nice guy.
Am I right?
You are right!
Well, I don't have to worry anymore.
Go to hell!
Damn you Cantonese Bastards!
They say they'll fetch me the doctor.
But they told officers
to come and arrest me.
You Cantonese, all are bastards.
How are you?
Ting Ting...
I'm fine.
It's pouring get on board first.
I won't get on your boat!
I warn you, don't come to my side.
Dad!
Shut up!
Ting Ting.
She is seriously hurt,
why don't you help her to the boat?
Ting, go with them!
I'll stay here to keep your dad company.
Don't be proud at a time like this.
Damn it, you've said enough!
I said I would not go with you.
But I didn't say my family wouldn't.
Help her up.
Be careful!
Take care!
Take good care!
Take care of here!
Take care.
My God, what the hell did I do wrong?
Why do you treat me like this?
The Gods are punishing you for your sins.
I ask you once more,
are you getting into the boat?
No...
Hold it!
Mom...
Sai Yuk, take Ting Ting out for a while.
I want to talk with your mother.
Go now!
Madam, I have one thing to ask you.
What's the matter?
Where is Tai Yuk?
He is back!
"The Beauty pulls the curtain up."
"She sits with furrowed brows."
"One sees the stains of tears."
"Who is she crying for?"
Madam, it's me.
Tai Yuk!
Are you Tai Yuk?
Yes!
Tai Yuk, we can't live
together in this life.
But we'll be husband and wife
in the next life, yes?
Fine!
Madam!
Mom!
Siu Wan!
Although you scold me all day.
I am not angry with you.
you'd be my father-in-law now,
you'd be my father-in-law for life.
When you reach Puishi Beach tomorrow.
The officers can never get you.
Siu Wan!
After finish your mission,
come and join us.
Young Master. Take care.
Macu, why are you crying?
He's just going to deliver the name list.
He is not going to die.
I have caught a cold.
Cut the crap!
Hurry up, dad is waiting.
Yes!
- Sai Yuk!
- What's the matter?
Can you swear?
What?
Swear you'd never marry me.
Why?
Remember our bridal night?
What?
You swore that if marry me,
your family'd...
Would all die, I remembered.
No matter what happens,
I will marry you.
My husband used to kiss me like this.
Did your wife kiss you like this before?
Forget I said anything.
Jabber.
Wear this!
How about you?
I have this.
- You take this along!
- It's time to leave.
Take care.
Sai Yuk, take care!
Take a horse.
It's better than walking on foot.
Beware of catching cold.
Take some food!
You take care too.
I just want the traitors of
the Red Flower Society.
Give me the name list,
and you will be spared.
We Hans won't betray our friends.
If only you Manchus go back to Machuria,
we won't go against you.
The Ching government
has ruled over China for generations.
But you still refuse to face facts.
Look,
our country is stable and prosperous!
Listen?
Shut up!
Death to whoever make a noise.
I ask you, where are the men
of the Red Flower Society?
When there is air,
there are members of Red Flower Society.
How many can you kill?
Okay, I will kill as many as I can.
Kill him!
How poor!
Kill!
Here is the list!
Great!
I've become the member
of the Red Flower Society!
I'll live and die with the list.
Sai Yuk!
Don't come over.
Or I'll kill him!
Retreat!
You have guts!
Aren't you scared?
I am prepared to be killed.
Give me the name list,
and you will be spared.
then you and your dad will be released.
Sai Yuk, don't give it to him.
You should know how the wind blows.
Just give me the name list.
I can guarantee you a prosperous future.
Are you bluffing?
My dad won't forgive me,
my mom will kill me.
The citizens will scold me.
History will give me a bad name.
I won't betray my people!
Great!
You have guts, I like your kind.
If we are not serving different bosses,
we can be friends.
I'll give you a chance.
If you can defeat me
before the rope breaks,
I will let you father go.
If you lose, give me the name list.
I used 30% of my power last time.
I think you are so gifted in kung-fu,
that I want to introduce you
to serve our government.
But, I don't think
there is a chance now.
I know every kinds of boxing.
I want to make you my student.
Since you bullied my dad...
I don't think there is any chance now.
Luckily I am protected by the mirror.
Go to hell!
Take it!
Go now!
I won't go!
Sai Yuk!
I am happy to see you so grown up.
Just leave me.
Our country is waiting for you.
I feel at ease even if I have to die.
Go now!
What I can do, many people can do too.
But I have one dad.
Sai Yuk, go!
Dad, I want to die with you.
Fong Sai Yuk, I am coming to help you!
I come to help too!
Use some force!
"Fuck you!"
Kill them!
Husband!
Sai Yuk!
Mom is here to save you!
You foolish kid.
How dare you leave mom alone?
I want to help too!
Macu, why did you bring mom here?
I didn't.
There is a branch of the
Red Flower Society at the Puishi Beach!
What a coincidence.
Your big mouth is an oracle.
Take care of dad.
Go to hell!
Go to hell! Why don't you die?
Why don't you die?
Mister Chan!
Husband, are you alright?
I am fine, Save dad!
Dad!
Save dad.
Go now!
Mister Chan, you are really great.
I admire you so much.
But, my master said,
I have to bring you corpse back.
Super shoes!
Watch mine!
Mom!
Brother Fong,
I will take Sai Yuk as my God-son.
I will train him in Kung-fu too.
Thank you, Master Chan.
I leave my son to you.
Mister Damn!
Sorry!
Master Chan!
Take care of him please!
You have never left me
since you were a child.
Master, we've to say good-bye!
God father,
may I take Ting Ting with me?
Sure you can.
Are you willing...
to let your son join the triads?
What do you think?
Fine, just as you say.
Ting Ting, let's go.
Dad!
Sai Yuk, don't bully my daughter.
Or, I will beat you.
Don't worry, I won't bully her.
You should take me as an example.
To be a man of virtuous persuasion.
Yes Sir!
Dad!
May I beg you for one thing?
What?
I've never seen you smile!
Can you smile for me once?
Make it next year.
Sai Yuk, follow me.
Dad, you'd take care.
Let's go!
Sai Yuk, take care!
You'll be good to me, won't you?
"The beauty put up the curtain."
"She sits with furrowed brows."
"Only stains of her tears are seen."
"Who is she hating?"
Son, you dad laughs!
How romantic. I am so happy!
You've forgotten something! Catch it!
"Red Flower Society Name List"