That punk!
I'll be right back, boss.
It's so great eating meat
after so long.
Who do we have here?
Isn't it our brave police officer?
You have time for dating
despite your busy official work?
Are these the guys?
Huh?
Hey mister.
I got no business with you today,
why don't you sit down and eat.
Oh, sir! I am almost
scared to death now.
You're lucky to
have a man like him.
Such courage, huh?
Hey, say it again.
- Damn!
- Sit down!
What are you staring at?
Acting the man
in front of your babe?
What are you gonna do?
Don't worry,
we know them. Go on.
Do you really
wanna fight with me?
Sit down and drink.
I'm going crazy here.
And if I want to?
If I'm not careful,
I may end up killing you.
Stop!
You're really talking
nonsense here.
What to do with this little brat?
Boss, what do we do with him?
He seems to be
ignorant of manners.
Teach him what
manners are about.
Did you hear?
Sang-hwan!
You bastard!
Hey!
That asshole!
You stupid bastard! We'll...
Stay away!
Have a drink?
Let go!
Shithead!
Asshole...
Boss! Are you all right? Boss!
Let go, damn it! You shithead...
You have the right
to remain silent.
Stop!
You have the right to
choose a lawyer.
What the hell are you doing here?
Huh?
Come here...!
Damn!
Come here!
What did I do wrong?
Okay, I screwed up.
Let's drop it now, huh?
Didn't you teach me that crap
so I can catch bad guys?
Look, you listen carefully.
Some people dedicate
their lives to that crap.
We're not trying to
help you relieve your stress.
Then what about me, huh?
Do I look like I'm here
because I want to be?
- So do you feel better now?
- I feel great.
Yeah, you beat up those guys
like you wanted.
Since we have nothing left
for each other,
let's just split up
before things deteriorate.
And who was the one
that started all this?
I have no reason
to see you anymore.
And if you need to win so badly,
try winning over yourself first.
Can't even control your own self.
Hey!
Yeah? I don't need you anymore.
I'm leaving.
Sure, I can't do anything right.
But damn, the more I think of it,
the angrier I get!
Hey, what did I do wrong?
Where are you?
They started the whole thing!
Who are you, mister?
Did you come here to study, too?
Wait a second,
you're that jaywalker...
I said, where is Mu-un?
I told you he went
to the mountains.
That's not the answer I want.
Wait.
What are you doing here?
This guy here...
Sang-hwan, don't.
We're no match for his chi.
Hey, mister, what are you...!
Who are you, mister?
I ask the questions.
Eui-jin!
Sang-hwan!
You should not point
a sword at just anyone.
Stop!
Stop this right now!
Have you lost all decency?
Doing this to young kids?
Please, no more killing.
- I want the key.
- You monster!
You stay here.
He's wounded,
this is our chance.
We aren't strong enough.
Nonsense!
It's too dangerous alone!
Sang-hwan!
Let's stop wasting time.
Give me the sealed key, and the
Seven Masters need not fight.
You don't understand, do you?
In this day and age,
even with the power of Arahan,
do you think you
can rule the earth?
I just want to create order.
What order?
I have learned just one truth.
Only a supreme power
can guarantee peace.
You haven't learned that
power shifts with the wind.
You wretch!
Master!
Go back!
You'll feel better with some rest.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I shouldn't have challenged him.
It was unavoidable.
But was it you who wounded him?
No.
I think Sang-hwan used
Sound Vibration Technique on him.
Was that man one of
the vanished Seven Masters?
We have long called enlightened
male masters Maruchi,
and women masters Arachi.
Maruchi and Arachi, between
mortals and the enlightened,
were entrusted with the key to
attain the state of Arahan.
Arahan is an enlightened state
when one has nothing more to learn.
To be enlightened on the
principles of all creation,
also means you have the power
to rule over the world.
Such power may create desire
that leads to huge sacrifice,
so the Seven Masters kept it a
secret from anyone else.
The man who struck Mu-un
is one of those Seven Masters.
Long ago, a man who betrayed
heaven almost got the key.
People realized that when a
corrupt man seized hold of the key,
unstoppable chaos and evil
spread as a result.
Ceaseless greed made children kill
parents, brothers kill brothers.
And yet the enlightened masters
could not intervene in the world,
for it was against the
law of nature to do so.
Ordinary humans failed
in their quest for peace.
Hearing the cries of an orphaned
child, Heug-un broke the covenant
and rushed to intervene.
Ultimately the flames of war
consumed both worlds.
Seduced by the power of the sword,
Heug-un lost his self-control.
He decided to become Arahan
himself to bring order to chaos.
But the Masters knew that
Heug-un, full of rage,
would only re-start the
cycle of terror and misery.
Until they could find
a true Arahan,
they hid the key in their bodies,
and sealed Heug-un underground.
But unable to cast off ambition,
Heug-un endured in a wicked chi,
preserving his life
and returning to us now.
The weight of the key's
chi alone is so great
that no ordinary
Tao disciple can bear it.
For me, bearing the key
was no ordinary burden.
Now it's time that I
let go of this burden.
Welcome.
Pull over.
Eui-jin, I don't know
what to say, but...
Yeah, same here.
Seeing what happened to Master Mu-un,
it made me think a lot. But now...
I said pull over!
Go wherever you want.
Hey, Eui-jin!
Hey.
Have you gone mad?
He may just be
another person to you,
but to me, he's a father.
Then what am I?
Sang-hwan,
don't you get it?
Do you still think
you can become Maruchi?
If you're not joining in,
will you let go?
It was nice knowing you.
This is just too much.
It seems we've
a long way to travel.
Let's have some tea.
It must have been hard,
hiding it all this time.
I'm sorry, but I don't
have the key either.
Jeez, what am I supposed to do?
Hey, wait up!
Excuse me.
First of all...
should we call the
insurance company?
Hey, your hand's bleeding!
Hold on, let go.
Give me the glasses.
Wait, okay okay...
Wait... you should calm down first.
Wouldn't you be upset?
I know how you feel, but this is
something you've trained for.
What?
You said to control oneself!
Let's not get worked up.
At times like this,
we should try thinking calmly.
That guy wants the key, right?
Your dad doesn't have it.
All the other Masters were
eliminated because of it!
That's why there's hope.
Think about it.
He must think your father is the
last one who knows where it is.
Would he just kill someone
like that? No way!
Don't worry.
Then where do we find him?
Now, that's a problem.
Are you going to keep
talking nonsense?
Dammit!
I'm trying too.
Are you the only one with a temper?
This bugs the hell out of me,
I'm worried too!
If those who wish for enlightenment
get a key and stand on this altar,
the path to Nirvana opens.
Eui-jin...
Wasn't the key
connected to this place?
The meridian points
in your body are blocked.
You'll die unless I take
emergency measures.
Don't be stubborn,
surrender the key.
Freedom from attachment
means freedom from fear.
I'll take on Heug-un,
you look for my father.
And then run far away.
- I'll join you soon.
- Wait, Eui-jin!
Cripes, she's got
no sense of strategy.
I'm telling you, girls should
serve in the military too.
Jeez, are all
museums this complicated?
Impressive that you
found me, wench.
I know you've been
out of touch,
but it's not nice to call
a lady a "wench," asshole!
Where is he?
Hey, you!
Concentrate.
Are you in the
broadcasting room?
I don't know where I am, either.
Then how can I find you?
Heug-un has corrupted my chi.
Don't just use your eyes,
open your five senses.
Oh, darn.
Okay then.
I'm not sure where you are,
but... just stay there for now.
Dammit!
This way?
Spread the chi around you.
Prepare for the attack!
Concentrate the chi
into a point of light!
Master!
Master...
Can you feel my chi?
Who told you to come here?
I'm telling you,
you have no sense of strategy.
What?
Hey, jaywalker!
Cool, huh?
I'm the one you want.
Let's rumble.
Master Heug-un.
Without renouncing attachment,
the key leads to self-destruction.
Times have changed.
Let's leave the key
with these youngsters.
A sword can slaughter a pig,
or cut through the world.
Power comes to
the man who can wield it.
Renounce all...
The things we see are just the
shadow of things we can't.
Renounce all...
One who aspires to be Maruchi
must renounce all his desires,
and the door to
enlightenment will open.
The moment you renounce yourself,
you feel a true freedom
that exists between earth and sky,
it is then that you
can command gravity.
In the act of going,
you find understanding.
And in the constant practice,
you find enlightenment.
The moment that
you command your ego,
the gate of
Arachi's heart will open,
and you will become Maruchi.
What's all this blood?
Hey, mister!
My stomach hurts!
That key doesn't
seem to fit you.
And you're in
the wrong spot!
Tired already, mister?
Another round?
Give up, you...
But know this...
Nature did not
abandon the world,
it is the world that
abandoned nature.
The tao never
abandoned people,
it was people
who abandoned tao.
As long as there is a path,
there will be people following it.
Eui-jin! Eui-jin!
Hey, wake up!
- Eui-jin, bring me the dye.
- Yes.
Can you empty this?
Yes.
Excuse me!
I'll just run to the bank...
Huh, it's the police!
You guys are such a pain.
You're breaking my heart.
Freeze!
Bong... Officer Bong!
Officer Bong!
Are you okay, Officer Bong?
Corporal Yoo, I tried my...
When are you gonna
learn to shoot a Palm Blast?
Hey, let's see you try it
at a moving person!
Try doing it just like before.
Look!
Look over there. You shot
at him, and what happened?
Haven't you learned...
I was looking over here!
Look what happened
to Officer Bong!
You learned it way before me,
can't you do it right?
Hey, I usually do fine.
You wanna see?
Anyone can do it in practice.
It's real situations that count.
Did you see me shoot back there?
Yeah, I saw it.
You think you're good, but...
Just quit it, okay?
Shouldn't you take him
to an acupuncturist?
That kid Sang-hwan called.
There will be a police raid today.
A raid?
See you later, Dad!
Eui-jin, wait!
Is this place illegal?
Oh, don't worry.
We were recommended this place.
They're better than Hippocrates!
Sang-hwan said there
will be a raid today.
Anyway, go to the storehouse
and take some of the
cheapest aphrodisiacs to him.
Jeez, I'm busy today!
Careful on your way home at night...
Why are there so many raids?