Random thoughts
for Valentine's Day, 2004.
Today is a holiday invented
by greeting card companies...
to make people
feel like crap.
I ditched work today.
Took a train out to Montauk.
I don't know why.
I'm not an impulsive person.
I guess I just woke up
in a funk this morning.
I gotta get my car fixed.
Hi, Cindy?
It's Joel... Joel!
Listen,
I don't feel very well today.
No,
food poisoning, I think.
It's goddamn freezing on this beach.
Montauk in February.
Brilliant, Joel.
Page is ripped out.
Don't remember doing that.
It appears this is
my first entry in two years.
Sand is overrated.
It's just tiny little rocks.
If only I could meet someone new.
I guess my chances of that happening
are somewhat diminished,
seeing that I'm incapable of making eye contact
with a woman I don't know.
Maybe I should
get back together with Naomi.
She was nice.
Nice is good.
She loved me.
Why do I fall in love
with every woman I see...
who shows me
the least bit of attention?
Hi.
I'm sorry?
- I just said hi.
- Hi. Hello. Hi.
Okay if I sit closer?
How far are you going?
Uh, Rockville Center.
Get out! Me too!
- Really?
- What are the odds?
Do I know you?
Do you ever shop
at Barnes & Noble?
- Sure. Sure.
- That's it!
- Yeah?
- I've seen you, man!
Book slave there for,
like, five years now.
- Ah. I would have thought I would've remembered you.
- Jesus! Is it five years?
It might be the hair.
- What might?
- It changes a lot.
The color.
That's why you might not recognize me.
- It's called Blue Ruin, the color.
- Right. Yeah.
- Snappy name, huh?
- I like it.
Yeah.
Anyway, this company makes a whole line
of colors with equally snappy names.
Red...
Red Menace, Yellow Fever, Green Revolution.
That'd be a job,
coming up with those names.
You think there could
possibly be a job like that?
I mean, how many hair colors
could there be? Fifty, maybe.
Someone's got that job.
Agent Orange!
I came up with that one.
I apply my personality in a paste.
Oh, I doubt that very much.
Well, you don't know me, so...
you don't know, do you?
Sorry. I was just...
I'm trying to be nice.
Yeah. I got it.
- My name's Clementine, by the way.
- I'm Joel.
- Hi, Joel.
- Hey.
No jokes about my name.
Oh, no, you wouldn't do that.
You're trying to be nice.
I don't know any jokes about your name.
Huckleberry Hound.
I don't know what that means.
Huckleberry Hound?
What are you, nuts?
It's been suggested.
Oh, my darlin', oh, my darlin'
Oh, my darlin' Clementine.
You were lost and gone forever
Dreadful sorry Clementine
No?
I'm sorry. Just... It's a pretty name, though.
It really is nice.
It's, uh...
It means "merciful"
Right? Clemency?
Although it hardly fits.
I'm a vindictive little bitch,
truth be told.
Gee,
l-I wouldn't think that about you.
- Why wouldn't you think that about me?
- I don't know.
I just...
I don't know.
I just, uh...
You seem nice, so...
Oh, now I'm nice?
Oh, God.
Don't you know any other adjectives?
I don't need "nice"
- I don't need myself to be it,
and I don't need anybody else to be it at me.
- Okay.
Joel?
It's Joel, right?
Yes.
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
I'm a little out of sorts today.
My embarrassing admission
is, I really like that you're nice right now.
I mean, I can't tell from one moment to the next
what I'm gonna like, but...
right now...
I'm glad you are.
I have so much stuff that, uh,
I probably should, uh...
- Oh! I'm sorry. Okay.
- L-I'm writing, and...
- No, no. I just...
- Sure. No. That's okay.
- I just have... You know, this is...
- Okay.
- Ohh! Hey!
- Take care, then.
Jesus!
Hi. I could, uh,
give you a ride, if you need.
It's cold.
- Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
- Yeah?
It is frosty.
- You're not a stalker or anything, right?
- I'm not a stalker.
You're the one that talked to me.
Remember?
That is the oldest trick
in the stalker book.
Really?
There's a stalker book?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
I gotta read that one.
Look, I'm sorry if I came off
sorta nutso. I'm not, really.
Oh, it's okay.
I didn't think you were.
Did you wanna have a drink?
I have lots of drinks,
and I could, um...
Um...
Never mind.
- Sorry. That was stupid. I'm embarrassed now.
- No, no, no, no.
Good night, Joel.
Two Blue Ruins.
Thank you.
Drink up, young man.
It'll make the whole seduction part
less repugnant.
I'm just kidding!
Come on.
You're kinda closed-mouthed,
aren't you?
I'm sorry.
It's just, you know,
my life isn't that interesting.
I go to work, I come home.
Don't know what to say.
You should read my journal.
I mean, it's just... blank.
Really?
Does that make you sad or anxious?
I mean, I'm always anxious, thinking I'm not living
my life to the fullest, you know...
taking advantage of every possibility,
making sure I'm not wasting one second
of the little time I have.
- I think about that.
- Yeah?
You're really nice.
- Ohh!
- God, I have to stop saying that.
I'm gonna marry you.
I know it.
Um... okay.
Joel, you should come up
to the Charles with me sometime.
It gets frozen this time of year.
- That sounds scary.
- Exactly.
I'll pack a picnic.
A night picnic.
Night picnics are different.
And, um, we could...
Sounds good.
But I... I should, uh, go.
Now.
You should stay.
No, I really... I'm... I...
I have to get up so early.
I would like you to call me.
Would you do that?
I would like it.
Yes.
Wish me a happy Valentine's Day
when you call!
That'd be nice.
What took you so long?
I just walked in.
Mm-hmm.
You miss me?
Yeah.
Oddly enough, I do.
Oh!
You said "I do."
I guess that means were married.
I guess so.
Tomorrow night?
Honeymoon on ice?
It's really solid this time of year.
Whoa! I don't know.
- Come on. Come on.
- Eee!
Come on.
Come on, come on.
Whew.
Oh. So beautiful.
Isn't it?
Uh, don't go too far.
- Whoo! Oww! Ow!
- Whoa! Oh!
- Are you okay?
- Ouch! Fuck it.
Ohh! Oh, my ass!
- I think I should go back.
- Come on. Come on!
What if it breaks?
- "What if"? Do you really care right now?
- Huh?
Come here. Please.
Come on.
- Ohh.
- Ooh-hoo-hoo-hoo!
- Slidy-slidy. Slidy-slidy.
- Whoa!
- This is good.
- Here, let me show you this one thing.
- What are you doing?
- Whoa.
Come on.
Think I heard a crack.
It's not gonna crack or break or...
It's so thick.
Show me which constellations you know.
Um... Oh.
I don't... know any.
Show me which ones you know.
Okay.
Oh. Here's Osidius.
Where?
Right there.
See?
Sort of a swoop and a cross.
Osidius the Emphatic.
- You're full of shit. Right?
- Nope.
Osidius is right there.
Swoop and cross.
Shut the fuck up!
Clementine.
Cock-a-doodle-doo.
- Hey.
- Sorry to wake you, but we're... here.
Ahh.
Can I come over to your house...
to sleep?
I'm so tired.
Okay. Um, yeah. Sure.
- Let me get my toothbrush.
- Yeah. Oh.
Just...
Yes?
- Can I help you?
- What do you mean?
Can I help you with something?
No.
What are you doing here?
I'm not really sure
what you're asking me.
Oh.
Thanks.
"I need your lovin'"
"Like the sunshine"
"Everybody's gotta learn sometime"
- We're looking for 159.
- What number's that?
I don't know where that is.
Jesus Christ, you'd think they'd light the number,
or at least put a number on...
- Is that him?
- I think so.
Yeah, that's him.
Wait. That's him.
- Hey, Joel.
- Frank.
Oh, shit.
Jesus. The only Valentine's Day cards I get
are from my mother.
How pathetic is that, huh?
You're lucky you have Clementine, man.
She is way cool.
Hey,
you got any big Valentine's Day plans with her?
No.
Well, it's only a day away.
Better make some reservations or something.
Don't want to end up at Mickey D's. Right?
McRomance!
You want some fries with that shake?
I have to, uh,
go to sleep now, Frank.
It's 8:30.
Ohh! Okay.
Okay. Okay.
Whew. Okay.
Showtime at the Apollo.
Shh, shh, shh. Hey.
Quiet.
Hey, Joel. What's up?
Oh. Hi, Frank.
I only get Valentine's Day cards
from my mom.
How pathetic is that?
You're lucky you have Clementine, Joel.
Hey, you got, uh, any, uh,
big Valentine's Day plans with her?
No.
It's only a day away.
Better make a reservation or something.
Don't wanna end up at Mickey D's.
Oh, no!
Yes! You know, Valentine's Day is three
goddamn days away! I want it resolved.
I'm willing to be the one to resolve it.
So I call her,
and she's changed her number.
So I walked over to Antic Attic,
you know, to get her something.
I thought you know, I'd go over to work,
give her an early valentine, and...
You won't believe it.
She's there with...
this guy,
this really young guy.
And she looks at me
like she doesn't even know who I am.
Excuse me?
Can I help you find something, sir?
Hey, Clem-ato.
Patrick! Baby boy.
- What you doing here, baby?
- Just came to surprise you.
Let me know if you need something, sir.
You look good.
- How are you?
- Pretty good. Pretty bored. Pretty tired.
Uh-huh.
- I so want what's in your suit.
- Oh, good.
Why?
Why would she do that to me?
Hey, does anybody want a joint?
Oh, God, Rob, give it a rest.
Oh, God.
She's punishing me.
- I know, honey.
- For being honest.
- It's horrible.
- I should just go to her house.
No! No, no, no.
You don't wanna go there, man.
You don't wanna go there.
Get off. It's too...
- Right.
- Yeah.
I don't want to seem desperate.
Joel, why don't you just see this as a sign,
make a clean break. Right?
Right?
All right, Joel,
look, man, seriously.
- Rob!
- Here's the deal.
Don't do that. Rob, what are you doing?
No, no, no, no.
What's your fucking suggestion, Carrie?
What's your brilliant, reasoned solution?
You're gonna make this about our shit now?
This isn't about us.
I agree. It's not about us.
It's about Joel, who's an adult, okay?
Not Mama Carrie's kid.
What are you...
That's your laundry!
That's great.
That's good.
Okay.
- What is it?
- I don't know. It's some place that does a thing.
Good morning. Lacuna.
No, I'm sorry.
That offer expired after the new year.
Yeah, sure.
We can fit you in...
How about on the fifth?
That's a Wednesday. All right, great.
Could you spell that, please?
Okay, and we'll need
a daytime phone number.
Great. Have a nice day.
See you then.
May I help you?
- I'm Joel Barish.
- Excuse me?
I'm Joel. Barish.
I have an appointment with Dr...
Mierzwiak.
- Here. Could you please fill this out?
- I just want to talk to him.
- You still need to fill the form out, sir.
- Really?
- Thank you.
- Great.
I don't have a pen.
There's a pen right there.
- Good morning. Lacuna.
- Oh.
Oh, yeah, that offer. That's done now.
That expired after the new year.
Mr. Barish?
How are we today?
Not too good, actually.
- Boo!
- Oh, my God! Stan!
- Sorry. Sorry, I was just...
- I'm working!
Sorry. Sorry.
- Here, Doctor.
- Thank you.
You should not have seen this.
I apologize.
This is a hoax, right?
I mean, this is Clem...
I assure you, no.
Mm-mmm.
There's no such thing as this.
Look, our files are confidential,
Mr. Barish,
so I can't show you evidence.
Suffice it to say that Miss, uh...
Miss Kruczynski was not happy,
and she wanted to move on.
We provide that possibility.
"Miss Kruczynski was not happy
and wanted to move on.
We provide that possibility."
What the hell is that?
Nicest guy she ever went out with.
Oww! Fuck!
God, Rob! Give it a rest!
It's okay.
It's all right.
Carrie,
I am making a birdhouse.
What can I say, Joel?
You know Clementine. She's like that.
She's impulsive.
She decided to erase you
almost as a lark.
A lark.
Why? Why? Why?
Why did you do that?
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
I'm sorry, Doctor.
He just barged right in here.
Okay. I want it done.
I told him pre-Valentine's Day is our busy time.
- Oh, th-th-that's... that's okay, Mary.
- But there are people waiting.
Mr. Barish, if you'd like to, uh...
to come inside.
- And, Mary, if you could take care of Mrs. Woo.
Good-bye, Mrs. Woo.
- Yes, of course.
Now, the, uh...
the first thing
we need you to do, Mr. Barish,
is to go home...
and collect everything you own
that has some association with Clementine.
Anything.
And we'll use these items to create
a map of Clementine in your brain.
Okay?
So we'll need, uh,
uh, photos, clothing, gifts,
books she may have bought you,
CDs you may have bought together,
journal entries.
We want to empty your home...
We want to empty your life
of Clementine.
And after the mapping is done,
our technicians will do the erasing
in your home tonight.
That way, when you awake
in the morning,
you'll find yourself in your own bed
as if nothing had happened...
a new life awaiting you.
Wake up, buddy!
No, I'm sorry, Mrs. Sobel.
You can't have the procedure done
three times in one month.
Well, it's just not our policy...
How are you today, Mr. Barish?
Hello. I'm right here.
I know it's an emergency,
and we'll do everything we can...
We can fit you in on the first of March.
Maybe you could talk to the doctor,
a- and he...
All right, so let's make an appointment.
What day would you like to come in this week?
- Mr. Barish.
- Um, he's really busy this afternoon.
Maybe tomorrow would be better.
Around 12:15? Can you do that?
February is very busy for us
because of Valentine's Day.
This is, uh, Stan Fink,
one of our most experienced
and skilled technicians.
He'll be handling
your case tonight.
Great to meet you,
Mr. Barish.
My name is Joel Barish,
and I'm here to erase
Clementine Kruczynski.
Very good.
Now, tell me about, uh, Clementine.
Uh, I was...
living with this woman, Naomi,
uh, a couple years ago,
and my friends Rob and Carrie
invited us to this party at the beach...
I don't like parties.
Naomi couldn't go, but I went...
and I, uh, met Clementine.
I'm sorry.
Let's start with
your most recent memories...
and work backwards from there,
more or less.
There's an emotional core...
to each of our memories,
and when you eradicate that core
it starts its degradation process.
By the time you wake up
in the morning,
all the memories we've targeted
will have withered and disappeared,
as in a dream upon waking.
Is there any risk of brain damage?
Well, uh, technically speaking,
the procedure is brain damage,
but it's on a par with
a night of heavy drinking.
Nothing you'll miss.
Comfortable?
What we're doing here, Mr. Barish,
is actually creating a map of your brain.
Okay, let's get started.
If we want to get
this procedure underway tonight,
we have some work to do.
I want you to react to these objects, Mr. Barish,
if you will.
There's a good story behind this one...
Uh, actually, Mr. Barish,
I'll get a much better emotional readout...
if you refrain from any sort of
verbal description of the items.
Just try to focus on the memories.
Oh. Sorry. Okay.
Healthy activity up there again.
Healthy readouts. Very good.
- Here's another object.
- That's so...
Next item. Okay.
Potato head.
Just focus on the memories.
Patrick, do me a favor.
- Hey, Patrick, do me a favor, will ya?
- Yeah.
Can you check the voltage regulator?
What do we got there?
- Uh, voltage looks fine.
- Really?
Well, I'm not wiping as clean as I like here.
I'm...
Well, uh, technically the procedure
is brain damage.
Check the, uh...
Check the connections, please.
Oh, there you are.
I...
Why am I...
I don't understand what I'm looking at.
Why am I
standing here and...
Oh, my God.
Déjà vu.
This is so...
All right, we should get started.
If we're gonna get the procedure...
Underway tonight,
we have some work to do.
I'm in my head already,
aren't I?
I suppose so.
Uh, this is about right.
This is what it...
This is what it would look like.
Very good.
We'll dispose of these mementos
when we're done here.
That way you won't be confused later
by their unexplainable presence in your home.
Ah, there we go.
- Patrick?
- Yeah?
- Patrick, can you check...
- Patrick?
- I'm getting some sort of readout of my own voice.
- Patrick? Patrick?
- Why are there so many wires?
- A lot of equipment.
- Does that help?
- Are you sure you set that thing up properly?
- How's that?
- How are you today, Mr. Barish?
- There we are, Mr. Barish.
- That's better.
- I don't know if I like this.
- Think I might try this, then.
We're almost done now.
Mmm. Journal.
That would be invaluable.
"I met someone tonight.
I don't know what to do.
Her name is Clementine,
and she's amazing."
- Whoa!
- Jesus!
- What? What?
- Come on! Careful! Step back!
Just take it easy.
That's fine.
Let's not roach the guy.
All right, you got that one.
- This place is sort of a dump, don't you think?
- It's an apartment, Patrick.
Patrick.
Well, not a dump, then,
but sorta plain. Uninspired.
And there's sort of
a stale smell.
Patrick, can we just please
get through this?
- We got a very long night ahead of us. Come on.
- Yeah. Yeah.
This is the last time I saw you.
It's 3:00.
I kinda sorta wrecked your car.
Were you driving drunk?
It's pathetic.
I was a little tipsy.
Don't call me pathetic.
Well, it is pathetic.
- It's fucking irresponsible. Could've killed somebody.
- Oh, God.
- I don't know... Maybe you did kill somebody.
Should we turn on the news and see?
- Oh, Christ!
- Should I check the grill to see
if there's any children or small animals?
- I didn't kill anybody!
It's just a fucking dent, Joel.
You're like an old lady or something.
Well, what are you like?
- A wino?
Jesus,
are you from the '50s or something?
A wino?
Face it, Joely.
You're freaked out because
I was out late without you,
and in your little wormy brain...
you're trying to figure out,
did she fuck someone tonight?
No, see, Clem,
I assume
you fucked someone tonight.
Isn't that how you get people
to like you?
I'm sorry. Okay?
Clem, I didn't mean it.
All right?
- Clem?
- Your keys.
- I was just... I was just...
- I won't need them anymore.
Angry or annoyed or something,
I don't know.
Clem?
Mary's coming over tonight.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Just thought you'd wanna know.
I like Mary. I like when she comes to visit.
I just don't think she likes me.
She likes you okay.
So... Maybe I should invite my girlfriend over.
I have a girlfriend now.
- Do whatever you want.
- Did I tell you I have...
Yeah.
Did I tell you
I have a new girlfriend?
We gotta focus here,
Patrick.
Yeah, the thing is,
our situation is...
is a little weird.
My girlfriend situation.
I'm sure it is.
You gotta be...
Clem, let me drive you home.
Get out of my face, faggot!
Look at it out here!
It's all falling apart!
I'm erasing you, and I'm happy!
You did it to me first!
I can't believe you did this to me.
Goddamn it.
Clem! Can you hear me?
By morning you'll be gone!
The perfect ending
to this piece-of-shit story!
Is there something wrong
with a girl being attracted to me?
Is that a problem?
No, I think it's... funny.
So, who do you think's better-looking,
me or this guy?
Patrick, let's focus, buddy.
Remember that girl
we did last week?
The one with the... potatoes?
That girl?
Yeah, that... that's this guy's girl.
- Right.
- Yeah.
Was. We took care of that.
- Oh, God!
- Well, uh...
I kinda fell in love with her that night.
What? You little fuck...
- What?
- She was unconscious, man.
Well, she was beautiful, and...
I stole a pair of her panties as well.
- Jesus!
- What?
It's not like...
- I mean, they were clean and all.
- Don't tell me this stuff, man!
I don't wanna hear this shit!
- They were clean!
- What? D-Don't! Stop!
- Okay. Yeah! All right!
- We got work to do.
There's, um...
There's more.
After we did her, I kind of...
went to where she works
and asked her out.
You what?
- Jesus.
- Jesus, Patrick!
Do you have... any idea...
how unethical...
It's not really that bad.
What? Get that look off your face.
What's wrong?
Patrick, you stole a girl's panties!
There's someone here.
He stole your underwear.
I don't see anyone.
Joel?
Where are my boots?
"Why are you showing me poisons?
Can't you understand English?"
"Potions, I said. Potions."
"Love potion, please."
I'm fucking crawling
out of my skin!
Should've left you at the flea market.
"First thing to do is...
Sift in a cup of powdered whale heart."
Wanna go?
I want to have a baby.
Let's talk about it later.
No! I want to have a baby.
I don't think we're ready.
You're not ready.
Clem, do you really think
you could take care of a kid?
What?
I don't wanna
talk about it here.
I can't hear you. I can never the fuck understand
what you're saying.
- I don't wanna talk about this!
- Fucking ventriloquist!
- We're fucking gonna talk about it!
- I... don't... want... to...
You can't just say something like that
and say you don't wanna talk about it!
- I'm sorry, Clem.
- I'd make a fucking good mother!
- I love children, I'm creative and smart,
and I'd make a fucking great mother!
- Oh, God... Mmm!
It's you, Joel.
It's you who can't commit to anything!
- It's going! It's going!
- You have no idea how lucky you are
I'm interested in you!
Maybe I should end this right here, Joel!
- Leave you at the flea market
with this stupid costume jewelry!
- It's done. This is crap.
- Maybe you could find yourself
an antique rocking chair to die in!
- All the pain, confusion...
- Oh. Hi, Patrick.
- Hi, Mary. How's it goin'?
- Hey, you.
- Oh, it's freezing outside.
- Find us okay?
- Yeah.
- Mmm.
- Hot!
Poor guy.
Mmm? Oh.
Don't you have anything real to drink?
Uh, we haven't really checked... yet.
- Patrick?
- Uh, yeah.
Uh, let me do the honors.
Mary hates me.
Never really had much luck
with the ladies.
Maybe if you stop
stealing their panties.
- There's more.
- No!
- Yes.
Hey, hey!
Oh, you didn't want any,
did you, Patrick?
- Uh, no, that's okay.
- Wait.
"Blessed are the forgetful,
for they get the better even of their blunders."
Oh.
- Oh!
Mmm!
That's Nietzsche.
Beyond Good and Evil.
I found it in my Bartlett's.
What's your Bartlett's?
It's a quote book, Patrick.
It's a book of quotations.
I think Howard will be in Bartlett's one day.
Definitely.
Howard is pure Bartlett's.
Can you wake him up?
You can't wake him up.
Mmm.
You don't tell me things, Joel.
I'm an open book.
I tell you everything.
Every damn embarrassing thing.
You don't trust me.
Constantly talking
isn't necessarily communicating.
I don't do that.
I want to know you.
Hmm?
I don't constantly talk.
Jesus!
People have to
share things, Joel.
Mm-hmm.
That's what intimacy is.
I'm really pissed
that you said that to me.
I'm sorry.
It just... really just
isn't that interesting.
I wanna read some of those journals
you're constantly scribbling in.
What do you write in there
if you don't have any thoughts or passions or...
Iove?
November 19, 2003.
Dinner at Kang's again.
Are we like those poor couples...
you feel sorry for in restaurants?
Are we the dining dead?
I can't stand the idea of us being
a couple people think that about.
I like that.
How's the chicken?
Good.
- More?
- No. No. Thank you.
She's gonna be drunk and stupid now.
Hey, would you do me a favor...
and clean the goddamn hair off the soap
when you're done in the shower?
- Yeah. Oh. Yeah.
- It's really...
- Gross.
- It's just...
- Repulsive.
It's repulsive.
Patrick, can we get through this?
Patrick.
Hey, Tangerine.
Oh, Patrick, it's you.
I'm so miserable right now.
- Why? What's wrong?
- I don't know.
- Excuse me?
- I'm so confused!
Can I help you find something, sir?
Confused? What are you confused about?
Everything's fine.
Baby, come here.
Scared of what?
- Do you love me?
- Of course I do.
Where's the self-help section?
Do you think I'm ugly?
No! You're beautiful!
Maybe I should come over.
I don't know.
L- I'm a mess, Patrick.
Well, just let me come over.
I'll cheer you up.
Okay.
Stan, can I leave for a while?
My girlfriend's really upset.
Patrick, we're right in the middle
of erasing this poor man's...
Let him go, Stan!
Let him go. I'll help.
- See?
- How hard can it be?
- She hates me. She wants me to go.
- Go.
All right.
I'll be right over, Tangerine.
You like?
Oh, man!
I matched my sweatshirt exactly.
- I like it.
- You do?
- You look like a tangerine.
- Ohh!
- "Clemen-teen" the tangerine.
- Mmm! Juicy!
- And seedless.
- I like that.
I like tangerines!
Can you see me doing ducks?
- Tangerine.
- Joel. Ducks. Quack-quack.
- How does he know to call you that?
- How did who know?
Oh, my God. Clem?
That's what they called themselves.
The Clash...
the only band that mattered.
They called themselves that for a reason.
- It's amazing, isn't it?
- Like social justice... Yeah, it's totally incredible.
What Howard gives to the world.
Yeah.
To let people begin again.
It's beautiful.
You look at a baby,
and it's so pure and so free and so clean.
And adults are, like,
this mess of sadness...
and... phobias.
Howard just makes it all go away.
Oh, my God.
- Baby, what's going on?
- I don't know. I don't know!
I'm lost, I'm scared,
I feel like I'm disappearing.
- Disappearing?
- My skin's coming off! I'm getting old!
- Nothing makes any sense to me!
- You're not getting old.
- Nothing makes any sense. Nothing makes any sense.
- Ohh, Tangerine.
Nothing makes any sense.
- Nothing makes any sense, Patrick.
- It's okay. It's okay.
Hey, let's go out dancing. Yeah?
You wanna go out to Montauk with me?
- Montauk?
- Yeah.
- No! Come up to Boston with me.
- Sure. Yeah. We can go next weekend.
No, no. Now. Now.
Yeah. I have to go now.
I have to see the frozen Charles now.
Hi, it's Joel.
Um, leave a message after the beep
and I'll get back to you.
Pick up! Pick up, man!
W-W-W-W-Whoa.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Hello? Yeah, what's up?
I got into a little situation
with the old lady.
Can you handle things tonight alone?
I'm really sorry, man.
Don't worry about it.
I got it under control, man.
- He's pretty much on autopilot right now anyway.
- Thanks, Stan. I owe you big-time.
Dude, I gotta go. I gotta go.
Charles.
Come on, Charles.
"Look! You and me on the Charles River.
I could die right now, Clem.
I'm just happy. I've never felt that before.
I'm just exactly where I want..."
- I'm so excited. Yea.
- I'm excited too!
- Cool.
- Oh, uh, I, uh...
I got you this...
- What?
- Thing, um...
Happy early Valentine's Day.
Oh!
Wow. What is it?
Uh, I don't know.
Open it up.
Oh.
It... It's gorgeous!
- You like it?
- Yeah. It's just my taste. Really.
I've never gone out with a guy
who bought me a piece of jewelry I liked.
Thank you.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Joely?
- Yeah, Tangerine?
Am I ugly?
- Mm-mmm.
- When I was a kid, I thought I was.
Can't believe I'm crying already.
Sometimes I think people don't understand
how lonely it is to be a kid.
Like you don't matter.
So, I'm eight...
and I have these toys,
these dolls.
My favorite is this ugly girl doll
who I call Clementine.
And I keep yelling at her:
"You can't be ugly! Be pretty!"
It's weird.
Like if I can transform her,
I would magically change too.
You're pretty.
Joely, don't ever leave me.
Pretty. Pretty.
Mierzwiak, please
let me keep this memory.
Just this one.
I don't wanna hold your hand.
Come on.
- Whoo!
- Whoa!
Stop it!
I could die right now, Clem.
I'm just...
happy.
I've never felt that before.
Mmm.
I'm just exactly...
where I wanna be.
Clem?
I wanna call it off.
I'll give you a sign.
I wanna call it off!
Can you hear me?
I don't want this anymore!
I wanna call it off!
"When you ain't got nothing to do
I think I'll marry you"
Is anybody there?
- Clementine?
- Joel?
- Clement...
- Joely?
- Clem!
- Joel?
Clem!