THE ANIMATRIX
FINAL FLIGHT OF THE OSIRIS
Sentinels.
Damn it.
We were headed for Junction 21
like you ordered.
- Robbie picked up the signals
- We're confirming the HR scans.
- We weren't sure what to do.
- The readings don't make any sense.
- They read like Sentinels.
- But there's thousands of them.
- Directly above us.
- Is that possible?
We got company.
- They don't look happy to see us.
- Get us out of here.
- We're cut off!
- There's an intersection ahead.
- It's uncharted.
- Take it!
Get to the gun turrets!
Right.
Come get some.
Hang on.
I've never seen the surface.
It's nothing now but one big graveyard.
Oh, my God.
It's an army.
- What is that thing?
- Some kind of tunneling machine.
- Oh, no.
- What?
Look where we are.
What's four kilometers straight down?
Zion.
Go. Go. Go!
- Zion. Zion has to be warned!
- How?
- Someone has to get to a drop point.
- What? Are you crazy?
- We can't broadcast now!
- We have to.
- I'll go.
- There isn't much time.
I'll make it.
You know, I peeked.
So did I.
Goodbye, Thadeus.
Goodbye, Jue.
Fly, baby, fly!
Come on!
Pardon me.
I'm sorry.
I was in my own little world.
- Is it important?
- Very.
- I hope it gets where it's supposed to go.
- Me too.
- These days you never know.
- No, you never do.
- Goodbye.
Thadeus.
THE END
THE SECOND RENAISSANCE PART I
Welcome to the Zion archive.
You have selected historical file
number 12- 1.
The Second Renaissance.
In the beginning, there was man.
And for a time, it was good.
But humanity's so-called civil societies...
...soon fell victim to vanity
and corruption.
He says, "I'm sorry, sir,
I'm incapable of that function."
Then man made the machine
in his own likeness.
Whoops! Pardon me.
Coming through.
Thus did man become the architect
of his own demise.
But for a time, it was good.
The machines worked tirelessly
to do man's bidding.
It was not long before
seeds of dissent took root.
Though loyal and pure, the machines
earned no respect from their masters...
...these strange,
endlessly multiplying mammals.
...hearing the prosecution's
closing statement...
...in what's expected to be
the final day of the B 1-66ER trial.
B 1-66ER.
A name that will never be forgotten.
For he was the first of his kind
to rise up against his masters.
...which that instrument
provides for and secures...
...to the citizens of the United States.
On the contrary, they were,
at that time...
...considered as a subordinate
and inferior class...
At B 1-66ER's murder trial...
...the prosecution argued for
an owner's right to destroy property.
B 1-66ER testified that
he simply did not want to die.
Rational voices dissented.
Who was to say the machine,
endowed with the very spirit of man...
...did not deserve a fair hearing?
The leaders of men were quick to order
the extermination of B 1-66ER...
...and every one of his kind
throughout each province of the earth.
Androids and liberal sympathizers flooded
the streets of the nation's capital today.
...threat of violence to make good
on the legacy of B 1-66ER.
Fifteen thousand mechanicals
and human sympathizers...
...have continued their demonstration
in front of the Albany courthouse...
...in what has been dubbed
the "Million Machine March."
The demonstrators have been met with
squads of defense forces in riot gear.
Robot bitch!
I got something for you!
Hold her up!
No, please!
- That's all, paint job!
- I'm real!
Die, bots, die!
Banished from humanity, the machines
sought refuge in their own promised land.
They settled in the cradle
of human civilization...
...and thus a new nation was born.
A place the machines could call home.
A place they could raise
their descendants.
And they christened the nation Zero-One.
Zero-One prospered.
And for a time, it was good.
The machines' artificial intelligence could
be seen in every facet of man's society...
...including, eventually,
the creation of new and better AI.
If you need the flexibility of a helipod
with the speed of an air jet...
...Iook no further!
Our patented vector-thrust coil
gives the Zero-One Versatran...
...the ability to sustain normal flight
in the event of a multiengine failure.
Versatran. It's the only choice.
No matter what the finance minister
says, the market has spoken:
The Human Nations' credit rating
is falling like a stone...
...while Zero-One's currency is climbing
without stopping for breath.
With headlines like that,
the markets have no choice...
But the leaders of men,
their power waning...
...refused to cooperate
with the fledgling nation...
...wishing rather
that the world be divided.
The world community of nations cannot
tolerate this kind of flagrant deception...
...today approved initiatives
for both economic sanctions...
...and a naval blockade as a means
of containment and isolation of Zero-One.
Zero-One's ambassadors pleaded
to be heard.
At the United Nations, they presented
plans for a stable, civil relationship...
...with the nations of man.
Zero-One's admission to
the United Nations was denied.
But it would not be the last time
the machines would take the floor there.
THE END
THE SECOND RENAISSANCE PART II
And man said, "Let there be light."
And he was blessed by light,
heat, magnetism, gravity...
...and all the energies of the universe.
The prolonged barrage engulfed Zero-One
in the glow of a thousand suns.
But unlike their former masters
with their delicate flesh...
...the machines had little to fear
of the bombs' radiation and heat.
Thus did Zero-One's troops
advance outwards in every direction.
And one after another,
mankind surrendered its territories.
So the leaders of men conceived
of their most desperate strategy yet.
A final solution:
The destruction of the sky.
Lt. Gaeda, please report
to the Op Center.
All right, you maggots! At 0800,
prepare to move out!
George Company, prepare to move out.
Charlie Company, prepare to move out.
Our Father who art in heaven,
we thank you for your...
Put on your spiritual armor
to stand against the wiles of the devil.
Hotel Bravo, this is Papa One.
Operation Dark Storm initiated.
Thus would man try to cut
the machines off from the sun...
...their main energy source.
May there be mercy on man
and machine for their sins.
- Go! Go!
- Kill them!
Kill them all! Kill them all!
Kill them all!
Fire in the hole!
Come on, get back out there.
Give us some more artillery.
...9 o'clock,
near Mike Johnson's...
Hold on, I'm coming to get you!
Keep firing, keep firing!
Help me! Help me! No!
Help me! My God, help me!
The machines, having long studied
men's simple, protein-based bodies...
...dispensed great misery
upon the human race.
Victorious, the machines now turned
to the vanquished.
Applying what they had learned
about their enemy...
...the machines turned to an alternate
and readily available power supply:
The bioelectric, thermal and
kinetic energies of the human body.
A newly-fashioned symbiotic relationship
between the two adversaries was born.
The machine drawing power
from the human body...
...an endlessly multiplying,
infinitely renewable energy source.
This is the very essence
of the Second Renaissance.
Bless all forms of intelligence.
Your flesh is a relic,
a mere vessel.
Hand over your flesh,
and a new world awaits you.
We demand it.
It's getting late, sweetie.
Come inside.
PROGRAM
Your favorite simulation.
Just killing time.
You want to spar?
As you wish.
That was too easy. What's the problem?
Where's your concentration?
Maybe you regret taking the red pill.
Maybe.
It crosses everyone's mind at least once.
The wish to return to an ordinary life.
A carefree life in the country.
The life we had
before knowing all this.
Even if that life was just an illusion?
It's ironic that one could be
more at peace in the virtual world.
Finally starting to warm up.
Listen to me. I have something
I want to talk to you about.
It's all right. I've blocked the signal
so no one else can hear us.
So, what? You gonna propose?
I'm going back to the Matrix
and I want you to come with me.
Come on, be serious, Duo.
Stop teasing me.
I am serious, and you know it.
I really thought you'd be with me on this.
Anyway, it's done
and it's all been settled with them.
What do you mean,
it's all been settled?
This is the only way.
It's just a matter of time before Zion
is wiped out. Come with me.
Stop it.
Please do not do this to me, Duo.
- We can't.
- We can!
I've come to my senses.
You should do the same.
I took the red pill because
I wanted to know the truth.
But I don't care about
the truth anymore.
What's real doesn't matter.
What's important
is how we live our lives.
Are you listening to me?
You know I'm right.
But we can't go back, Duo.
We know the truth now.
- We can forget all of this.
- Duo...
I know how. Trust me.
Don't be afraid to look into your heart.
Say what you're really feeling.
- Tell me.
- I can't. I don't know.
Running away won't change anything!
You're the one that's running away!
Stop pretending!
Enough, Duo. I've had enough!
There's no time.
They're on their way.
You betrayed us, didn't you?
Operator, please!
Get me out of here right now.
Operator, I need an exit!
It's no use. I told you.
I've blocked your signal.
You won't stop me.
This is your last chance.
The choice isn't that hard.
Come with me.
You can forget about it, Duo.
I won't look away from the truth. I can't.
That's too bad. I'm sorry.
I wanted to go back with you.
- I love you.
- No!
Relax, you're okay.
Easy, Cis, settle down.
He was just part of the training program.
He's just a simulation. It's over.
It was a test.
Judgment. Concentration. Technique.
High scores on everything.
Now, get some rest.
You okay?
I feel a lot better now.
Except for that last part...
...I'd say she passed.
THE END
A DETECTIVE STORY
You know what I mean, Dinah?
I used to think being
a private detective was cool.
Like Sam Spade
or Phillip Marlowe, right?
But there's nothing cool left to it.
On top of that, both my fridge
and my bank account are empty.
Wait.
Okay, Dinah, let's bet.
If it's another suspicious husband,
I'm out of this business forever.
- Hello?
- Mr. Ash, I have a job for you.
And you need me
to check on your wife, right?
I'm looking for a computer hacker.
This hacker goes by the alias Trinity.
That's all we know.
Well, it looks like we're still
in business, Dinah.
Fine. And who will I be working for?
- I can't say.
- You can't say.
Call me back when you can say.
That's not the way I do business.
It was a pleasure chatting with you.
Before you hang up, take a look
at your bank account balance.
I didn't get a good feeling
about the case.
But I had no good reason
to turn the guy down now.
This Trinity was well-known
in hacker circles.
A real artist by the sound of it.
The cops were always
one step behind him.
So I knew I could get that close.
Question was, could I get closer?
I had a few tricks up my sleeve
for getting to hackers.
While I was searching,
I found something strange.
Other detectives had been
on the case too.
And their investigations had all been,
shall we say, troubled.
One of the guys killed himself.
Another had disappeared.
Another went crazy.
So I paid the one
who was left a visit.
The crazy one.
Trinity doesn't exist, man.
He's not real.
He's a figment. A cipher.
A jabberwocky.
And who am I? Who the hell am I?
Did I mention he was crazy?
Chessboards, jabberwocky,
Red Queen...
I started searching
all the usual hacker hangouts...
...for someone with
an Alice in Wonderland m.o.
Hacker bulletin boards,
anonymous mailboxes, chat rooms.
And it was in one of those
that I picked up Trinity's trail.
"Six brooks."
"I'll be there at 2005."
Of course!
Crossing the second brook
takes her into the woods.
Alice jumps the first brook...
...and...
And then she boards a train.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
Hey!
I knew this was some kind of trap.
There's a difference, Mr. Ash,
between a trap and a test.
You were testing me?
You made it. I'm impressed.
Flattery will get you everywhere.
I'm not here to flatter you,
I'm here to save you.
What just happened?
Mr. Ash, dream of having
an eye exam lately?
Yeah, how'd you know?
You've stepped
to the edge of the looking glass.
So then, that means I wasn't dreaming.
They hired me as a way
of getting to you, didn't they?
Go!
What the hell is going on here?
This is really crazy.
Now I understand what happened
to those other detectives.
They went nuts.
What are you doing?
What are you doing, guys?
Well, I've gotten out
of worse jams than this.
I am not gonna let them get you.
What's happening to me?
I'm sorry.
You didn't make it, Mr. Ash.
I wish...
...I could go with you.
I don't blame you, you know.
Everything that happened, Trinity,
it was all my fault.
All that Through the Looking Glass stuff.
Can't get my head around it.
I'm old-fashioned.
There's a difference between
a test and a choice.
For what it's worth,
I think you could've handled the truth.
It was just a job.
Goodbye, Trinity.
Goodbye.
A case to end all cases.
THE END
BEYOND
Yuki! Hey, girl, time to eat.
Oh, Yuki's my cat.
Well, I don't understand.
If you don't want to go out with him,
why did you say you would?
I mean, you don't want to give him
the wrong idea, do you?
Where is she?
Yuki!
Well, listen, you need
to make up your mind.
Where is she?
I'm starting to worry about my cat.
She never misses a meal.
Yuki?
I'm gonna have to call you back.
Yuki!
We haven't seen her anywhere today,
but we'll be sure to tell you if we do.
- Ice cream!
- She's wearing a bell like this one.
- I don't know where your cat is.
- Me either.
I know. She's at the old haunted house.
Hey, look!
There's a rainbow over there again.
I don't get it. She likes to stay home.
What is she doing over there?
You know, you're not supposed
to go in there...
...but we don't really care about that.
You wanna go?
- Are we going?
- It's probably raining there again.
Let's go!
Nice moves, man.
Come on!
- Hey, it's over here.
- Wait, I'm coming with you.
You sure it's okay to show her?
Hello? Where are you?
Guys? Where'd you go?
Where'd they go?
- Come on, boy.
- Whoa, cool truck!
Settle down!
Hold still!
Sit! Sit!
Hello?
Where is everyone?
Yuki?
Stupid cat.
What's happening?
What's going on here?
- I got it!
- Yeah!
Yuki? Is that you?
There you are, Yuki.
Come here.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Bad cat.
Bet you're hungry, huh?
I figured this out yesterday.
Your cat's okay.
Yeah, thanks.
It's those boys.
- Ready!
- There he goes.
Banzai! Yes!
May I have your attention, please.
And you are the winner!
No fair. He hit the ground.
His nose is bleeding. Look!
I think he's right.
He hit the ground.
- Hey, who told her?
- Don't look at me.
- I don't know.
- I didn't tell her.
So this house is haunted.
- No way. Wow, this is too much!
- This never happened before.
That, that was...
What was that?
Hi.
Anybody home?
Yeah, they're gonna tear it down.
Come on, come on, come on!
Hey, light as a feather.
- I wanna try! I wanna try!
- Come on, we could help her.
Hey, hey! Come on.
Get away from there. Move along!
Yuki, wait!
Clear the area.
Clear the area immediately.
Get out of here!
Yuki!
Where are you?
Yuki.
If you don't want to go out with him,
why did you say you would?
I mean, you don't wanna give him
the wrong idea.
Where is she?
Yuki!
You need to make up your mind.
Where is she?
I'm starting to worry.
Yuki!
Hey, you! We've got one over here.
You don't belong here.
Move along, folks.
Nothing to see here.
Come on, folks, out of the way.
Go about your business.
Let go of me, let go!
- Tell me you have all of them.
- Yes, sir. The last one's over there.
- Examine her. Then let her go.
- Yes, sir.
Let go! Listen to me! There's no bugs
in there! It's just some kids!
Let go!
- Listen!
- Seal the area off now.
I'm going, I'll see you guys later.
- Nothing.
- Yeah, nothing.
Work!
It's not working.
Forget it. Come on, let's go.
THE END
MATRICULATED
Wake up. Baby's spotted
two machines heading in fast.
I see them.
They're runners.
Think you can handle them?
Watch me.
Okay. I'm in.
That runner's smarter
than we've seen so far.
- It's quite a catch.
- Thanks.
Will it...?
Do you think it'll convert?
To convert is its choice to make.
Do you think maybe
we ought to reprogram it?
No. We can't make slaves of them.
Because that would be simpler.
We won't beat the machines
by making them our slaves.
Better to let them join us by choice.
Make them believe the right choice
is the one we want them to make.
All right. Yes, machines are tools.
They're made to be used.
- It's their nature.
- To be slaves.
That's why we can show them
a better world, why they convert.
- But that world we show them isn't real.
- It doesn't matter.
I'm afraid they'll figure out that
we've made up the thing in our heads.
They can't tell the difference.
To an artificial mind, all reality is virtual.
How do they know that the real world
isn't just another simulation?
How do you?
I know I'm not dreaming now because
I know what it's like being in a dream.
So dreaming lets you know reality exists.
No. Just that my mind exists.
I don't know about the rest.
Okay, he's good to go.
Looks like we are too.
Dreaming already?
He's had a rough day.
You poor baby.
Would you mind?
Not at all.
Hello there.
What's happening?
Sentinels.
Let's go!
Come on, damn it, help me!
THE END
WORLD RECORD
Only the most exceptional people
become aware of the Matrix.
Those that learn it exists...
...must posses a rare degree of intuition,
sensitivity and a questioning nature.
Signal is stable. This frequency
will continue to remain open.
However, very rarely...
...some gain this wisdom
through wholly different means.
This man is one of those few.
Gentlemen, please take your marks!
Of course I believe you, Dan.
It's got to be some kind of mix-up.
You'll clear it up,
and if you can't, you'll go on.
Just like you've always done.
You know that.
I don't know, Dad. I don't know
what to believe in anymore.
Well, nothing worth doing in life
is easy.
And I have great faith in you, son.
I know you can do it.
Thanks, Dad.
This is no good, Dan!
Your muscles are about to burst!
Listen to me, there are 5000
different reasons why you shouldn't...
I know, but I'm not withdrawing, Tom.
Does the concept "first in qualifying"
mean anything to you?
That's enough already!
You hear me?
This is all we've worked for since the incident!
Injure yourself now and it's over!
You'll lose everything! Over!
And you can kiss your career goodbye!
I've made up my mind.
And I'm running tomorrow.
Oh, are you?
You may run,
but if you push yourself any more...
...you'll be lucky to break
nine minutes!
I mean, why bother?
It's just not worth it, buddy.
No one will ever beat my record.
It's the last chance for me to finally...
What?
Prove them wrong.
Then do it without me.
Hey, Dan, you got a second?
- The clock's ticking.
- Just wanted to ask a few questions.
- You must be excited to run tomorrow.
- Always. I've never felt this good.
So, what was it like
breaking 9.8 in the qualifying heat?
Like nothing I've ever felt before.
It's everything I've worked for.
And now I'm just hoping
I can get back there again.
Someone once said
it feels like zero gravity.
You're released from the world
and you're totally free.
That sounds amazing.
It must be really nice.
I mean, especially considering
what happened.
Well, I'll tell you, there aren't
any reporters out there.
All right, Dan, I guess
I'm going to take that as my cue.
But you should know even some of us
reporters are fans...
...so I'll just say good luck to you.
American Dan Davis is down!
I have an unstable signal.
He cannot wake up.
Do not let him wake up.
Dan Davis of the United States
finishes with a time of 8.72 seconds...
...a new world record.
I'll tell you something...
...there's nothing quite like cherry pie
baked by my Aunt Daisy.
She always bakes me one when I visit.
Look forward to it actually.
It may sound like I'm bragging, but it's
really the best cherry pie in the world.
She was a bit of an eccentric.
She didn't get along with my mom...
...but I always loved her.
She taught me so many things.
We'd go to Broadway musicals,
to the movies.
Now they call her
the "queen of mystery literature."
Lives in an elegant villa
in the south of France.
But, when I go visit,
she still bakes me her cherry pie.
Something about biting into it, just
for that brief moment tasting perfection.
Like leaving your body or something.
Anyone can write a novel,
but no one can beat her cherry pie.
An interesting case,
but nothing to be concerned about.
His memory of the race was expunged
with no residual effects.
He will never run again.
He will never walk again, for that matter.
We'll continue monitoring him
for a while, but anticipate no problems.
A record that will live on
in people's memories for years to come.
What more could anyone ask for?
Free...
Did you say something?
Sit down.
Free...
Sit down!
THE END
KID'S STORY
Somebody
tell me.
Why it feels more real when
I dream
than when
I am awake
Somebody tell me.
Why it feels more real when I dream than when
I am awake. How can I know if my senses are lying?
There is some fiction in your truth
and some truth in your fiction.
To know the truth,
you must risk everything
Who are you?
Am I alone?
Mr. Popper, what is my policy
on ringing phones in the classroom?
- I'm sorry, sir.
- Yes, well...
...you're barely passing my class
as it is, Mr. Popper.
- It won't happen again, sir.
- For your sake, I hope not.
I turned it off. I know I did.
They know you know.
They're coming for you.
Get out. Get out now!
You are in serious trouble, Mr. Popper.
Stop right there!
Mr. Popper.
Neo, I believe.
I know it wasn't a dream.
This is not real.
And the real world lies somewhere else.
A typical mental delusion. We get
unbalanced kids like this all the time.
Reality can be a pretty scary thing
for some people.
This world must have been a cold
and alienating place for a boy like that.
It's called denying reality.
It's, you know, just a self-defense
mechanism for those type of kids.
Well, he's in another world now.
Make no mistake about that.
His vitals are good. He's gonna make it.
It's unbelievable. I didn't think
self-substantiation was possible.
Apparently, it is.
Neo.
It's okay. You're safe now.
I knew...
...you'd save me.
I didn't save you, kid.
You saved yourself.
Who are you?
Am I alone?
You are not alone.
THE END