What is it?
It's Bobae's interview
I just wrote it...
If you could do the article
like the last time...
For free?
Huh?
Can you lend me some money?
Don't have it
Get a pay advance
Yun Hwa
Is Bobae's article ready?
- No, not yet
- What's going on?
You're here to work not enjoy lunch
Kyong-hee, what about your interview
with Director Hwang?
I'm working on it
and I didn't even eat lunch
Then you had more time
to finish it!
The Interview was just yesterday
Stop talking back!
What are you all just
standing around for?
Get to work!
Work!
Think about your families
You're the one's they depend on!
Who's gonna feed
and clothe them?
What are you doing?
Huh?
Just had lunch and coffee...
Have lunch?
Were you with Kyong-hee
last night?
Nothing happened
We just had dinner, really
nothing more
Don't try anything to her
you'll regret it
She's not my type
What's wrong with her?
She's better than any other...
Stop clowning and get to work!
Yes.
It's pretty good
I'm busy, today
Can I pick the menu?
You must like fish
I love it
Why aren't you eating
Miss Song?
Call me Yun Hwa
We're the same age
Why the sudden change of mind?
Waiter, we ordered eel sushi!
We already had it
Why aren't you eating?
I don't like raw fish
Huh?
Why didn't you say so?
You wanted to pick the menu
Oh, geez...
Now I feel bad
It's okay
I can eat this
I wanted to pay...
But you didn't eat anything
Still I should have paid...
I was planning to pay anyways...
I'd rather starve than to
have a girl pay for my meal
And I can afford it
Good-bye
Huh?
You have work to do
We didn't even talk
How about some coffee?
Do we need to talk?
No, but, hah, hah...
you're right,
the article is going to
take some time
I should really be getting on it
Hey, it's me
You're car stopped again
No, no it's not empty
I'm here at the...
Hello? Hello?
Another busy day at the office
You all have a deadline to meet
Be alert, alert!
Do a good job
we're here to make money...
Okay, work, work, work!
Great! Good work, everyone!
It's selling like hot cakes!
- Wonderful
- Are you treating us?
Treat yourself!
Such a scrooge!
You two!
Their storming to be interviewed
Kyong-hee!
Did you write the interview
or copy it from a book?
It's exactly what he said
Who's going to understand that?
You should have used easy words
We're no rocket scientists
Why're you picking on me?
Do it right, then!
Yun Hwa!
You're grateful, huh?
Thanks to me, you just earned
everyone's respect
Thank you
It was nothing
But...
I still think you should
take off the glasses
That's odd
Don't you want to look pretty?
Oh, that temper!
- You really are something!
- What?
You embarrassed me
in front of everyone!
Is that how you treat
all your lovers?
No, you're the strange one
Get this straight
I'm still your boss
And you want me to
overlook your mistakes
because we're lovers?
Do you?
It's a cold world we live in
Unless you're smart
They'll spit you out
This is no game
That's corny!
This is corny?
Yeah, this is really corny
Corny...
Yes
2 o'clock?
Okay, thanks for your time
I'll see you there
It's none of your business
whether I wear my glasses!
You guys lovers or something?
Gee whiz!
Take it outside!
Is that so hard?
Kyung-Hyun!
- Today, I...
- I'm busy
Are you avoiding me?
I'm not
I really am busy
I need to drink, or I'll flip!
No, I'm really busy
You said I was a study case
I'll show you everything, tonight
What are you talking about?
I never said I wanted to study you
- What?
- I'll see you tomorrow
Hey!
Oh, shit!
Bang, Bang
Answer it!
Answer the phone!
Honey, please get it
Hello?
H, Hello?
Oh, who?
Geez...
Do you have to do that
in front of the door?
Sure
Doesn't it bother you?
She may have eaten something weird
And have bad breath
or something
Nope
Is she vaccinated?
- Oh, that's sick
- What do you know?
You never kissed before, jerk!
I choose not to
It's like smoking, a bad habit
You didn't have a chance...
I'm bushed!
Hey, are you busy?
This is hot!
Kiss of Fire!
Enjoy it!
Give me one stronger!
Miss, try to savor the drink
and slowly feel the love rising
I don't know anything
about cocktails
But I do know a little bit
about love
I've been in love more
than the number of cocktails
you made
do you know anything
about love?
Hey, Jeanie
mix up a
'sex on the beach' for her!
Kyong-hee
- You're here
- It's late
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have
called you, but...
No, I'm glad you did
Same for me
Kyong-hee...
Hey, you're beautiful tonight
You know...
I've waited for your call...
It's true...
Stupid!
- You shouldn't have said that
- What?
Stupid!
Hey, Kyong-hee!
Geez, what is this saying?
You're no friend
I mean I'm no computer whiz!
Now, what? What do you want?
Hey!
- Can you erase the glasses?
- Why?
For what?
- Just do it
- You like her?
- What?
- Do you like her?
Forget I asked!
You do
What are you talking about
She's not my type
And I told you, until I make it
in this field, I'm not falling for a girl
Love has nothing to do with business
Oh, all right
Do what again?
Forget it!
Good morning, sir
What's wrong, did someone die?
Let's go
Where?
Min Joo's interview
Can Mr. Yang go with...
Oh, okay
Choose one
What?
Either me or your wife
- No, Kyong-hee...
- You know
I can't do this anymore
Can't we just go on this way?
For who's sake?
- Kyong-hee, please...
- Hurry up and decide
It's up to you
Whatever you decide
let me know by today
Before I go home
Your monthly allowance?
Same as anyone my age
How much do you drink?
But, your questions
aren't very different from others
Huh?
Your articles seemed unique
That's why! liked it
That's her style
It sounds like regular
but she's reading the person
And then she puts that on paper
Well, then I'll get serious
What kind of love
are you looking for?
Wow, that's heavy
Hmm...
- The kind of love...
- Min Joo, ready?
- They're ready to start
- I think they're starting
Aren't you going to interview me?
Today is Min Joo's day
Then, see you next time
I'll be back soon
You'll be here, right?
What were you thinking?
- Get more extras, stupid!
- Yes, sir
Looks like a sad ending
It's rain
Rain comes with sad endings
Too obvious
Excuse me, who are you?
Entertainment World
interviewing Min Joo
Oh, good
Can you help us out?
Don't move, just listen to me
You will all be walking
when it starts to shower
All of you open your umbrellas
and move on
Those that don't have one
Run quickly
- Okay?
- yes
Don't look at the camera
- Okay
- Let's try it
We're ready, sir
- Okay, let's shoot!
- Alright
Don't be nervous
Walk naturally
Who's nervous?!
- What are you doing?
- It's broken
- It's not opening
- Oh, great
Let's run!
Oh gee
Here, use this
One more time
You're lucky
you look good in pictures
You're really lucky
Your attention, please
Um...
Due to personal reasons
Kyong-hee
who's been with us for over
three years has decided to leave us
We should wish her all the best
and hope to meet again
Let's not be too sad
Kyong-hee, we'll miss you
A farewell party?
Geez, what party!
I'll get you a job at a steak house!
Damn it!
Well, let's go out
It's on me!
Cheap S.O.B.!
Hey, Kyong-hee!
It wasn't a sad ending
You're right
Hey
You two!
She's your study case?
Her?
Everyone's made me
out for a fool
Good luck
Ajerk and a fool!
A good combination
So drunk so early
- Are you alright?
- Hey, you...
- What?
- You better be good to me
Don't say that
- I'm always good to you
- Just don't argue
No, honey
Not, there!
Be nice, okay?
I'm you're savior!
What's wrong with you today?
Why?
I've gone mad, trying to make
the biggest decision of my life
Hello?
Auntie?
Are you sleeping?
Sorry
No, I just couldn't sleep
No, nothing's wrong
Auntie, you know that thing...
You know what I'm talking about
I wanted to know are you sure
all I so is close my eyes
and that's it?
There's more, isn't there?
Come on...
Such as...
You get all hot
Or your head feels like
it's on fire...
No, someone said...
Okay, good night
You're right, she looks better
without the glasses
Take a look
She actually looks good enough for you
Come and take a look
Come on
I saw it
You saw it?
Yes, right up close!
All this, for nothing
I could undress her!
You want me to?
I will
You, son-of-a-bitch!
You ungrateful, son-of-a-bitch
I'm sorry
You're saying
you're not in love?
How far did you go?
I'm gonna punch you
Don't deny it
Do as you will
I don't have time for you
Why do they say that
breaking up hurts less
after the first one?
Don't look at me like that
Unlike you
I can have relationships
and not be scared of getting hurt
They called today
So, you got your wish
- Hey
- Yang!
What?
- You're early, today?
- Yes
Where'd it go?
I... I took off my glasses
but I feel weird
Where's my change?
Here it is
I bore you, don't I?
The coffee is too sweet
I envy Kyong-hee
She's straightforward
friendly, and outgoing...
And so little...
Why am I like this, I ask myself
I get upset with myself
But I'm a good runner
By myself...
Why are you telling me this?
what?
Talking about yourself
Right now!
- I just wanted to...
- Let's go back
Yes, good job
Yun Hwa!
Your cover, from now on...
I'm sorry...
Who are you?
Is this Yun Hwa?
You had face surgery?
Yun Hwa! Yun Hwa!
What's wrong with her?
How should I know?!
I already pushed it
Yun Hwa!
Gosh, thatjoke cost me
three days your absence?
From now on
your articles will be titled
'Yun Hwa's Photo Essays'
- What?
- The boss thinks
it'll do the Magazine a lot of better
With your article
Photos of Min Joo Kim
Kyung-Hyun quit
He got a better offer
Aren't you getting any offers?
Can I ask a favor?
What?
That...
You're uncle's magazine office...
To reporter, Yun Hwa...
Can you give it to her?
Hey, Joon-Sup...
Hey!
You give it to her in person
or throw it away!
Entertainment World
Hold on
Air Cleaning?
Wow!
I'm buying dinner
my treat
Celebrating the Kiss!
Hello?
Hold on
Yun Hwa you're bad
work habit's back
Hello? Speaking
Hello?
Long time, huh?
Really?
How have you been?
So, so
I was foolish
I knew it was a mistake
when I left
I thought about us, a lot...
I was crazy to...
you're such a sweet...
- Can we...?
- I'm sorry
I can't hear your words
What are you doing here?
I went by the office and
they told me you were here
What do you want?
I just...
You know...
I wanted to ask you...
It's not that important...
What is it?
The 'he' in your diary...
is it me?
You read my diary?!
No, by accident
Tell me, is it me?
No, it's not you
It isn't, I knew it...
I wasn't sure
it just sounded like me
For a second I thought
you know...
I was over myself, huh?
Well, I gotta go
I have to meet my boss, so...
I'll be going now
Wearing your glasses, again?
You look better without 'em!
Good-bye
She's coming!
- Hold it straight, straight!
- Hold it right!
Kyung-Hyun said if we didn't do this
he'd blow the building up
Kids nowadays mean it
They do, for sure
I'm sorry
Without your permission
We'll wrap it up
Leave it
I'll do it, later
Have a good weekend, all!
- I'll be going
- Alright
It's raining, dreadfully...
I feel like a drink
Let's go
I used to get so sentimental
but now I get upset if my wife
forgets my umbrella...
I miss my single life
Mr. Yang!
I forgot to tell, you
Your wife called
and she said she was on her way
with the umbrella. Sorry
- Bye
- Thanks
Well, I'll ask someone else
Don't stay out there
wait in here
Hurry up!
The smell is making me sick
Okay, be right out!
Do we have to go, here?
They sell my skin lotion
Gosh why are you so particular?
I'm hungry
You're well?
Honey!
Hungry? Let's go to dinner
You want to go out?
I want ribs
- No, something better
- I'm so lucky
Taxi!
Honey, come on!
Oh, all right
Smells good?
You're really in this movie?
That's right
I come on during the climax
of the movie
I spent the whole day
with Min Joo Kim
- it wasn't even funny
- The boss doesn't like his staff
to be too loose like that
Bad image for the company
Forget about the past
Drinks...
I'll get some drinks
I know it's here...
Where is it?
Here it is!
It's been awhile
It's starting
Hurry up, Come on
The movie's about to start
Uh...
The movie's...
starting...
What are they doing?
I didn‘t know this was a musical!
Hey, when are we going to
see you?
There he is
Isn't it?
You're only an extra!
Oh, this movie is pretty bad
Where did he go?
- He has the car
- Probably got embarrassed
How can he show us
this bad movie?
The umbrella is broken
Joon-Sup?
It's me
Did they all come?
Bunch of losers
You know what...
I saw her today
at the theater
Isn't it weird
Here?
Phone booth
We did our scene here
No, I'm alone
Why?
I just thought that...
If I came here
she would be here, too
What?
Yeah
I ran away again
Hey!
I see her in two months
and all I say is
'it's been awhile
the movie's starting'
That was all I said
Funny, huh?
I'm stupid
She's not coming
She's not...
You know...
I think it's over
I can't see her again
I can't even cry at this moment...
Huh?
Yeah...
Now I can't...
Can I come in?
Yun Hwa!
I was just...
Do you...
Do you want to kiss?