Hello?
Hey babes, are you up?
You little sleeping beauty you...
Wake up or else I'll come bite ya!
That was a morning call service
for Ms NA Nan
Ever since I started getting salary
instead of allowance, I simply
Forgot how a good morning felt like
KIM Joo-hyuk
Every morning, I was confronted
with problems I needed to solve
Should I go take a big one, or no?
Should I wash my hair, or no?
Everything had to start with
a swift decision making
Singles
Hey
Didn't I tell you
not to call in the morning
Unless there's a big sale?
Your voice is no good
for a morning call
Hey, I have a hole on my head
Must be Alopecia
You stressed over work too much
What if I turn bald?
Don't worry it'll grow back in no time
- Hey!
What?
What the hell are you doing?
Close the door!
- Jesus!
- You scared the hell out of me!
- You said you were coming home late
- The appointment got cancelled
You could've called
What? I'm supposed to get
permission to come home?
Here we go again.
Aren't you guys sick of fighting?
Come out! I need to go
I'm not even half way there yet
Then cut it short
Okay, I'll hang up
Sorry, Nan... hello?
Too salty
Any soup?
This is way too salty
Roommate
Roommate, 46th boyfriend
- Move out!
- Whatever
Wait!
Excuse me
We still have leverage
If we alter the designs
according to changing
customer preference and
carry out a more aggressive
marketing scheme
we still have a chance
- Hey, Chun!
- Yes?
If that's how you're going to play
just forget about it
It was too early
Didn't I tell you that
it was too early, moron!
You're right on
That's precisely why I said
we needed a more
cautious strategy
that's suits 1492's image better
but then...
That's what I said, asshole
What happened there?
It has to be here somewhere
- Asshole
- Isn't he, isn't he?
Forget it
Hey, Chun... try harder, okay?
What should I wear
for the presentation?
I think
I'll just go on a shopping spree
Focus on the action plan
rather than your outfit
Espresso, right?
LEE Dong-mi!
Yes?
Hope things are going well
I have faith in you.
You know my taste, right?
- Did you hear about MAH?
- What about him?
He had a thing with LEE Yoo-jung
from human resources, you know
- Now, LEE Yoo-jung too?
- Yeah
What's wrong with people?
- That's so pathetic
- Totally
- Sorry... I'm kind of late, huh?
- That's okay
It's still not easy getting out
on time after all these years
They're now telling me to
get married to my face
You don't look too good
- You don't eat well, do you?
- I'm fine
Ta-da!
Let's drink this later in the room
Isn't it pretty?
It smells good too.
Smell it
- Nan...
- Don't you like it?
Nan... it's not easy, is it?
It's okay, really...
It's hard for me too
What?
Let's end it
You didn't order yet, did you?
Aren't you going to take order?
How's the project going?
- And what about the thesis?
- We're finished
I don't know
About our relationship
I let him go nice and clean
It always rains in movies
right about now
Let's eat
I guess she's really not coming
Would you if you had a suite?
I bet they did it already
Shower, you idiot
Here!
Guess significant others are
more important than friends alright
Of course, You can't have sex
with friends
Is that all you can...
talk about?
Every male and female problem
starts with sex and ends with sex
You make it sound like
you're pretty good at it
You don't know me
I don't wanna know
People with big mouths
are actually poor in bed
I really am good in talking and...
- You know
- That's what you think
- Hey, babes... should I teach you a lesson?
- Get off of me
Would you like to feel it?
Get your fat leg off of me, lady
I won't hit you
You can be honest with me tonight
Do you wanna move out?
Hey!
I was going to let this go
But you got me going
- Come on, really! Really!
- Hey, stop! Stop!
Hey, Nan!
He let me go, because he loves me.
Because he loves me
Fuckin' asshole!
He should've let me go before then
What am I, a joke?
I'll break him
I'll rip him apart
And have him dry to death
My heart's breaking
Hey
I'm feeling filthy, Dong-mi
let's go hit the spa
I think that it will definitely help
boost sales
My reputation's on the line here
So I'm sure you'll take care of it.
I have faith in you
Don't worry, Mr Chun
This is the new branding strategy
Forget that
Just hand over all the prep work
to Hae-jin here
I'm sorry?
Hae-jin will be going to
the New York Collection this year
But wait... already booked the flight
and made a hotel reservation
Okay, well... in that case
kindly go ahead and
Cancel them
Oh... my...
What are you gonna do?
Nan!
This kind of unfair relocation
is not acceptable
Why don't you just fire me?
If you want me to quit
I'll do that for you
I don't want to work for a company
that gets dictated
by someone like Chun
who shamelessly steals ideas
and avoids responsibilities
I will show you what's up
through a lawsuit if necessary
Just wait and see!
What is it?
Sit!
Thank you, sir
I always thought of you
as a father figure
Thank you
Come on, let's meet up.
I miss you
Let's meet up and talk, baby
Not tonight
I'll be finished early today
Let's meet up, okay?
I'll wait for you
I have books and CDs.
I'll wait for you listening to music
I'm okay, baby.
Come on... I wanna see you
I said I'm okay!
What's your problem!
Do you have other plans or something?
Are you seeing another girl?
What the... is she crazy?
What is wrong with her?
Hey, what's wrong with her?
I have books and CDs
I'll wait for you
listening to music, okay?
I might die
before I turn thirty out of anger
I feel like dieing
Don't you think that's enough?
Call me when you get this message
You're killing me here
If you're going to kill yourself
call me
So that I can go clean up
your corpse
What a bunch of assholes...
The oldest trick
in the damn fucking book!
What do they expect you to do
at a restaurant?
Just quit.
You do what you need to...
but you're not going to look too good
when you can't pay your bills
Let's face it... they get over a thousand
applicants just for a borough position
And they're all Masters
and Doctors
Is that how you
sympathize with people?
I'm just talking reality here
In any case
Nan needs a grand each month
- She has to pay off her loans
- Fuck
- pay for utilities, and...
- credit card bills
- Fuck
There's only one conclusion
Just show up to where
you were re-Iocated
And we'll figure out...
The rest later
Fuck!
Hey, Nan... what is it
that you really want to do?
What I want?
I used to have dreams
I wanted to become a manager
when I was 27
When I was 23
I wanted to become
a world renowned designer
- That's my really dream
- When I was 20
All I wanted was becoming
a career woman
When I was 19
Getting into College
meant everything
We all just wanted to move out
back then
Well... we achieved
that dream alright
- Cheers!
You can still see stars
You're right!
No the stars have fallen
just as my heart has broken
Dong-mi, we have to pay for
utilities tomorrow
- You little...
- When I get my hands on you...
Excuse me!
Yes!
Welcome to Chili's!
I'm quitting after pay day
I'm telling you... it's manual labor
Stop bitching about it
And go right ahead
- You're sleeping already?
- What time is it?
It's late Go to sleep, okay?
Get some rest
Bitch!
Is everything okay?
What's going on?
Don't worry.
It's no fire
Everything's okay?
You should've called if you were
going to pop a smoke shell
I am so sorry
911 is no joke, lady
I'm sorry
Roaches these days
- Survive smoke shells
- You're right
I'll do it, I'll do it
I'm sorry I totally forgot
- I'm sorry
- Not easy, huh?
I'm sorry
I'm going nuts
The Nashville project
will help us
respond flexibly
to fast-changing
web market trends
at the same time
gives us a local market
understanding
Next is a an action plan prepared
by Ms Kim Hyun-jung
- which will...
- Oh
That's enough for now
Let's talk about event planning
Will you turn on the lights?
Why don't you sit too, Dong-mi?
VPs of Europe and Asia regions
will be attending the conference
meaning that we'll really have
to focus on the details
KIM, kindly prepare a simulation
model and showcase the demo
And SHIM, define the roles
of the participants
- for the second event
- Okay
And LEE!
Yes, sir!
Prepare with Hyun-jung
Party food and beverage
Selecting the menu won't be easy
As Europeans
have picky tastes
Sir, then who's doing
the Nashville presentation?
What do you mean?
That's my job, isn't it?
Hyun-jung and I have worked
day and night
on this project
Why should we
be handling party prep?
LEE Dong-mi!
I think you're deeply mistaken
Who said female assistants
could give presentations
to directors?
The conference starts next week
We're going to camp
out in the office
LEE Dong-mi
Can I see you for a sec?
What's with you?
Are you gonna quit after this
or something?
You know damn well how things
are run around here
Have a seat
I really like
the Nashville project
You totally read my taste
I think we can be great partners
You just need to follow my lead
Just need to follow your lead, huh?
Do you wanna go for
a few drinks tonight?
I have special plans for you
I have plans too, you know
Impatient type, huh?
- Wait
- Why?
I don't know about here...
Let's go to my room
Shall we?
- You said your room
- Well, I mean... um...
- Wow!
- Oh my god!
This is the special plan
for you, fucker
You fucking shit
Out of my way!
Look at your underwear taste
That was Dong-mi's
last corporate action
Hey, Na! That's you, right?
Good to see you
You look good
Your legs look well trained
So...
What brings you here?
Came here to report
the receipts, huh?
Okay, okay
I'll stop by soon
to help boost sales
Just been a little too busy
I'll stop by soon with the kids
Keep up the good work
9th, right?
What a shame, huh?
What?
This elevator, it's too slow
PARK Soo-heon speaking
Hold on, wait
One sec
Yes... 783...
I find it strange that a person
could hate someone so much
You're bound to meet
someone like that
I'm way too rational
- Miss!
- Yes!
Look at you...
I really need to quit
Just go
What, are you starving yourself?
Thought you were on a diet?
When you're jobless, you just need
to treat yourself whenever you can
It's different from going on a diet
It's about survival
Hey, Tae-wook's getting married
at the end of this month
Oh yeah? And?
Think about who'll come
LEE Jee-hoon?
Should I go there or no?
Stop eating
Don't even drink water
You can't afford to gain weight
And we'll go get massages, okay?
What's with you suddenly?
You need to go there and
make him regret dumping you
Look at you! You look awful
Really?
- Are those freckles there?
- Where? What?
You're vitamin deficient.
Here get loaded up
Have some greens
and vegetables too
Eat
Hey, there's Joon
Joon, here!
- Is that Ji-hae?
- Guess so
I heard so much about you two
You're prettier in real life...
both of you
Joon said so many nice things
about you
I was dieing to meet you
I heard that you guys
are like butt buddies
That actually looks real
It is real
That's what I thought too
How do you know?
Look, the zipper blade
is too dense
I bet the logo will come off too
Let's see
You didn't have to lie to me
That came off real easy
Welcome to Chili's
- How big is your party?
- What?
Did you make a reservation?
No
- You know me, right?
- Excuse me?
Oh yeah...
Guide him to his table
I'll guide you to your table, sir
- Did you ask for me, sir?
- Yeah...
The beer taste is a little...
That can't be
How is it?
Tastes fine to me
No way
What's wrong with it?
You sure
you didn't feel anything strange?
That's weird... thought my lips touched
Sir, is this a joke?
Bingo! Now I remember him
Look at his creepy smile.
The guy from the elevator!
But why is he here?
Maybe he has feelings for...
Welcome to Chili's!
It's my college alumni get-together
Guys! Come on in
It's him again
Still creepy.
Looks awfully boring
Here's your card
Why don't you show me, your real intent, Mr!
Say it! Just say it!
- Have a good night
- Good night
Welcome to Chili's!
It's my high school alumni
get-together
Hello?
Oh yeah? Toad's coming too?
- How's he doing?
- He's definitely a player
Good taste though
He's here again
Come in
- Welcome to Chili's
- Come on, come on
So today's your junior high alumni
get-together, huh?
No, it's my kindergarten alumni
get-together
Hey Toad, let's go!
Welcome to Chili's
- Nan!
- Hi, Nan
Long time no see.
I came here to help boost sales
It's packed here
It was good today
What was it
at the end of the presentation?
Thank you for the...
Look at this uniform
You can be a model
I knew you would do well
but not this well
It's all because you're healthy
Sorry for being healthy
I knew from the beginning
That you would fit in better on-scene.
You look great
Am I right or what, Young-sook?
Have a good time
Oh yeah... one more thing
- Yes
- Keep up the good work
- Are you alright?
- Are you alright, sir?
I'm not filling out no forms
You should send this fucker to jail
Please calm down.
Let's take this one by one
How many times do I have to tell you?
I got punched while I was talking
Right? Right?
Can't I even talk?
What ever happened to freedom
of speech?
Didn't you touch
this lady's butt over here?
Jesus...
I did it to cheer her up...
as a mentor
Yes I did
It was a friendly gesture
What's wrong with that?
What is this guy, her pimp?
You saw what happened
All I did was telling the truth
We just talked right? Right
Hello!
Anyone?
Hey!
Let's have dinner together later
Didn't quite work out today
So why did you get involved?
How can I just watch then?
So are you gonna treat me
to dinner or what?
Well... I'm sorry for all this, but...
I could treat, you know
NA Nan... out!
Hey!
You're not gonna leave me here
are you?
Let's go
Have a good time
Hey! Hey!
I got my pride back
for the first time in a long time
It's still working
Do I need anything else?
You would need collateral
Collateral... hmmm...
Collateral?
Collateral!
You think start-up is for anyone?
Don't you trust me, dad?
It'll be quick, okay?
You know me, dad!
Just get married!
I'm not getting married.
I need to start my business
- You little...
- Well, I...
Come on, this is my last wish
You never do anything for me!
Christ... what am I doing here?
Should I carry them then?
Then...
you expect me to carry them?
Just pay the bill soon
Hey, this is nothing you know
Once I start my biz
I'll pay you back ten-fold
You're serious about this, huh?
You wanna work with me?
Look at you all excited over a bill
Let me in on your start-up
I bet I could work with you in style
You sure know
what you talking about
Come here
I'll give you
A kiss
What are you doing?
- I'm serious
- Wait
If you cross this line
I don't know...
Oh, yeah?
What are you gonna do
about that, huh?
- I might really go for it
- Yeah? Come on!
Wait, wait I think I could do better
Wrong! You know
how popular I am, Come here
You and your action plans...
let's stop
This is no action plan.
What are you doing in there?
- Let's stop, Dong-mi
- You're just too cute, you...
- Come here, here
- You're killing me
- Kiss is not for a person my age
- What's killing you?
You're sooo cute, you.
Come here, you...
I thought you had a date today?
Today's the day
I may have failed my diet
'cause of drinking
but I still look darn good
I'm coming, LEE Ji-hoon!
Hey, long time no see.
Why didn't you guys call?
He looks good over there
He used to be a little skinny
before though
- But now...
- Hey, stop, stop
Whatever... look at your belly
Hook me with a girl
He's looking
He's looking at me
Yeah, lose some weight!
Look! I'm doing just fine without you
Act confident.
You're good, NA Nan!
Wait!
You go, girl!
Welcome to Chili's!
Oh my...
How have you been?
Come on, answer him!
I got relocated
to the restaurant division
I heard.
So you're a manager, huh?
- So work is fun?
- Yeah...
Want some coupons?
Oh my god
- Oh lord! Daddy, my stomach!
- Give me some pepper powder
- Want some coupons?
- Funny?
I wanna kill myself
She's turning into you
What?
She just looked like
female godfather
So?
This is what
the world's done to me
I used to
get scared by bugs
Like your girl friend, you know
Why are you brining her up?
- What's wrong? Things aren't working out?
- How would I know?
Jesus, Lim, Jeong Joon!
That's what love is all about.
Just let it be
This tastes good!
Hey, this is no laundry.
You're making the Kimchi all soggy
- Do you guys Do That too?
- What?
Are all women like that?
What are you talking about?
Forget it
What?
This guy's been asking me out
He's tall, able
and his family's pretty well-off
And I like him too.
What should I do?
Kill the fuckers, don't you think?
So
she's been double playing
Don't talk like that
I'm still young.
I still want to do things
And meet new people
That's bull shit
She never considered
marriage with me
I mean...
who would want to marry
someone like me anyways?
So? You guys are breaking up?
We don't have to break up
just because we're not getting married
We could be good friends.
You know, like Dong-mi and Nan
- Can you be friends with her?
- No
- So what did you say?
- I said let's be friends, then
You idiot!
I'll make her so happy
That she'll never be able to forget
about me
Whatever!
I will never let him forget me
for the rest of his life
For the rest of his life?
Write a god damn novel
Do you know
what she's doing to you?
The other guy's rice
and you're noodles
No one likes eating rice everyday
So she wants to have noodles
every now and then
Ji-hae likes noodles better
She just wants good memories
She'll get married
to some rich guy
and have you hanging
on the side
You know what I'm talking about
It's like sticking gum under your desk
and chewing it at your convenience
You're just
a piece of gum to her, idiot!
When will you grow up?
You're too old for that shit
Stop talking like that, Dong-mi
Hey, she's selling herself
She's just looking for
security in life
I said, stop talking like that
Like you have the right
to talk like that?
Fuck
At least, I don't sell myself
I leave everything in the open.
You got a problem with that?
- Leaving everything in the open?
- That's right!
Oh, okay... so that's love
I'm sorry, but why is it so funny
Hearing the word love from you
Asshole!
Hey, Dong-mi, come on out!
And Joon, apologize!
What the hell is this while making Kimchi?
You're supposed to be friends
I'm really pissed now
Shoot... how am I gonna
take the Kimchi home now?
Excuse me!
Hey
Hop in
Why?
Thought you'd be tired
and I have a car so...
I'm tired alright
And it's probably impolite
to turn him down
- Don't you wanna know who I am?
- What?
Oh... sure...
I work for Uno Securities.
My name is PARK Soo-heon
Okay
I used to work upstairs from you
Oh
How about a date
One day?
Excuse me?
What do we do now?
Hey
Are you sure you can fix it?
Didn't I tell you?
I used to be a mechanic
in the army
Good night
Seoul 31 BA 9160...
Aquarium?
Does he want to go fishing
or something?
I don't think he'll give up easily
Don't eat anything
just because you're hungry
Shoot, bust again
Don't rush into anything
- Here are utility bills
- Hold on one sec
I put mine down
so you pay the rest tomorrow
You didn't make up yet?
Hey! Lend me some money
I want to get out of here
but don't have enough deposit
Lee, Dong-mi
It was deposit that got you into
living with Joon in the first place
Do you even know how expensive
the rents are these days?
Forget it then!
I won't ever ask you
for money again
If you make up with Joon
I'll lend you the money
Forget about it
I'd rather get a loan
I am sure of it
You know how he is bet
he's losing sleep over this
figuring out how to make up
He just left
his share of the utility payment
down to a cent
In any case, if you want my money
make up with him
- Hey!
You go first
I'm moving out
before the end of next month
I said, I'm moving out!
I'm not kidding, you know
Okay
Hey
Come sit over here
Either find another roommate
Or you can take over my deposit
Okay
I apologize for bringing in
different guys all the time
That won't happen again
until I move out
Good for you, huh?
You can
walk around naked now
I'm not being sarcastic
- Hey, listen...
- You listen...
So don't bring that bitch
back here until I move out
I don't want to see her ever again
- That slut got us into this
- Hey! Dong-mi!
She has a name you know
Whatever... she's a bitch
Want me to say that again?
B I T C H
- Off of me! - Nope
Not happening
You bastard...
come on, I'm dizzy
Ji-hae said...
she said I'm a nice guy
But then you know what?
I'm a nice guy she doesn't
want to be with
Nice guy equals
loser!
Nice guy...
You see... nice guy is
the only thing I can be
I...
don't have money
and I don't have connections
I mean...
what's wrong with
my parents being farmers?
I'm not ashamed of my family
Should I be, Dong-mi?
Idiot!
That's right, I'm an idiot
You really are an idiot
You're not the only one
Come on, stop
Hey, Mr Crocodile!
Crocodile!
Look at that fishy!
He's a menace
Dong-mi's right
I shouldn't eat anything
just because I'm hungry
Don't get too close.
It's hot
You know my arms
are cramping up too
This feels much better
Creepy and boring...
Childish and greasy too
Could be worse though
I mean... at least his looks
are somewhat decent
Okay, I gotta go.
I'm watching a play
What?
Hello?
- Okay, hang up, I'm here
- What are you doing?
What?
What? You slept with Joon?
- Fuck!
- I'm sorry I'm late
Why do you have to
come home so late?
What brings you here?
Wanna sleep over, huh?
Of course!
How am I supposed to see him?
I don't care.
I'm out of this
It's all because of you!
You told me to make up with him
and look what happened
It's all your fault!
I told you to make up with him
not sleep with him
Just get over here!
Guys...
Why don't you two just get married?
- What?
- Hey!
You guys are sharing
the same house anyway
Why not share the same bed?
Not in a million years
That's total nonsense
I'd rather go to hell
Same here! No way!
So then why did you do it?
Why did I do it?
See ya!
So we finally came to
an agreement over few drinks
We decided to forget about
that night's little trouble
Don't sleep again, okay?
Of course I'll sleep.
I'm going home
But I wished they would sleep again
And get married
They could make a great couple
Is this what you call service?
I'm terribly sorry.
There was a slight mix-up
I could let go of the late order
but you didn't even get
the order right
I was sure that
the order I got was...
That's okay.
I got this
I'm so sorry. I will have the
ordered plate for you immediately
Please be understanding.
Enjoy your meal
And again, I'm terribly sorry
Is this your first time here?
You can't just take orders randomly
You need to pace the orders
so that I can work at ease
Get a pace
You can't just be running around
like maniacs and
expect things to work
Train your people right!
Sorry
I'm sorry
Not easy, huh?
When you're feeling like that just say
This fuckin' sucks!
Come on, try it!
Huh?
Is there anything that you can do?
You can't smoke, you can't swear...
can you at least drink?
Oh yeah... you can fight
It's that good?
What is it?
Hey!
Yes?
If...
your husband gave you
ten grand each month
would you stay home or work?
What do you think?
Well... I think you'd work
And then, you'd probably
bitch about it everyday
And if your husband told you to quit working,
you'd bitch about that too
You are right on.
Perhaps you should become a fortune teller
Are we feeling comfortable now?
I don't know... whatever...
This is good.
I like this
Honey!
Honey... honey.
I like the sound of that
I want to hear you call me honey
from now on
I'm don't like the way
you talk to me
How old are you?
25...
since four years ago
Let me see
- I only have coffee
- I don't care if it's tap water
This is good
I asked him
for a cup of coffee, but
maybe I shouldn't have
let him in
Why do I feel like
I'm the inviting one?
I think I need to go
I don't know
what I'll do if I stay
That's it for today
Nan...
keep your door locked.
I might just burst in later
- Good bye
- See you
Can't go like this.
I just can't
I can't go like this
Maybe this is too fast.
This is way too fast
I should stop.
I need to be rational
Is this a dream?
That's because you haven't
been getting any lately
Just like people need to
eat to live
sex is the same
You need to have it every
now and then to stay healthy
You really need to work on that
Is this because I'm near
my period, you think?
Sleep with him!
Are you crazy? I don't even
know how this is gonna go
That's why you need
to sleep with him
You need to check things out
before you become too attached
In any case, if your body
wants it, you need to have it
Fucking sexaphoic
Your order's ready
Carribean salad
and fajita steak nachos
Old timer's ready
If you need ketchup, it's over here
Do you need anything else?
If you need drinks or...
Can you clean this up.
Enjoy your meal
How about the bund?
Next time
Do you want to go
get some coffee?
I know this sky lounge
They have a great view
Are you tired?
A little
- Can you turn that down a little?
- Sure
I said, turn it down!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I just have a headache
- I'll get some aspirin.
- Don't bother. Pharmacies are closed
Convenient stores are open
I said, don't bother.
Don't make me talk
Can't you see I'm not feeling well?
Couldn't you just play along?
You should've told me
You can't tell?
Do I have to tell you everything?
Forget it!
What's with you?
You've been
making me feel uncomfortable
Uncomfortable?
How can you sing
if you feel uncomfortable?
Sorry for singing... jesus
Maybe I should of cried
Why are you being sarcastic?
When was I being sarcastic?
Nan!
Tell me what happened
Couldn't you just do that?
Just talk about things with me?
What am I?
Your chauffer?
I never asked you for a ride
You liked it! You'd get mad
if I didn't pick you up
Whatever... you and
your piece of shit car
I...
met him today
He's getting married
I was doing so well...
He said she's really nice
And he said he's sorry
You...
tried hard to love him...
and
you tried hard to forget him
That's all that matters
Did I wake you?
Want some coffee?
Sure
This is good
Close your eyes
Come on
All set
It's been a while since
I've been carrying it around
I know that this maybe
a little awkward
But let me get this over with
Will you marry me?
There are only two things
to ask yourself at our age
Will he make a lot of money?
Or will he fulfill my desires
every night?
You know...
I want to marry someone
that is madly in love with me
You like him, don't you?
Yeah
I like him
but I'm not sure if it's love
Let's drop everything
and just get married
Marriage?
Hey! That's the only way we'll
make big money at this age
Only then, our parents will
let loose some funds
And we can start up a
company with that money
That's fraud
How's that fraud?
I'll stay married and just use
the money for business
What if your husband
doesn't let you?
That's his loss.
If he doesn't
want in, that's his problem
If not, forget it
- Then marry Joon!
- Hey!
If not, forget it
Stop making jokes like that
Do you even know
how he's doing?
What?
You mean, with Ji-hae?
She's quitting her job
She just needs to fix
the wedding date
That's impressive
I'm impressed by Joon
and his idiotic nature
Sometimes I feel like
he's mentally challenged
I mean why would you waste
time on something like that?
They say love lasts
That's why he's an idiot
I had one already
They say eating lasts
Really!
You happy?
Man... I'm sweating
Of course I'm happy
Let me ask you the question again
Would you quit if I gave
you ten grand each month?
What if I quit?
You can study
I know you still want to work
in the fashion industry
Why don't you get
into it aggressively
You know in studying
Study?
To be frank...
I think I'll get
relocated to New York
That's why I rushed our marriage
Now you can study...
of course
without the ten grand I promised
What is there to think?
Isn't that what you
wanted all along?
You're right
Fix him some breakfast each morning
get jiggy at night and
he'll pay for your tuition, living expenses...
you just hit the jackpot
You're right
You meet a man
and problems solved
God, how unfair
Stop it I'm not even sure...
it just doesn't feel right
Whatever... that's your luck
What ever happened
to the blind date?
Forget it
Do you know how it feels
to be a chunk of meat?
I can't handle the thought
Well, congrats to you!
Thanks!
I don't know
what's wrong with me
You said you weren't feeling well
before too, Go take a dump
- This is good
- What?
Now you two can get married
What?
This is why Joon got dumped and
you never had a decent boyfriend
Why didn't I think of this before?
Now I can leave carefree
I knew there was something
left unfinished. This was it!
Now you can start
up your business
Joon will say yes
and I'll throw you guys a party
Congratulations!
You're not feeling well, are you?
This is it.
Marriage and start-up all at once...
Congrats, you bitch
I think Joon's here
- Hey, hey!
- Nan, you're here!
Joon, look.
Look
- What's that?
- Two lines, you see?
- It means pregnant. Isn't it great?
- Yeah! How awesome?
- You have a baby
- That's so great!
Congratulations.
I really mean it!
She got the ring
and they set the wedding date
I can't believe it
Are you that happy?
You should be ashamed of yourself
Congratulations! That's great!
You finally did it, huh?
Don't worry
there's nothing to be ashamed of
That's right
What do you want to eat?
I'll cook it for you
She wants meat
You sure it's not you
that wants it?
- Okay, meat it is
- Right on
Wait!
If you say a word...
I'm going to kill you!
I decided to go to Chun-cheon
What?
Didn't I tell you this before?
Director Park wants me to come
So I was going to tell you
two to merge, but guess not
Dong-mi, you should
look for a new roommate
I guess so
- Are you for real?
- Sure
I like being home
Hey, Dong-mi!
What are you doing over there?
Come here and peel onions at least
Why just me all the time?
Do you want pregnant
Nan to do it then?
When will you grow up?
You're right.
What was I thinking
Hey, Nan... stay still, okay?
Let's party!
What should I do?
We were far from our dreams
but we celebrated anyway
Congratulations on running away
from a broken relationship, Joon!
Congratulations on getting pregnant
with your friend's baby, Dong-mi!
Nan! Congratulations for the
hideout marriage from reality!
Congratulations.
I really mean it...
Sir, should I change this
design slightly, or no?
- I think the color looks good
- It looks good?
Nan!
What are you doing here?
Are you back?
No, I have a meeting here
Long time no see
I heard that the new
brand is a home-run
- Congratulations!
- Thank you, Nan All thanks to you
What are you talking about.
That's totally all you
- Mr Chun!
- Yeah
How have you been?
I was a little worried
are you sure you are alright?
I don't remember much
Hey, do you want to
go grab some coffee?
Didn't we have it before?
I need to get running
You'll come and help boost
sales next time, right?
- Have a good day
- See you
- Mr Chun!
- What?
Keep up the good work!
- See you later, Nan
- Okay, See you!
- Oh, bye
- Take care
When I saw them, I suddenly
came up with a thought
Do I belong here?
Maybe I do... yeah...
or maybe not
Thank you for coming
Maybe it's here
Or maybe it isn't
- Thank you for coming
- I don't know
What the hell
Here comes a new dish
Um, I...
- So long
- What?
I'm quitting
My kid's pretty big now
and it's too hard to manage
But...
She wants to put more time
into her kid's education
You should leave it to the school.
That's not enough
So I filed a recommendation
for branch manager position
with both of your names
Don't get upset because neither
of you don't make the position
- Actually, I was going to...
- I don't know what's going on
but let's do what we can
FIT is a school
Calvin Klein went to
Parsons is supposed
to be good too
I think we'll need two cars too
You have a license, right?
I have to go, right?
Right!
Why?
You don't want to
live in a foreign country?
Well... no...
Oh, and...
- Again?
- I know...
Here, eat I heard
that it's the same as
having born a baby
So eat everything, okay?
Did you tell Mr. Securities?
Wear long sleeves even if it's hot.
Don't expose yourself to cold
Really think about it whether
it's work or marriage
Got that?
Any side effects?
They said I might not be able
to have a baby ever again
You poor thing...
I just can't believe this.
I can't believe it!
Did you have to do it
after having heard that?
You should've just had the baby
Don't worry.
You'll have a baby again
You're right
What?
I knew you would react like that
so I didn't get it
Hey, get up! Get up!
Where are we going?
To the hospital
You think this is funny?
Oh... my belly...
What? What?
Watch your mouth!
The baby's listening
What are you kidding me?
The baby's so sensitive
that once the camera was put on
It raised his hand like this
Hi!
Where?
Oh my...
Isn't it adorable?
Let's go!
What if I want it?
Then stop Joon
You have the right to do
that and marry him
What if I don't want to get married?
Why?
Then why would
you want the baby?
- Because it's mine
- What?
It's my baby
So are you sacrificing for Joon?
The baby's listening
Okay, okay
Ok?
Listen you don't have
anything got that?
If you have the baby you won't get a job
nobody will date you nor marry you
Are you okay with that?
Why do you have to be so pessimistic?
Why can't I date people
when I'm this sexy?
Plus, I'm going to make a lot of money
and live happily ever after
Christ
You might lose your father, mother
and Joon all together
Are you sure
you can handle that?
I got you, don't?
What is it?
Jesus...
Didn't tell you not to drink
that much?
You're fucking up your stomach
- Are you okay?
- I'm okay
You sure?
Yeah, get out!
I'm going to pee
Oh... okay
Hey, Dong-mi
why don't you come with me?
We can share offices
and work together
- Joon!
- Yeah?
Worry about yourself
- Think about it
- If Dong-mi leaves, Seoul will cry
Just get me a boyfriend
before you leave
Fool!
Is that so hard?
You inconsiderate asshole...
- Here!
- What?
I think you forgot,
but I'm a man too, you know
I'll let you borrow me
one last time
Okay
How's that?
Hug me harder
Like this?
Harder
Harder?
This is pathetic
Dong-mi finally started her
business through her fan club
Those people would die for her
if they had to
Or that's what she says at least
Who is it?
Is it you?
Can't be all of you...
Are you still
going to have the baby?
What if your baby asks
who the father is later?
My baby will only thank me
for bringing it into this world
Okay
it's your choice
Just do it
I'll be the father,
and you can be the mother
I'll go out and make
money to buy milk
If someone gives you shit
I'll handle it
Nan...
And if anyone looks down on
you for being a single mom
I'll beat the crap out of them
So don't worry, okay?
Got that, LEE Dong-mi?
Whatever
You should've said something already
Who washes their face in the kitchen?
I felt bad, that's why
Don't feel sorry
Soo-heon
Sorry
I thought
I had talent in fashion
But I think it was all fruitless
Trying so hard
to reach for the stars
But when I started to work here
One day, I just felt like
maybe this is it
I'm not exactly sure
if I have talent in this
but I want to try
I want to see the end of it
I need to figure out
what I'm made of
That's the first step
I need to take, right?
So...
That's why I can't get married
For a while
Is anything else broken?
Tell me now I don't want
you washing your face
in the toilet
Don't worry!
I can take care of myself
Did I ever tell you that
I'm really good at waiting?
Romantic, huh?
Yeah
Stop! Stop!
So we're here
Thank the lord
Huh?
I took care of everything.
You won't have any problems
I'm gonna get going
Let's part here
I don't want to make a
scene at the departure gate
You know...
people crying, hugging
running back from the gate...
With the camera spinning
and all?
Exactly
I'm gonna go
That's it
I'm really going
Don't expect me
to run
back to you from the gate!
Just go!
Okay
As soon as he left
everything became unclear
Out of sight, out of mind...
will we last as a couple?
Will I do well at work?
One thing was sure...
the fact that
nothing has yet happened
And whatever happens
there'll be problems for
which answers exist
Isn't it cool?
The voice is so cute
What's with the color though?
Are you sure you used
to be a designer?
I think your taste is a little off.
You think our baby will like it?
I'm not exactly sure of its taste
Then...
How cute are these?
They're so cute.
So cute
It's a doll, a doll.
I can't make up my mind
You want me to
have daughters only?
How would a boy manage laces or pink?
I just can't make up my mind
Who cares!
Couldn't you get something blue?
How about this?
Sorry.
I'm going to breast feed
Are you stupid? You can't
breast feed the whole time
Besides
you can use this for water
Oh yeah...
why didn't I think of that?
Babies drink water, right?
I'm so stupid
You'll love this one
What's that?
- Voila!
- What's all this?
- Turn the switch on...
- Okay
- And put it on your belly...
Testing!
Hey, baby... it's your auntie
Or is it your aunt
- No, it's your daddy
- Can the baby really hear this?
- Of course
- So the baby's listening now?
Yeah
Hey baby... are you listening?
This is your mom, over
The lady that just talked to you
never really liked you
So...
No, no... I really want to see you
Same here! Listen to me, baby...
It's going to take some time...
In a few days, it will be new years
I expected to solve
one of life's two homeworks
before I turned thirty
Marriage or a successful career
I'm still a single that didn't
succeed in my career
Who cares though?
I'll make something out of
myself before I turn thirty
If not, whatever
At age thirty
it starts all over again
NA Nan... you go girl!
Go girl!