Morning.
Remember that rose garden
I told you about?
They'll be in full bloom soon.
Let's go see them together,
soon.
Say,
which road do you take
to work?
Fried eggs today?
Did you want something else?
No, they're fine.
- Bon appetit.
- Enjoy.
Bon appetit.
I had a scary dream last night.
What was it?
I can't remember.
Off you go.
I'm off.
SWEET LITTLE LIES
Iwamoto.
What's up?
- With what?
- You seem spaced out.
Did you get a weird call?
No, just a call about a college
club reunion coming up.
What kind of club?
Scuba diving.
That's surprising.
Yeah, I'd forgotten all about it.
OK, that's fine.
Also, you have two magazine
interview requests.
Are you free next Wednesday
starting at 2pm?
Sure, that's fine.
Also...
Won't you drink your tea?
Yes, thank you.
Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Tomi, will you take some potatoes
home? You like them, right?
I can have them?
Satoshi's mother sends so many.
But they always sprout
before I can use them up.
Potato sprouts are
poisonous, right?
- Solanine?
- Yeah, that's the one.
Maybe I'll raise them on the sly.
If things get bad we can
poison ourselves.
If things get bad?
That's you killing him
and yourself. Scary.
But you and your husband
don't need any poison.
Why not?
Because you seem
so happy together.
We seem happy together?
Welcome home.
Hi.
Thanks.
Tomi came over today
to discuss my exhibition.
She told me her
boyfriend proposed.
Oh, yeah?
But she says she's not
interested in getting married.
Here.
Tomi said an ex-boyfriend
cheated on her.
So she can't trust men
and has no illusions
about marriage.
That's terrible.
What is?
Him cheating on her.
If you cheat on me,
I'll stab you.
Good evening.
Welcome.
Nice to see you.
Enjoy.
Looks delicious.
You're such a good cook, Ruriko.
No, I'm not.
You put grated carrots
in here, right?
You don't like carrots?
No, I like them.
My brother still
won't eat carrots?
He's such a picky eater.
I sneak them in, but don't tell him.
Where is he?
One second.
Hello?
- You guys are such a strange couple.
- Why?
Calling each other by cell
in the same house.
I mean, locking your room
is such teenage behavior.
It's a habit.
Don't you hate it, Ruriko?
But the cell phone is handy.
That's not what I mean.
You're perfect for each other.
A rose blooms on the bush.
There is no greater mystery.
What?
I saw this movie.
It said what couples need are
a red rose and a white rose.
The red rose is passion.
The white is truth.
Couples get along if they have
both of those.
Are you listening?
- Sure.
- Really?
Say.
We'll get to the station soon,
won't we?
Shall we stop for
a cup of tea somewhere?
- No, I have to go.
- Already?
Yeah, I have to go to the electronics store
and I won't be needing dinner.
We can't even spend
your day off together.
See you later.
Off you go.
Hello.
Iwamoto!
You never show up anymore,
not since you got married.
You're right.
You're looking good.
Of course.
Cheers, then.
Have you been diving?
Not at all.
What a waste, after you got
your instructor's license.
You know that hostel in Izu
we trained at every year?
We're all going to go diving there.
Want to join us?
I'd love to go,
it's been so long.
I wasn't sure which,
so I brought red and white.
- I'll have the red, then.
- Sure.
Thanks.
Cheers.
You're in the I.T. Business?
That's right.
Miura, what do you do?
I work in an aquarium.
You don't look the part.
I don't?
I don't mean anything by it.
I started diving because
I wanted to watch fish swim.
I love how slippery fish are.
I like fish so much better
than mammals.
Because you can't tell
what's on their minds.
You can't tell what's on
mammals minds either.
What's your wife like?
What's she like?
Well, she's beautiful.
I know that.
Do you ever fight?
Not at all.
What? Never?
You've been married 3 years, right?
You're really in love.
Not really.
She has a loose grip on reality.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No, not for a long time.
Do you still love your wife,
as much as you did 3 years ago?
I'll get more wine.
Hey.
Going home already?
Yeah, I've had it.
Your wife is waiting, huh?
It's not that...
See you.
Hey!
Can I see you again?
I'd like to see you again.
Can I?
Sure.
See you.
Welcome home.
Hi.
How was your reunion?
I saw Nemoto again.
He sends his best to you.
That's all?
A younger alumna gave me
guest tickets to her aquarium.
She said to bring you.
That's all?
Yeah, that's all.
Strange smell.
I'll take a bath.
Are you hungry?
No, I'm fine.
OK.
What a great crowd.
It was your most crowded
show ever.
Thank you so much,
you really saved me.
The pleasure's mine.
I'd like to go celebrate
but I have to go home.
Satoshi doesn't like being
home alone. I'm sorry.
No, no, next time.
Shall we have a sip of wine?
- Really?
- Remember that gift bottle?
Oh, great, I'll go get it.
Are you Iwamoto Ruriko?
Yes.
Could you give me this bear?
Are you the one who called?
You know him?
He keeps calling, asking for Nana.
I keep turning him down.
I saw them all,
but this one is special.
I told you, it's not for sale.
You like teddy bears?
No, not usually.
My girlfriend loves this bear
and just has to have it.
You're so kind.
You can have it.
- I can?
- He can?
Her name is Nana.
I'm home.
OK.
- You're home.
- Hi.
- Did you eat your dinner?
- Yeah.
- What did you eat?
- A beef-rice bowl at the station.
Oh.
Would you like a cookie
I was given?
Sure, thanks.
How was your show?
Good. Lots of people came.
Someone who insisted
on having Nana came.
He seemed desperate so
I gave it to him.
Yeah?
Are you renting all those?
I'm Tsugawa Haruo.
You gave me the teddy bear,
Nana, at your show.
Oh, hello.
Do you live nearby?
Yes.
Me, too, 10 minutes
by bike.
Miyako, this is Iwamoto Ruriko.
Really? Oh, wow.
It's like a dream.
This is Miyako, my girlfriend.
Is Nana well?
Yes, she's staying at home today.
I'm so happy to meet you.
Could we buy you a cup of tea?
I'm sorry.
I don't have time today.
Too bad, but next time.
OK, next time.
Excuse me.
Promise?
OK, I promise.
Hello?
Oh, sure.
Why do you play music while
you're playing a game?
I kept knocking.
Sorry.
I found some lychees
today, still on their branch.
Oh, yeah?
Enjoy.
Thanks.
What?
Can I sit next to you a little?
Sure, go ahead.
Ruriko.
Yes?
Um, why do you
want to be here?
Am I bothering you?
It's not like that.
There you go.
Thanks.
There isn't enough romance
in this house.
- Romance?
- Yes, romance.
That's not true.
Yes it is true.
What should I do?
I don't know.
To tell you the truth,
I don't even know if we need it.
But I do know it's missing.
Maybe it's missing because
it's not necessary.
Sometimes when I'm with you,
I get so lonely.
I'm sorry.
This room is so relaxing.
Maybe because
the table's so cold.
Here, enjoy.
What is this?
It looks like a potato.
It's called "Pomme de terre,"
a French pastry.
It's made out of potato
and marzipan.
I see, there's even a sprout.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I do.
A lover actually.
He pays me so he's a lover.
Did I surprise you?
No.
Don't tell my brother, OK?
But you know, recently,
he's cooled off.
Want to know a good tip?
Solanine is best
for a double suicide.
Potato sprouts have a poison.
If you grow lots of them, cook them
and eat them together, it's over.
Solanine isn't a poison.
You'll just get a sick stomach.
Really?
That's right.
You're so funny.
I see.
Hello?
Yes, he is.
OK, I'll tell him.
Iwamoto, a guest
for you at reception.
A guest?
- Were you surprised?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry, I just suddenly
wanted to see you.
I thought lunchtime
would be OK.
Sorry, is it creepy?
No, not at all.
It feels nice to be outside.
I work at the aquarium everyday,
so I feel like I'm
locked up somewhere.
You should have called first.
I'm not always at work.
Well, it's fine.
I just took a chance.
Besides, you were there.
Shall we sit here?
For you.
Thanks.
These lunch boxes are
really famous.
I'm into gourmet stuff
and I love to eat.
I can tell.
That's mean.
Are you saying I'm fat?
No, no, no.
Here's some tea.
Thanks.
You never visited the aquarium.
I gave you those tickets.
Yeah, sorry.
What's your job
at the aquarium?
My job?
Well, let's see.
It's not a glamorous job.
Prepare their food and clean up.
And fish eat fish.
So my hands always
smell fishy, right?
They don't smell.
Really? I'm glad.
I just had a good idea.
Let's eat lunch together
every Wednesday.
Wednesday's my day off.
It was just an idea.
- Thank you.
- Thanks. I'll just check inside.
Oh...
I'm not sorry.
I always wanted to.
Always?
Since I first met you
at your show.
I have to go home.
OK, see you.
Why do you look scared?
I'm not.
Hold me.
Hold me until I say it's OK.
Thank you.
I like windows.
Outside it's night and it's dark,
but inside,
it's safe.
Want to go to your room?
No, I...
You want to play your
game, right? Go ahead.
Thanks.
My fourth one.
What?
I have a promise with Satoshi.
To not smoke more than
10 cigarettes a day.
I try to keep stupid promises.
How often do you do it
with your husband?
Do what?
This.
We don't.
Not true.
Be careful.
It's true.
Of course, we did it for a while,
after we got married.
But not in the past 2 years.
Huh.
But you sleep together?
In a double bed?
Yes.
We'd better stop doing this.
Why?
Because it scares me.
I'm scared, too.
You won't stop this, Ruriko.
Why do you think so?
Because you're passionate.
Probably because I am, too.
What does it mean
to be passionate?
I have to go home.
I've fallen for someone.
Even though I only want
to love my husband.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
I won't be that late,
I'm fine.
OK.
Will do.
Enjoy.
- Shall we?
- OK.
Cheers.
Delicious.
Yes, it is.
Is this OK? Was your wife mad
because it was so sudden?
I told her I'm with
a club member.
Right.
The one called Miura.
She remembered that you came
to our wedding after-party.
She remembered you're cute.
Doesn't your wife get jealous?
She does.
My wife says, she's jealous of not just
women, but my boss, my colleagues,
even my desk at work.
Strange.
Sounds a little complicated.
I can't really understand that.
But that's probably because
you're so honest about everything.
You think?
She won't know
if you don't tell her.
Excuse me.
This is the best restaurant
in Tokyo.
It's in the magazines and usually
there's a one month wait for a table.
Thanks for the food.
Isn't this absolutely delicious?
I don't like shrimp.
You don't? Really?
Then, I'll eat yours.
I'm so happy.
Meeting at night,
it feels like a real date.
You think?
Will you see me again at night,
from time to time?
Remember those plans to
go diving with Nemoto?
- They were canceled.
- They were?
Nemoto said he couldn't go,
even though it was his idea.
I see, too bad.
Yes, too bad.
So, shall we go?
Together, the two of us.
It was just an idea.
Satoshi, do you think
I'm passionate?
Passionate?
No.
Really?
Oh, good.
Ruriko.
Yes?
Do you have any secrets
you keep from me?
Of course, I do.
Diving?
I'm not going diving,
Satoshi is.
Why are you going, too?
I'm going to read on the beach.
I like staring at the ocean.
So do I.
It's on a holiday,
so I couldn't see you anyway.
I'm not mad I can't see you, I don't
want you to travel with another man.
He's not another man.
He's my husband.
What?
One more time.
I'm already dressed.
Undress again.
What a beautiful day.
Say, what will you do
if I break up with Miyako?
I wouldn't do anything.
There's nothing I can do.
I thought you'd say that.
I have to go home.
Wait, I'll see you home.
You can sleep.
No, I'm fine.
I feel like we're running away.
From what?
It doesn't matter what.
Here.
Take a look.
It's amazing.
It's nice to share memories.
We see the same things and
remember the same things.
Are you newlyweds?
Is that how we seem?
Yes, you get along so well.
To tell the truth, we're eloping.
What is it?
This spot OK?
Yes, I'll be reading.
I'll be off, then.
Isn't it a little creepy?
Diving where people have died?
If you say that, you can
never go diving.
I see your point, but...
Be careful, OK?
You're unbelievable.
I'm sorry,
but I had to see you.
What on earth were you thinking,
doing this?
I looked for you for 2 hours.
Thankfully, it's a small harbor.
I heard about the double suicide.
You did?
I thought it was you two.
Why?
I wonder why...
Have you seen the ocean?
Yes, plenty.
Let's go, then.
I had to see you.
I missed you, too.
I had to come to see you.
Don't be mad.
Why would I be mad?
I'm so happy to see you.
That's the truth.
- But...
- But?
No, it's nothing.
Aren't you cold? I am.
I'll make some tea.
It's OK, sit down.
Thank you.
If you hadn't invited me,
I might never have gone
diving again in my life.
No, I'm the one that's happy
being able to dive with you.
Oh, I'm so happy.
I was afraid you might not
really show up.
That I couldn't see you.
Actually, I was
a little anxious, too.
That you might not be here.
Of course I'd be here.
Anywhere you ask me to.
I promise.
When I was waiting for you,
all alone,
and just listening to the waves,
it really cleared my head.
I was just filled up
with wanting to see you.
I bet you can't imagine
the terror of losing you,
if I ask you for more.
I have to go.
Stay a little longer.
Satoshi's a window.
Satoshi is my window.
Good morning.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
Hey, poached eggs, today?
Yes, they're poached.
- That's great, I've been craving one.
- Craving?
I'm glad.
We think alike.
Bon appetit.
Enjoy. Bon appetit.
The human body is warm, isn't it?
You didn't know?
I'd forgotten.
Maybe what I really want
is your body heat.
I have to go.
Women look so small
when they're dressed.
Why do they look so big
when they're naked?
We do?
The four of us should
go out together.
Miyako wants to see you.
Besides...
Besides?
I want to see what he's like.
Your husband...
Thanks.
Thank you.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Oh, it's Nana.
I brought Nana here to see you.
I often take her abroad
with my job.
Oh, where do you work?
At a travel agency.
I escort newlyweds and
elderly couples on tours.
So, Nana's been
all over the world.
Until I met Nana,
I thought only lonely people
wanted teddy bears.
But I was wrong.
The bears you make are lonely.
Please.
Thanks.
Don't you attend?
Ruriko's shows.
It's just not a world
I understand.
I keep meaning to go...
Not me, I'd be
the first one there.
I mean, if it was
Miyako's show.
What are you talking about?
I'm the jealous type.
I wouldn't even want
other people to see it.
He doesn't need to see my
shows for us to be connected.
It's scary.
What is?
I feel like we get better
each time we meet.
You don't want us
to get better?
That's not what I mean.
You're so mean.
Leaving already?
I feel too comfortable here.
If I stay, I won't be able
to leave.
Then I hope you can't leave.
You can't leave and you don't.
Don't be impossible.
Ruriko.
What?
I might break up with Miyako.
I want to break up.
Even though our breaking up
might not affect you.
Why don't you say something.
Tell me it doesn't affect you.
Just be your normal, rational self
and say it doesn't affect you.
Either that, or...
Or just lie and tell me
it does affect you.
It does affect me.
And that's not a lie.
I can't lie to you.
You know that, right?
Because you won't
lie to me, either.
And you see...
See what?
Do you know why
we can't lie to each other?
We lie to whomever we
want to protect.
Or whatever we're trying
to protect.
Just the way you lie
to Miyako.
And the way...
I lie to Satoshi.
But I love you.
You're cruel.
Ruriko?
I'm sorry.
Time for tea?
No thanks.
The moon is white tonight.
Did you notice?
Ruriko.
Yes?
Want me to hold you?
It's a first.
Your wanting to hold me.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
How did he know?
I told them it was our anniversary
when I reserved.
Really?
This is a first.
Well, then...
That's all right.
You act like it's special.
It is special.
But we'll be back next year.
Marriage is forever, right?
What a lovely restaurant.
A co-worker told me about it.
Please thank them for me.
It's crowded, isn't it?
It's popular.
The best restaurant on Tokyo.
It's in all the magazines and
takes one month to book.
Really?
Not hungry?
Come on,
say something.
Can I hold your hand?
What are you thinking?
Nothing... What?
Nothing.
What is it, Tomi?
I know it's sudden.
I'm going to get married.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm sorry to be late.
No, I'm sorry.
Don't be. I got to take
a break, so I'm happy.
Suddenly, I wanted
to see you at work.
Is it OK?
Here at your job?
There are lots of couples here,
so we'll stand out less.
Every day, I marvel at how many
different kinds of couples there are.
It's mysterious how in couples,
males and females start to look alike.
Look.
See?
Don't they look alike?
And those two, too.
Something wrong?
I'm sorry, I just
remembered a deadline.
I'm sorry, I'll make it up
to you next time.
What were you doing?
Nothing special.
Nothing?
That's right.
Just spacing out.
Don't touch that.
Hello?
I'll be right back.
- An emergency?
- Sorry.
That's fine, I'm free
so I'll wait here.
If my brother comes home before
you, what should I tell him?
Ruriko... you're glowing.
Give this back to Haruo.
I don't want it anymore.
Don't think you're the only
lonely one.
I didn't think you'd come.
No.
I worried.
I worried a lot.
You hold on to this.
That's her fate.
This isn't...
The least bit sweet.
Calm down.
I'm the one that split up.
Why are you crying?
It makes no sense.
It makes sense.
Because I love you.
That's...
That's terribly sweet.
Ruriko.
See you.
Say...
This deep?
Hello.
Plant this, too.
Oh, sure.
Coffee?
Do you want a cup?
It's nothing to be sad about.
Say, look at that.
Do you know what it is?
I don't.
It's aconite.
Its flowers are quite beautiful.
A long time ago,
I used it to kill my husband.
Why?
No reason.
Well, I guess
because I was lonely.
Human beings are monsters
while they're alive.
But once they're dead,
oddly enough,
they become human.
Care for sugar?
And now?
Yes?
You're not lonely now?
Of course...
I'm lonely.
Whether you're together
or alone,
it's lonely.
A rose blooms...
on the bush.
There is no...
greater mystery.
A rose...
There is no greater mystery.
Past its bloom,
it falls from the bush...
as the light.
What's wrong?
Get closer.
I want to be even closer.
I wish that door would just
stay closed.
And we'd be,
trapped in here together,
forever.
See you.
Ruriko?
Welcome home.
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
I designed a new bear.
Oh, I see.
It looks like you.
Thank you.
Shall I hold you?
I'm home.
I'm the one that came home.
Were you away?
Yes, I was.
I was away.
I'm home now.
Welcome home.
And you?
I'm...
I'm coming home soon.
We'd better get going.
It's pretty far.
Sure.
What's that?
It's their wedding present.
Tomi wanted them.
Remember when we talked
about sharing memories?
Maybe it's not enough
just to have memories.
Maybe it's more important
to remember them.
To remember them together.
Shall we go?
Starring
Miki Nakatani
Nao Omori
Chizuru Ikewaki
Juichi Kobayashi
English translation by
Linda Hoaglund
Subtitle timing, editing and additions
for this version by famitsu1
Special thanks to
ikeda69
Based on a Novel by
Kaori Ekuni
Written by Kyoko Inukai
Music by Takeshi Senoo
Director of Photography Isao Ishii
Directed by Hitoshi Yazaki