Excuse me, I'm just getting changed.
- Chief Inspector Tung is here!
- What's he doing here?
Keep him talking,
I'll be in the back.
Chief Inspector Tung?
- Please, come in.
- For you.
Thank you. How can I help you, sir?
- I was just passing by.
- And the flowers?
I confiscated them from a hawker.
I must say you've got a
very pleasant place here
so bright and airy
and beautifully decorated.
It really has a woman's touch
about the whole place.
And such a wonderful scent
of fresh flowers, too.
Oh, yes, your two officers
are right...
My two officers what?
- My two officers are what?
- Where are your officers?
They're all downstairs
waiting for me.
I'll patrol around this area everyday.
Just in case.
What is it?
- Are you all right?
- Indigestion.
It's hiccups. I have a cure.
Does it work?
It's a very ancient remedy.
It can cure hiccups.
You're cured. It always works.
- Are you better now?
- Yes, I am.
If you have hiccups again,
you know what to do.
I was wondering...
- Why don't we put them in a vase?
- Yeah? Sure!
Let me help you.
- Where's the water tap?
- Behind you.
Normally I close this window
when I'm cooking.
Are you cooking now?
No, I'm not cooking now,
I may as well leave it open.
You've got a problem here,
but I can fix it.
Thank you.
Here.
Don't move.
It won't hurt,
it's just a little water.
Stand back or you'll get wet.
It won't take too long.
I'll go and get a towel.
All right, the coast is clear.
I'm sorry. I fixed it,
but I got all wet.
Thank you.
- So you know about plumbing?
- Sure.
I was chief of waterworks before.
My uniform's wet.
- I'll hang it up for you.
- Thank you.
Enough heroics.
You're still here?!
There are lots of police downstairs.
Keys.
Quick! Hurry!
Maggie!
Where are you?
- Finished! Where will I put them?
- In the living room.
Can you hang this out to dry
and lend me a shirt?
- What's up?
- It won't open.
Let me.
The humid weather
makes the wood expand. Hold this.
Try this side.
There.
- I hope this will do.
- It will have to.
- Thank you.
- I'll iron your jacket.
No, it can't be ironed.
It must be hang-dried.
It's all right.
I'm patient. I can wait.
- That's what it was!
- They're...
They're handcuffs.
We use them on prisoners.
When you arrest a criminal,
you put this end on his arm
and you put this end on your own arm,
so he can't escape.
When there are two thieves
and one runs off, then...
Bingo! This guy can't move.
While you run after that guy,
this guy can't move. He can't escape.
- I left my keys in my jacket.
- I'll get them.
That must be your cousin.
Hi.
- It's Chun!
- Really? Tell him I'm not here.
No! He's here to see me.
- Tell him you're not here.
- He's already seen me!
Why did I handcuff myself?
I must hide.
I need a hiding place.
I'm just changing.
- Give me a hand.
- Go over there.
- All right, quickly.
- Go that way!
This way.
Ow! That hurt!
- Quick!
- Where will I hide?
- Under the bed.
- All right.
- This one here, it's safer.
- All right, the sofa first.
You must get under the bed first.
- All right, whatever you say.
- Come on, hurry.
Don't move.
- Sorry, I was just changing.
- That's OK.
- Chun, is this your beat now?
- Yes, it is.
Nice place you have here.
So, do you have any complaints
about the district?
- Yes, a lot.
- Really? What are they?
Well, it's becoming dangerous
around here. Just last night...
Forget it.
- Please, sit down.
- Thank you.
- I'll go and make some tea.
Oh, no. I've no hot water.
I'll get some drinks from the shop.
Don't worry.
Chun, do you visit everybody
as part of your police duties?
Yes, of course.
- I'd better go.
- Good idea.
Bye! Take care, Chun.
Don't forget if you're ever
in the area, feel free to drop by.
Me?
You're...
If Chun's gone, I'd better go, too.
What are you doing?
I thought I'd give you
a goodbye kiss.
No, you don't!
That was wonderful.
Hurry up now, or you'll be late.
You've had your kiss, now go.
- When are you going?
- Now.
I promised to meet
some of my officers.
- Well, OK?
- No. There are two men up there.
Another two?
- How did they all get in my house?
- What now?
- Come on, this way.
- Right.
Where are the damn keys?
Who are the bravest cops in history?
The Hong Kong blue boys!
You should see the way we catch them
Rain and hail and heat and typhoon
Nothing stops us, because
we're the toughest cops ever!
And who are the greatest people
in all Hong Kong?
It's our policemen
They don't need to catch any robbers
Because they're the crooks
They take bribes and get rehousing
They're clumsy and useless
Keep going, keep going.
And Mr Tung,
why do you have a moustache?
Because I'm proud of myself
Who are you? Let's get him!
- Are you alone?
- What are you doing here?
- Was it you?
- Go on, beat him up.
- Talk!
- Stab him. Stab his heart.
- Stab his thigh. Kick his ass.
- All right.
He's going to die!
Are you going to talk or not?!
- Go on!
- Don't hit him any more.
- Stop. He's not moving. Is he dead?
- No, he isn't.
Tell us or I'll blow your head off.
Hold it! I've got two hostages.
Move and I'll shoot them both dead.
- We have a hostage, too.
- Choy, are you OK?
Sure, he might live.
OK, we'll exchange a hostage,
but no funny business.
Move it!
Choy, are you hurt?
Don't move an inch.
- Sir, he did it!
- Go find the keys for me.
I was really worried about you.
I work for the dowager empress.
So what are you doing here, then?
I'm here to arrest rebels.
The Hong Kong police can't touch us.
We have different laws here.
And our laws apply to everyone
in Hong Kong, including you.
Lock him up along with this one here.
Send them back to Manchuria.
I can't find them, sir.
I know, let's shoot the lock off.
- What if you miss?
- I won't.
Lock them up first.
What about me? Look at me.
Be careful, sir.
Don't worry about me,
just get Ma back to the prison.
I'll change my signature next time.
Chief, your hand.
My hand's holding important evidence
which proves they're thieves.
- Where are your keys? Open it.
- Yes, sir.
I have the cuffs, but not the keys.
All right, I'll take them in.
Dragon, you're not free yet, you
have to be back in prison by sunset.
- I'll take him back.
- I can do that for you, sir.
- Come on, let's go.
- Move it.
You know what to do.
Out of the way! Stand back.
Dragon, you know the rules,
don't you?
Yes, sir.
Sir, can you take off the cuffs?
I won't run away.
I don't have my keys with me.
Dragon Ma, you're a dead man!
- Who are you?
- We're victims of your heroism.
We'll kill you today.
I've nothing to do with this.
Get lost, then.
- What about me?!
- Good luck.
This is for Captain San-po.
My keys! My keys!
- Stop there. Do you know who he is?
- I'm a superintendent.
We don't give a shit!
- Hey, up here.
- What?
- I said up there.
- I didn't hear you.
Come on, we've got to work together.
- Higher.
- Stop.
Out of the way!
Not that way.
We're police!
Help, we're being attacked.
This way, come on.
We've got to jump.
Quick!
- Stop there.
- Come on. Quick!
Come on, this way.
Open up. Open up.
Hold it!
- Over here, officer.
Why did you hit me?
Try this.
Come on.
- Come on.
- Upstairs.
No, you don't.
No, this way.
This way.
Come on.
You almost got me killed!
This way!
You! Tell me who you are
or I'll kill you.
Help!
Come on.
That hurts!
- It's them.
- They're officers!
Get the men inside, hurry!
Come down, the cops are coming.
Let's go.
- Bread?!
- Let's go.
- But it's bread!
- So what?
- They've gone.
- Everyone back to the station.
What?! Go after them!
- Where are you from, sir?
- Shandong.
- In all Shandong, there's no one...
- ...as tall as me?
No, as clumsy as you.
What's that?
Come on!
Once you're back in Canton,
you'd better keep a low profile.
- There are spies everywhere.
- I'll be careful.
I don't have much time.
Please give this to Maggie.
I hope when we meet again,
it will be in victory.
Sure.
- Goodbye.
It's Chun.
- Hey, Superintendent.
- Warden. Nice to see you here.
- Are you OK?
- He almost got me killed.
- Where are you going?
- Back to my office.
Great, you can take him back to jail.
Have you got the keys?
Go find the others.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Goodbye, Dragon.
Goodbye.
- Waiter, a cup of tea.
- Yes, sir.
This isn't the way to the prison.
It's a short cut to another place.
Where?
Hell.
What are you doing? Let me go!
What are you doing?
- Hurry!
- Let me go!
What are you doing?
We'll say he fell
in the water if they ask.
Right.
Come on.
- He doesn't look too good.
- He's hungry.
- How do you know?
- Aren't you hungry?! We all are.
- His head's real hot.
- He's got a fever.
This is all Dragon Ma's fault.
It's not Ma's fault,
it's all our own fault.
If I'd found us all proper jobs when
we landed instead of looking for Ma,
we'd never have ended up like this.
You should have said that
from the start.
But he killed many of our brothers.
It's his job, he's a policeman,
like it's our job to kill people.
- Why didn't you say that before?
- Yeah!
Who cares? Let's see
what's wrong with him first.
Are you all right?
I'm hot and cold.
- The hot and cold thing!
- What?!
- We've got to get some medicine.
- Come on.
- Thank you for letting my men go.
- Is there anything else I can do?
I came here to capture
some assassins.
Is our Government offering any help?
There's a reward of 5,000 taels
for each of them.
Maybe I can be of help then.
Chun, that will be brilliant.
- It was you who saved my life.
- If we didn't do what Chun asked,
you wouldn't have gone to jail.
- We owed you one.
- Why did you set me up?
We needed money to buy weapons,
so we did a deal with Chun.
Then we realised
we'd helped him set up a good cop.
Where's the necklace?
It's in the Commissioner's study,
inside one of his books.
You did save my life.
I guess I'll let it go this time.
- Are you going?
- Don't worry.
- I won't tell anyone your secret.
- That'll only help our revolution.
- But you still worry us.
- Really?
- You still want to be a cop?
- What else can I do?
Join us, the revolution.
If we had comrades like you,
we'd have a better chance.
I won't join you.
Are you still angry
about what we did?
You've got to bend the rules
to achieve a noble goal.
We're even prepared to sacrifice
our lives for the revolution.
That's exactly why I can't join.
There's no way I can bend the rules.
However noble the cause,
I can't change.
As far as I'm concerned, I couldn't
break the law to achieve any goal.
However, I do admire you.
I think one day you'll succeed.
I understand that to overthrow the
Government, lots of people must die.
But I won't ask people to do that
because I don't know what will be
left once the sacrifices are over.
So I'll remain a policeman.
I think every life is precious and
I want everyone to have a happy life.
A country of 400,000,000 people
is made up of individuals.
If they hate their lives,
how can they love their country?
I see what you mean.
I'll remember your words.
We're both working
for the people but in different ways.
So being a policeman
is noble after all.
But they won't let any good policemen
exist in a colonial region.
They'll destroy you.
I'm here to fight those people.
- Take care.
- Goodbye.
Uncle Koon,
she only left me a letter.
- Why did she leave in such a hurry?
- Maybe it was urgent.
- Thank you. I'm going. Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
OK, I'll go.
- Give me that axe.
- Let's hope this works.
Be nice.
Excuse me, brother, I need some
medicine, and can I pay later?
Sorry, we don't do that here.
But a life is at stake.
We're not a charity.
If everybody was like you,
we'd soon be out of business.
- Give it to him.
- Right.
But I'd like to know who you are
and what I did to offend you.
Perhaps I arrested your friends
by mistake before.
Wan, I'm going.
You can put it on my slate.
- My friend.
- What's wrong with your friend?
- The hot and cold thing.
- What?
- It's probably typhoid.
Keep quiet!
Uncle Koon, run!
Now you have a warrant,
no one will stop you.
This way please, sir.
- Move along.
- This is police work.
Here he is.
- Did you get it?
- Yeah, look.
- I saw Dragon Ma, too.
- Did you kill him?
No, he paid for the medicine.
They're all upstairs.
Uncle Koon, you first.
- See you later.
- Keep it.
Come on.
- It's Dragon Ma.
- Why is he still alive?
- Here, take this.
- Be careful.
Come on.
- Mr Chun, is something wrong?
- No, it's just an arrest.
- But we heard gunshots.
- None of your business, carry on.
Go on!
Move along.
Get going!
Dragon Ma, I'm going to kill you.
- Move it.
- Hurry it up.
I think this is
what you're looking for.
Chun, why the hell are doing this?
I'll tell you, you have your
conditions and I have mine.
Thank you. This is the one.
Yan-kit, why did you betray us?
You bastard!
So what? I'm merely carrying out
my duty to arrest rebels.
What do you want?
- Chun.
- Yes, sir.
- Your reward.
- Thank you, sir.
- And the others?
- I'll take them back with me.
- The boxes are ready, sir.
- Damn you, Chun!
- You were saying?
- Do you know what you're doing?
- What are you suggesting?
- You won't get away with this.
Don't worry, I will get away with it.
What have you got against me?
You were against me from the start.
I've nothing against you personally,
but you keep interfering.
And you had my men arrested.
The longer I let you live,
the more problems you'll cause me.
I was just doing my job
as a policeman.
You're a good cop, I'm a bad cop,
so we're never going to see eye to eye.
It's either you or me.
Do you understand?
That's enough. I'm not interested in
listening to your stories.
That's right. You'd better leave
before the night market starts.
But I don't want that man around.
Of course, I intend taking care
of him after you leave.
- Get on with it.
- Let's do it.
- Help!
- Maggie.
- Shut up!
- She knows nothing.
Forget her. I have something
special in mind for you.
- Take him away.
- Yes, sir. Move!
- Move it!
- Stop that!
Throw him in there.
- Go help the others.
- Yes, sir.
Yan-kit, switch it on.
Don't think you can get out of there.
It's impossible.
This batch of soy sauce
will be delicious.
Our company is famous for its sauce
and it's for export only.
Your flesh and blood will be in every
bottle, all to be shipped overseas.
Isn't that wonderful? Well?
You're doing fine.
Let's see how long
you can keep it up.
I think we need to add a little oil.
A little more there.
- He's escaped!
- After him!
Run!
Get the notebook.
Come on, hurry. Use the stairwell!
- What's up?
- It's a dead end.
Come on, this way.
Hurry! This way.
Hurry!
- Hurry up!
- Get a move on.
Don't let them escape.
You'll have to climb down.
- It's all right. Don't be afraid.
- No.
Take the basket.
- Come on.
- Hold on.
Just do like I do. I'll go first.
I'll catch you on the ground.
Go on, jump!
- You're safe. You can get off me.
- Quick!
This way.
Come on. Quick, but be careful.
Quick! Help her.
Help!
Try to find a foothold. Hurry up.
Give me your hand.
Don't come any closer.
Hold on tight!
Jump, I'll catch you.
No. Wait a minute, I'll get a board.
Go on, jump!
Let go! Come on!
- Take the notebook.
- You keep that. I can't make it.
Take the notebook and leave here.
We'll never escape.
- All right.
- Go!
Keep an eye on those two.
Block the exit.
Dragon Ma?!
- Give us the notebook.
- I've eaten it.
- Give it back and we'll let you go.
- If I'd wanted to go, I'd be gone.
Enough talk.
- We'll give you one more chance.
- No thanks. I don't need any more.
Get him!
- It's fits me.
- Get going.
- How do I look?
Go on.
Go to hell!
Luck is on my side.
Get the notebook.
Have you got it?
What are you doing?
Why did you hit him?
Get him!
You go that way.
Go back!
- Go and block his exit.
- Yes, sir.
Dragon Ma is not our friend.
But if you lay a finger on him,
we won't be very happy.
That's right.
Don't worry, I'll handle this.
Chief, Mr Chun has the situation covered.
Hold it!
- It's the warden.
- Bastards!
Excuse me, I have an appointment.
- Out of the way!
- Come on!
Hold it, Chun!
Here's your money.
Don't pull the rope
or the whole thing will come down.
Look out, it's falling.
Get out of the way!
Make sure Dragon's all right.
Thank you, whoever you are.
He's all right!
Chun's under there!
- Let my men go free.
- Why?
I'm a representative of
the Ching Government.
My men were acting in self-defence.
They must be allowed to leave.
What did you say?
- Did you hear that?
- No, sir.
- You hear what he said?
- Not a thing.
That's just what I thought.
- Dragon, are you all right?
- Yes, sir.
You're finished!
Let them go.
- Thank you.
- No need, I owe you one.
Dragon, what's going on here?
Dragon Ma.
- Do you remember why we came here?
- Yes, we do.
He's dead. Let's go.
- Dragon, who are they?
- Just some friends.
- You didn't introduce us.
- That's because I don't know them.
Dismissed!