Maybe I wore it down by dragging it along so much.
I'll go back to the store by myself!
I'll be waiting with Marlene.
Cloud, you'll come back too, right?
A little late there!
Isn't this fun, Boss?
What should I call out next?
Mother?
Figure it out, you who lack filial piety.
Go, Cloud!
There you go!
Haiya!
Nuoo~
Fly!
Not done yet!
Here!
Mother!
Boss!
Hey, pal.
Is this thing powerful?
It's a refinement of Shinra technology.
So you made it...?
I don't know about powerful,
but it sure is flashy.
Oh, really?
You like that, don't you, pal?
Guess there's no overtime today, yo?
Mother...
Mother!
Let's go, Cloud.
I was finally able to meet mother!
What's going to start now?
Mother will tell me.
...the spirits don't know anything, huh?
I'm just a marionette, after all.
Just like...
the old you!
Cloud, I brought you materia!
Don't shake it!
Hey, Cid!
Hurry and let us down!
Shut up!
Just jump! Jump!
Let them fight by themselves.
Wha?!
That guy's a spirit of Sephiroth.
You could say he's kind of like a larva.
Larva? Bug? He's a bug?!
Calm down, Princess.
You're saying
that he'll turn into Sephiroth one day?
Hey, do you think that Cloud knows that?
Probably.
I see...
Let's leave them alone.
I don't get it! Explain!
It's man's talk.
Discrimination!
Discrimnaaation~
Calm down, Princess!
Us men don't understand either!
Two years ago...
That strong feeling
that he definitely had during the last battle...
Though it was just two years ago,
somewhere along the way, he lost that feeling.
I think that it brought Cloud back to us.
Tsh... I'll wait 10 minutes.
Cloud sure is a pain, just as always, huh?
He's honest.
I'll show you my Reunion.
It's been a while, Cloud.
You lost your Geostigma?
How unfortunate.
Just what are you hoping for?
The spirits of the deceased who carried the Geostigma...
That, with the Lifestream, guides the flow of worlds.
Eventually it infringes on the planet...
What I hope for, Cloud...
is to use this world as a ship to sail the darkness of space.
As Mother did before me, you see.
One day we will discover a new world.
We will create our shining future on that ground.
What will happen to this planet?
Who knows... that depends on you, I guess.
Sister?
Oho... What made you stronger?
I don't want to tell you.
I thought of what to give to you as a gift...
Shall I give you despair?
Kneel, and show me your figure, begging for forgiveness.
What is most important to you?
Would you give me the happiness of stealing it from you?
I pity you who understand nothing.
There is nothing that isn't important!
Stay there for me, trapped in memories.
I...
I won't become a memory.
Brother...
Kadaj?
Huh?
Let's stop working so hard...
Is that you... Mother?
Let's go back with everyone, shall we?
OK.
He did it!
That's how it goes!
See?
Just like I told you.
A man!
Cloud-san's a man!
Cloud can do anything if he puts his mind to it!
Hold on tight, you guys!
You were always with us, weren't you...
Thank you.
Let's all go home together.
We can all have fun together.
Cloud!
Cloud's going to come back too, right?
Mother...?
Again!
How many times is it that you called me Mother now?
Isn't it nice to be yearned for?
I don't need a kid as big as this one!
Too bad...
Your place isn't here, I'm telling you.
Sister told us...
Cloud will come here, she said.
Welcome home.
I'm back.
There are still kids who have the Geostigma.
Yeah.
Alright, now we're getting you cured.
It's all right now.
Try your best.
Now, everyone jump in!
It's cured, it's cured!
You're all right now, aren't you?
Yeah.
I'm...
I'm not alone.