I've waited for a long time, Tezuka.
Sorry,
but we will be the champions.
The rules of the matches are one set match
and a tie-breaker. That is all.
Heard you guys are the "Golden Pair"
who has some invincible acrobatic double play.
- What double play? Can Seigaku really do it.
- One set match. Seigaku's serve. Play.
Go, team, go!
Jump a little higher.
Eiji.
The situation doesn't look too good.
- It's all right. It's still only-
- But...
Seigaku!
- Fight!
- Seigaku! Fight!
To give you guys so much trouble. Sorry!
Momo.
This is embarassing, right.
Eiji, use that move.
Okay.
- Yes!
- Happy.
- Keep it up.
A comeback is possible
because this is a game of doubles.
Reporting from Japan. Hai.
Game set and match.
Won by Hyotei. Seven games to five.
Oi, Echizen. I thought you were going to America.
Or are you getting ready to go?
Forget it, watch our show.
He's here. Echizen.
Second round. Doubles two.
Hyotei's profilic pair against Seigaku's incredible pair.
Here I go.
15 - Love
Yeah, we scored. That's great.
30 - Love
40 - Love
Game Hyotei. One game to love.
15 - Love
It's starting to progress.
Great, great.
What kind of joke is this?
- Defend.
- Yes.
Yosha!
Note: Inui is collecting data in real time
because the power of the opponents
exceeded the data that he had collected.
Game Hyotei. Five games to two.
You're gonna be defeated.
- Kaidou, can you still continue?
- Watch carefully.
Thanks for the hard work.
See, a straight shot.
Hundred percent.
Unfortunately, your ball won't make it over.
- Data tennis is starting to show its abilities.
- It's really a strong method.
Use that move.
Yosh.
Do it, Kaidou.
Game set and match. Won by Seigaku.
Seven games to five.
It's a pit between physical peserverence.
We can't lose.
Third match is beginning.
Hyotei's Kabaji against Seigaku's Kawamura.
One set match. Hyotei to serve. Play.
Hadoukyuu.
15 - Love
What!
Winner will be Hyotei.
If this continues, we'll lose.
Taka-san, that is...
I will definitely win this match.
I want to be in the Nationals.
Single-handed Hadoukyuu technique.
I can't play anymore.
Kabaji's stamina is actually drained.
The last ball doesn't count.
Singles three no game.
Chiku'so!
I'm sorry everyone.
Takashi, I love you okay! Good work!
Oyaji...
Don't give up.
Go, go.
Taka-san, lend this racket to me.
Fourth match is starting. Singles two.
Hyotei's Akugatawa against Seigaku's Fuji.
- Disappeared?
- 15 - Love
Wow, for real?
Seriously amazing, it disappeared. Amazing.
Disappeared.
No shit.
30 - Love
Disappeared again.
Amazing!
40 - Love
No doubt about it,
Fuji Shusuke is a genius.
Wind. I will show you. Hakugei.
I'm lucky,
I just tapped it a little like this.
Careful!
One more time,
the wind hasn't stopped.
Everyone is pressing forward.
Game set and match. Won by Seigaku.
Six games to love.
Next match is beginning. Singles one.
Hyotei's Atobe against Seigaku's Tezuka.
Tezuka?
Isn't he the Seigaku captain?
I can see better here.
What are you doing here
when not even regulars sit here.
- Go away.
- Go away. Oi.
- But I'm part of the team, aren't I?
- That's not what it is about.
Why would a fellow like you
be allowed to sit on the bench!
Why aren't you on the way back to America?
You're... a pain in the ass.
Echizen.
Look after it.
'Kay.
All for Atobe!
- All for Atobe! All for Atobe! All for Atobe!
The winner will be... me.
This place sure is crowded.
There he is.
- Are you done?
- Yes, I'm satisfied.
It's the first time we are playing against one another.
- Are you prepared, har?
- Yes.
Let's have the best match...
...of course the result will be my happy ending.
- Up or down.
- Up.
Up.
Of course.
The elbow...
One set match. Hyotei to serve. Play.
Here I go, Tezuka!
15 - Love
Be awed by my prowess.
Doesn't matter to me.
30 - Love
You're too naive.
Watch closely.
Oi look there,
Tezuka isn't moving a single step.
If it's not Zero-Shiki
then it will be Tezuka Zone.
All the balls that Atobe delivers are spinning towards Tezuka.
It's like they are attracted to him.
30 - 15
He returned all my balls.
It's coming.
30 - All
You're not playing badly eh, Tezuka.
But it seems like that arm
have not recovered fully, right.
What about his arm?
Heard he's got an injury in his left arm.
Don't talk about strange things, Atobe.
Just play with me seriously.
The four of us will practice with you.
That's called the Rondo to Destruction.
Remember it well.
That's high!
Oi, why didn't he smash the last ball?
It won't matter much just to win.
Let him play with that arm,
that's slowly breaking down.
If you go on playing the way you do,
your arm will be shattered.
No matter what, I want the team members
to go to the Nationals together.
- Hah!
- Game to Seigaku. One game to love.
Tezuka, you're really...
What a fearless guy.
30 - All
It's already been an hour into the match.
Tezuka, your arm would have already exceeded its limit.
Do you want to destroy your arm
just to win this match?
Here comes the Rondo to Destruction. Take this!
Again.
40 - 30
Yes!
Hyotei will lose?
Hyotei gonna lose?
Impossible.
One more ball.
One more ball left.
Just a little more.
- Tezuka!
Stay away!
The match is not over yet.
Tezuka-kun,
that's enough from you.
Excuse me, what will happen if Tezuka-kun
gives up the match? What will happen?
You don't know eh?
You don't know.
Excuse me, what will happen?
Saa... The one who's having a match with the sensei?
That Atobe is just waiting for this to happen.
- Captain, don't play any more.
- Please!
- Captain!
Tezuka!
- Do your best.
- I will.
Seigaku! Fight!
- Ike! Ike! Ike! Ike! Ike! Seigaku!
Ike! Ike! Ike! Ike! Ike! Seigaku!
Don't lose this after you've beaten me.
I will not lose.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Atobe.
Let's settle this.
Okay, come at me.
Game set and match.
Won by Hyotei's Atobe.
Seven games to six.
Hyotei! Hyotei! Hyotei! Hyotei! Hyotei!
Everyone, it's time for the next player.
Understood.
With Hyotei Gakuen winning two games too
and with no games left, the reserves will play.
Hyotei's Higaki against Seigaku's Echizen.
Echizen, do you still remember what happened
one month ago on the tennis court?
Higaki, we're counting on you.
- We are counting on you!
Isn't this what idiots say?
Don't be jabbering around me.
Apologize Higaki.
I can't forgive what you said just now.
If I lose, I'll kneel on the floor to apologize.
Higaki, you know what you gotta do?
The day I lose to that chibi is the day I die.
I'm a pro.
Sixth match.
Hyotei's Higaki against Seigaku's Echizen.
You... are the pillar of Seigaku.
Ah, you don't have to be so bothered,
it's just a tennis game.
But chibi, it doesn't matter
what kind of genius you are,
I won't give any chances. I'm the real genius.
A dog that doesn't bite barks the most.
Hoh! A kid like you wouldn't know.
Weak, huh.
Love - 15
- Out!
- 15 - All
30 - 15
That fellow.
40 - 15
Game Seigaku. One game to love.
Seigaku leading.
Damn kid, dares to look down on me.
Higaki!
Careful not to get hurt.
The match will start in a short while.
We are currently preparing the court lightings.
Everyone, please be patient.
15 - Love
You still don't know how I play?
Stand up!
Is he trying to break his leg?
Ku'so.
Echizen.
Echizen! Fight!
Oi! You guys are noisy.
You alright?
Show some respect! Oi!
Shut up!
Let's go.
What is it?
Don't be too bothered about
what the doctor said.
Don't force yourself to talk.
Those words will come naturally, okay.
Our dead parents will want that.
If it's about money...
...you don't have to worry.
Ku'so!
There are many better players in the country.
Try playing with them.
Experience it yourself.
You'll... be the pillar of Seigaku.
Don't kid around.
That's impossible...
...even if you do that.
I want to get stronger...
...stronger and stronger.
I will become stronger.
Amazing!
Yes! A comeback!
Concentrate!
Note: Echizen is using Split Step
to ease the pressure on his injured knee.
It also helps him to reach for the ball faster.
30 - 15
- 40 - 15
- Yosha!
Concentrate.
Concentrate harder.
Play with your spirit.
I will not lose!
This ball!
This is the ball.
This ball.
Ganbatte!
This ball!
Ah!
Announcing the results of this match.
Won by Seigaku's Echizen.
He did it!
- Good game! Wonderful!
- You're awesome!
I'm so glad!
I'm so glad! Awesome!
You're awesome!
Come back to training.
From today onwards,
we'll be challengers.
Captain, tell me if you need help
with your arm's recovery, okay.
I will remember.
Both team players
please assemble for the closing ceremony.
- Ike! Ike! Ike! Ike! Ike! Seigaku!
Ike! Ike! Ike!
Bow.
Thank you for the game.
Nanjiro-senpai.
Oh, sensei.
My son has been under your guidance.
Mada mada desu ka?
First, I better give a call to America...
...or they will come looking for me.
Later.
Echizen...
...this is yours.
Captain.
Oi, that's Rokkaku Chuu.
Is that Shitenhouji!
That is Higa Chuu?!
Look, even Rikkai is here...
Amazing.
Does it bother you?
Not really.
- Yosh, let's go.
- Hai!
- Yosh!
Mada mada da ne.