The foreigners are bringing over
them scary-ass foreign bugs, man.
They coming here in their luggage.
It's my job to prevent possible infestation...
- ...and contamination. That's my job.
- We doing business inside.
I can't let you come and hose
the place with bug spray.
Hey man. Maybe you need to talk to your manager
about that plan because that's my job.
- Manager's busy.
- Okay, that's your call.
That is your call, player.
But just remember this.
First thing tomorrow morning...
...the city...
- ...they gonna send their quarantine people.
- Quarantine people?
They gonna shut you down.
Non-compliance.
Wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
Hold, man, come here.
Let me talk to you for a minute.
You ain't fucking with me, are you?
See that little motherfucker up there?
That's me. That's me.
I am a licensed exterminator, man.
Why I gotta fuck with you?
Look. Come here. Let's do this.
You take me to a small place.
Small room. Office or something.
You knyow. Someplace upstairs,
away from the customers.
That way when I set these bombs off,
the fumes, they don't go down there.
And then we come back later
and fix the rest. All right?
- Okay. Get a couple bombs. Come on.
- That's what I'm talking about.
You don't wanna be bit by one
of these motherfuckers.
Swell you up all around the neck.
Look like Oprah. Come on, get the door.
You know, some of these bugs
they got E. Coli and Mad Cow disease.
Check this shit out.
Is this Jackie Chan's office?
Oh, snap!
Man, you got a Jacuzzi?
Look at the ball.
How many freaks you get in here?
I bet you sit yours right there on
that ball. Sit on the ball, baby.
Sit on the ball. Keep it wet, baby.
- Smack! Smack it! Smack it!
- Hey! Hey!
- Just do your thing and go, bro.
- Yeah, all right, player.
All right. Look here.
Now you keep the door closed...
...and give this shit a full hour
before anybody steps in here, all right?
Damn.
- You're clear.
- Let's do it.
All right.
- You're crazy.
- I'm a father.
- Blow it.
- Daria...
...get ready to move.
What was that?
"Sometimes you just need
an old friend?"
- It came from the office.
- Watch her. Don't let her leave.
- They're not here?
- They're here.
- They're just somewhere else.
- What are you talking about?
- He stashed them here somewhere.
- What the hell we gonna do?
- Everybody just go.
- But, T, what about you, man?
I gotta save Vanessa. I gotta find them!
- I'm not leaving you.
- Yes, you are. Now go!
- Right here. Hurry up. Come on.
- Oh, shit.
Yo, T. Come on, dog. Let's get the hell out of here.
They're right outside.
Shut the fuck up and get out of here!
You know, I got the big one.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Keep it in your pants.
Who's in there?
You're wrong.
What you want?
- Yeah!
- Move away from him. Come on.
Nice cubic. Yours are real. Not.
I told you this was gonna take a while.
I was thinking about those diamonds
so I made a few calls.
My Defense Department connection
called me back and he tells me...
...about this rumor out of Taiwan about these
black stones. Only they're not jewels.
- Pretty beat up.
- Fell down the stairs.
Enjoy the jail sex, Fait.
Seven advances, 11's out!
Next up, 8 versus 12!
Eight versus 12!
Fighters report to the cage!
Let's go.
We're still here, T.
Got anything you want us to do?
- Nothing yet.
- What?
Nothing. Nothing.
Unofficial entry number 12!
- Unofficial entry number 12!
- Hey, 12's right here!
Kind of small, ain't he?
Let's go, chickenshit.
You're the chickenshit, buddy!
Not today.
I know this wasn't the plan,
but if you don't get in and fight...
...they'll throw us out
and we'll never find this guy.
- Sorry.
- Just find the ring.
- Hey. Two grand on the white guy.
- You got it, Archie.
Let's go! Come on!
Are you ready? Are you ready?
You win.
- You suck.
- Shit.
No quitting! Get your ass back in there!
Put me down! Goddamn! Come on!
- Put me down or I'll kick your ass, Bruce!
- I'm not Bruce.
Come on. Get up. Get out of here.
Get out of here.
Kick his ass!
Come on! Kick his ass!
Kick him. Take him down.
- Okay. He's all patched up.
- Ready to move.
Let's go.
Get the car. Stay close.
Hey! That guy's got my fucking quad!
I'm gonna get that motherfucker!
Hey! Wait!
Five grand on the Chinaman.
He's my friend.
At this very moment, a man
identified as Anthony Fait is leading...
...police on a wild high-speed chase
through downtown Los Angeles.
And get this, folks.
He's driving an all-terrain vehicle.
Yeah!
Come on! Kick his ass!
Oh, yeah!
Come on. Come on down.
That's the way to get that buck.
- Yo.
- I'm here.
Aboveground parking garage
in Chinatown. Get there.
I know the place.
Hey. Thanks, man.
- Do you like my new ring?
- Where is he?
Well, open the door.
Glad I brought my stunner.
All right, bud. You ready for the q and a?
Where'd you put the stones?
I ain't selling you shit till
I know where the ceiling is.
How much money
do you want for the stones?
- Where's my fucking butter, chick?
- It's almost ready.
See, I hate foreplay. Fucking warm-up.
A bitch gotta be ready to come off
the bench and score some points.
Just take the rock to the motherfucking
hoop strong. You dig?
Instead of doing this back-and-forth shit,
my idea is you come up with a number.
A very high number. You see,
I'm throwing a number so high...
...that when I hear it just...
It just gets me off.
And then, bam! Bust a nut,
roll over, go to sleep.
You like that?
Yeah, I like that.
Oh, shit!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Shit! Okay, okay, okay!
And it looks like this parking garage is where
it will end. As police have sealed...
...the building and continue
their search inside for the man who...
...led them on what certainly had to
be the most extreme chase we've ever seen.
- Don't know why these idiots do it, Barbara.
- They never get away, do they?
They sure don't, and they just endanger
innocent citizens in the process.
Here's another car exiting the structure.
Police talking to the driver,
inspecting the vehicle.
Well, the police know they have him
trapped inside the parking structure.
Knowing cops the way I do, I can tell you
they're good and PO'd, excuse my language.
And they're not about to let this guy
slip through their fingers.
Mr. Chambers is resting.
He says not to bother him.
Hey, baby.
Please don't go.
You want me to stay?
Yeah, I need someone to stay here
and help keep me awake.
Wait a minute.
I know that face.
A lot of men had that look on their face
when I got married.
I knew the stones were in there.
He was a tough guy at first, but when I got
close to his nuts he sang like Céline Dion.
Question is, how we gonna
get them out of there?
That place is always jumping.
Yo, dog, something's not right.
I got the same feeling.
The doorman.
Where is he?
Everybody stay put.
- Sorry.
- Watch my nuts, all right?
No Chambers' guys.
Something's wrong.
This guy looks better dead.
He said they were here in the fountain.
Where are they?
This can't be fucking happening.
They have to be here!
That's it? One stone?
- Ling. He has the rest.
- How the fuck do you know?
I know.
Okay. He has the stones.
I mean, she can't hurt him.
She's just a little girl.
She's only 8 years old. He'll let her
go, right? He'll just fucking let her go!
What am I gonna do?
We have to go.
Now.
- We're back in business.
- Good.
- We don't have to babysit much longer.
- I hate kids.
- Is everything else ready?
- Just have to test the device.
It's called the Dimaster Oscillator.
Not test. Calibrate.
Which I'm now ready to do.
Goggles?
Here you go, man.
Thanks.
Please work. Please work.
Please work.
Daddy, please. Daddy, please.
Please answer, Daddy, answer.
Want me to get that?
- Yeah?
- Daddy?
Vanessa?
Daddy, please, come and get me...
...I wanna go home!
Calm down, baby. Calm down.
Where are you?
I don't know!
I'm in a van inside a big building.
They painted the windows.
I can't look out!
You gotta help me, sweetheart.
I have to know where you are.
- I'm scared!
- I know you are, honey.
Just try to stay calm. Concentrate.
Look around. What do you see?
I don't know. I can't see anything.
You gotta try, sweetheart.
Try to see something.
I'm going. I'm trying.
I see chairs and green light.
Chairs. Green light.
Where's the light coming from?
I can't tell. There's a machine.
It's like a laser show.
- Laser show?
- Daddy...
...hurry! I'm scared!
- I wanna go home!
- Okay, calm down baby. Calm down.
It's gonna be all right, sweetheart.
Daddy's coming!
Daddy?
- Vanessa?
- Daddy!
Vanessa?
Vanessa!
Great!
Shit!
- He's doing it here tonight.
- Doing what?
Selling the stones. The Thai laser
emits green light. He needs it to enrich them.
- To show their power.
- What the hell are you talking about?
What are these stones?
A new form of synthetic plutonium.
Small and portable, but mega-powerful. Am I right?
There's a bunch of international
scumbags who'd pay a lot of money...
...to get their hands on those.
And then, look out world.
Enough of this shit!
How's it gonna get me
back my daughter?
We're operational.
The buyers will want to arrive
and leave quickly.
Somewhere private,
accessible by aircraft.
Vanessa did say she was inside
of a big building.
Could be a hangar.
There's about a dozen
little airports around here, man.
We ain't gonna never get them all.
- Flight plans.
- Yeah, flight plans.
They gotta list a destination.
Every aircraft that takes off...
...has to file one with the Aviation
Administration or risk getting shot down...
...by the U.S. Military.
So you get that list...
...and maybe we can find out where
the sale's going down.
Daria, call the aviation people.
Use our L.A.P.D. Credentials.
We need flight info on all aircrafts
coming in or going out.
Miles, the no-gun policy
is no longer in effect. Break out the heat.
Everybody else, get ready to move.
Tommy, create a diversion.
I got just the thing if we can fit in it.
Wick Airfield. Five private choppers arriving
tonight within minutes of each other.
- Sounds like our best bet.
- Better be for Vanessa's sake.
Let's go.
You are the world's foremost
arms dealers.
You all know that weaponry equals power,
and in the world of weaponry...
...nukes rule.
But nuclear material is hard to obtain
and difficult to handle.
But what if it weren't?
That's the question that brought
you here tonight.
And this is the answer.
A unique, man-made element.
In its present state it's completely inert.
Zero radiation...
...zero volatility.
One small fragment easily transformed
into a source of immense energy.
More powerful than weapons-grade
plutonium 100 times its size.
Goggles on.
So, what the hell does Taiwan
gotta do with this?
We developed the stones.
They belong to us.
Okay, what about the guy you're after?
How come you know him so well?
We grew up together.
We joined the government at the same time.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
You were on the same side?
He betrayed us. He killed our team.
He tried to kill me too.
If you don't take this
motherfucker out, I will.
The stones first, then him.
Creating a highly reactive
radioactive isotope...
...requires altering the atomic structure
of the original material.
Normally this is accomplished
by adding neutrons.
Here, we're using electromagnetic distillation
to strip away protons.
In the process, the fragment's potential yield
is increasing exponentially.
We're now reaching the yield level
of a sidewinder missile.
Enough power to take out a tank.
A Tomahawk cruise missile,
enough to destroy a building.
Scud.
That's a few city blocks gone.
Hiroshima.
Two Hiroshimas.
New world order.
The purpose of today's sale
is to begin trading...
...a new commodity on the black market
and to determine its value.
There are 50 stones available
in the first sale.
And the opening bid
is $200,000 per stone.
Bids, please.
I'll bid one million for five stones.
- I'll bid 1.2 million for five stones.
- 1.5 for five stones.
- 1.7 million for five stones.
- 2 million for three.
- 5 million for six stones!
- 5.2 for six!
- 5.7 for six!
- Sold.
- Seven million for 10 stones!
- 8.5 for 10!
Miles, what do you see?
We got five choppers.
Two armed sentries.
Checking the perimeter.
Perimeter is clear.
I'm moving inside.
They're still doing the deal.
There's a camper there.
- And the windows is painted out.
- Vanessa said she was in a van.
Can't see out. It's gotta be it!
Once we get her,
you two disappear fast.
I'll keep her safe.
- 8.7 million for 10 stones!
- 9 million for 10 stones!
- 9.8 for 10.
- 10 million for 10 stones!
- Sold! There are 37 stones.
- 16 million!
Miles! Hit them!
- Done.
- Tommy and Archie, watch the van. Punch it!
- 24.5 for 15!
- 24 and three quarters...
Twenty-five for 15!
Freeze, motherfuckers!
I knew it.
You heard the man. Party's over!
- I knew it.
- Just be cool.
Fucking amateurs.
Come on, man, just be cool!
I said, don't move, motherfucker!
She's out! She's out!
She's on the move.
Another time.
- There's a guy after her.
- Stay right here. I'll go get her.
- Holy shit!
- Come to Papa!
Shit! That motherfucker's shooting!
- What do we do?
- Shoot him!
Easy for you to say!
You do him.
Don't let him get away!
Oh, shit! Shit! Archie, I'm out of ammo!
- Fire the M-60!
- Get me closer!
Give me that!
How many times do we have to kill you?
Get him! I got this.
Go! Go!
- Go!
- All right!
- What happened?
- I don't know!
We're out of balance!
Retract the landing gear! Do it!
Do it now!
Shoot him down!
Shit! I'm out of ammo! What now?
- Load the cannon.
- How?
- Put the giant bullet into the hole!
- Oh, shit.
Oh, shit!
- There he is! There he is! I got him!
- Archie, shoot this motherfucker!
We're hit!
- Hey! Hey!
- You shot him in the ass!
We got it!
Shit!
Time to end this my way.
- Let her go!
- Let go! Daddy!
Daddy!
Damn! No shot.
You were lucky last time.
You won't be lucky again.
Daddy!
Come on, baby. Come on.
Wrong kid!
Definitely the wrong father!
- My baby!
- Daddy, I knew you'd find me!
So glad the angels kept you safe.
Another one?
You know it.
Never gonna let you go. Ever.
Guess we both got what we wanted.
So, what happens to the stones now?
They'll be destroyed.
Guess I'll be spending some time in jail.
Jail?
Come on, man. He just saved the planet, man.
Can't he at least get probation?
I'll do what I can.
- Thank you.
- That's great.
Because we make a hell of a team,
am I right? Except for you.
'Cause you're law enforcement.
But the rest of these guys we gotta stick together.
And a white guy comes in handy.
You wanna rip off a country club,
or somebody needs to hail a cab. Right?
- So, what percentage are we talking?
- None.
That low, huh?
It's about time I got my shit together.
- About time we all did.
- I'm with you, T.
Come on, buddy, it's just getting fun.
Well, I mean, you know,
it's not that fun...
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Faith.
So you guys are all just gonna
up and go straight?
Yeah. You ought to try it yourself, man.
I could do it. I've had straight jobs.
Have you?
- I've had plenty of straight jobs.
- Really? Name one.
I sold Avon.
- You were an Avon lady?
- I was an Avon man. All right?
- You got a problem with that?
- No, it's fair.
- Why you looking at me like that?
- I'm not! I'm not! It's okay.
I'm just fucking with you. But my mama
sold Avon. And don't be disrespecting her.
- I know her. Remember the party?
- She whipped your ass.
No, she sucker-punched me.
That ain't the first time you
been sucker-punched by a big woman.
You know, I think
I got kind of a fetish.
Did you just say my mama had a fat ass?
No, I said I have a kind
of a fetish for big women.
- Oh. But she do got a fat ass though.
- Yeah, she does have a fat ass.
You can see it when she's sitting
on your fucking head.
I've seen it. I had to rub that ass
naked when I was a teenager.
You know, you look a lot like her.
Except her hair is different.
Yeah. I shave my beard,
she keeps hers growing.
- Yeah. You know what?
- What?
I'm gonna write a movie about all the shit we
got through. I've been taking a few notes.
It's gonna make a lot of money for us.
I'm calling it Sidekicks.
We're the real stars of this.
We shot down the damn helicopter.
- Who's playing you?
- I've been thinking about that.
First I thought Arnold Schwarzenegger,
then I saw him one time at the gas station...
- Midget.
- He's like 5'6".
- Got a terrible lisp.
So I'll go with Mel Gibson.
We have similar features.
Right. I see the forehead.
- Yeah. And you? Guess.
- Denzel!
Denzel!
- You noticed I've been cutting it down.
- And he's been beefing up.
- I'm trying to get it down to Denzel's weight.
- You know who will be your girlfriend? Oprah.
- Big Oprah or little Oprah?
- Medium Oprah.
That's the one I like
because the eyes are straight.
- This is about reality.
- Right. Realism.
- Yeah. So you know who's my girlfriend?
- Who?
Halle Berry. And let me tell you why.
It'll add a whole different element.
This is gonna be an interracial couple.
She's never done that before.
Also, Fait. I've been thinking about
that a lot. I'll go with Shaquille O'Neal.
The most dominating player ever in the NBA.
You saw Kazaam.
- Right
- It wasn't the right material.
He's gonna kill with this stuff.
And Su, I've been thinking about him.
- Remember the movie Sixteen Candles?
- Yeah.
- Who am I thinking about?
- Molly Ringwald?
- No, the Donger!
- Oh! Okay!
How funny was that guy?
What happened to him?
- He waiting tables someplace.
- He was funny!
- Yeah, he was. Hey, Daria.
- Daria? Who you got?
- Winona Ryder.
- Yeah, she's good. She'd be good.
- Yeah, she's good.
- She'd play a thief.
She'd play a thief. She a good actress.
The whole elbow thing.
Remember when she's going to court
and hit the one elbow, broke that elbow.
- Electricity went through her body.
- She's a ventriloquist with the elbows.
Now who do we get to direct this thing?
You know what?
We should get the same dude that directed
Romeo Must Die and Exit Wounds.
- The director, the Pole, Polack.
- The Polack?
Yeah, we'll get him in there.
Exit Wounds, did you see that?
- I saw that.
- The best part...
- The end.
- The very end.
- Over the credits. The rest of it sucked.
- You can't have the movie without the end.
- There's no movie.
- Whatever happened with those two guys?
I heard they're gay.
Yeah, of course. Hollywood.