Fine, but...
You are insurance broker?
My last name's Cheuk
Mr. Cheuk
It's getting more and more complex
You come so far to indemnify. Very nice
Stay for dinner
Sure, sure
What is that?
Watch it. You'll know
I'll watch it later
Mr. Cheuk
Mr. Cheuk, he's calling you
You are hard-working
Still working while on leave
I want to settle this quick for Onion
Dr. Woo, you work hard too
Ain't you on leave?
Mr. Cheuk, I think we never met
How do you know my name?
We never met...
Doing insurance
you had to know everything
Onion died too suddenly
We had to check people out
Occupational disease. Blind guess
Mr. Cheuk, you look not well
Your lips are dark
You better have a check
It's professional. Not blind guess
I queued and
bought a cheese cake
For dessert
Try it. You'll feel better
Autumn hates cheese
She only likes fruit candies
The octagon ones in colorful cans
I can't believe it
You know even that others like to eat?
I don't eat cheese
Why do you know?
Are you checking on me?
You think I killed him?
No... How could I?
I don't mean it
In fact, I am...
Here it comes again
What's the matter with you?
How's it going?
Sis, do you have slippers?
For men or women?
Better check out...
the nearest hospital
Just in case...
Autumn?
Back in her room. She's pissed off
I didn't mean it
I didn't check on her. Please tell her
Okay, okay...
You threw...
everything up
Have some cheese cake
Sis
The doctors often suggest...
...not to eat too rich after vomiting
No cheese cake. You have something flat?
Apple
Have it
Can we talk,
Dr. Woo?
Sure
Can we donate Onion's money...
to the hospital...
...for ophthalmology studies?
He wished to help
Sure. I can suggest to the hospital...
...to launch a fund...
for the blind people
I thought you really were busy,
have no time to go to concerts
Now I know
I am quite jealous of him
Sorry,
it seems not respectful
I think...
he doesn't want to see you like that
Could we go to concert tomorrow night?
Can we talk tomorrow?
Hope to see you tomorrow
It's getting cold. Let's go in
It's late. Please go
Give Mr. Cheuk a ride, would you?
Where's Mr. Cheuk?
I don't know what you want
I won't...
Iet you hurt Autumn
I don't have time. Stop the car
You want to vomit?
Thanks for having taken care of Onion
Bye
Where are you going?
I won't let you go back and bug Autumn!
Would you please get in?
I won't leave
I didn't ask you to leave
I won't let you bother Autumn
Let me go back with you
Okay?
Mr. Cheuk,
personally I don't like you
But...
you are a patient to me
You might get pneumonia,
triggering epilepsy
Get in, would you?
Thank you
I must keep an eye on you
You broke my car
I have to take you to the police
You like her
You do too
Right
She told me she cared about me
You've been in our hospital?
Did she take care of you?
But the way I see it...
I think you've got it all wrong
What do you mean?
Nurses always cares about patients
Especially someone like Autumn
But it's different from...
what you think
I am not saying this because I want her
I hope you get it
Didn't she read the letter?
Will she believe it?
Maybe she never ever like me
She just pities me
I am just a common patient to her
I know you want me to regret, right?
How could angels be so unkind?
Good morning
- Good morning
- Staying late?
No, I have a date with you
Not sure if I can get up. So I stay
Where is he?
Who?
Mr. Cheuk! My car's locked
He didn't leave?
Never mind. I'll make some coffee
- Take a seat
- Okay
Could you give me a ride later?
Where to?
Anywhere, take a break, go to concert
Sure
Did you read it?
You wait a whole night here for that?
I read it
Good! You finally got it?
I am sorry... Mr. Angel
I was irrational
You didn't hear a thing
Are you alright?
Did you really read it?
Didn't miss anything?
I don't know what's in your apology card
And this tape's blank
But I accept your apology
Please proceed with my indemnity
and stay away from me afterward
If Mr. Cheuk ever comes...
to the hospital again
Do pay us a visit
We are in charge of ophthalmology
I know, I specialize in the blind
I'm always there. So I understand them
Sometimes I even touch their books
Like Onion's point diary
I know a lot from that
Diary?
I didn't know she'd react that way
Even ask me out tonight
She wants...
to see Onion's diary
But when did I write diary?
Sorry, I really can't...
It's okay. The show is boring
I'll take you back
No, it's fine. Thanks for the ticket
You have a date with someone?
Him
I can take care of myself
Give me a call if you need me
Diary, diary...
The whole diary in one day?
What the hell. No time
Excuse me. I am late
It's alright. I am early
This is...
I think you better not see it
You might feel upset
You know point alphabet?
Sure, more than ten years...
I specialize in the blind
Could you read it for me?
Okay
Where to start?
Where you met each other
Sunny...
That's it?
No, there's more...
October 16, 1997, Sunny, Vomit
Dr. Woo said it's medical reaction
A new nurse came taking care of me today
Her name is Autumn Yue
She is clumsy
She kept saying...
"Sorry"
She made a mess,
but I didn't pick on her
I even feel good about her
Why am I still talking fine?
She doesn't know that I am Onion
I am just someone reading Onion's diary
Go on
November 2nd, 1997, Rainy night
Autumn said she'll come give me...
a hair cut after work
It's raining so hard. She might not come
She is already 49 minutes late
Feeling disappointed,
I heard footsteps hurrying up
"Sorry..."
Sorry. I'm late again
49-minute is nothing
I was thrilled she came
Finally, she finished
It looked like an onion
She starts calling me Onion ever since
December 7, 1997, Sunday, Good day
It's the second time Autumn cut my hair
I can smell her
Just when I was enjoying
My left ear hurt so much suddenly
And I heard she keep saying...
I'm sorry
Oh, I cut you ear
You're bleeding. Are you okay...
I shook my head, saying: Nothing!
She's all freaked out, almost crying
If only I could talk, I'll say
I am so happy she comes
Just a little pain. No big deal
Enough!
Stop it
I am sorry. Please burn it
Wait!
He pointed all that,
and rub it on the street
Don't you want to know more?
What happen if I know it all?
You won't understand how I feel
Only Onion will
He's dead. What's the diary for?
To save your memory?
No
I say
Just now...
I felt Onion's back
I used to think I just pitied him
Then he died
And I realize
it is so painful without him
I love him all the time
Why didn't I tell him?
I wanted him to know
I wished he's the one playing sax
Why didn't I ask?
My second wish is to be with him
Why didn't I say it?
Now I can't
Can it start all over?
What's memory for?
Just one day...
Give me one more day, can I?
Please!
You!
Why did you crash him? Why?
None of my business...
He rushed out...
Come on! Hit me!
I have nothing after all!
I shouldn't have come back!
I shouldn't have. Let me go!
Hit me!
I miss you so much...
You always miss me, huh?
Sit
What do you want to drink?
Anything
Your daughter?
Salty Lemon Seven
Thank you
Not so much. You will drop dead
You want to die?
No, I don't
My neck sores. Give me a message
When are you leaving?
Taiwan
Two more days
Are you coming back?
No
Sit
You're leaving, why stir things up?
Can't take anything with you
I know now
I just want to see her
If she's happy, I'll be happy
Now and see
Don't think too much
If she knew Onion's leaving again
She's be upset once again
What's that?
You want a florist shop, don't you?
My investment
Can't take it with me. Not in Taiwan
Okay
I'll sent you some later
What do you want there?
I'm going
Take care
Right...
If you see my daughter
Take good care of her
I will
Don't bug others anymore. Go
Not fair occupying other's thing
Hello, it's you
Me
Can't hear you. What's your name?
Cheuk
What do you want to talk about?
I wanted...
to phone-in long time ago
But I can't
In two days, I had to go
I've done everything
So I try this
Nothing special
You've done everything,
you feel good?
Better than a few days ago
A few days ago?
You felt bad a few days ago, why?
I saw the reality of the world
Ugly world,
you mean?
No, not ugly
But seeing it through your eyes
The world's different
Through eyes, you'll have greed
You want to possess her
The eyes fool
Interesting
Give us more details
Try not to see with eyes
Quietly close your eyes
In this minute of silence
Feel with your purest heart
You may find everything different
Feel the beauty and
happiness with heart
You'll have rooms...
of imagination
You seem to know yourself
Could you hold?
We'll talk more
Now, let's go to music
Okay, audience
If you have experience...
like Cheuk's
You might want to try
Close your eyes,
it may help
You scare me!
Sorry
I shouldn't call you so late
Never mind. What's the matter?
I know it is not scientific
But I really feel it, he's back
Slow down. Who's back?
Onion...
He's back with me
Very close
I don't believe in paranormal
I know how your feel
Just imagination. You miss him too much
It happens...
when a friend died
Should I come over?
That's not necessary
I know what you mean
I know you'd say that
But it's not imagination
Onion is back
Okay now
Sorry, I bother you
Thanks. Good night
Good night
This is the real Cheuk
The one we met is a crook
I've checked
He's on vacation, in US
For your own safety,
don't meet with him
Let's report to the police, shall we?
No. He didn't come again
Are you alright?
Take care of yourself
This is my final night
Why do you tail her all day?
Can you make her happy? I can help
That's not me
The one who played sax wasn't me
I don't want to lie to you
You mean Onion played it?
It's Cheuk
Cheuk!
Cheuk! Cheuk...
Come out! Onion!
Cheuk! Onion, come out quick!
I know you're here!
You're not coming out, are you?
Are you okay?
What's wrong with you?
You want to kill yourself?
Stupid!
I should have known you're Onion
And you're the one who played sax
Onion!
Freeze, Onion!
I am not him
Onion's blind and dumb, and dead
Stop imagining things
There's other for you. Such a fool!
I am the Cheuk. You know it
No, you're not
No, I'm not
I am a liar. I'm fooling you
You satisfy?
You've disliked me, haven't you?
Is there something...
you can't say?
Is there a special reason?
Why do you reject me?
I didn't...
I am not him
Fine
That night...
you just touched one line of the diary
and you told me...
everything about us
How could you know?
Unless you are Onion
It's fine you don't admit
You must have a reason
Just don't leave me alone
I am so careless
I didn't realize
until I see all the proofs
I am so dumb
Are you going now?
Yes, I had to
You'll never see me again
I am not anyone...
Forget it, Onion is dead
He never comes back
You must take care yourself
Go! Go!
Okay!
Excuse me, please wait
I have one last question
If you were him,
Seeing the one he loves so painful
What do you want her to do?
Forget me and love someone else
Live happily again
Let go of the painful memories
Okay! I'll tell him now
I've forgot his death
I won't carry the pains with me!
I will love someone again
And that's you!
But he stays...
in my heart
It's fine if you don't admit it
I don't care if you're Cheuk
But I know, I always love...
Who is the one I always love
Onion, you listen up
I love this person in front of me!
Don't go away
Don't leave me alone...
This is...
the meteor shower night
China is the best place to see it
I'll be here with you tonight
Onion told me
Your first wish was that he could watch
the meteor shower with you
It's the same you watch it with me
There's no meteor shower yet
You're a good person. God will help you
Then help me keep Onion!
Stay with me forever, would you?
That's my second wish
Onion had a second wish too
But it's already impossible...
It's 2:30 in the morning
Ten minutes to go...
for the peak hour
I wonder if Cheuk...
...will call again tonight
Hello, I'm Cheuk
I appreciate people caring about me
I want...
to say something to my love
Why not say it directly to her?
Because...
of fate
When I didn't expect anything
I owned her love unexpectedly
When I wanted her...
or made a choice
she went away, disliked me
I am leaving soon
Keeping the most unforgettable moment
Laughter or tears
I hope every bits of memory
be with the one I love most
Carry on with her life. Be strong...
Five days is very short
I want to tell friends in the air
Hold what you have
Now, or in the future
Even if it slips away...
I have no regret of this life
That's so touching
If only you were my boyfriend
May I offer any help?
Could you play a song...
for my love?
Sure. Let's go for the meteor shower
Before I hang up
I hope everyone close your eyes again
Feel the one...
by your side with your heart
You'll have better feeling
Meteor shower!
I've fulfilled my first wish
Make a wish, quick
No...
I did last time, you still have to go
Come back
when the meteor showers
"Wait for you"
Finally, I know what is meteor shower
The tears of the sky...