Here you go.
- You don´t want me to wait?
- No thanks, l´ll walk back.
Georgie.
How could I have forgotten?
l´m so sorry.
Take your pick.
Billy-boy.
Except for the one on the end.
That´s already taken.
Sorry.
I remember you.
And I remember we beat you.
l´m not afraid of you.
I know how old I look.
It´s just that I remember you as a kid.
Welcome home, Bill.
I wish it was under happier...
Come on, let´s go out.
I realized that I shouldn´t create any more
paranoia than we already have here.
I got a taste of it myself, earlier.
At least people seem to care now.
Or maybe it´s just that l´m a grown-up.
I feel so thick, Mike.
I don´t remember much at all.
I don´t even remember why I came back,
except for Georgie.
l´ll bet it doesn´t all come back at once.
How come you remember?
I never left, how could I forget?
I look on the street corner
and there we were. Seven of us.
Lucky seven.
Man, that just came back.
Something else.
- One of us lived around here.
- Right.
Bev!
Right down the street.
She was poor. Her father was the janitor.
This was Poor Town.
Yeah, still is.
Yours?
l´m a bachelor, Bill. It´s all I need.
It´s clean and better yet, paid for.
- You hungry?
- I haven´t had an appetite since your call.
l´ve arranged dinner tonight for all of us.
Have you seen the others?
No. l´ve had a feeling all afternoon...
...I could tell when everyone has hit town.
We´re not all here, yet.
No.
You, too?
There it is. It´s powerful stuff.
Here´s to remembering.
What?
Maybe this will stimulate
those old memory banks a little.
Silver.
I found it in a pawn shop a year ago.
Something made me buy it.
It has a flat tire, but that´s all
that´s wrong with it. Here´s the kicker:
I bought this tube repair kit on impulse.
Three months before I saw this bike.
There was some kind of force
guiding us that summer.
I don´t know if we created it
or it came to help us.
Maybe it´s still here.
l´m going to change clothes.
"l´m getting bugged driving
up and down the same old strip
"I got to find a new place
where the kids are hip"
Oh, come on!
Not the Paramount, you slimeballs!
Where are the people
supposed to get their culture?
- May I help you?
- Mike Hanlon.
He stepped out a short while ago.
- l´m pretty sure he´s coming back.
- Good.
l´ll wait here for him.
Come on, Tozier, get a grip.
You looked like you could use this.
It´s just water.
Thank you.
A little young for you, isn´t she?
Beep, beep, Richie.
I didn´t hear that.
I didn´t!
I beg your pardon?
Come on up, Richie!
I got a balloon for you.
Don´t you want a balloon?
What´s the matter,
one balloon not enough?
Try a bunch!
Is everything all right?
Last chance, Tozier.
Get out before it gets dark tonight.
You´re all too old to stop me.
You´re all too old.
Tell Mike Hanlon if you see him...
Excuse me. Do you have Prince Albert
in a can?
You do? You´d better let the poor guy out.
Tell Mike Hanlon that I had to go.
I had to get cleaned up. Tell him.
Tell him.
Tell him l´ll see him tonight.
Last chance, Tozier. Get out!
Get out while you can.
Excuse me, ma´am...
...is your refrigerator running? It is?
You´d better catch it before it runs away.
All right!
Son of a gun.
Not just any cards, Bicycle.
They always make the best noise.
Bill?
I see it.
Follow up on the Miller thing.
l´ll call Todd myself.
What about the engineer´s report?
What´s that?
You´re breaking up.
l´ll call you from the hotel.
Pull over here.
Wait for me.
You´re it! You´re it!
- You´re dead, fat boy.
- Come on!
You´re going to die!
Come on!
You´re dead! You´re dead!
- You´re it, porky.
- You´re it!
- Have a nice trip.
- See you later, porky.
- Are you okay, buddy?
- My knee.
Lucky for me you had that hankie.
Be prepared. You can keep it.
l´ll be okay now.
Hang tough, champ. You´ll make it.
Ben Hanscom!
Nice to see you again.
What have you been up to all these years?
We can´t wait to get you
down here with us.
You´re only in my mind.
Any spare change, mister?
Hey, who walked all over your grave?
I wasn´t going to hurt you.
I don´t even know you.
Let´s go.
- Derry Inn, did you say?
- Yeah.
Reliving your childhood down there?
Something like that.
Saying hi to some old ghosts.
Time does go by.
Here´s that prescription.
How old are you now?
Eleven. Almost 12.
Come with me.
Relax, l´m not going to bite you.
Most of your troubles comes
from being so tight all the time.
Take your asthma, for instance.
You know what a placebo is?
I got to go.
It´s water with a squirt of camphor
to make it taste like medicine.
No.
Your doctor is weak and your mother
is determined that you´re ill.
You´re caught in the middle.
It´s a lie. I do have asthma.
Sir?
Your prescription.
Nothing like a good pull
on the old lung sucker.
Thank you.
Junior, bring me a cigar.
You can´t have one, Granddad.
Mr. Keene?
Mr. Keene. Hello.
Cigar for the old man?
l´m sorry. I don´t have any.
l´m Eddie, Sonia Kaspbrak´s son.
Any licorice?
I was always partial to licorice.
I wanted to thank you for trying
to tell me the truth long ago.
You look a little peaked, sonny.
l´d better go.
Hydrox.
H2O. Water.
It´s only water.
It´s all in your head, sonny.
You do remember me.
Mr. Keene?
Get out of Derry while you still can.
Mr. Keene, please.
Beware, little Eddie.
Beware, girly-boy.
No cigar, sonny.
I was always partial to licorice.
I must have rung the wrong bell.
I was looking for Marsh.
There´s no Marsh here. Unless...
Do you mean Alvin Marsh?
Yes, my father.
Oh, Miss...
...I hate to be the one to tell you,
but your father´s been dead for five years.
But on the bell...
Kersh. I thought it said, "Marsh."
l´m Mrs. Kersh. I knew your father a little.
- Come in for some tea.
- No, I couldn´t.
You could and you will. I insist.
Feel free to look around.
Perhaps you´d like to freshen up?
Did you fall asleep in there? lt´s teatime.
Tea.
Tea would be nice.
I love what you´ve done with the place.
It´s so different, so cozy.
How kind you are, miss.
I call all the young girls, miss.
Don´t take offense.
No.
Go on, dear, drink it while it´s nice and hot.
Don´t trouble your pretty little head.
l´ll get it.
It did say Marsh on the doorbell.
If you´re wise, you´ll run, dear.
Because to stay will mean worse than
your death. They float down there.
They float.
I worry about you, Bev. I worry a lot.
It won´t do you any good to run.
You´re not real! Not real!
Beep, beep!
Since you first introduced me to him
I told you he was a twit.
- Remember?
- I didn´t ask you here to insult Bill.
How dare he do this to me.
You´ve complained about him
since we started the picture.
He´ll never work in movies again.
You know that.
If you could have seen his face.
It was frightening.
Nothing like a crisis to bring
the estranged couple closer together.
Or perhaps pull them farther apart,
if the gods are smiling.
Greco, please.
I am simply pointing out that this
could be a blessing in disguise.
Could you give me a few days?
I shall pretend I didn´t hear that, Audra.
I can replace your imbecilic husband,
but not you.
Don´t think about leaving.
You´ve worked hard to get where you are.
I know you won´t jeopardize that.
Or damage our professional relationship.
Or turn a friend into a violent enemy,
ready to crucify you at any cost.
There´s no need to talk now.
See you tomorrow.
International reservations, please.
l´d like a seat on your next flight
to the United States.
l´m looking for the Hanlon party.
Eddie?
- Eddie Kaspbrak.
- Haystack!
- What happened to the rest of you?
- Gone but not forgotten.
My god.
Where´s Richie Tozier
when you need a good line?
- Ben?
- l´m afraid so, Bill.
Look at you.
- Mike, is that you?
- Such as I am.
Who wants a drink?
- Set them up.
- l´ll have one.
- What is this?
- That´s my dog.
- l´ll have a club soda, okay?
- This is pretty good.
Tozier, get a grip.
Don´t let them see you like this.
It was a flashback
from too much fun in ´67. Get a hold.
You´re working too hard.
I got a toast. I propose...
Who got bald, who got wrinkled...
...and how many of God´s children
got wings?
Beep, beep, Richie!
- Hey, buddy, how are you?
- Fine, fine. You?
Beverly?
What a bunch of handsome old men.
Hi, good-looking.
Richie.
Eddie!
l´d rather catch you than anyone else
in the world, Beverly Marsh.
I saw all of you standing there and so
much came flooding back, like a wave.
What are we getting ourselves into?
l´m so proud of you.
Where´s...
Are you all right, Bev?
Yes.
No. I...
I saw something today.
- Same with me.
- Oh, man!
- What I saw at the library...
- Was it Pennywise?
With both barrels, it was Pennywise.
He´s working on us already.
- Trying to chip away.
- Maybe that means he´s afraid.
It. It´s afraid.
Oh, man. It!
Help us remember, Mike, fill in the gaps.
Yes, because I don´t know what
you´re talking about.
I can´t remember much of anything.
When I try, it clouds over.
Didn´t you feel it?
As soon as I crossed the county line
a veil dropped over my eyes.
Maybe it´s the water.
Water? Maybe it´s the sewer.
This is battery acid, you slime!
l´m okay.
I remember who Pennywise was now.
Big white guy, red nose...
...about 75 feet tall,
mouth full of razor sharp teeth.
Oh, Eddie.
What the hell is happening, you guys?
What is going on?
l´m sorry. It was a very vivid memory.
l´d forgotten I stared into that creep´s face.
You saved Stan´s life. Remember?
Yeah.
Yeah, now I do.
Speaking of Stan. Stan? Stan!
- Where is his royal straightness?
- You talked to him, right, Mike?
I think he´ll be along.
We ought to start without him.
We can fill him in when he gets here.
- Mike, help us remember.
- Wait a minute.
This is the first time since I got here
that I feel good. Halfway safe.
Let´s have a couple of drinks,
some good food and a couple of chucks.
- Leave the wolf out the door.
- Spoken like a real loser, Richie.
Hey, to the loser´s club.
To the loser´s club.
Talking about your wives?
How many times have you been
to the altar, Richie?
Four or five. Women all want
the same thing. No offense, Bev.
None taken, creep.
Welcome to the fourth century.
Ben, are you married?
Nope, l´ve dodged the bullet
a number of times, now.
Eddie?
l´m seeing a wonderful woman,
but with work I don´t have much time.
Take it from me, spaghetti man,
better dead than wed.
- Any little crumb snatchers for you, Richie?
- None that I know of.
- How about you, Bev?
- What?
How about you?
l´m not married.
- What happened to those glasses?
- Contact lenses.
For the many times as you broke
those glasses...
...you should have had stock in an
adhesive tape company.
Me and Henry Bowers.
Please tell me he was hit
by a freight train and put out of his misery.
No such luck. He´s at Juniper Hills.
Ever since he confessed to murdering
all the children.
- He was down in the sewers.
- He tried to kill Stan.
He was going to kill us all.
I remember when they pulled him out,
his hair was white.
- He was babbling about a bright light.
- And a clown.
No one believed him.
Except when he said he killed them.
- We didn´t say anything.
- Not a word.
But It was the killer and we stopped lt.
We thought we did.
Henry.
Henry Bowers.
Up here, sharp stuff.
Up here!
You helped me once. Remember?
You chased those brats.
Almost got them. Almost.
Don´t you want another chance?
You´ve got to go back and finish the job.
Go back to Derry and kill them all. For me.
Kill them all.
Kill them all!
This has been a real hoot...
...but I have a plane out at 6:00 am.
You´re not leaving?
Bev, you want an adventure?
You want to relive that old nightmare?
I love you, but count me out.
l´m going to a hotel.
In the morning,
l´m on a plane and out of here forever.
- I will remember all of you fondly.
- Richie?
- We´re all scared. Don´t be ashamed.
- Maybe he´s right.
Are you talking about going back
in the sewer?
We haven´t talked about anything yet.
Give Mike a chance to fill us in before
we scatter to the four winds.
Is that too much trouble?
I just want to go get some sleep.
Is that too much to ask?
- Why don´t we show Mike some courtesy...
- Guys! Come, on!
It´s all right.
If Richie wants to go, he goes.
We came here based on the strength
of a promise.
Everyone at this table
made good on that promise.
Wherever we go from here...
...I have no expectations.
Well said, Michael.
It´s taken care of, Richie.
No, you can´t do that.
That´s just the way it is.
A toast to Mike Hanlon.
A man without whom none of this
would have been necessary.
I can see my fortune now:
"You´ll be eaten by a big,
greasy monster. Have a nice day."
Dummy up, everybody.
What is it? Is something wrong?
Our friend had an asthma attack.
l´m much better now. Thank you.
Everything was okay?
Fine. Thank you.
l´m not so sleepy anymore.
Let´s get the hell out of here.
Is this the Uris residence?
Is Stan there?
This is an old friend, Mike Hanlon.
What are we supposed to do now?
A little soap and elbow grease
ought to clean this right up.
Why are we the only ones
that can see this?
l´m stumped. Let´s ask the answer man.
Oh, Mike?
Michel...
...garçon?
Hello, Stan? Mike Hanlon.
Is this the Uris residence?
l´m trying to reach Stan Uris.
Tell him if he hasn´t left yet,
he´s a dead man.
We all managed to show up.
That matches your real hair.
Is anyone from out of town?
I flew in from L.A.,
and my tail section is tired.
It´s great to be back in Derry,
breathing that old Derry air.
I have never felt so much love in one
room in my entire life.
Eddie, get their names
for my Christmas mailer.
Wait, put Denbrough there,
on my Norman Mailer!
This man is like the brother I never had.
He is the brother I never had.
Stan?
Thank you.
Stan is dead.
He cut his wrists in the bathtub
right after I phoned him.
Stan was the last one to see It
that summer.
Remember?
He just kept saying
it wasn´t empirically possible.
Even seeing the clown
didn´t make it real for him.
Nothing did.
Until that afternoon in August.
I was coming down Chestnut Street.
I saw Stan running like something
was after him.
Go!
- Go!
- Hi yo, Silver. Away!
Stan saw It that day, I honestly didn´t.
I was pedaling too fast to turn around.
I didn´t want to see it. Whatever it was.
It took hours before he could tell me
what happened.
He was in Lampkin Park by a bird feeder.
Watching birds.
Like a good boy scout. Remember?
He used to call it collecting birds.
Stan...
He said he didn´t mean
to go into that house, but...
...this voice kept whispering to him.
Being Stan, he figured there was
a rational explanation.
Hello?
Stanley.
Yeah? l´m right here.
He was trapped.
He held his bird book out
in front of him like a shield and...
...say loudly the names
of all the birds he could remember.
Longneck finch...
...speckled grouse, Baltimore oriole...
...gray egret, hammerhead woodpecker
and brown thrush.
Brown thrush.
The day we went into the sewer...
...Stan saw lt.
Face to face.
He saw what was behind the clown.
He ran up to me in school and said:
"I saw lt, Eddie.
"I looked right into its..."
Some kind of lights.
"I looked right into its deadlights."
I hadn´t thought of it until now, he said:
"I looked into its deadlights
and I wanted to be there."
Deadlights.
- I need a drink.
- Me, too.
l´m sure I have something here.
Anybody else?
Sorry l´m late. Let´s see who´s here.
Billy-boy!
You still here, Richie?
We didn´t expect you to stick around.
Nice nose job. No one would ever suspect.
Haystack...
...putting on a little weight?
Bev, your dad isn´t worried anymore.
Your dad loves your taste in men.
Wheezy, how´s your sex life?
What´s your sex life?
Mike you did it. You got us all back here.
It´s the only way you´d ever see us
since you´ll never leave this town.
I made it. l´m in the deadlights now.
It´s true what they say.
We float down here and you will, too.
In fact, they all float!
They all float!
My God!
I don´t know about the rest of you,
l´m getting real sick of this place.
l´ll listen to anything anyone has to say,
but can we go someplace else?
Please!
Help me with the stuff.
What is it?
"He thrusts his fists against the post
and still insists he see the ghosts."
It says that over and over again.
My mom gave me that to say...
...to help with my stutter.
No offense, pal, it ain´t helping.
Let´s get the hell out of here.
What do you say?
Henry!
Down here.
What are you doing down there?
You have a problem in there,
you need help with, Henry?
That´s a good boy.
You don´t have to talk. I can hear
what you think and they can´t hear me.
- What do you want?
- Same thing you want.
I want to pay them back.
Yeah, pay them back.
You have to get out of here
and go back to Derry.
I need you, Henry. We all need you.
They can´t hurt you.
We didn´t think they could hurt us
back then, but they did.
- Bested you all summer.
- Don´t talk about that.
I can take care of them
if they only half believe.
But you´re alive, Henry.
You can get them if they believe,
half believe or don´t believe at all.
One by one, Henry.
I can´t get out of here.
There are wires on the windows and...
...Koontz on the door tonight.
He´s the worst.
I hate him.
l´ll take care of Koontz.
Lead the way, Henry.
Lead the way.
l´ve had it with you. Your head will be
be bouncing off the floor!
No, Mike.
I will have no need of this stuff.
Thanks for thinking of me.
But none for me, thank you very much!
- Richie, you´re shouting.
- I know!
Beep, beep, Richie. Beep, beep.
Talk to us, Mike. Tell us stories.
So we don´t have to remember
what we saw in the library.
Don´t let it get you. Fight it.
I saw myself today.
I saw myself back there.
I know it´s just camphor water,
but I need it.
Take it easy, pal.
If it works, it´s good medicine.
You believe in it, that´s all that matters.
l´m sure you all remember
what happened 30 years ago.
There was a rash of killings,
disappearances, mostly of children.
Everybody was afraid,
but nobody did anything.
Until we went after lt.
We almost killed lt.
Henry Bowers confessed
and the killings stopped.
Until this year, exactly 30 years later.
First thing you should know:
If you count backwards in 30-year
increments, every date corresponds...
...to a huge disaster in Derry´s history.
In 1960, the big fire at the Black Spot Club.
In 1930, the explosion at the old ironworks.
In 1900, the massacre at Drake´s Creek.
And on, and on.
The biggest mystery is how 253 settlers
just disappeared without a trace.
Thank you for that illuminating,
if somewhat morbid, history.
She didn´t want to know.
You knew about this even then...
...Miss Douglas didn´t want to know.
It´s a disease, Bev.
The Derry disease.
None of them wants to know.
- It´s too horrible they...
- They act like nothing happened.
I remember a man, Mr. Ross...
...he was on his front porch,
I was coming home from school.
Henry Bowers was waiting
right outside my house.
I saw Mr. Ross across the street.
He looked so concerned, I thought
he was going to help me, but...
...he just turned around and went inside.
That was when I knew there was
something terribly wrong with Derry.
How did you get out of that, Bev?
Daddy came home, one of the only times
I was glad to see him.
So, it´s 30 years later
and the killings are right on schedule.
Six so far, maybe more.
Some have disappeared with no trace.
I wanted to be certain
before I called anyone.
I became certain when I found something
at the latest crime site.
That was just yesterday.
Anyway, this is it.
Georgie?
There´s something special
about us being together.
We found each other that summer
and together we were strong.
Otherwise, It would have picked us off,
one by one.
Is it an accident that none of us have kids?
Including Stan.
When we first came together,
we were all losers.
Now look at you.
Six of you left Derry
and became unusually successful.
Big-time breadwinners.
Leaving you holding the bag.
You kept the lighthouse for the rest of us.
I feel like a real jerk about that.
Me, too.
It´s no one´s fault.
Our parents decided who stayed and went.
When I grew up, I wanted to stay.
I think you stayed because you had to.
I don´t know what will happen
when the sun comes up...
...but I appreciate what you´ve done
for everyone.
- Good evening. You´re up late.
- How much farther is Derry?
About 500 yards to the city limits.
Thank God. I nearly fell asleep.
I feel like l´ve been driving forever.
Cross the bridge at the barrens
and turn left.
The barrens?
Yes, where they used to play
when they were kids.
Thank you. l´ll be going now.
Don´t you want your balloon,
Mrs. Denbrough?
Don´t you want it?
They caught me and started slapping me.
The coach found me crying
and I thought he would help me.
Instead, he made fun of me and I got mad.
I said, "You coach track, right?"
He sneered at me and nodded, and I said:
"Listen, stone-brained son of a bitch,
l´ll go after the track team.
"l´ll run down everything you got.
"l´ll beat your best
and expect an apology from you."
All right.
So you did it?
I ran until my heart pounded so hard...
...I thought I would pass out.
After my first mile, I puked, then fainted.
Finally, I was holding up my pants as I ran.
I ate salads like there was no tomorrow.
By March, l´d lost 70 pounds
and l´d grown two inches.
Every time I ran, I felt like I could fly.
- And you went out?
- I went out for track like I said.
First time I was out there
I won the 220 and the 440.
I just blew away the coaches.
After practice I walked up to the coach...
...and I asked for apology.
He was so furious, he hit me.
- No! After all that...
- It was perfect!
- You beat him!
- And everybody knew it.
I graduated from El Paso High
with a letter in track.
The coach lost his job
over that little love tap.
It´s great! You ought to write that down.
- Bill´s our writer.
- Only horror stories.
We haven´t talked about what
we´re going to do, if anything.
Oh, Mike.
Listen, kids.
This campfire stuff is fun, it really is...
...but no matter how painstakingly
we go over these sewer plans...
...or how many damn flashlights
or helmets you got in that box...
...when the sun rises, l´m dust,
and I suggest the rest of you follow.
And get the hell out of Dodge!
- I cleaned it up once.
- Cleaned what?
The blood.
I cleaned the whole thing up
that very same night.
I decided if I was going to sleep in this
house again, l´d have to know the truth.
To see if anyone besides me
could see the blood.
What happened in here?
Somebody get murdered?
You see it? You really see it?
Come on, let´s clean this up.
Until that moment,
I thought I was going crazy.
It was strange to be happy
about something so grim.
I fell in love with all of you that day.
After we cleaned it up,
the blood never came back.
It will be morning soon.
- l´m cold.
- Me, too.
- l´ll get you something.
- There´s a shawl in my room.
Give me your key and l´ll get it.
Richie, you have a key?
Listen up.
Stay together. No stragglers.
- Just get the first thing you find.
- I need to stretch anyway.
Ben.
- Don´t go alone.
- I need a refill anyway.
l´ll join you.
l´ll take care of Richie.
We meet back here in three minutes,
no more. Keep your doors open.
Hello, nigger. l´ll pay you back.
l´ll pay you all back.
Oh, good. You found lt.
l´m glad we´re alone for a minute.
I want to tell you something.
"Your hair is winter fire. January embers."
- "My heart burns there, too."
- It was you.
l´ve been waiting a long time
to thank the poet.
- Did you ask Bill first?
- No.
I knew it was you.
l´ve always known it was you.
I think I must have been waiting
until we were both ready.
l´m ready now. Are you?
Kiss me, fat boy!
Mike! Mike!
Mike!
I got him.
- In a minute.
- Give me a hand.
Watch it! Okay, easy.
- In the car.
- Hurry up!
Go! Go! Go!
If Mike dies there will be five of us left.
Who comes next? Which one of us?
Why is It doing this?
Why does It hate?
Why is It so mean?
Oh, Ben.
I want to tell you something.
Remember what my father was like?
I fell in love with a man who...
...who turned out to be
everything I hated in my father.
Why would I do that?
How could I be so blind?
If you see it now, you´re not blind anymore.
Congratulations. That´s a miracle.
Besides, at least you fell in love
with somebody.
At least you felt something.
That´s a miracle, too.
You have the heart of a poet, Ben.
"Your hair is winter fire."
- Why did you say that?
- You wrote it didn´t you?
"Your hair is winter fire.
January embers."
I first thought it was Bill,
but it was you, wasn´t it?
Damn it, is that you or the clown?
I don´t know what´s going on!
How am I supposed to know?
It´s me.
"My heart burns there, too."
- Mike will be okay.
- Can we see him?
He´s not out of the woods yet.
One of you can go in for a minute.
Mike?
Everyone else is right outside.
- Henry?
- He´s dead.
- Police?
- Not yet.
We can´t trust anyone.
If anyone asks, a party got out of hand.
You were dancing on a table and fell off.
Anyone who´s seen me dance will buy that.
- What are you going to do?
- I don´t know, man.
I honestly do not know.
My jacket. Outside pocket.
It´s silver. It can kill lt.
We left these down in the...
You went back?
I was pretty sure It was asleep.
Pretty sure?
You went alone?
Ten years ago my life was going downhill.
I was close to suicide.
Maybe I wanted It to wake up and kill me.
Took me all day in the dark.
I found one right away.
In the drain trap.
The one that hit Pennywise was lodged
in a crack in the wall.
I figured we might need them again
some day.
When I came out I got my life together.
The only change was this.
Almost overnight.
Fear.
Bill.
If you decide not to use those...
...if you leave, l´ll understand.
That is a dead body.
You´re not suggesting we walk out
and leave it here?
That´s what I am suggesting.
- I think we should call the police.
- I agree.
You don´t understand. This whole town
is It in some way. All of them.
Bill´s right.
If we call the police something bad
will happen to one of us.
Maybe all of us.
Have it your way. Stan is dead.
Mike came close. l´ve seen enough.
- l´m with you, boy?
- You can put this behind you like that?
l´m too old for monster hunting.
So was Mike.
So was Stan.
Is that how you feel about it?
I don´t know.
I can´t stay in this room much longer.
I suggest we turn on the TV,
hang a "Do not disturb" sign on the door...
...go outside and figure out what to do.
I second that.
The Police Chief said the victim...
...a five-year-old girl,
was playing near her home.
Authorities have not determined
if there´s connection...
...between this
and the other missing young children.
They did say, however,
that the body was severely mutilated.
In other news, a series of robberies
in the East end has local...
Just put that on my card
and send me the receipt.
- Certainly.
- Me, too, thank you.
Loads of fun. Got to go.
Need a ride, Bill?
- Where are you going?
- Airport.
- I guess we are, too.
- Come with us.
I just saw something
and I don´t know if it was real.
Or if any of you would have seen it.
I can´t go.
If I do l´m going to live with this
until I go insane.
Until I can´t tell the difference
between my life and my bad dreams.
For years l´ve been paid to scare people.
But l´m the one who´s been scared.
All my life.
I don´t want to be scared anymore.
l´m going back in.
This time I will kill lt.
Help me!
Please, help me.
Did anyone think to bring something
useful, like a machine gun?
I brought this.
It´s all I saved from those days.
- You were a dead shot.
- You couldn´t miss.
It was like it was supposed to be Bev,
remember?
You hit Pennywise in the head
and broke it open.
- And underneath it was a light.
- Bright light.
Deadlights.
We saw them, too, for a second.
Bev?
- Bill, how on earth...
- Mike went down and got them.
These are for him and Stan.
- Lucky seven.
- We´re all here now.
What the hell are you going to do now?
Sing Kumbaya?
Wake up. Take a breath.
Do you smell that?
That´s death.
It´s not for Mike or Stan or Henry Bowers.
It´s for us and it´s in the air.
Losers fight lt, losers die.
And you know that, don´t you, captain?
- You don´t have to go down, Richie.
- Right.
I didn´t have to get on a plane,
go to dinner or come here.
Now I don´t have to go in.
I still say we should have brought
a machine gun.
The first thing I saw here
was one of those damn pom-poms.
- This purse looks new.
- Oh, dear God. It´s not possible.
- Audra.
- What?
What in God´s name?
She´s down here. It´s got her.
Wait, damn it!
Audra!
Audra. Audra.
Bill, come back, Bill!
- Do you want to get killed?
- Oh, god, Bill!
God, Bill, you all right?
It´s my fault. She followed me.
- I told her...
- Bill, that´s enough!
If she´s here there´s only one way
you can help her.
You know why we´re here
and we´re going to do it.
We need you to stand up for us like before.
Or none of us will get out of here.
Come on.
Stay close together.
- Looks like we´re off the map.
- I think...
That way.
We´re here.
- The roots all grow down.
- Yeah.
- Remember the walls cracked.
- When It came.
Dear God, please don´t let these things
come to life.
- Don´t think that, spaghetti man.
- Don´t call me "spaghetti man."
I think something´s coming.
- My boat.
- Georgie.
It´s all your fault.
Oh, Georgie.
You sent me out and It killed me.
No. No, Georgie. I didn´t know.
Remember that´s not Georgie. Fight it.
It was in the drain.
It was in the drain. And you let It kill me.
Oh, no. I loved you.
- Damn it, that thing is not your brother.
- Come on, man, fight it.
You are...
...not George.
George is dead...
...and it´s not my fault.
You killed my brother, George,
you bastard.
Let´s see you now.
Show yourself.
You killed my little brother...
...and now you´re going to pay.
Go while you still can.
This is your last chance.
Show yourself.
Silly boy.
You still think you can see me.
You´ll never see me.
You see only
what your little mind can allow.
Go now!
For if you stay...
...you´ll lose your little mind...
...in my deadlights.
Like all the others.
Bill. We can´t fight that thing.
That´s like trying to fight smoke.
Don´t you understand
what Mike was telling us?
It feeds, Richie.
It wakes up every 30 years and it feeds.
In order to feed it has
to take on some kind of physical form.
It´s here.
Down here. Somewhere.
- Are we strong enough?
- We have to be.
I have to tell you something
before we go in there.
- Eddie?
- Yeah.
- l´ve been lying.
- About what?
When I said I was seeing someone.
l´m not. I haven´t ever...
...I mean l´ve never even been with anyone.
- Are you saying you´re a virgin?
- Yeah.
I can´t help you, but thanks for sharing.
Let him talk.
You see...
...I could never sleep with someone
I didn´t love.
l´ve never really loved anyone.
Except you guys.
Audra.
- For God´s sake!
- Wait for us, buddy.
It´s Audra. l´m going to get her.
Damn you to hell.
Please, dear God!
"He thrusts his fists against the posts...
"...and still insists he sees the ghosts."
It´s taking him. Bill!
Come on, guys! We got to...
Where are you going?
What am I going to do?
This is battery acid.
I believe in Santa Claus
and the Easter Bunny.
I believe in the Tooth Fairy,
but I don´t believe in you.
This is battery acid. Now you disappear.
Please God, don´t let me miss again.
Eddie! Eddie!
Nice shot.
Don´t you talk! Don´t talk!
You´ll be fine, spaghetti man.
Richie, please.
For the last time, don´t call me that.
You know how I...
Eddie!
Eddie.
This isn´t over.
If that thing comes back when l´m 70...
- Let´s finish lt.
- Once and for all.
Audra.
It´s all coming down.
That´s how l´d like to remember us,
if I could remember us.
Standing there by the lake
with the sun going down on our childhood.
This is my last entry. Just in time.
Just before the fog of my brains
swept all my memories away entirely.
Just weeks later, I look back on that time...
...not from memory, but from the pages
of this book. The nightmare is over.
Police involvement was brief and cursory.
As is always the case here in Derry.
With no further need
for a lighthouse keeper...
...I feel I may move on
down the road a piece.
Richie´s still knocking them dead.
He has a part in a movie.
574. Take 18, mark.
He costars with another comic,
a guy any of us would have told you...
...looks and acts like Eddie Kaspbrak.
And cut.
Ben and Bev left Derry together.
Headed west.
In a week they were married,
a few weeks later they were pregnant.
Another curse broken.
Bill and Audra are still here.
I wish the news were better.
Audra´s condition is unchanged.
They´re leaving today.
Hey, Audra. It´s time to go.
Bill thought the time away from work
might help.
But I guess Audra´s gone for good.
One of lt´s many casualties.
Locked in that haunted place
where she saw its deadlights.
Bill has been visiting me every day.
We laugh about our failing memories.
Sometimes we have to ask
each other´s names now.
His sadness is profound. I wish there was
something I could do.
Something I could have done.
Hi yo, Silver. Away!
Wait.
This bike saved Stan´s life once. Mine, too.
We went so fast I think we beat the devil.
I don´t know if I could go that fast again.
Hold on.
Beat lt. Beat lt, Audra.
Beat lt. Beat lt.
Come on.
- Bill?
- Yes.
- What are we doing?
- It´s all right. Hang on.
Hang on, it´s okay.