[Helicopter Approaching]
Red Baron, control,
Red Baron 5.
Radio:
Go ahead, Red Baron 5.
Roger. Orbiting southeast
corner sector Alpha Charlie.
We've spotted what
appears to be a spacecraft
just outside the surfline.
Alert Rescue and advise
to remain on station for 45 minutes.
And we'll squat 7700
for a radar fix.
Radio:
Roger.
Rescue,
I have Red Baron 5.
Report a possible
spacecraft offshore
southeast sector
Alpha Charlie.
Immediately launch chopper.
Effect pickup and recovery.
Base radar will vector.
Man:
Every body out! Come on!
Let's go!
Ha! Ha! Ha!
Sergeant, get that
half-track down here
and get a cable out
to those frogmen.
Yes, sir!
The general, sir.
Anybody in that thing?
I don't know, sir.
We just beached it.
All right,
open her up.
Open it up!
Welcome, gentlemen,
to the United Sta--
- Did you call the zoo?
- Yes, sir, we're in luck.
Sick bay's almost empty,
except for a mauled fox cub
and a deer with pneumonia
and a depressed gorilla.
The apes will be hidden from the public.
They'll be quarantined.
They need medical attention,
it's available right on the spot.
And the experts can start giving them
the once-over first thing tomorrow.
- General Brody's very pleased.
- Oh, me too, me too.
We can't allow monkeys to leave
their messes on the floor, huh?
Have they been fed?
Raw steak or something?
The zoo tells me that chimpanzees,
like all apes,
are vegetarians, sir.
They suggested oranges.
Good God!
What's the matter, Corporal?
Excuse me. I didn't mean to
disturb you while you're dressing.
What the hell am I saying?
They're pretending to dress, sir.
What do you mean pretending?
They are dressing up!
- Where did they get clothes?
- They brought them with them, sir.
- What?
- In that suitcase.
Suitcase?
Uh...
Greg, maybe you should
give them their oranges.
Uh, well, they're--
They're going
to the zoo infirmary.
Arrange for a police escort
at 1630 hours.
They'll have company there.
There's a gorilla
in the next cage.
Why did he do that?
[Animals Screeching]
Here you are, old fella.
Boy, you really are sick.
Hello, missy.
Have a banana.
Have it your own way, mate.
- Zira!
- I'm not his mate. I'm yours.
Control yourself.
I think they're trying to be kind.
This cage stinks of gorilla.
Cornelius, where are we?
What's happened?
I know where we are.
I know what has happened.
In some fashion--
and I lack the intellect
to know precisely how--
we have traveled from Earth's future
to Earth's past.
But we saw
the Earth destroyed.
And Earth will be destroyed
just as we saw it.
Only since seeing it,
we have passed through
a backward disturbance in time.
Did you notice the date meter clicking
down after the shock wave hit our ship?
Yes.
We have returned to Earth nearly
2,000 years before its destruction.
That is another reason
for us to keep silent.
Our human captors will not
be edified to learn
that one day their world
will crack like an egg
and burn to a cinder because
ofan ape war of aggression.
[Growling]
Apes, at this instant in time,
cannot yet talk.
For the moment,
we should follow their example.
[Tiger Roars]
[Elephant Trumpets]
[Bear Roars]
Oh, the driver gave me
this report from the air base.
Better read it
before we start the test.
Yeah, it's the usual
imitative behavior.
"Mimicking salutes,
handshaking, sitting on chairs,
eating off plates with knives."
- Well, what is it, Lewis?
- There was sort of
- Full of food?
- No, clothes and it seems
I don't believe it.
[Bear Roars]
Hi, Dr. Dixon.
Dr. Branton.
- Good morning, Arthur.
- Morning.
- The female's a bit uppity, sir.
- Oh? Okay, I'll be careful.
I see you've prepared
the Wisconsin multiphasic.
We'll begin with that.
Um, go easy now, Stevie.
Oh, they look
pretty docile to me.
Yes, but don't
take any chances.
Unless the spacecraft
was remotely controlled,
they must have been conditioned to push
at least some of the right buttons.
I mean, they can't be morons.
All right,
we'll take the female first.
Arthur, would you set up a cha--
Well, she seems
to be pretty smart.
All right,
let's make it more difficult.
They, uh, haven't had
their breakfast yet?
Not a bite.
Just as you ordered.
Good. We'll offer the banana.
[Sighs]
- Well, why doesn't she take it?
- Because I loathe bananas!
- Zira!
- I don't believe it.
Yes. Arthur, I think
Dr. Branton needs some air.
Zira, are you mad?
Dr. Milo, please,
do not call my wife mad!
I did not call her mad.
I merely asked her ifshe was!
And I repeat the question.
Are you mad?
- I hate deceit!
- Well, there is a time for truth
and a time not for lies,
but for silence.
And until we know who our friends are
and who our enemies--
And how in the name of God are we
to know that unless we communicate?
- We can speak, so I spoke.
- And we can listen!
Yes, to a lot of
psychiatric small talk!
- And we can watch.
- A display of primitive apparatus!
Primitive?
It's prehistoric!
- Couldn't test
the intelligence of a newt!
- I am calm!
- Zira! Zira!
- Stop arguing!
- [Grunting]
It's too late for that.
Use your heads
and start thinking.
Now that they know we can speak,
how much will we tell them?
- Milo!
- [Gorilla Growling]
[Trumpets]
[Roars]
[Door Slams Shut]
We'll need a full autopsy.
With special emphasis
on the cranial and oral areas.
Let us know when the report comes in.
Will you, please?
I'd better do this alone.
[Monkey Screeches]
Um, we mean you no harm.
Do you understand?
We will not hurt you.
- Poor Dr. Milo.
- Doctor?
Yes. Doctor.
You killed him!
No, I didn't. He did.
- One of your own kind.
- Zira: He's a gorilla!
Well, look, there's
nothing to be afraid of.
You see, he's in chains.
He's under sedation.
Do you understand that?
I should. I've been doing it
half my life to humans.
Humans?
I'm a psychiatrist.
Oh, well, I'm--I'm
a psychiatrist too.
Do you have a name?
My name is Cornelius.
This is my wife Zira.
And I'm Lewis.
Lewis Dixon.
Nobody's going to believe this.
Believe what?
- That primitive apes can talk.
- Primitive?
Uh... well, I mean
that in our, um...
primitive, um, civilization,
apes just don't talk.
I mean, I think
it's important that when
our primitive security
precautions are lifted,
that the first time
you say anything in public,
you should talk
to what we primitively call
the right people.
May I say something...
personal?
Please.
I like you.
I have from the beginning.
[Murmuring]
- Good afternoon, gentlemen.
- All: Mr. President.
I'm aware that what I have to
tell you may conceivably create
- somewhat wider than the Grand Canyon.
- [Laughing]
Nonetheless, it is true.
Yesterday, a U.S. spacecraft
splashed down off
the Southern California coast.
It was one of two that
have been missing in space
for over 2 years now.
To be exact, the one commanded
by Colonel Taylor.
[Murmuring]
Have they identified the bodies,
Mr. President?
They have identified
3 bodies, yes, all living.
[Murmuring]
At the time of their rescue,
through an unfortunate accident
one of them was killed early
this morning in the Los Angeles Zoo.
- Zoo?
- What would astronauts
be doing in a zoo,
Mr. President?
They are not astronauts,
General Faulkner.
- They are apes.
- [Murmuring]
Chimpanzees,
to be more precise.
They're harmless, friendly,
and by all reports
extremely intelligent
and sophisticated creatures.
But naturally, being animals,
they cannot tell us
where the ship came from
or how they
came to be in it.
I have, therefore,
decided to convene
a Presidential Commission of lnquiry
in Los Angeles tomorrow.
The 2 surviving apes
will be presented to the commission
for their inspection.
The press will be invited to attend,
not to participate.
I don't believe
that we can withhold
this extraordinary discovery
from the world any longer.
[Speaking French]
[Speaking German]
[Speaking Japanese]
One of the 2
American spaceships
believed until now to have
disintegrated in orbit,
splashed down unexpectedly yesterday
in the Pacific Ocean
off the coast
of Southern California.
And is stated
to have been manned--
if you can call it manned--
by monkeys.
Reporters:
General!
No comment.
I have nothing to say, gentlemen.
- Reporters: Senator!
- I'm sorry, boys, not now.
I haven't the time now.
A little later, please.
Reporter:
Here comes the chairman.
Later. Later.
As the president's
senior science advisor,
what do you expect to experience
from this historic meeting?
- Fear.
- [All Talking At Once]
All right now,
after I break the news,
I want you to start slowly
with simple answers to what will
certainly be
simple questions.
And if the questions
become less simple?
- Be yourself.
- Your better self, Zira.
- Please.
- [Knock]
All right, it's time.
What do they think
we are, gorillas?
I'm sorry.
That's it.
Just be seated.
Uh, Mr. Chairman,
members of the commission,
Iadies and gentlemen,
my name is Lewis Dixon.
And I am
the animal psychiatrist
who has been in charge
of these 2 apes
since they came to
the Los Angeles Zoo.
My associate,
Dr. Stephanie Branton
and I are ready
to answer your questions.
What may astonish you
is that, um,
our chimpanzee friends
are ready to answer
your questions too.
Not by signs, not by looks,
or movements,
but by words.
- Ha ha ha!
[Gavel Strikes Bench]
Dr. Dixon, as a zoologist,
I know and respect your work,
but if you think you're going to turn
a presidential inquiry
into a ventriloquist's act,
I have to inform you--
And I have to inform you, sir,
that these two apes
have acquired
the power of speech.
Come now, Doctor,
you know as well as I do
their brain system
is not developed
in either the vocal or
abstract thinking area.
Yes, sir, but I repeat
that they have the power of speech.
And it is for you gentlemen
to assess how far that power
can be exercised intelligently.
Well, may we be told which
is the female of the species?
Did she rise as a reflex
to you having indicated her,
or in answer to my question?
That's for you to decide.
- Have you a name?
- Zira.
[Crowd Gasps]
Certainly she can articulate,
which, in itself,
is extraordinary!
Uh, but, Dr. Dixon, are we
to infer that Zira is her name
or some phrase
in her language?
Infer what you will,
Mr. Chairman.
I suggest you
rephrase the question.
What is your name?
Zi-ra!
One might as well
be talking to a parrot.
A parrot!
Mechanical mimicry. Unique in
an ape vocally, without a doubt,
but, uh, does
the other one talk?
Only when she lets me.
[Laughs]
- Dr. Hasslein?
- No... nothing.
- Mr. Chairman.
- Yes?
- What is the male's name, please?
- Cornelius.
- My lawfully wedded spouse.
- Wedded?
We'll take that up later,
Your Eminence.
Cornelius, do you and
your lawfully wedded spouse
speak any language
other than English?
What is English?
I speak the language
taught to me
by my father and mother,
who were taught by their
It has been the language
ofour ancestors
for nearly 2,000 years.
As to its origins,
who can be sure?
Gorillas and orangutans
ofour community believe
that God created the ape
in his own image.
Nonsense!
Cornelius, as an intellectual,
you know damned well
the gorillas are a bunch
of militaristic nincompoops.
And the orangutans are
a bunch of blinkered,
pseudoscientific geese!
As to humans, I've dissect--
I've examined thousands of them.
And until now, I've only discovered
2 who could talk in my life.
God knows who taught them.
Where we come from,
apes talk.
Humans are dumb.
Where do you come from,
Cornelius?
I'm not sure.
Dr. Milo was sure.
Dr. Milo was a genius
well in advance of his time.
When the spacecraft
first landed on our seaboard,
it was Dr. Milo who salvaged it.
He studied it
and half understood it.
Half?
Was half enough?
It was enough for us to escape
when war became inevitable.
Enough for Dr. Milo
to be murdered in your zoo.
Enough for my wife and I
to be here now.
- From where, Cornelius?
- I told you, I'm not sure.
Maybe the female knows.
Of course the female knows!
We came from your future!
That doesn't make any sense.
It's the only thing that does.
- Mr. Chairman.
- Yes?
Cornelius, you spoke of war.
- War between whom?
- The gorillas and whoever lives--Iived.
- Will live.
- Who won the war?
I don't know. Chimpanzees are pacifists.
We stayed at home.
- But you left before the war had ended.
- In a spaceship.
- Which Dr. Milo learned to navigate.
- Correct.
Cornelius.
Did you know Colonel Taylor?
No. Is he a soldier?
We are peaceful creatures.
We are happy to be here.
May we be unchained?
Here they come.
Gentlemen, do you have--
No comment.
- No comment.
- Mr. Chairman, a word.
- I'll give you one-- preposterous.
- Well, can you define that,
Mr. Chairman?
As head of this commission,
it will be our duty to sit through
the facts of this bizarre affair
and pass our conclusions
onto the president of the United States
for implementation.
- What a load of hogger mogger.
- Dr. Hasslein.
- No comment, please.
- How will you advise the president
to handle this
unique situation?
- No comment.
- All right then, Dr. Hasslein,
could you tell us how you
personally would handle it?
No, gentlemen,
no comment... yet.
Doctor.
You were fabulous!
You were marvelous.
They loved you. All that applause.
But there was a moment--
There was when he
started to ask us--
Zira!
- Cornelius, I think we should tell them.
- No.
- But only to Lewis and Stevie.
- Oh, Zira.
I have to be honest
with someone.
Cornelius, please.
You tell them.
Well, you see...
we did know Colonel Taylor.
We came to love him.
I don't understand what harm there could
be in telling that to the commission?
Where we come from,
apes did not love humans.
They, uh, hunted them
for sport,
much as you would animals.
Yes. We use their bodies,
alive and dead,
experimentally for
anatomical dissection
and scientific research.
Well, we do the same thing
to animals.
I mean, as a scientist,
I sympathize,
but I agree that that's a revelation
the masses would not take kindly to.
I think you did the right thing
in denying knowledge of colonel Taylor.
- There was another reason.
- Stevie: What?
They would have asked
if he was still alive.
- And is he?
- Oh, no, no, no, he can't be.
Well, how did you know?
Because
from the windows
of the spaceship...
we saw the Earth...
destroyed.
Stand by.
Good evening, this is Bill Bonds
reporting from Los Angeles
where the biggest story since
the moon landing broke this morning
I repeat, talked to the
Presidential Commission of lnquiry.
With me this evening in the studio
is Dr. Otto Hasslein.
He is a senior scientific advisor
at the White House.
And he'll be giving us his views
on the crucial statement
made at this
morning's session.
Dr. Hasslein, as I recall,
when you asked the male ape
where he was from,
the female replied,
"From your future."
- Yes.
- Would you believe that?
Absolutely. I think
it is the only explanation.
Well, maybe the explanation
needs some explaining now.
You've written several
learned dissertations
on the nature of time.
Could you explain in terms that
our viewers at home will understand?
How, for instance,
a person, or persons,
could travel from
time past to time future
or, indeed, vice versa?
Mr. Bonds, I think that time
can only be fully understood
by an observer with a godlike gift
of infinite regression.
Could you explain
infinite regression for us?
- Roll the film.
- I'd more than happy to.
As a matter offact,
I came prepared to do just that.
Now here's a painting
of a landscape.
The artist who
painted that picture
says something is missing--
what is it?
"It is I myself, who was part
of the landscape I painted."
So he mentally takes
a step backward, or regresses,
and paints a picture of the artist
painting a picture of the landscape.
But still something is missing-- and
that something is still his real self
painting the second picture.
So he regresses further
and paints a third.
A picture of the artist
painting a picture
of the artist painting
a picture of the landscape.
But because something
is still missing,
he paints
a fourth and a fifth
until he paints
a picture of the artist
painting a picture of the artist
painting a landscape.
So infinite regression then is--
It is the moment when our artist
has regressed to the point of infinity,
and himself, becomes part
of the landscape he painted
and is both the observer
and the observed.
Well, now in that
peculiar condition,
what would he be observing
if he were observing, let's say, time?
He would perceive, Mr. Bonds,
that time is like a freeway
with an infinite
number of lanes,
all leading from
the past into the future,
however, not unto the same future.
A driver in lane "A" may crash
while a driver in lane "B" survives.
It follows that a driver,
by changing lanes can change his future.
Now, Mr. Bonds, I do not
find it difficult to believe
that in the dark and turbulent
corridors of outer space,
the impact of some distant planetary,
even galactic disaster,
jumped the apes from
their present into ours.
Indeed, the proof lies
in their arrival among us.
And in their spoken,
and I repeat spoken testimony.
Thank you very much,
Dr. Hasslein.
It's certainly the most incredible story
this reporter has ever covered.
I think that by their intelligence
and their good humor,
the 2 so-called "ape-o-nauts"
have already captured the hearts
of the entire American nation.
They will not be required
to appear before
the commission tomorrow.
That hearing, of course,
is going to be held in private.
They will, however, be taken
from the zoo infirmary to a hotel,
and they will be given
an extended tour of the city.
This is Bill Bonds reporting
for Eyewitness News.
- Good night.
[Siren]
[Dog Barking]
- Your luggage, ma'am?
- Of course, it's mine!
Address, please.
- The zoo.
- [Laughs]
40.
May I measure
your inside leg, sir?
- No.
- Oh.
Dr. Cornelius, tell me,
how do you find our women?
Very human.
Very good.
Excuse me.
Madam Zira, I represent Furand Feather,
a pet magazine.
Do you think I'm a pet?
Well, yes, I do, rather.
- Say, why don't you try some?
- What is it?
Well, it's sort of
like grape juice plus.
Wait! Just a sip!
Madam Zira,
what is your favorite fruit?
Grape.
And that's the way
it was tonight
at the Beverly Wilshire Hotel.
- Ha ha ha.
- Tomorrow, Zira is to speak
at the Bay Area's Women's Club.
And later, she'll accompany Dr. Hasslein
to the Museum of Natural History.
Meanwhile, Cornelius will attend
a prizefight. That's his first one.
Later, he'll visit Disneyland
to dedicate a new boat
for the Jungle Cruise.
Now, for a look
at the weather.
Sunny California will not
be exactly that tomorrow.
Clouds will cover the coastal area
with light showers predicted.
The downtown--
[Knocking]
- Tired?
- A little.
- How is that?
- Soothing...
but very wet.
[Applause]
A marriage bed
is made for two,
but every damn morning
it's the woman who has to make it!
We have heads
as well as hands.
I call upon men
to let us use them!
[Crowd Cheering]
How do you like it,
Cornelius?
Beastly.
A giant flesh-eating dinosaur.
Now, its scientific name
is a compound
of the greek antron
which means "hollow"
and dimas which
means "body frame."
Referring to
the backbone or vertebrae.
Now, this little fellow
is Camptosaurus Marsh,
a primitive duckbilled dinosaur.
Its scientific name is
a compound of the greek kampto,
which means
"flexible or bent,"
and sauros,
which means "Iizard."
Its generic name,
therefore, is "flexible lizard."
In 1879, O.C. Marsh
of yale University
described the first known species
from the Jurassic beds
of arikoma.
Since then,
other specimens have been found--
- It must have been the shock.
- Shock, my foot!
I'm pregnant.
I shan't leave you
until Cornelius is back.
- No, no, no, no!
- No, I insist. Please sit down.
Now, is there anything
I can get you, Zira?
Well, I have a strange craving.
That is only natural.
For grape juice plus.
Grape juice plus?
It's in the--
the refrigerator.
All right.
Is this it?
Here we go.
Lewis said only a sip.
Zira, it is an excellent restorative,
I assure you.
Especially in cases of pregnancy,
you know.
- How long have you known?
- Oh, since well before the war.
Mmm.
- Do you mind if I smoke?
- Uh-uh.
Oh, no, I shouldn't,
not in your condition.
Who won your war?
It wasn't our war.
It was the gorillas' war.
Chimpanzees are passion--
pacifists!
We stayed behind.
We never saw the enemy.
But which side won?
Neither.
But how do you know that
if you weren't there, Zira?
When we were in space,
we saw bright, white,
blinding light.
Then we saw the rim
of the Earth melt.
Then there was
a tornado in the sky.
Wooo.
I feel magnificently sleepy.
The date meter
on the spaceship.
What did it read
after Earth's destruction?
19...
73.
And before-- before
the white light and the tornado?
39...
50...
something.
Before the white light
and the tornado?
Zira: 39...
50...
something.
- So?
- So you have evidence, Mr. President,
that one day, talking apes
will dominate this Earth
and eventually destroy it
by 3950 something.
I doubt that we shall
still be in office by then.
And according
to the NASA experts,
who are still subjecting the spaceship
to microscopic scrutiny,
the precise year
of what you merely inferred
to be Earth's destruction
is recorded on the flight synthesizer
as 3955 A.D., presumably.
Now, what do you expect me
and the United Nations--
though not necessarily
in that order--
to do about it?
Alter what you believe to be
the course of the future
by slaughtering 2 innocents?
Or rather 3, now that
one of them is pregnant.
Herod tried that,
and Christ survived.
Mr. President,
Herod lacked our facilities.
He also became very unpopular,
historically unpopular.
And we don't want
that to happen, do we?
I am saying that our 2 visitors seem
to be charming, peaceful people--
or rather creatures--
and that the voters love them.
Do you want them and their progeny
to dominate the world, Mr. President?
Well, not at
the next election, no.
But, one day,
if the progeny turn out
as well as the parents,
who knows,
they may do a better job ofit
than we have.
By destroying the world?
Are you quite sure that what
they saw destroyed was the world?
- Well, aren't you?
- I consider it dispassionately
as a possibility,
not hysterically as a fact.
Mr. President, we have their own
testimony that they provoked the war.
And they seemed to have provoked
you pretty thoroughly into the bargain.
I'm not saying that you're wrong,
Hasslein, but I am saying
that before I have them shot
against the wall, I want convincing
that the handwriting on the wall
is calculably true.
Now... convince me.
By their own testimony we know
that apes one day will acquire
the power of
intelligent speech.
By Zira's testimony, we know
that she is pregnant with child.
By my own testimony we know
that it's genetically possible
for this child-- provided, of course,
always that we permit its birth--
to bear or beget
a talking ape by a dumb one
in a present-day jungle
or a present-day zoo.
Do you truly believe that
by deliberate present-day action
we can neutralize
that possibility?
- That we can alter the future?
- Yes, Mr. President, I do.
Do you also believe
that we should?
Given the power to alter the future,
have we the right to use it?
I don't know.
I've wrestled with this, Mr. President.
I just don't know.
How many futures are there?
Which future has God, if there is a God,
chosen for man's destiny?
If I urged the destruction
of these 2 apes,
am I defying God's will
or obeying it?
Am I His enemy
or His instrument?
An assassin would say the latter.
- Do you approve of assassination?
- Well, Mr. President,
we condoned the attempted assassination
of Hitler because he was evil.
Yes, but would we have
approved killing him
in babyhood when
he was still innocent?
Or killing his mother when
he was still in her womb?
Or slaughtering
his remote ancestors?
We have no proof, Hasslein,
that these apes are evil.
- Mr. President,
there are very strong indications.
There were hesitancies
and small discrepancies in
Which suggests to me that
if they were properly interrogated--
Are you suggesting that they
were improperly interrogated?
- Let us say unprofessionally.
- You want it professional?
- The full works, Mr. President.
- Tell that to the commission.
I'll abide by their findings.
Having convened in secret session
at the request of the president,
the commission makes
the following interim recommendations--
"1. The public
should be informed
"that the apes, after
their arduous space voyage,
"and the fatigue arising
from its intended publicity,
"are to be afforded rest and privacy
in a location whose identity
"will not be divulged
to the public.
"2. Since, however,
"there is justifiable cause
for suspecting
"that they have withheld vital
information from this commission,
"the 'ape-o-nauts' will, in fact,
be escorted by Dr. Lewis Dixon
"to the installation
known as Camp 11.
"Held there in his care
for interrogation by the CIA
under the guidance and supervision
of Dr. Otto Hasslein."
Zira:
When we were in space,
we saw bright, white,
blinding light.
Brighter than this?
- Ooh.
Zira: Then we saw
the rim of the Earth melt.
Then there was
a tornado in the sky.
That's your voice, isn't it?
How can I tell?
I don't even remember.
Why don't you remember?
Because Dr. Hasslein
made me drunk!
Why did you tell something
to Dr. Hasslein when drunk
that you never told
the commission when sober?
Because you and your husband
were frightened
for the safety of yourselves
and your unborn child?
I withheld nothing.
Nobody asked me.
But if somebody had asked...
I should have said
that chimpanzees
had no part in
the destruction of Earth.
Only the gorillas
and the orangutans.
What's the difference?
You're all monkeys.
Please do not use
the word monkey.
It is offensive to us.
As an archaeologist,
I had access to history scrolls
which were kept secret from the masses
and I suspect that the weapon
which destroyed Earth
was man's own invention.
I do know this: one of the reasons
for man's original downfall
was your peculiar habit
of murdering one another.
Man destroys man.
Apes do not destroy apes.
Cornelius.
This is not
an interracial hassle,
but a search for facts.
We do not deny the possibility
of man's decline and fall.
All we want to find out
is how apes rose.
Well...
it began in our prehistory
with the plague
that fell upon dogs.
- And cats.
- Hundreds and thousands of them died,
and hundreds and thousands of them
had to be destroyed
in order to prevent
the spread of infection.
- There were dog bonfires.
- Yes. And by the time
the plague was contained,
man was without pets.
Of course, for man,
this was intolerable.
I mean, he might
kill his brother,
but he could not kill his dog.
So humans took
primitive apes as pets.
Zira:
Primitive and dumb,
but still 20 times more intelligent
than dogs or cats.
Correct.
They were quartered in cages,
but they lived
and moved freely
in human homes.
They became responsive
to human speech,
and in the course of less
than 2 centuries,
they progressed from
performing mere tricks
to performing services.
Nothing more or less than
a well-trained sheepdog could do.
Could a sheepdog cook
or clean the house
or do the marketing for the groceries
with a list from its mistress
or wait on tables?
Or after 3 more centuries,
turn the tables on their owners?
How?
They became alert to
the concept of slavery,
and, as their numbers grew,
to slavery 's antidote,
which, of course, is unity.
Well, at first,
they began assembling in small groups.
They learned the art of corporate
and militant action.
They learned to refuse.
At first, they just
grunted their refusal.
But then,
on an historic day
which is commemorated
by my species
and fully documented
in the sacred scrolls,
there came Aldo.
He did not grunt.
He articulated.
He spoke a word which
had been spoken to him
over time without number
by humans.
He said...
"No."
So that's how
it all started.
Clip one, please.
Cornelius:
Where we come from, apes talk.
Humans are dumb.
You recognize your husband's words
to the commission?
Yes.
So humans were dumb.
Were they happy?
Clip two.
Zira:
As to humans, I've dissect--
I've examined thousands of them.
And until now,
I've only discovered
2 who could talk in my life.
Why did you change words
in the middle of a sentence?
Repeat first three seconds
of clip two.
Zira: As to humans,
I've dissect-- I've examined--
- What was the word you didn't finish?
- I can't remember.
- Play the loop.
- Zira: Dissect--Dissect--Dissect--
- Complete the word, monkey.
- Look, I have told you--
- Complete the word!
- Dissect--Dissect--Dissect--Dissect--
Dissect--Dissect--Dissect--
Sounds as if I had hiccups!
[Laughing]
Call for Dr. Dixon, please.
Dr. Dixon?
Dr. Hasslein calling Dr. Dixon.
P.A.:
Calling Dr. Dixon.
Ah, Dr. Dixon. Come in.
- Be good enough to administer
this to the female.
Sodium Pentothal.
1/2 gram l.V.
- Dr. Hasslein,
I'm an animal psychiatrist.
You have
the commission's authority.
And that of the president.
Please.
Zira, I've been asked
to give you an injection--
You can't use that! We only
use those things for killing.
- Killing?
- No, this is not for killing, Cornelius.
This is for relaxing.
It won't harm her.
- Will it harm my baby?
- No, it won't.
So, Zira, if you would
just come with me, please.
Lewis, you can't
use that on Zira!
- Please, take him to his quarters!
- Really.
No, you mustn't!
Zira! Zira!
Please.
Just lie down on the couch.
And bare your arm, please.
You don't have to tell me!
This has the same effect
as grape juice plus.
Now count backward from 10.
10... 9...
8... 7...
6... 5.
4.
What comes after 4?
2.
- Thank you, Dr. Dixon.
- It's customary to stay.
- Zira.
- Hmm.
You worked
in a room like this.
Hmm...
Bigger. Not so pretty.
And there you practiced--
Comparative.
Comparative what?
- An--an--an--
- Anatomy?
- Anata--
- Whose anatomies did you compare?
Apes and humans?
Zira, say yes
if you mean yes.
- Yes.
- So you dissected other apes?
Ye--yes...
when they died
a natural death.
And humans, too, of course.
Yes...
as they were made available.
- Available?
- Gorillas hunted them for sport
in nets and with guns.
The survivors were put in cages.
The army used some
for target practice.
We could pick from the rest.
In the interest of science,
you dissected, removed,
and statistically compared...
bones, muscles, tendons,
veins, arteries,
kidneys, livers, hearts,
stomachs, reproductive organs,
nails, tongues, eyes,
noses, nervous systems,
the various reflexes.
Reflexes?
Of the dead?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Of the living.
You can't make
a dead man's knee jump
any more than you can test
a corpse's reaction to a lobotomy.
You were advanced enough
to perform experimental
brain surgery on living humans?
Oh, yes.
We even tried to stimulate
their atrophied speech centers.
Did you try to stimulate
Colonel Taylor's speech centers?
Of course not.
He could talk already.
When you left,
was Colonel Taylor alive?
We loved Taylor.
We did all we could
to help him--
Cornelius and l.
Cornelius!
She needs a nap.
She'll get it.
Orderly.
- Sir?
- Take the female ape to its quarters.
We must get this
to the commission.
- [Bangs Gavel]
- Gentlemen, gentlemen.
I've received an off cial notification
from the president
ratifying the final recommendations
made by this commission
in light of
the tape recordings
delivered by Dr. Hasslein.
If you'll be seated,
we'll get down to business.
Now, let me review
our conclusions.
"1. By a majority vote,
"the commission finds
no solid evidence for hostility
"by either ape
towards the human race
as it is presently constituted
in this year, 1973."
- I disagree--
- Let me remind you
that this was
by a majority vote.
"The male's attitude is that
"of a deeply interested academician
"who studied the alleged future
downfall of the human race
"with the true objectivity
of a good historian.
"The female's case is different,
"in that she undoubtedly committed
"actions against the human race
"of a sort which,
if committed today,
"would be called atrocities,
"but would they be so called
in 2,000 years' time,
"when it is alleged that humans
"will have become dumb brutes
"with the intelligence of animals?
"It's been noted that
what apes will do to humans
"is no more than what humans
now do to beasts.
"Nonetheless,
the commission is sympathetic
"to Dr. Hasslein's conviction
that these apes' progeny
"could, in centuries to come,
"prove an increasing threat
to the human race
"and conceivably end
by dominating it.
"This is a risk
we dare not ignore.
"Therefore...
"the commission
unanimously recommends
"that the birth
of the female's unborn child
"should be prevented
"and that after
its prenatal removal,
"both the male and the female
"should humanely
be rendered incapable
of bearing another."
I now declare
this commission dissolved.
Savages!
They are savages!
Jabbing needles
into my pregnant wife.
I've done that too, dear,
and worse.
Taylor thought
we were savages at first.
Did they make you tell them
about Taylor too?
They made me tell them
everything, Cornelius.
- Brutes.
- Shall I tell you something?
I'm glad I did.
We can't live with lies.
After this, I doubt
we shall be allowed to live at all.
Do you mean that?
Ohh...
How long?
A week.
Maybe sooner.
They treated you like dirt.
- [Door Opens]
- Ma'am, sir.
Chow time.
I'm not hungry.
Well, maybe somebody else is
who can't talk yet.
Oh, come on, ma'am.
It's pure vitamin C.
You better drink the soup
and eat the oranges
- for that little monkey--
- Grr!
What have you done,
Cornelius?
Nobody makes a fool
out of my wife.
We just ought to leave.
I'll be going back
with Dr. Hasslein soon.
I have to tell them.
- You've got to come help me.
- I'll come right away.
Itjust seems so cruel
and horrible and-- I don't know.
I'll see you.
- Cruel, Dr. Dixon?
- Unbelievably.
Zira wants her baby.
- So do l.
- But dead.
- Yes.
- You'd prefer the parents dead too.
Shall we go?
[Telephone Rings]
Gate four.Just a minute, sir.
I'll take a look.
No, sir. The lieutenant
hasn't checked in yet.
- Good night, Charlie.
- Night, Ed.
Yes, sir.
I'll give him that message.
"Contact the motor pool."
As soon as I see him.
[Hangs Up Telephone]
- [Telephone Rings]
- Gate four.
Oh, yes, Captain.
The supply truck isn't
due until 0600 hours.
- Well, I'm sorry, sir.
- Good night, Charlie.
I said, "good night."
We can't contact them
until then.
Well, the depot's closed, sir.
Okay, sir.
I'll be off duty,
but the relief
comes on at 0430 hours.
I'll have him pass
the message. Yes, sir.
Zira, what's the matter?
I...
I think my pains have begun.
Oh, my dear.
Administration, Doctor.
It's urgent.
- What happened?
- The apes killed their orderly.
- Where are they?
- On the run.
Now they've killed.
For that, they must be killed.
It has to be done
before we start a stone rolling
that'll gather enough
poison moss to kill us all!
Look.
I'll go back to camp.
- I'll find Lewis and get help.
- No. No.
I just lost my temper
with the boy.
- It's better now. I can walk.
- Listen to me.
They may punish us
for what we did,
but at least the baby
will be born.
- Were they armed?
- No, I don't believe so.
Then there's no need
for a shooting match.
Not strictly speaking.
I am speaking strictly,
Hasslein.
Science regards
these apes as unique.
People regard them
as practically human.
The killers of today
could become
the mass murderers of tomorrow.
I can think of no one
better equipped emotionally
to persuade the people
of that possibility,
but, in a democracy,
we do not shoot
unarmed suspects on sight
for a murder
in which their participation
is still legally unproven.
I want them taken, yes,
but taken alive.
Is that clear?
Quite clear, Mr. President.
You lost, miss?
Oh, it's you, Dr. Branton.
Be careful.
There's been a murder.
- Murder?
- The monkeys have killed
What? I don't believe it.
How did it happen?
All I know is they've
killed their orderly,
And I've been given orders
to find them. Drive carefully.
There will be a lot
of vehicles in the area.
Cornelius, what have you done?
I didn't mean to kill him.
He was teasing Zira.
I hit him with a tray.
- Please believe me.
- I do, Cornelius, but they won't.
- Where's Zira?
- She's back there.
Stevie... she's in labor.
Oh, God. Get in.
Stevie, you won't
take us back to the camp?
Get down.
I have a better idea.
Now, wait a second.
Just a moment.
Let me get this straight.
You are asking me
to risk imprisonment
for the sake of two
fugitive apes?
The answer is
a thousand times... yes.
Oh, yes.
I do it for you
and for Stevie
and for your two
distinguished friends.
- Uh, notorious now.
- The hell with notoriety.
What is a husband
expected to do?
Stand by and see
his wife insulted?
Aren't we rude
enough to each other
without having to be
rude to animals?
Anyway, he didn't mean
to kill the boy.
Los trato bien, muchachos?
Si, patron. Salud!
I sure appreciate
what you're doing.
You helped deliver
our last baby.
Now you will deliver our next.
Lewis!
What took you so long?
I had to make some excuse.
They think I'm searching.
- Armando's been a saint.
- Saint Francis would have
- Never.
- Say hello to Heloise
and your goddaughter Salome.
- Hello, Salome.
- The first chimp ever born in a circus.
Los Angeles has had four.
Los Angeles isn't a circus.
It's a zoo.
So New Yorkers say.
Lewis is here.
Lewis, I was not responsible
for the death--
I know, but you will be responsible
for a birth. How is she?
The pains are coming
every five minutes.
Every four.
[Chattering]
- Look. Look at Heloise.
- [Baby Chattering]
She's showing an expectant mother
what to expect.
Mama. Mama.
Say it. Mama.
- Mama.
- Zira.
Zira, don't waste your breath.
You know the child
of two primitive apes
will never learn how to speak.
I'm getting into practice.
Mama. Mama.
Mam--
[Moaning]
There. That's good.
Come on. Over here.
What are we going to call...
- Him.
- him?
Milo?
Milo.
- Milo.
- Congratulations.
Oh.
[Coughing]
- No?
- No.
- But, sir--
- Captain, I'm aware
the areas we first established.
Evidently, we were wrong
because you haven't found them!
Thank you.
Dr. Dixon, can you pinpoint
the probable date of the baby's birth
with any degree of accuracy?
Well, I never examined her,
but from appearances
I'd say a week to 10 days.
If that's close,
she can't have gone far.
- Where do apes go?
- To other apes.
Of course. Captain, I want you
to start an immediate search
of every menagerie,
zoo, and circus.
I'll augment your force
with the city police,
and I want to be kept informed
about all results.
- Yes, sir.
- [Door Closes]
- Lewis will think of something.
- I am so sorry.
I had planned it so well.
In one month, we move on
to our winter quarters in Florida.
I could have released you
in the Everglades.
You might have lived
happily ever after.
But now...
what can I do?
You have done enough
to make us grateful forever.
I did it because
I like chimpanzees best of all apes,
and you,
the best of all chimpanzees.
I did it because I hate those
who try to alter destiny
which is the unalterable
will of God.
Ifit is man's destiny
one day to be dominated,
Iet him be dominated by you.
All I can now do
to help you
is give you this
for the baby.
It's a medal of
Saint Francis of assisi.
- Who is he?
- He was a holy man
who loved and cared for animals.
- Yes.
- Oh, thank you.
We'll hang it around
the baby's neck
for protection, huh?
- Thank you.
- Yes.
And now, my dear,
dear friends,
before the police come
and the audience gathers,
you and your pretty baby must go.
Lewis is on his way.
- Armando.
- Yes?
I should like to say good-bye
to Heloise first.
Ifshe could speak,
she'd say she's sorry.
I know, but we
understand each other.
All right.
This is as far
as we dare to take you.
The police have roadblocks
on every main exit.
- Here are your supplies.
- Thank you.
Can you read a map?
I'm an archaeologist.
I can even draw one.
We're at the city limits
at the southern edge
of this oil field.
Over this hill,
you'll pass through
more oil wells,
an abandoned refinery,
and you'll be looking
down at a harbor.
It's a graveyard
for old ships.
I played there as a kid.
There's a derelict tanker
at one end.
- You can hide there for a week.
- A week?
Until the commotion dies down and
we can smuggle you back to the circus.
Then you can travel
with them to Florida,
found a colony in the Everglades,
and live happily ever after.
[Baby Crying]
Mama. Mama.
Mama.
It's time that
you were moving on.
- Lewis.
- Yes?
If they find us,
we shall be killed?
Ultimately.
Then, uh... give us
the opportunity
to kill ourselves
if that moment should come.
Please.
I shouldn't do this,
but I guessed you might ask.
You're the second human
I've kissed.
And you are the first.
Come along, Zira.
Now, don't dawdle.
The ape with the kid?
She's been with
the circus seven years now.
The baby's birth was
registered 16 days ago.
Look how he's growing.
The first chimpanzee
ever to be born in a circus!
Do you realize what
a distinction that is?
It's like being
the first fish born on land.
- Nothing.
- It's like being the first bird
the first baby born
on the moon.
It's like being--
Ha ha ha!
Negative! Negative!
Negative!
We'll catch them
sooner or later.
Later we'll do something
about pollution.
about the population explosion.
Later we'll do something
about nuclear war.
We think we've got all
the time in the world!
How much time
has the world got?
Somebody has to
begin to care.
Ah! Like stars in space.
Isn't it beautiful?
Yes, it is...
from here.
Well... ha ha ha!
We must move on.
Hmm...
[Baby Crying]
- Who found it?
- The field superintendent.
Routine service check.
It was hidden in the workings.
- She didn't need this anymore.
- Why don't we get moving?
- We've called in for helicopters.
- How long till they get here?
20 minutes.
They're running down
a fire report
in the Simi Valley.
- Keep me posted.
- Yes, sir.
- What's the matter?
- They found Zira's suitcase.
[Horn Honks]
Did Lewis really play here?
It was probably cleaner then.
It stinks... of man.
Oh, no, no, no.
That's oil and dead fish.
Is that what man
wanted oil for--
to kill fish?
You don't like them
very much, do you?
- Who?
- Humans.
We've met hundreds
since we've been here,
and I trust...
three.
Mama. Mama.
Mama.
He wants feeding.
Oh, yes, well, um...
there must be someplace
cleaner than this.
I'll look around.
Zira:
Cornelius?
I see you've had
your baby, Zira.
The Presidential Commission has
empowered me to take it in my care.
Give it to me.
[Baby Chattering]
Cornelius!
[Tires Screeching]
Spread your men out
along the pier!
All right, men!
Move out!
- Get them down there!
- Move! Move! Go!
Down to the end!
All right! Let's go!
[Tires Screeching]
Stevie.
Zira.
I want that baby. If you won't
give it to me, I'll shoot.
[Baby Shrieks]
My God! Stop him!
[Gunshot]
Aah!
- [Gunshots]
- No!
[Gasping]
Keep your men here!
Come on!
Zira!
What's she doing?
Oh, my God.
Armando:
All hands on the guy lines.
Drop the bale ring!
All extra hands
in the back yard.
Come on! Let's go!
When you get
that canvas packed,
I want every hand
on the menagerie tent.
Intelligent creature.
But then, so were
your mother and father.
[Ah Ah Ah]
Mama.
[Oh Oh Oh]
Mama. Mama.
Mama. Mama!