Wash, wash away what's mundane.
What's boring and what's vile.
Wash, wash and let snowy skin shine.
Wash, wash off the heat,
the hot and the bad air.
lt's great, really great!
Wash, wash until
one's happy all over,
and human traits are restored.
Pure, simon pure, one's soaring.
Cleaned thoroughly
and snowy all over.
A bath is great, really great.
Great, truly great.
Great, wondrously great!
What a relief to clean off all
hatred with acrimonious out of way.
Could this be the will of Heaven?
Go faster!
Faster!
Master.
Watch out!
Suang.
What's the matter, Miss?
We should've arrived but hadn't!
lt's getting dark.
You cry at start of wedding trip.
But you're yearning to get married.
l'm bored inside the sedan.
Miss, bear with it!
They say the groom is a scholar.
He can even compose verses.
You're going to be a happy couple.
Suang, don't be a gossip!
Porters, hurry up!
Our lady is impatient.
All right.
Suang, what happened?
Nothing, Miss!
Don't ever come out; it's taboo.
Yama's here to snatch a bride.
Please don't go.
Miss.
Please let her go,
l beg you.
l'll get you, dead or alive.
A bright moonlight before the bed.
Could...
Ghost?
What are you up to?
Are you mute?
This is my gem.
What are you doing at this hour?
lf you're seeking donations, sorry!
What does this gesticulation mean?
l can't help you.
l've starved for days.
A gentleman is not covetous.
Man is by nature kind.
lt's cold!
Old gentleman, come and take shelter.
l don't mind any visitors.
Except...
Could he have left when the rain stopped?
What did you say?
Never mind. Drop in!
You're cold.
l'll get you hot tea.
Old sir, let me do it.
Drop in!
Take care!
The blanket will kept you warm.
Don't try anything foolish.
Get going, old gentleman.
Keep away!
He looks poor. He couldn't be rich.
Want to murder?
l've never seen
a more unreasonable man.
Get going, old gentleman.
Don't worry, l'll protect you!
Don't push me out.
l must get back the books.
My book!
Don't tug at me!
Don't take away my books, my house.
Don't take away my books.
Give it back to me.
Give it back to me! Hear me?
He must be deaf and dumb.
You can't understand?
Look, please give it back to me.
Thank you.
Foolish you.
When are you going to
return them to me?
Priest's son.
Run!
Priest's son's here. Get going.
Better keep away from
this kind of man.
Go faster!
Sister!
Uncle, you're buying the etui again!
Thank you.
Priest's son's here. Get going.
The ghost-catcher's son's here.
Get going.
Go!
He doesn't seem to be so awful.
You've dropped it.
You burned my house.
Where can l sleep?
You know?
How long can l live there?
Without A Gate?
Without A Gate,
how can l have a home?
How observation.
Anyone wanting to be a hero
is observation.
The house seems unoccupied.
Splendid!
This is the best house
l've ever lived.
l'm really grateful to you.
Please accept my salute.
He's quite a good guy.
Why are the people in town
afraid of him?
Scholars are highest
in social standing.
Penniless,
they write priceless words.
Let me dry the rain-soaked scrolls.
Thank you.
What is it?
So he's coming.
l'll sell this. See you in a minute.
Priest's son.
lt's quite valuable.
l already gave my article's valuable
l also knew l'd win recognition.
Well, boss, take it!
Good, this amount!
How much is it?
5 cents.
5 cents?
Yes.
Good!
You must be reconciled to
humiliation.
After being put into print,
it might be a hit.
l know you have talent.
l admire you too. Try hard next time
Take care!
Boss, so you're taking it for tissue
That's not fair. lt's a masterpiece!
Masterpiece?
Who'd read this stuff?
l bought it out of charity only.
l'd rather die than take your money.
What a hare brain.
Money and power can be set ablaze,
but not love.
Don't burn it.
No way. No one will enjoy it.
What's a scholar?
l'll burn it out all.
Don't burn it.
Burn it!
Out of my way.
All rubbish, burn it all.
l'll burn it all.
Fire...
Beans can be made into soup.
Well, l'll sell beancurd soup,
not compositions.
A bridal dress.
Had planned to get married.
Only to be snatched by King ghost.
l tried to jump to death.
lnstead, l become a roaming spirit.
He kept on chasing me.
What should l do?
Where are you, Miss?
You died so tragically.
No clean soil on earth,
l'll send you one.
Retired and take no interest in
mundane affairs!
Miss?
Miss...
Nonsense!
Can't you see l have moustache?
Between the sexes?
Don't you know the etiquette.
Please do help our mistress.
l dreamed she was pursued by ghosts.
There's nothing. l can do.
Ghosts won't mind you,
unless offended.
Don't be silly.
Get out of here at once!
There are lots of evils here.
Go now.
Miss...
Wait for me, Miss.
l'll be able to see Miss soon.
King Ghost?
Let me see if you've aged.
Trying to bewitch me?
Dare not to look at me?
Come on!
Not too old, after all.
Sense ofjustice.
Sense ofjustice?
Evil now reigns supreme.
Why talk about justice?
A heavenly match.
You defy rules of nature,
and have harmed so many brides.
l do what l like here.
You'd better behave.
l'm not afraid of trouble.
l'm not afraid of death.
Today, trouble comes my way.
l'll settle it my way.
Too early to tell who wins.
Naughty...
How naughty you are.
l'll kill you.
You're lucky.
- Alright.
- Priest.
Get going.
You haven't paid yet!
Give me a bowl of beancurd soup.
Why don't you go away?
Why should l? l did nothing wrong.
Sister...
King Ghost again?
Sister, where are you?
First thing is to rescue people.
You haven't paid. Don't go away.
Don't go away.
A wasted trip.
You've sunk deep
after several months.
Half human and half ghost.
Can this lousy gate offer protection
Observation.
Where's that bastard going?
You may speak now.
What happened during my absence?
Master, since you left,
l did many great things
besides cleaning the house.
First...
There was a leak on the 4th tile
on the roof.
l've fixed it already.
Besides, the staircase
doesn't creak any more.
Because l've also fixed it.
Time hung heavy on my hands
when you were away.
No, l mean l have time to practice,
and to catch ghosts too.
Master, why is the ghost fiercer
when older?
Older man becomes more difficult.
Master, you think l'm a bore?
One more thing l must tell you is...
That old ghost has very long hair.
He yelled behind me fiercely.
Master, l missed you daily
since you left.
All nonsense, except this.
Why are you coming back?
What did you say?
Any more nonsense,
l'll gag you forever.
No, l don't mean you, l...
Nothing.
lsn't this the Yen lmperial Mansion?
lt was so magnificent here,
but now...
So it's you.
Pay me for the beancurd soup.
What are you doing here?
lt's not right not to pay.
People like you are the cause of
social depravity.
No wonder everyone's shunning you.
Think it over.
Look at you, a lousy priest.
What did you say?
No one here wants beancurd.
Go now.
So you're not mute!
Shih Erh, so you brought him in.
You made trouble while l was away.
No his fault.
Well, let the beancurd soup charged.
Offset the rent.
lt's now even between us.
lt's not a question of money.
Without A Gate
never admits outsiders.
Why have you brought the trouble?
Master, l burnt his house.
Mind your speech.
No more nonsense.
There must be a place for me
in this wide world.
Master.
Look, you did a fine thing again.
Don't go too far.
l'm ready to leave.
Why curse him?
Master.
Today's Lantern Festival.
Suang, why are you so silly?
A ghost can fare worse than a man.
Miss, with you as my companion.
l'll be satisfied.
You combed my hair
when l got married.
Miss,
l hope you'll have another lover.
Then l'll comb your hair
for you again.
l don't even know
when l can be reincarnated.
How can l cherish any illusion?
Miss, what day is today?
The Lantern Festival.
Floating the Lanterns
in memory of the kin.
Miss,
let's float lanterns and make a wish
Don't be foolish.
Come on.
No wonder master says,
Scholars are sentimental.
Observation.
lf l were you,
l'd have died long ago.
Go now!
Miss, l know your wish.
Stop guessing.
That rude scholar kept staring at us
l didn't mean that scholar.
You're sharp-tongued.
l'm not joking, l'm serious.
You know why l'm called Shih Erh?
Many thought l had 10 brothers.
ln fact, 'Shih' means 'Pick'.
My master picked me up
when l was an infant.
l have neither brothers nor friends.
lf l love a girl
and dare not tell her,
about it, what should l do?
l'm not joking, l'm serious.
Just go and look her up.
She's already married.
Life is not a bed of roses.
Persevere so long as you live.
Look, the future is bright.
Now the future is bleak.
Don't worry, it's bright in my heart
lt's just got wet.
Don't run around. Mind the wolves.
Come back.
Light the lantern.
The candles burnt out.
l can walk on this road,
even with closed eyes.
l'm used to walking in the darkness.
Are you all right? Come on.
You said you could walk
even with closed eyes.
Observation.
A dark road is not easy to walk.
Does your chest hurt?
No, it's perfectly all right.
Scholars are a nuisance!
Don't worry,
l've already told master.
Don't keep it in mind.
Don't go out so often at night.
Remember, the rules here are:
First, no pawing around.
Second, no loitering.
- Third...
- l must go to bed.
Good night.
Come back.
Master, still not in bed?
l finished it, as ordered.
Go to bed then.
Where?
Master.
Are you addressing me?
Yes, l was passing through,
and found something wrong
with this house.
Right, l feel it too.
Master, excuse my saying so.
The trouble lies with you.
You're possessed. Understand?
All priests say the same thing.
There's no trouble other than,
that picture in your hand.
Nonsense. How dare you?
Something must be wrong with you.
What's it?
l'm only feeling sorry for you.
lf l bought your picture,
you'd be safe,
and l'd take the picture away.
Nonsense, money means nothing to me.
lt's valuable,
l won't sell it for anything
in the world.
Master,
since the painting's priceless,
would you let me have a look?
But you must return it after seeing.
Don't! She is a monster.
Watch out!
Great.
Master has knocked down her skirt.
Want me to follow her?
Can you beat her?
Luckily,
she didn't take away the gem.
Shih Erh, you're good for nothing.
You toy with feminine items
without practicing.
You don't understand.
These are all his loved ones...
What? Shih Erh.
Shih Erh.
l'll help you sell the soup
in future.
What a pity!
My master always said l'm hopeless.
You master...
Don't mention about my master.
lt's heavy.
Must be hard for you every day.
Take care!
You, too.
You look eerie, take care!
Don't worry!
He's much weird.
l'll go and catch ghosts.
Wait! Where are you going?
l'm going up to get some paper.
Master, you really want to fold it?
Master, it's a boring game.
Can't l not fold it?
No.
Let's practice fencing.
What are you folding that for?
What for?
Master, l'll fold it too.
Master, can it fly?
You must fold
1,365 pieces continuously.
Folding this requires
patience and concentration.
Keep your mind on the paper crane.
l know, and put my heart to it too.
Don't talk feelings to me.
l have no feelings, only for wine!
To put wine feelings into it?
Nonsense! Fold!
Thank you.
So beancurd soup sells better than
essays.
Another girl was caught by
King Ghost.
She knew that,
or she wouldn't have married him.
King Ghost's cruel;
he steals brides.
l told you not to talk behind
other's backs.
People may hear it.
Yes is yes.
Yes...
Who'll be the next bride?
The daughter of Mrs. Li, l think.
You'd better watch out.
Are you all right, Miss?
You made me blind.
lmpossible!
l'll help you, take care.
l'm thirsty,
l want to drink beancurd soup.
Sorry, my beancurd soup's sold out.
Take beancurd then.
There's no beancurd either.
Let me grind it for you.
Miss, it's very late now.
You'd better go home!
This is my home.
This?
Master, when l listen to your voice,
l know you're handsome.
- Let me touch...
- Miss, don't!
l must take a close look at you.
Let me find it back.
Here it is.
Master, don't go away.
Master, you're very handsome.
You said you were not afraid.
l didn't say that,
but l don't believe.
Do you believe it now?
Facing you every day,
l can't help believing.
Halt!
What are you doing?
Only a joke!
Don't put on airs.
Have you seen Shih Erh?
Are you looking for him?
Nonsense!
l'll tell him if l see him.
Don't tell him l'm looking for him.
Nonsense!
Damn Priest.
Shih Erh, what are you doing here?
Master told me fold cranes here.
Where you away just now?
Master has been looking for you
everywhere.
l was out to see Master. Don't
tell him l've been looking for him.
The master and pupil are funny.
Shih Erh, thanks for
tidying up the house for me.
What? l haven't even has time
to clean my own.
Who did it then?
l know. Must be a ghost.
Nonsense!
What's love that causes vows of
life and death.
We fly in pairs everywhere,
braving hail or storm.
Good verse.
Who filled in these for me?
Something fishy about this house.
Shih Erh, what happened?
lt's haunted here.
Haunted?
Tsui, you painted beautifully.
Thank you!
This must be your dream lover.
Nonsense!
She looks like the girl l know.
Why?
She's poor and blank.
There's nothing dirty here.
l'm the dirtiest.
l haven't taken a bath for days.
Go now. l must go to bed.
Good night.
Yell for me if anything happens,
except in nightmares.
All right.
l'm tired, l must go to bed.
So it's you!
How did you come here?
You...
Don't be afraid!
Keep away!
l won't hurt you.
Hurt me? So you're a ghost.
Right, l am a roving ghost.
l jumped to my death down
the precipice.
l was on the way to my wedding.
Someone forced you to die?
No, King Ghost kidnapped me.
The wedding retinue all scattered.
l was left helplessly alone.
So l jumped over the Black Cliff.
What a triumph for chastity!
But they kept on after me.
l have to hide in the picture.
But why should it be me?
l know you're nice to me.
My stay will get you in trouble.
l'd better go!
You'd better stay here.
The two priests make me worried.
Could they be...
She's my cousin from the countryside
Don't hurt her!
Stop lying. She's a ghost.
But she's a benign ghost.
No, she's a pitiable ghost.
Would you leave her alone?
Did l say l'm to arrest her?
You're a very good man.
He's Shih Erh.
She's...
Mo Chiu.
Beautiful name.
Why? Are you in the mood for that?
Master's coming back any moment.
l'd better go. He hates ghosts.
No, l won't allow that.
l'll hide you somehow.
Hide? Where to hide?
Even if you hide it,
- my master can find.
- Shih Erh!
All finished! Master's back.
Shih Erh!
Are you here?
Master.
What is the mischief now?
The scholar's sick, needs tending.
But you didn't nurse me!
He just slept.
Let's go back!
ls he seriously sick?
Very sick. Head and stomach aches.
Though a book worm, he's a good man.
l better look him up.
Master!
Some fever. Prepare some medicine.
Last night he painted,
and caught the draught.
He's painted only a lotus
the whole night?
No wonder he's sick.
With the picture there,
he'll die soon.
Master,
the painting is his lifeblood.
Master, don't take it away.
l'm doing this for him.
But he's faking illness.
No!
He does not have to.
Master.
l told you Master's trouble.
Now Mo Chiu has no place to live.
Maybe it's in the books.
You are all so nice to me.
l'm gratified even if...
l fail to reincarnate.
Stop it. Or l'll cry.
l'll help you
to get the picture back.
Shih Erh, mind your master.
l won't let him find out.
1365. Should be enough.
Steal the picture from Master.
Fly now.
Fly now!
l beg you. Fly.
Be nice and do me a favor.
What are you doing?
Look, priest.
You talked about flair of life.
How about yourself?
l didn't want to do it.
But l must help them.
Then why splitting them up?
Splitting them up? One's human,
the other's a ghost.
She hasn't wronged you.
She deserves better.
l'm helping her.
So that she could reincarnate.
Reincarnate?
He's out to split you up.
Splitting up?
Ghosts have no humanity.
She sticks to you,
meaning to harm you.
l know. She's suffered enough.
And you, trying to harm her.
lt's you who has no humanity.
Humans and ghosts don't mix.
l won't mind your business any more.
Master is eccentric.
But he was right.
Priest, where's Mo Chiu?
Give her back to me. Or your life.
Master, you...
You, too, don't have faith in me?
The alter is ruined.
Can't catch ghosts.
Don't try to fool me with masquerade
You still deny you caught Mo Chiu?
Master doesn't seen to be lying.
Maybe she left by herself.
She's gone!
She did it for my safety.
She could be caught by King Ghost.
l must save her.
Then, why standing here?
Master, l know where he'd go.
Say it!
Behave yourself.
Mo Chiu, where are you?
l'm looking for you.
Mo Chiu.
So l've found you.
Why do you want to hurt me?
Shut up. King Ghost hates
romantic types.
Get killed.
Demon,
you dare to attack a scholar.
Shih Erh, she's the one you love.
Help.
Hold it.
So you finally know me.
You have it on you all the time?
Master, she...
You must no be infatuated.
Kill me, please.
l'm painful under
King Ghost's control.
She's ghost. She'll hurt you.
Fate! Fate!
You're the one fated to be bad.
Scholar, you are meddlesome.
Priest, you forced him into it.
He did not dare teach you a lesson.
You...
Damned fool, you won't live long.
You curse me after
what l did for you.
Shih Erh, go back with me.
You won't listen to me?
l taught you for years.
l had obeyed you too much.
Don't believe in people, keep aloof.
People in turn treat me as dirt.
l'm not different from a tree.
Kid, l understand your feeling.
They say love is stronger than metal
lt's a lie. Sword is stronger.
The love game is not ours to play.
lt'll hurt you.
You're not loved,
so not qualified to judge.
There is not life without love.
Love is like arm to leg.
A man with no love is a cripple.
A man without love is like
a dead body.
The shit you know.
Say no more!
You're going to mention your age!
l know man and ghost shouldn't love.
But we loved, earnestly.
Spark of the moment becomes
eternal love.
You tell me,
what have you done.
Or got?
l...
l can answer it for you.
Nothing!
Absolutely nothing!
Even the son is a pick up.
Shih Erh.
Mo Chiu, where are you?
Mo Chiu!
l take it you won't reappear.
Regretfully, we're not for this life
Since you won't come out.
No point for me to stay.
l won't be happy without you.
All's so unreal, like a dream.
Mo Chiu.
My soul and blossoms.
Like a dream, beyond man's world.
One moment may be lifetime.
You turned dust into fairy mountain.
A deep imprint of kissing lips.
A gentle wiping of tears ofjoy.
Toddy the dream has come true.
lt festers in your heart.
Let dream be locked in my love.
Let all true love be poured out.
And let there be eternity!
Don't take us away.
Shih Erh, help me.
Master!
They were snatched by King Ghost.
l knew it already.
Let's go and rescue them.
Come back.
No use. They're destined to have
this crises.
Why should we rescue them?
Master, you're not doing anything?
Love, love. lt's beyond me!
But l know what it is.
Two sharing all perils,
not afraid to die.
You're destined to
lifelong loneliness.
Stop it. You lecturing me?
Right, you said man
and ghost are all bad.
The two prove your wrong.
They are frustrated by
Heaven and ghosts.
You too wanted to split them up.
The world is so unfair.
Right, there is no justice.
Man or ghost commits offences.
There is no safe place all around.
l'm helpless,
so l hid here.
But what's the meaning of a life?
Live for centuries.
And you're like the tree.
Right, can the tree take a bath,
pick and bring you up?
So what?
At heart you're selfish.
- You traitor.
- You, old mule.
Shut up your mouth.
Fool.
Going there is inviting death.
l had rather killed you now.
As though l hadn't picked you up.
Go and get killed.
Love, what the hell is love?
What darn thing goes by
the name of Love?
What God-forsaken thing is Love?
Love can be pure, soft,
even many splendored.
Love can be a tryst, an affair,
even a commitment.
Solitude is no big deal
if there is love.
l care, laugh or cry because of love.
Tell me what then is this thing love.
Heaven, in Love, ages.
But love lives.
You can't see clearly, can't wake up
l'm a bigot, a nut because l love.
Now what the Hell is this Love?
Love... keeps the knight on his horse
Love.
Why should you persecute us?
Simple! Nobody is to get,
what l couldn't get.
You're selfish!
Snatching brides
because you're not loved.
You've broken up many matches.
To us, there's very unfair.
Heaven hasn't been fair to me either
Calamity hit before l married.
l have never had a moment of warmth.
Least to say, love!
l thus have no worry, no pain.
l'm set to wipe out
all love and care.
So everyone is feeling less like me.
You're wrong.
Love doesn't have to be painful.
Only you haven't met it!
Just like me and him, two worlds.
But our love transcends everything.
That's bliss.
We're inseparable.
He won't sacrifice himself for you!
And l don't believe in true love.
Suppose there is. lt won't last.
Mo Chiu...!
Get away fast!
Don't hurt her.
Kill me instead.
You sacrificing yourself for me!
Thank Heaven for
this moment of truth.
Hold me, tight!
Mo Chiu!
Are you alright, Mo Chiu?
Yes.
Why did you hurt Mo Chiu?
That was King Ghost.
Too late. Run!
- Mo Chiu, come on.
- Come on.
You can't get away.
Mo Chiu, come here.
- Mo Chiu!
- You mustn't go.
l want to save Mo Chiu!
Don't.
Find the master.
lt's me. Let's go.
Master!
Look out for traps. Go!
You can't get away.
You're interfering and wicked.
So what?
Shih Erh, the sword.
Sword's back in sheath.
The gate to Hell is closing.
Poor scholar.
Mo Chiu!
- Go now, get out of here now.
- Where is Mo Chiu?
Hurry up.
Get going!
Mo Chiu!
- Take him.
- Mo Chiu!
You must leave this place.
l won't!
lnto the picture, l'll lead you.
Get going.
We are bound to be separated.
You'd better go now.
Mo Chiu!
Help us.
Let me be with Mo Chiu.
Mo Chiu! Too late. Run.
l must stick to Mo Chiu.
Walk into the painting, Mo Chiu.
Mo Chiu!
Hold it and climb in.
- Mo Chiu.
- Don't.
Hung Chien, don't...
Mo Chiu.
Grasp it fast.
Come.
Too late. Run.
l'll be with you all my life.
Tsui Hung-chien, grasp it tight.
No time.
Tsui Hung Chien.
Master, aren't they foolish?
You're the fool.
Do what you like to do.
l'll come to get you, priest.
Take good care!