Yes!
Open the gate
Open the container
What's so astonishing?
Where is the skull
of the dinosaur?
Dunno!
Speak up
Don't stand here!
Go search
Yes
Go
Backward, backward...
Slowly, be careful!
Come on... Be careful
Put the skull into the
other container
Get ready and set out now
Yes
Yee calling console, roger
Are you alright, Yee?
The skull of the dinosaur is ready
All the thieves were killed by me
Report your location
I am now in the Ta Nien
How dare you to kill
so many of my men!
You want to kill me
with this toy gun?
Kid, I'll show you
what a gun is!
Damn you,
you wasted one of my bullets
What else will you show me?
Yee, answer what
had happened!
Yee...
I am attacked
Which one attacked you?
I dunno, he is protected by helmet
And he has a golden gun
I've seen such powerful gun before
Send somebody to inform him
Yee, what's happened?
Answer now, Yee
Prime Minister, until now,
we haven't got any clue about the
missing of the dinosaur's skull
But the top spies of our organization
were almost killed
So, we meet some difficulties
during our investigation
This dinosaur's skull is the grade
one treasure of our country
No matter how,
you've to get it back
Yes, sir!
I'll try my best to get it back
Be hurry
Yes
Guard
What is that?
Report sir, these files
are over 10 years
I am going to burn it to ashes
Wait
Yes
Why the special file of
our spies is here?
This man's figure and IQ
is not qualified to be spy
He is a reservation
No, his ancestor was a hero
His background is clean,
he can be trusted
OK, send this guy to
take this mission
Don't you think that it's safe
for you to hide up right here?
It's useless, an attractive man
like you...
No matter where you hide,
you are always obvious
and outstanding!
Your blue eyes...
Your handsome look...
Your great skill in chopping...
And your glass of dry Martini...
They betray you!
But, although you are
so wonderful,
we have our own regulations,
no matter what,
you have to pay for what you
did last night
Why didn't pay me after hooking?
I think our relationship
is based on love
I can't imagine that,
it's just business
You need money before you love
I understand
If I had money,
I would have paid you
Vegetable is the latest craze,
poor business, you know?
Take the pork as a part
of the payment
Thank you
You are something!
We'll meet sooner or later
If you are interested,
why don't we meet tonight?
It won't be wasted!
What? That pork vendor didn't pay?
I will ask someone to
teach him a lesson
Forget it. By the way...
He is a very special
and handsome pork vendor
Han was a great hero
But time didn't give him chance...
Chai?
Man Si?
I hope you call my
full name: Da Mansi
Da Man Si
No problem, Man Si
Thank you
You're welcome, Man Si
We have a mission for you
Really?
They haven't forgotten me!
How are you, Rose?
We haven't met for 10 years,
you are still so pretty
I am not Rose
She died last year
I am her daughter, Rosy
She had a daughter!
Let uncle hug you
Later please, the Commander
is long waiting for you
Go in please
Alright, uncle will be back soon
Alright
Take this liver to make some soup
It's good to your health
You haven't been back for ages
Don't you remember there
is a glass door here?
Commander
Ling Ling Chai,
I'm glad you're bacs
Yes
Give me a cigarette, please
And knife please
Sorry
To be a swordsman,
I won't forget my weapon
Forget it
Swordsman?
I've waited for 10 years,
I think I was forgot by the country
No way, even a piece of toilet paper
is useful to us
This example fits!
I'm well prepared for any kind of work
Alright, I am glad you will
function at the right moment
Lately, we discovered the biggest
bones of an ancient dinosaur
But its skull is stolen
The thief is a very mysterious one
We just snow that he is using
an invincible golden gun
And he wears a super helmet
This invaluable treasure is
suspected to be stolen...
By Lai Yau-wai who is named
the King of Smuggling in Hong Kong
So, you are sent to Hong Kong
to investigate this case
Have you seen Rasic Park?
No, but I watched Jurassic Park
I see
Which kind of dinosaur is that?
Is that the one which screamed?
Right, the one which
screamed like this...
That one is so cruel,
it loved eating kids
No, the one in China
wouldn't eat kids
You're right
We send Da Mansi to support you,
who trained you 10 years ago
Mansi
Commander, I'm Da Mansi
Man Si, how is it going?
I invented some new product,
I hope it will help you
Torch?
No, this is not a common torch
It needs no batteries but a solar torch
When there is light,
it'll light up
But if there is no light,
will it light up too?
No! Never
But will it light up if there
is no light at all?
Good question,
turn off the light
Yes
Light it with another torch,
then it'll light up
See, isn't it?
Turn on the light
Yes
This invention is really creative
Look at the guard of that way
Suppose he is the man
with the golden gun
This is called "Super Spy's Chair"
This is for you to watch your
enemies for long duration
Are you scared or not?
Are you scared, right?
This is a powerful invention
Not bad
And I'm now trying to create
a super weapon,
which includes 10 kinds
of killing weapons
If this is successfully made...
Mansi, let's talk in my office
Chai, have you been pork vendor
in these 10 years?
Be exact,
a sad pork vendor
I am a sad vegetable hawker
Luckily, I've a part time job...
in the Central Psychological
Research Centre
What's your job?
To be researched!
Not bad
Ling Ling Chai, remember
The dinosaur's skull represents
the esteem of our country
It's not allowed to be
with the foreigners
During the investigation,
you've to keep secret
And, the man with a golden gun
is extremely mysterious
And he is so cruel
You will be very dangerous
Ling Ling Chai,
do you have any question?
May I be excused?
No way, you've to set out
tomorrow morning
When you reach Hong Kong,
someone will contact you
Yes
Anything else?
No
I'll sponsor $200 to you personally
Buy a better cloth before
you go to Hong Kong
Don't lose the face of our country
Mansi
Buy me a cup of tea
Remember to take back the change
Yes
Mansi, Commander,
I'll try my best for my country
Good speech, good pal
Good pal, good speech
Good
Are you crazy?
You use a pork vendor
to look for the dinosaur?
He was a very good spy
Don't you think I am a fool?
He hasn't been a spy for ages
He doesn't snow how to
shoot now, does he?
Deputy Captain, don't worry
I sent him for this mission,
I know his ability very well
Of course you know him
Only you know what's in your mind
I think, since the skull
is stolen in Zhen Yang,
it should be taken care
by the northern people
Anyway, you are not trusting me
Right, I am not trusting you
I've already sent my fellows
to investigate the case
Well, we needn't talk much
Please leave
This man will disappear
in this world now
Go to Hong Kong now
Send this document to a man
called Ling Ling Chai
Get a chance and kill him
Hong Kong
Hello
Can I help you, sir?
Yes! Well...
I've booked a room
What's your name?
My name is Ling Ling Chai
Hi
Sorry, your name isn't found here
What?
Please check it again
Sorry, you didn't book Regent Hotel
You booked Regent Motel
Boss,
you are so smart looking
I will charge you $70 only per day
Check out before 12 noon
Wear this, it'll be great
Really?
Is that alright?
Yes, but this doesn't fit me
Do you want any hooker?
Good idea, what kind of girls
are provided?
Mainlander or local girl,
just cost $150 each
I want a local one
Alright
Auntie, what are you doing?
I am going to take off
your trousers
Why do you do that?
You want local girl, right?
I am famous in this zone
It's you!
So? Are you tailed?
Come to eat, hurry up
Come on, eat
Hi
So many pretty girls
in Hong Kong
You are so kind hearted
Do you always feed the dogs?
You love painting?
Yes, how about you?
I don't like it
I am a pork vendor
What song is it?
Li Heung Lan
By Jacky Cheung?
I know it, but not familiar with it
I know Li Heung Kam better
Really?
My name is Li Heung Kam
You are called Li Heung Kam?
Yes, I am Li Heung Kam
You are Li Heung Kam
So Li Heung Lan must be your mom
Yes, she is my mom
Li Heung Lan is your mom
Do you smoke?
No, what for?
Come out
Why there is a snipe?
The door of the cabinet
is not well closed
Obviously, there is a third
party hidden in
Step aside, it's really dangerous
Come out
Do you smoke Kent?
How do you know that?
This is dumped by you
Shit!
Come on, wear your shoes
After tasing heavy transportation,
I am a bit nervous
But I can say one word
without hesitation
I am a really great spy
Return the slippers to me please
To take this mission,
I am well prepared
For example, this is model F40
It seems to be a mobile phone
See, this platinum layer here?
In fact,
this is a shaver
It will benefit us...
To shave before going to
any sudden occasion
This is model 911
It seems to be a shaver
In fact...
It's a hair dryer
You needn't so many
hair dryers, need you?
This is a cover only
Let me tell you...
This is a shaver
See?
That's why you are so smart!
You're flattering me
If you lose this hair dryer,
what'll you do?
You can't give me any hard time!
I am a wise guy
In fact, what I am wearing...
are hair dryers too
You know, being a spy,
Outlook is very very important
Thank you
Do you have any battery?
It's out of battery
No
Forget it, I will handle it later
I wish to know that,
being an excellent spy,
what gun do you use?
Can you show me?
What a shame, in fact
I don't know much about gun
I am good at...
Dagger!
Dagger?
Right, it's dagger
Spell, D A G G E R!
So wonderful
In fact...
I know, why not back to our topic
Being a spy,
you've to know something about gun
This is called UFO Rifle,
it's suitable for long ranged shooting
The range is 200 meters
This is 224 tiny spittoon bullet,
it's specially made for me
I love this name
357 Magnum
So great!
It's together with steel shot bullets
Can it kill a dinosaur?
You have to try it
with a real dinosaur
China made PPK,
its used by mainland spies
The range is 120 meters
But it's too noisy
With this,
you can kill without noise
What's stucked inside?
I think cotton
So simple?
How about toilet paper?
You are smart and
you are humourous
I can't see anything inside
It's cute
Does this fit?
Mine fits too
May I try?
Alright, how?
It's raining, let me close
the window first
What's up?
Why are you shot?
I am trying to test this gun
This gun shoot towards the back!
Why didn't you inform me earlier?
You are bleeding
Wait for me
What are you doing?
I am testing this gun, too
Are you shot?
Why didn't you tell me
before testing?
This gun is named "Nicked Gun"
It shoots backward first,
then forward!
Why didn't you tell me first?
You are bleeding,
cover it first
Kam, why are you sweating?
I am bathing
Where is Ling Ling Chai?
He is still here,
but don't worry
I will finish my mission soon
No, now the plan is changed
Kill him in Lai Yau Wai's home
So we can set Lai up
And no one would suspect
that is done by us
Wait one more day
You want me to wait another day?
Why are you bleeding?
Nothing, I have brushed my teeth
This is the blood of the gum
What kind of teeth brush
you are using?
Broom?
How are you?
Hi, Ling Ling Chai
Commander
I am glad to see you
in the toilet
How is your co-operation?
Not bad, Kam is nice
She is a good friend of mine
Kam, what do you think about me?
Other than your smart look,
I've nothing else to say
There is something else,
you may know it later
Hope you would finish
your mission soon
Yes. Got you
Kam, take back your gun first
Thank you
Don't move, let me help you
Save this for yourself
I am fine, thank you
I tell you, never test the guns alone
I love it, so what?
Waiter
Yes
I've heard that the bean cube
pudding is famous here
Sure
It stinks!
It's famous for its stinks!
Can you bring me another one
which is famous for it's delicious?
I'll bring you bean cube
pudding, too!
Is that true?
True!
Imagine this is stink bean cube
So, it'll be perfect
Give me some deep fried ones
The Hong Kong shopping
centres are so wonderful!
Yeah
How is your wound?
No big deal
Never test the guns which
you don't know
I should have learnt playing
dagger from you
I dare not be your teacher,
but I tell you
The real dagger
is not played by hands
Guess what
Air
Use the air to govern your dagger
So, nothing can't be chopped
Don't you believe,
I will show you with this knife
It's alright, come and eat
Kam, are you still mad at me?
Don't be silly
What made you think
I am not mad at you?
I am very mad at you
Kidding? How angry are you?
I would like to
shoot you to death
Kid, why are you
taking our picture?
Calm down
I can tell you are artists
I am trying to find some
sources about love
From your eyes,
I can tell you two are lovers
So, I can't help taking
your pictures,
hope you don't mind
So, take back the pictures
I will keep this one, thank you
I am sorry
Don't mention it, take it
Mister, did you spit it?
Yes, anything wrong?
Nothing, I just want to know...
From your words,
are you coming from Hunan?
Yeah
I came from Hunan too.
Which district are you from?
Cho Tao District
Me too
What a coincidence!
Which village?
Shang Yang Village
What a coincidence!
We are from Shang Yang Village too
Really?
We meet our neighbour here!
Give way please
A dog always barsed near
the entrance of our village
I kept that dog,
but it disappeared at last
And I found out that it was eaten
That heartless bastard dumped
its bones at the entrance of the village!
Did you do that cruel thing?
No, no...
Why your cheek turns red?
No, not red
Your smile is so embarrassing
Not embarrassing...
I suspected that it was done by you
No...
Is that done by you?
No... No
Not you?
No, not me
- Not you?
- No
- Was it done by you?
Thank you
Don't mention it, just a meal...
By the way
We Hunan people can't be despised
When we go back to our hometown,
we'd be rich and famous
I won't bother you then
If we meet again...
I will treat you breakfast
See you
Wait
Well, wait a minute
Two of my friends are going
to take something
They will return soon
Let's wait for them and
shop around, alright?
Thank you so much,
we have something to do
Never mind
It's hard to get a chance
to meet your old friends
Have a chat,
and I'd like to go to toilet
That's good
Shut up, I just say once
Got it?
You are so smart among
the Hunan people
I know you mind your
outlook very much
In fact, if you forget your hat,
you'll look more handsome
Don't wear hats so often
I loved wearing hats
But someone told me
the hat makes the hair feel stuffy
so it's easy to let me
become bald head
What bothers them?
They just have to take something only!
How is it? Kid
Are you still angry with dad?
You always fool me,
and I just fooled you once
Alright, I am going to buy you
some pop corn then
Really? Let's go now
You fool me again! Bastard!
I wanna beat you!
It hurts
I asked you not to shout!
You are back!
I want to beat you to death!
Police, freeze!
Don't move
We are neighbours
please help me
Don't come over
Bastard!
How are you?
Calling console, calling console
Send ambulance here,
many people are shot
Here is the 4th floor of
Royal Castle, over
Go away, or I'll kill
Tak... Tak...
Go away
Give my son back to me, I beg you
Get lost...
I've this only son,
I beg you
Get lost
Give my son back to me...
Watch him and I've controlled this place
Freeze
Let's go
Hung, hurry up
Hung, be quick
Hung...
Hurry, leave the scene
They're coming down,
be careful
Vaudeville?
I thought I could kill
with somebody's hand
But the plan failed
Have you received my order?
How can you make your
own decision?
I know!
I do hope to understand Chai
Shut up
Who do you think you're
to raise this question?
What is he, that's none
of your business
Remember, your mom &
dad were betrayers
Your grandpa was a traitor
So you're a traitor
It's fate
If I didn't let you stay with me,
you would have been
executed with them
Your life is mine
So you'd obey my order
Is that clear?
Kam I know you may
be kind-hearted
You know what he is now?
He's a beast
He was a nasty guy
Raped the pregnant woman
& the little girls
Look, the girls and so small
These pregnant women are big
They were dragged
to death by Chai
Not only for me
But also for the public
Any questions?
No
OK, let's do as our plan
Kill him in Lai Yau Wai's home
Got it
Are you alright?
What does that mean?
Nothing, I think, you've
locked up for a long time,
and you didn't answer me
That's why I just broke in
and watched
Are you bathing?
Yes, I'm fine
Please close the door
I can't imagine that'd happened
I said, get out & close the door
Yes... well... I'm sorry...
Get out!
What do you want?
Give it or not?
What?
Money for the dead
For the dead?
Tak's dad
Who's Tak's dad?
The innocent one who was shot
dead in the shopping centre
Donate money for the dead?
Can we give Tak's family
through the press?
Maybe
What name should we write?
The kind-hearted guys?
Up to you
Since we're not close friends!
Just donate $500, that's enough
Up to you
Can you pay that $500 for me?
What?
When I finish the mission,
I'll be awarded $500
So I can pay you back
What?
Trust me! I won't forget my words
Alright
Put it properly...
Go... again
Again
This is dangerous explosive
Watch this day & night
Yes
Lai Yau Wai always deals
with smuggling
The lost cranium of dinosaur
may be related to him
That's him
Take action when there's
a chance
Any more questions?
Yes, is Lee Heung Lan
your mom?
As I know, she's a traitor
Sorry, I've no question
Time's up. Let's go
Kam, if we finish the
mission tonight
I'll return at once
So, tell me what you like
I'll send it to you
No, thanks
I've to send you a gift!
White roses
You're very romantic
Maybe, I'll send it to you
Very romantic
If we've time,
I'd like to visit the karaoke
in Hong Kong
I'll keep contact with you
You know,
my voice is like Jacky Cheung
My Adam's apple can
move up & down!
This is the key of the rear door
Hurry up, or you'll have no time
I'll sing you a song
Why not "Lee Heung Lan"?
I tell you,
I'm forced to stay with you
Don't mention Lee Heung Lan
in front of me
Don't sing in front of me
I don't want to hear your bull shit!
I appreciate your straight character!
This key is not important to me
This is not a simple box
This is a special box
called "Magic Box"
It can send me
to Lai's home safely
& beautifully
Magic Box!
Why are you here?
What do you want?
I'd ask you that question!
Oh shit!
I haven't adjusted the angle
So, wrong direction
Now, it's OK
Magic... Shit!
The door is opened. Go in
Kam, I am not fool...
Clean the blood first
Alright
I think this box
is wrongly positioned!
Adjust it, that'll be alright
Don't waste my time!
It'll be alright!
Give me one more chance
Magic Box...
Excuse me,
Dry Martini please
What're you looking?
Give me another glass
That's too much!
What're you looking?
Chai, how is it going?
Dangerous!
The guests look so nasty!
But very kind!
You won't understand!
Sir, how about you?
I'll take care myself, thanks
Mr Lai, your call!
Hello?
Target discovered
Pay attention, the cranium...
Listen, I'll say once more
Put the bones into hot water
to remove extra fats
That cook it with fish
snout for an hour
When will you come back
for the soup?
Cut the crap!
My wife is inside
Romario sent it to Pai Bi-to
Pai Bi-to scored with
his wonderful skill
Chai, how is it?
Can't you listen?
We believed that a man called
Pai Bi-to stole the cranium
Then he used his
personal skills...
Shoot & score one mark
But the signal is weak here
I'm planning to dig a tunnel
towards his sofa
And to hear what he'll say
Chai, cut the crap!
Go to some place else
which receives better
Kam, radio receiver is
being disturbed there
I can't hear
the words of Lai Yau Wai
Chat
try a place which is not crowded
In front of me
there is a piano only
Go & try
Alright
Not clear at all
Don't move, sit well
Right
I feel embarrass
to sit here alone
You love singing songs?
Sing
Alright!
I forgot the lyrics
How is it?
Normal, not special
Like Jacky Cheung or not?
Fair!
You're really great!
You're great to change position
in such short time!
You're somebody, I guess
Be frank
I'm waiting for a very
important man
I think, you know him too
Sorry, no comment
I won't force others
But I've something to tell you
I really appreciate you
I love you
Got it? Here is very dangerous
I don't know where
the killers are hiding!
Will that be so beneficial?
I was shot
How can you walk freely then?
Luckily I've put on
bullet-proof vest
But no bullet-proof trousers
This is for you
Where do you get it from?
I got it while I was escaping!
This is rare!
You're really lucky
Don't be so serious! Nuts!
How do you know that?
Many people say so
The killers of the Man
with a Golden Gun are inside
Go now
Who is he?
I'm here, don't worry
Cripple, sit here
Let me handle it
Bump him to death
You're lucky to escape!
How are you?
Bandage and cotton,
any scissors?
Yes
I can't get any scissors
Forget it
The bullet is shot into
the bone of my thigh
And it's pressing my artery
which locates near the trigeminal
My left brain is lacking oxygen
And the right part of my body
is starting to be palsy
I've to cut the wound and
take out the bullet
Let me do it
This is a famous knife
which is used by a famous smith
It's made by special iron
Net weight 40 catties
16 tales and 4 oz
It's not easy to be taken
by ordinary people
It needs special skill
In order not to contact
the nerves and vessels,
help me to widen the wound
Hold it
I can stand it
Can't you see the bullet?
The black one?
No, that's trash
Higher
The white one?
That's bone
The silver one is the bullet
I see it
It's clipped deep inside
Dig it out
What?
Go ahead
Like this?
Yes
Do you need anesthetic?
Turn on the video
Have you put a wrong tape?
No, this is called
"Shifting attention"
You mean it's the stance of making love?
You want to cheat me?
I mean this is the way
I use as anesthetic!
Have you read the story of Wah Tor,
the greatest doctor of China
Once Kwan Wan Cheung
was playing chess during an operation
Now, I am going to
watch blue tape
under an operation too
Go ahead
Watch it later
Alright
The bullet is too close
to the bone,
nerves are around
It hurts, hold it
Black too?
Why do you stop?
I want my blood to concentrate
to one part intentionally
I don't want to lose
much blood
Forget it, just go ahead
It's blocking my operation
Why don't you move it aside?
Yeah! Come on
Use more force...
What? Do you feel pain?
I am not talking to you
I am talking to the darkie
Sorry... Sorry
So much blood
You broke a vessel
What'll I do?
Go on watching the tape
Can you hold it?
Chat with me,
ask me some questions
Don't let me sleep
I am afraid I won't wake up
after sleeping
What's your name?
I am called Ling Ling Chai
You may ask some
difficult questions
Difficult?
There is a farm, the number of
chicken is 4 times of the ducks
The quantity of ducks is 9
less than the quantity of pigs
The total quantity of
pigs and ducks is 67
How many legs do the animals
in the farm have?
Let me ask you
Alright
Who is the man and
the woman of the picture?
My parents
Why can't we see their face?
When I was small, they died
so I don't have much memory
Oh, I'm sorry
We are orphans
that's why we can
make friends with each other
Kim
Thank you
Don't mention it
Hold it, don't die
Can you turn off
the air condition?
I feel cold
Chai
Chai...
Luckily, I've practised
Chinese Therapy
But about disinfection
and stop bleeding...
This is so wonderful!
.224 Tiny Spittoon Bullet?
It's only used by you
Where is your UFO Rifle?
It must be put on the car outside?
In fact, it's you who shot me
Since you have to kill me,
why did you save me?
What's the relationship between
you and the man with a golden gun?
You needn't ask,
I won't tell anything
Being a spy,
I can't kill you,
so there is only one result
Come on
Alright
You can't make it in
such a short distance!
Poor aiming
I can't help
About killing and fighting,
don't bother me anymore
I'd better watch my tape
Just pretend that
I've never seen you
Chai, don't go,
you can't go back
Commander is the man
with the golden gun
The dinosaur's...
Why are you taller?
You told the truth at last
You look thinner!
It's not easy to be a betrayer, isn't it?
Miss, do you have any plaster?
You look so lovely
I know why Commander Chan
was killed by you now
I want to see your Commander
Please show me the way
You know, Siu Kam
betrayed our country
I don't know
Our country trusts her
so much and she...
Who beat you up?
I think it's done by the man
with a golden gun
Where is Siu Kam?
Where is she?
I don't know, she's lost
So careless!
The enemy is too cunning,
they appear everywhere!
How is your wound?
It'll be alright
You are bleeding!
Sign this, and go to the hospital
for treatment
It's urgent!
Guard. Yes
Send him to the hospital now
You needn't worry much
This way, please
What are you looking,
come on
We are waiting for you
Why an execution now?
Let's choose some other ways
No, we have arrived
So serious!
What's the matter?
Nothing
You mean nothing?
I am in trouble now
Don't move
If anything happens,
tell me clearly first
Go
Ling Ling Chai, you signed and
you admitted that you're a betrayer
You stole our country's treasure
which deserves a capital punishment
You'll be executed now
Go back
Wait, I am innocent...
I didn't see any
national confidential
You should have conscience!
Everybody knows
I am a blind man
You framed a blind
to read national confidential
unlawfully?
Pal, I am a good friend
of Commissioner Chan
I always have meals
together with him
- Wait...
My dad is Commissioner Chan
If you kill me,
I will ask him to kill you
Ready
No... no
I am so smart
I don't want to die
No, no...
Damn!
What an ugly face!
So ugly!
Good shot
Yeah!
Next
My 30 year's practice
is useful now
Get ready
Do you want to kill
a martial arts hero as me?
Not that easy
Ready
Execution now
Take this container to
the boundary in 30 minutes
The buyer is waiting
Yes
More
Your buyer was killed
Now the skull is none
of your business
We will send it back to
Zhen Yang by ourselves
Surrender now
Or you will be killed
Man with a golden gun
I've caught your fellows
You'd better surrender now
Damn!
You claim yourself a man
Luckily I've wore bullet proof vest
I shouldn't have risked
my life for you
You didn't say a word
but just beat me?
You want to beat me?
Beat him!
I'm forced to be a betrayer
I co-operate with you
I know where he is.
Follow me
Come on, I'm waiting for you
Be careful. Go away
I can shoot you to
death this time
Stop looking!
Use our powerful stance!
High temperature flame!
I don't believe your armour
can stand the High
temperature flame
Shit! I'm sorry!
I used up the gas last night!
Sorry for not informing you
Sorry, real sorry!
Playing ball?
I'll blow it off
Your turn now
Don't forget me!
Wonder Fist!
I shouldn't have provided
you good living
You betrayed me for
a pork vendor!
Chai's just been killed
You loved him?
I'll send you to hell with him
Chai!
I know your trick!
If yes, why didn't you
tell me beforehand?
Ling Ling Chai
Chai, are you alright?
Alright, I am fine
Please don't say official lines
Aren't you executed?
I am so mad about this!
You made me lose one hundred!
Out
Bad boss, bad fellows
I can't imagine your fellows
are more greedy than you
What a shame to stand
in front of the words
"Faithful to our country"
If you, the nasty evil,
still exist in China,
our people won't have better lives
I have to kill you now
Don't you think you
trash can kill me?
Trash?
I used up all my days
to invent this
"Super Weapon",
product serial Killing 3000
It's combined to 10 killing weapons.
Now, it's done
Chai, step aside
Far away
Far far away!
Really?
I wish to see it
Killing 3000
Knife
Bicycle chain
Fire powder
Acid
Drugs
Gun
Grenade
Triangle sharpener
Every kinds of weapon can kill
Now, it's combined into one
Are you scared?
You nuts!
You should have been killed
Wait
Man Si
Chai, I depend on you
Well, I've no other choice
I have to fight alone
Butcher's knife?
Butcher's knife
No!
Bastard! Let me see
how powerful you are
I will let you see my power
Damn you!
What kind of knife is it?
Butcher's knife
It's used to kill beast!
Give me $5 pork please
My stall is temporarily closed
come back an hour later
Can you waste an hour for that?
I don't think you need more
than 3 minutes
3 hours are not enough
for me instead!
Chai, let's go home
Don't waste any time
And this place is nice
Damn!
Chai, it's a shit!
Our spy satellite
is lost in the space
It's related to the safety
of our country
Now, I am newly promoted
don't you want me to have trouble?
Come back and help me
I am now dealing some
loving affairs with my girl
About the country, that's peanut,
just forget it
Man Si
I've told you many times,
I'm called Da Mansi!