It's millennium year, besides HK
Macau also goes back to China.
It all looks prosperous and stable.
I'm Ho, from Macau.
There's nothing special about me.
But I want to tell you
a love story of a triad member.
This story occurs around me.
In Macau,
except porn and gambling industries
there's nothing else.
I am a waiter at a nightclub.
I work there because
my girlfriend is receptionist there
and I love her so much.
The boss of this place is Yu.
And recently
he has invited some new bosses
and that's Ben Hon
and Miss Thirteen from HK.
Tonight the boss he's serving is Cock.
In fact, I've known him since childhood
but I guess he has forgotten me already.
You two come here the first time,
so you must enjoy.
Let me get two beauties
for each of you, OK?
- So few?
- No, I'd prefer sitting here
Prepuce, come on
don't tell me you're still virgin.
Right, his ear.
- Prick at it.
- It's through!
Right, where're your assistants?
What assistants?
- You have many assistants?
- Miss thirteen.
She knows you two come
so she keep two beauties for you.
- She's so good to me?
- Coming.
Let me introduce my partner to you.
Brother Yu, come on.
Yu Yeung, Master of Macau.
There's no master in Macau anymore.
We business just do
some mischief business.
- I'm Cock.
- I've heard about you for ages.
- I'm Prepuce.
- Sit down...
- Cheers...
Have you sold the 323 yet?
Why? You ask me not to sell it
before it reaches $3.
On the contrary
I bought in 500,000 shares
when it was at $1.8.
Cock, do you buy shares?
Me? Last month I did the queue as others
and bought that...
I forget the name... tom. Dog. Come.
It's Tom. Com.
You went for the queue?
Your men queued for you.
I did tell you it's dog. Come.
Right, you dog come.
You take me as dog?
Mr. Yu, that 774 wants to set up website.
- Is it worth buying?
- Yes,
Everyone is sensitive to number recently.
They seem to bee hit by number spell.
But it is in trend now.
We must stick to the trend
being on the walk.
Right, our nightclub is doing
"selecting hostess on the internet"
You want a try?
So trendy? Show me how to.
Point at it.
Not that troublesome now.
You can find any girl
on the internet now.
From Beijing, Dailian, Harbien...
Even from Szechuan.
Isn't it better...
to see the girls actually?
Like now, I can't even touch them.
And I don't see then naked.
- There's one...
- Cock
- Sister!
- No problem...
You so care about me?
I've prepared a dozen for you.
I want one who is sweet.
I don't want tom boy.
You imply me?
Cock
you know, Miss Thirteen
has changed a lot now.
Sure, everyone of Hung Hing
know you live together.
A gay or lesbian can become straight too.
No man wants me
so we work together for money.
Brother Yu, please give them some shares.
No thanks
I need not run the place
though I like girls.
You'd better find a girl and get married.
No girls will want
to marry people like us.
What about the Preacher's daughter?
She wants to learn Japanese in Japan.
I've parted with her for ages.
Who are you with now?
Stand still,
and let Brother Cock choose you.
where's no real love in this world.
I just love all girls.
Cock, choose the one you like.
The girl in black.
How is it, Cock?
Your taste has changed?
You love young girls?
I like her as she's cute.
Want another girl?
OK, where's Prepuce?
No, I prefer sitting.
My mission is over, I'll leave now.
No, sister
I want to drink with you all night.
Damn you!
You are to get up at 10 tomorrow.
- What for?
- Watching the stock market.
What?
Stock market, it makes money, nuts.
Enjoy yourselves.
Prepuce
- You want some wine?
- Who are you from?
- Hangzhou
- Hangzhou?
From Hangzhou...
Must you take a bath so long?
Hurry up, I need it badly.
- Take a shower.
- Here comes Hangzhou beauty.
Is the West Lake in Hangzhou very pretty?
Of course.
Someone says there're ten famous scenery?
Sure, have you been there?
No.
But I'll have the chance
to screw a Hangzhou girl tonight.
Take bath now, don't bullshit.
Why must you force me for a bath?
There's real show after the bath.
Real show after the bath?
- Right, go now.
- Is there candy.
Yes, quick...
What are you doing?
Kid...
Take your hands off, what are you doing?
I've asked you to quit many times
but you never listen.
Shit, if I don't, how can I get money
to build a house home?
- You speak back?
- Don't beat women!
Brother Cock, she's my girl,
none of your business
- Come with me!
- Hands off, what are you doing?
You're daring!
Bastard, you disturb my VIP?
You must undergo what you've promised
She's a hostess, she must work out.
I only want to take my girl away.
Brother Ben, let him off, don't beat him.
Stop beating...
- Bastard!
- No...
Brother Cock... I'm Ho...
I'm Lok Wing Ho.
I didn't expect to see you here.
She's Cutie, very cute.
We've been dating for 3 months.
I ask her not to be hostess,
but she doesn't listen.
I don't know
why I'm so jealous this time.
Brother Cock, thanks for helping me.
Or else... I... I don't know
what would happen.
Don't know?
The worse is you lose a hand or leg.
First dating?
Are you of age already, kid?
I remember...
I was 12 when my sister
nearly married you.
Now 19 years old, it's 7 years.
Why are you in Macau?
You forget I was born in Macau?
I see.
I remember asking your sister
when she moved in...
"I'm a mixed of HK and Macau."
- You remember?
- Yes
My name is Wing Ho
and Ho stands for Macau.
My name means I belong to Macau forever.
Where's your sister?
She's in London now.
For a long time?
We only talk over the phone
several times a year.
Frankly speaking, Brother Cock
I want very much you become
my brother-in-law. It's really.
I want to be your brother-in-law too.
- Is it hurt?
- Yes
When I the first time moved in
a estate in the age of five,
I remember that
everything was so new to me.
Someone is moving in.
- A child.
- Go take a look.
Where do you live?
Do you know us?
- Where are you from?
- Mom!
Ho, what's wrong?
- Someone bullied you?
- No!
Madam, we just want to help.
Don't call me Madam,
you may call me Sister Chin
Sister Chin!
Take it upstairs for me.
Very cute.
This chick belongs to me.
Take it back, chick
Chick...
Gee, come and help.
Chick, come and help.
Where are you from?
From far away, I'm a mixed.
You're a mixed?
Sure, I'm a mixed of HK and Macau.
I moved from Macau.
- Then I'm mixed too.
- Are you?
Sure, I used to live in Saukeiwan
and now I live here.
So I'm a mixed of Kowloon and HK.
Of course not.
- Keep the change.
- Thanks...
You live here?
Yes, your expression is weird.
No, I live over there.
Do you? What family members do you have?
Mom and Uncle.
We're neighbors now, nice to meet you.
No problem...
And we become neighbors now.
- So don't bully me and my brother.
- OK
I'm called Gee.
You mustn't call me Chick from now on.
Call me Chiu Shan Ho.
No
I want to call you Chick...
Chick...
Bitch, you steal my book?
What? I'm going to pay.
You're going to pay?
You're going to fooling me.
I don't want it.
Don't go, I won't let you go.
- What do you want?
- I want to search you.
- I'll call molest!
- You threaten me?
You know who I am? I'm Tim.
Have you watched kung fu movies?
The evil man in there is me, Tim.
You won't let me search you
then you can never leave.
You bully a girl? Are you a boy?
Who are you?
I'm the here in movies! I beat evil men!
What evil men?
Don't panic, I'll protect you.
Forget it, let's go.
Want to leave after stealing my book?
I didn't steal it.
She said she didn't.
Stop beating...
Stop fighting...
Don't worry, Cock can fight well.
You mean he can?
Don't worry, he can hold on.
You won't help him?
- You know who am I?
- Hurry
Damn you! Kill you...
Damn you!
I'll beat you whenever I see you!
- Are you alright?
- I'm fine.
- Really OK?
- Alright.
Chick... come out.
What is it?
Your mom knows you had a fighting today?
She's too busy to take care of me.
- Why?
- She has to work.
You mean it.
My mom is strict to me.
I can tell your mom is furious.
Why don't you go to school?
I don't like doing homework.
It's simple, let me teach you.
No.
Your face...
It doesn't hurt, look it's OK.
I must thank you for today.
No, I should protect you.
Why?
You live opposite me,
so I must protect you.
What if I don't live opposite?
- I still will.
- Why?
I don't know.
Anyway, tell me if anyone bullies you
- And I'll stand out for you.
- All right...
- Do you hear?
- Yes, I do.
- I'll repeat it to you!
- Good.
- I'll forever protect you!
Say it again.
Protect me forever!
- Repeat again!
- Protect me forever!
Let's play football.
No, it's boring.
Where to?
None of your business,
you're not counted in!
- We don't revenge?
- Sure!
I'll call you up tonight
and let's discuss.
I won't talk on, I must go now, bye.
Is he mistaken?
Is this Three-Man-In-A-Boat?
Chick, what are you doing?
I thought you wouldn't come
so I don't com.
Of course not.
But mom called me when I was leaving.
- She won't let you out?
- Of course not.
Stand up, now, quick.
What for?
Get up, come here.
Close your eyes. Don't move.
- It hurts!
- I'm very happy!
I like biting others
whenever I'm happy or upset.
You're nuts?
Of course not
mom say I've made progress in school.
So she bought me a cassette player.
I can listen to Leslie's song
when I go to school now.
Good, your mom pampers you so much.
If you will study hard...
your mom will pamper you too.
No way.
Now you don't go to school,
what are you going to do?
One need not always go to school.
I want to be a Boss!
I'll walk the world
with Prepuce and Wrinkle.
Boss? Boss of triad?
I'll not talk with you
if you become triad boss.
If I don't, others will bully me.
No one will bully you
if you behave yourself.
What about Tim?
If you stay away from him,
he won't find faults in you.
Anyway, I hate triad people.
You know why I come to HK
with my brother?
How come I know?
As my dad used to be triad boss in Macau.
I hate him!
What about you?
What do you want to become?
I want to study abroad
and make lots of money.
I must buy a house for mom and brother
and get a handsome rich man
who is good to me.
You're dreaming.
Everyone must have his ambition.
Being a boss is also an ambition.
You still say?
Then I'll become stunt man
like Jackie Chan.
OK?
OK! Show me some kung fu.
- This is Seven Chop. Isn't it nice?
- No.
This is Dragon Fist, nice?
Do me some kicking.
You fat bottoms!
Don't beat me...
Don't go, dare you throw at me?
Fat bottoms, don't go!
Don't go!
Set fire! Quick!
Dare you bully my girlfriend again!
Let me burn your paperstand!
Put out the fire now!
You two bastards dare set fire?
Come with me!
My paperstand...
Compensate now!
- What are you doing?
- Compensate me now!
Set fire? You burnt a horse
you know it's serious?
You'll be sent to jail, you know?
You do nothing but stir up trouble.
Now dad's paperstand is burnt down.
Boss Bee, we dare not again!
We live in the same estate.
We must help each other in future,
got it?
Shake hands and be friends!
Cock!
Cock, Prepuce, Wrinkles, Tim
are the 4 rascals in our estate.
Luckily my mom Sister Chin
can control them.
Collecting garbage!
Take our all garbage!
You, he and me...
Chick!
Softly, my son is ill.
Chick is not the name? Call him Cock!
Mrs. Leung
why don't you
take your son to a doctor...
but keep him in here instead?
Keung, let's go to see the doctor!
When did your Chick become Cock?
Stop shouting.
We're not shouting.
- It's not noise control zone.
- Right.
And you, Mr. Leung
your son keeps stealing
porno books from my stand
I wonder if he's impotent?
What? My son is only 12...
Mrs. Leung, when I was 11,
I began wanking...
I shouldn't have told you!
- Keung, let's go to see doctor!
- Return books!
Why fear? You fear your mom scolds you?
I don't fear that.
- No? What do you fear then?
- Right.
Anyway... don't shout near here, OK?
- You live here, not the opposite side.
- Right.
Anyway, don't shout.
I watch it here.
If you must shout, go elsewhere.
OK...
- 100 for 1 set!
- Play 4 rounds!
4 rounds, 3 fold at least!
Let me go first.
- Where's your sister?
- Studying.
- Where are you going?
- None of your business.
Bastard, don't be busybody.
He's right.
You stand for that bastard?
None of your business.
She's studying, Cock is wooing her.
Don't insult her, what wooing?
She's studying, we live opposite.
We must look after each other.
You'll soon become chief.
Sister Chin!
Chick, what is it?
Gee is studying, we don't make a noise.
You disturb her by standing here.
Go inside...
OK
And the English exam tomorrow
is important.
Be good.
Let's start!
I sit here, you find yourself a seat.
- And you two sit oppositely.
- Troublesome.
- Why? You fear someone will cheat?
- How to?
Quiet, OK?
Quiet, don't disturb his girlfriend.
But playing mahjong does make noise.
What do you mean with noise?
Haven't you heard this song?
If you're in love, you lose money.
You'll lose much, kid.
- You'll lose much...
- Go on playing.
Hurry.
You lose all!
You pay me $128
Prepuce is right, if you lose,
means you're in love.
Is it finished?
It smells good, who is cooking?
Really.
Sister Chin does.
She's always pretty.
Go to hell!
You pay me $128, time to eat now.
- Pay now.
- Hurry.
Frankly speaking,
does she know you love her?
I needn't make that so clear?
Will she let you woo her?
Man, she lives opposite me
and we've always seen each other.
We've been in good terms...
she should know?
Have you ever... made love with her?
Shit! She's not that casual.
Not even a caress?
- That means you never!
- No!
Nothing ever?
Gee...
Look at her, what is she like?
She's a cute angel.
Gee, what a coincidence?
- What a coincidence!
- We happen to meet here.
Of course not,
he comes all the way for you.
Where's that fatty and Wrinkles?
Aren't you the Four-Man-On-A-Boat?
They're busy,
so I come to wait for you here.
- How's exam today?
- Not bad.
Lok Wing Gee, they're your friends?
They live opposite me.
This is Cock, this is Tim.
I won't hinder you, we'll leave now.
- Bye...
- She called you Camel?
- Lok Wing Gee!
Lok Wing Gee
Why are you here?
Your friend is pretty clever.
I'll leave now, won't hinder you.
- So soon?
- Right...
- Sit for more a while.
- Bye...
- Where are you going?
- Back home.
Why do you come here for?
There's an amusing movie
so I come to ask you for it.
I know, "A Horny Man"
I want to see it too.
OK, I'll get tickets.
You can... take it as relaxation.
I've got it.
You're so good to me.
I have an appointment.
Sorry, Chick, my friend asked me first.
- He has arrived, bye.
- Bye
You've waited for long?
Gee!
Cock! Come here.
This is George, this is Cock.
Chiu Shan Ho!
Nice to meet you!
Cock lives opposite me
we've grown together.
We're sort of buddies.
Sort of Buddies?
Cock, let me ask Ho
to see that movie with you.
It's time we leave, come on, bye.
Bye.
Go home and see porn movie!
You play with me.
Press this...
You've lose.
Stop bothering brother.
Go and play there, go.
- Hey, is her troublesome?
- It's Ok.
But I am bad at playing this.
We'll eat soon, wait a while.
Are we really eating here?
Mom is the best cook.
I want to eat Japanese food with you.
People say movie stars always go there.
Next time, mom wants to chat with you.
- Eat now.
- It smells good!
Help yourself...
This is my mom's best dish,
Coke Chicken Wing.
- Eat one.
- Thanks.
Mom, explain how you cook it.
I marinate chicken wings with coke
so they taste sweet.
Mom's Coke Chicken Wing
is my favorite dish.
It tastes really good, Aunt.
It's better than those
prepared by restaurants.
George, where do you live?
Jardine Hill.
It's rich area, isn't it?
I want to see that area too.
I'll go too, I want to play TV games.
Go to hell! Eat now!
My parents seldom stay in HK.
George, where did you meet Gee?
I met him in a library.
I'm not asking you.
I went to borrow books, and so did she
then we met each other.
You young men are open.
- Eat now, come on.
- Eat more.
You snatch my girl? Go to hell!
I got dumped, help me.
Can you comfort me?
Can you just comfort me?
Comfort my lips.
You're bad, come on...
How is it?
Don't shout...
What are you doing?
Why don't you become my boyfriend?
Damn your boyfriend...
What is it?
- I'll pay you... $90.
- No way.
Get me $100.
Go away! I'll come for you later...
How is it?
Tell me if anyone bullies you,
I'll teach him a lesson!
None of your business!
I know none of my business
but you live opposite me
so I must take good care of you.
I know you're not interested in me.
Of course I'm not as rich as George...
- He's born with a silver spoon.
- Stop mentioning him, OK?
He bullies you?
None of your business, I repeat.
You mean none of my business?
Why can't you tell me everything
just like when you were small?
You won't even do that?
He said, this estate is not for human.
Ass-hole!
He even said he hates
my brother pastering him.
Ass-hole!
He says he loves
the Coke Chicken Wing my mom makes.
Ass-hole!
You're nonsense, don't curse every time.
He means to part with you.
Have you got some money from him?
What do you take me as?
Then... Has he slept with you?
Chick, mind your vulgar words.
You think so dirty.
Of course I must make it clear.
If that ass-hole takes advantage of you
I will not only kill him.
Everyone in this estate will kill him!
I won't talk with you now!
I'm comfortable now.
In fact...
I don't understand, not now
I didn't understand
when I was small already.
Why are you so tall?
- OK, I'm not short indeed.
- What?
Thanks, Chick.
I won't think about that ass-hole again.
You shouldn't get along with
that ass-hole from the beginning!
If you want a man,
you must get one from our estate.
They're all like you,
I can't get an ideal one.
What? At least I am not horny.
I want rice roll.
OK, let's eat rice roll.
Eat it, and shit on him!
Stop!
Get off!
Get off!...
Have you courted a girl
called Lok Wing Gee?
What do you want?
How dare you dump her?
No one can do that!
Aren't you Brother Cock?
What? Why are you stammering?
I've parted with Gee already
but I haven't wronged her.
You haven't wronged her?
You cheated her love, you've wronged her?
You screwed her, you've wronged her?
- Have you screwed her?
- No
No? You must have held her hand!
I don't care, you touched my wife.
Now, in order to heal her wound.
- You must compensate $54,000!
- $54,000!
Brother Cock,
I don't have so much cash with me.
No?
- Go and draw from ATM!
- Right.
Ray at once or I'll beat you
every time I see you!
Go!
- What do you mean?
- Come out.
So late?
What are you up to at this late hour?
I want to give you a watch.
Why give me gift?
I bought you this
from my part time salary. Take it.
Why give me such valuable thing?
You know I will never take it.
I have reason, it's related to you.
What's that got to do with me?
That bastard bullied you
so Tim, Prepuce, Wrinkles
and I want to beat him up.
- You beat him?
- Of course we must teach him a lesson.
He can dump everyone but not you!
Did you injure him?
Nothing, just minor injure.
Doctor says he'll stay in bed
for 3 months.
You're too much!
What too much?
I asked him to compensate...
to heal your wound.
So I bought a gold watch with this money.
I don't want it!
You're no different from a triad member
Living in this housing estate
all others take us as triad members,
though we're not.
You can stay clean by yourself.
No one asks you
to get along with the triad.
Already.
What?
Me and Ho Nam
Tim, Prepuce, and Wrinkles
have followed a boss.
You've joined the triad?
You've joined the triad...
I hate triad members most!
Good, triad society.
Triad members can beat others
and do blackmailing.
They are up to doing all evil deeds!
- I won't talk with you anymore!
- Gee...
Gee...
So lonely? Where's your Cheese cake?
- What Cheese?
- I mean Gee.
Let's eat in night bazaar tonight.
You'll treat, Brother Cock?
I've put the gold watch to pawn shop
I've got lots of money,
let's eat like king.
Didn't you want to send Gee
the gold watch?
She rejected it, she won't take it.
Sister, Brother Cock.
Go!
Wait...
Can we get into position, Boss?
No warm up needed now?
Tim, go, beat him!
Earth Monster, Earth worm... no.
Sucking... no, rubbing the knees!
Right! Kick at his legs hard!
Try to get this!
Great, I've got it!
- How can you do that?
- Come out a bit more...
Left...
So hardworking? Want to kill others?
Boss!
So lonely? You don't woo girls with them?
Woo girls?
Boss, when will you take us
to shopping area?
You want a fame?
Of course we do!
We mustn't forever stay here?
We must see the world to make a fame.
- You want a fame?
- Of course.
or else I can't improve life.
Furthermore, if I have no fame...
no one will know you.
You mean it, good!
- I'll take you to disco tonight!
- Yeah!
I've an appointment with the Fukienese.
They always steal Mercedes
and Volvo cars.
It's evil to steal cars.
It's just make a living.
I hear you're frustrated.
I'm fine.
Just be smart.
Boss!
Foreign girl! Boss, blond hair!
Tim, you'll like her!
Beautiful...
Can we touch her, Boss?
There're many girls here!
I'll have a great time now!
How is the container truck affairs?
It's fixed, Boss, very safe.
Are you sure? Just don't spoil it.
Brother Fook, Brother Bee has come.
- Has he?
- Come in.
- Brother Bee!
- Brother Fook!
I'm sorry... I come late...
It's OK... Sit down...
- Great Brother Fook.
- Brother Fook!
Sit down...
These are the new force from the estate.
- Are they?
- Please teach us more.
Good youngsters
You're lucky to have Bee as Boss.
You'll surely make a fame.
- You're mighty.
- What?
It's reported in papers,
8 Mercedes are stolen.
- You must have made a big profit.
- Just a little.
- Mamasan, bring your hostesses in!
- OK
- Young men, cheers!
- Come on...
Brother Bee, for your health and money!
- You too...
- Cheers!
Brother Fook, can we eat this watermelon?
Sure, help yourselves...
These kids are impolite...
Mamasan, get us more watermelon!
Brother Fook, here come the hostesses.
The girls have come...
How to arrange for them to sit?
I don't dare who you are.
If you are here, you must get one!
Tall girl, where do you want to go?
Come and sit here.
Fei, Brother Fook wants you, go at once.
- Come here...
- Sit with Brother Fook
and serve him well.
- Very good.
- Not bad...
Let me kiss you! Come on...
Drink with Brother Fook.
You're shy?
Brother Fook, cheers.
You're not like a whore.
- Right.
- I like that!
Brother Fook, it's her second day here.
She's fresh here.
Fei? Fei...
Fei, I'll take you tonight! Come on...
Very pure.
Do you know she works here?
- Drink with Brother Fook!
- Come on.
Come, don't be shy.
Brother Fook, cheers.
I dare say...
No one is as competent as me
with dealing with Mainlander.
It's not easy to smuggle cars.
There're lets of obstacles, Brother Bee.
Everyone knows you have
good relation up there.
Not only with good relation
but my dick is getting hard on.
Come and touch it, come on.
Touch it, and see if it's hard. Come on.
Brother Fook! Take it easy!
What do you mean?
Who do you think you are?
- Man, what is your name?
- I'm called Cock!
I didn't mean bad.
Sorry, Brother Fook, he's drunk, sorry.
I am not drunk, Boss.
- What do you want?
- I want to take your girl.
- What?
- She's my wife!
I didn't know she works as a clubgirl.
- She's your wife?
- Yes.
Man, let me tell you.
She's hostess here, and gets my money.
And... who are you
to talk to me like this?
But I like you as you're daring
I like guys as you.
Tall girl, come here!
Go home with your husband!
Manasan, get me a hostess with big busts!
Sure...
- Brother Fook, I'm really sorry.
- It's alright now. Be alert!
Brother Fook, I... I didn't mean bad.
She's really my wife.
We've been quarrelling recently.
She looks through me now.
I know she works here to irritate me.
Right? You mean to make me angry!
Gee!
Why? Kid, go and chase her now!
Chase now! Woman are simple.
Go and make love with her,
then she'll calm down.
Go!
- Nuts. Brother Bee, cheers!
- Come on...
What's his name?
He's called Cock.
Cock? Good name...
Lok Wing Gee, stand there!
Go away! I don't want to see you!
Why do you work at nightclub?
I want to make money.
Tell me if you do, I'll help you.
I need $150,000, can you help me?
I've borrowed $120,000 salary,
so I must work.
I must go back now.
Why do you need so much?
Mom is sick,
we need money for her operation.
Go away!
I don't care
I've paid for you tonight,
I'm your customer.
What do you take me as?
What do you think then?
You really want to be a whore?
I ask you, if the boss just then...
wants to sleep with you, what'll you do?
Mamasan will help me out.
Mamasan will help me.
Which mamasan will help you?
You'd better trust me!
What for?
Can you help me? You have money?
What do you take yourself as?
You're just a lousy scoundrel!
Right, I'm a lousy scoundrel.
I'm not rich, what about you?
You're a rich girl?
You're pretty? But you're now a whore.
Right, we're the perfect couple.
You're a whore, me a scoundrel...
Get lost! I don't want to be
a couple with you. Go away.
You think you're very special?
Why stay here when you can't help me?
I must work now.
Why, a quarrel?
You're making a show?
Why are you dressed like this?
Come on, try her.
- Can I?
- Try her...
- Is she bouncy?
- Very bouncy.
Again.
I'll show you one more time.
Stop fighting!
I'm always this lousy.
You're injured.
Lok Wing Gee
remember when you moved here at first
that Tim bullied you hard
and that I beat him up?
Chiu Shan Ho, you're not a child anymore.
I just want to tell you,
if anyone bullies you
I'll stand out for you.
I will not only beat him,
I'll kill him too!
Nuts.
Yes, I'm nuts! Where are you going now?
I go back to work.
Why must you go back to work?
I go to change clothes.
You thinks I want to wear this?
No, you look good in that.
Gee didn't tell my you were in hospital
or I would have visited you.
Anyway, we live opposite.
What's that go to do?
You are never home.
Do you have good business
with Brother Bee?
Being a scoundrel is never a good job.
What are you looking?
You must study hard,
and don't turn bad, OK?
Hey, you want to correct my son?
No, I know I am not up to that.
- Mom.
- Did I say something wrong?
Can you respect my mother?
None of his faults, I have sore throat.
Gee, you and Ho go and ask a nurse in.
Sister Chin, you'll be alright soon.
Gee works very hard for your illness.
I know she's a good daughter.
Chick, you really love Gee?
But Gee will never love me.
She's not a rich girl at all.
I'm a scoundrel.
If I'm smart, I can be a boss
if not, I'll be small potato forever.
Gee is different.
I think she must have
her plan for future.
But we can't always fulfill our plan.
Just like me
I never expected to marry Gee's father
I thought I could get a perfect husband
but we parted at last.
When I was small,
I found you very strong
as you alone raised two children.
You're very great.
In fact, I'm a loser.
I only want my daughter
finds someone who loves her.
Chick, will you love Gee
with whole heart?
I always thought... you hate me.
There're kind-hearted scoundrels too.
Maybe you'll be a good man.
I'll treat Gee well.
Time for injection, please wait outside.
What did mom tell you?
When I grow up, I know what fate is.
Sister worked so hard
for mom's medical expenses.
After so many incidents, I begin to know
why my girlfriend becomes hostess.
Mom died two months later
and Brother Cock accompanied my sister
to Macau, as he had promised.
How come there's no taxi?
Cock!
Where're you going with this stuff?
I'm going to Macau with Gee.
Why to Macau? Take the next hydrofoil.
Come chat with me.
Boss, I don't want to go.
You know, Sister Chin is dead
and I promised I'd
take care of her children.
You said you wanted to go last time,
come on!
- It's no good, Boss.
- Come on!
Anyone answers?
Brother Cock doesn't answer.
What's wrong?
Eat some roast goose, it's delicious!
No, Thanks.
What are we going to discuss?
Never mind, since Boss takes us here
of course we must eat.
Don't hurry, Gee will wait for you.
You freshmen are not bad.
Brother Fook, you won't just ask us
to eat roast goose.
Nothing...
I'm going to Macau.
but you bring me here.
What are we going to discuss?
Gee is waiting for me at the pier,
you know?
Tim, they hide weapons under the table.
They say some guys from Hung Hing
want to snatch my places.
They are also going to
use speed boats to smuggle cars.
Brother Fook, are you suspecting us?
Boss Bee, you mustn't say so.
We're buddies.
We must take initiation.
You bastard! Kwan!
Boss! Run!
Macau has changed a lot.
The pier used to be tiny
and now there's helicopter service too.
Where did you settle your mom's ash?
Hau Cee Cemetery.
Both your mom and sister are tough women.
That time if you left with us
it would be wonderful.
In this world... everything is destined.
I didn't go to Macau with your sister
because I had to begin my fugitive life.
Boss, how to go to 2728, So Koo Bay?
You want to look for Foul Wah?
He's my cousin.
That boat over there
Damn it!
You peep at me?
What do you mean?
Run... where can you run? Peep at me?
I didn't peep at you.
I just looked at you wash your hair!
Damn it! You peep at me?
Damn! What did you said.
- You... take it easy!
- Bastard! Damn you!
- What are you doing?
- I come to look for someone...
Who?
My cousin, Foul Wah.
You're Cock?
Your cousin has just gone to Taiwan.
He told me before he left
that you'd come.
You're sister-in-law?
Right, come here...
This is cousin of your brother-in-law.
Something happened to him,
so he takes shelter here.
So it's a scoundrel on the run.
Don't bullshit! I speak your dialect.
She's my sister, call her Chu.
Sister, when are you going to put him?
Of course on the fishing raft.
Cock, I have a shop in HK.
so I often go outside.
Stay here, though the place is small.
No, it's a nice place here, fresh air.
There's fish to eat,
and things to see, not bad.
- Let me take it.
- I'll take it myself... thanks.
- Sister-in-law, quick, please.
- Time to eat...
Cock, just ordinary dishes, don't mind.
No, I like simple food.
Bastard! What do you mean?
I don't mean this.
I wouldn't insult sister-in-law for sure.
Lazy bone...
Sister.
Is this correct
to describe such a scoundrel?
Enough! Stop speaking rudely.
I was only joking.
If I dislike you,
I wouldn't eat with you.
Narrow-minded.
Sister, can I enter for Miss HK?
No, you enter for Miss HK?
You might catch more fish
as you're so pretty.
Aren't I pretty?
Cock, if Chu really enters for Miss HK
does she get a chance?
Right, is there a chance?
Yes! If I am one of the judges
I'd surely give you
a Prize of Miss Tough!
What?
Stop behaving rudely, you're a girl.
I must attack you at night.
Attack me? Let me kill you first.
Kill you... Eat on, stop speaking.
It's all cool.
Very windy, go back.
Can I sit with you?
Have peanuts.
You're from Taiwan.
Why do you stay in this small village?
We are from a small village of Taiwan.
Since sister married Wan
we come to HK
we have no family in Taiwan now.
Why are you on the run?
No, I killed the boss, so I run away.
I tell you, I have sixth sense.
What sixth sense?
I can sense danger
before it actually arrives.
So mighty?
- Where's your boyfriend?
- What?
Your boyfriend.
I have none. And you,
where's your girlfriend?
I used to have one. Now no.
Why?
She left me.
- She's gone?
- I left.
Why ask so much?
Nothing, I'm just curious.
OK, I'll go back.
No, sit for more a while.
I can sense danger here.
What danger?
I catch you now?
Come on.
I told you I have sixth sense,
you believed now?
How come we caught this shoe?
Still staring at me?
Chu, the balance.
These fish are a bit little.
Talk with my sister for that.
- Where's your dog?
- What dog?
What dog? I'm human!
You fool me?
Damn you bastard!
- Well...
- Yes.
What is the sixth sense you mention?
Any human is born with 5 senses.
Seeing, hearing,
smelling, touching, tasting
and the sixth sense is an additional one.
It's a sense that cannot be described.
Only some people have it. Understand?
I have this sense too
I sense that someone is following us.
Run! Quick!
Damn you! You have someone to back you.
It's their choice not to buy your fish.
Business talks about fair competition.
I don't care, I must eat your today!
How can I greet you?
Who's most famous here?
Adam Chow.
- I'm called Sister Chow.
- Damn you!
Run!
Don't get near!
Do you know his brother-in-law
Foul Wah is on the walk too?
You want to die?
Lightly... it hurts.
The bruises won't fade if I rub lightly.
- Does it hurt here?
- Yes.
Don't shout around.
Here, does it hurt?
Horny!
You say I don't know,
now I make it and you call me horny.
you do it yourself.
OK, help me, I don't know how to.
Does it hurt here?
I rub for you, but why must you kiss me?
No, as you kiss me
so I must kiss you back.
How can I face others?
It's fair now
Don't kiss me again,
or I'll kiss you back.
It hurts!
Did I bite you?
No, my leg still hurts.
Sorry...
I'm hungry.
Please cook me some noodle.
OK, you need food for energy.
And now, number 12, Miss Lok Wing Gee.
I'm Lok Wing Gee.
I'm 19, a student.
My resolution is to become an accountant.
If I become Miss HK
I'll promote HK and make HK famous.
Thanks.
Miss Lok Wing Gee
gives a good answer.
No wonder she's the hottest this year.
I'm hungry, is it ready?
What's wrong?
What to court Miss HK? NO way for you!
I finally know what a dog is.
What a dog? It's a monstrous dog.
- Horny.
- Not as horny as you.
My sixth sense tells me
that I'll meet a man who pampers me much.
Very much...
- What is it?
- Go sell the fish.
Where's your dog?
I'll have it bite you
if you laugh at me again.
Great, you have a dog bite you.
Prepuce, Cock speaking.
I don't care whatever you do
you must get me Gee's phone number.
OK, where are you?
Don't care for that.
Lok Wing Gee... someone says
you were once a clubgirl.
No comment.
I make this chicken best.
I'll make some food, wait.
We have our duty,
please say something, Miss Lok.
Who are you looking?
It's me, Chick.
Where are you? In HK?
I've always been in HK.
They say you killed someone,
and you're on the run.
I'm not on the run,
I'm only hiding for a moment.
I don't want you to get involved,
so I didn't call you up.
You call me up now?
I read papers that some one bullies you
so I want to know the situation.
Chick...
I miss you much.
Me too.
I want to see you too.
I want see you.
But there's no traffic here.
What do you mean be this?
The first ferry begins at 6 tomorrow.
Where are you now?
I'm in Lamma Island.
Cock, I heard all
your telephone conversation.
I was lying on the bed
but I wasn't sleeping. Go back now.
She is more important to you.
I only want to tell you.
These 2 months were
the happiest time in my life.
And... my sixth sense is never accurate.
Cock!
I want you to buy me high-heeled shoes.
I want to wear them all my life.
You've promised?
I'm getting married!
Want to get married?
Have you thought over?
I've thought over
I must get married one time.
But if my life is like Gee.
I believe in this whole world...
all men will envy me.
I don't think so,
your girl is nice and pretty.
She'll be ruined if she marries you.
Boss, is it true?
You should back me up,
but why this remark to me?
I thought you never want love.
You're against it?
I've talked with the Fukienese.
Go get married,
they say they'd spare you.
- Thanks, Boss.
- Thanks for what?
If you hadn't killed their boss
the new boss is still a nobody.
He should thank you instead.
Boss. Be my parent for wedding.
You want to get married
at this young age.
I'll say you'll get divorce soon.
Boss.
You've put tonic on?
Why drag the face?
Shit
they haven't told us a price yet
- But we must pay whatever they ask for.
- Right...
$39,900 to get my wife, it's a bargain.
I say, my wife is priceless.
- Priceless.
- I have no idea.
- She's worthy.
- Damn!
Will Boss Bee come?
I don't know.
Don't worry, I asked him this morning
and he said he'd come.
It's alright now.
He still pampers me.
Why does it take them so long
to fetch the bride?
- Right.
- Brother Bee...
Pin, Chee, how's your boss Bear?
Boss Bee, I want to work with you.
Why do you want to work with me?
Boss Bee, look.
What's happened to you?
That boss is SM maniac.
He not only beats us,
and want to sodomite us.
Is Bear such a person?
Don't go!
Don't let him run! Kill him!
Brother Cock...
How is your sister?
Sister is arriving soon.
Not Brother Cock,
call him brother-in-law now.
Brother-in-law... sister is coming.
You're pretty.
Time has come,
go to worship ancestors now.
Can you repeat, hubby?
you speak it very lovely, come on...
Hubby
Again...
- Wrinkles, Boss Bee...
- What?
Quick! Burn that ass-hole!
You bastards! Free me at once!
- What is it?
- Something happens to Boss Bee.
- I'll get drunk tonight.
- Don't get drunk.
Cock.
Drive now, what are you doing?
Speak something now.
Stay with these women.
We three go to see the situation.
You must come back on time.
It's 11 only, well soon be back.
No way, we're the righteous guys.
I must tell my wife now.
- Hurry, it won't take more than an hour.
- No way!
Don't go!
Don't be like this,
go and stay with your mom, OK?
Who is more important, your boss or me?
You're most important.
You're most important in this world, OK?
Boss, hold on! Here we come!
Boss!
How are you? Boss, are you alright?
Don't be angry, Cheese.
Don't worry, it'll be alright.
It's more important than the wedding,
you say.
- Boss, you alright?
- Boss, it's alright now.
Chee and Pin are beasts!
Help boss get in the car.
I'm wearing a suit for your banquet.
- I believe you...
- Help the boss in the car!
OK, Brother Cock.
Kid! Don't die!
Cock!
Police! Freeze!
Don't fire!
Sit down!
You won't start a fight on today.
Don't worry, Gee,
it's going to be alright.
I assure you can get sleep
with Cock tonight.
Go!
Shut up!
Since I became a policeman...
I've never see triad
dressed so nicely for a fight.
Cock!
Miss...
- Can I talk to her?
- Hurry up!
What shall I do, Cock?
Sorry
Cock!
I still remember
all friends and relatives
waited all evening
and the groom never came
and neither did the bride.
The judge sentenced me manslaughter
and I was given
four and half year imprisonment.
The first thing I did
when I was released is to find you two.
But I failed to.
We went back to Macau.
Later my sister went to England.
She said this city
reminds her the unhappy past
so she wanted a new life.
How is she now?
She gave my a call last year
but she said
she'd be getting married soon.
Drink more... help yourselves.
Cock, when did you come?
Congratulations!
- You're back?
- I'm back for almost a year.
What are you up to now?
You hold wedding banquet in a restaurant?
Have you watched the sign? Albertini.
Don't understand.
I'm not called Ben Hon anymore.
I have an Italian name
Albertini Hon.
Very cool!
Have you watched "God Father" at HBO
It's classic.
Now that we're on the walk.
We must run an Italian restaurant
and get an Italian name. How to run?
- Sister!
- Cock!
Thanks... Long time no see.
Yes, your husband is called... Tini?
Albertini
Have you got a weird name then?
I'm Ginanori Paolighetan.
And shorted to Thirteen Ghetan.
- Right, correct.
- How so?
- Here comes Big Fei, let's drink.
- Good, come on...
Is the VCD you produced of high quality?
Can't you put more
artistic elements in them.
Don't make it like pirated VCDs.
And you must not put mosaic at them.
Big Fei!
No mosaic please!
Open up like this! Right!
- Why lose temper?
- I'm teaching the son!
Your son? Are you mistaken?
How can you say that?
His son is editor
in a publishing company.
How old?
My son in only 16,
finishes primary school.
So I help him a bit in literature field.
A porn magazines is literature?
Then Ben Hon runs this Albertini.
Makes him the tycoon
of nightclubs and restaurant?
Right.
- Your jacket is cool.
- I bought it in France.
Brother Kei, come in.
I put this on, thinking the banquet
being held in Chinese restaurant.
So I went home to change clothes.
No, the Chinese costume makes you
stand out, come on...
- Will this do?
- Cool, sign here!
I become an elephant now.
Look at Sis, she seems
to enjoy more than you.
Congratulations! Sister-in-law.
Don't say such thing,
take Brother Kei to VIP room.
No matter what enjoyment, let's cheers.
It's even better with red wine.
This place is not bad.
Everyone is here today?
Right, my friend hasn't arrived yet.
He's just come back from England
he runs gambling stall in China Town.
Does he?
He's called Chris Chong.
He has business in S.E. Asia
and in Philippines.
Which field?
He's my idol anyway,
he's like Harrison Ford.
Like Harrison Ford?
- He's coming soon.
- What is it?
Ho Nam has come.
Here he comes!
Ho Nam.
- Congratulations...
- Thanks...
You finally get married.
You come back now?
I've been to Taiwan for one year.
Where's Liar?
Say no more, we parted and
she went back to Kuala Lumpor.
- She sends you this.
- Thanks.
- What about me?
- Double.
OK, ready, 1, 2, 3!
Hello
- Hey, Ben! Congratulations!
- Thanks.
I have an Italian name, Albertini.
Let me introduce, my wife, Virginia.
- Hello
Thanks for coming.
Come... let me introduce you some friends.
Big Fei
Brother Kei
- Brother Kei
- Hello
- My wife
This is Prepuce.
Cock.
He and Chan Ho Nam are
the two best guys in Hung Hing.
Ho Nam has just left.
Chris Chong comes from England
just for my wedding.
He's my idol.
Nice to meet you!
Let me introduce, my wife, Virginia.
Hello!
Chris, you're big boss
in London China Town
no wonder your wife
is as pretty as Miss London.
You're bride today,
you're prettiest today.
Thank you!
Help yourselves, drink more.
Drink red wine.
I wish the newly wedded couple...
Love each other forever.
- Thanks
Virginia,
drink with the pretties bride now.
- Cheers!
- Thanks...
Cheers...
Thanks
Don't you want to meet sister?
Don't you know she's back?
I wouldn't be
as shocked as you if I knew.
Mr. Chong, I want to ask you.
Is cultural business
in London China Town prosperous?
Quite good.
I mean Chinese porno books.
You're interested in that too?
How are you?
Long time no see.
I'm doing research work
in this field recently
and I'm going to
publish an artistic book.
Give me a call if you have time.
You know each other?
No.
I only asked her
about the weather in England.
She has husband, don't woo her.
Thirteen! Someone wants to see you.
- Who?
- Go and take a look.
Who?
- I'm happy. You show up now?
- You're pretty!
Why are you still so rude?
This is my candid side.
I come all the way back
from Taiwan to congratulate you.
Thanks!
I didn't expect you love a man.
Right, we must try everything.
- Hubby, come here...
- What is it?
- My buddies, May Cheung, is she pretty?
- Just so so.
- Say no more, take a photo.
- Good...
1, 2, 3, cheese!
Got it, we'll share the market
I'll surely count you in.
OK. Bye.
Buy another for it.
Is brand name in HK
better priced than in Europe?
I really don't want
to go to Kuala Lumpor.
Give me a reason.
I want to see my brother.
This bear is for you.
Still take me as a little girl?
I've always taken you as a little girl.
If you give me this,
it'll only be cut open by Customs.
You know they check severely in Malaysia.
No one will check your things.
There's nothing in there, why fear?
I really don't want
to go to Kuala Lumpor.
I stay here and wait for you here.
You have a date?
Nuts! I only want to see my brother.
I hate others insult my talent.
I haven't been back for ages,
how come I have date?
You still deny?
- What does this number represent?
- Old lover.
Nuts!
I'll call up my brother now
just to prove it to you.
I'm not stupid! I'm not thick!
It's me.
How come you know which room I stay?
Can we chat a while?
Go ahead.
I miss you,
I didn't expect to see you again.
It's true.
I want to have tea with you tomorrow.
I don't care if you're married
I want to court you again.
Don't tell me that is your brother.
Give it back to me!
Who is it? No more topics?
Hello, Chris.
Brother Cock, everyone knows
you're expert at courting girls.
Do you know Virginia is my wife?
I know.
But she's my old friend.
Ex-Lover or old friend?
I'll call you again tomorrow, bye.
Bitch!
Stand there!
You must obey since you're my wife!
Do I treat you good after we got married?
What are you doing?...
Listen, I don't want
another man look at you!
No way... I won't let them look at you!
I won't let another touch you!
You belong to me, got that?...
You bitch...
No! Not now, never can they!
Bitch...
She's going out.
- Sister
- Where's Cock?
He's been waiting for you
long time outside.
How is your husband now?
I sneaked out when he didn't notice.
He must be very angry now.
He beat you up?
I never know he's so jealous.
I don't want to be
related to him anymore.
Do you know he's the
biggest drug dealer in Europe?
He runs business, he runs restaurants.
I think he shouldn't be drug dealer.
He and me are the same type.
You needn't be so frank.
We'd better leave this place first.
He keeps taking me
everywhere these years
so he's making use of me.
No wonder he insists on packing for me.
I don't understand
why did you marry him?
I'll just marry
whichever man I run up to.
Why?
I can't wait.
If you hadn't dumped me
and gone for a fight.
We'd be together now.
I'll never forget
what happened that day.
Let's start again.
I don't know what he will do
he keeps all my stuff.
Let's talk with him.
I dare not face him anymore.
Brother Cock
You're come at the right time,
don't waste the airtime.
You're playing movie The Fugitive?
Chris, you've been acting
all these years.
I've never snatched a woman
with others on the street.
But for your sake... I can get more crazy.
Virginia
I apologize about last night
I don't want to be with you,
I want a divorce.
But that takes procedures.
Take back your document,
if you want to leave HK.
Chris
It's useless to keep someone next to me.
When Chris Chong took the document out.
- Do take care.
- I thought he pulled out a gun.
But he told sister.
He was a gentleman when he met sister.
So he must be gentleman when they part.
But Chris Chong
is a well-known drug dealer.
Interpol have been
checking for him for ages.
He has done all the deeds.
And when he wanted to leave HK.
He was arrested.
Brother Cock wants to
court sister a second time.
Sister finally agrees to marry him.
It's a happy ending.
But the story hasn't ended yet.
I've checked almanac
15 of August is the best day.
Many people will get married that day.
So we put forward by 3 months,
it's today.
We go all the way for registration.
When did you become superstitious?
Men on the walk are a bit superstitious.
Do you know why we didn't
get married last time?
I've checked at last.
As that day was unlucky day.
You always have a saying. It'd be OK
if you didn't go for the fight.
Don't worry.
I won't go fighting anymore.
It's all done.
This time at the wedding.
I must hold lots of banquets.
You have so many friends?
I don't care.
I'll offer banquets to people passing by.
And our banquet will be hectic.
I must make our wedding big.
I want the world to envy me
I want to tell them I have a pretty wife.
- A prefect pretty wife.
- You're bad.
Sure I am.
I've planned already.
Let's go honey moon in Macau.
Macau?
I was joking, I want somewhere better.
Olympic Games will be held in Australia.
I won't care about business.
I've made some money these years.
So I want us to live peacefully.
I'll spend all my time with you.
There's plenty of time, you needn't rush.
Why are you in such a hurry?
I'm going to get married, but not you.
Why you're in a hurry?
Wife, I must ask you to help me.
I want many children.
May be 10!
We must retire soon.
Then we can travel round the world.
The children can take care of themselves.
And then we'll be happy.
Wife, I've prepared for their names too.
The eldest son will be called Sai Tsang.
He'll be a love machine like his dad.
Then is Sai Kong, Sai Pang.
But never Saigon, it's bad.
Anyone with the name Chiu is great man!
Brother Cock finally checks out
the motor killer was sent by Chris Chong.
From then on, if anyone sees Cock
and still thinks he's not a good lover
that he is a horny triad member.
I can tell you, you misunderstand him.