Once upon a time Kwok Ching
and his wife Wong Yung
were given a sword by Yueng Guo.
They melted it together with gold
and made two swords.
The first was named To Lung,
and the second Yee Tin.
All their knowledge, even about
the techniques of Ngo Fai
and the most powerful kung fu scroll
were hidden in the sword
The owner would rule
the world of martial arts.
To obtain these swords
both good and evil
fought many battles.
Two groups were formed.
The first being led by the Shaolin.
Shaolin.
Wu-tong.
Ngo-mai.
Kun-lun.
Hung-tung.
Wah-shan.
Their opponent was a sect
from Persia.
The mysterious Ming sect
Called the Evil Cult by some.
This cult fought against the Yuen-dynasty
and the government, all the time
Their camp was stationed at the Bright Summit
The four leaders of the Cult
were extraordinary powerful
Being, Purple Dragon
White Eagle, Golden Lion
and Green Bat
The hatred was strong,
friendships amongst themselves were forbidden
Chang Tsui-san, the fifth pupil
of Chang San-fung, was righteous.
He didn't like these silly rules
and fell in love with Yan So-so,
daughter of White Eagle.
And started a friendship with Tse Shun,
Golden Lion.
Shing Kwun was the master
of Golden Lion
To get into the sect,
he killed Tse Chuns family
Tse Shun took the sword To Lung...
and killed many inoccents
out of revenge
Tsui-san en So-so didn't want to reveal
Tse Shuns hideout
and went to
The Island of Ice and Fire
to live in seclusion.
Tse Shun had the sword To Lung,
but not the secret of the sword.
Until the 100th birthday
of Chang San-Fung
Tsui-san took his wife and son
Mo-kei to his master
- Sugared Crab
- That's what I want
One please
- Enjoy it, Mo Kei
- Thank you
You weren't coming
- This is about Wu-Tong, it's possible.
- Who knows.
They'd do anything for To Lung
Dad, what do they want
with godfathers sword?
Never name your godfather again
I won't do it again
Whoever asks for your godfather
and whatever they do,
don't say a word, OK?
Yes, because we can't betray our friend
- That wouldn't be righteous.
- Good boy
- The master must like you a lot.
- Is he nice?
He's the best
- Chang Tsui-san...
- It hurts
The Jinx-scream destroys your brain
Use your inner force,
or you'll go mad.
Where are you? Show yourself!
The Jinx-hand?
Mo-kei.
The infamouse jinxes
Chang, if you want your son back
tell me where Golden Lion is.
Dream on
If we hit your son
with the Jinx-hand...
- ...you know what will happen.
- How dare you
The child is innocent.
Why would you hurt him?
Let him go, the Wu Tong and the
Ming sect will appreciate it
Are you threatening me with
Wu-Tong and the Ming sect?
Even with that old Chang
they won't stand a chance
Really?
- Master.
I, Chang San-Fung,
ask you to let the boy go.
Well, well, the famous Chang San-Fung
is a fatso, I'm stunned
OK, my fame is a bit exaggerated.
Who cares?
Fatso, is you fear the Jinx-hand
Let him tell me
where Tse Chun is.
OK
Tsui-san, tell him
Master, Tse Shun is my friend.
It wouldn't be the right thing.
Indeed, we can't have let that happen.
You wouldn't be able to face anyone anymore
Please grant us our honour
Old man, step aside if if you fear death,
or you will die on your 100th birthday
Sighing won't do you no good
I turn 100 today.
I don't want to get mad
But you are forcing me.
I will teach you.
Brother
Hit the boy once,
and I will hit him 100 times.
Man, your master is a hothead.
He always has been.
- OK, we will release them both
at the same time - No tricks.
One, two, three
Mo-kei.
Watch out
- The Jinx-hand
- Mo-Kei
Bring him to Shaolin. No, Wu-Tong.
I'll get an antidote
If we keep going like this, Mo-kei will die.
Stop.
How is he?
The Jinx-hand is powerful.
We'll have to wait for the antidote
- But Mo-Kei.
- Mom, it hurts so bad
Relax.
Here is some candy.
Take one if it hurts
It will make you forget the pain. OK?
Shaolin, Ngo-mai, Hung-Tung,
Wah-shan and Kun-lun...
want Chang to tell
where the Golden Lion is.
Today is my master's birthday
He didn't want a party
so we'll keep it small
Nice of you to come, we will
thank you later. Good bye.
We don't want to disturb master Chang
But he has to turn over Tsui-san to So-so
and tell where Golden Lion is.
Only after that we will leave.
Master No-mercy, do you think
you can ask for anything?
We want to take revenge on the Evil Cult.
We want Tse-Shun, no matter what
If you won't turn him over,
we will fight for it.
Your kung-fu seem fine.
Show me
Chang Tsui-san, come outside
or all the elders will be killed
Stop.
Master No-mercy, don't push it.
There you are with your wife.
Where is Tse Shun?
- I will not betray him
- Then you deserve it.
You are befriended with that killer
I will shake you awake
Slut
- You?
- Stupid nun.
- You
- Even with that sword you are nothing.
If your master weren't my best friend,
I would teach you a lesson
You are unworthy of Yee Tin.
I will save it for your master
He should send a better student
to get it
Chang San-fung, how dare you protect him?
If we attack
you are not capable to kill us all
If you are tired
you will be in trouble
Is that a threat?
Master, this is all my fault.
Let me take care of it
Well, arrange it than.
But if I have to, I will fight
Elderlings, you want to know
where my friend resides
And you want his sword, To Lung,
to rule all alone
But I will never betray him
On his age, my master doesn't have to
put his life in danger for me
I will answer you now
- Tsui-san...
- Daddy...
Why did you kill yourself?
Tsui-san...
Mama, why did he do it?
Mo-kei, remember all those faces
You have to remember each and every of them
They have been stained with his blood
Dad died because of them?
You have to revenge the death of your father
They will have to pay for it.
Miss Yan, the death of your husband
fills us with grief
But now you alone knows
where Tse-Shun is.
Come over here, master Hung Man,
I will tell u.
- But then you have to let us go.
- A monk is true to his word
I will tell you alone
Can you speak louder?
There you can find Golden Lion.
Go get the sword quickly
But where is it then? Miss
- She didn't say anything
- You want the sword for yourself.
Mama...
Mo-kei, mama tricked them.
Do you see the power of deceit
Always remember, never to trust a woman.
The prettier she is,
the better she can lie.
Mama...
- Master, we have to revenge them
- First save Mo-kei.
Mo-kei...
Master
- Your inner strength is great
- But you will not recover from your cold attacks.
If that cooking monk
hadn't jumped from here
he could have healed you
with his Solar stance
Solar stance?
Mysterious Shaolin kung-fu,
as powerfull as the Moon stance
But the parchment
has been lost for 300 years
A cooking monk in Shaolin
found it by accident in a Sutra
He learned the kung-fu
and got away with it
Then he dared me.
Chang, you are really good.
The Solar stance makes invincable
But you have to be a virgin
when you learn it
If I wouln't be invincable
why would I train so hard?
Chang San-fung, cya.
Completely nuts
If he were still alive
his kung-fu could have saved you
If you learn the kung-fu as a virgin
you are stronger
But nnow
I have a hard one every morning.
What?
- Why don't I have it?
- You are weak.
- Master
- What, Ching-su?
No-Mercy has send her student ChowChi-yu...
- ...to get Yee Tin
- Chow Chi-yu?
How are you doing, master Chang?
No-Mercy temper any better now?
She studies buddhism now,
and is improving
She is lucky with such a polite student
Mo-kei, give her Yee Tin.
Mo-kei, are you the son
of Chang Tsui-san?
I...
Yes, Mo-kei is the orphan of my uncle.
I am Sung Ching-su.
My father is the oldest
of the seven heroes of Wu-tong.
Thanks, brother Mo-kei
Chi-yu, stay a couple of days.
Let Yuen Kiu teach you our swordplay.
Thank you, master Chang.
Brother Mo-kei.
Are you watching?
Master Chang loves you so much,
you will probably his succesor.
Don't be afraid, Mo-kei is not allowed to
learn kung-fu. We look after him
Sister Chi-yu, you want to practice together?
He has been hit by the Jinx-hand
and will never learn kung-fu
Father
Ching-su, The master wants to practice
the Tai-chi sword for three months
We will accompany him
You must take care of Wu-tong,
in the meanwhile
- Thank you, father.
- You have to work hard.
Mo-kei cannot learn kung-fu,
so you are responsible
Master Chang has made 100 pills
for Mo-kei, each day one
- For his cold-attacks
- Ching-su will look after him.
What is your business over there?
Mo-kei, what was that?
- Someone was peeking on you.
- Really?
- They are cruel. I am afraid.
- They already left.
I'm still afraid.
Would you stay with me?
I knew you wouldn't.
I would like to.
I know you like me.
- Are you warm?
- No.
You are sweating all over.
How dare you, you think you are
a real womanizer, don't you
- Ching-su, are you okay?
- I am in charge now.
You're to blame for your parents death.
Now your flattering master Chang
So that he helps you overcome your cold-attacks
If I would get his energy
I would be kung-fu master now
- I curse your mother
- Shut up.
Is my uncle your father at all?
Or are you the son of a whore
- Brother Ching-su.
- Get him, I will chop his hand off.
Look, Wu-tong is no heroe after all.
- Friend, who are you?
- I am not your friend.
Get dressed.
Slut.
Come over here, if you dare
Wu-tongs kung-fu is nothing.
Ming is much stronger.
Chi-yu, attack her with Yee Tin.
- Biatch
- So, Yee-tin is here.
Run away for the Wu-tong dogs.
- Don't insult Wu-tong.
- You are insane.
We'll chat later
Biatch, feel the power of my sword.
Your sword is what I came for.
Can it break my chains?
Wu-tong, swordstance.
Go away.
Quickly, over here.
- Your kung-fu is really lousy.
- Later.
They will kill you if they get us
Moron, this is a dead end.
Mo-kei, you mingled with Ming
and desacrated our temple
As leader of Wu-tong I cast you out.
Warriors of Wu-tong!
Show no mercy.
- I'm sorry, miss.
- Siu Chiu.
Are you seducing him now?
Where did you intend to go with him?
Nice and soft
- Why did you let go?
- But I taught them...
- Didn't your father teach you something?
- He died years ago.
Your name is Chang Mo-kei.
Is your father Chang Tsui-san?
- Your servant Siu Chiu.
- Get up.
I insulted White Eagle.
He put me in chains
Then I ran away
to get the Yee Tin sword.
- And fortunately you saved my life
- Get up, I'm not your master.
You touched me again.
As grandson of White Eagle,
you are my master.
I haven't seen him since my birth.
What is that sound, a monster?
Let's go
- This way
- No, that way
That I would get a visit in my time.
You are?
I am the soul of hell
- Are you a student of Wu-tong?
- I am Chang Mo-kei.
It has been long since I ate human flesh
Chang San-fung had me suffer,
so I can eat his student
- Are you the cooking monk?
- Do you still remember me?
The girl behind you is very pretty.
I bet she tastes a lot better.
She doesn't belong to Wu-tong.
Eat me instead
And brave too.
Old man!
Heer...
- Master Chang, how are you?
- It is so cold.
What have you done to him?
He was already wounded.
Who messed you up?
The Jinx-hand, eight years ago.
That one is fatal.
All these years master chang
must have given his energy to you
He surely must love you very much.
Old man, can you cure him?
Only my Solar-stance can help him.
But why would I cure Chan's people?
Chang Mo-kei,
if you call master Chang a bastard...
...I will teach you the Solar-stance
Never
Do you have to hit him as well?
Call Chang three times
a shameless bastard...
...and you will never again
suffer from colds.
On top of that, you will be invincable.
Simple, isn't it?
Say after me:
Chang is a shameless bastard.
A shameless bastard...
...are you.
Fine. We shall see
how you survive the night
Master
- So cold!
- Really cold?
And now? Still cold?
Better this way?
Impossible!
Master Chang having such a brave student
I am still alive.
- Master, have you recovered?
- Siu Chiu...
- Master, do you carry a weapon?
- No.
- Something is poking me.
- Really?
- Upright?
- What is it?
Nothing.
Damn, I hope she isn't pregnant.
- So fast?
- What did you say?
That I woke up very fast.
Master, if you survived yesterday
you will make it through.
Keep on dreaming.
Yesterday you were lucky.
You will suffer from three attacks a day.
If nobody passes energy to you,
you will die.
You mean...
Chang Mo-kei,
if you don't learn my Solar-stance...
the rest of your life will be freezing.
Leave Wu-tong, become my student.
No, master Chang is good to me.
You are ill.
Why do you want him
to learn your kung-fu?
Ten years ago I was beaten
by Chang San-fung.
Im still pissed of because of that.
My student has to be better
than his students
Teach me instead.
If a woman learns the Solar-stance...
her breasts will vanish
and she will have hairy arms and legs
And a beard and a man's voice as well
- Would you like that?
- Never mind.
His back is broken.
He moves with that ball.
Promise him now
and withdraw that promise later on.
Wu-tong is just and sincere
Still he wants to learn me his kung-fu.
That is suspicious
But I refuse.
You can not force me.
You think I cannot?
Siu Chiu.
- Let me help you.
- I don't want to
The sun appears.
The blood flows backwards.
Don't put my arse against my head.
Air from the belly flows through the body
I'm about to break
Sea of blood, straight back, sun bathing.
Portal of life, Ken-Suk
Chang, you learned the first stage
of the Solar-stance
You know my kung-fu now!
And you will never get rid of it.
I will force you to learn second stage.
Unless you die, or betray on Wu-tong.
He was too stupid to have the biatch.
Kill Mo-kei.
I was too late, but I could kill her
but not save Mo-kei.
Kill me instead, as compensation for
uncle Chang
Alright, I will kill you
This way we will not get Mo-kei back.
It is of no use.
Ching-su did all he can.
Poor Mo-kei.
Maybe it is better he died.
Shaolin wants us to join
and besiege Bright Summit
For peace and justice
Yuen Kiu, take the elders,
Ching-su and Chi-yu along with you.
Yes, master
The ninth stage, The Sun in Heaven.
Chang, now you've learned all stages
of the Solar-stance
You now posses powerfull energy
and your injuries cured.
Nobody can beat you now.
Master, I suceeded.
Thank you, master.
So you wanted to learn it after all.
You have to suffer.
You didn't want to teach me nothing
but only wanted to beat my master
But I tricked you.
I have to revenge my parents.
Therefore I wanted to learn.
You sly fox.
Beautiful women are not to be trusted
nor are nice people
I will kill you.
I have got your kung-fu.
How would you do that?
Look out, he is very powerful
Old man, forgive me.
You have cured me.
- Thanks for your teachings
- You sly fox
When I have my revenge,
I will come and save you
We will see who drops dead first
You will never make it together.
It will not be a happy end.
I have made it through
Shaolin, Ngo-mai, Hung-tung,
Kwun-lun and Wah-shan...
you are stained with
the blood of my parents
I will make you pay.
You have such a hard look in your eyes
If you would like I, for eight years,
saved on all you hatred
and suffered from continuous insults
and being finally able to fight back,
you would have the same
Are you returning to Wu-tong?
Ching-su is the only son of my uncle.
I can not kill him
I am not going to Wu-tong.
With the help of my Solar-stance
I can go wherever I want.
I am going to my grandfather
- He can free you
- Thank you
We will be in danger together.
Do not call me Master
But I will be happy to serve you.
Will you allow me?
You are so kind to me
Now that you are so powerful,
all girls will fall for you
You will surely forget me soon.
As long as the sun shines
I will not let you go.
Master!
Sugared crab candies
Look, they sell sweets over there.
The last thing my mother bought me,
before the Jinx-hand hit me.
I got three to eat when I was in pain
- You ate the first after they died, right?
- This one I tried to keep.
Bring wine and food.
The six clans are launching a raid on Bright Summit.
I am sure they will destroy the evil Cult
If we are too late
we will miss the great moment
If we are in time,
we will be slaughtered as well
There are the four masters and
the banner of the Five Invincable Elements
You think a small potato like you
could be victorious over them? Stupid monkey
She is sure to be with the Evil Cult.
Get her.
We have to hide.
You can not do anything here.
- She belongs to the Ming sect?
- I don't know her
Let us discuss the attack on Bright Summit.
I will do all I can.
You know them?
Of course, it was them who
hit me with the Jinx-hand, eight years ago
Stay calm, against those kung-fu masters.
We have no chance
- Mr. Deer.
- Hello.
Master, we all depend on you
Please send my regards to His Highness.
See you
Who is hiding there?
Show yourself.
What are you doing there?
Kid, what are you looking at?
He seems to be familiar to us
Forget it, it is just a couple
that are enjoying themselves here.
Let's go
- I just wanted...
- Lucky you didn't do anything. Look.
He must be very influencial.
Even Mr. Deer and Mr. Crane are his companions
- He..., that is a woman.
- A woman? Like my mother?
- She is pretty, like your mother
- But so are you.
The Bright Summit is surrounded.
We have to go over there.
The evil sect is well prepared
The five elemental flags are all prepared.
Even Way Yat-siu, the green bat has come to help.
Even thought he is against
King of White Eagle
If the Queen of Purple Dragon
and the King of Golden Lion return...
it will become difficult for us
If King of Golden Lion is back, that is perfect.
We can get his To Lung sword.
- Are you also interested in my Yee Tin sword?
- Yes of course
I would not dare.
She can read my mind, but she does not
know I want to rape her.
OK. If you rape her,
I will take her students.
- What a hard job, pal
- My pleasure
What are you two talking about?
We decided to donate the treasure
of the Evil Cult to the poor
Queen of the Purple Dragon
is the holy lady of the Ming sect
She disappeared many years ago.
I believe she went to Persia
After a severe fight, King of Golden Lion
was blinded. He won't be difficult to handle.
But King of White Eagle and King of Green Bat
will not be so easy
- Uncle, I have an idea.
- Speak.
King of White Eagle has a grandson,
the son of Chang Tsui-san.
His name is Chang Mo-kei.
He died months ago.
King of White Eagle does not know this.
He is an old man.
He will be very happy
if he meets his grandson again
If this grandson attacks suddenly
he will have a great chance to kill him
Great idea.
We will kill and rob king of White Eagle
and King of Green Bat
We will sell all the women as hookers
We are from honourable martial arts schools.
We will not do something so low as that
I will not allow you
to use my passed nephew
We just want to help the poor.
I agree with master Yuen Chun.
You asked someone to act as Mo-kei?
Who is the most suitable person then?
The son of Mr. Sung is the best choice
I won't allow a student of Wu-tong
to do something as disgraceful as this
While you're planning devious tricks
watch out for you can be struck by lightning
A bat's dart, the green bat,
Wai Yat-siu.
Wai, let my wife go.
Your wife is so fat, it is no big deal
to suck her blood
Dammit.
Sister No-mercy, you have killed my wife.
If someone is bitten by Wai Yat-siu
one will lose his mind and obey him alone.
If I would not have killed her
we would have had an extra enemy.
You can not compete with her,
she is too strong
Wai does not know the power of Yee-Tin yet.
He used Mrs. Ho as a shield.
But I believe he is hurt
by the energy of my sword
Your Highness.
Are the six clans already near the mountain?
Your Highness, they have arrived
Raise the five elements
when they are halfway up...
- Half of them should die.
- Yes.
I have returned.
Your Highness.
Green Bat, I am happy you came to help.
This means you are loyal to your sect
Old man, I got some information for you.
And I fought with No-mercy too.
Her Yee-tin sword is really powerful
- Are you alright
- Of course I am alright
Set up the positions now.
And if someone who claims to be the grandson
of White Eagle, named Mo-kei, kill him.
What did you say?
My grandson?
They will send someone
to act as your grandson to assasinate you
If your Holy Fire Tablet is still there
I am not afraid of Yee-Tin
Bullshit, if master Yeung
wouldn't have been there with his magic stance
She would have killed everyone easily
- Ights, this damn hurts.
- Are you wounded?
Of course, but I can't lose my face
in front of them.
- I will cure your injuries
- Useless, you have to suck out the poison.
- No Problem
- Really?
- Yes, I am true to my word.
- Friend, here is the wound.
It is alright if you don't have to suck,
but you also don't have to kick me.
There's many of them
- They are not of the Ming Sect
- What kind of banners are those?
They are my clan's, they are now entering
the forbidden zone of the five elements.
Five elements?
Don't retreat, we are from decent schools.
We are no cowards
- If you want to be a coward, then die
- You are right
- After you
- Chi-yu, Give me Yee Tin.
Yes, master
Go!
Let's retreat.
After them
I am Siu Chiu,
the maid of King of White Eagle
And this is his grandson,
Chang Mo-kei.
- Are you Mo-kei?
- Yes I am.
King of White Eagle wants everyone who
calls himself Mo-kei to be killed.
Run!
Quickly, this way
I am Chang Mo-kei.
Kill him.
You are fighting the wrong one
Great Solar Stance
Well done.
Hero, to which school do you belong?
Master, that is Chang Mo-kei.
The son of Chang Tsui-san?
How did he become so powerful
Where are you taking me?
This is the forbidden zone
of the Ming Sect.
Are we going inside?
Only a master will survive that.
If he would die outside
the ones who carry his corpse...
Should commit suicide in there.
What about you?
The king does not allow his maid
to join his sect
Freeze!
Time to go.
Don't you move a step more
you will suffer a terrible death
If w stay here, we will come to
a terrible end, you fool
Commander, what do we have to do?
This is the grave of the masters
It is riddled with traps
if they go in, they will surely be killed
Let's go back and help the others
What is the matter?
- I am afraid
- You don't have to be.
Look, these are only skulls
I think they belong tho the ones
who carried the corpse
Let's leave this place
We are surrounded by Flag-soldiers
I don't want to hurt my grandfathers men
with my kung-fu
I don't have a choice but to continue
I know there is a way to Bright Summit
You are only a maid of White Eagle.
How come you know all these things?
I heard it, thus I know.
My grandfather locked you with
such a strong and heavy chain
He probably had his reasons to do so
- Who are you, are you deceiving me?
- Don't you trust me?
I want to know the truth
I made an oath not to tell anything
I did not want to hurt your grandfater
And I will not hurt you either
Let me keep my secret.
I promise I will tell you,
when the time is ready
Alright, we'll discuss later
There are tracks on the floor
Yeung, you are the master
of the Evil Cult. So what?
You took my beloved.
So what?
I never thought you would die in here
I, Shing Kwun, now use the Six schools
to destroy your Evil Cult
And now I also want your Magic stance
Then I will be invincable.
And I will become
the head of the Yuen-dynastie.
Even without the sword To Lung...
I will be the supreme master of martial arts
The master of the Ming sect disappeared
20 years ago, he died right here.
This must be Shin Kwun.
The enemy of my god-father
He became the dog of the Yuen government
He got the six schools
to attack the Ming Sect
and dragged my god-fathers family to death
Who is there?
Chang Mo-kei.
You did not die?
Why do you hate the Ming sect
and my father?
Why did you kill them?
Yeung Ting-lin stole away my loved one
I have done it for years
with his wife
At last he discovered it
That is why he became mad.
He wanted to kill me
My love wanted to save me
and comitted suicide
For 20 years I've hidden in Shaolin
Just waiting for my chance
to destroy the Ming sect
You seduced his wife and ruined his Evil sect?
Is that fair?
What a shame.
No matter if it is right or wrong
Don't dare to criticize me
Chang Mo-kei, I will send you
to your parents
You will die.
What kind of kung-fu is that?
Great Solar stance
I never imagined you could beat me
In fact,
Chang Tsui-san had a secret.
What is it?
Get away, I will try to break it with my
Great Solar Stance
Master, don't use your Solar Stance
I am afraid everything will collapse
Do we have to die here then?
No, we have to find another exit.
Here are some inscriptions
Those who come here
should bow for the skeleton
If not, the soul will trouble you
If we are going to die, we will be souls too
We don't need to be afraid
Maybe it will be of any help
We should respect the dead
and bow to them
Master Yeung.
Sorry to disturb your rest
Help us escape and we will
revenge you and kill Sing Kwun
What does it say?
- Persian
- Can you read it?
Of course
Those who bow to me,
will get my Magic Stance
Those who mastered it,
can push the stone away
Then you will reach the Bright Summit
The Magic Stance is inscribed on the rock
He was very wise
He knew Shing Kwun would never bow to him
so he designed such a trap
Try it, so we can leave this place
It is not right to steal the secret kung-fu
of the Ming sect
Here it sais
you have to pass a message from Yeung
He wants King of Golden Lion
to be his successor
He must also guard the Magic Scroll
and acquire the Holy Fire Tablet
Your god-father is his successor
So you are to learn their kung-fu
But how long does it take?
It sais for ordinary people
it takes 30 years or more.
Great kung-fu masters
can manage it in six hours
I already know the Solar Stance.
I can do it in six hours
Go ahead then.
King of Green Bat, are you hurt?
Don't waste it.
Where are all the women
Over there
Do you want me to drink your blood?
- We are the red cross
- We come to save people
He is bleeding
Let's get him
You are saving people?
- Only nymphomaniacs
- and those who reincarnated wrongly
How?
We kill them to let them
reincarnate again
If I wasn't wounded
I would have killed you myself
Old bluffer,
I have stopped the bleeding for you
King of White Eagle,
you are really unbeatable
- We will pursue no further
- But dad, he is injured.
Why don't you kill him
He fought against five, and won
If he manages to do that,
how can we call ourselves heroes
Stop
What's the matter?
You don't attack?
- We, Wha Shan school will attack now
- Deliver all your rings and jewelry here.
- Women undress now
- If not you will be killed
It is really unbelievable
to be bullied by such jerks
Old bluffer, let's fight together
For our beloved sect
This is the end.
Go with your sister, Chi-yu
Kill all the people of the Evil Cult
and extinguish their holy fire
Yes, master
King of White Eagle.
You are a great kung fu master
Your Eagle Claw Stance is famous.
Like the Dragon Claw of Shaolin
You'd better commit suicide.
Old bluffer, don't be so impulsive
Listen
I, Chang Mo-kei ask you to
stop your fighting for a moment
You are not dead?
Is he the son of So-So?
Your grandson?
Thank you for your attention
The battle between Ming
and the six schools
is a trap set by Shing Kwun, master of Tse Hun
Please keep calm, and do not fall for it.
Bullshit, evil cult is so cruel
Wai Yat-siu is a bloodthirsty maniac
Tse Hun killed many people as well.
They deserve to die
Yes, I need blood for practicing
Chickenblood, pigblood and my own only
It was you who killed Ho of the Kwun-lun school.
I did not bite her.
About manslaughter, old nun,
you killed more than I did
How dare you?
Shing Kwun serves Yuen.
He wants us to kill ourselves
Believe me, master
And where is Shing Kwun now?
For 20 years he has been hiding
with the Shaolin
He wears a mask.
How dare you frame my uncle Yeun Chun
Where is Yeun Chun now?
He sneaked into the graveyard
to steal the Magic Scroll
He killed master Yeung.
Siu Chiu, make yourself clear.
Grandfather,
I will no let anyone hurt you
You have insulted Shaolin.
Your mouth is too big
Try my Dragon Stance
Mater, would you let us go,
if I can beat you?
Deal.
Go ahead
The Dragon Claw stance is more powerful
than our own kung-fu
This guy is really very powerful
If I make 6000 points
he has at least 10.000
Dragon Claw stance
OK, I will stop fighting now
I just come to stop your fighting
not to create any more trouble
By the way, I used Shaolin kung-fu.
It is not an insult at all
Please forgive me.
Alright, let's go
Chang Mo-kei, I challenge you.
They have pushed my father to his death.
Now they come to slaughter people
for no reason at all.
I have to revenge my father.
No, if I fight now, I will fall into
the trap of Shing Kwun
I have te keep my calm, be wise in my fight
against the government
Watch out for her sword
Right, don't fight her.
Master, please go ahead
Magic Stance
Damn you, ugly nun
- Siu Chiu
- Yes
Thank you master
Brother Mo-kei, I had to betray you.
Please forgive me
I never minded that
Please, bring this sword to your master
Anybody else want to challenge me?
Chi-yu.
Brother
Don't die
Mo-kei.
Let's attack them together.
We can beat them
This girl is so pretty
Rape her.
Who dares to take advantage of her
is the enemy of Wu-tong.
- A little misunderstanding...
- We will call for some whores
- We will not rape her
- Let's go, you bastard
Master, don't die.
Don't leave me
I have got the Solar Stance.
I will not die
But this week,
I cannot use kung-fu again
Please rest, Mo-kei.
Pay a visit to master Chang, when possible
By helping you, we betrayed
the other five schools
We should leave soon
Or they will think
we support the Evil Cult
So what, who knows, he might
save Wu-tong one day
- Watch out, you.
- Ching-su.
Uncle, bring the sword Yee-Tin
to master Chang.
Be sure Sister No-Mercy don't get it
- Alright
- Master
- Let's go
- Be careful
Master
Yau Tin-tsing, Wai Yat-siu and the five
elements greet master Chang.
I am not your master
The one using the Magic stance
is our master
The sects were divided all these years
in two groups.
The Golden Lion and the Purple Dragon
They were competing for leadership
You have saved us
Who could be a better master than you?
Master Yeung wanted my godfather
to be his successor
You or your godfather.
It does not matter
Your highness
The Wah-shan School is returning.
They want to launch an attack.
Goddamn, the bastard
I am Chu Yuen-chang.
The time is running out.
We are waiting for your orders
There are many casualties. Hide yourself
on the graveyard. What are you thinking?
If you want to be our master,
we will do anything you say
Listen, followers.
Hide yourself on the graveyard
When we have recovered,
we'll have our revenge
Bravo, holy master
Wonderful, nicely done
It is a really a blessing
to have you as our master
I just have the the position
of my grandfather temporarily
Can I speak freely?
Although you did not want
to be our master at first...
...I saw in your eyes
you wanted to become our master
We have so many followers
and we battle against the government
We have great strength
and you want to have your revenge
When you become master, your chances
of getting revenge will become much larger
Then you can overthrow the Yuen-dynasty
and become Emperor yourself
- The chance is big
- Bullshit
King of White Eagle is old and
King of Green Bat is unpredictable
You have no much use of them.
Whatever happens...
...You can count on me.
I support you
I see the ambition in your eyes
As my right-hand you will have
your succes much faster
You are very wise.
I would surely like to be master
But wise people are usually disgusting
- I understand
- Be gone
Let's leave this place
Wah-shan is a good school,
but you are scum
Let us live...
I know a secret.
Tell!
We overheard lately
that students of Wu-tong
have been attacked by Shaolin.
They all got caught
They have been kidnapped
but not raped.
Master, we have discovered that mr Yang is hurt.
He lays ahead
- Uncle Yan
- Master
- Mo-kei.
- How are you?
On the way to Wu-tong
we saw Shaolin-monks
They poisoned us with the vapour
That is the strongest weapon in battle
Whoever smells or eats it,
loses his kung-fu and strength
There is an antidote that can save him
I held my breath
so that I could escape
My brothers have all been captured
and taken away
Then I ran into two monks,
which were so very powerful...
...that I was beaten.
They broke all my joints
What a cruelty
Let us free our uncles in Shaolin
Sold out, ask further on
I will do so.
All the doctors are occupied and all
the herbs are bought by one man.
Weird
Maybe those monks
No, they live closeby
in the mansion with the green willow
They know we need those herbs
to save Yan
This must be a trap
The green willow?
Welcome.
The master is expecting you already
- May I know his name?
- You will learn it soon
Did you want to trap us?
Speak up, or I will suck your blood
The blood of my men
does not taste well
If you want,
I have some fresh blood for you
Why won't you say who you are?
I am Chao Min,
an unknown to the world of martial arts
I have no importance
- If you are afraid, leave this place
- Watch it.
This is the woman from the restaurant
Grandfather.
She is a Jinx-master
This will be a heavy fight
What a bunch of losers
I never thought
you to be so strong
that you would beat the six schools
and rule the Ming sect
What a young hero
Why did you buy all the herbs
and rented all the doctors?
I heard master Yan was wounded
by the shaolin
The poor doctors are often very bad,
so I arrested all the poor doctors
But I have prepared
some 'Black Jade Past' for him
Master
We are no friend of yours.
Why do you help us?
The Yuen-government wants heroes
to be friends with it
You are the greatest kung-fu master in the world
This gift is nothing
Black Jade Paste is a very valuable
and potent medicine
Why would she give it away like that
You are manchurian
Emperor Yu Yang is my father.
It is foolish of Shaolin to challenge you
We will help you eradicate them
Master, is that the Yee Tin sword?
Yes, it is
We will solve it ourselves
We don't want no mingling of the Government,
thank you very much.
Do stay, I have prepared a meal for you
I will get changed first
may I be excused
We are leaving
Do you know we're having Black Jade paste
Damn... How cocky can one get
Is it true, or isn't it?
It smells nice.
A trap, get out of here
What is wrong?
We are so tired,
we have no strength anymore
The poison
All my brothers are poisoned by this
But I held my breath
What do we have to do?
I will get the antidote.
Look after them
You are keeping your word
and have a drink with me?
Why did you set a trap for us?
Nobody asked you
to get the wooden sword
One of you was greedy
That's why they got poisoned
- Give me the antidote
- Are you begging me?
- Or are you forcing me?
- Where are those jinxes
- Call them out
- Are you afraid of them?
I will not tell you where they are.
So you will be scared.
Don't think I will not beat you
just because you are a woman
I know, so I decided...
...to attack first
Yuen is so powerful and mighty...
...and has a very large territory.
You are just a man alone
How do you intend to overthrow our government?
The Yuen people hate the totalitarian regime
I support these people
We have armies of volunteers
It is the will of the people
Can you beat the will of the people?
Master Chang, why not play a duet with me?
- Enough playing
- I love it
Master Chang,
do you want to see my legs?
Just tell me.
Why do you take my shoes?
You are so cunning,
how dare you call yourself hero?
I'm no hero.
I am a cunning woman
- I tell you a secret. Women are cunning and devious
- I will not argue on that one
If you don't give me the antidote,
I will burn the house to ashes
I won't give a damn
But your companions are seriously poisoned
If they don't get the antidote
within 4 hours...
...they will never regain their kung-fu.
Time is running out
Jinx-palm.
- That was not the jinx palm
- I know, I don't know it
I just wanted to scare you
If I wouldn't have taken back half the energy
I would have killed you just like that
You don't want to kill me.
You fancy me
Bullshit
Do you love your maid more?
- Or me?
- I will kill you
Go ahead
Answer. If you don't,
I will not give you the antidote
You love the maid more than me
But I have sent sister No-mercy after her
Devious bitch
If you leave just like that...
...your companions will never
re-gain their kung-fu.
I don't have a choice
- Are you going to give it or not?
- No
For the last time!
Never, whatever happens
Are you not afraid?
Once I will be yours
resistance is futile
There is nobody anymore.
You can do with me as you please.
Shameless
Mo-kei, I could give you the antidote
and the 'Black Jade Paste' as well.
But!
You have to promise me three things.
Master, where are those Ming people?
They have disappeared
Master, look
There is sister No-mercy again...
Siu Chiu, leave here
The master wants me to stay
So I have to stay.
You bastards,
what evil deeds are you planning?
Master, they seem to be poisoned
No step forward,
or I will suck your blood
What is there to look at?
I drank too much blood, I spit it out.
I once let you go.
This is my chance to destroy
all evil in martial arts
Master, it is not heroic to take
such an advantage
Fuck off, biatch
If you can withstand three attacks of me,
you can kill me
- How dare you?
- You can also have three goes
If I lose,
then you can do whatever you want
What a sharp tongue
If you survive three of my stances,
I will let you go
Come on
- Siu Chiu... Are you okay?
- Everything alright?
I can stand it
Two to go.
She is seriously hurt
Let me finish her.
I should not take my words back
I wouldn't dare
Siu Chiu, leave us here.
Don't do it
One more time
If you want to die
you have the right person
Master, are you alright?
- Siu Chiu.
- Master.
Go!
Green Bat, give them the antidote
Mo-kei, why did Chao Min give it to you?
Beware of traps
I have had her eat three of them.
They are ok
Siu Chiu.
Master.
What a couple
- How dare you come over here?
- Why not?
Your master promised me three things.
That's why he got the antidote
If they won't go against my conscience
and not against heroism
I will not let you marry such a pretty girl,
Siu Chiu
That does not go against your conscience,
does it?
Master Chang, not so easy
When I think of something else,
I will know where to find you
I have never seen
such a devious woman
This woman must be a great foe
of the Ming sect
There must be something behind
the Shaolin attack on Wu-tong
We are going to the Shaolin temple
to get the truth
Are you alright, master?
Master No-mercy, the emperor
Yu-yang would like you to be his guest.
After you
Why is it so quiet here?
This is Chang Mo-kei,
together with King of White Eagle
and King of Green Bat
to visit your master.
Our master does not want to see anybody
We have come from far.
It is urgent.
Tell that to your master
He does not want to see you,
please go away.
Wait, your movements are different
from the Shaolin kung fu
And your head has just been shaved
You are no real monk
Like I said, he is fake
- Let's get him
- Right
Look, master
'First kill Shaolin, then Wu-tong'
'We, the Ming sect are the most powerful'
It is a trap.
Have all the kung-fu masters
of Shaolin been killed?
Maybe poisoned with the 'Odour'
They will surely have been taken away
- Goddamn.
- What is it?
'Kill Shaolin and Wu-tong'
They are probably going to Wu-tong now.
Let's hurry there
You wanted to leave just like that?
Master, you better leave first.
What is the matter?
Hung Shang of the Shaolin
wants to speak to master Chang
Master, a great disaster
has come over Shaolin
The Evil Cult has struck.
Everyone except me has died.
For real?
The evil ones have captured
all the masters who raided Bright Summit
If you don't do anything, the Evil Cult
will control the world of martial arts
Rise
Take care, master
This monk is fake, he is from the Evil Sect
Where is your father and uncles?
Mo-kei is not dead.
He joined the Evil Cult
He learned a lot of evil magic.
My father and four uncles were not prepared
They were assassinated by him
All five of them
Ching-su, what has happened?
Master...
How dare you try to kill me?
Even a scapegoat could not fool you
Master you should be a man of the world
You are good in kung-fu.
You shouldn't be a Taoist monk over here.
Why not follow me,
and work for the government?
We will become rich together
Chang San-fung, you still remember us?
So all the problems all these years
- were the work of the government
- Yes, you are right
His majesty wants you to be his
head of the government
If you are willing to work for us,
your school will be prosperous.
And your students
will become generals in the army
to settle the riots for the government
I, Chang San-fung,
will do what seems right to me
I will not betray on the clans.
If you are not going to work for us,
you will go straight to hell
No panic, I am scratching my back.
Chang, how much blood have you got?
Protect the master
Stop, I will deal with this myself
Magic Stance
- Master
- Everything alright?
- Mo-kei.
- How are you?
Ching-su, that bastard,
tried to assassinate me
How did you get so powerful?
You asked me to keep my virginity
and I kept my word
Every morning it points straight up.
No woman wants me.
Therefore I am still a virgin
You have plenty of opportunities.
Better use them
Cut the crap
Your Highness
How can you be that impolite
to master Chang?
How are you, master Chang?
I am Chao Min.
Your Highness
Master Chang, don't be so stubborn
Do you want your students to be killed?
Men should die once.
But we should go meaningfully
Master, don't panic, I am with you
Master Chang, do you remember,
you promised me three things
Are you going to keep that promise?
If they don't go against my conscience
and heroism, I will do it
First: You can not use Solar Stance again
Do you want him to be chained up?
What a sharp mouth.
I will silence it soon enough
Second: No more Magic Stance
Alright, I promise
Which kung-fu are you going to use then?
Teach me any.
Why not the kung-fu of Wu-tong?
- Is it any good?
- Of course
Master, Let's do it
Tai-chi grows from nothing.
Master, I cannot make it, quickly
Come on, children,
I will teach you Tai-chi
The origin of the motion.
The origin of everything.
Positive and negative are bound together.
Can not be separated
Two elements that support each other
Stay calm
Think about your respiration
Concentrate your mind, focus your attention
Turn soft to hard.
Use both soft and hard.
In Tai-chi there is both soft and hard.
Use them both
Generate as much force as you need.
Mo-kei, you already got Solar Stance
You can learn any other kung-fu very fast
Tai-chi is about intention,
not the stance
Forget all your stances
Only then you can be victorious
- Do you still remember?
- I forgot
- What is their name?
- Don't remember
- What is your father's name?
Good... But one thing.
Show no mercy
Congratulations, you have a very good student
And you a very good grandson.
I will let you go now, the last promise
Chang Mo-kei, I will not let you
repay me that easily
I have got the life
of the six schools in my hands
If I don't go back,
they will be killed in three days
What do you want?
You are lucky today, come with me
Not that easy
Ok, then not.
I will stay another ten days
- You'd better prepare for the funerals of your friends
- You can go
But Ching-su stays here.
Don't leave me here, your Highness
Such a heartless dog.
It is useless for me to keep
You can have him
Master, I deserve to die.
I am useless
Master, please let me go
How can you face your father like that
Mo-kei, we've grown up together.
Please beg master to let me go
Uncle Sung has only one son
If I kill you,
he will not have any descendent
Alright
Master,
I have finished all his kung-fu
- Let him live
- Alright
Thank you, master
Chang Mo-kei,
you still owe me one more thing
If you want to save the six schools,
come and visit me in the Capital.