[Onlookers shouting]
Ohh.
You see what happened there?
I'm pretty sure you hit me.
No. I give you left, left.
You think I'll give another
left, and I gave you a right.
I'm just telling you...
that's what boxing's
all about, OK?
You show your opponent
one thing,
and you do
something else.
That's how Ali took
the title from Foreman.
He beat him with a rope-a-dope.
Don't you remember?
I don't remember what day
of the week it is.
That's right. Everyone thought
Ali's arms had run out,
that he's on empty, but he's
just setting Foreman up.
He's letting him
burn himself out.
And then in the eighth round,
he comes.
Poor George
has got nothing left.
I always liked
Bruce Lee movies.
Now you're learning.
Don't look at my hands.
Look at my shoulder.
That's where the punch
is coming from.
See?
You're still
looking at my hands.
Now come on,
let's try it again.
Come on, focus!
Come on! Shoulders, shoulders!
- Here.
- Nah. You keep it.
- Come on, you won.
- Yeah, but I always win.
I mean, I feel
so guilty about it.
Shut up and take it.
You know why you didn't
beat me today, Hale?
HALE: You've been boxing
for 20 years...
and you're better at it
than I am?
No. You don't have
the will to win.
Well, your insight
is shattering.
You had me today.
You could have shut me down,
but you blinked.
Yeah, well, we were
only sparring, buddy.
Thinking like that
is exactly why you lost.
- Now take this.
- It's yours.
No, no, no, take it.
If you didn't give it
everything you've got,
then I don't want it.
Go ahead.
You don't understand.
It really is yours.
I took it out of your wallet
while you were in the shower.
- General.
Major, were you recently
promoted past me?
No, sir.
Then why are you smoking
in my briefing room?
Sorry about that, sir.
That will never happen again.
Sit.
You take off in the Stealth
at 0-dark-30.
Fly a simulated,
low-level border penetration.
Nap of the earth
all the way.
- Scare cows, wake the farmers.
- Not tonight, buddy.
We're flying the B3
with two live nukes.
GENERAL: Palmdale's
concerned about...
low-level gamma
and x-ray diffusion...
screwing up the peripherals.
They want to send up a couple,
see if anything glows.
- 61s?
- Big ones. 83s.
Whoo! Crowd pleasers.
DEAKINS: How's your head?
HALE: All right. I'll be fine.
DEAKINS: I'm sorry about that.
HALE: Don't worry.
I'll get you back.
Ah, now you're dreaming.
After you, major.
HALE: These exercises
are fantastic.
When we go to war
against Utah,
we are really going
to kick ass.
Ground control,
ready for rollout.
Park ranger.
I'd like to speak to you
about this campfire.
WOMAN: Should I go?
MAN: No, Wanda. You stay put.
MAN: Yeah, I know.
No wood fires in the park.
Wanda has a cold,
and I'm trying to keep her warm.
Sir, have you seen
any other hikers...
or campers
in this area?
Not this time of year.
What's the fine for this?
RANGER: Pretty steep.
Secured.
MAN: Jesus Christ.
Drag him out of there.
Be smelling that all night.
HALE: Climb heading 287,
flight level 200.
DEAKINS: That's 287, 200.
HALE: I don't think
that Aurora Project...
is going to happen for me.
Spoke to your buddy Taylor.
He doesn't feel like I have
enough fighter time to qualify.
And what did you
say to him?
Thank you very much,
sir. Good-bye.
DEAKINS: You'll never change,
will you?
And that, my friend,
will be your downfall.
- Know what your problem is?
- Yeah. I'm always right.
- You think you're always right.
- That's deep.
You should have made
colonel by now,
but you're too busy pushing
at everybody all the time.
DEAKINS: That's an awesome
responsibility, isn't it?
DEAKINS: McMurren control,
this is Go-Seven.
Colonel, you boys
in Utah still awake?
Copy, Major Deakins.
We're ready and waiting.
Be advised,
we're going to catch...
your sorry little butts
this morning and bite down hard.
You may pass that
along to Captain Hale...
with my compliments.
DEAKINS: Wilkins
is giving us attitude.
You want to take
a turn tonight?
HALE: I'll fly in one ear
and out the other.
He won't even know
we were there.
DEAKINS: Hale says that
if anyone can catch us, you can.
And everyone get a fix.
They're about to
turn out the lights.
- Ready, captain?
- On your command, major.
Go to war.
HALE: Initiating stealth mode.
DEAKINS: River valley approach.
Here we go.
MAN: Colonel, they've gone
to stealth mode.
WILKINS: We lost them on radar.
Anybody still holding?
MAN: Got capture
on their heat signature, sir.
- Good.
- They may be running cold,
but the air above
ten-five is colder.
Good man, Frenchy.
I like that.
DEAKINS: Descend
to 400 feet AGL,
altimeter setting 3001.
HALE: Air speed
.7 Mach 3001, 400 feet.
Nap of the earth.
Here we go.
MAN ON RADIO: Terry, you been
through the Needles entrance?
TERRY: No, why?
MAN: Mrs. Parker just called.
Oh, God. What is it this time?
Another UFO?
Or did Elvis drop by for dinner?
MAN: She didn't mention him
but said a bunch of trucks...
went through the Needles
entrance an hour ago,
and she thought
they looked suspicious.
Clyde, what exactly does
a suspicious truck look like?
CLYDE: I don't know,
and I have no idea.
Me neither.
CLYDE: The thing is, she said
one of the trucks was ours.
You're the only one out tonight,
so if it wasn't you...
She was probably
just hallucinating.
Don't worry.
I'll check it out.
MAN: Lost them.
WILKINS: Damn.
Come on, keep hunting.
Keep hunting.
DEAKINS: We're below their eyes.
Proceed to primary target.
HALE: Descending to 200 feet.
DEAKINS: Ridge coming up
in 6 seconds.
HALE: I got it.
Whoo! Very nicely done.
- Excellent.
- Switching to autopilot.
Almost
as good as me.
I left a few trees behind.
I'll try to do better next time.
You really love
this shit, don't you?
Where else can you fly
a $2 billion plane...
800 miles an hour
100 feet off the ground?
That is a fact.
You're in for life, huh?
As long as they'll have me.
Aren't you?
Nah, nah.
I don't think so.
I mean, come on.
You said it yourself,
I should be colonel by now.
Instead, idiots like Boone
become general.
Boone is not
such a bad guy.
If he had a thought
go through his head,
it would be the quickest trip
in North America.
Oh, nah.
Flying doesn't mean
what it used to mean to me.
Not the flying.
Carrying the nukes. I know you.
You love having the power of God
at your fingertips.
You get off on it.
Look out your window.
There's something wrong...
with the terrain
following here.
Shouldn't that starboard ridge
be on our port side?
Aah!
[Alarm beeping]
Here she comes.
No!
HALE: What the hell
are you doing?
Clyde, I'm looking
at half a valley,
and there's nothing going...
Holy shit!
MAN: I got them!
[Cheering]
DEAKINS: McMurren!
This is Deakins! Hale's lost it!
I'm punching out!
Oh, shit!
Get me search and rescue.
We got pilots down.
MAN: Plane crashed
18 minutes ago.
The White House chief of staff
is on his way up.
Good morning, gentlemen.
So, do I wake the President?
- Bill.
- Jack.
Well, what have we got?
We're going out with this.
Rick's team prepared it.
"The United States Air Force
regrets to announce...
"that early this morning
a C141 heavy-lift cargo plane...
"went down
over the Utah desert.
"The status of the crew
has yet to be determined...
Yadda yadda yadda."
That's very nice bullshit, Rick.
- Thank you, sir.
- We'll go with that.
Wait.
We're making a mistake.
Giles...
You have some input
you wish to share with us?
Yes, sir.
[Clears throat]
"Aviation Week"
has been following...
the development
of the B3 for years.
They have guys camping out
in lawn chairs all night...
out by the Whiteman
perimeter fence,
watching just in case
one of these things take off.
They're going to know
that one took off last night,
and they're going to know...
that it didn't come back.
We put out a press release...
saying a C141 went down in Utah,
they'll put 2 and 2 together.
"Aviation Week"
is going to run a story.
Everyone's going to know
what really happened,
and we're all going
to look extremely stupid.
[Murmuring]
We're better off
just telling the truth.
The truth?
How'd you get this job?
[Laughter]
- Rewrite it... like Giles said.
- Yes, sir.
I want you to go to Utah.
I'll have my C21 standing by.
That was good work in there.
"Guys in lawn chairs..."
I don't know, Giles.
Sometimes you scare me.
Hell, sir...
sometimes I scare myself.
MAN: Move! Move! Move!
Come on!
Wallace, over there!
Reed, check over there!
Kelly, check over there!
[Beeping]
- See anything?
- Not a goddamn thing!
Colonel, this is Rhodes.
Go, Max.
Aircraft disintegrated.
Negative survivors on site.
Checking payload. Over.
You watch your needles
there, chief.
Over here!
[Whistles]
Take that end.
KELLY: The nukes are gone.
RHODES: Colonel!
We got ourselves
a Broken Arrow.
You find those nukes, chief.
If your Geigers
pick up more rads...
than you get off a toaster,
I want you out of there.
Broken what?
Broken Arrow. It's a class IV
strategic theater emergency.
It's what we call it
when we lose a nuclear weapon.
I don't know what's scarier,
losing nuclear weapons...
or that it happens so often,
there's a term for it.
They've found the wreckage
90 miles outside of McMurren.
No bombs on board.
This is a real nightmare.
We don't know where
the damn things are.
Cappy, put 2 more teams
in the air.
I want Chief Rhodes backed up
to the fullest extent.
Why didn't they go off?
They have to be armed
to detonate.
They're designed
to survive crashes intact.
They could lie
in burning jet fuel...
for 5 hours... no problem.
So, what the hell happened?
In his last transmission,
Major Deakins said
that Captain Hale lost control.
It's possible one of them
may have hit weapons release...
during the confusion.
[Groans]
Deakins.
You won that round.
Sir! Please turn around!
- Who the hell are you?
- Park ranger.
Just put it down,
and I won't have to kill you.
This isn't a standoff.
I've got the gun.
I never keep it loaded.
Thought you said
it wasn't loaded.
[Gunshot]
I lied.
Now, who the hell are you?
I'm a captain
in the United States Air Force.
Captain, you're under arrest
until we get this sorted out.
Lady, you're missing
the bigger picture here.
Uh!
Hold still.
All right?
I have already had
a hell of a morning, lady.
I can't tell you
what's going on,
but I need your help, OK?
This is a good way
to convince me.
We both know the gun is loaded.
If I wanted to, I could blow
your head off, right?
Yeah.
But I'm not going to.
Come on.
I got a radio in my truck.
It's this way.
RHODES: Got them!
[Beeping]
We got one.
[Vehicle approaching]
How you doing?
Hey. You guys need
any help?
It's an Air Force
training exercise, sir.
I'll have to
ask you to leave.
Hey, no problem.
We just, uh...
Oh, jeez.
Any sign of Deakins?
Maybe the son of a bitch
is dead.
DEAKINS: What
a terrible thing to say.
DEAKINS: Get them.
You assured me
everything would go smoothly.
Everything is going smoothly,
I assure you.
Our merchandise is not
where it's supposed to be.
It's right down there,
Mr. Pritchett.
Everything's on schedule.
[Beeping]
Sir, we got one intact.
Let's go find the other one.
Move! Let's go!
Care for a Coke
or something?
MAN: 2 gunships left McMurren
and are headed this way.
- Wonderful!
- Don't worry about them.
I worry. What about
the other pilot?
- We saw him eject.
- Huh.
Captain Hale. I seriously doubt
that he's alive.
I punched him out when we were
scraping the valley floor.
MAN: There's a report
that a park ranger called in.
- She saw a pilot come down.
- Really?
Find her.
I got it!
[Beeping]
Hello? McMmurren, come in.
Go, Max.
RHODES ON RADIO:
McMurren, come in. Over.
Max, are you there?
McMurren?
Max.
[Static]
McMurren, come in.
[Gunfire]
Move!
Going to open the access panels.
Going to drop in
a couple grenades.
It won't go nuclear,
but it will destroy the bomb...
And whoever's
trying to steal it.
I can't let you do that, chief.
And why not?
All clear!
- Where is your truck?
- Just around the bend.
- How did you find me?
- Saw your chute.
Don't step on that!
There. On that black stuff.
It's cryptogammic soil.
Very fragile.
One footprint takes
centuries to repair.
Come on. Jump. Yeah.
Thought it was a mine
or something.
Endangered dirt.
That's a new one.
[Buzzing]
Colonel Wilkins,
this is Airman Kelly, sir!
- Go.
- Chief Rhodes is dead!
They're all dead!
What the hell happened?
What the hell happened?!
[Buzz]
It's the nuke!
It's open! It's wide open!
Kelly, come in!
What happened?
Oh, God! What am I going to do?
Whoo!
Recall search and rescue.
Get me Washington.
I want N.E.S.T.
On this right now.
- You missed your calling, boy.
- Yeah, Deak. I even bought it.
MAN: Make sure
you get Hale! Go!
PRITCHETT:
I'd like to remind you...
there's two attack helicopters
headed this way.
Not anymore.
They've just been recalled.
MAN: I'll check the perimeter.
That's where they're headed.
They're going over.
Get to work.
You see, Mr. Pritchett...
they believe they've got
an exposed core...
And that changes
things remarkably...
Because you can't send
people out...
to an active radiation area.
That wouldn't be right.
First, you have to
take a picture from a satellite.
That takes an hour and a half
to change orbit.
Then they send in a N.E.S.T.
That's a Nuclear
Emergency Search Team.
Closest one is
about 2 hours from here.
By the time they find us,
we'll be gone. So relax.
HALE: Can your radio
get a signal to McMurren?
I'll have Clyde
patch us through.
We can get your people in here.
Then I can go feed my dog.
Clyde, this is Terry.
Do you read me?
Hello? Clyde, this is Terry.
Why the hell are they
shooting at us?
HALE: We don't have time
to discuss it right now.
Come on.
Let's have some fun.
Aah!
- You OK?
- Yeah.
Give me your gun.
Come on.
- You have any more bullets?
- Yeah.
We need to get out
of this canyon.
We can get out
up that way.
Now, if I could get
that bastard to hold still.
- I have an idea.
- Wait. I didn't mean...
Oh, shit.
Don't shoot!
Where is he?
I don't know.
No.
Go!
PRITCHETT: Holy shit!
Novacek must have hit
a canyon wall.
- You think?
- Maybe.
Maybe?
You said you'd planned
this thing carefully.
How are we going to move
those things now?
DEAKINS: Use the trucks.
The trucks!
Now, you listen.
I've spent a lot of money
underwriting this,
and frankly, you're beginning
to shake my confidence!
Well... yeah.
Well, I, uh...
I do appreciate the money
that you and your associates...
have invested
in this operation, but, uh...
it is an operation.
It's a military operation,
and you don't know dick
about that.
I have been in the military
for 20 years.
I planned and flew
over 100 missions in the Gulf.
I put these boys together
because they are motivated...
and they are
highly trained, like me.
This is what I do,
and this is battle,
and battle is a highly
fluid situation.
You plan on your contingencies,
and I have.
You keep your initiative,
and I will.
But what you don't do
is share command.
It's never a good idea.
It's still my money.
And if we succeed,
you and your friends
will get a ton of it.
If we're successful?
Look, Mr. Pritchett,
I will deliver the weapons
to the destination,
but I can't depend
and I can't guarantee...
that those assholes
in Washington...
won't do something stupid
like not pay.
What if they don't?
Well, if they don't...
The Southwest will be
a quiet neighborhood
for about 10,000 years.
[Telephone rings]
Wilkins.
Fax me their last transmission.
How much radiation is tracking?
- Fax that to Mr. Prentice.
- Yes, sir.
So far, we're not
picking up any.
That's kind
of strange, isn't it?
I mean, with an exposed core?
The breach may not be
as bad as we thought.
Colonel... what if this
wasn't an accident?
What are you saying, Giles?
GILES: In his final transmission
before the crash,
Major Deakins said
Captain Hale lost it.
We all assume that
to mean pilot error...
or equipment failure,
but what if he meant...
Hale intentionally
lost the plane?
But why would he do that?
Two nuclear weapons
would be worth a lot of money.
To who, son? There are easier
ways to buy nuclear weapons.
Go to one of the old
Soviet republics,
they'll fix you up with a couple
for the price of a BMW.
Sir... I meant, how much
would they be worth to us?
How much would we pay
to get them back?
Hold on.
These nukes have codes that
prevent people from using them.
Of course.
And no one knows
these codes, right,
except for the President
and you guys?
Access to the codes
requires the highest security.
Not even the pilots
have these codes, right?
MAN: Where is
that N.E.S.T. Team now?
They just took off, sir.
The E.T.A. In Utah
is 96 minutes.
- Correct 10, left.
- 10-4.
- It's OK.
- It's not OK!
I want to know
what's going on right now!
We were carrying nuclear weapons
on our plane last night.
My former commander
is trying to steal them.
- Oh, my God.
- That's why I need your help.
Without the helicopter,
he won't be able to move them.
Deak will have a backup plan.
He'll be prepared for that.
Trucks. He's got trucks.
Last night Clyde radioed me...
that someone came through
the Needles gate with trucks.
He won't take them towards town.
What else is around here?
The river.
[Coughing]
Do you mind?
No, I don't mind at all.
Care for one?
- The one in front has the nukes.
- How do you know?
There's only a driver.
They're keeping the weight down.
- Give me your gun again.
- What are you going to do?
I'll think of something.
Wait. We know where they are.
Let's get to a phone
and call for help.
If they make it to the river,
I'll lose them again.
You get to the phone, OK?
- Then I'm going with you.
- No, you're not.
You're going to need help.
I don't have time
to argue with you, OK?
The nuclear weapons are
my responsibility, not yours.
You're a park ranger.
I'm a military officer.
Just go to the phone.
This is a bad idea.
Hi.
Hale! Well, goddamn!
Run him down.
Get him!
Fuck!
Don't panic.
Bulletproof glass.
You can get out now.
Looks like we got ourselves
a standoff.
- Aah!
- No... we... don't!
Go! Go!
OK... you can come.
Stay down!
Would you mind not shooting
at the thermonuclear weapons?
Where's St. Jude's
hospital from here?
Salt Lake City, I think.
- Shit!
- What?
We're losing gas.
They must have hit the tank.
We need someplace
to hide these things.
I know a place.
Uh!
What the fuck
are you up to, Hale?
Don't even.
Stop!
Aw, fuck!
You learn that
in survival school?
New Jersey.
Trenton, New Jersey.
What is this place?
It used to be a copper mine.
They shut it down
a couple years ago.
Why would they have a new lock?
All right.
Good move, Hale.
I didn't see it coming...
But you're going to pay for it.
Saddle up, boys.
This place has been prepped.
Deak's been here.
What? You think
he's coming back?
That would be my guess.
May not have a lot of time.
What are we going to do?
We'll just take away
his reason for being here.
Want to help me
unload these things?
Where do you think
they're going?
Same place we were...
the only thing on this road.
My God.
Are you sure you know
what you're doing?
When you fly
with nuclear weapons,
you're trained
to retrieve if possible,
disable if necessary,
and destroy if essential.
And what are we doing?
I'm going to disable it.
You have to arm
these things with a code.
If you enter the wrong code
3 times, the nuke goes dead.
All the circuitry
shuts down and shorts out.
Pretty soon
these things will be...
nothing more
than paperweights.
[Beeping]
Hale, pick up.
Pick up!
Come on, buddy.
Pick up the phone.
Buddy, huh?
Son of a bitch.
You tried to kill me.
The friendship is over.
That doesn't mean
I don't like you.
Hell, I'm impressed.
I figured you'd have packed up
and walked off by now.
You figured wrong.
Now I got the nukes.
Guess what, Deak.
I'm going to deactivate them.
[Beeping]
You hear that?
That's me punching
the wrong codes.
Pretty soon these things
will be absolutely useless.
Might as well turn around
and drive away.
Outstanding, Hale.
That's the spirit.
Damn. I'm totally screwed now.
[Beeping continues]
Unless I thought of that
ahead of time.
What?
You're kidding.
Didn't work, did it?
I used uncoded circuit boards.
You just activated
a nuclear warhead, my friend.
Setting off a nuke in this mine
has been my plan from day one.
Otherwise, some D.C. Civilian...
might say
I haven't got the guts.
Fuck!
He's insane.
I considered bringing you in.
You know why I didn't?
- Because I would have said no?
- Nah. I'd have just killed you.
I was afraid you'd say yes...
because you don't have the balls
to go through with this.
We both know that.
How deep is this mine?
Uh... about 2,000 feet.
That's plenty.
I'm going to be there
in a few minutes.
Get out of there
as soon as you can.
It's your last move, buddy.
I can think of another move.
I'll keep these together.
If one goes off,
the other gets buried
under a billion tons of rock.
How does that sound?
You wouldn't
do something like that.
You sure about that... buddy?
Shit! Fuck!
He's going to do it.
Let's get him.
We've got to be gone
before he gets here.
[Grunting]
I can't do this.
Listen, you told me
this is a copper mine, right?
- Right?
- Right.
The blast will fuse this place
into one big solid copper pot.
- But they're coming!
- That's right.
If I don't get these to a safe
level before they get here,
God knows where he'll use them.
Just keep an eye
on the timer, OK?
All right.
[Faint rumbling]
What is that noise?
Water. There's an underground
river beneath this place.
Let's get these things unloaded.
[Elevator running]
I understand, sir.
I'll advise N.E.S.T.
Of the situation.
As soon as the ground is clean,
I'll send in a dozen gunships.
We'll secure the whole area.
Yes, sir.
- Giles Prentice, sir.
- Wilkins.
- Good to meet you finally.
- Likewise, sir.
That was the chairman,
Mr. Prentice.
According to an N.S.A.
Radio intercept, you were right,
but it's Deakins
stealing the nukes, not Hale.
[Beeping]
TERRY: Now what?
We get out of here
before he shows up.
How many times
do I have to say it?
Please don't shoot
the nuclear weapons.
[Beeping continues]
Kelly, we found the nuke.
We're at the end of tunnel "A."
Put the cold one on the
elevator, and we'll be along.
A service tunnel.
Come on.
Make sure Hale
doesn't get back to the bomb.
And, Johnson,
the clock is ticking.
- Where are you taking us?
- Back to the elevator.
These service tunnels
run between the main shafts.
Now... if we take
the next right...
Aah!
Hey, Hale.
Nice move with the nukes.
Shows initiative, determination.
Proud of you!
But I think I gave us
too much time.
30 whole minutes...
I don't know.
Shows a lack of total
commitment, don't you think?
So I took it down to 13.
I'll be right back.
[Gunfire]
Bitch!
- All set.
- We'll be right along.
Are you OK?
DEAKINS: Well, I got to go.
You two have a nice time
down here.
And don't forget to say hi
to Johnson for me...
when you see him.
HALE: 20 bucks says
you're going to see him first.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You're going to ransom
Salt Lake City, aren't you?
Why do you say that?
St. Jude's hospital.
You'll hide the warheads
in radiology...
so they don't show up
on satellite scans, right?
Huh. Well, I'm impressed.
Thank you.
So, how much you ask for?
Lots. I got a broker
in Stockholm...
that's going to buy me
5% of Volvo.
For the rest of my years,
I'll live off the dividends,
happy in the knowledge
that I'm helping to make...
the safest automobiles
in the world.
HALE: So that's what this
is all about? Money?
- Yeah.
- Bullshit.
DEAKINS: You tell me why.
Go ahead.
You tell me why.
Because you've been passed over
for promotion so many times,
you want to show the bastards
you're right.
Maybe it's because
everybody's cashing out,
so why the hell not you?
Maybe your mother dropped you on
your head when you were a baby.
Who the hell cares?
There's no difference
between you...
and a guy who
shoots up a schoolyard.
You both got a head
full of bad wiring.
- What was that?
- You're fucked in the head!
Ha!
I pissed him off.
Uh, uh... it's this way.
Hey, hey, hey!
Where the hell's the other one?
Shut up.
Help us. Come on.
Aah...
PRITCHETT: What
a Mongolian clusterfuck.
Get the goddamn thing in.
Let's get out of here.
HALE: That was the only way out.
Oh, man.
That's it, then, isn't it?
You have any family?
No. Just me and Fred.
Fred. Uh, who's Fred?
Your boyfriend?
No. My dog.
The river.
Oh, my God.
They hit it digging a tunnel.
That's why they shut down
the mine.
Come on.
Hang on.
Four minutes to detonation.
You stupid bastard!
We'll all be killed!
We'll be fine, Mr. Pritchett.
Please keep your voice down.
I'm trying to concentrate.
This should be it.
That seam doesn't go anywhere.
Oh...
One o'clock. On the road.
MAN: Attention.
We are federal agents.
Stop your vehicle immediately.
Oh, God! Oh, God!
How does that gunship
fit into your grand strategy?
You don't know
what you're doing!
This is out of control!
I must have been...
[Gagging]
Hush. Hush.
MAN: Stop your vehicle.
I repeat,
stop your vehicle immediately.
[Both take deep breath]
We'll get in front of him.
Do not move,
or you will be fired upon.
Ah-ah!
We are federal agents.
Throw down your weapons
and keep your hands in sight.
I just realized something.
I never actually
killed anyone before.
I mean... I dropped
bombs on Baghdad,
but never face-to-face.
I don't know
what the big deal is.
I really don't.
Turn your electronic equipment
off now.
Throw down your weapons.
[Rumbling]
[All talking at once]
- We're losing power!
- Oh, my God!
Control, people. Control.
We've gone red!
Trip the relays!
Aah...
I said, goddamn,
what a rush!
Whoo!
Son of a bitch!
Shock wave took down
the damn chopper.
That's E.M. P...
electromagnetic pulse.
Nuclear blast
sends it out for miles.
Everything electronic
shuts down,
including choppers
and radios.
Hell, we just shut down
McMurren's field communications.
That will put a dent
in their response time, huh?
- Deak, you the man!
- I'm the man!
Shouldn't we be evacuating?
We're fine. It was underground.
Colonel Wilkins
to General Creely.
How do you know?
If it had been
a surface detonation,
we'd have felt a different kind
of ground tremor.
We'd also be burned,
blind, and dying.
We're 10 minutes behind.
Mr. Pritchett, would you mind
stepping outside?
It went off underground,
thank God.
What do we do now?
First, we nail a huge
goddamn lid on this thing.
And with all due respect
to your boy Giles...
and his belief that honesty
is the best policy,
from now until
the end of the world,
what happened in Utah today
was an earthquake.
Hey, it's OK.
My God.
We set off a nuclear bomb.
The walls shielded the blast.
None of the radiation
leaked out.
- We're all right.
- Look at my hands.
- Why are they shaking like that?
- Because the water was freezing.
- That's not normal.
- No, it's OK.
We're just cold.
Just need to get warm.
OK? All right?
Hey, look.
See the butterflies there?
If there was radiation,
they wouldn't survive.
Now, would they? No.
All right?
I guess not.
It says so
in the detonation manual,
that if you see butterflies
after detonation,
you're going to be fine. OK?
It doesn't say that.
I promise you, though,
we're fine.
How far downriver
does this path go?
Three or four miles.
We should get to Deakins
before he gets out of here.
Wait.
Looks like there's
just two of them.
There's more coming.
[Vehicle approaching]
MAN: I thought you said Hale
wouldn't be a problem.
DEAKINS: He surprised me, too,
but he's dead, so let's go.
- Sink it?
- Steal it.
- Let's move it.
- They're coming.
Get out of the boat.
Get out of the boat!
Well, your friends
in Washington...
should be getting
the package now.
Yep. I'm sure we got their full
and complete attention.
Let's move it.
We're on a tight schedule.
[Starts engine]
...$250 million by 1400,
Utah time.
This deadline is not negotiable,
and there is no grace period.
The second device is on a timer.
Shortly after you receive this,
the timer will be activated.
At 1401, I will make a call.
If you have complied,
I will stop the timer.
If you have not...
Yes. Yes, sir. I understand.
[Telephone ringing]
- Creely.
- Please hold.
The President is asking if we
know where the device is headed.
If Deakins had a plane waiting,
it could be anywhere.
- We just don't know.
- I do.
One moment, sir.
This is Colonel Jamison.
They've found Captain Hale.
He's at Lake Powell.
This is a really bad idea.
- Sir, the prisoner is secure.
- All right, Tom. Good job.
You gentlemen can R.T.B.
I'll take it.
Roger, sir. Returning to base.
They found the raft
on the other side of the lake.
Tracks from a heavy truck
ran out on the paved road.
- What about the girl?
- What about her?
What about her?
She's an innocent victim.
I got her involved.
You're going to hit that truck
with everything you've got.
I don't want her
becoming a casualty.
Maybe giving her up
is OK with you,
but we're military officers.
We took an oath,
one officer to another.
We have a responsibility
to save that woman's life...
and get back the weapon.
I have a responsibility
to follow orders...
and return you to McMurren.
Do you understand
what orders are, captain?
- Yes, sir, I do.
- Good.
Because I'm about to break them.
- Any argument, Mr. Prentice?
- No, sir.
Just for the record,
I'm not entirely a civilian.
I was actually a lieutenant
in the R.O.T.C. At Yale.
Good for you, lieutenant.
- Is the radio still down?
- Afraid so.
Your chopper will be
refueled in two minutes.
I wish I were going with you.
Captain, what exactly
are you looking for?
- Tracks.
- As in railroad tracks?
Yeah. Deak knows you're covering
every inch of asphalt.
I'll bet 20 bucks
that nuke isn't on a truck.
- It's on a train.
- Let me see the map.
Salt Lake is northwest of here.
These tracks curve east
before Salt Lake.
Why would he do that?
I don't think he's going
to Salt Lake.
But that's where
the closest hospital is.
You found the radiology tag.
That's what's bothering me.
I think he planted it...
to make the person that found it
think that's where he's heading.
- He's doing a rope-a-dope.
- He's doing a what?
Rope-a-dope. It's a boxing term.
Ali and Foreman in Zaire.
I know what the rope-a-dope is.
What's your point?
My point is that everything he
shows us says he's heading west.
He's actually heading east.
Denver.
You said you had Salt Lake
sealed up pretty tight.
What's it going to hurt
if we check out Denver?
DEAKINS: Shepherd!
Any trouble with the train crew?
SHEPHERD: Not a bit.
They went like lambs.
Good for them. Let's get
that satellite dish wired in.
- Already done.
- Excellent.
With this remote, you can shut
the bomb down face-to-face...
or dial it in over the link.
All right.
Let's close this deal.
I want to be airborne
in five minutes...
en route to the mountains.
Contact Washington. Tell them
the bomb's on its way to Denver.
Then contact Geneva.
When the money's in place,
I'll shut down that puppy.
Smile, boys.
We're about to retire.
Let's get this bird unwrapped.
Uhh!
We haven't met.
I'm Max.
Uhh!
You probably thought
I was a computer nerd.
Ha ha ha! Wrong.
I was a Navy S.E.A.L., lady.
You should see what I can do
with just my thumb.
You just saved me $3 million.
I owe you one.
Shoot yourself.
We'll call it square.
Whoa. Attitude.
Now, where's
my little buddy Hale?
He left you alone, didn't he?
Oh, that's his speed...
100% pussy.
He's got more guts
than you think.
But would he have enough guts
to eat a bullet...
before he'd help someone
vaporize a whole city?
I think he'd fold, but not you.
I think you've got
more guts than he does.
I think you'd eat a bullet.
Let's find out.
Now, press four.
Ooh.
Ahh, I said push four.
Go ahead.
Push four.
Ahh.
Four.
Eight.
Seven.
Go ahead.
Please.
Seven.
Starting at ground zero...
and moving out
in concentric circles,
we have, in terms
of immediate effect,
100% fatalities to 30 miles,
90% at 40 miles,
dropping roughly 10%
for every 10 miles after that.
Two.
One.
Enter.
We estimate...
250,000 dead on impact...
and another quarter-million
projected within the year.
Enter.
Come on. Just push "enter,"
and it's done.
Which is it going to be, hmm?
Ahh. Hmm.
To tell the truth, I thought
you were going to fold.
Well, I'm dead either way.
So do it yourself, asshole.
Open the door!
Night-night, honey.
HALE: Cover me.
WILKINS: Good luck.
Uhh! Uhh!
Bring it in.
Give me your hand.
OK... you can come.
Get me down there!
Let's give those guys a haircut.
Shit!
Get down!
Freeze!
- Wow.
- That was a first for me, too.
Uhh!
[Engine sputters]
MAN: This is where
you two get off.
TERRY: No!
[Grunting]
[Men talking]
- We're leaving, now!
- Yes, sir!
- Where's Shepherd?
- He's supposed to be here.
Find him!
[Engine revving up]
[Dripping]
Cut the power!
Aaah!
DEAKINS: Goddamn you, Hale.
We're never going
to get clear in time.
We need to shut down the nuke.
You hear me?
- You need to disarm it.
- Find Hale.
Oh, God. Your shoulder.
- Help me off with this.
- Oh, God.
No matter what, this train
can't make it to the city.
So you stay here
and uncouple the car.
I'm going to go after Deakins.
- I'll see you soon.
- You promise?
Fuck them if they
can't take a joke.
What the fuck are you doing?
Shut that son of a bitch
down, now!
This ain't what I signed on for.
I'm not ready to die,
not for you.
Everybody dies, Kelly.
I'm as good a reason as any.
Come on. Come on.
Hale!
Incoming!
Uh!
Yaaah!
[Thud]
Come on out, Deak.
It's over.
Ha ha ha!
You lose.
I still got my finger
on the trigger.
That's the remote trigger.
You see, if I press
this button here, you lose.
And if I push this button...
The weapon is disarmed.
Why don't you disarm it, then?
I'm not in the mood.
Get rid of your weapon.
Come on.
That-a boy.
Now you can shut it down.
You just have to
come and get it,
and $20 that I took
from you last night...
Says that you won't.
- You're out of your mind.
- Yeah. Ain't it cool?
I'm serious. Your mind
has taken a walk off the map.
Maybe, but I'm still
going to kick your ass.
All right,
you're bleeding, aren't you?
Good. Let's see if we can't
get more out of you.
Uh!
Ahh!
Every fight used to go
to a knockout.
Know how it feels
to be knocked out?
Your brain presses
against your skull,
and it feels like this.
[Gunshot]
Ah!
[Grunts]
Feel anything like that?
[Beep beep]
I win.
Sir, please turn around.
My name is Riley Hale.
Terry Carmichael.
HALE: Pleased to meet you.
TERRY: You know, you're still
under arrest, captain.
HALE: Oh, yeah?
I guess you better take me in.