Mr. Taransky...?
She's...
She's walking?
Don't tell me
she's walking.
She can't walk.
- Nicola!
- This, this...
- not this.
- Nicola!
- How was your massage?
- You're in breach.
- Cigarette.
- Is this about the new pages?
Because I made
the changes,
all the changes
you wanted.
You are virtually
in every scene.
It is not the size
of the role, Viktor.
Am I, or am I not
entitled
to the biggest trailer
on the lot? Hmm?
It's the biggest
on earth.
I swear.
It's a 50-foot
Airstream.
They don't make them
any longer.
- Taller, Viktor.
- Taller?
- Taller!
- What?
Eh.
You've insulted me
for the last time.
You're right.
It's actually--
It's actually taller.
- You're right. It's amazing.
- Coffee!
Wait a minute.
The tires are
overinflated.
See? It's just this.
See? Look. Here.
- The air comes right out.
- This is sad.
See? It's lower already.
Nicola, I beg you.
Don't do this to me.
You know,
I had three other offers.
I only signed on
to this picture...
- out of loyalty.
- Well, then show me some.
They're going
to shut me down!
It's not working, Viktor.
I mean, my God!
The scene
with the thousand geese?!
I don't understand
this film!
Nobody is going
to understand this film.
I already put out a press release
citing creative differences.
So just let it go.
You went to the press?
Do we have everything?
All right.
You know what?
You're right.
You are right.
And when you're right, you're right.
- Thank you.
- Let me help you with these.
'Cause you oughta go.
- I don't deserve you.
- Oh.
This film doesn't
deserve you.
It deserves much,
much better than you!
Creative differences?
The difference is
you're not creative.
To hell, please.
Jack?
Jack, are you there?
She's good.
You can hardly tell
she's reading off a teleprompter.
I'm right here.
Right beside you.
Look.
I've analyzed this footage.
We've got everything
we need in the can already.
If I could just make
the proper adjustments,
we can finish
this film without her.
Viktor, according to the writ
her attorneys filed at noon today,
they'll sue if the film is released
with Nicola in a single frame.
They will sue, Viktor.
They're serious.
So let's recast.
Nicola Anders is
the only actress in the world
that could play that part.
- It's a remake, Hal.
- That's right.
Nicola Anders is not
bigger than this picture.
Of course she is, Viktor.
No other name is going
to sign on now.
Who needs a name?
We'll cast an unknown.
I'm not going to play
opposite an unknown.
- We can't sell an unknown.
- The numbers don't work.
If we ever want to be in
the Nicola Anders business again,
we have to cut our losses
and shelve the picture.
No!
I will not give in to that
blackmailing--
Viktor,
let's take a walk.
Ridiculous performance.
I told you she was bad.
No, yours in there.
Why do you always have to make
things so difficult for yourself?
Difficult?
I'm being difficult?
Yes. Mm-hmm.
Elaine, do you know
what these are?
Mike 'n' Ike's?
They're not just any
Mike 'n' Ike's,
These are cherry
Mike 'n' Ike's.
Do you know why I,
Viktor Taransky,
two-time Academy Award
nominated director--
Viktor, that was "Short Subject."
--overseeing the most cherished
movie project of my entire career,
am walking around with--
look, look, look...
pockets full
of these... things?!
I have a feeling
you're going to tell me.
I'm going to tell you why.
Because Ms. Nicola Anders,
supermodel
with a SAG card,
has it written
in her contract
that all cherry
Mike 'n' Ike's
be removed
from her candy dish,
along with strict instructions
that any room she walks into
must have seven packs
of cigarettes waiting for her--
three of them opened;
that there be
a personal Jacuzzi
within 80 paces
of her dressing room;
and that any time
she travels,
her nanny must fly
with her first-class.
So, what's wrong
with that?
Elaine, she doesn't
have children.
Don't you see?
They're mocking us.
They're mocking--
we're at their mercy.
What happened?
I mean, we always had movie stars,
but they used to be
our stars, remember?
We were the ones who would
tell them what to do.
And we would tell them
what to wear,
- who to date--
- That's what you want?!
When they
were under contract to us,
we could change their names
if we wanted to.
- More than once.
- Viktor,
do you realize
you're nostalgic
for an era you weren't
even born in?!
I do remember why I got
into this business.
- You seem to have forgotten.
- Oh, please. Come on.
New York-- Cassavetes.
Remember?
- Here we go.
- What were we doing?
We were trying to make
something important.
I don't know.
Shine a little light
in that darkened cinema.
It's called a projector.
Illuminate hearts and minds
with a ray of truth.
I thought that's
what we were doing.
I have good memories
of those days, too.
I do, but this isn't
about that--
or you, or me,
or some high-minded ideal.
This is business.
- Spare me.
- Look around.
Who do you think pays
for all of this?
This is about investment
and return.
I'm not interested
in investment and return!
in who pays for anything!
I'm trying to make a movie!
I'm responsible
for this, Viktor.
Those days
in New York...
It's over, Viktor.
You're not renewing
my contract?
How can I?!
Your last three pictures tanked.
No bankable star is going
to work with you after this.
I mean, if you just
compromised a little.
Well, it's not every day
you're fired
by the mother
of your own child.
You and I both know
that I kept you on
after the divorce
for old time's sake.
And so you could still hold
your head up in front of Lainey.
- I fought for you.
- Yeah, well...
I'm sorry, Viktor.
Dad!
- Sweetheart.
- Hey, Dad.
- How are you, honey?
- Good.
I'm sorry Mom canned you.
I'm going to finish
this picture.
Lainey, I'm going
to finish it.
Because it's important.
I know you will, Dad.
You're Viktor Taransky.
I'm Viktor Taransky.
'Kay.
Bye, Dad.
- Hi, sweetheart.
- Hey, Mom.
Are you okay?
I'm Viktor Taransky.
Mr. Taransky?
Mr. Taransky,
thank God.
I've been trying
to see you.
I've been calling.
Your assistant
won't put me through.
I told her it was a matter
of life and death.
I was afraid I wasn't going
to get to you in time.
Please, just...
- Keep your distance.
- I did it!
I did it!
I licked skin,
I licked hair,
- I licked every part of her.
- I'm going to call security.
I'll call security
if you don't back off.
I have her,
Mr. Taransky.
The answer
to your prayers.
- The answer to this.
- I was misquoted.
I have your new leading-lady
right here.
In my pants.
Please, sir,
I don't know you.
- I don't know where you come from--
- It's me!
Mr. Taransky, don't--
Don't you recognize me?
The Future of Film Conference
in San Jose.
Remember that?
Hank.
Hank Aleno.
I was a keynote speaker.
You must remember my speech.
- "Who Needs Humans?"
- Right.
You were booed off
the stage.
- Whoa, that's got to be...
- Eight years ago.
And that whole time
I never left my computer.
Uh-huh.
Good for you, Hank.
Well, it's good
and bad.
That's what caused this.
The eye tumor.
- Microwaves from the screen.
- I'm sorry.
Don't be,
because it was worth it.
You have to see her.
Oh, I've seen those.
- Not like this.
- I'll take care of that.
Yeah, well, you're talking
about a "syn-thespian."
- A virtual actor.
- No, we call them "vac-tors."
"Vac-tors"?
I need flesh.
- Flesh is weak.
- It can't be done.
It can be done.
With my new computer code,
it can be done.
You and me...
we can do this together.
I don't know anything
about computers.
See, that's why--
that's why you're so perfect.
You have something...
- that I don't have.
- What's that?
An eye.
An eye for performance.
You know the truth
when you see it.
I know.
I mean, I've seen
your movies.
I love your movies.
- You love my movies?
- "Straw God."
That changed my life.
You saw "Straw God"?
I have seen every frame
of your work.
You're the only
filmmaker
with the artistic
integrity...
to realize my vision.
You and me,
art and science--
We're the perfect
marriage.
Hank...
I've had
a rough day today.
But, I tell you what,
I'll call you
about this next week.
- We can talk.
- I won't be here in a week.
- The tumor is inoperable.
- I'll call you about it, okay?
That's what I'm trying to say.
The tumor is inoperable.
I'll be dead.
Well, I'm already dead.
Call me!
This week!
Please.
What do you mean
she won't work with me?
She's done nothing.
She doesn't have
a single credit to her name.
Better no credits
than a Taransky credit.
Art,
you don't understand.
I've mortgaged everything
to finish this film.
The creditors
are calling me.
They're at the door
for God's sake.
Hello?
Damn it!
Mr. Taransky.
Mr. Taransky!
- Mr. Taransky!
- No, I'm not him!
- I'm not him!
Mr. Taransky!
Hank Aleno!
I represent the estate
of Mr. Hank Aleno.
It was his last wish
that you have this.
What is it?
I have no idea.
He wanted you
to have it.
Valarie!
Valarie,
what are you running from?
From Valarie.
Valarie, no!
Jack, are you there?
Something like this
can happen and what...
was it for?
Why are we here?
Is that what
you're asking, Jack?
Why are we here?
No why...
just here.
Just here.
Ladies and gentlemen
of the jury,
I know I may be guilty
of a crime,
but it was committed with
the purest of intentions.
I wanted to send a message
to the acting community
who...
put themselves above
the work,
who put themselves above me.
So, what did
you guys think?
So fake.
Totally artificial.
Like we're suppose to believe
that was 19th century Lisbon.
- Come on.
- Guys...
Who's looking at the sets
when she's on screen?
Oh, yeah.
There he is.
That's my dad,
Viktor Taransky.
- She was magnificent.
- She's absolutely unreal.
Breathtaking.
She wasn't too...
cartoony, or anything?
The nun?
Or are you talking about
the mother?
A star like that, who cares about
the supporting cast?
Congratulations again.
She's not of this earth.
- You should be very proud.
- Oh, not of this earth.
And the rest of the film,
what did you think?
She's a miracle.
Where did you find her?
Well...
I saw her picture...
on the computer.
A computer?
You really didn't notice
anything unusual about her?
Only her brilliance.
To be honest,
with what you had
to work with,
I was expecting
a train wreck.
- You really pulled it off.
- I did?
Yeah. I have a feeling Mom's
going to take you back after this.
Back on the lot.
That's what--
I know. I know.
Come on, let's go.
A dazzling new ingenue
has come from seemingly nowhere
to capture the hearts of movie-going
audiences around the world
in her debut film
"Sunrise, Sunset."
But who is Simone?
We know so little about her.
And why the secrecy?
All we know for sure
is that she was discovered
by little-known director,
Viktor Tarinsky.
Taransky.
Simone!
Simone?
- Good to see you, too, Elaine.
- Where is she?
- She's not here.
- Why isn't she with you?
Why? Because she would never come
to something like this.
She's intensely private.
Back to work, everyone.
She's not here.
Hey, listen.
Have you read the reviews?
They're love letters.
Listen to this one.
Oh, here.
Simone has the voice
of a young Jane Fonda,
the body
of Sophia Loren,
the grace of well,
Grace Kelly--
ha-ha--
and the face...
of Audrey Hepburn
combined with an angel.
- Almost right.
- I can't wait to meet her.
Oh, I don't know
if that's going to happen.
Why not?
She is somewhat
of a recluse.
That's how she stays
so pure.
She isolates herself
in her art.
Viktor, it's my studio.
Elaine, it's my actor.
There are other studios.
There's only one Simone.
Okay, have it your way,
Viktor.
Hello, Walter.
Nobody came in
or went out,
- just like you said.
- Very good.
- Mr. Taransky?
- Yes?
Is Ms. Simone
coming in today?
She's already here.
She arrived before you got here.
She's going to leave
long after you're gone.
Remember,
under no circumstances
are you or anybody else
ever to enter this set
without my express
permission, understood?
Yes, sir.
Mr. Taransky?
What if it catches
on fire?
Let it burn.
Good morning, Simone.
Good morning, Mr. Taransky.
Simone, a star is...
digitized.
Do you know
what this means?
We have stepped
into a new dimension.
Our ability
to manufacture fraud
now exceeds our ability
to detect it.
I am the death of real.
...death of real.
Too much Meryl Streep.
A little less Streep.
And a little more...
Bacall.
Is this better,
Mr. Taransky?
Much.
While we're at it,
there's a little
something
I want to add
to your repertoire.
You've got the wrong
Holly Golightly.
Remember that thing
Audrey Hepburn does
in "Breakfast at Tiffany's"?
How do I look?
Give me Audrey.
Perfect.
Perfect, Simone.
Oh, God.
I'm so relaxed
around you.
I'm so myself.
You did create me.
I just brought someone
else's dream to life.
Mr. Taransky,
we both know I was nothing
without you.
I was computer code.
I was ones and zeros.
I was nothing.
Well...
that's true.
I don't want
to boast, but...
Are you ever going to tell
the truth about me, Mr. Taransky?
I'm going tell
the truth about you.
Why wouldn't i?
Of course...
with Hank's tragic passing,
his secret did die
with him.
This is
a classic case of
technology in search
of an artist.
Someone with integrity,
someone with vision,
someone who can see.
See beyond
this irrational
allegiance
to flesh and blood.
Someone who can see
that with the rise
in the price of a real actor
and the fall in the price
of a fake,
that the scales have tipped--
naturally in favor
of the fake.
Someone who can see
that if a performance
is genuine,
it doesn't matter
if the actor's real or not.
And what's real anymore?
Most actors these days
have digital work done
to them.
It's a gray area.
The only real truth
is the work.
I'm going to tell
the truth about you
after your next picture.
You're so beautiful.
You're too beautiful.
We're going to fix that.
Is this on?
I will not be taking any questions
regarding Simone.
I do, however,
have a statement
to read on her behalf.
"To Whom it May Concern:
I'm deeply grateful
for the extraordinary
public response
to Mr. Taransky's film.
At this time I will be
conducting no interviews,
or making
publicity appearances--
- This is unbelievable.
- I politely request that the press
respect my privacy and let
the work speak for itself.
Yours truly, Simone."
Viktor!
Who is Simone dating?!
Where did you find her?
- Is Simone her real name?
- Didn't I make it clear?
No questions
regarding Simone.
We're just trying
to get some answers.
I will make
my final statement.
Ms. Simone begins production
on her new film today--
"Eternity Forever."
This is a project
which has been near and dear
to my heart since I wrote it
nine years ago.
Thank you.
Would you answer
a question regarding Hank?
Hank?
Who asked me about Hank?
Funny, why is the movie
dedicated to Hank?
Are they involved?
They were at one time
inseparable. Yes.
And now?
Now...
sadly to say,
only in spirit.
Thank you.
Your car will be ready
in just a minute.
We gave you
a complimentary car wash.
- Oh, really?
- They're cleaning the engine now.
Thank you.
- Viktor, hey.
- Hal.
I am so happy for us.
The film, the chemistry.
Nothing against
Nicola Anders,
but I think
that Simone and I,
we really worked
great together.
- You were never together.
- Still, the connection was undeniable.
You can't--
Look, I have not read
"Eternity Forever,"
but it is fantastic.
And I know I would be perfect
for the part of Clive.
- Clyde.
- Clyde, right.
That's what I'm talking about.
Yes, perfect.
Come on, man.
Look, I ran into Simone
on the lot.
- Really?
- Yes, really.
- She never mentioned it.
- She's busy right now.
People coming at her
from all angles.
Maybe she didn't want
you to know, huh?
I strongly sensed
that she thought I would be
perfect for Clyde as well.
- Really?
- Strongly.
Excuse me.
Sure.
Hello?
Simone, it's so great
to hear from you.
How are you,
sweetheart?
You'll never guess
who I'm with.
- You met him on the lot the other day.
- It was more in passing.
No, you're not
even close.
Hal.
- Hal Sinclair.
- What's wrong now?
I'm getting nothing from her side
of the conversation.
No, I don't think
he put on weight.
Anyway, listen. Do you think he'd
be right for "Eternity Forever"?
He's not the right type?
You want to go
in another direction?
Well... we'll try and talk her
into it, don't worry.
Anything you can do.
- Anything.
- Yeah, listen, honey.
What is this,
some kind of jamming device?
This is a bad place to talk.
Maybe he's just
talking to himself.
Taransky's not
that good an actor.
Honey, I know you want
to do charity work.
No, they've taken
special precautions.
Some kind
of new encryption.
Why would they do that?
Well, whatever it is...
it's dark.
Dark?
Yeah. Very.
All right,
we'll talk about it
at the beach house
this weekend.
- Can you ever stop doing that?
- Why?
You'll lose yourself
in that thing.
You gotta get out more.
How you gonna meet boys?
Dad, I know
plenty of boys.
You do? Who?
Where do you meet them?
You meet them
in those chat rooms?
How do you know you're not talking
to some middle-aged freak?
Dad, I can spot a middle-aged
freak a mile away.
It's beautiful today.
Let's go outside and eat.
And Lainey,
leave the computer, please.
Okay.
Dad, it might be better
to eat inside.
Stay here.
What is this?
What the hell is going on?
What are you doing here?
- You're trespassing.
- You can't hide her forever!
Simone appears only
when I want her to appear!
Sounds like a prisoner.
- What are you, holding her hostage?
- You're the hostage.
I mean, you look kind
of captive to me.
Lainey,
don't you ever wonder
where I'm really
hiding Simone?
Just as long as I know
where you are, Dad.
- Bye, Dad.
- Bye, honey.
Hello, Viktor.
Sorry I got her back late.
Oh, no problem.
Hey, you want
to come in?
- Hi.
- Hi, Honey.
- Hi, Vik.
- Kent.
Viktor, we simply
have to discuss
"Eternity Forever."
I still haven't received
Simone's script notes.
There aren't any.
If the filmmakers
are happy,
she's happy.
She considers herself,
you know, an instrument.
So she's really going
to do all this nudity?
It's on the page.
We have to do something
about this budget.
It's completely
unrealistic.
You allowed nothing
for limousine service.
- She drives herself.
- Uh-huh.
- Hair and make-up?
- Does her own.
- Theater training.
- Oh, she was in the theater?
Where?
You want her resume?
I'll send it to you.
Okay, great. Thanks.
At least, Viktor,
contingency for wardrobe.
Anybody can go up a size.
I guarantee she will not
gain an ounce.
She is so disciplined.
Well, we've gotta do
something about this--
- "Stuntwoman."
- What about it?
- Well, there isn't one.
- She doesn't need one.
- Does all her own stunts.
- Even the fall from the plane?
- Even the fall from the plane.
- Oh.
Shoot it
on the last day.
Listen, Viktor.
I want to talk to you now,
not as Elaine, Studio Head,
but as Elaine, ex-wife.
Hey, second ex-wife.
Seriously.
You got lucky this last time.
But you need
to be careful.
We both know you wouldn't be
making this overblown art film
if you hadn't convinced
Simone to be in it.
Elaine...
talking to you now,
not as Viktor, Director,
but as Viktor,
your first former husband,
what happened to you? Huh?
Experience, Viktor.
That's what happened
to me.
Yeah, I've seen this
a hundred times.
- Really?
- Yeah.
These young stars
destroying
the very people
who discovered them.
I'm worried about you,
that's all.
This woman,
she controls your destiny.
She doesn't control
my destiny.
There's something
about her I don't trust.
Hi, Jane.
Thanks for taking me back,
Mr. Taransky.
I know that it looked like
I sided with the studio,
but I've always believed
in you. Honestly.
Don't worry.
I understand.
- Are they--
- They're all here.
Okay, thank you.
Hello.
Viktor.
I just want to say
I am delighted
to have such
a wonderful cast
assembled here
for "Eternity Forever."
A reminder:
as a condition for working
on this picture,
you will not be rehearsing
with Simone.
You will not be shooting
Actually, you are forbidden
from contacting Simone
at any time, for any reason,
whatsoever.
- Works for me.
- How will you shoot our love scenes?
- Body double.
- For her?
For you.
Anyway, Simone insisted
on speaking with you herself
before filming started.
I believe she's on the line now.
Simone, are you there?
I certainly am,
Mr. Taransky.
So are we, Simone.
Why don't you leave me alone
with my co-stars, Mr. Taransky,
so we can get to know
each other better?
Absolutely.
I'll be back in a minute.
Hi, who's there?
Don't be shy.
Introduce yourselves.
I'm Mac.
I turned down
a Bertolucci film to be here.
Hi, Simone.
I'm Corel.
Hi, I'm Claris.
You used to date
my cousin, Dell.
I'm Hewlitt.
We can rehearse in private
if you like.
My name is Lotus.
God, I can't believe
I'm talking to you.
We are going to become
such great friends.
Hi, Simone, it's Hal.
It's great to be working
together... again.
Is that everyone?
Well, obviously,
as you know, I'm Simone.
Who else?
I just want to start
by apologizing
for my process.
I know it's an unusual way
to work,
but I just find
I relate better to people
when they're not
actually there.
Oh, of course.
Of course.
I don't have much to say,
Except, that I know
it's gonna be a great project
if we all just trust
Mr. Taransky's vision.
Always do
what Mr. Taransky says.
If in doubt,
do it the Taransky way.
I know we're gonna make
a wonderful movie together.
Together.
Absolutely.
Veronica.
What you don't understand,
Clyde, is that love--
Still too big.
I like it,
but it's too big.
All right.
Smaller teardrops this time.
What you don't understand,
Clyde,
is that love
is like a wildflower.
But that flower only grows
on the edge...
of a very high cliff.
Perfect.
Simone. Simone.
Simone.
Gonna be a little change
in plans, Simone.
You have no idea
the effect
your performance
is having on people.
We can't stop now.
These films,
they're speaking
to the human condition.
We're changing lives.
People need to believe
you're real.
To reveal the truth now,
it would be too cruel.
You're gonna get in
a lot of trouble, Mr. Taransky.
Now, why do you have
to bring that up?!
I mean,
everything's a risk.
But it's worth it,
isn't it?
We've done
enough work today.
You've been cooped up
in there too long.
So how about...
you and I going
out on the town?
Tonight, they're going
to see you
with their own eyes.
Excuse me.
I will be checking in
a very special guest.
- A Ms. Enomis.
- Ah, Ms. Enomis.
Now, Ms. Enomis
demands her privacy.
So, you will switch off
all surveillance cameras.
I alone, will escort
Ms. Enomis to her room
via the rear exit.
She must not be disturbed
at any time,
for any reason whatsoever.
I'm sure I can rely
on your discretion.
Understood, sir.
Thank you.
There she is!
Who is it?
It's Simone.
Okay, I think
everybody's here.
Now!
I think we're
all right now.
Oh, thank God
for you, Faith.
Thank God for you.
This is way above
and beyond
the call of duty
for a stand-in.
I must tell you,
you have no idea
the service you've
performed for Simone,
shielding her
from these animals.
Oh, no, Mr. Taransky.
Thank God for you.
- For me?
- Yeah.
How many directors
would go
to so much trouble
to protect an actress?
It's incredible.
You know,
we're gonna have
to go back
to my place,
just to, you know,
keep them off the scent.
Of course.
You look so...
So much like...
um, like her?
Oh, yes, of course.
Like her.
But you're
so very beautiful
in your own right.
I do find myself strangely
attracted to you, Mr. Taransky.
Call me Viktor.
Viktor.
- Oh.
- Oh, Viktor.
- Viktor.
- Yes?
- This is so exciting.
- Yes.
Do what you do
to Simone?
What?
What did you say?
I said do whatever
you do to Simone.
What I do to Simone?
Call me Simone!
Simone?
Yes. Say it again,
please.
I want to know what it's like
to be her just for one night.
Please, call me Simone.
You're with me so you can
be close to her?
Is that a problem?
Okay. Excuse me
just a minute.
Is something wrong?
Well, actually,
maybe we can do this
some other time
- or something.
- Are you busy tomorrow?
Gentlemen,
the Presidential Suite.
Ahem--
I think that should
take care of everything.
Yes, sir.
I believe it will.
Leave me for a moment.
Simone.
- Brilliant.
- Elaine!
- There she is.
- The picture--
The picture.
It's a revelation.
Thank you.
We all worked
so hard.
- It was you.
- No, it was all of us.
It was incredible.
Thank you all.
Thank you.
- Whoa!
- Viktor!
- Is she here?
- Viktor, is she here?
Oh, I'm fine, Hal.
How are you?
Somebody
said she was here.
Jesus.
That's her glass.
Jack Daniels,
straight up.
- My kind of woman.
- Come on, where is she?
I don't know.
She's, uh...
Is that her
by the fountain?
You know,
between you and me,
- she doesn't really exist.
- Simone!
- Simone's here?
- Why didn't anybody tell me?
- She's here?!
- Simone!
- I got your glass!
I'm your biggest fan!
Simone!
- Simone!
- Simone?
Get out!
Not you two.
She goes to a major
Hollywood A-list party
and we don't get
an interview,
a comment?
We don't even get a photograph?!
Is that what
you're telling me?
Nobody got a photograph.
Nobody ever gets a photograph.
We have our best people
on it, Mr. Sayer.
Get better people!
What about the 24-hour
tail on Taransky?
They're camped out every place
he goes; every concierge,
every maitre d',
they're all on the take.
But this Simone woman
is good.
Obviously, that is not
her real name.
She uses
an assumed identity.
She travels under
a false name.
She checks into
a hotel under an alias.
Never stays in the same place
two nights in a row.
What about the satellite photos?
What happened?
- Nothin'.
- Nothing from space?!
What about
the fingerprints?
What happened when we dusted
that whole hotel suite?
Well, we have some
of Taransky's fingerprints,
a lot of yours...
and none of hers.
No one is that perfect,
that pure.
You know, I had something
on Mother Teresa once.
But then she died
and it just wasn't
worth it anymore.
I know how to flush out
this Simone woman.
A tell-all story
from her childhood.
You have one?
I will when you're
finished writing it.
Please don't
make me do this.
Guard, open this door
right now.
Mr. Taransky gave me
specific instructions
never to open up this door.
- What are you doing?!
- Mr. Taransky!
- Why did you do this?!
- We have to talk to her!
- We know she's in there.
- Okay.
What is this about?
We've got the tracking numbers
for "Eternity Forever."
They're in the toilet.
She's gotta get out there
and sell the film.
What do you want her to do,
go door-to-door?
Even Garbo would be on the talk show
circuit if she were alive!
It is precisely because she
doesn't crave the limelight
that people love her!
- This is bullshit!
- She is about the work,
- and only the work!
- This is overshadowing the work.
If you can't handle her,
I will.
It's not a good time.
She's emotional.
Today, her mother dies.
Scene 42
of "Good for Nothing."
- This is not a good time.
- It never is.
- Step aside!
- We're going in!
- This is ridiculous!
- No! No!
- What are you doing?!
- Simone!
I trusted you.
- Simone?
- You can come out, it's Elaine!
- We just want to have a meeting.
- We can talk,
- girl-to-girl. Just us.
- Where is she?
- She's gone.
- Where are the sets?
- God, that is so like her.
- Where are the cameras?
Viktor, we're not paying
for this are we?
What is all this?
Well...
I suppose
it was gonna come out
sooner or later.
I guess I'm actually
relieved in a way.
I can just say it finally.
She's a computer--
addict.
What?
She's a computer addict!
She's buried in here.
Day in, day out.
Of course.
I should have guessed.
It's why she never
goes anywhere,
- Why she's never seen in public.
- Now you're getting it.
Probably spends
her whole life in chat rooms.
- The one place she can be herself.
- Anonymous.
Only it's worse.
It's far worse.
She's extremely
agoraphobic.
She has a morbid fear
of people,
of germs,
places, heights--
- Name it.
- This is terrible.
How is she going
to plug the film?
- Yes, indeed.
- She has to do publicity.
Maybe I could get her
to do something.
Maybe a television
talk show or something.
Yes!
- Taped.
- Make it live, please.
- Live?
- Please.
She'd never go there.
It would have to be remote.
We can work with that.
I can't promise anything.
- We understand.
- Thank you, Viktor.
- Don't grovel.
Thank you.
Give her our best.
That agoraphobia--
it's like a plague.
It's out of control
in Europe.
It's so good of you
to protect her like this.
She wanted you--
No, no.
Don't touch that.
Germs.
She wanted you
to have that.
She was there.
She was right there.
Yeah.
Oh, my gosh.
She didn't,
by any chance,
happen
to mention me?
Actually, she did.
She, uh...
she said that she thought
you were very beautiful.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Would you want to go
and get something to eat,
or something?
Viktor,
I'd love to, really.,
but don't you have
to go talk to Simone?
If I can find her.
Well.
All right. Good.
- Thanks, Viktor.
- Thank you.
I'm gonna-- Bye.
Tonight,
on Frank Brand Live--
Since taking the nation
by storm
in her debut movie,
"Sunrise, Sunset,"
no one has managed to land
a live television interview
with this fabulous
shooting starlet, Simone--
until now.
she's agreed to talk
with us tonight
from the set
of her new film.
Welcome, Simone.
So glad you can find time
in your hectic schedule to be here.
It's my pleasure.
Wonderful to be
with you, Frank.
No one can accuse you
of being overexposed, Simone.
Why have you stayed so completely
out of the limelight?
I guess I just think actors
talk too much.
Does the world really want
to hear my life story
just because I have a movie
opening on Friday?
Wow.
She is all woman.
Of course, the problem
with shying away
from publicity these days
is that it tends
to attract even more.
Don't I know it.
But the only reason
I'm here now,
is to put the attention
back where it belongs,
on Mr. Taransky's film.
And you don't secretly want
the attention?
I'm not even sure
I deserve it.
You see, after tonight,
I'll have just as much
screen time on your show
as I have in my movies.
Now, how is that healthy
for a performer?
Because you have to understand,
Frank, none of this is real.
Who I am on screen
and who I really am,
they're two totally
different people.
Change of topic.
You have been
romantically linked
to dozens of men
in the press--
Mick Jagger, Steven Hawking,
Fidel Castro,
most recently,
Viktor Taransky.
Is there a Mr. Right
in there somewhere?
You know, Frank, I'd rather not
discuss my private life.
But Viktor and I,
we are inseparable.
Oh, Viktor.
You dog.
I wouldn't be here today
without him.
Would you like
a moment, Simone?
No, I'm okay.
Okay.
Then let's talk about
this work
you care so much about.
Sure.
Where would you like
to start, Frank?
- How about the nudity?
- I know where that is.
Nudity's just never been
an issue for me.
I know that tree.
- Clothes are simply an option.
- I know that tree.
I know where that is.
What exactly was it
that attracted you
to your first two projects?
I suppose what I like most
about the movies I'm in
is that they're not about
special effects.
And they are better
for it, I might add.
We appear to be having
some satellite difficulties.
But, before we lose you
completely, Simone,
I just want to say
thank you.
Thank you, Frank.
Goodbye.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Simone.
I've been here before.
On my honeymoon
with my ex-wife.
Yeah, look.
It's the exact
same tree.
And look
in the distance.
The mountain.
It's a hotel.
I don't understand.
Could they have built
that hotel since yesterday?
Get in the car.
Simone! Simone!
We don't do the photos,
you don't get the cover.
It's as simple as that.
Yes. Written answers
to written questions.
Didn't we have
this conversation before?
Yeah, web site interviews,
no problem.
I think people are gonna
love "Eternity Forever."
"Eternity Forever"
is my finest work.
I loved working
with the director
of "Eternity Forever."
He's a genius.
You wish.
It's wonderful being
a movie star.
But there's so many other ways
I want to express myself.
But it's not enough
to be a movie star.
You have to be
a pop star, too.
If you really want
to make a difference.
Nice boat, Taransky!
It's not a boat,
it's a yacht.
I know
what you're up to.
You know, I really
don't have time for this.
I think you do,
'cause I know it's a fake.
It's bogus.
You used an old library shot
for the background.
She never
was in New Mexico.
She never even left
the studio.
I've done my homework.
- I've studied her.
- I bet you have.
I've looked at every piece
of publicity she's done.
And as far as I can tell,
there's no evidence
that she has ever left
the studio.
Oh...
And for some reason,
this woman leaves
no paper trail?
Now, I've obtained a copy
of your bank account.
I know you have
power of attorney,
but so far,
you have not turned over
a single solitary cent
to this woman.
I keep it in a trust.
I know that's what you want
people to believe,
but I gotta tell you,
embezzlement
is a serious matter.
Not to mention abduction.
- Abduction?
- Yeah.
Off the record.
I want to know
how you're doing it.
Is it drugs?
Is it mind control?
Is it blackmail?
Is it all three?
What do you do? Do you keep her
locked in a box somewhere?
What is it exactly
that you want?
I want to see her.
Unless you show me
Simone live and in person,
I show these photos
to the authorities.
You want to see her?
All right.
You've got a deal.
You want to see her?
You're gonna see her!
Good!
Mr. Taransky.
- Hello, gentlemen.
- We're all ready.
This time tomorrow night,
she'll be standing right here
in front of 100,000 people.
We could've sold
this out 20 times.
Yeah, the sound check
went great.
The laser show
is good to go.
I gotta ask you,
though,
you ordered
an awful lot of smoke.
Well, that's the way
she wants it.
After you told us
about the death threats,
security guards
are under strict instructions
never to take their eyes
off the crowd.
Excellent. Here, Simone wanted
you to have these.
- Unreal.
- And remember--
no cameras,
no binoculars.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Viktor Taransky Promotions
is proud to present Simone--
live on stage
for the debut concert
of the Splendid Isolation tour.
Let's get you into hair
and make-up.
No.
Yes.
You know, it's easier
to make 100,000 believe
than just one?
And now, the one,
the only, Simone!
I love you...
LA.
It's great to be here.
# Looking out #
# On the morning rain #
# I used
to feel so inspired #
# And when I knew I had
to face another day #
# Lord, it made me feel
so tired #
# Before the day I met you #
# Life was so unkind #
# But you're the key
to my peace of mind #
# 'Cause you make me feel #
# You make me feel #
# You make me feel
like a natural woman #
# Oh, baby #
# What you've done to me #
# Done to me #
# You make me feel
so good inside #
# Good inside #
# And I just wanna be #
# Wanna be #
# Close to you,
you make me feel so alive #
# 'Cause you make me feel #
# You make me feel #
# You make me feel
like a natural woman #
# You make me feel #
- # You make me feel #
# You make me feel
like a real... #
# You make me feel #
# Feel like a... #
# You make me feel
like a real... #
Thank you.
Never stop believing.
Yeah! Simone!
# What you've done to me #
# Natural woman. #
I said I didn't want
to be disturbed!
Viktor.
My two favorite girls
in all the world.
We just stopped by
to congratulate Simone.
Well, you know...
she's lying down.
She's exhausted.
Yeah, I can imagine.
Listen, thank Simone
for the tickets, okay?
That's a good color
on you.
It was
a great show, Dad.
I can't believe
she's doing this.
Taking advantage
of him this way.
- It's cruel.
- Why?
Obviously, this can't last.
She's gonna dump him.
Viktor won't be able to take that,
he's too sensitive.
This'll destroy him.
Elaine, do you realize
that you can't stop
talking about Viktor?
I have to talk to her.
I've been meaning
to talk to you.
I'm starting to feel
like I don't exist.
Dad?
Oh, hi, baby.
Thank you.
So how's your love life?
I do okay.
What about you?
Well, you know me.
Married to my work.
I noticed.
You know I don't like
to get between you and mom,
but she's feeling
down right now.
She broke up with Kent.
She thinks
you're with Simone.
Ah, Lainey.
That's so ridiculous.
I don't have
a relationship with Simone.
I know, I know,
but Mom doesn't.
Maybe if Simone spoke
to her she could
straighten things out.
Dinner maybe.
Dinner?
I don't know
about dinner.
That'd be difficult,
I think.
- Maybe a phone call?
- It's too impersonal.
They have to meet
face-to-face.
Well, I'll think
of something.
The escalating violence,
tragic loss of human life,
and threat of all-out war
was overshadowed today
by the announcement
of the Oscar nominations.
- Hello?
- Is this Elaine?
- Who's this?
- Oh my God. Is that you, Simone?
- Yes.
- You look beautiful today.
- Thanks, I--
- Where are you?
- I'm right here.
Beside you.
- Oh!
- I borrowed Viktor's car.
- Hi!
- Hi.
I'm really late.
I would love to talk to you,
But I'm on my way
to see Viktor right now.
Simone, I know what's
going on between you two.
Oh? No. Oh, Elaine,
there's absolutely nothing.
It's strictly
a working relationship.
I just don't want
to see Viktor get hurt.
Sounds to me like you still
have feelings for him.
Well, we have
a daughter together.
I don't love Viktor.
I could never love anyone.
I'm in love with the camera.
Simone, I recognize
the coat you're wearing.
I gave it to Viktor
on his birthday.
Christ.
Elaine, I just--
Whoa.
God! Oh my God!
I tell ya.
- Are you all right?
- This does look awful. I know that.
But, Viktor,
he's just so crazy about you.
Could you go
to the Oscars with him?
No, no, no.
If you won't do it
for him,
I ask you, please,
do it for me.
Okay. Okay.
For you.
For you I'll go.
Thank you.
Well, here's my exit.
All right.
I'm glad that we talked.
- Oh, yes. Bye.
- Bye!
Goodbye.
Oh!
And, the winner
of Best Actress...
is...
Oh, my goodness.
We have a tie.
The winners are Simone
for "Sunrise, Sunset"...
Thank you.
...and Simone
for "Eternity Forever."
Unfortunately, Simone cannot
be with us here tonight
but thanks to the miracle
of modern technology,
she joins us live from her
Goodwill Tour of the third world.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Simone!
Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
This means
so much to me.
I'm just sorry I couldn't
be there with you.
First, I want to acknowledge
my fellow nominees.
I don't even feel I belong
in the Best Actress category,
Iet alone with these
wonderful human beings.
And I also wanna thank
my co-stars
and the studio, of course.
And as always,
I dedicate this to Hank,
without whom none of this
would be possible.
I love you, Hank,
wherever you are.
Thank you.
Who's Hank?
Her agent?
- Her father.
- Oh.
Why didn't
she thank you?
She did.
Didn't she?
No.
And of course,
I must thank my collaborator,
Viktor Taransky,
without whom none
of this would be possible.
And of course,
I must thank my collaborator,
Viktor Taransky,
without whom none
of this would be possible.
Why didn't I say it?
How could I forget
to say it?
I wrote it.
And of course,
I must thank my collaborator,
Viktor Taransky,
without whom none
of this would be possible.
Excuse me, Mr. Taransky,
Are you ready
for your casting session?
Nicola is here for the role
of Simone's sister.
Viktor.
So much has happened since
we last saw each other.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
- Why don't you sit?
- Thank you.
I never got a chance
to properly apologize
for what happened
on "Sunrise."
Oh, that's okay.
I know. I understand.
When I saw what Simone
did with the role,
I mean,
I fired all my people.
I went into rehab.
I took some acting classes.
I changed my whole look.
She really,
really inspired me.
Would you like me
to read?
Oh, sure.
That would be good.
Who do you think
you are, Carlos,
coming in here
like this?
My husband's sleeping
in the next room.
You think
I won't call out?
Do you think
I'll just...
give in to you
without a fight,
Iike I did the last time
and the time before that?
I wish you were dead.
I wish we were both dead.
Oh...
that was just wonderful.
Wonderful acting.
Thank you.
You could play the lead.
Isn't that Simone's part?
Of course.
Of course it is.
You have such
a beautiful line,
right, right there.
It's not a wrinkle,
or anything,
it's like a dimple.
Right--
when you smile it--
I was thinking
of incorporating
something like that
in Simone.
Cosmetically altering
Simone to look like me?
Oh, yeah.
That would be crazy.
Yes...
that would be nuts.
Would you like me to try something
different with this, or do it again?
No, it's fine.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you, Viktor.
Happy birthday, Lainey.
What do you think?
It's fantastic.
It's what she drove
in "Eternity Forever."
- I know.
- See?
- You have to thank her for me.
- It's from both of us.
You know,
you won't be able
to drive it till you get
your permit,
but you can take it around
the lot, okay?
Here.
What's the matter?
I can't accept it.
Why?
Why, honey?
I don't want a car, Dad.
What do you want?
I'll give you
whatever you want.
The old Viktor Taransky.
I can't stand
to see you like this,
clinging to Simone's
coattails.
It used to be
all about the work
and now it's all about her.
And then she's not even grateful
enough to thank you.
Oh, no, that was me.
There you go again,
blaming yourself.
Can't you see
what she's done to you?
She's taken advantage.
Mocking you.
You deserve better
than Simone.
- I have to go, Dad.
- Okay.
Oh, sure.
She comes in all the time.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- Is she nice?
- We've become very close.
She told me she wanted to look
at my script next week.
- Jane?
- Gotta go.
I'm leaving early.
If anybody needs me,
I'll be at the beach house
having dinner
with a certain someone.
Elaine Christian, please.
Elaine.
Hi.
I was in the neighborhood.
I just thought I'd drop by.
You don't use
the front door anymore?
Uh... no.
When is she coming over?
- About now.
- Oh.
Okay. I'll just stay
until she gets here.
Well, she's...
already here.
What?
Elaine...
Simone is not coming
over tonight
or any other night.
- I want you back, Elaine.
- I want you back, too.
Oh, Viktor!
Wait! Viktor!
This is crazy.
Who are we kidding?
I can't compete
with Simone.
- Well...
- What woman can?
I'd rather have you
than Simone.
- Believe me.
- Oh.
That's so sweet.
No, but I can't
let you do that,
make that kind
of sacrifice.
- No. No.
- God, this is strange.
You know, I have stabbed
people in the back
and clawed and slept
my way to where I am.
- but--
- You have?
Well, it goes
with the territory.
For some reason,
I can't betray Simone.
I can't.
There's a goodness to her, Viktor.
- No, there's nothing to her.
- Oh, Viktor.
You say that now,
but in the morning
you would
go back to her.
- No. No.
- You would, Viktor.
She's gonna retire.
She'll never work again.
Of course she will.
Her public will demand it.
- Not if I don't let her.
- You?
- Yeah.
- How can you stop her?
I'm gonna tell you
a secret now, Elaine.
Simone isn't
a real person.
I invented her.
Every actor
is an invention.
- Elaine--
- Please.
You're lucky she's loyal enough
to stay with you.
Maybe she's staying
out of pity.
Who knows? I mean,
she certainly doesn't need you.
Listen,
she's thin air.
- She's pixels.
- What?
Computer code molded by me
from a mathematical equation
I inherited from a madman.
How much have you had
to drink?
There's no Simone.
- I'm Simone.
- You're Simone?!
I've done the impossible.
I have recreated
the infinite nuances
of a human being--
a human soul.
I have taken nothing,
and made it something.
I have breathed life
into a machine.
- I made a miracle.
- Viktor, please stop.
- Please.
- I swear, Elaine.
As God is my judge,
I swear.
I made Simone.
I made her.
- You made Simone?
- Yes.
Viktor...
she made you.
You bitch.
I'll destroy you.
Bravo!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Had a rough night?
Let's see if they still
love you after this.
You made me.
I made you first.
Well, we're back
on "Good Morning, Good Day,"
and we are here once again
with the incomparable Simone.
Simone, before the break
you were taking a rather
controversial position.
I just think
all elementary schools
should have a firing range.
How else can the children learn
to defend themselves?
If there is a hole
in the ozone layer,
how come I can't see it?
Immigration? God!
Isn't it crowded enough?
But God created
furry animals to be worn.
Have you ever tasted
dolphin?
Pan-fried with a little
garlic and fennel.
Everybody always talks about
the negatives of cigarettes.
But look at the benefits.
I mean, you don't eat
as much.
And you've got something
to hold in your hand.
We always knew Simone
wasn't like other celebrities.
- Oh, no.
- She speaks her mind.
She certainly does.
It's plastic, Hank.
I know that's the way
you'd want it.
She killed you, Hank.
Now she's killing me.
She's a serial killer.
But I don't know
how to stop her.
I mean, she's taken on
a life of her own.
I can't just come clean,
you know,
make some confession,
because...
I've defrauded millions.
They'd turn on me.
I just can't
put the genie
back in the bottle,
because...
if she suddenly
stopped working,
you know, just dropped
out of sight,
they'd never let it rest.
I tried killing
her career,
but they like her
even more.
What am I gonna do?
Not another word, Hank.
You are truly a genius.
Thank you, Hank.
Thank you.
What's the matter,
Viktor?
You look so sad.
Don't you love me anymore?
It's over, isn't it?
I know what you're thinking,
Simone.
This is
a phoney-baloney world.
We're all living
one big lie.
So, why shouldn't
you live, too?
You're more authentic than
all these people who worship you.
And that's the problem.
You're looking
at the real fraud.
I told myself this was
all about the work.
But if that were the truth,
it wouldn't matter to me
that you get
all the attention.
And it does.
It does.
I'm sorry, Simone.
Here I was trying
to convince
the whole world
you existed.
but what I was really
trying to do
was convince them
that I exist.
It's not that
you aren't human.
It's that I am.
I'm sorry, Simone.
It is my sad...
and solemn duty...
to announce...
the tragic passing
of Simone.
How did she die?
It was a rare virus
she contracted
on her Goodwill Tour
of the third world.
Did she suffer?
Mercifully, it was quick.
I feel awful.
It's a great loss.
You know, we're going to
have to restructure your deal.
Can I see you later?
I mean, go away
for the weekend?
How could you bring that up
at a time like this?
One minute, Mr. Taransky.
Oh my God.
This has got to be a mistake.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be
used against you in a court of law.
- You don't understand.
- Viktor!
- It's a mistake!
- I'll call my attorney.
Dad!
Elaine, call Bernard!
That's why
it was so light.
I heard him say,
"Die, bitch.
I'll destroy you."
It was so strange.
He actually wanted
to replace Simone with me
in his new movie.
He's a sick man.
He was a controlling madman.
She was a prisoner.
I blame myself.
I wish I had done more
to stop it.
Forgive me, Mr. Taransky.
I'm just trying
to understand here.
Now, all these films
and TV appearances
and magazine covers
and internet interviews,
publicity photos,
snapshots from her childhood...
All fake? Hmm?
This is fake.
Fake, fake, fake,
fake, fake.
- All fake?
- Yes.
You understand perfectly.
So, I will confess
to fraud
but not to murder.
And a fan club
with a worldwide membership
in the millions,
that's also bogus?
No. No.
The fan club's real.
It's just what
they were worshipping
is a computer code.
Ones and zeroes.
You couldn't have killed Simone
because there was no Simone.
- Right. Exactly.
- And this Hank Aleno
that you keep
talking about,
the renowned failure who also
happens to be so conveniently dead,
now, perhaps this man
that you claim helped invent Simone,
is an invention himself.
Oh, no. No.
This whole thing is insane!
There is no Simone!
Look.
Even her name is fake.
It's not Simone.
It's "Sim One"-- See?
"Simulation One"!
It's a computer code!
You really hated her,
didn't you?
Perhaps you could explain
this to me, Mr. Taransky.
Or is this tape doctored, too?
This is footage from the marina's
closed-circuit camera
on the night in question--
altered of course.
Can you tell us
why you're disposing
of the body of a woman
who doesn't exist?
Well, it's not her body.
It's her body of work.
Viktor, Viktor, Viktor.
Viktor.
I know. Look.
Look. Look.
Why don't you just
come clean? Huh?
Just tell the truth,
you're gonna feel better afterwards.
I'm telling the truth,
and I don't feel so good.
Hey, we all know
what happened.
In a fit of jealous rage,
you killed Simone and you dumped
her body off the boat...
- Don't say that.
- ...that she bought for you.
I did--
I can prove--
I can prove it
to you.
Let me just
take you there.
I'll take you
to the spot.
I can prove it.
Here. Here.
Come on.
We can just go there,
can't we?
- Let's just go. I'll take you there.
- Oh, Viktor.
Okay, good.
Thank you.
Good work.
Now you'll see.
What is this?
No, there's drives
and discs.
Where are the discs?
You have to go back down
and get them.
- That's where they are.
- We can't go back down there.
- There's discs down there!
- Calm yourself!
- Please! Just--
- Sit him down.
You must go down
and get the drives.
Hey, you see what's
down there?
Plead guilty.
Plead guilty
and throw yourself
on the mercy
of the court.
It's the best deal
you're gonna get.
I could get
the death penalty.
Yeah. Yeah.
You certainly will
if you go to trial.
A jury, in this kind
of ugly mood.
You killed an icon,
for God's sake.
- Bernard, listen to me!
- Viktor!
Bernard,
I didn't kill anyone.
Viktor, come on,
it's in the paper.
There's no one to kill.
Bernard,
I'm a filmmaker.
I was trying
to say something.
I wanted recognition.
I wanted
to be appreciated.
So I created her.
Bernard,
there's no one to kill.
Do you understand?
An insanity defense.
Beautiful.
Fantastic.
- What are you doing?
- "I created her."
Viktor! Jesus!
Jesus Christ, Viktor!
What am I doing?
Oh, what am I doing?
- Get me out!
- Viktor!
Get me another lawyer.
I want another lawyer!
Why can't people just
take responsibility
for their actions
anymore, huh?
You know, I can almost
forgive him for killing her.
But, to deny her existence?
I can never forgive that.
Because obviously
she existed, right?
I know it just as surely
as you're sitting there.
She was the most
vital woman I ever met.
So you did meet her?
Yeah, Lainey,
what are you getting at?
I'm the head
of a major studio.
Do you think I'm gonna make
a three-picture deal
with an actress
I never met?
No. No.
I mean, really meet her.
Like in the flesh.
I know it's embarrassing
to admit it,
but when I think about it
honestly, I haven't.
I've never really seen
Simone up close...
touched her.
Been in her physical presence.
Have you?
Well--
we don't want
to believe daddy
because we don't want to believe
that we were taken in too.
But, Lainey,
there's no evidence
that Simone isn't real.
Listen to what
you're saying, Mom.
I mean, is there
any evidence that she is?
Do you have any idea
what you're doing?
What's that?
One part of Dad's story
may have been true.
Simone may have
contracted a virus.
Certain viruses
can be cured.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Listen to me.
There's a psychiatrist
in Ventura,
well-respected,
who is willing to testify
under oath that you have
diminished capacity
due to the trauma
of your divorce,
10 years of abject failure
in the movie business
and a bump on the head
you sustained as a child.
No more.
I can't go along
with this horseshit.
- Come on, Viktor.
- I did it.
No. No.
Viktor, come on.
- Tell them they can fry me.
- No, Viktor, please.
- I did it!
- Viktor, please.
It was premeditated!
- Can you please lower your voice?
- I strangled her.
I bludgeoned her!
I set her on fire
and then I killed her!
- I did it!
- Excuse me.
I think you better
see this.
Breaking news:
International media star
Simone is alive and well.
Her studio released this footage,
just minutes ago.
Simone reading today's edition
of "The LA Times."
Who says the only bad publicity
is your obituary?
Details at the top
of the hour.
She's indestructible.
He's coming.
Viktor.
Oh, Viktor.
Oh, honey.
I don't know what you did
or how you did it,
- but thank you.
- Well, it was Lainey.
But don't thank us
too fast.
You know what we have
to do now.
What?
Well, why stop
at one character
when you can have
a whole cast?
You have to finish
what you started.
We can do it together.
- Haven't we done enough?
- Could we go, please?
Where we going?
Well, I was thinking...
how about you and Simone,
moving in with me and Lainey?
That's wonderful.
What do you think, Lainey?
About you and Mom?
Well, about me and Simone.
What I did.
Everything.
I'm sorry.
Your mistake wasn't
making something fake, Dad.
We're fine with fake.
As long as you don't lie
about it.
Oh, come on, Viktor.
It's not
a death sentence.
No. It's life.
Hey, Viktor,
remember us?
We probably never met.
I'm Milton.
How are you?
Max Sayer from the Echo.
- Hi!
- It's life.
Just call.
Five minutes.
All we need
is five minutes.
Good evening,
and welcome.
Simone, the question
on everybody's mind
is simply... why?
Frank, you know
as well as I do,
Iiving in this fish-bowl,
the insatiable appetite
of the media,
with everything
that was going on in my life,
I just needed to drop out
of sight for a while.
I ju
I needed time,
and Viktor bought me that time.
- I owe him so much.
- We all do.
But now I understand
you're eager
to get back to work
and it's not the kind
of work
we were all expecting.
It's true.
I can reveal I am considering
a career in politics.
And what, may I ask,
brought this on?
I suppose this little man
had something to do with it.
- That beautiful baby.
- Yes.
You see, Viktor and I
are both very concerned
about what kind of world
our new son, Chip,
is going to grow up in.
Aren't you, Viktor?
Oh, yes.
Hi.
Oh yes.
# Looking out #
# On the morning rain #
# I used to feel
so inspired #
# And when I knew
I had to face another day #
# Lord, it made me feel so tired #
# Before the day I met you #
# Life was so unkind #
# You're the key
to my peace of mind #
# 'Cause you make me feel #
# You make me feel #
# You make me feel
like a natural woman #
# When my soul was
in the lost and found #
# You came along to claim it #
# And didn't know
what was wrong with me #
# Till your kiss helped me name it #
# Now I'm no longer
doubtful #
# To what I'm living for #
# And if I make you happy #
# I don't need to do more #
# 'Cause you make me feel #
# You make me feel #
# You make me feel
like a natural woman #
# Woman #
# Oh, baby, what you've done to me #
# Done to me #
# You make me feel
so good inside #
# Good inside #
# And I just wanna be #
# Wanna be #
# Close to you,
you make me feel so alive #
# 'Cause you make me feel #
# You make me feel #
# You make me feel
like a natural woman #
# You make me feel #
# You make me feel
like a real... #
# You make me feel #
# Feel like a real... #
# You make me feel
like a real... #
She likes
chicken pot pie...
just like me.