Presented by
Raymond Chow Man Wai
Producer
Leonard Ho Koon-Cheung
Planning
Jackie Chan, Corey Yuen Kwai
Starring
Jackie Chan
Sammo Hung
Yuen Biao
Co-starring Deannie Yip Tak Han,
Pauline Yeung Bo Ling
Production Manager Corey Yuen Kwai
Production Planning Woo Po Chiu
Script Szeto Cheuk-Hon
Story Leung Yiu Ming and Gordon Chan
- Have some tea.
- No, thanks.
Executive Director
Corey Yuen Kwai
Director
Sammo Hung
Brother Wah, we achieved what
we have today through violence.
But times have changed.
We can't be criminals forever. Can we?
That's true.
Brother Wah, let me get to the point.
Your man seized my cargo at
West ShaTin two days ago.
Stop the nonsense, these matters are trivial.
Brother Wah, are you
denying your involvement?
No, l accept full responsibility.
- Where's the payment?
- Your cargo can't be sold without refining.
We'll settle our account slowly.
- Next time, be careful.
- Wah, you...
A mistake on your side cost you two lives.
lt's a misunderstanding.
Brother Wah, please don't kill me.
Don't kill me.
- OK, l won't kill you.
- Thank you, Brother Wah.
Thank you, Brother Wah.
Brother Wah, you said you wouldn't kill me.
lt wasn't me.
Boss, how about him?
Unemployed now?
Start work for me tomorrow.
Thank you, Boss Wah.
- Want some money?
- What do you mean?
Nothing, l just thought you might need it.
- Any conditions?
- Forget about Cheng.
No way. l'll get him, no matter what.
- How dare he rape me?
- Trust me, it's for your own good.
For my own good? ln what way?
You'll definitely lose this case.
lnstead of offending the bully,
you'd be better off keeping the money
and winning a friend.
You're not the judge,
how do you know l'll definitely lose?
We'll meet in court.
Mr Lung, can't you convince her?
- Who are you?
- They are Cheng's good-for-nothings.
Watch your words, bitch.
Don't do anything foolish.
Mr Lung, you have your job,
l have mine, OK?
Enough. lt's none of your business.
Help me.
Help.
Come out.
- Please stop. Don't hit me.
- Go back and...
Are you all right?
Stop pretending. You're with them.
l'm not acting.
Objection. Counsel is judging
the plaintiff's morals.
Nightclub girls make their living honestly,
it's nothing immoral.
ln real life, immorality doesn't cost anything.
Objection overruled.
To save time and taxpayers' money
on this case,
the defendant would make
a plea of no contest.
As the statement made
by the plaintiff is suspicious,
l ask your honour to acquit the defendant.
Legally, the defendant
hasn't raped the plaintiff.
Ethically, he might have made a mistake.
Objection. The defence is misleading.
The court observes law, not ethics.
Objection sustained.
Delete the defence counsel's last words.
Your Honour, l rest my case.
Defendant Mo Shih Cheng, please rise.
Before the verdict,
l must thank both the counsels.
The prosecution's presentation
has been terse and to the point.
The defence's plea of no contest
has saved the court time and money.
This court now finds
the defendant not guilty.
With no right of appeal.
The defendant is released forthwith.
Court dismissed.
Court.
Thank you, Lawyer Lung.
How could you hit him in court?
lf he doesn't sue you, the court will.
- l know.
- Why did you do it?
Are you my boss or my assistant?
l'm your assistant hired by your boss.
- Where are you going?
- Court 2, a wife-beating case.
- After that?
- Lunch.
l'm going for lunch too.
Should l wait for you?
- How about that?
- OK, see you at the entrance at 12.
Let's go. What were you saying?
l was saying that
l'm your assistant hired by your boss.
This isn't an appropriate time
to discuss that.
- Where are you going?
- Toilet.
- After that?
- Leave the toilet.
- Then?
- Guess?
- Go for coffee?
- OK.
- Don't see you much lately.
- You didn't call.
- l'll see you later.
- OK.
Casanova.
Let's go.
Boss.
Miss Yip, how do you do?
Have you thought it over seriously?
l don't want any compensation.
l want your factory to stop production
until the drainage system
has been improved.
Your factory keeps pouring
waste water into my fish pond.
My fish are nearly all dead.
How much is your fish farm? l'll buy it.
Money is not everything. l'm not selling.
You don't sound like
a wise businesswoman.
Every business has a code of ethics.
We have to look after our environment.
l don't understand.
Miss Yip, l'm a businessman.
l only care about my profit.
l don't care about other things.
Tell me the sum and l'll pay accordingly.
l won't stop production in my factory.
How much is your factory worth? l'll buy it.
The negotiation is over.
l'll apply for a court injunction
to stop your factory production.
See you in court then, Miss Yip.
Boss, l'll settle her.
Shut up. Get a new lawyer to play with her.
lt'll be a time-consuming case.
- Don't let the case affect our production.
- Yes.
- Have some tea.
- Thank you.
- Lawyer Mun, it's been a while.
- You hardly go to the races.
l've been out at sea mostly.
Let me introduce you to Miss Wen,
a lecturer in geography and ecology.
- She's also our main witness in the case.
- Hello.
This is Lawyer Lung,
he's in charge of this case.
- Hi.
- Lawyer Mun, let's get to the point.
- Good.
This is the report.
Lawyer Mun, can we settle this out of court?
Yes, your client's factory
can stop production
and solve the waste water problem
immediately.
My client can pay any
compensation but can't stop.
My client can pay any price
for your factory to stop.
Good, both our standpoints are quite clear.
Right. Whether we win or lose,
we'll be paid anyway.
What standard did you use
to determine the water quality?
The 1986 standard of the
Commonwealth Health Organisation.
Commonwealth? ls it complicated?
lt's not simple, or l wouldn't
have to spend years studying it.
True. l must take you out for dinner
so you can explain the standard to me.
Everything you need to know is in the report.
That signals the end of the meeting.
- l have to rush to court.
- OK.
- Let's go for tea sometime.
- l'll go first.
- OK.
- l'll see her out.
- Thank you.
lf you attend court late,
you can do one more case.
- Miss Wen, where are you going now?
- The library.
- After that?
- Lunch.
Me too, should we lunch together?
- No.
- Why not?
- l'm used to eating alone.
- Me too.
l hate eating in a big group.
Should we have Japanese?
- No.
- How about Korean?
l'm not lunching with you.
Hey, it's just lunch.
No big deal.
Another failed attempt?
You should go for a big lunch
to console yourself.
Everything here is impressive.
This is a .38, similar
to the ones used by undercovers.
HK$700 each, ten per cent off.
This is a .45 Colt. Your comrades
should be familiar with this.
HK$1200 each. l have more.
This is top. M1 17 automatic rifle.
One cartridge can fire 15 bullets. Nonstop.
lf the cops see you with this, they'll run.
- ls it convincing?
- Let me show you.
The sound and the sparks make it look real.
- l want them all.
- Thank you.
Less 20 per cent, HK$77,000.
Fatty, what do you want?
Sorry, cash. No credit.
Hey, we were referred by Big Brother Seng.
l even sold him some
grenades without a discount.
lf we had HK$77,000,
we wouldn't need to rob.
How do you rob when you're broke?
l've an idea.
Look.
HK$15 each. Buy one, get one free.
Have these watermelon knives.
Fatty, haven't you heard
of the formidable revolutionary warriors?
You bastards. Trying to bully me?
Do you know what l did before l sold guns?
l was a fight instructor.
Hello.
- Wong Fei Hung, what are you doing?
- What? l just finished fighting.
Fighting? See you
at the usual place in half an hour.
What's in it for me?
Something rewarding.
ls this the reward?
This fish farm costs HK$10 million.
15 per cent commission,
isn't that rewarding?
- Yeah, but it's not that easy.
- l won't have called you if it was easy.
Get lost.
- Scram, now.
- Miss Yip, please calm down.
Don't let me see you here again
or l'll douse you with gasoline.
l've lots of money. l won't sell my fish farm.
How is it?
No problem. Please go back now.
- Hey... hey...
- You're a thief.
Hey, l'm Jackie.
Hey, don't...
Don't...
Don't you recognise me?
- Who are you?
- Are you blind? l'm Jackie.
- l can't tell.
- l'm...
Hey, it's me.
- Jackie?
- That's what l said.
What is it?
- What's happening?
- l saw someone earlier.
- That was me.
- What are you doing here?
l'm looking for the light switch.
Are you blind or what?
Here it is.
Do you want a coffee?
Why did you want to see me?
l want you to use your Kung Fu skills
to bug a house for me.
How could you keep fish like that?
No sugar, no milk.
That will spoil the purity of the coffee.
Don't you know?
l know.
What did you say before?
l wanted you to...
The last sentence.
l was asking why
you keep your fish like that.
The fish symbolises my life.
Keep going forward and never turns back.
- What are you here for?
- l want you to bug a house for me.
Let me air the room first.
These birds are capitalist.
These fish are communist.
They are two different ideologies.
Do you understand?
No, l only know
they'll eventually die in your hands.
- Why are you here?
- l want you to bug a house for me.
How could you do such an unethical thing?
Should l hold a knife to her neck
and ask her to tell you everything?
Good idea, but let's pretend
l didn't mention anything.
No.
You're my friend.
Your problem is my problem.
l'll help you. Why are you here?
l wanted you to bug a house for me.
Don't laugh. Are you serious?
lnitially.
This society is too pressurising.
You are mentally ill.
Yes.
- Who the hell are you looking for?
- Who are you?
- Why are you in my house?
- Your house? Which one?
Block A, 9 Lok Yeung road.
This is Block B, Block A is next door.
l'm sorry, l must have made a mistake.
Why are you so clumsy?
l'm sorry. l'm new here.
l won't be as clumsy in the future.
- Are you all right?
- l'm sorry.
- l can help you with the luggage.
- All right. Thanks a lot.
- l'm sorry for the inconvenience l caused.
- Don't worry, we're neighbours.
Stay for a while.
No, thank you.
- You want some tea?
- No, thank you. No, thank you.
Nothing for you?
No. Bye.
No problem, at least we met.
Strangers are friends you haven't met.
We'll eventually be good friends.
l met them yesterday to see
if we could settle out of court.
lf we could have settled out of court,
l wouldn't have applied for the injunction.
A court case could be a waste of time.
Did you get anything
unusual from the meeting?
Their lawyer asked me out to dinner.
That's not unusual.
A lawyer asking me out would be unusual.
Cousin, you shouldn't be pessimistic.
l'm not pessimistic, l'm just plain stupid.
When l was young, l was too choosy.
Since we're cousins, l'll be frank with you.
lt's really stupid
to remain choosy at your age.
l'm not choosy at all.
As long as they are healthy,
l don't care for shape or size.
They don't even need to have a job.
Ambition and responsibilty
are not important.
Any man would do?
Any man would do.
Yes, as long as he doesn't have a pot belly.
Attack! Beware of the enemy.
Be alert.
No obstacle.
Move in again.
Hey, hey. Did you accept the lawyer's date?
- Why not?
- Why should l accept the date?
At least you can find out
more about the case.
Right?
Ah Ling, l need your help here.
Shit, the receiver is not waterproof.
Hey! Are you a burglar?
Go and die, go and die!
Come back.
lf you slip through my fingers,
l'll catch you with my legs.
You can't escape.
What's happening?
- What are you doing?
- He's a burglar, l caught him stealing.
- Burglar!
- Go and call the police.
Everything is fine now.
We finally caught him.
Either of you could be the burglar.
This is Mr Wong, our new neighbour.
Thank you, Mr Wong.
Don't mention it. As neighbours,
we should look out for each other.
- You're too reckless.
- How is it?
You're on bail, let's go.
Do l have to go to jail? l can't go to jail.
- l can't even breathe here. Help me!
- OK.
l failed in the mission,
but you still have to help me.
OK, let's go.
- You can go now.
- Thank you.
Hey, let's take the lift.
No, l can't breathe in lifts.
l'll take the stairs.
OK, let's go then.
You go home first, l'll join you later.
- Hey, what a coincidence.
- Yeah, what a surprise.
This is Lawyer Lung,
representing Wah Chemicals.
- He's the one.
- Wah Chemicals.
This is my cousin, she owns Yip Fish Farm.
Nice to see you.
lt'd be nicer if we weren't
in the police station.
- Besides, we'll meet in court soon.
- That's true.
- Miss Wen.
- Yes?
- This afternoon...
- Are you asking her out?
- Yes, is it OK?
- Are you asking her or me?
lf you're asking her, look at her and ask.
l can't do lunch.
- How about dinner?
- Great.
May l have your contact number, please?
l'll call you later to make arrangements.
What's your phone number?
Bite it tight. Your hands are too busy.
- Thank you.
- This sofa is more comfortable.
Sit here, this is the most comfortable
part of the whole sofa.
- lt feels good here as well.
- Really?
lt can't be. Let me try.
lt's true. l've never noticed the difference.
- Cheers.
- Did you spike my drink?
- What?
- l feel dizzy.
- lt's only just reached your stomach.
lt's a two-pronged attack.
Some of it has gone to my head.
Touch my head, is it very hot?
No.
Perhaps it's a case of self-indulgence.
lt's more like a case of infatuation.
- Hello.
- lt's Tung Te-Biu.
- What now?
- l'm in your room now.
- What?
'ln your room.'
Have a good rest, then. l'm with someone
right now, talk to you soon.
Where were we?
- Hello?
- lf you don't come in now, l'll come out.
Don't. l'll come right away. OK.
l've something for you.
lt's in my room, l'll go and get it.
Make yourself at home.
Hey. How did you get in?
- There. lt's quite easy to climb in.
- Hush, not so loud.
- l want to ask you something.
- What?
How could a righteous
and responsible man like me,
who is loyal to his friends
and contributes to society
be facing so much frustration
and psychological trauma?
You didn't understand my question?
l'll repeat it.
Jackie. Jackie.
A call for you.
Coming.
l'll answer your question later.
Stand back now.
- Here.
- 'lt's her?'
Thank you.
- Hello.
- 'Jackie, where are you?'
At home... Hello, hello...
- l thought you had something for me?
- Yeah, l'll get it.
Just a moment.
You're with the woman who sued me.
You don't need to bug her house to pull her.
Tell me honestly, what are you playing at?
ls my future of any importance to you?
Also, you've not answered my first question.
OK, give me one more night.
After tonight, you can ask
all the questions you want. OK?
Same way out. Go.
Go now.
- Where is it?
- l've made a mistake, it's not in my room.
- Can you guess what is it?
- l need to use the bathroom now.
Bathroom? lt's over there.
Hey, you haven't learnt.
You still keep your key under the mat.
The battery of my mobile went flat earlier.
l've good news for you.
l've moved next to the fish farm owner.
We're fast becoming friends.
You're her neighbour?
- One of the women is here.
- What?
Go and hide.
- Why switch off the lights?
- lsn't it more romantic like that?
- l prefer the lights on.
- OK then, we'll have a table lamp on.
Let's start our candlelit dinner.
- What happened?
- l'll check.
- What is it?
- Nothing, the dog tripped on the lamp.
- The dog tripped on the lamp?
- Nice coat. Where did you buy it?
l bought it when l was studying in Canada.
Good quality stuff.
l'll hang it up to avoid creases.
No way.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
What is that noise?
- Wood creaking in the dry weather.
- Oh.
Let's continue our dinner.
The steak is delicious.
l forgot to replace my cupboard last week.
lt must have cracked.
Don't let it affect our mood. Let's eat.
Stupid burglar.
First my neighbour, now my good friend?
Stupid, catch me if you can.
The timer on my radio is switched on.
l'll turn it off.
- Bastard.
- You're the bastard.
Stop fighting.
- Stop fighting.
- Burglar.
- Burglar, your mum!
- Don't involve my mum.
- He's my friend.
- ls he?
l caught him at my neighbour's last night.
l asked him to bug the house.
- ls he your friend?
- Yes.
He's your friend, the woman is your friend.
You asked me to bug your friend.
You sent a friend to catch me.
Am l your friend?
- That's no way to treat a friend!
- Misunderstandings.
You two calm down, please don't fight.
l'll get rid of the woman now
and explain everything.
Hey, look at me.
Don't fight.
l won't be long.
No fighting. OK?
- Go and die.
- You...
- What?
- What yourself?
What a nice dinner. Are you done?
Oh, you don't like beefsteak?
We'll have other meat next time.
- We should call it a day now.
- Why?
- l've not touched a thing yet.
- lt's fine.
See you soon.
Stop fighting. Stop it.
Can you two stop it?
Please.
l'm sorry.
- What happened to your eye?
- What did you say?
Really? l feel fine. Nothing happened.
- l forgot my coat.
- Wait here.
Watch out.
Your nose is bleeding.
Really? l feel fine.
You must be drunk. Bye-bye.
Stop.
Where's my table?
Let's see. lt's there.
Great.
- Hey, what now?
- That's my line. What now?
l don't care what you two are doing.
l'm sticking
to my plan of pulling that old woman.
l'll get her to sell the farm
and take 20 per cent commission.
Money is not as valuable
as a lot of other things.
True. Like gold, silver and diamonds...
l meant righteousness,
ethics and freedom. City pig.
What did you call me?
Stop quarrelling.
Don't worry. When l need to l'll beg
those women to drop their charges.
ls it worthwhile?
Your comment will earn
you a bump on the head.
That might be worthwhile.
Misbehaving in public could land you in jail.
Are you threatening me? Look, the place
is filled with good-for-nothings.
Suspicious character, you better behave.
The world is coming to an end.
We don't have many days left.
l won't spend
the last few days in jail, fuck off.
- l'm sorry.
- Hey, how could you hire him?
Don't point at me like that.
- What do you mean by that?
- l don't mean anything.
Quit the meaningless blabber
in my presence.
lt's only because he cares about you.
He wasn't like that in the past.
You've really changed a lot.
Man must keep evolving
to make life interesting.
Not like him, asking meaningless questions.
How boring.
Stay calm. Drink up.
Have a drink. Cheers.
- Boss Wah, this way please.
- After you.
- Peace from now on.
- Jackie.
- Hey.
- l'm with Boss Wah, l'll introduce you.
OK. You go first. l'll come over later.
Excuse me.
Maybe not. Let's go together. Come on.
Boss Wah, let me introduce...
This is Jackie Lung, a partner at my firm.
He's handling your case.
- Boss Wah.
- Lawyer Lung, my pleasure.
Whether my factory stops production
all depends on you.
l'll try my best. They're assisting me.
Boss Wah, l'll serve you well.
l'm very hard-working.
Boss Wah, your case is in Jackie's
capable hands, you shouldn't worry.
That's marvellous. Be at home.
Boss Wah, we're collecting
evidence against our opponent.
Boss, something's wrong.
What's happening?
A Child Praying To Guanyin. How's that?
- Stop.
You're blocking my view.
Stop fighting. Stop.
Stop.
Let's go.
- Don't run.
- Forget it.
l'm sorry to drag you into this.
People always wrongly identify
me as some other bad guy.
Wrongly identify?
You've so many men surrounding you.
They're all armed as well,
you can't be good.
Don't go.
Sorry, my friend is drunk.
Never mind, you three are good at fighting.
Fortunately you're working for me.
lf you were working for my enemy...
Don't say that you're my man in the future.
You lot were embarrassing.
Boss, l didn't know
they had two new fighters.
Fighters? What about you lot?
- Get rid of the lawyer.
- That lawyer is relatively unknown.
How could he be unknown
when he's all brain and brawn?
Would it take a tattoo
on his forehead for you to notice him?
- That ship is beautiful.
- The one l'm taking you to is nicer.
Hello, they're here.
This way, please.
Mr Lung. Miss Wen.
Do you like it?
- Yeah, but it's a bit too posh.
- Nothing is too posh for you.
Lunch itself is boring,
we need other perks to spice things up.
Wow, Jackie...
l hope this isn't an everyday meal for you.
That depends on whether
l'm eating with you.
- l'm not used to the attention.
- l'll do it myself next time.
This meal must be very expensive.
l'm throwing all my savings into this to make
up for what happened the other night.
You should keep
some of your savings for other girls.
l'll use the interest on them. Cheers.
Excuse me, l need the bathroom.
- Please show Miss Wen to the toilet.
- OK.
Miss Wen, this whole ship
has been hired by Mr Lung.
Do you want to try the Gents?
- No.
- This way, then.
Miss Wen, please.
Quick. He's upstairs.
Hurry.
What are you doing?
He's inside.
Don't lose him.
Jackie. Jackie.
What's happening?
- Today's date ends here.
- What?
Let's go.
You're drowning the plants.
Miss Yip, come here, please.
Yes, crimebusting hero.
What's my reward for being a hero?
- Do you want a pot of flowers?
- l want to spend an evening with you.
ln one evening, we can eat
a lot of things and chat a lot.
Since we're good neighbours,
why not be good friends?
Friends are for betraying...
Fewer friends, less betrayal.
- l'm willing to be betrayed by you.
- Your eyes have betrayed you.
They're telling me you're not sincere.
You're only interested in women.
l'm interested in finding a female friend.
Trust my mouth, not my eyes.
Your mouth has a scar, how can l trust it?
This scar belongs to the nose.
Don't get it wrong.
Be it right or wrong,
l appreciate the invitation. Bye-bye.
Don't reject me.
We're only going to eat together.
Let me go. All men are alike,
they only know about food and movies.
l know about other things too.
l keep them in my heart.
l'll wait for you at the Glasshouse tonight.
l won't come.
l'll wait till you come. Don't disappoint me.
You must come, l'll wait forever.
l'll wait till you show up.
l definitely won't come.
He's for real.
- Miss, l'd like to make a call.
- Sir, l'm also making a call.
Take your time.
l'll see how long he can last.
Stupid man, l thought he'd wait for me
forever. All men are unreliable.
What are you going to do?
Don't look around, just turn right.
l asked you out and you said no.
Then you turned up but wouldn't come in.
Walk away. Wherever you go, l'll follow.
Actions speak louder than words
in courtship...
Thank you for giving me the chance.
l know what's on your mind.
You wanted to see if l meant what l said.
l said l'll wait forever and l meant it.
Even if you don't trust me,
you'll have more self-confidence.
Don't you know that you're beautiful?
Roly-Poly, l wasn't talking to you,
don't get carried away.
l was talking to the lady next to you.
Hey, lady in the black fur coat.
Walk slower, don't run away from me.
One shouldn't rush on a path of love.
Give others and yourself a chance.
lt takes two to tango. Do you get me?
Hey, lady with a scarf
without a black fur coat.
Thanks for standing still
to ponder what l've said.
Don't bother, it's unimportant.
l just wanted us to be friends,
nothing complex.
Are you done?
Don't catch a cold.
l'm sorry. l went too far.
l couldn't think of any other way
to get your attention.
You're a moron.
You have all the attention you want now.
Do l know you?
Where would you like to dine?
You decide.
We're going for dinner now.
Please excuse us.
Dinner time. Please excuse us.
SPRlNG ROLL RESTAURANT
A warm feeling rushes to my ears
A cupid's arrow
is turning in my heart
A gentle touch joins us together
and sets my heart racing
My love will bring you warmth and joy
Happiness in your heart will rise and grow
The warmth you feel will never fade
when our hearts are joined
Happiness in your heart will rise and grow
The warmth you feel will never fade
Love is like an electric current
My love will bring you warmth and joy
Tell me honestly, are you dating me
just so you can win the case?
What about you?
Are you seeing me for the same reason?
l really don't care about winning the case.
When l lose one, l'll win another.
l get paid either way.
A good girlfriend is different.
l haven't met one in ten years.
When l met the right one,
she could have been spoken for.
A good man is hard to come by too.
Most good men are married.
Don't stare at me. You're not a good man.
Because l'm not married?
Are you all right?
lt's just a kiss. Why the slap?
lt just happened.
What do you want to do now?
Yes, it just happened.
What can l do now?
l'm sorry.
OK, you can slap me again.
You can even pull a knife on me.
Hit me one more time.
lt's boring to catch your own fish.
The pleasure of fishing
doesn't depend on getting the fish...
- lt depends on eating the fish?
- No.
The time you spend
waiting patiently for the fish...
That peace of mind you get
is pure pleasure.
Why do fishermen
have so many wrinkles then?
lf you're going to be difficult,
l won't talk to you.
Have you thought of selling the fish farm?
Why?
Sell it and come to Australia with me.
We'll open a dairy farm there.
We'll spend our time milking the cows...
Don't worry, we'll spend
most of our time on horseback,
riding on the emerald pastures,
looking out over the horizon.
Riding over the mountains,
free like a floating cloud
The freedom in the mountains
reflects peace in the city
The beauty of the crescent moon
Reflects peace in the city
ls this a marriage proposal?
Up to you. l'm an easy-going person.
- Can l tell you a secret?
- Yes.
My father put it in his will that whoever
marries me will inherit the fish farm.
Hey, why are you reacting this way?
That's a big secret.
Now l've something serious to hide.
l feel burdened by it.
lmpossible, that's my secret.
l'm not good at keeping things to myself.
l might blab it out one day.
That's why l feel pressurised.
Keep it like your own secret then.
- My own secret?
- Yes.
Do you feel better now?
Yes, much better.
lt feels different
to treat a secret as your own.
ln a place far, far away
there lives an old woman
Catch this.
- l got you there.
- You're evil.
Don't worry, l'm here.
No, go and see why the light went out.
Don't you think a dark world
for two people is romantic?
No. lf there's no power,
food in the fridge will spoil,
our rice and soup will all be half cooked,
there's still something in the oven...
- Go and see what happened.
- l'm no generator.
l can't help even if l know what happened.
lt's not short-circuited.
Who is it?
Jackie?
What happened?
Jackie, what happened?
- Someone is trying to harm us.
- What should we do?
Go to the sitting room with this,
count to three and turn it on.
- But...
- Go now, quickly.
Jackie, l've turned it on. What next?
Be careful.
What? Tung Te-Biu?
- Have you gone mad?
- l'm not mad.
- Do you know what you're doing?
- Yes, getting rid of a witness.
- Let me go.
- Cousin!
- Cut it out. What happened?
- None of your business.
- You're so rude.
- l'm better than you.
You just wanted her to sell the fish farm.
What did he just say?
Nothing, he's lying.
- Stop fighting.
Stop, stop.
- l can explain.
- Don't listen to him.
- Shut up.
- You shut up, it's all your fault.
You asked me to bug her house.
She's suing me and you don't care.
- You're despicable.
- Don't listen to him. He's lying.
Listen to me.
Ah Ling, let me explain,
things are not as complex as you thought.
- lt's a simple matter.
- lt's really simple.
Get out of my sight.
Ah Ling. Let me explain.
- Explain in court.
- Ah Ling!
Ah Ling.
You've ruined everything.
lt was ruined the minute
he caught me bugging the house.
l've told you, right? lt was a mistake.
- See who you hired.
- Hey, Ah Biu...
Enough... l can only depend on myself.
l know that this is a world without love.
l said l would help you win the case.
Win the case? You can't even win my trust.
- You two are useless.
- Haven't you had enough?
Are you taking it out on me? Come on.
- Don't push me so hard.
- l can't control...
- Big nose, you hit me?
- Any time.
And l can hit you any time.
We've called the police.
Keep on fighting, if you dare.
l've used all the tricks available to get
the Commisioner to drop the charges.
The three of you are too
old to fight in the street.
Excuse me.
Why were you fighting? Over women?
The skinny one fought over two women.
The fatty did it over a woman.
l did it over two men.
l got up early in the morning to get
you off the hook, what's my reward?
What do you say?
l'm lovelorn.
lf it was me you loved,
you wouldn't be lovelorn.
We've lost a lot of fish.
What should we do now?
That factory is manufacturing illegal drugs.
l don't believe you will stay there.
l don't believe you're not hitting the brake.
A good dog would not block the way.
- l'm not a good dog.
- Nor a good man.
- l'm a good man.
- You're a love cheat.
l didn't cheat you.
l invested emotionally as well.
- Really?
- Can't you feel it?
No, l've no feelings for you.
You wasted my time and emotion.
For a bit of commission,
you betrayed me and yourself.
- Why didn't you dodge?
- l wouldn't have come if l wanted to dodge.
- That was too risky.
- But not enough to kill him.
l was talking about you.
lf he got hold of the spanner, we'd be dead.
l'm not like that. Please let me explain.
lnitially, l did get
close to you for the commission.
After spending some time together,
l realise that l've fallen for you.
You just wanted to be
the boss of a fish farm.
lt did cross my mind,
but to prove my true love for you,
you can sell the farm
for charity before marrying me.
Sell the farm for charity?
Are we going to live on air?
l don't mind living on air.
As long as we don't have to live on shit.
Even if l don't sell the farm,
we'll have to live on air.
The factory kept dumping
waste water into our farm.
l'll check what they're doing in the factory.
- Get in the car, then.
- Yes.
Hey, why are you so obedient?
- Let's go, then.
- OK.
Your friend is here.
- Ah Ling.
- Say nothing, save it for the court.
- Take care.
- OK.
l want to help you but l can't.
l don't mean any harm, l just wanted
you to drop the case against me.
l'll drop the case
if you promise not to stalk me.
That is not a problem. l'm on my way.
Why are they against me and not you?
That's the power of love.
- Hey, do something for me?
- OK.
- l can't pay.
- l don't mind.
Come with me.
Hey...
- Hey, you don't have to act like that.
- l'm being cautious.
We'll split up now
and meet here in 20 minutes.
l've got you in shot
to prove that you're working.
Follow me.
What kind of factory is this?
How do you do?
Sorry to interrupt, l'm going now.
Bye-bye, see you later.
How is everybody doing?
- What's this?
- Nothing - a telescope.
- Give it back.
- Get him.
Don't move. You can't touch me.
Fatty. How did you get in?
Hi, how are you?
Don't move.
Don't let him escape.
OK, go for broke.
Get him.
Calm down, everyone,
that's the end of him.
Tie him up.
District Court civil case number 2346.
The Yip Fish Farm is applying for an
injunction against Wah Chemical Works
for continuing production.
The court will be presided over by Judge Lo.
Let me go. Why are you tying me up?
lf he wakes up, give him another jab.
Stupid Fatty.
Since l'm related to the plaintiff
and to show my impartiality in the case,
l've entrusted all specimen tests
to the Hong Kong University
Oceanography Department.
The results show that
the lead content in the water
is two per cent higher than normal.
And the oxygen is three per cent
lower than the standard.
Thank you, Miss Wen.
Your Honour, no more questions.
Defence counsel, this is a civil case.
The statements given
by the witnesses are professional.
l advise you not to use the usual
psychological tactics in your argument.
Yes, Your Honour.
Miss Wen, before you started
giving your statements,
you vowed to speak nothing but the truth,
is that right?
- l've not forgotten.
- Miss Wen Mei Ling,
please answer
the following question sincerely.
Do you love me?
Can he ask that?
- Objection. That's irrelevant.
- Objection overruled.
- None of your business.
- What happened?
lt's up to me to overrule any objections.
Defence counsel, please explain
the relevance of this question.
l'm sorry, Your Honour.
Please believe that l have
sufficient reason to ask the question.
l'll explain after the witness
has answered the question sincerely.
Miss Wen, do you love him?
Your Honour, can we talk
about the water quality?
l'm testifying as an oceanography expert.
l know you're an oceanography expert.
You're not only an expert,
you're also a woman.
The court would only object to a man
asking another man about love,
because that's abnormal.
As to a man asking a woman
whether she loves him,
it's perfectly normal.
lt's not illegal, either.
l can't find a reason to object
to him asking this question.
So you must answer his question.
Your Honour, l don't wish to discuss
my love life in the court.
l disagree. The Court insists.
Do you love me?
You have to answer this.
l don't.
Making a false statement is an act
of contempt of court. Did you know that?
He might sound a bit threatening
but it's true.
Sorry, Your Honour. l might be a bit harsh
but this question is very important to me.
lt's right for young people
to take love seriously.
Miss Wen, please think
twice before answering.
- Do you love me or not?
- Why are you forcing me?
An oath taken outside
the court means nothing.
lnside the court, it's legally binding.
To lie in court is a criminal act.
l want to know for real
whether you love me or not.
The answer you give will not only
affect my work in the future,
it'll determine the course of my life.
Sentimental men like you are rare.
l'm a judge, l decide
who's wrong and who's right.
But l can't decide
whether he's the one for you.
You'll be the judge
of this case within a case.
We're waiting for your verdict.
l...
love him.
Your Honour, since we're in love
and she and l are representing the plaintiff
and the defendent respectively,
for impartiality and
in the interests of both parties,
one of us has to withdraw from the case.
Your Honour, please allow my withdrawal.
Permission granted. Hearing adjourned.
Court!
- lncompetent service.
- Stupid man.
Since you didn't give me the chance
to say it, l said it all in court.
Keep the change.
- l'm sorry to interrupt, but l've no choice.
- What happened?
- Excuse me.
- Nothing. Go home, l'll come round later.
- Let's go.
Get a cab for yourself.
l've something to attend to.
Hey.
Boss.
This is where we started,
he went that way and l...
- Wait for me here.
- No.
- lt's dangerous inside.
- l'm not afraid.
- l can't take care of you.
- l'll be all right.
- Are you clear?
- Yes. Let's go.
- Put this on.
- Why?
You'll see later.
Ah Biu...
- Be careful.
- You too.
- Hey, be careful.
- l will.
- Dump him into the sea.
- Yes.
'Hey.'
Don't move.
- We're looking for someone.
- What?
We're looking for someone.
Whoever you're looking for isn't here.
He's here. We came together
and l've not seen him since.
He must be here, we can't be wrong.
Shut up.
The court might be your territory
but this is mine. l want you out.
We mustn't be rash. Let's go.
They're producing illegal drugs here.
Get rid of him.
- l said l can't take care of you.
- l said l'll be all right.
l don't believe l can't deal with you.
Wong Fei-Hung, how are you doing?
l'm very high.
Bastard.
Get rid of him
and you'll have half the factory.
Leave it to me.
ldiot.
- Wong Fei-Hung, are you all right?
- Not really.
- Call the police.
- OK.
Bitch! How dare you upset my production!
Jackie, Jackie.
My hand hurts.
That's the point.
Trying to poison me?
Goodbye, my friend.
Ah Ling.
Does it still hurt?
- No.
- Didn't l tell you not to come?
- l was worried about you.
- Don't do that again.
The love birds are mooning
and you're moaning.
Can you wake up, please?
Why didn't you tell me you were here?
What happened?
lt was...
Sweetheart.
Darling.
Love over friends.
A warm feeling rushes to my ears
A cupid's arrow
is turning in my heart
A gentle touch joins us together
and sets my heart racing
My love will bring you warmth and joy
Happiness in your heart will rise and grow
The warmth you feel will never fade
When our hearts are joined
Happiness in your heart will rise and grow
The warmth you feel will never fade
Love is like an electric current