How many times last night?
Seven...
Is that possible?
If you read that book
you could do it even ten times
Oh OK!
Jerk-off king
What if we stop growing
because of this?
I guess we shouldn't
over do it
But I keep getting hard-ons
I know, me too
How was this morning?
It's been three days.
Must be nice!
I haven't done it even once yet
How could someone who jerks off
seven times a day do it?
Maybe your right...
Was Candy
in your dreams last night?
Yesterday, finally
I grabbed
- Her hands
- Then?
I came
Did you see
Candy's in your dream?
No, it was too dark
in the water!
Have you seen a woman's?
No, you?
Not yet!
But I suppose Sang Min has...
What's wrong?
I get a hard-on whenever I hear
words that sounds like "pussy"
That must be tough
Gosh!
Are you okay?
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine!
Be careful.
Sang Min!
Your acting is getting better
How was she?
Of all the women
I have touched so far
She was the firmest
Sang Min
have you seen a women's?
- You haven't seen it, yet?
- No. Have you?
Of course, I haven't
Young Jae has
a porn tape at his place
Let's go borrow it
from him
Sure!
1988 Yong Chun Middle School
Attention! Greetings
Good morning
What is it?
No greetings?
Young Jae was
on duty last week
Who is it this week?
It's Chun Soo
but he isn't here yet
Then the class captain can
do it instead
Attention!
- Greetings!
- Good morning
I always say this
but students should
fulfill their duty and
teachers likewise
By doing so, the peace of
this society is maintained
And being late for school
is against student's duties
Always remember this.
Understood?
Yes, sir.
Class captain, you tell Chun Soo to see
me in my office when he comes
Yes, sir
Okay!
That's it for today
Attention!
- Greetings!
- Thank you, sir!
Young Jae!
Should I buy you a drink?
No, I'm fine!
Shame on you!
I refuse to watch it!
Good thinking!
Let's eat instead.
What does
a woman's look like?
You sure
you don't want a drink?
No, it's okay!
I'll just tell you.
It looks something like this.
It's strange looking.
Does it taste
like that too?
Do you think
it needs seasoning?
Can we go watch your tape
when your parents are out?
Only if you take us
to the warehouse
with the porn magazines
My dad will kill me. I've only seen
it through the window
I'll get kicked out too
if my parents find out
Hey!
your eating your lunch
after the second class?
Are you sure
you're students?
Good!
I was hungry.
Teacher wants to see you
Damn, if he has something to say
why doesn't he come to see me
Yesterday I rooted a girl
I met at the roller skating ring
What is rooting?
You know, humping.
Why were you humping at
the roller skating ring?
No stupid!
Don't you know fucking?
How did you do it?
First we went to the park and
started drinking
Then I asked her!
What did you say?
Hey, they call me stallion
are you gonna give it to me?
Give you what?
Damn! Shut up.
Then what happened?
She said
her nickname was Candy
and she said okay.
Okay for rooting?
So I started humping away
Then she screamed like a cat
and scratched my back
- Want to see the marks?
- Yeah!
Okay!
Loneliness or sadness
can't make Candy cry.
But when she bangs
does it really work?
Can you feel it?
Yeah, I think I need to do
it just a bit more
What about you?
Don't disturb me!
I'm gonna come!
Let's do it too!
Do what?
Rooting!
How can we do it
without a girl?
No problems, we'll hook up on
Sunday at the roller skate arena
I'm not interested
in animal sex
Does that look
human to you?
Did you come?
Look at Dong Hyun
studying hard
Yes, mom!
The melons are really sweet.
Eat some?
Okay!
"Fantastic Adolescences"
She moaned softly
and she brought
her lips
close to my chest
Then she tickled me
with her tongue
She licked my ears
and she kept going
lower past my neck
to the angry
part of my body
then started petting
My fingers are
being sucked into
her tidy cave
Her cave was
flowing with sweet juices
Strong aromas of fruit...
aromas...
I realised whilst eating a melon
that there are many ways to eat it
Of course, if the melon was to be
in platonic love with me
I would never have rooted it
Listen to that.
Kids are doing drugs
and sleeping around...
even middle school
students are doing it!
But thank God
our Dong Hyun is not like that
That's right!
What?
No, no.
Keep shaking!
What about her?
Kinda flat
Sang Min
what about them?
Oh!
I'll try to hook them up.
Hey, I don't want to.
Wanna ride with us?
Cheers!
What are your names?
My name is Hoon, Park Hoon
and my nickname is 'Big Unit'
I'm Min, Oh Min
and they call me 'Stallion'
My name is Hyun, Min Hyun
My nickname is 'Crazy Train'
I'm Seok Gu!
Ji Seok Gu, and my
nickname is Casanova.
Are you gonna
give it to me?
Give you what?
Hey, give him yours
This?
Hey, did you guys come
here to have sex with us?
No, of course not
Bullshit!
If we wanted to
would you?
You know, I mean...
- Give it to you?
- Yes!
Do you even know
how to root?
She said root!
I think we should go.
Yes, I think we should.
See ya next time.
Stay right there
you little piece of shit! Sit!
Undress
Take off your clothes fuck wits
Didn't you hear me, assholes?
Hurry up and kneel!
Close your eyes.
Now I want to hear sounds
of your nicknames
Crazy train goes chi-chi
and the stallion goes hee-hee
Got that?
Big unit is...
you are...
squirt-squirt!
I like that.
You go squirt-squirt, understand?
If you don't do it properly
I'll cut your faces
- Got it? Understand?
- Yes!
Start
Open your eyes
and it's a shaving day.
Excuse me.
Do I know you?
I'm Yoo Ri!
Kim Yoo Ri
From
Gwang Chun high school.
Ah, Kim Yoo Ri
What are you doing here?
- I am the new trainee teacher.
- Is that right?
It's time for
the staff meeting
Your swift
attention is requested
Okay, see you around.
Hey, is that him?
Your high school crush?
Your handsome prince?
Are you nuts?
How can he be a prince?
Hey, you just saw him.
How can you say that?
But I think
he's a dull looking dork
Can't you tell the difference
between dull and natural?
New trainee teachers
shall look after
your students according to your subjects
until the Sports carnival next month
That's it for today.
- Hey, Mr. Gong!
- Yes.
Your class for the second straight
month finished last in test scores
Any thoughts on this?
Nothing huh?
No, sir.
Well, then keep up
the good work.
Good morning?
I am Hwang Gap Tae
the P.E. teacher.
You must be the P.E trainee teacher?
I knew it at first sight
because you were so tall
I am the P.E trainee
Good morning. I am Yoon So Jung.
Nice to meet you!
I am the math trainee.
Calm down!
Let's say hello
Dong Hyun
what are you doing?
Attention!
At ease!
- Greetings!
- Good morning!
Why aren't they bowing?
We are at ease, dork.
- Attention!
- Enough!
This is our new trainee
Kim Yoo Ri.
No, I mean trainee teacher
Ms. Kim Yoo Ri.
Say hello and
please cooperate with her
Good morning!
Nice to meet you all?
I just want to
say that everyone
should study hard
Because your teacher is
having a very tough time
as a result of
everyone's test scores.
If your grade falls by one for
this month's exam
you run one around
school playground with me
If it falls by 2, then it's twice around
and if you fall by 3, you get the idea?
- You know...
- Wait!
If it falls by
more than 10 grades
You'll run 10 rounds
carrying me on your back
Well, that's enough
I expect extra attention
and preparation for
this month's test
Miss Kim
we'll study hard,
if you sing us a song.
Enough!
Stop being foolish
Please just one song.
Please...
Do you promise to study hard
if I sing you a song?
Yes!
Whether I am sad or
filled with worries
I don't cry
Why should I cry? I'll never cry
Let's go run out
to the field smiling
Let's sing a song looking
up the bright blue sky
My name is, my name is
my name is Candy
When I'm alone
I get lonely
Then talk to
myself in the mirror
Smile, smile
smile Candy!
Don't cry Candy!
Trainee teachers are
still teachers
You start giving in to everything
they ask you to do, there is no end to it
Think of yourself as a
real teacher from now on
Okay.
And I'm sorry
about my behaviour.
After all these years
I didn't even greet you properly.
Good morning Mr. Gong.
Morning!
Are you okay?
I did all that for him.
Do you really love him?
Of course!
Why?
You are really
going to kiss Mr. Toilet?
Of course, I will
He will fall in love with me.
Just you wait
Hey, what did you call him?
Nothing
I didn't know there were
such dirty princes
He should at least shave.
Why?
You don't know how much it
hurts to kiss an unshaved man
Lips are not the only place
you get to kiss, y'know.
I have only ten behind me
how can I fall ten grades?
You should be happy you
get to run with Candy!
I can't run since I don't
have anyone behind me
You two are lucky. You guys can
fall more than 10 places
I'll fall more than 20 places
and carry Candy for 20 laps
I'm gonna fall
more than 30 places
I may not carry her but I wish
I get to hold her hand at least
Hey, you wanna make a bet who
gets to hold Candy's hand first?
What's the bet?
I say, you do
- Okay!
- I'm on!
But can we not call our
trainee teacher 'Candy'?
It keeps reminding me
of Chun Soo's Candy
Then what?
How about mermaid?
Mermaid will hold my hand first
I suppose you are confident?
What's up with him?
He gets hard on whenever he hears
a word that sounds like "pussy"
Must be tough
Do you have a boyfriend?
Not yet!
Don't ask or
think about irrelevant things
Your exam is tomorrow
Tell us about your first love.
If you study now and I'll tell you
during the lunch break
Teacher
what is 'freedom' in English?
Freedom?
Isn't freedom
something else?
What is freedom?
The tampons, you dork!
Freedom is
the most important thing.
Hmm, what day is it today?
Yes, the 16th
You translate, number 16
Okay!
Can't you translate
even a short sentence?
Oh right!
Tampons...
What?
Tampons? You idiot!
You idiot
why did you say tampon?
You stupid!
Is that all you think about??
You pervert!!
Isn't that a good sight?
Yes. I couldn't wait for lunch time
when I was a student
No, I mean the trainee
She's pretty, has a hot body
and even sings well
She is just a child
Please watch your tongue
That teacher was my first love.
What's he doing now?
That's a secret
Then what about the first kiss?
Not yet...
but I think I will soon
With who?
Hm well...
How do you make babies?
Do I have to answer that?
Don't worry, we will teach him
Thanks, Dong Hyun
Teacher!
Just call me Hyun
Min Hyun?
It's a real pleasure
to meet you
It's an honor
Me too!
Can I have your autograph?
Oh, sure. Why not
- Me too
I can't write with this
It's ran out
Why don't we have lunch, okay?
- What's with them?
- Try some of this!
I love hot peppers
Oh, it's hot?
I suppose you
should try some too
What did you just say?
How's been
the last couple of days?
Tough?
No, it's fun?
You made it so easy for me
That's good
By the way, what made you decide
to become a teacher?
It's doesn't pay well and this job
requires commitment and duty
What is wrong with
being a teacher?
I think teachers are the best
I am even going to
marry a teacher
You still
sound like a student
There are lots of differences
between love and reality
Always think twice
No matter what
I am going to
marry a teacher
I wonder
who you will marry
I really wonder
- Teacher!
- Yes?
You don't have a girlfriend
do you?
Why?
Does it show?
Yes!
Who would like
an old teacher like me?
They say, where there is
a will there is a way.
Someone will
surely come your way
It felt like silk
I felt electric shocks all over my body
when the pen and her hand
You win! Seok Gu
your wish is our command
Lets go to your parent's motel and
peep at people have sex
Are you going to rest?
Give me a room
That'll be 5000 won and
your room is 308
Sit down
Let go
Is that rooting?
Let's...
do it one more time
Do what?
This time
it's her underwear
What?
You want to touch her pussy?
No, you have to tell the color
of her panties
Okay, let's do it
No, you can't do that
Why not?
That's something you
shouldn't do
But if I win I am going to go
to Seok Gu's warehouse
Me, too
You shouldn't.
I am warning you
Miss
Hey, it's you
Dong Hyun
What are you doing here?
Oh. Well Nothing
I live over there
Oh, I see
Did you come to see
the Mr. Gong?
No, why would I?
I was just passing by.
Oh, do you like melons?
Yes, I eat it almost everyday
Good, why don't you take these.
Thank you!
- Enjoy them
- Oh, no!
Miss
I'm okay. Thank you
Just wait here, okay?
Are you okay?
Sure are you okay?
Just wait here.
Where are you going?
Go on? Take this
Thank you Dong Hyun
Are you all right?
- Are you all right?
- I'm okay. It just grazed
Are you sure?
Let me take a look
Can you stop looking?
Sure
Thanks for the jacket
Study hard for the test
and enjoy the melons
I'm going now
Okay!
What are you doing?
Hey, come on
Okay.
I am not gonna do it
What is this?
Is this rape?
I will be your fiance soon?
It took me 100 days to kiss
Fine! Suit yourself!
Keep it till the end
We'll do it on our honeymoon then.
I'm gonna sleep. Damn!
Honey!
What?
I am busy. I have to go
Okay!
I'll undress
Wasn't it hot?
I'll turn around
Honey
Yoo Ri
I'm sorry!
I come back later
Yoo Ri, if you could come back
in 40 minutes
No
we were about to leave
Yoo Ri, you look very sexy with
your clothes all wet and stuff
You want to look sexy?
Thirsty. Yes thirsty. You don't know that
because you are thirsty
Right, I heard
from So Jeong
this morning
Listen carefully
all men are the same
If a woman comes in with
her clothes all wet
All men are seduced
Everybody is seduced
Mr. Toilet
that teacher is a man too
Let's go
It's raining.
Where are you going
holding your underwear.
Are you crazy?
One more thing about prince
Wait!
The important thing is to make him
forget the fact that
you were once his student
Then it's up to
your sex appeal
Aren't you gonna go?
Yes! Hey, don't give up.
You can do it
Let's go!
You top is a bit too wet
Hurry up.
Dear DJ Bae
Hey, hey!
Did you hear!
Big News!!!
Listen!
Shhhhh!
Tea Sik from
another class looked up
the Ms. Kim's
skirts with a mirror
And she wasn't
wearing an underwear!
Let's go look.
Let's go!
Wait!
This will do
I'm so so... Sorry
It does hurt.
Having a conscience is
a virtue
and it takes courage to keep it
If you're gonna cheat don't
get caught. Understood?
Yes!
Ms. Kim!
I can't read the question 14 properly
It says
"who is the historical figure?"
Ms. Kim!
Why?
I can't read question 15.
Can you please write it on the board?
Sure!
I'll kill after the test
I guess we have to come up
with a better idea
I'll say!
I'm gonna look in directly
How?
I am going to stick
my face under her skirt
No way!
Are you daring me?
Watch this
You little pervert!
You idiot
always thinking
about dirty things
You little pervert!
You idiot
Good thing
I have changed today
That crazy idiot
Mr. Gong!
Would you like to
have dinner together?
Or you can starve
if you want
Okay!
let's go
Seok Gu, no!
My God!
What are you doing there?
- You are really crude, man
- Why am I?
You're the one
who stopped us from looking
and now you're
the first to see her underwear
Really no panties?
I can't tell
She really wasn't
wearing any
Anyway, you won.
so make a wish
Let's go to
Seok Gu's warehouse
Are you sure
she wasn't wearing any?
Beijing shark's fin
Woo Long sea-slug
Order something delicious.
It's my treat
Chinese food is all the same.
I'll just have noodles
Try something
more expensive
Okay, Then can I have noodles
with extra noodles?
Sure.
Then I'll have noodles too
Fried dumpling
will be on the house, right?
Why did you
bring the cup noodle?
I'm gonna eat it
when I'm hungry
Did you bring the keys?
It's raining
It's pretty heavy.
Do you have an umbrella?
Of course not
I do!
By the way, you know who will be charge
of class from tomorrow?
- Yoo Ri!
- Yes?
The class.
Have you prepared?
Yes, don't worry
What's this?
Shaver, an electric shaver
Thank you
but I wouldn't need it
I like the natural look
I like it natural too
but it hurts
No, it doesn't
Of course
it doesn't hurt you
What if two of us get to...
Two of us do what?
Do you know
what the kids call you?
I appreciate it.
Thank you!
There must be pictures of it
You never know, we might get to see
women from all around the world
- What is it? Aren't you going in?
- Let's have one more bet
What this time?
Her tits?
Rooting, why?
Chicken?
You're on.
I always wanted to do it with
a Brook Shields
look-a-like
Okay?
I always thought Ms. Kim would
be my first anyway
C'mon, can you guys stop it?
You're the only one
who saw her underwear
Right, selfish pig
If you give up on the sex magazines
I'll give up too
Okay, rooting it is
Why don't we go out?
I'll buy you a drink
Aren't you
too young to drink?
Do I still look like
a student to you?
Once a students
always a student
I'll buy the drink
But it's going to be
soft drinks for you
Yes
- The rain has stopped
- Yes!
I really enjoyed dinner
Don't mention it?
You are going to buy
the drinks anyway
You are going
have soft drinks anyway
Mr. Gong
do you remember this?