There are some things that just don't
happen no matter how correct in theory
Like the NBA Dream Team getting beaten
by the Korean team,
or Miss Korea marrying a hotdog vendor
We all know too well that things like
that just don't happen in real life
Excuse me, Miss. You failed to practice
safe driving
Am I under arrest?
May I see your license, please?
Well...
Miss, you're headed for some serious
trouble!
What's going on?
She's got the nerve to drive like this
without a license
I'm really sorry
It's just that my driving test is 2 days away
and I just wanted to get some practice
You gotta turn all the way around with your
right arm on top of the passenger seat...
Like this?
Do you work this Saturday evening?
Yeah, I think so
Oh well...
Take it just in case.
It's a play that I'm in
You're an actress?
Actually a student.
Second year Theater major
I live in the dorms
but I'm here on vacation
Hey you! You can't do that here
OK, we're leaving!
Hey wait...
I just want to buy some flowers
Thank you
A PROMISE
Run! Run!
I didn't know traffic officers had
so many diverse duties...
Thank you for the flowers...
It was my first time being
invited to a play
I had a great time
Then why did you leave so soon?
You got your license!
Congratulations!
Let's have lunch. My treat
I can't leave this area
Really?
Do you like ramen?
Ever meet a soldier who doesn't?
Wow, this is delicious.
What's your recipe?
It's a secret. I'm planning to open
a franchise later
If you're studying drama,
then you must want to be an actress
Not everyone who studied drama
becomes an actor
I don't really have a dream
I'd like to be a good performer,
but I don't know
I'm also thinking about studying abroad
Why, do you have a dream?
When I was a kid, I wanted to be
a baseball player someday
I did play in junior high
But I didn't get big enough.
It also didn't seem like I had the talent
So I quit
Sometimes you have to readjust dreams
Guess what it is now?
What?
A baseball umpire
A baseball umpire?
Funny, huh?
Now that I think of it,
your gestures are like that of an umpire
calling "STRIKE"
I promise to come and see your game
when you become one
Is that a promise?
Of course.
You came to see my play
A fat lady...
She is eating and suddenly
she gets fuming mad
You know this joke?
No
Well she suddenly gets really mad
Guess why?
Why?
The food in her bowl kept disappearing!!
Funny, right?
That's really old!
Geez, I just heard it yesterday...
I'm leaving tomorrow
Oh. Back to school already?
Wait a second
New Driver
You have to post this for 6 months
I'll write you!
Hey... Seonghoon!
Officer Lee!
Sorry, man
Officer Kim,
what are you still doing up?
You went to a 4-year college, right?
Are there two 'L's in "especially"?
He spent most of his spare time
writing to her
To this day, I call him for a spelling check
when I get stuck writing articles
His days of constantly
writing her paid off
I was looking for a traffic officer
It's been a long time, Bumsoo
Yeah
Why do you keep smiling?
I'm just glad to see you again
So you're staying in Seoul for good?
I have some year-end leave coming up
Maybe we can go see a play together
Do you feel better?
The night air isn't good for you
Stop blowing "ping, ping"
and blow hard, go "poong"
Better?
I get overnight leave this weekend.
How about a play?
And I get year-end leave this month,
if it's OK with you...
What's wrong?
I'm going abroad to study...
Going abroad?
So Soon?
But you didn't mention anything
in your letters
I wanted to tell you in person
Why didn't tell me sooner...
I mean...
You've been so good to me
But... I... I... love you!
In grade school... you wait for your
first field trip with bated breath
Marking the calendar...
Losing sleep the night before
But once you get there,
it's not what you expected
I think happiness is not the field trip
itself but it's in the waiting,
I think love is the same way
We feel happiness not
when we achieve love
but when we know there is
a possibility of love
I know that. I don't know much
and I don't have much
And I know this sort of
situation is not for you
No. It's not that at all
I like you too
But if I acknowledge my feelings now,
it will just confuse me further
Bumsoo, let's just be friends!
I'm in love with you and so I cannot
accept your friendship
What's wrong with him?
We're wearing seatbelts, right?
Once he said...
He thought about the number of
people in this world
who exchange 47 letters and go on living
as strangers
Out on the field, the umpire is the law.
When you make a call, you must mean it
And when calling "Strike", the sound of
"k" is most important
It's not just "STRIKE",
it's "ST~~~Rl~~~KKE". Got it?
Yes, sir
Well, let's start one at a time
Don't make the "kk" sound so obvious
That doesn't mean you do away
with it all together
Not bad... Just some more vibration
after "ST"
Now, you know you ain't here to sing
the blues
Louder, kid. They gotta hear
you out in the outfields
Yes, sir
The batter's chest, knees and
both sides of the home plate
make up the four points of
the invisible rectangle
A strike is when the ball
passes through here
The ball went past the ankles...
I said the knees
Strike. It's in the middle
All catchers are frauds.
Look at the ball not the mitt
- Strike!
- It was just within the homeplate
You're still not loud enough!
On the record, she was history
But human emotions don't always
go by the record
Hyun joo!
Hey, you're by first base.
You ain't gonna need to call "STRIKE"
I remember being a nervous wreck
my first time on the field
Want some?
Is this OK?
Sure.
Nothing like it to calm the nerves
Good, huh...?
Hey, first time on first base?
Aren't you the baseball player,
Kim Sunghan?
I'm not a player anymore.
I've been coaching for three seasons
I was a big fan of yours way back when
Stop it. You're making me feel old.
Just call me Coach Kim
Son, how old are you?
Twenty-seven
What an age to be!
The ball was faster!
Your foot was off the base
Not bad for a rookie
You guys... It's not funny
With over-time,
a game can go well over 5 hours
Sometimes holding your piss is more
important than making the right call
Hey, Lee, it's agreed, right?
Come on. Stop meddling
A show has its own rhythm.
I can't do a close-up here!
Come on. We're both players here.
You did an extreme close-up on Kim
That shot was required.
Why don't you direct?
Ok. I give up.
How about in the last scene?
You do a close-up on Harin
and roll the credits, huh?
Ok. I'll think about it
Are you ready Harin?
Let's do a set-up with the camera!
What did you think of my interview?
It was fine
But you could be a bit less logical.
It can be a work as a turn-off
Is it better to look ditzy?
Well you know... A pause here,
a blush there
Mr. Byun, how've you been doing?
Mr. Bae. It's been a long time
Harin, this is Mr. Byun Jimin
You're Yoo Harin, right?
Nice to see you
I'm gonna go get the car
I really like your show.
I read the original novel
Well, I'll see you next time
How does "The Truth of Love" end?
You said you read the novel,
didn't you?
Actually, I only got half-way
through the book
Goodbye, now
Is that right? Hey Coach Kim,
go and make an appeal!
The manager made me come out.
Let's just go through the motions
Hey, you watch that soap opera on T.V.?
I don't watch much T.V. these days
You're missing out.
It's called "The Truth of Love"
I skip baseball highlights for it
These days
Hey throw me out of the game.
I have a killer hang-over
Really? Ok, Out!
What're you talking about?
Why am I out?
Keep an eye out for the ball.
You can get hurt pretty bad
Hey, aren't you going to bed?
Yeah, I'm almost done...
I saw "The Truth of Love" last night
You did! Pretty great, huh?
That Harin, what a babe
Believe it or not, I know her
Everyone knows Harin. I know her too.
She just doesn't know me
I knew her a long time ago
You guys went out?
You could say that
Stop joking.
If so, then I dated Sharon Stone
It's true. I even know her real name
Whose side is he on?
All right. Let's show our client
over there what we can do. OK?
Cut!
Let's set up for the next shot
Merry Christmas, girls
Merry Christmas
Bye
Nam Hyunjoo, who's that?
May I see that?
That Hochang and his snoring!
Stop with the excuses.
There must be a reason
Stop the bullshit and drink!
Hey, Kwangtae
Kwangtae? My wife is here and you're
still treating me like a kid?
Sorry, I'm late
Why are you here alone?
I know you're new and all...
But our KBO Umpire's New Year's
party is for couples only
Yeah. I heard.
But give me a break this time
What break?
We enforce the law on the field
So go out and get yourself a woman.
I said go on. Get on out here!
Thanks for coming
Did you wait long?
No, I'm fine. Let's go in
You got yourself a date?
Hey, isn't she the 'bat girl'?
This is really different from
the place we were at before
Don't worry.
This place isn't that expensive
It's nice to hear you say "we"
Fried ramen with seafood
Cold ramen with Vegetables
I told you it wasn't expensive?
This is red pepper ramen?
Red pepper ramen's soup is good
but the noodles are even better
This was fried in vegetable oil,
right?
It's called "farm oil"
Are you also coming out with ramen
fried in soy oil?
I'm finally reaping the rewards of focusing
on the ramen instead of ice cream
Dessert time
Bumsoo, are you alright?
Oh, my god, look out...
Seungyun!
Yes?
Do you like me?
No. I love you. Now, come on
You shouldn't love me
Why not?
Field trips. Field trip is not good.
It's the waiting that's important
What are you talking about?
Come on!
I'm saying that you shouldn't love me
Do you have someone else?
Yeah. I'm in love with someone
I've been in love with her for a long time.
You know her too
Who's she?
Is it Miss Song in the broadcast studio?
Nam Hyunjoo!
Who in heaven is Nam Hyunjoo?
Oh yeah, Everyone knows her as
Yoo Harin
Who? Yoo Harin? The actress?
Yes, I'm in love with her
Get over it. The male population
of Korea loves her. You're drunk
No. I've been in love with her since
she was Nam Hyunjoo
We exchanged 47 letters and
I taught her how to drive
I went to see her play
This is too much. And you're hurting
my feelings
Stop making excuses
Speaking of letters, I sent Brad Pitt
over a hundred
Talk about being in love
Yoo Harin is Nam Hyunjoo...
Mr. Yoon. An exclusive! Lee Miran
has an illegitimate daughter
What? But baseball season starts tomorrow.
Let's sit on it for a few days
In a few moments, the 98 Korean
League will officially begin
We are honored to have a very special guest
to throw the first pitch of the season
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome actress Yoo Harin!
There are some reporters here.
Let's stay until the 3rd inning
Ms. Yoo, could I have your autograph?
Sure!
Thank you
Busy today?
The usual.
Hey, I got her autograph
OK, I'm out.
Stop rubbing it in!
Let's get going
Nice going
Lee Miran refuses to withdraw her suit
I think you should lay low
in another department
Who knew that exact replica of hers
would turn out to be her niece?
I heard the baseball division
could use your help
I liked number 3 more.
I could rely on number 4 for a hit
If you aim for base stealing, you may
reach a 20-20, you ever feel tempted?
Sure. But the question is, am I up to it?
Who's your favorite actress?
huh...?
Give my regards to Mr. Bae
Sure
Bye
That Choi Yoo Ree. Pretty good nose job
You two have a alot in common
She was represented by Mr. Bae once and
she also did commercials for "Naumyun"
She was in a "Naumyun" commercial?
Don't you remember?
She'd smile seductively and a guy would
say "I'm hungry for 'Naumyun"
She got her first big break with that
Oh yeah
What's with your skin...?
I'm just tired
Did you have dinner?
You want some ramen?
No, I have an interview
Hey, what are you smiling at?
The umpire by third base,
he's an old friend
You mean Kim Bumsoo?
How'd you know his name?
Hey, come on,
I'm in the third grade!
Excuse me, were you one of the umpires?
Yes
Could I ask you something?
Oh, yes, go ahead
The audience kept yelling out what sounds like
"Pitcher buck", is that "buck" as in F.U.C.K.?
No, that's "balk". B.A.L.K.
but people yell out "F.U.C.K."
Bumsoo!
Hyunjoo!
So, your dream did come true
So did yours
Well, I kept my promise right?
I promised to come and see your game
You'd already fulfilled it before
You came to throw the first pitch
at the opening game
You were there?
I was by first base
Why didn't you say anything?
I used to think that I'd see you again
when you returned from your studies abroad
But when I saw you on T.V.,
I knew I had no chance
I worked as a guide for
a commercial crew from Korea
That's when I met my current manager
My whole life changed after that
You once said that dreams
had to be readjusted
Thank you for the Christmas card
How do I look?
Strike... Is that right?
Woa! That loud?
They have to hear you in the outfields
Wait, hold on
Call out my name!
Hyunjoo...
You OK? You look nice
You look nice too
- You like it?
- Yeah...
Can you walk around like this?
What do you wanna do?
I want to try that
What? A corn dog on a stick?
Yes
Wait! I'll get one...
Hey! That's Yoo Harin!
Mr. Yoon, who is the biggest name
in Korea today?
President D.J. Kim!
No, I mean in entertainment
Yoo Seungjoon, Han Sukkyu...
Readers are not interested in
the private lives of male stars
Yoo Harin?
June 8th...
That's Yoo Harin?
White SM, License plate 7486.
Chamsil Stadium parking lot. July 3rd
She's dating a baseball player!
LG's Kim Yongsoo, he's hot these days.
Wait, isn't he married?
Even better! That's what I call news!
I focused on popular baseball players
at first. Nice families, good looking
However, Yoo Harin's been caught
on my radar 5 times at baseball games,
but each time it was a different team
That means it's not a player
Baseball fanatic,
attorney Kim Hyungon
That's right.
He's got the money and the prestige
But all five times,
he came with his wife and kids
Author Song Yoohee, working
on a novel about baseball
You mean Yoo Harin is a lesbian?
But Song Yoohee is not a lesbian
How would you know?
I've got my ways
Millionaire Jeon Jaegwang,
a very likely candidate
But I did my research and
found out he's impotent
Then, who the hell is it?
Here's our man!
Actress Yoo Harin and Sportscaster
Ha Ilsung's Secret Rendezvous?
What is it?
Yoo Harin is seeing someone else
Stop poking around.
You're making me out for a fool
I'm sorry, but I thought you should know
He's not even worth your time
You have an N.B.A.
That's M.B.A.
He's just a KBS baseball umpire
KBS?
Yep
You mean KBO!
Sorry sir.
I apologize for my ignorance
He's probably punk she knew
before she was famous
The bullets have run out,
The bad guys corner Harin
At that moment,
something falls from the sky
Guess what?
It's "Naumyun".
And you see the following on screen
"I'm hungry for 'Naumyun"!
May I join you guys?
Yooree, what's your latest project?
A new film called 'Nostalgia'
You're doing that film?
Why not? Am I not suitable?
That's because you only read
half the book...
The main character's personality
changes in the end!
Care for some coffee or ice cream?
Coffee, please
Same here...
Me too
Ice cream, please
Just a moment, please
Oh, could you sprinkle
some ramen crumbs on top?
Pardon?
Don't you know ramen crumbs?
You don't look too happy
Did Yooree get to you about 'Nostalgia'?
Why did Yooree quit doing
commercials for "Naumyun"?
She basically didn't like ramen
That was the only reason
I've never mixed business and pleasure
At least until now
But now I find myself jealous of
a baseball umpire...
What, now you're checking up on me?
Harin, wake up and smell the coffee
You're playing a cruel game with this guy!
Let me off
- Let's not act like children!
- That's exactly why I want to get off
You've been doing this for two years
and you're still alone
You're a disgrace to KBO umpires
Dude, go out and get yourself a date
I'm gonna go make a call
Don't even think about coming in alone
Hey, drink up
Who's this?
Hyunjoo?
Bumsoo!
Yes?
Isn't that wrong?
Shouldn't it be "No Parking" not "No Park"?
Yeah. That's right
"No Parking" not "No Park"
You haven't changed at all
Shouldn't you be going in?
And leave you here alone?
You think, maybe we were too hard on him?
Maybe he went home
Poor kid, where would he find a girl
at this time?
He's a good-looking kid, what's with him?
Bumsoo, you're back?
Sorry if we came down on you too hard
So, that's what took you so long
You've proven yourself
as a genuine KBO umpire
You're very pretty
You look like this actress
Aren't you Yoo Harin?
Oh gosh... I'm a big fan of yours
"The Truth of Love"
what are you doing here?
Could I have your autograph?
You guys get to first base yet?
So what are you going to do off season?
Catch up on lost sleep?
That's a long way off.
We still have the Korean Series
Don't mean to brag but our group
has been chosen for the Korean Series
That lucky son-of-a-gun.
Bumsoo's getting a lot of good experience
I'll try to make it to the game
Why don't you come and
throw the first pitch?
If you agree, I'll turn over
homeplate to Bumsoo!
Wow. A second year rookie getting to
referee homeplate in the opening game?
Great.
I'll ask my manager to arrange it!
Hey man, how about a song?
Yeah, give it your best shot
I'm pretty tone deaf...
Let's see...
Hurry up!
Sir, could you give us some privacy?
Sure
We're here already?
Yeah. Is this the right place?
Why didn't you wake me?
- I had a really good time
- Me too
I'll be going now
OK
That night, on the happiest day of his life,
he wrote his 48th letter to her
I've had my suspicions about your personal life
but I didn't want to say anything
I'm sorry
You're barely ranking tenth
You hold the record for the fastest
entry in the polls
and now it seems you'll hold one
for the fastest exit
It isn't like you to harbor
on popularity polls
I've seen cases like yours
When you've had your fill,
you start whining for the normal life
I remember the first time I met you,
on location for Yooree's commercial
I'd hate to see you have to
go back to your old life
What's this?
You wanted the role
Wasn't it Yooree's?
It wasn't final
Make your mind up quick.
Filming in Paris begins next week
Attn: Nam Hyunjoo
I'm sorry about what happened last time.
I was out of line
I guess I was jealous
I sometimes wonder if we had met in school,
I would've been better at expressing myself to you
Ms. Yoo, I brought up your mail
Thank you, Samshik
I thought that you might crave ramen
on location in Paris
Thank you
Let's go
Where are you going?
The flight to Paris leaves at 8 p.m.
The entry form for the Korean Series.
Please sign it
You're calling the opening game.
Congratulations!
What's with your eyes?
Hold on
Here let me see that
This works well on black eyes
Hey, Yoo Harin's lover!
Yoo Harin's Millionaire Beau
Geez. Another millionaire business man
It was yesterday. You knew
we wouldn't be back in time
To the Right!
Miss. Yoo, have you heard the news?
Is it true that you're retiring
after the release of 'Nostalgia'?
Gentlemen, I've informed you of
the location of the press conference
What's going on, Mr. Byun?
What in the world is going on here?
While you were on location,
there were a lot of rumors about us
I think it's time for us to clarify
our relationship...
You Harin's Millionaire Beau
I think this may be good for you too
Harin, am I your manager or what?
The opening game of the Korean series which
was delayed, is scheduled to begin at 2 p.m. today
Do I still have to go on today?
It's too late now. Everything's been set.
You'll do fine!
Who's that?
He's going to throw the first pitch.
Head of the Songpa district office
What happened to Yoo Harin?
I've had a hell of a time screening
these questions
It might help you to review them first
Thanks
Samshik!
You've got a spelling error
in every sentence
What can I say, I'm a drop-out
Are you ready?
Harin, what's wrong!
I have a promise to fulfill!
What are you talking about?
Harin, what's going on?
I'm going to go throw the first pitch
What the hell?
Yoo Harin!
Go ask for Mr. Park from KBO
I'll make the call
Hey, Bae! What the hell is she doing?
Hey, what'd you say to her?
You ever talk to me like that again,
I'll kill you
I'm sorry for the confusion
Due to unforeseen circumstances,
the press conference has been moved
All right, let's do it!
Thank you for coming
OK, Ms. Yoo, have a seat. When I send
you the signal, just come on out!
OK
Ladies and Gentlemen,
Despite the unexpected rain, the 1998
Korean Series will now begin
We have a very special person here today
to throw the first pitch
Please give a warm welcome
to Ms. Yoo Harin!
More good news! Joining us today
is Ms. Yoo's fiance
This is even better than
the press conference, huh?
Just as expected,
a marriage announcement!
Ladies and gentlemen, Miss. Yoo Harin
will now throw the first pitch
You know what to do
Mr. Yoon, front page news, Yoo Harin's...
What are you doing Kang?
Just wait
Go ahead, Ms. Yoo
Go ahead
Thanks for the 48th letter
I've gotta hurry! This is an exclusive!
Yes. Yoo Harin and Byun Jimin
have announced their marriage...
Mr. Yoon? This is Kang, will you
just trust me one more time?
'It's over between us'
'I wish you the best'
Aren't you going to yell "Play Ball"?!
Hyun joo!
Get out to my way!
I warned you!
Oh my lord!
This is all I know of their story.
Some say it's like a fairy tale
But it doesn't seem too educational
to pass it on to our children
Who knows how many times the sun rose
in the west without our knowing?
Who knows?