It's only movie making,
it's real fighting.
When we were training with Sammo,
sometimes he would bring
real fighters in to train us.
If you just fight, without caring,
it won't look good on the screen.
The audience can't see your power.
So we have to tell people
that this is a movie.
So when you block,
he's got to stop.
Don't think because you're bigger
than me, you can blow me off screen
because then there's no one left
for you to fight.
You've got to work together.
It's just like dancing.
Just like dancing -
two people together, but the
difference is there's power in it.
You have to explain this to people
who are new to the business.
Some people are better suited than
others, just like Michelle Yeoh.
Some take longer. I was happy
to have trained quite a few.
When I watch them,
like Michelle Yeoh, Joyce Godenzi
and Christy Chung, who starred in
the first film I directed, I'm happy.
So, it's a speciality
of Hong Kong people
to make normal people
look like great fighters.
It's not just Hong Kong people
who can do it.
Foreigners often come here to shoot
and they look good
because of our techniques.
It's the way we plan
and position the camera.
If you're a good fighter,
we let you do ten or so moves.
If you're not, we give you two
then we change the angle.
Then we edit it, add sound effects
and it looks good.
I learned a lot when
I was training with Sammo's group.
Working with Sammo, we
acquired a lot of different skills.
The meaning of Sammo's stunt group -
his so-called "family group"...
Nowadays, they hire you
on a day-to-day basis
and you do your stunt work.
But Sammo's group
was like a real family.
When we were stuntmen,
we had to learn about props...
We learned about lighting,
we used to watch the gaffers
because inside the studio,
even when they were shooting drama,
we had to be on the set.
And then we'd sleep -
we were only in our teens.
And then later we understood
how to shoot the drama scenes
because there was only
so much sleeping we could do.
We learned how Sammo did the drama
scenes, how he arranged the actors.
We were there every day so we ended
up helping to organise the extras.
Sometimes the prop man would be busy
building an aeroplane chair
and we would help him build
these wood chairs.
Sometimes we would help
block out the light,
we didn't have computers then,
so we would hide the wires manually.
We learned many skills
that stuntmen don't need to know.
We thought it was
a waste of time then,
but now I see it was well worth it.
I directed two movies myself.
I didn't have to rely on
anyone telling me
to do things this way or that way.
I'd learned this from Sammo.
What I was willing to learn then
has now proved useful.
Now it's,
"Ah, I know how to do this,"
as I have acquired the experience,
which is a good thing.
I feel there's a karma between us.
I don't think I will ever meet
someone who is so...
I can't explain.
Although he was my boss,
he was also my teacher.
He was a very good teacher.
I remember when
I was in primary school in Lam Wan,
I swam to a float...
The first time I met him,
before my career had started,
he also swam to the float
with a friend,
"Sammo Hung! The action movie star!"
In the 10 years I've been under him,
I think we spoke
on less than 100 occasions.
What I mean is...
- "Is that OK?"
- "Yes!"
That was it.
There was very little conversation.
It was strange.
It was like telepathy.
The most we spoke was
the occasion when we were
in the studio shooting a movie
and Sammo told me
to go up to his office.
It was in Golden Harvest
and it was on the third floor.
I was scared, I've never been called
to his office before.
I was afraid
but I really respected Sammo
I got there and knocked on the door.
I couldn't look. "Sammo?"
He said, "You're here."
I couldn't speak and Sammo said,
"I've got a vampire movie
and you can star in it so get ready."
I was surprised!
I just went...
I didn't even thank him.
"Go on, back to work."
That's the most Sammo
ever said to me.
Our relationship,
we communicated with our eyes.
Which was good.
I feel Sammo cared for me.
He was quite powerful.
He was fearsome when he was angry.
If you were late or
couldn't do an action piece,
he shouted at you and
everyone on set would be quiet.
Thankfully, in all the 10 years I was
with him he never told me off once.
There was one time
when a martial arts expert was late.
He shouted at him until he left.
I was on a morning shift,
seven o'clock start,
I was young and went out a lot
and couldn't get up,
I got to the set just before noon.
When I arrived,
he came over to me...
I saw the other fighters and
got the feeling I was in big trouble.
He came over and said,
"Don't be so late next time".
He used this casual manner in which
to speak to me.
I was so scared.
So, I feel that he cares for me.
Because of our relationship,
I'd risk anything for him.
I'd do falls,
get hit by a car, get burnt...
Even after I'd been injured,
I'd still go and help him out.
It wasn't a business relationship.
He never said, "Kar-Iok,
jump down from the second floor!"
"OK, how much?"
It was never like that.
Sometimes we did get paid
and sometimes we didn't.
That's because
we had a good relationship.
So, when he said, "Kar-Iok, you're
going to star in my next movie,"
I was very happy.
I really enjoy working for Sammo,
he didn't have to do that.
It wasn't like, "I've done
you a favour, now you do me one."
I followed him for ten years.
If you can endure it for ten years,
after four or five years,
you should make it.
I was quite happy
with The Scorpion King.
It was an action film
with a lot of dialogue -
I had never done one before.
As I remember, this was my third film
where I was the lead.
For me...
The director may have really wanted
to make a kung fu thriller
but for me, it was a chance
to expand my speech.
At the time, I was happy
but there was a trade off.
The more dialogue I had,
the less action I was given.
Maybe he did want a dialogue based
kung fu film after all.
So, I did not feel disappointed
as I felt I'd have the chance to do
an action film I liked.
Back then, there was a lot
of this type of collaboration.
Yuen Tak was the fight coordinator
and Yuen Kwai the action director.
Lau Kar-leung was
a famous action director.
Why did we choose him
to play the part of my master?
We hoped to have Lau Kar-leung's
renowned kung fu in it.
This was the best thing about
making films in Hong Kong back then.
We could put
many people's ideas together.
Even I put my own ideas into
the design of the action sequences.
For instance...
Yuen Tak and Yuen Kwai
would ask Lau Kar-leung
what part of the Scorpion style
looks good.
Master Lau would then do it
and Yuen Kwai would choose
the parts he liked
and use this for the film.
This was how the action sequences
were created.
A lot of Sammo Hung's films
are like this.
If you look back,
you'd see some bits of Yuen Woo-ping
or Yuen Kwai, Mang Hoi...
All the action directors...
Yuen Biao, Lam Ching-ying...
All of them...
Sammo Hung's troupe was like this.
We all came together
to create something.
Which was the best way.
We worked as a team to do something.
I was very happy to work with him.
I have never...
Lai Tai-wai showed me a tape of him.
He said that this Korean actor
was to star in a film with me.
I watched it. It was quite vicious.
In all my years of action films,
I had never seen one like this.
But when I filmed with him,
there were no problems.
He started his career in films, too.
He was experienced in kung fu
and stunts...
I also started out with martial arts.
We martial arts experts...
We call it a lesser role.
We react to the first move.
Martial artists
are used to following the first move.
We fight best this way,
so we coordinated well together.
Yuen Jeung had a good attitude.
Some people just fight for themselves
and don't care about others
but his attitude was good
as he helped others... like me.
For example, his movement was large
and mine was small and sharp
and I'd have to wait for him.
So, I'd add another movement
so our timing was right again.
A good attitude
makes everyone feel good.
He was a good match.
In a recent film I made,
I specifically had him
be in it to help me.
Yuen Jeung is
a very good action star.