Speak up!
Do you still want to
keep your mouth shut? Speak up!
All your party members
are arrested by us.
If you still want to waste time,
all of you will die!
Tell me who is Hui Man-keung,
so just Hui will die.
Otherwise,
all of you have to be killed.
I am Hui Man-keung...
Get the one who answered first.
How many member are there
in the Taiwan People's League?
I know Hui Man-keung
has got the name list.
Are you Hui Man-keung?
You must have the list.
This ship won't
go back to Taiwan.
Now, it's going back to Shanghai.
I'll let you go if you tell me.
Otherwise you'll be regret.
Betrayer!
Get him!
He's fallen.
Drag him up.
Long live
the Taiwan People's League...
It's time to clear your commode,
get your commode out.
High collar, tight suit.
Moustaches and with a
gentleman stick.
Go on clearing your commode.
Come and take a look,
perfume from Paris.
Just arrived in Shanghai!
Brother Lik,
smell this for me please.
Let me have a look.
It smells good.
Brother Lik, does this suit me?
Smell it please.
You are so innocent!
It fits you most.
Brother Lik, and me too.
Brother Chiu.
Brother Chiu has come!
Brother Chiu...
Stay quiet.
This is from Brother Chiu!
Your payment.
Check it carefully.
Buy one pineapple chocolate,
it's delicious.
Brother Chiu!
Pay, pay now!
Brother Chiu is nice and rich,
Brother Chiu'll be richer.
Damn it!
Can you say something else?
These two ladies look nice.
Look at that bastard! Let's go.
I am powerful! Come and have fun
in the Tri-star tonight.
Brother!
Damn it! I hate raising my head
to talk others.
Are you tall?
Don't hit my head, OK?
Squat now!
You bastard! It's much better.
Your body stinks!
Why do you sell perfume?
This is your payment
for clearing shit!
Hold it.
You sell perfume, huh!
Don't you think
you are somebody now?
I tell you, you are a man
who clears shit!
You are always under me.
Don't forget, I am your boss.
You stink! Horrible smell!
Spray some perfume
to cover your stinky smell!
Bastard! How dare you be cocky?
He is scared by me!
Damn you! Damn you bastard!
Damn you bastard!
Don't you think
I dare not beat you?
I can kill you just by one blow!
You dwarf, stand properly.
Go and eat shit!
Stop fooling me, OK?
I wanna beat you to death.
I picked up this gun over there.
- Stop bothering me from scolding.
- Look.
- Damn it, damn your whole family!
- It's real.
Is the guy dead or not?
You got it over there?
Dying young! What a pity!
It just fits.
Betrayer!
Fainted! You are good
at taking advantage!
Will he be a rascal? It's not
wise to offend triad members.
There are bullets in the gun!
Hide it, hurry up.
If we are seen by the police,
we will be put to jail.
He's waken.
Get up.
I am not used to raise my head
to look at others.
Got it.
Tell me, who are you?
That's none of your business.
You stole my gun.
Return it to me.
All of us here are heroes.
We earn our living
in this messy world,
anyway, I am their boss.
Right.
That's right.
You blame me of
stealing your gun?
You mean I am a thief!
In Shanghai, only two kind of
people are holding guns.
Either cops,
or thieves.
Which type are you?
Bullshit, return my gun to me!
Hand him to the police station,
maybe we'll be awarded.
Will they give us money?
We have suffered much instead!
Say that Shorty Chiu!
He doesn't take any glance at us!
Enough, shut up!
Why not throw him to the river?
So he will be
bitten death by fishes!
Lik, come and eat some dumplings.
Eat while it's still hot.
Don't just care of eating.
Pack up of business now!
Make money is more important!
Mom, he seems to be hungry.
Let him try some, to let him eat
food cooked by excellent cook!
Alright.
"Collection of Love Letters"!
I taste the candy carefully.
Too see whether it is as sweet
as your picture in my mind.
Even a man is moved,
a woman will be moved easily too.
Today we only show to soldiers,
no ticket scalper today.
There must be surplus too.
So be a soldier, if you're,
you will get a ticket.
Bullshit!
So what!
Miss Leung, good morning.
Brother Lik, good morning.
Miss Fung, good morning.
I've bought tickets for you.
Sorry, Miss comes late.
Now the movie has been started,
we won't watch it today.
Thank you!
You are going to miss
a very good chance.
I got front seats today! You can
watch it without obstacles.
Forget it! It's not a concert,
front seats aren't attractive.
Just sell the tickets,
or it'll be a waste.
Sell it? Alright...
If you can't sell it,
I'll pay you next time.
Forget it.
See you.
Bye bye...
I've fooled him!
Miss, I don't understand that,
you have watched
"Gone with the wind" for 3 times.
Why do you still
enjoy watching it?
The lead is like a person I knew.
And I have different feelings
whenever I watch it again.
So what?
Come out... Hurry up.
Hurry up!
Get in.
Bastard, are you looking
for death?
Let Miss Fung go.
It's too dangerous.
Hurry up! Leave at once...
Kill him!
Fire! It's on fire.
Don't go!
Are you beating me? You bastard!
- How dare you beat your boss?
- Where is Miss Fung?
- How dare you beat me?
- Say! Tell me!
Help!
Go to hell!
Why do you seize my car?
What are you doing here?
That bastard is too tough!
He's a pain in the ass!
Come out.
I won't come out.
Bastard! I won't come out, never.
Come out.
Bastard, you broke my tyre,
I want you to pay for it.
I tell you,
this is imported from USA.
I want you to pay for it,
I make money by this.
If you don't pay for it,
I'll ask the cops to arrest you!
It's not wise to
offend me, you know? Pay!
Mr. Ting, Mr.
Fung will see you later.
Fung will come out soon.
Alright, thank you.
Shorty Chiu is a
dog of Brother Wing.
If not supported by Wing,
he didn't have guts
to do such thing.
What a mess!
Women shouldn't be dragged by men
What a bastard!
Watch Miss.
Before the case is settled,
don't let her go out.
Ask the owner of the cinema
to show her the movie at home.
Give the young man
who saved Ching-ching some money.
Watch him, he maybe in trouble.
Yes, Mister.
My name is Ting Lik.
I am the house keeper
of Mr. Fung.
Mr. Fung appreciated it
very much, this is given by him.
Money?
No, please take it back.
It's an appreciation
from Mr. Fung.
If you refuse to take it,
he will be unhappy.
I know.
But I can't take it.
I did it not for money.
Please tell Miss Fung,
we are good friends.
I am leaving.
This way please.
Have you ever been bitten by dog?
It won't lose its mind and bite.
Brother Lik.
Are you leaving?
I've come for a long time.
The Big World is the territory
of Brother Wing.
Don't go for movie any more.
Come and see me only.
Don't worry,
I will watch movie
on every Wednesday.
I just want to do anything
which worries my daddy.
You saved my life,
how can I thank you?
- Give me a hug.
- What?
It's a joke, bye!
Can you send me something?
What do you want?
I've got it.
What did you take?
This letter has been written
by me for a long time.
I've kept it with me for days and
didn't get a chance to give you.
Don't watch here,
go home and read carefully.
Don't think of me.
See you!
How lucky I am! Wonderful!
Come and put out the fire!
Put out the fire!
It's dangerous! Run now!
Where is my mom? Where is she?
- Brother Lik.
- Where is my mom?
I can't find her!
I can't find her.
Why don't you take care of her?
Why don't you save her?
- Brother Lik, what are you doing?
- Get lost!
Let me go!
Brother Lik,
it's a big fire! Don't go!
- It's getting worse, Brother Lik!
- Get lost.
It's dangerous,
you can't go in, run!
If you don't go now,
it'll be too late!
Drag Lik out!
Drag Brother Lik out, hurry up.
Hurry up!
Let me go!
I want to save my mom!
My mom is right in.
- Let me go!
- Come out first, Brother Lik.
Your mom isn't inside,
go out first.
Let's go. Go!
- Mom!
- It's dangerous!
Get him out! Hurry up.
- Let me go.
- Stay calm first.
She isn't your mom!
That's why you don't care.
Take a rest first.
Brother Lik, have some water.
Come on, drink some water.
It's hot.
Are you hurt?
Thank you, I am called Ting Lik.
Everyone calls me Brother Lik.
You saved my mom,
I will protect you from now on.
Fine.
What's your name?
Call me Keung.
Siu-keung, what a nice name!
Brother Wing said if we don't
hand Brother Lik to him,
he will burn any place we stay.
So we can't
make a living in Shanghai.
I think this isn't
a simple matter.
Because we are staying
in Wing's territory.
So he is pushing us
to hand him Brother Lik.
Do you want a beat up?
Stop it.
Take it back.
You are so anxious,
you must be in great need of it.
I think you
need it more than I do.
His boss Wing won't let you go.
That's why he burnt your place.
And he pushed your buddies
to sacrifice you. What'll you do?
He wants me only.
- My life doesn't worth much!
- Just take it.
Mister, do you want any girl?
Let me find a pretty one for you.
Stop bothering me,
I don't want any girl.
You look nice!
I am going to see the boss.
Don't get yourself into trouble.
Don't you worry I can't escape?
I think, starting from tonight,
we will be famous in Shanghai.
I don't want
others to know my name.
I will call you Chun from now on,
so no one knows your name!
- Brother Lik.
- Cheung-kwai, why are you here?
I am going to do business
in the Tri-star.
Put the gun inside his box.
Bastard, you've come!
I am coming to send Brother Wing
some crabs.
Check whether
they are armed or not.
Brother Wing, they have come.
You bastard!
Crabs?
You are giving me face
to send me crabs!
You can't escape this time.
Bastard, I have waited you
for a long time!
Come on... let's play mahjongg.
Kid, where are you going?
Someone inside wants
the shoe shine service.
No one needs you tonight!
Leave! Get lost.
Tri-star isn't
suitable for children.
I will play a game with you.
Choose the biggest you can.
Sixty thousand.
Your turn.
Just forty thousand?
Do you wanna die?
Let's see how far you can go!
Sorry, you are
so unlucky tonight.
How dare you betray me?
Do you remember
who raised you up?
Damn it! Do you know it?
Who is the boss here?
Chiu is my brother,
how dare you offend him?
Don't you want to
live any longer?
Did you think with your ass?
Did you eat shit?
Let me hit you to wake you up!
Don't you want to live?
Draw any domino you like.
Go ahead.
You are like a dying dog!
Open it.
Show me.
Just ten thousand.
No!
Don't kill!
Go to hell.
Stop fighting!
Have you fought enough?
Freeze...
Be frank!
You cops can't take anyone away
you like.
Mr. Chu, you've misunderstood it,
we don't come for an arrest.
Uncle Lau invited me
to eat crabs.
Such nice crabs,
let's finish it first.
You haven't come to have fun in
Tri-stars for a long time.
How is Mr. Fung?
Mr. Chu, you still
remember Mr. Fung.
How can I forget him?
But they killed
Brother Wing here,
if his fellows want me to hand
the murderer, what'll I do?
You know, this is a place
for fun only!
If there is anything happened,
that will...
If you don't cover Wing's gang,
that'll be alright.
I will take Ting Lik away.
For the rest,
We will deal with it.
Brother Four, what action
will the police station take?
What's the matter?
Nothing has happened!
I asked my fellows
to clean the scene.
Nothing has happened!
Lik, from now on, the territories
of Wing will go to you.
I will back you up.
Shorty Chiu can't
hide up any longer.
From now on, we will take over
the shit business in Shanghai!
We will be rich!
Come on, fix the shit! Hurry up!
For anything I get in Shanghai,
I want to share it with you.
I am only a visitor in Shanghai.
I will leave this place
when my work is finished.
Let's wait and see.
Maybe, you don't want to leave
for something unknown.
Miss Lai-man.
Thank you.
Damn it! Hurry up...
Is that OK?
I haven't done such thing before.
Brother Lik,
come and give me some comments.
Should I re-decorate it again?
This is given by Miss.
What's her name?
Fung Ching-ching.
Will she marry you?
Of course!
How can she reject my proposal?
This is rule!
What else can you say?
Where did you get the gold?
- Don't you know it?
- I don't know.
See you...
I just want to be
fair and reasonable.
You killed Wing and then Mr. Chu.
As well as the Commissioner
of Custom Department.
What do you want?
I always have a dream.
I can't waste my life.
I want to get the most
precious thing in Shanghai.
I tell myself,
when I'm qualified, I'm rich,
I must marry her!
I want to be your son-in-law.
Young man, you want to get
my most precious thing!
I think, if you don't mind,
nothing will bother.
So confident?
Lik. I have an important friend
in business.
I want you to meet him,
to communicate with him.
Then, come back and tell me
your point of view,
this is very important to me,
you should understand.
I will do as you instructed.
This cinema has been
bought by me.
you can watch movie
any time you like.
I want to make movies too.
To film everything about you.
You, me...
our family...
and our children.
Don't worry,
I've talked to your daddy.
He's agreed our marriage.
I am sorry.
Please give me some time,
I'll explain this to you.
I'll give you 3 days.
Wonderful!
Wonderful! I can't imagine Keung
will take woman home!
Even Keung falls in love too!
Let me take a look
at my sister-in-law!
I've got you!
Ching-ching?
Are you Fung Ching-ching?
Ching-ching,
do you like Ting Lik?
In fact, I like another guy.
Last summer...
Who is it?
Be careful!
Hold me.
Miss.
Room inspection.
Something happened,
it's emergency!
Miss, an escaped soldier
from kirin ran into this train.
They want to check your room.
What do they want to see?
Miss hates people looking at her
in this way.
If Mr. Fung knows it,
we'll be in trouble.
If you are impolite to Miss,
you will be complaint certainly.
What's the matter?
This is Miss Fung's room,
how can you check it?
You are bleeding!
Blood on my hand too.
Luckily they didn't see it.
Let's take a look over there!
Let's go.
Take care of Miss,
I'm going to take a look.
I heard that many Taiwan soldiers
escaped from North East.
I pity you and your buddies.
You will lose much blood!
Let me treat your wound first.
Wasn't it terrible to be trained
in Japanese camps?
Do you want to go South?
Cut the crap.
What's up?
I am tired.
There is an escaped soldier!
Don't let him go!
Freeze...
I don't drink.
Smoke?
I don't know smoking.
Come on, you smoked last night.
Well, why are they
so polite to you?
What's the relationship between
your dad and the Japanese?
I am different from my dad.
He has friends
all over the world.
He makes money in peaceful days.
Now, the NE is in a mess,
he makes money from the mess too.
Many people hate my dad.
They hate me too.
One day, my dad wasn't home,
so I sneaked out.
I went to the North by train.
But no matter where I go,
my father's friends
are next to me.
I am like an escaped soldier.
I was found eventually.
I was taken to this train and
I was sent back home.
Wonderful!
You won again! I lost!
Later, I sent
that guy to hospital.
His leg broke,
he became a cripple.
I am useless,
I can't do anything.
I can't change
anything around me.
I can't go out either.
I hate myself so much.
I really hate myself.
- Let me show you around.
- Fine.
Will you come to Shanghai
to visit me?
Shanghai isn't the place
I am heading to.
I am different.
I am homeless.
My dad hates men
getting close to me.
You are the first one
to dance with me.
May I know your name?
Don't ask my name.
After the next stop,
we are going to say goodbye.
We have to take another train
after the next stop.
Please get yourself ready.
It's impossible for us
to see again.
I don't want to see you leaving.
Close your eyes.
So you won't see me leaving you.
Ching-ching.
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
Dad, I am going out.
Lai-man...
How are you, Lai-man?
Miss, he mistook me as someone,
I fainted after a strike.
How come?
Miss, who are you chasing after?
Do you know him?
What do you know?
Miss.
What's happened?
It's no big deal, don't worry.
Thank you, doctor,
let me send you to the door.
Ching-ching, I am sorry.
In these months,
I've used your name
to write to Lik.
His letters are so passionate.
He has requested to meet you.
I thus replied it wouldn't be
allowed by Mr. Fung.
I know it's my fault to do so,
but I don't know what to do.
Ching-ching, I've got your reply.
I feel like standing on the
highest mountain of the world.
My best friend said
I was losing my mind.
I just told him,
I tried hard for you future only.
Ching-ching, I can't wait.
I want to live with you.
I will tell Mister Fung.
Ching-ching, will you blame me?
What did you say?
So, will you be fond of Ting Lik?
Yesterday night...
Why did that guy assault you?
Did he mistake you
as someone he knows?
Yes, he said he did.
But he asked me
where I made the dress.
Why did he ask such question?
I am puzzled too.
When I told him
the address of the tailor,
he then released me.
- May I ask...
- Is this dress made by you?
Yes... yes.
Where is the woman now?
I don't know.
- Speak up.
- I really don't know.
I know you've come to Shanghai,
that's why I try to find you.
What's your name?
You need not know it.
We won't see each other again.
Go up.
Go.
Go in.
Jump.
Trust me.
Close your eyes.
- Are you alright?
- I am fine.
Let's go.
Hui Man-keung,
aren't you looking for me?
You are Hui Man-keung,
aren't you?
I've got you at last!
Ching-ching?
What's her name?
Fung Ching-ching.
Will she marry you?
Of course! If only I propose!
Lik, before I knew you, we...
You can say anything you like.
Forget it.
Will our relationship
be hurt by a woman?
What a nice speech!
If you are married
and you discovered that,
You wife bathed with me
and slept with me,
then I tell you not to harm our
relationship because of a woman,
is that alright?
- What did you say?
I didn't know she is the woman
you are loving most!
Didn't I tell you?
I told you everything!
- But you didn't tell me anything!
- I have nothing to tell you.
I will leave Shanghai
once my job is finished.
At that time, everything
in Shanghai will go to you.
I don't want your sacrifice.
I can give you anything,
but why do you fight
for Ching-ching with me? Why?
Alright, you said you would leave
after finishing your job.
How about Ching-ching?
Can I take her along?
Fung King-yiu won't
let you do it.
Alright.
I am leaving.
But, remember,
take good care of Ching-ching.
Otherwise,
I will kill you.
Give way.
If you take yourself
as a soldier,
better commit suicide
in front of the comrades.
Few hundred members
of the Taiwan People's League...
were sent to NE for training
by the Japanese,
two troops went for
a mutiny together.
But a hundred of your fellows
were unable to escape,
why were they killed in Shanghai?
Except you!
Did you betray your buddies?
I didn't betray them.
After the mutiny,
we moved out of Kirin.
We planned to go back to Taiwan.
God knows!
The one who liaised with us died.
We lost contact with you.
After getting on board,
we discovered that our identities
were disclosed by betrayers.
Why weren't you killed?
Since the list of our party
was kept by me.
The comrades
wanted to protect me.
What a nice speech!
Why did you fight for your fame
and wealth in Shanghai instead?
My clothes were stained
by my buddies' blood.
So I swore.
I wanted to avenge them.
No one will trust
what you are talking.
Now, I want to execute you
right here.
The foe I want to
find has appeared!
If you kill me now,
you will never know
who betrayed our league!
Give me one chance,
give me one chance!
If you don't kill me now,
I can't even escape,
Give me few more days,
so I can take revenge for
my buddies by my own hands.
Lik, I have an important friend
in business.
I want you to see him,
to communicate.
Then come back and tell me
what you think about him.
This is very important to me,
you'd understand.
Mr. Fung,
your son-in-law has come.
I'll arrange it.
I won't miss it.
Ting Lik works without control.
He will ruin the plan of
the Japanese troops in Shanghai.
But it's not
necessary to feel pity.
Our plan is going to start.
Mr. Ting,
our boss invites you to go in.
His car is here,
but he is not around.
- We can't find him!
- Yes.
- How is it?
- We can't find him.
Where is he?
Brother Chun is back.
Brother Chun...
they found Miss Fung at your
home this morning.
So they are looking for you.
Are you Brother Chun?
Mister and Miss Fung are waiting
for you at home.
I'll follow you.
My dad looks fierce,
but he loves me very much.
Long live
the Taiwan People's League...
How can you let
Hui Man-keung escape?
What are you still thinking of?
Mr. Fung.
- Daddy.
- Ching-ching.
Your real lover is someone else.
In fact, I rather feel surprise.
Well, Ching-ching,
introduce your friend to me now.
Fine.
- Uncle, I...
- He is called Hui Man-keung.
I see, Mr. Hui.
Nice to meet you,
sorry to let you wait.
Are you the son-in-law
to be of Mr. Fung?
Now, I am not.
But Mr. Fung is the one
I respect most.
He asked me to see you,
that's why I come.
It doesn't matter,
since you come to see me,
I'll arrange something specially
for you.
Sit down please.
Do you want to be Mr.
Fung's son-in-law?
He won't let others
take away his daughter.
Ching-ching's friend
is my friend.
Mr. Hui, where is your hometown?
Kwangtung.
Some years ago,
we moved to Beijing.
I haven't eaten mutton
in Beijing for years.
Mister, I am now going to
prepare the midnight snack.
Fine.
Mr. Hui, please take a seat.
Uncle Leung, just go ahead.
Mr. Hui, the Japanese has
messed up the North.
What kind of business
can you do then?
We businessmen
won't care about politics.
Mr. Hui, what kind of business
are you dealing with?
My family trade tea.
Tea?
Well, can people grow tea
in the North?
I said, my hometown is Kwangtung.
Mister Fung asked me to kill you.
I won't let you die comfortably.
I will enjoy enough
before your death.
Daddy, he is just joking.
Girls shouldn't interrupt
parent's talk.
Look at you! I haven't seen you
for one day only,
your dress is so dirty,
Why don't you get changed now?
Mr. Hui, want a cigar?
I will do it myself.
- Daddy.
- Miss...
- I heard gun shot.
- You can't go in.
What's happened inside?
Let me go!
Get lost.
- Don't come close.
- Daddy.
Get lost.
- Miss...
- Let me go.
Miss!
Daddy...
Get lost!
- Why do you want to kill him?
- Leave me alone.
Hands off.
No!
Stop!
Uncle Lau,
Brother Lik is upstairs.
Why do you come here?
Since Mr. Fung's death,
Miss seems to be mad!
She has no response to anything.
Now, it's all a mess
in Fung's family.
Everyone wants to kill Mr. Hui
and take over Mr. Fung's place.
Mr. Ting, I hope you to forget
the hatred against Mr. Fung,
for the sake of Miss Fung,
can you come out to do something?
Ching-ching.
Ching-ching. Don't worry,
for you,
I'll fight for what you deserved.
Sure I will.
From now on,
Fung's business is my business.
All of you should remember...
the benefits
which Mr. Fung granted us.
Don't ruin the regulations
which are set by Mr. Fung.
And...
Hui Man-keung's life is mine.
No one can kill him,
except me.
The list which you want.
If you want to kill me,
just go ahead.
Fung King-yiu is the man behind,
We all know it.
Now you killed our foe,
when will you go back to Taiwan?
Don't you think
I am valuable to you anymore?
Everyone in Shanghai wants to
kill you now, you are in danger.
Leave with me.
Hui Man-keung.
Happy New Year!
I am going to inform Brother Lik,
keep an eye on him.
Brother Lik, he is on the way.
Ask all buddies to wait
for me out there.
- Brother Lik, we want...
- Listen.
Tonight,
either one will leave this place.
No matter who will go out,
you should take any action and
pretend nothing has happened.
Agree?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Happy new year!
Listen, Brother Lik asked us
to wait outside.
Let's go!
Go!
What's the matter?
What did Brother Lik say?
Brother Lik said,
he wants us to wait outside.
Never go in no matter
what's happening inside.
No way!
This is Brother Lik's order.
They are buddies!
Brother Lik said
no one could enter.
Stay calm. Stay calm...
The old days and things
will leave after the count down
Why do you look for me?
Why don't you leave?
This is a ticket.
If you have chance to leave,
try your best
to go back to Taiwan.
If...
there is sand of Shanghai's
beach under your foot,
I think you'll regret
to be named Hui Man-keung.
No matter what you tell me,
I won't tell you the reason
why I killed Fung King-yiu.
I don't come for an explanation.
I just want to see...
how you keep your promise.
I think you've misunderstood.
I won't promise
anything to anyone.
Stay quiet...
Dear friends,
the critical moment has arrived.
1936 is coming soon.
Time flies.
Another year is coming.
Be nice to Ching-ching.
Or I will kill you, I swear.
Headless bullets!
I pay everything I owed you!
- Brother Keung.
- Don't hold me.
Brother Keung.
I am so happy to hear you
greeting me Brother Keung.
Let me walk out alone.
Let him go.
Don't you think you are great?
You want me to kill you.
Have you though of
your buddies' feeling?
Have you thought of my feeling?
I can't imagine that
you are so selfish!
Let him go.
Do you want to be hero?
Alright, I won't give you a hand.
Walk out alone.
Yee-yung,
don't let Fung's fellows go in.
Got you.
Let's go, let's go in.
Brother Keung...
Keung!
Brother Lik, Fung's fellows
have arrived, they are out there.
What'll we do?
What to do?
No matter what,
I want him leaving Shanghai safe
and alive.
Take him away.
Be careful.
Come on. Hurry up.
Mr. Ting...
Hui Man-keung
has been killed by me.
Let's go back to see Uncle Lau.
I want to go in and take a look,
Can you hear me?
Mr. Ting said he killed Hui
Man-Keung, don't you trust him?
What are you nagging?
Don't you think Mr.
Ting is cheating you?
Are you alright?
Let's go.
Brother Lik!
Brother Keung, hold it.
We are taking you to see doctor.
From now on, I want to share
what I have with you in Shanghai.
I am only a visitor in Shanghai.
I'll certainly leave
after doing my job here.
Let's wait and see.
Maybe you don't want to leave
for something unknown.