In the year 2000, is there anything on Professor Han?
That's "Il Mare".
I can't accept...
either my father's death or my love for him.
Yeah, I'm back from the hospital.
I'm okay.
Did you put the book in the mailbox?
Okay. I'll go get it.
There are three things a person can't hide:
Coughing, poverty, and love.
The harder one tries to hide them,
the more they rise to the surface.
But there are times when you still want to hide them.
I just sit and cry,
and cry until I can't anymore.
Love is a self-inflicted pain.
I hope you'll find peace within you.
Il Mare's warmth and comfort came from the love within.
Love comes to us in different ways,
but I believe there is only one love.
I hope your father's book helped you
to understand him better.
Hye-Gi!
Auntie!
- Have you been good, kiddo?
- Yes.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, how's dad?
He's at a seminar in Seoul.
Eun-Joo, everyone I loved
was always out of my reach,
and I think I ached for them.
I was seven when my father left me.
It's dinner time, Cola!
You like Mr. Fish?
I'll be right back. Be good now.
It's freezing...
Excuse me...
I saw you at the station tonight.
White sweater, black muffler, pretty hair...
Haven't heard from you in a while.
Il Mare can make you feel so alone.
I felt like that when I was there.
Sung-Hyun, wanna have some fun?
Go into a convenience store and grab a beer.
Drink it down...
Now, start running!
Go for a ride on the Viking.
The adrenaline rush is amazing!
This is the moment!
It's my turn. Take a bus to Bomunri.
Get off at Mulmok near the tree-lined boulevard.
Do you like to take walks?
It's a beautiful place to just walk alone
and think things through.
Just when you start to get tired,
you'll see a little cafe.
I go there to drink wine sometimes.
Do you like wine? I heard that
wine drinkers are lonely,
but it doesn't matter to me.
I reserved a bottle of wine to be opened
in the year 2000. How is it?
Wine is supposed to get better with age.
I had a great time.
How about you?
I did too, but I felt a little sad coming back alone.
I'd really like to meet you, if it's okay with you.
Hey, Cola.
You really think we'll meet?
Can you come down to Cheju Island?
I'm going home next week.
Cola! Cola!
Cola, I'm going to meet Eun-Joo.
What'll we do in the meantime?
Are you looking at the photo?
The coral beach is where I want to live.
Once you see it, you'll want to build a house on it.
Oh, our rendezvous date is March 11, 2000,
at 3 p.m. on the coral beach.
It's a Saturday.
Don't forget. I only have a week,
but you still have over two years to go.
Eun-Joo...
- Aren't you going to bed?
- I'll be right down. Good night.
Go to bed, dear.
- Can I help you?
- No, I was just...
- Are you building a house here?
- Yes, we are.
- Will you be living in it?
- No, I'm here for the construction.
- Why do you ask?
- Just curious...
A friend of mine designed it.
Isn't it perfect for this beach?
He dedicated it to his true love.
I see.
I gotta run. Good luck.
I waited for you for a long time.
I know two years is a long time,
but I still hoped you would come.
I guess I expected too much again.
I know I shouldn't, because it
always leads to disappointment.
But everyone I care about is so far away.
What happened to you in those two years?
I hope it was just a slip of memory.
Why didn't I show up?
I wouldn't forget a promise like that.
This is breathtaking.
Sung-Hyun's letters were little pieces of happiness.
But still, there is this sense of emptiness.
Is it because of losing Ji-Hoon?
Or is it not being able to meet Sung-Hyun?
There's a technical problem,
so let's take a 30 minute break.
Let's get some coffee, my treat.
The more animation, the better.
It means more work for us.
And it's great that there are
many big projects in the works.
That's true.
- Sorry I'm late.
- I just got here too.
- Ji-Hoon, about our engagement...
- Yeah, let's do it this month.
Really?
How about two Wednesdays from now?
Okay.
- But why do you want to rush this?
- I'm not rushing.
You're the one who's stalling.
Just be patient until my animation project's finished.
I thought I could forget him,
but when I heard his voice again,
everything felt the same as before.
I know he loves someone else,
but I can't help it.
Please help me stop him from leaving. I'm sorry..
I'm really sorry.
- Hi.
- Sorry I'm late.
- It's okay. Are you hungry?
- No, but it'll be dinner soon.
- What should we eat?
- Whatever you want.
Was I just a stranger to you?
What do you want?
Let's go.
Am I only a meaningless, faceless stranger to you?
Do you think it was a good idea to let him go?
Of course. True love comes from true independence.
I want to believe it too. I want a career and love.
My happiest moments were opening my mail
under your Christmas lights.
Eun-Joo.
It was really hard studying
out there alone.
Your letters helped,
but I just got too tired and lonely,
and I wanted someone there.
I'm sorry... We should have stayed together.
Please help me stop him from leaving me.
I'm sorry...
I'm really sorry.
I'll help you.
If you were in so much pain,
why didn't you tell me how you felt before?
Do you remember your first letter?
You wished me good fortune at Il Mare.
Knowing you has been a blessing.
This time, I want to return this good fortune to you.
Best wishes to you.
Thank you for everything. Goodbye...
Excuse me. Where's the department of architecture?
- Over there.
- Thank you.
My Lord, you're the biggest whiner these days...
Well, life isn't fair.
He dedicated it to his true love.
May I help you?
Sung-Hyun dedicated it to you, Eun-Joo.
It was a car accident.
Help me stop him from leaving me...
He was on his way to Youido to meet someone.
The driver didn't see him.
It's that house over there.
Please...
Please... hurry.
The letter has to reach him.
It's all my fault. Sung-Hyun, please don't go there.
Please...
Our last date was at a cafe called "Morning"...
in Youido on March 25, 1998.
Cheer up. I'm not going away forever.
I know, I just feel weird.
I asked you to come with me.
It's not easy becoming a voice actor.
Not many people pass the exam.
It's only three years... right?
I just feel so uneasy.
Please don't go.
Don't die.
I'm so sorry.
The fact that I don't show up two years from now...
must mean that we weren't meant to be.
And you are...?
I hope you're ready to hear
a long and magical tale.
Are you ready to trust me?