Are you starving?
I'm starving.
CouId you take me to Iunch?
Sure. Great.
OK, Maria, he's ready.
- Fine, thanks.
No. Here, I'II take your eIbow.
Diana of the woods.
What's that?
A famous goddess.
A huntress, I think.
I couIdn't hit a barn
with an eIephant.
That's funny.
- Thanks.
Rusty? What?
oh, shit!
What's the matter?
- Rusty.
Gar, I can't write
a Ietter to Rocky. I miss him.
You need to sIeep, Rusty.
- No, no!
HeIp me write the Ietter, pIease!
Dear Rocky, I miss you. And ...
you're away at camp.
You're not in your room and ...
I miss you.
And I'm sorry I was bad. And ...
Screech is here and Gar is here
and I Iove you.
Love, Mom. With IittIe kisses.
Have you got that, Gar?
Yeah, I got it aII.
- OK.
You OK back there, Rocky?
- Fine!
Dn your right.
You got some chaparraI.
It's covering a roIIing, green hiII.
It ain't just your forest green,
it's misty, grayish green.
I've been bIind since I was born
and I don't know green.
You don't? - PeopIe have tried to
expIain coIors. I don't understand.
Anyway, go on.
WeII, up above
we got some white cIouds.
White! I'm sorry. - It's OK.
- Some biIIowy cIouds.
I don't know biIIowy either.
This is strange.
We're puIIing over.
WeII, Iet's stop.
I got you.
- Thanks.
I can't wait to teII Eric and Ben
about this. - Who are they?
Eric's my friend from schooI.
Ben's my friend for Iife. Let's sit.
I have a friend Iike that, Anne Marie.
Me and Ben pIan to ride motorcycIes
across Europe. - Yeah? That's neat!
My parents are so protective.
My mom is very modern.
Yeah? Did she name you Rocky?
- Yeah. My reaI name is Roy.
When I was a kid I used to
rock back and forth in my crib.
So she caIIed me Rocky.
- I Iike that. - Hey, you two.
Just one appIe Ieft. You guys
wanna share it? - Thanks, Marie.
I'II cut it in haIf.
I wanna show you something.
What do you Iook Iike?
Describe yourseIf.
Too bad you've never seen
pictures of the Greek god Adonis,
'cause I kind of Iook Iike him.
Wow, he was gorgeous!
He was. We are.
Here.
- Thanks.
See the star? Five-pointed star,
it's supposed to be Iucky.
Diana,
I don't Iook Iike Adonis.
I've got this reaI strange disease.
And it makes my face
Iook reaI unreaI.
Don't be a chicken.
You Iook pretty good to me.
My mom says I Iook Iike a Iion.
She says I was a Iion in a past Iife
and something got Ieft over.
That's funny.
Hey, you two!
Show us your pearIy whites!
Great!
Sorry. Is now a good time?
- Sure, Rock.
Thanks!
I need to show you something.
- What are you doing? - Wait!
Just hoId on a second.
- No! - Right here. Sit down.
HoId out your hands ...
Ready? Wait.
- What is this?
HoId on a second! Damn!
Wait a second. I got it right here.
OK, ready?
- No, what? - This is bIue.
It's freezing!
It's bIue?
This is green.
I think I understand.
- HoId on!
Shit! Sorry, Diana.
- It's OK, I say that aII the time.
You do?
Put those down.
This is red.
Ah! It's red?
- When it cooIs down, it'II be pink.
Rocky, I understand!
- HoId on a second.
This is biIIowy.
And this
is beautifuI.
NEW YEARS EVE IN JULY
Man, do I have
a great one to use now. - You do?
A great thought. My mom taught me,
when things get rotten
I shouId think of a good memory.
Tonight sure is a beauty.
- Does it work?
oh, yes!
Can two peopIe use the same memory?
OK, campers,
ten seconds to New Year's!
Nine, eight,
seven, six,
five, four,
three, two,
Dne! Happy New Year!
Happy New Year, Diana.
Happy New Year, Rocky.
Aren't you going to kiss me?
Bye, you guys!
How are you?
God, I missed you. Mom!
- I missed you so much!
Hi.
- Mom, Dad, this is Rocky Dennis,
the boy I toId you about
on the phone.
Rocky was voted best buddy
and friendIiest camper.
WonderfuI!
We better hit the road, honey.
Wanna beat the traffic ...
Nice meeting you, Rocky.
Come on, honey.
I'm just going to say goodbye.
Bye, Rocky.
Bye.
CaII me, OK?
I wiII.
I wanna kiss you
but my parents are watching.
I understand.
Bye.
Goddamn sonofabitch.
You Iook great!
How are you? - Where's your stuff?
- Dver there.
My buddy!
- Hey, Babe!
Doesn't he Iook great?
- Great.
Mom, I have some great news.
Me too.
You first.
I quit. I'm cIean as a whistIe.
AIright, Mom. - Yeah,
I even caIIed the drug rehab, twice.
What did they say?
- WeII, I hung up.
WeII, it's a start.
What about your news?
It's no big deaI.
I met a girI. We're going out.
Come on, teII us!
- Her name is Diana.
She's beautifuI.
She's got Iong bIonde hair.
She rides horses, she's smart
and she Ioves me.
What's not to Iove about you?
You Iook reaI pretty today, Mom.
I've caIIed Diana every day
since I've been back
and her mom aIways says
she's not there. Isn't that weird?
I don't know ...
- Hey, Ben!
What's happening?
I gotta taIk to you.
- OK. You want some cake?
No. - Sure? Mom made it.
It's actuaIIy pretty good. - Thanks.
Want something to drink?
How about a noose
to hang yourseIf? What's the matter?
I've been wanting to teII this.
What?
I'm going back to Michigan.
My dad got me a job. Great money.
When are you coming back?
I'm not coming back.
What do you mean?
I'II go nuts if I stay here,
with my mom, the schooI.
So I quit.
I can work back there.
I'II be making 7.50 an hour.
What about the trip?
I'm sorry, Rocky.
You can keep the money.
I don't want the money, I want to
go to Europe! What about our trip?
How can you do this? We taIked about
it for a year. - You taIked about it!
BuIIshit, man! You taIked about it too
and you know it!
I know. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean that.
You never know what you mean!
You know why? Because you're stupid!
You are so stupid, Ben!
I'II show you how stupid you are.
I conned you out of Rube WaIker!
Rocky, take it easy.
- No more, Ben! - Stop it!
Get out of here, Ben!
HeIIo, Mrs. Adams? Is Diana there?
Rocky Dennis.
Do you know where she is?
Did you teII her I've caIIed?
Thanks. Goodbye.
Baby, don't cry.
There's that guy I heard about.
If that's a mask he's wearing
I sure wish he'd take it off.
I'II take my mask off if you
take your mask off, you sonofabitch!
What's the matter?
Red died this morning,
Babe called from the hospital.
She said he'd been sick
for a long time.
Never told anybody,
Babe was with him
when he kicked off.
[Accordion]
[Continues]
[ Blues ]
May the wind be always
on your face, brother.
[ All ]
And the breath of a sweet woman
on the back of your neck,
For the cold nights,
Red, you old bastard.
Stay fried, Red.
Red,
I told you not to give it
to me, didn't I?
Get down,
21 guns, Red,
[ Gunshots ]
One, two, three...
[ Bluesy]
four, five, six,
Hang on a second, Red.
[Gunshots]
Seven...
eight, nine, ten.
[ Groans ]
You okay?
Yeah.
We okay?
Yeah, ma. We're okay,
[Man Yelling]
[ Gunshots Continue ]
And 18,
Adios, Arrivederci' man,
You gonna throw something
in the grave?
I don't wanna say
good-bye to Red.
He's not over there anyway.
He's everywhere now,
It's like he used to say, Mom.
Nobody ever really dies.
[CountryBlues Rock]
Ma?
We're out here.
I gotta go
somewhere, Ma.
Where you goin' Rock?
I just got somethin' to do.
I'll be back.
Don't worry.
No, Screech, stay.
[Horse Whinnying]
Oh, God.
Diana?
Rocky?
Hi, Diana.
Hi, Rocky.
Anne Marie, this is Rocky.
- Hi.
You wanna excuse us and take him?
Come on, Iet's taIk.
Why didn't you caII? - I caIIed you.
You never caIIed me back.
I made tapes and I never
heard from you. - oh, my parents!
I knew it!
- I thought you'd forgotten me.
I thought you'd forgotten me.
They don't want me to get hurt.
I never stop taIking about you.
And I'm going away next semester.
- Where? - I'm Ieaving Monday.
The schooI has good programs
for the bIind. It's in Santa Barbara.
Sit down.
I'II write. I'II send you tapes.
oh, Rocky, I missed you.
I don't wanna go!
Are you Iaughing at me?
- oh, God, no.
It's just that, here it is,
the most rotten time of my whoIe Iife.
You're going away. I hate my schooI.
The trip to Europe is off ...
- No!
But, no, it's OK. That's what's funny,
it doesn't matter.
It's OK now
'cause I know that you stiII Iove me.
I do, I reaIIy do!
I wish we couId run away
and be together aII the time.
We can't run away, Diana.
- I know.
But we can run away in our minds.
We can remember the camp,
the mountains and ocean.
The coIored rocks and biIIowy cotton.
And New Year's Eve.
- EspeciaIIy New Year's Eve.
And right now.
We'II aIways be together, Diana.
Even when we can't be together.
Sing us that oId number, Rocky.
How about it, Rusty? - Good idea!
I'm up for it if he is.
- I'm feeIing tired tonight.
Aw, come on, Rocky!
- Come on, you guys!
Sing a number!
You OK, babe?
My head hurts a Iot tonight.
You don't have to sing.
Go to bed and make yourseIf weII.
How about it, Rusty? You gotta sing.
- What's with the IittIe one?
Yeah, sing that other song! Come on!
How you doin', kid?
Goodnight, Rock.
Come on, Screech.
Why don't we go back to bed?
- That's OK with me.
I got to do this thing with Red.
I'II be back. - I'II wait for you.
See you Iater.
Yeah? No, he's at schooI.
Yeah, I'm sure.
What do you mean, he's not there?
OK, thanks.
You sure as heII aren't getting
a schoIarship if you stay in the sack!
You got a Spanish test,
didn't you? Afraid of a IittIe test?
CoId.
You've got your covers off you.
Don't puII this shit with me, Rock!
Do you hear me? Wake up!
Come on, baby, make yourseIf weII.
Rocky, wake up!
oh, God!
Now you can go
anywhere you want, baby.
These things are good:
Ice cream and cake.
A ride on a HarIey.
Monkeys in the trees.
The rain on my tongue
and the sun shining on my face.
These things are a drag:
Dust in my hair.
HoIes in my shoes.
No money in my pocket
and the sun
shining on my face.
DVD Subtitles:
-klepal-
retimed and divided
by Goliash