Dai Minh Khai country,
going from extremity
To strengthen Jiangshan
Emperor set a home network protection
provides security seriously
He trains street orphans under
a strict totalitarian
regime
Within the law, these
secret guards bypass
judiciary procedure
Outside of the court, they
have their own code of law
They are called JINYIWEI,
The Brocade Guards
Their commander
and the best fighter
is given the name QINGLONG
He was granted
the FOURTEEN BLADES
Inside this box houses
fourteen different
steel blades
Eight of these blades are marked:
Sky, Earth, Rank, Law, Wisdom, Trust,
Benevolence, Bravery
That are used for interrogation
The remaining six are used execution
First to kill those who disobey
the court and the emperor
Second to kill those who interfere
with the imperial administration
Third to kill those who
practice grafting
and bend the law
Fourth to kill those who commit treason
Fifth to kill guards who lay their
Jinyiwei brothers
The last of them, a Golden Sword:
Fulfill your mission or,
failing that lay down your life
These orphans are alone in the world
Under wise rule
They defend the country
Yet under fatuous rule
They become a walking terror to
the people
In JINYIWEI are involved in highly
military and political affairs
When missions go awry, they often
lose their lives
Meeting their sorrowful fate
THE NORTH
PRINCE QING'S ROYAL CITY
Prince Qing is the uncle of the
Emperor
During the last Emperor's reign, he led the army in a failed revolt
Which cost him both his legs
And resulting in his exile
My Lord
All is arranged regarding our plan
has presented an satisfied
with Jia Jingzhong
But I am digusted at the thought of his greedy face
More disgusting is the fact that
he is the reason I am still alive
Indeed you've given him what you've promised
Now he even wants more
Greedy souls are what I'm after
Money is countable
Nothing but some numbers
What I loathe are unsettled debts
THE FORBIDDEN CITY QIANQING PALACE
Your loyal slave Jia Jingzhong
is here to wish your Majesty a long and healthful life
Tuo is here, noble Father
Tuo Tuo
Do you know why I have called for you?
I shall fulfill your wish, my beloved, adoptive Father
My Lord
JINYIWEI HEADQUARTERS
Qinglong
Our kingdom is under siege
Zhao Shenyan is conspiring to revolt
You must reclaim the treasure box that the emperor has bestowed upon him
In it is solid proff of his treason
Do you have the Emperor's Order
General Qinglong, bow to your order
Emperor Secret Order
Counselor Zhao Shenyan is conspiring to revolt
The Emperor has ordered for Jinyiwei Qinglong to execute the mission
Bai Hu and Zhu Que
will take lead in your absence
Xuan Wu will be re-stationed at the East Chamber
With his Majesty's Royal Blessing
General Qinglong receives his Majesty's Order
THE COUNSELOR'S RESIDENCE
Father, I am afraid
It is alright, Shouzheng
Shenyan
Let us leave together
Madame, I cannot do that
Is it because of the box
It must be the Jinyiwei
General Huang
You must escort Madame out of the city tonight
Yes
Father...Father
Father...
promise me
You must come for us
I promise you son
Father...don't forget
Now quickly, to the study
Mum, I'm afraid
Don't be afraid
Brothers
Do not make me strike
Kill
Councilor
please hand over his Majesty's treasure box
You should know
I would rather die
than surrender
to this corrupt court
Show yourself
Shouzheng
Father..Father
Let him go, let him go
You are despicable
I know I will not get it out of you
Forgive me, for I am here on a mission
I'll have to ask him
Shouzheng, don't be afraid
Listen to me
Shouzheng, he is lying to you
Tell me
Shouzheng, you must not tell
I said you must not tell
I didn't tell
Uncle said he will grant me any wish
I said..
I said
I wanted you back
Did Jia Jingzhong not tell you
the Imperial Seal is in the box
Qinglong
Did you ever think
If this seal were to fall into the wrong hands
How many lives
would be sacrificed and killed
Enough
To protect this Seal
It is your duty as Jinyiwei
Greetings to General Xuan Wu
Xuan Wu
You bastard
Let me out if you dare
I will kill you
Xuan Wu
You are wasting your breath
Kill them
Xuan Wu, when people see the glory of your success
They will forget the sinister nature of your means
I was right
Guards, release Bai Hu
Tuo Tuo is here on behalf of my Father
Coming to Sir Jia's aid
We know of Qinglong's escape and to avoid unnecesary trouble
I will help Sir Jia to get rid of Qinglong
Do you have proof
That you are indeed Prince Qing's daughter
Yours
Big Head
Use the money well
Boss
You even give us the dowry
When they come for you
What will you give them
Don't worry
I can handle it
Flag Bearer, here's yours
Boss
We are disbanded
What about this flag
Keep it
There won't be...
a Justice Escorts ever again
We could have kept going
We have been in debt too long
We can't possible keep up
Qiao Hua
We are all getting old
I could come with you
Father
I don't want to marry
Haven't the debtors already come?
We said we would pay them in two days
Qiao Hua
Sir, can I help you
I have a job for you
I am sorry sir
We have just closed down
Boss
There are three hundred taels here
When all is done
You get an additional three hundred
taels
Sir
Is it this chest you wish for us to escort
No...It's me
Thank you, thank you
Congratulations Boss
Quickly
Everyone
is to be searched thoroughly today
Wait
Sir Yang
Boss Yong
Why all the strict searching today
What happened
Jinyiwei Qinglong
is on arrest for treason
The Emperor has ordered
execution to anyone
who let him go at the gate
My daughter is getting married
Married
Didn't she get married last year
Let's
not talk about it
Oh.. right, right
Sir Yang, won't you help us out
We are in a hurry
Please let us through
Surely
But I'll have to search first
Sir Yang
Uncle Yang
My niece is prettier every time I see
Uncle Yang, you sure know how to joke
Alright, I've searched this one
Turn around, I'll escort you myself
You can let go of my hand
If it doesn't work out this time either
you should marry me
Quick
Come on
Go
Boss, it's our own wine
Give some to everyone
Order from Boss, we've had a long day
Sir, have some food
This is aged wine specially brewed
It is good for bruises
Have some
It will be good to your wounds
My Father started brewing this since he founded Justice
It's been forty-six years
When I was young,
I couldn't understand
When I grew older
and watched him
tolerating the ways of this world
I finally understood that the wine didn't help him
with bruises and wounds
I want to help him
But he refuses me
If it weren't for my marriage
He would never have let me come
I really wish
A hero in this world
Can take over Justice
What fragrant wine
Who...
is the boss around here
It's me. Qiao Yong from Justice Escorts in the city
We are new here, excuse us
We are the Sky Eagle Clan
He is the famous
"Blade Number One" The Judge of the Desert
Today, we Sky Eagles give you face
Why do people like to bully others Eighty taels of white silver
You will not pass if it is one tael less
Right
Has this world changed?
Must we common folk live without any respect and dignity?
Do not touch my flag
Flag Bearer
Boss
Dignity is within oneself
No one can take it away from you
Don't
You're risking your life
Charge
Who's there
Who would have thought
I didn't see
Sorry, boss
Sorry, boss... retreat
Boss, I saw the Jinyiwei plaque around
his wait with my own eyes
Go, go go..
Don't
He is in the carriage
I've been waiting for you
Jinyiwei Formation
Do you know I was the one who created this
Qiao Hua
Let me go
Jinyiwei Qinglong
Sir Jia thinks too highly of you
He's Qinglong
First kill, interfering with the higher power
Second kill, brother killing brother
I'll tell...I'll tell
It was Xuan Wu...he made me come after you
Who killed Bai Hu and Zhu Que?
Xuan Wu killed Zhu Que
Bia Hu was killed
by a girl from the West
sent by Prince Qing
Her sword was incredibly quick
Her name is Tuo Tuo
Go back to Jia Jingzhong
Tell him there's no longer a Qinglong from Jinyiwei
Tell him to leave me alone
Yes yes yes
Scram
Since you are a Jinyiwei
Our services to you end here
Your money
Please take it back
You will not harm my father
Let's talk about it
I only have one daughter
Please I beg you
You must travel to the East
And casually mention my name wherever you visit
to divert attention away from me
3 days later, at Cotton Village
You will have two choices
One
Have your daughter back
Two
Have her corpse back
Father..Father
Qiao Hua... Qiao Hua
Father, Father
You were peeking
I need to pee
What are you doing
Go
You may eat after you finish daming
We have guests
Papa, look
Come on, have a hug
Take a seat
Sir and Miss
We have some excellent broiled beef here,
would you like to try some
Yes, could we have half a kilo please
Let's have some on the juicy side, it would smell lovely
We also have some stewed goat's hooves in garlic
We'll have half a kilo of that too
Could you put more onion in it
Goat is a bit much for me
Surely
We have some grape wine as well
We don't want grape wine
I don't want wine from the West either
Half a kilo of white wine
We're hungry...get on it
Right away
Yes
Please enjoy
I may not know the ways of the world,
but I know my way around the table
I can't eat if you touch it..
take this
Check please
Everything Satisfactory, sir and miss
Yes
We have unbeatable prices too... just on tael and four pence
I don't have money
I'm your hostage
I gave it all to your father
Do you have money or not?
I knew by the looks of you two
That is was too good to be true
Boss, you just wait. I'm taking them to the guards
Wait just one minute
Do you know who he is
He is a Jin...
My family name is Jin
I'm sorry, we really don't have money with us
I hope this gold medallion will be enough
I knew that you had it all along, I'll get you change right away
What are you doing
We could have easily bought ten horses
with the money you gave them
Is Qinglong your real name
This is what they call me.. I don't have a name
How did you become a Jinyiwei
Brother
Brother, brother
I have no choice
Don't you think it is a sin
to have killed so many
I never ask why
I only ask when, where and who
Have you thought of quitting
There is no quitting in the life of a Jinyiwei
Our path is a short one
I will be done soon
If no one is after you
You could leave
To finish a mission is the only dignity for a Jinyiwei
Knowing fully well
my fiance is cheating behind my back
Having to feign ignorace and go forth with a wedding
How's that for no dignity
I wanted to devote myself to a man I love
But alas, his heart is not mine to have
I also wish for
a hero in this world
But alas, he kills without compassion
Still I have hope for the future
My mother used to tell me
It is fortunate to have hope
Everyone has chosen their own path
Quiglong, taht goes for you too
As long as you keep walking
You will see blue sky
Take this food
to the table
Go now
Here is our honey chicken
And this is toasted bread
And here, is our home brew wine
Let me know if you need anything else
Scram
Sir
Has the secret document arrived?
Yes it has
Let's get you some new clothes
Miss, you look gorgeous in this
It suits you well
Why don't you try this head scart too.. they match together
You look pretty
Try on another
I think this one looks even better
Can you do something for me
What is it
Go to the guard post
And find a man call Jia Jingzhong
If they ask you who you are
Give them this letter
But a woman walking into a guard post...
You'll look like a man in this
I have something else to take care of
I will come for you afterwards
Yes
What are you here for
I am here for Jia Jingzhong
Who are you
Surround him
Qinglong
When you could stay in heaven
Why invite yourself to hell
There is no quitting in the life of a JInyiwei
There is no quitting in the life of a Jinyiwei
What business do you ahve with Sir Jia
We Jinyiwei
never ask why
Only when, where, and who
Jia Jingzhong is planning to sell the three districts
And the gold will be delivered by Captain Xiahou himself
The twelfth day of this month
That is today
Qinglong, do you think you can do
whatever you want around here
To finish a mission
is the only dignity for a Jinyiwei
Capture him
Arrest him
It's a woman
Let me go
Greetings, Captain
Show me the way
Yes
What are you doing
Did I ask for your help?
You wanted to use me
Remember this
You are not allowed to be out of my site
Do you understand?
Give me your hand
Thank you
Waiter...Coming
We have guests
Coming
Table for two
This way
please
You've arrived just in time
If you are not in a hurry
You can watch the fireworks tonight
Want a room? Yes, We will be staying here for the night