This is Media-Break.
You give us three minutes
and we'll give you the world.
Good morning, I'm Casey Wong
with Jess Perkins.
Top story, Pretoria.
The threat of nuclear confrontation
in South Africa escalated today...
...when the military government
of that besieged city-state...
...unveiled a French-made
neutron bomb...
...and affirmed that it would use
it as the city's last line of defense.
The president's first press conference
from the Star Wars Peace Platform...
...got off to a shaky start
when power failed...
...causing a period of weightlessness
for the president and his staff.
We'll be back in a moment.
Is it time for that operation?
This may be the most important
decision of your life.
So come down and talk to one of our
qualified surgeons...
...at the Family Heart Center.
We feature the complete line
of hearts by Jensen and Yamaha.
You pick the heart.
Extended warranties. Financing.
Qualifies for health tax credit.
And remember, we care.
Three dead police officers,
one critically injured.
Police leaders blame
Omni Consumer Products, OCP...
...the firm which recently agreed
with the city to fund and run...
...the Detroit Metro
Police Department.
Dick Jones, president of OCP.
Every policeman knows
there are inherent risks in his job.
If you can't stand the heat,
you better stay out of the kitchen.
Although wounded, Officer Frederickson
escaped and identified this man.
Clarence Boddicker, unofficial
crime boss of Old Detroit...
...sought in connection with
the deaths of 31 officers.
Today he is free while doctors
at Henry Ford Hospital...
...fight to save
Officer Frank Frederickson.
Good luck, Frank.
Attempted murder?
It's not like he killed someone.
This violates
my client's civil rights.
Make it assault and I can make
bail in cash, now.
Listen, your client's a scumbag,
you're a scumbag...
...and scumbags see the judge.
Now get out of my police station
and take Laughing Boy with you.
Hi.
Murphy, transferring in
from Metro South.
Nice precinct.
Yeah, pretty good.
You work for a living down here.
Get your armor and suit up.
- No, you can't get a cup of coffee.
- Oh, sarge.
- Stark, any word on Frederickson?
- Still listed as critical.
His wife must be going crazy.
- Murphy?
- Yeah, that's me.
- Manson.
- Hi.
What brings you to paradise?
I think the OCP's moving
a lot of new guys here.
Omni Consumer Products.
What a bunch of morons.
They're gonna manage this department
right into the ground.
- Where you from?
- Metro South.
Welcome to hell.
- Murphy?
- Yo.
- Cut 10 guys loose on the east side.
- Try to get up when you're in a jam.
Try to get a Medevac
after you been jammed.
I'll tell you what we should do.
We should strike.
The funeral is tomorrow.
Department requests all officers
not on duty to attend.
Any donations for the family
may be given to Cecil as usual.
I don't want to hear any more
talk about strike.
We're not plumbers,
we're police officers.
And police officers don't strike.
Murphy. Front and center.
Ooh, tiger!
Lewis, come here when you're finished
fucking around with your suspect.
This guy's gonna be your new partner.
Murphy, meet Lewis.
Show him the neighborhood.
Glad to know you, Murphy.
Pretty neat.
I better drive
until you know your way around.
I usually drive
when I'm breaking in a new partner.
You really think
the old man will be there?
Why invite us?
All the division heads are bringing
their support teams. It's big.
They're green lighting Delta City.
No way. They never
move ahead of schedule.
Jones has the 209 series ready
and wants to show off.
- Tough break, Bob.
- What?
When ED 209 ran into serious delays...
...the old man ordered a backup plan.
95th floor, have a nice day.
Probably to light a fire
under Jones' ass.
- Yeah.
- Old Bob here gets the assignment.
Nobody in Security Concepts
takes it seriously.
Fucking Jones, I'd go
straight to the old man if I could.
Don't mess with Jones.
Be careful, man.
I hear Jones is a real shark.
- Who asked you, twerp?
- Bob.
What's the problem with the police?
Their union's been bitching ever since
we took over. The usual stuff.
But we'll turn things around.
Good. Very good.
Let's get started.
My friends.
I've had this dream
for more than a decade now.
A dream which I've invited
you all to share with me.
In six months
we begin construction...
...of Delta City.
Where Old Detroit now stands.
Old Detroit has a cancer.
The cancer is crime.
It must be cut out before we
employ the 2 million...
...workers to breathe life
back into the city.
Yes.
Shifts in tax structure have made the
economy ideal for corporate growth.
But community services,
in this case law enforcement...
...have suffered.
I think it's time
we gave something back.
Take a close look
at the track record of this company.
You'll see that we've gambled...
...in markets usually regarded
as nonprofit.
Hospitals. Prisons.
Space exploration.
I say, good business
is where you find it.
As you know, we now have a contract
to run local law enforcement.
But at Security Concepts...
...we believe an efficient police
force is only part of the solution.
No, we need something more.
We need a 24-hour-a-day
police officer.
A cop who doesn't need
to eat or sleep.
A cop with superior firepower
and the reflexes to use it.
Fellow executives...
...it's a pleasure to introduce you
to the future of law enforcement.
ED 209.
The Enforcement Droid series 209...
...is a self-sufficient
law enforcement robot.
209 is programmed for urban
pacification, but that's just a start.
After a successful
tour in Old Detroit...
...we can expect 209 to become the hot
military product for the next decade.
- Dr. McNamara.
- We'll need a subject.
- Mr. Kinney.
- Yes, sir.
- Will you give us a hand?
Mr. Kinney will help us simulate a
typical arrest and disarming procedure.
Mr. Kinney, use your gun
in a threatening manner.
- Point it at ED 209.
- Yes, sir.
Please put down your weapon.
You have 20 seconds to comply.
I think you better
do what he says.
You now have 15 seconds to comply.
You are in direct violation
of penal code 113, section 9.
- You have five seconds to comply.
- Help me!
- Four, three, two, one.
- Help me! Help!
I am now authorized
to use physical force.
Somebody want to call a paramedic?
- Let's go, Johnson.
- You pull the plug on this thing?
All right, don't touch him.
- Don't touch him!
- He didn't hear the gun drop.
He didn't hear it?!
Dick, I'm very disappointed.
It's only a glitch.
A temporary setback.
You call this a glitch?
We're to begin
construction in six months.
This setback could cost us
millions in interest costs alone.
Not necessarily, sir.
There's a Robocop program...
...I developed as a contingency
against just this sort of thing.
Thank you for your concern.
- This is something we could...
- Wait a minute. Dick!
Maybe what we need here
is a fresh perspective.
Tell me about your plan.
How long will it take?
We've restructured the police
department with some good candidates.
We can go to prototype
within 90 days.
Very good.
Get your staff together. I'll expect
a presentation in 20 minutes.
Thank you, sir.
That's how it is in the big leagues.
You see an opening, you go for it.
Watch your back,
Jones will be looking for you.
Fuck Jones. He fumbled the ball
and I was there to pick it up.
Too bad about Kinney, huh?
That's life in the big city.
When do we start?
As soon as some schmuck volunteers.
Pretty fancy moves, Murphy.
My son watches this cop show,
TJ Lazer.
Lazer does this whenever
he kills a bad guy.
- My kid thinks every good cop...
- You don't want to disappoint him.
Yeah, well, role models can be
very important to a boy.
Okay, I get a kick out of it.
All units, sector nine...
Well, that's...
Why don't you drive?
Shit!
- I don't believe it!
- What?
You burnt the fucking money!
I had to blow the door!
It's as good as marked, asshole.
You stupid, stupid asshole!
- Clarence!
- What do you want?!
We got a cop on our tail.
- Come on, speed it up.
- Move it!
- We ain't gonna outrun a cop.
- Slow down.
- Are you crazy?
- Shut the fuck up and do it!
Just do it!
This is 154. We're in pursuit
of suspect. Request backup.
- Roger, 154. Backup unavailable.
- Give me your piece.
Backup ETA, 15 minutes.
Bobby, get the door!
- Everybody load up!
- Let's go, come on.
- Okay.
- All right, here we go.
- What the fuck?
- Where'd he go?
Emil!
He's up here!
Get him!
Shit, Clarence, my leg.
Leon, pick him up.
- Ready?
- Nope, hang on.
Bobby.
- Can you fly, Bobby?
- Clarence, no!
Hit it!
This is 154. We've located that van
in sector 3D. Where's backup?
Backup unavailable. Estimate 20
minutes before units can arrive.
Well, you call it.
- Let's's do it.
- Okay.
Go.
Stay in touch.
Freeze.
Okay, let's see those hands.
Nice and easy.
Sure.
Mind if I zip this up?
We rob banks, but never
get to keep the money.
We steal money to buy coke,
then sell the coke to make more money.
- Capital investment, man.
- Why bother? We could just steal it.
No better way to steal
than free enterprise.
Smoke?
No, those things will kill you.
You want to live forever?
Don't move.
Go ahead and do it.
Dead or alive, you're coming with me.
Lewis?
Lewis!
I got a situation in here.
Okay, tough guy, get up. Get up!
Turn around and spread your legs.
That's right.
Lewis, where are you?
You all right?
Hands on your head.
Lewis.
Let us take over from here, Emil.
Your ass is mine.
No!
Not yet, it ain't.
Well, what have we here?
You a good cop, hotshot?
Sure you are.
You gotta be some kind of great cop.
Come in here all by yourself.
Where's your partner?
Guys, the other one was upstairs.
She was sweet.
I took her out.
I bet that really pisses you off.
You probably don't think
I'm a very nice guy.
Do you?
I think you're slime.
See, I got this problem.
Cops don't like me.
So I don't like cops.
Well, give the man a hand.
He's all yours.
- Look out.
- Turn around, man.
Hey, pretty boy. Hey, over here.
I'm out of ammo.
Me too.
Does it hurt? Does it hurt?
Okay, fun's over.
Okay, let's get out of here.
Good night, sweet prince.
Hey, wait up. Wait up.
Murphy.
- Get him over.
- Clear.
Ventilate him. Get the mask.
Okay, hit the door.
- Let me get pressure.
- Mask him.
Got a pressure of 60 pel.
We're gonna have to
intubate this guy.
All right, I got it in.
Breath sounds?
- You're in.
- Other side.
- Let's get the mask trousers up.
- Get the clothes off.
Clothes off. Prep him
for a central line.
Let's get some blood drawn.
Type and crossing, six units.
Pressure's dropping.
Central line's in, getting
pressure back. Normal saline.
Can you do that, Dad?
- I really have to tell you something.
- Blood pressure?
- I've got 40 pel.
- All right.
Coarse D-fib.
Okay, we gotta shock him.
Put the Foley in.
Let's blow the mask trousers.
- Okay.
- Stand clear.
Coarse D-fib.
Let's shock him again.
Clear.
Flat line. Let's go,
intracardiac epinephrine.
- All right, it's in.
- No pulse.
Let's go ahead and shock
a flat line and then quit.
- Okay, everybody stand clear.
- Clear.
All right, that's all we can do.
Let's call it.
What's the time?
6:15.
Sharp.
It's starting to roll.
Shit!
Bring in the L.E.D.
Lock it down.
- He's on.
- What's the story?
- We saved the left arm.
- What?
We agreed on total body prosthesis.
Now lose the arm.
Jesus, Morton.
- Can he understand?
- We'll blank his memory, anyway.
We should lose the arm.
What do you think?
He signed a release when he joined
the force. And he's dead.
We can do pretty much what we want.
Lose the arm.
Shut him down. Prep him for surgery.
The outer skin will be like this.
It's titanium, laminated with Kevlar.
Go ahead, shake his hand.
Come here often? How you doing?
Got a hell of a grip.
It's 400 foot-pounds.
He could crush
every bone in your hand.
All right, attach it to his shoulder.
I like that.
You're gonna be a bad motherfucker!
Hey, hey. Look, he's watching us!
This is for you.
Happy New Year.
We get the best of both worlds.
The fastest reflexes possible today...
...computer-assisted memory...
...and a lifetime of on-the-street
officer programming.
It is my great pleasure
to present to you...
...Robocop.
Come on, come on.
That's for you.
- That's for you.
- Go, Robo.
I'm what you call a repeat offender.
I will offend again.
I get my orders from a higher source.
Shut up, asshole.
- Go through the side.
- A cell is set for observation.
What's this all about?
- Who's this?
- Sergeant John Reed.
It's official OCP business,
so please, get lost.
- We got four or five days...
- Hey, this is bullshit!
I take my orders from...
What is this shit?
When at rest, you'll sit in a chair.
Yes, I understand.
What about tracking?
We check his exact location
with one of these.
How does he eat?
His digestive system is simple.
This processor dispenses a paste
that sustains his organic systems.
It tastes like baby food.
Knock yourself out.
- Let's start with tracking.
- Give me a grid.
- Got it?
- Clear.
- Target.
- Check.
Now follow.
Check.
Voice stress analyzer.
- It's up.
- One, two...
...three.
- Check.
- Record.
- Now playback.
- Bring it up 50%.
Full frame.
I think he's ready.
- We got it.
- All right, clear out.
What are your prime directives?
Serve the public trust.
Protect the innocent. Uphold the law.
That's good.
That's very good.
I fucking love that guy.
- It's Supercop.
- Look at that fucking gun.
Shit!
- This guy is good.
- He's not a guy, he's a machine.
What are they gonna do?
Replace us?
Come on.
- Reed.
- Yeah.
He needs a car.
Thank you.
Sure.
Anytime.
Oh, yeah. Go get 'em, boy.
I'd buy that for a dollar.
And guess what I'm going to do now?
Happy birthday, Bixby.
Is there anything else, sir?
Empty the register
and put the money in the bag.
Excuse me?
I said, give me your money, all of it,
and don't fuck with me!
Now move!
Open the safe, pops.
Open the goddamn safe!
- We don't have a safe.
- Shit.
There's your goddamned safe!
Now open the son of a bitch.
Quit stalling.
You better open that son of a bitch!
Come on!
I'm gonna blow her brains out.
- I'll open the safe.
- Good boy.
You better open that on the count
of three. One, two...
Fuck me.
Drop the gun. You are under arrest.
Fuck me! Fuck me! Fuck me!
Thank you for your cooperation.
Good night.
I'll buy that for a dollar!
No, please!
Don't touch me!
- Get away! Get away!
- We don't want your money!
Take it easy.
We don't want to hurt you.
Too much hair.
I know! We'll give her a haircut.
- Hey, hey!
- What?
There's more hair down there!
No! Don't!
Please.
Let the woman go.
You are under arrest.
Shit.
You better back up, pal,
because he's gonna do her!
He's gonna kill her!
Your move, creep.
No problem. It's okay.
Thank God.
I was so scared. Thank you.
Thank you.
Madam, you have suffered
an emotional shock.
I will notify a rape crisis center.
All units, sector six.
Please close intersections...
I don't care.
Get those men by the stairs, now.
Terrorism has never been a factor
in city politics before.
That changed today
when former councilman...
...Ron Miller entered
City Hall with a gun.
He's on the second floor...
...holding Mayor Gibson
and his staff hostage.
We do believe that Miller
has killed one of the hostages.
- Lieutenant, what's next?
- We wait. Terrorism is very tricky.
Massive and immediate retaliation
is the best policy. Unfortunately...
- Excuse us.
- Wait, where you going?
Statement, please.
Hey, let's have some crowd control.
Come on, get these people back!
- Where the hell are you going?
- Keep him talking.
One quick question here!
Who made you?
Are you invincible?
Okay, Miller. Don't hurt the mayor.
We'll give you whatever you want.
First, don't fuck with me.
I'm a desperate man.
And second, I want some fresh coffee.
And third, I want a recount.
No matter how it turns out,
I want my old job back.
- Okay.
- And I want a bigger office.
And I want a new car!
And I want the city to pay for it all!
- What kind of car, Miller?
- One with reclining leather seats...
...that goes really fast
and gets really shitty gas mileage.
How about the 6000 SUX?
Yeah.
Okay, sure.
What about cruise control?
Does it have cruise control?
No problem, Miller.
Let the mayor go,
we'll even throw in a Blaupunkt.
Lieutenant, don't jerk me off!
When people jerk me off, I kill them!
You want to see?
Get up, Your Honor. Get up!
Get up. Your public wants to see you.
Nobody ever takes me seriously!
We'll get serious now...
...and kiss the mayor's ass goodbye!
Robocop. Who is he? What is he?
Where does he come from?
He is OCP's newest soldier...
...in their revolutionary
crime management program.
OCP spokesmen claim
the fearless machine...
...has crooks on the run
in Old Detroit.
Today, kids at Lee lacocca Elementary
got to meet in person...
...what their parents only
read about in comic books.
Excuse me, Robo...
...any special message for all
the kids watching at home?
Stay out of trouble.
More fighting in the Mexican crisis...
...when American troops joined
in a raid with Mexican Nationals...
...against rebel rocket
positions in Acapulco.
Now this.
Red alert. Red alert.
You crossed my line of death.
You haven't dismantled
your MX stockpile.
Pakistan is threatening my border!
That's it, buster.
No more military aid.
Nukem.
Get them before they get you.
Another quality home game
from Butler Brothers.
Today labor leaders agreed to sanction
construction of OCP's Delta City...
...thereby creating one million
much-needed new jobs...
...despite questions about worker
safety in dangerous Old Detroit.
Robert Morton, vice president,
Security Concepts, OCP.
I can't comment on Delta City.
But I will tell you this:
Security Concepts projects the end of
crime in Old Detroit within 40 days.
There's a new guy in town.
His name's Robocop.
Hey, hey, hey, Bobby-boy.
Vice president. Congratulations.
- Handball Tuesday night?
- I would, Bill...
...but I've got some models
coming to my place.
I'd buy that for a dollar.
Welcome to the club, Bob.
You're making a name for yourself
in Security Concepts with Robocop.
I try.
Let me in on the bottom line, pal.
I hear Jones was plenty pissed.
You know, he's got this killer rep,
but it's a smoke screen.
He's lost his teeth.
The guy's a pussy.
Are we talking about
the same Dick Jones?
He's old, we're young. That's life.
I gotta go. I got a meeting.
Congratulations, Bob.
Thanks.
I remember when I was
a young executive at this company.
We used to call
the old man funny names.
"Iron Butt."
"Boner."
Once I even called him...
..."asshole."
But there was always respect.
I always knew
where the line was drawn.
And you just stepped over it,
buddy-boy.
You've insulted me.
And you've insulted this company
with your bastard creation.
I had a guaranteed
military sale with ED 209.
Renovation program.
Spare parts for 25 years.
Who cares if it worked or not?
The old man thought
it was pretty important, Dick.
You know...
...he's a sweet old man.
And he means well.
But he's not gonna live forever.
And I'm number two around here.
Pretty simple math, huh, Bob?
You just...
...fucked with the wrong guy.
You're out of your fucking mind.
You better pray...
...that that unholy monster
of yours doesn't screw up.
You hungry?
No, thanks.
Oh, no.
Damn rebels blew up
the airport in Acapulco.
Great, we were going there next week.
Hey, what was that?
Hey, look.
Bucket-boy's online.
Hey. Hey!
Halt. Stop!
Wait a minute!
- What's going on?
- I don't know. He just left.
He just left?
Roosevelt!
We got a problem.
Out of the way.
Take a look at this.
Shit! Call Bob Morton.
Jerry, book him.
I'll catch up with you later.
Hello.
I haven't really had a chance
to introduce myself.
I'm Anne Lewis.
Do you have a name?
How can I help you, Officer Lewis?
That's not really what I meant.
Don't you have a name?
Hold it. Sign right here.
You don't understand. I'm OCP.
Murphy.
It's you.
You really don't remember me?
Excuse me.
I have to go.
Somewhere, there is a crime happening.
Stop!
- What did you talk to him about?
- Nothing.
- Shit.
Stop!
Hey, you there! Stop!
You're in a lot of trouble, officer.
Come on.
I was assured full cooperation
by this precinct.
One of your grunts screws it up,
I'll have your job!
- What's the update?
- Hard to know.
- We have a glitch or what?
- He wasn't designed for somatic rest.
He had a dream. A dream.
This cop questioned him.
I didn't question him.
I asked his name. He didn't know.
Oh, great.
Let me make it clear. He doesn't
have a name, he has a program.
He's product.
- Is that clear?
- Sure.
Pull him in.
Run a systems check, the works.
Take him offline
because he had a dream?
What, are you kidding?
Let's get out of here.
Listen, Reed.
Try to keep one thing in mind:
This project doesn't concern cops.
It's classified.
It's OCP. You got it, mister?
Yeah, I got it.
Good.
Sorry, sarge.
I fucked up.
Forget it, kid.
This guy's a serious asshole.
Give me all your money, bookworm,
or I blow your brains out.
Now fill it up on number seven.
Don't do nothing stupid, man.
I'm a good shot.
I can hit you from here.
Hey, man...
...what you reading in there?
You a college boy or something?
I'll bet you think you're smart.
Think you could outsmart a bullet?
What do you say we find out, huh?
I'm talking to you!
What do you say, huh?
Drop it.
Dead or alive, you are coming with me.
I know you.
You're dead.
We killed you.
We killed you!
Who are you?
Can I help you, sir?
No.
What is it exactly that you want?
Hey.
You can't enter here.
Wait a second. Hey, just a minute.
This is a restricted area.
He's in.
Murphy, it's you.
Welcome, shopper. Let's take
a stroll through your new home.
This is a one-family house
built by ZM Industries.
Situated near schools and shops...
...this progressive development
has a growth factor of seven.
Wow.
Can you do that, Dad?
Say, it doesn't matter
who cooks in your family...
...because this kitchen
by Food Concepts...
...makes everything a snap.
Dad.
Come on, get your hat on.
Isn't he cute?
Come on, Dad. Come on, Dad.
I really have to tell you something.
I love you.
The master bedroom.
Functional space
with a touch of elegance.
Hey, have you thought it all over?
Why not make me an offer?
Where is Clarence Boddicker?
Okay.
- Shit.
- Let's talk.
Son of a bitch!
There's just something
about the way it sounds:
"Vice president."
It just turns me on.
God, you girls are so great.
I love to be with intelligent women.
Smart is so sexy.
I know.
Sometimes, I could just
think of something...
...and it could just get me so horny.
Yeah, well, a mind is
a terrible thing to waste.
I get bored so easily.
And you need lots
of stimulation, Bobby.
Yes, I do.
- Don't move.
- I won't.
Bob, save some for me.
Don't worry.
Must be the champagne. Stay here.
How you doing?
Bitches, leave.
Gee, Bobby. Bye.
You gonna call me?
The fuck are you doing?
Do you know who I am?
If you think you'll get away
with this, you got...
Goddamn it!
Stop!
I'll give you anything you want.
Just, please, don't kill me.
Hello, buddy-boy.
Dick Jones here.
I guess you're on
your knees about now...
...begging for your life.
Pathetic.
You don't feel so cocky now, do you?
Whatever he's paying you,
I'll double it right now.
You know what the tragedy is here?
We could have been friends.
But you wouldn't go
through proper channels.
You went over my head.
That hurt.
But life goes on. It's an old story,
the fight for love and glory.
It helps if you think of it as a game.
Every game has a winner...
...and a loser.
I'm cashing you out, Bob.
I don't think I want to pay that, Sal.
I don't give a shit what you want.
I set the prices here.
Listen, Sal, maybe you haven't heard.
I'm the guy who owns Detroit.
You want space in my marketplace...
...you'll have to give me
a volume discount.
Not into discounts.
Joe, show the man what we brought him
for Christmas.
Think about it, chum.
Good business is where you find it.
Okay, let me try
to put this in perspective.
You've killed a bunch of cops.
Word around is that you've got a lot
of heavy connections downtown.
You make a lot of my friends nervous.
A lot of people...
...want to see a guy like me...
...put a guy like you out of business.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm just not
making myself clear.
I don't want to fuck with you, Sal.
But I got the connections.
I got the sales organization.
I got the muscle
to shove enough of this factory...
...so far up your stupid wop ass...
...that you'll shit snow for a year.
Frankie,
blow this cocksucker's head off.
Guns, guns, guns!
Come on, Sal!
The Tigers are playing tonight.
I never miss a game.
Just kidding.
Go!
Come quietly,
or there will be trouble.
Fuck you!
Oh, shit!
Clarence Boddicker...
...you are under arrest.
You have the right to remain silent.
Fuck you!
Hey, wait a minute. Wait a minute!
I'm protected, man.
I've got protection!
- You have the right to an attorney.
- What is this shit?!
Goddamn it.
Goddamn it! Listen to me!
Listen to me, you fuck!
It's another guy! He's OCP.
He's the senior president.
Anything you say
may be used against you.
It's Dick Jones!
Don't you care, you cocksucker?
I work for Dick Jones!
Dick Jones!
He's the number two guy at OCP!
OCP runs the cops!
You're a cop!
Cop...
Yes, I am a cop.
I don't like it either, but listen!
You listen to me, asshole!
You're talking about shutting down
a major metropolitan police force!
Without cops,
this city would tear itself apart!
The union voted for a strike
last night!
We lost five guys last week!
We're getting creamed out there.
Book him.
What's the charge?
He's a cop killer.
Shit!
Just give me my fucking phone call.
I understand. The lawyers
will have you out in 24 hours.
Just don't say anything else.
Jesus, you really screwed up.
Don't you care?
I work for Dick Jones! Dick Jones!
I work for Dick Jones!
He runs OCP! OCP runs the cops!
Come in, officer.
I don't usually see anyone
without an appointment...
...but in your case,
I'll make an exception.
You are under arrest.
On what charge?
Aiding and abetting a known felon.
Sounds like I'm in a lot of trouble.
Better take me in.
I will.
What's the matter, officer?
I'll tell you what's the matter.
It's a little insurance policy
called "Directive 4."
My little contribution
to your psychological profile.
Any attempt to arrest a senior officer
of OCP results in shutdown.
What did you think?
That you were
an ordinary police officer?
You're our product...
...and we can't have our products
turning against us.
Still a little fight left in you.
Maybe you'd like to meet
a friend of mine.
I had to kill Bob Morton
because he made a mistake.
Now it's time to erase that mistake.
Get me Hedgecock!
There's trouble in the tower!
Prepare to fire.
- Wait a second!
- He's a cop, for God's sake!
- You can't do that!
- We have orders to destroy it!
- Oh, shit!
- You're maniacs!
Fire at will!
Move in!
Murphy, it's me.
Lewis.
Level three! He's on level three!
Over here, over here!
Open fire!
It's back.
Big is back.
Because bigger is better.
6000 SUX,
an American tradition.
Good evening.
I'm Jess Perkins with Casey Wong.
Top story: Santa Barbara.
Ten thousand acres
of wooded residential land...
...were scorched in an instant
when a laser canon...
...aboard the Strategic Defense
Peace Platform...
...misfired today
during routine tests.
It was a day of mourning
for the families...
...of 113 people known dead
at this hour.
Among them, two former
U.S. presidents...
...who had retired
in the Santa Barbara area.
A day of mourning for a country.
Police union representatives and OCP
continued negotiations today...
...in hopes of averting
a citywide strike by police...
...scheduled to begin
tomorrow at midnight.
Justin Ballard-Watkins has more.
They're still on duty.
But what about tomorrow?
That's the question we put to people
in the crime-plagued Lexington area.
They're public servants.
They got job security.
They're not supposed to strike.
It's a free society.
Except there ain't nothing free,
because there's no guarantees.
You're on your own.
That's the law of the jungle.
- Be very careful.
- Excuse me, please.
Remodeling.
Hi, Barbara.
Listen, I'm here to see Dick Jones.
But when I'm done,
I've got some free time.
Maybe you could fit me in.
He's expecting you, Mr. Boddicker.
You can keep the gum.
Hey, Dickie-boy. How's tricks?
That thing is still alive.
What are you talking about?
The police officer who arrested you,
the one you spilled your guts to.
Take a look at my face, Dick.
He was trying to kill me.
He's a cyborg, you idiot!
He recorded every word you said.
His memory's admissible as evidence!
You involved me!
You'll have to kill it.
Well, listen, chief.
Your company built the fucking thing.
Now I gotta deal with it?
I don't have time for this bullshit!
Suit yourself. But Delta City
begins construction in two months.
That's 2 million workers
living in trailers.
That means drugs,
gambling, prostitution.
Virgin territory for the man
who knows how to open up new markets.
One man could control it all...
...Clarence.
Well, I guess we're gonna
be friends after all.
Richard.
Destroy it.
Gonna need some major firepower.
You got access to military weaponry?
We practically are the military.
Did you bring the gun?
The precinct was deserted. Half the
force didn't show up for work today.
Everyone else walks out at midnight.
I guess we're on strike.
I wasn't sure what you needed.
I sort of grabbed things.
Your gun.
You asked for this?
I brought you some food.
No, thank you.
I'm not hungry.
You may not like
what you're going to see.
It's really good
to see you again, Murphy.
Murphy had a wife and son.
Where are they?
Well, after the funeral...
...she moved away.
- Where did they go?
She thought you were dead.
She started over again.
I can feel them.
But I can't remember them.
Leave me alone.
Happy birthday, Dave. She's from me.
Well, hey, can I have you both?
Sure!
We've had our shots.
I'd buy that for a dollar.
Hey, Emil. How's the Gray Bar Hotel?
Not bad. They let me keep the shirt.
And nobody popped my cherry.
Emil, how you doing, man?
Good to see you.
I get out of jail for free, then
I find this in the prison parking lot.
A brand-new 6000 SUX.
Still got the factory sticker on it!
Hey, Clarence!
Joey's got a car just like yours, man!
Clarence, what do you think, buddy?
What do you got there, Clarence, huh?
Whoa, a new toy. Can I play?
Watch this.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute!
Aw, shit!
- Fuck!
- Nice car, Joe.
- Fuck you, Clarence.
- Let me try that.
Cobra assault canon.
State-of-the-art. Bang, bang.
I like it!
- Give it up, faggot little man.
- Get your own!
Come on!
Do it, Emil!
Check this out!
Heads up, you guys!
He's in the steel mill. Let's go.
All right, cut the horseshit!
We're moving out.
Come on, Emil!
Get your ass in the van.
Come on, lard-ass! Let's move it!
Forget you, faggot!
What are you doing?
My targeting system
is a little messed up.
Can I help you?
Aim for me.
- Are you locked in now?
- Yes.
A little more to the left.
Here.
- I figure that's dead-on.
- Thank you.
Come on, man, let's smoke him!
The wrecking crew is here!
Where is that mother...?
Give that up, man!
Nothing fancy. Just kill him. Emil!
- What?
- In the van.
- You should get out of here now.
- Hey, we're partners.
Get the car.
Damn it. Shit!
Looking for me?
Cut him off!
Come on! Go on! Cut him off! Go, go!
Okay! Now I got you!
Help me.
Don't touch me, man!
Shit!
- Bye-bye, baby.
- Clarence!
Okay.
I give up.
I'm not arresting you anymore.
Hey. Now, wait a second.
Wait a minute. You're taking
this kind of personal.
Come on, man.
You're making me nervous.
Come on, you can't do this.
Come on now! Don't mess around!
Hey. Hey!
Now, don't get cute!
Die, you bastard!
Yeah! Yeah!
All right! All right!
I got him, Clarence! I got him!
Sayonara, Robocop!
Lewis!
Murphy, I'm a mess.
They'll fix you.
They fix everything.
The police strike could work for us.
We can have ED 209s
in place all over the city...
...and expect immediate
public support.
I've got one downstairs
guarding the building now.
You're illegally parked
on private property.
You have 20 seconds
to move your vehicle.
Whatever happens...
...this corporation will live up
to its guiding principles:
Courage, strength, conviction.
We will meet each new challenge
with the same aggressive attitude.
How can we help you, officer?
Dick Jones is wanted for murder.
This is absurd! That thing is
a violent mechanical psychopath!
My program will not allow me to act
against an officer of this company.
These are serious charges.
What is your evidence?
I had to kill Bob Morton
because he made a mistake.
Now it's time to erase that mistake.
I had to kill Bob Morton
because he made a mistake.
Now it's time to erase that mistake.
I want a chopper! Now!
We will walk to the roof very calmly.
I will board the chopper
with my hostage.
Anybody tries to stop me...
...the old geezer gets it.
Dick, you're fired!
Thank you.
Nice shooting, son. What's your name?
Murphy.