Early 21st century. Robot technology
undergoes massive development.
By mid-century,
Japan leads the world
in robot knowledge and application.
From domestic uses to weaponry,
Japan dominates the world market.
As the technology is extended
to the human body
the mood of
the international community
turns against use of humanoids.
Just as with nuclear power
and biotechnology before,
U.N. regulations are proposed
to limit robot technology.
Japan fiercely
resists this limitation
but the will of the U.N.
is unshakeable.
Japan takes the extreme step
of withdrawing from the U.N.
And begins a new policy
of national isolation.
Japan uses it high technology
to withdraw from world affairs.
10 years go by.
The resulting information blackout
turns Japan into a total enigma.
For an entire decade,
no foreigner penetrates the veil.
This is disrupting
my entire holiday.
Now that your family has already
left Washington for Denver.
Don't the Japanese
understand it's Christmas?
Dragging us miles out here...
At least the British, French
and Russians are here, too.
"S.W.O.R.D."
The R.A.C.E.
Final stand-by. We go in on my mark.
Dumb gig. Dumb time of year.
Just some Christmas party, right...
Do the job quick
and you'll home
for Mom's Turkey.
Each of the world's nations has
debated the issue of human evolution
and come to
the exact same conclusion.
Thus we can say that this result
represents a true and just future
for humanity.
If we at Daiwa Heavy Industries
have your endorsement,
I'd appreciate a round of applause.
Didn't think so...
The primary target is Saito
of Daiwa Heavy Industries.
We're working on a tip-off.
It might be a trap.
Keep your eyes open.
I said we didn't need 'em.
Why so many robots?
No idea. Ask the chief...
They're the latest Daiwa models.
Latest or not,
I don't trust them.
S.W.O.R.D.?
Darn you, Maria...
Get out of my way!
Darn.
Dispose of all the bodies.
What the heck's going on?
What's SWORD doing here?
Answer me.
Don't you know who I am?
For God's sake, I demand to know.
Leon!
"VEXILLE"
"SWORD HQ, Los Angeles"
It's a flagrant violation
of international treaties.
Wich ones?
They ignored just about every one.
Which part is metallic?
Well, it's bio-metal.
So this was his only robotic part?
I hope that's the case.
But during the raid
we confirmed his bio-signature.
It might've been added later.
Is that even possible?
Not with our technology.
If Japan is manufacturing
androids of this level...
It would pose a threat
equal to nuclear power.
This mean Saito's an android?
In any case,
there's nothing comparable
in the US, legit or otherwise.
It'll take forever
to reverse-engineer.
This reminds me of San Pedro
last month.
Zak...
Despite all the people
living in this city.
We only talk to people with
this badge or to our darn computers.
It's not the city's fault.
It's the age we live in.
Anything from Irene?
Not a word.
Sorry...
Hear anything about San Pedro
from Leon?
Really...
Was the tip-off for this misson
from San Pedro?
Correct.
Not that it's a secret any more.
"Port of San Pedro"
Why the need for us to guard this?
That's the latest
Japanese weapon system.
But any enemy would have 'em, too.
The battlefield is Japan's
showroom after all.
It's not right that everyone
treats Japan special.
Some day, they'll get
what they deserve.
Cease pursuit and withdraw.
You've got to be kidding.
I repeat, caese pursuit immediately.
This is our turf.
Zak!
Be careful.
SWORD...
December...23rd...Mt. Filar...
Beware...of a meeting.
Maria...
Leon trusted
the fugitive completely.
I mean,
even now I can't believe
it was an android.
Function-wise?
You couldn't tell it wasn't human.
Might it have been?
There was
absolutely no bio-signature.
But those eyes...
Autopsy results?
They sent the android back to Japan
after political pressure.
In the end...
they hardly laid a finger on it.
Really...
Maria...
Japan. Completely off our screens
for an entire decade.
But we ignore its
recent suspicious
activity at our peril.
We still don't know
the purpose of
the meeting at Mt. Filar.
But a State Dept. Order says
the politician we detained there
must be returned to his duties.
There's also strong pressure
from Japan to return Saito's limb.
As for the results of the autopsy,
it's composed of
undetecable bio-metal.
Judging from bio-signature analysis,
we strongly suspect Saito is
an android.
Android production is a grave
violation of international treaties.
Nonetheless, the White House
is urging caution.
Any action that
might harm good relations
with Japan, is forbidden.
But Japan is up to something.
Henceforth we at SWORD
will be on our own.
No matter what happens,
you can forget about
goverment protection.
We are to face this threat
to international society
and neutralize it by our own means.
Our mission this time:
to infiltrate Fortress Japan.
Japan has been veiled in mystery
for 10 years.
The time has come to unmask it.
These images are of Tokyo
10 years ago.
As you know, no-one has been there
since its seclusion.
Its most powerful corporation,
Daiwa Heavy Industries,
has dominated the economy
for the past years of isolation.
Daiwa dictates Japan's politics
and controls all aspects of life.
We also guess that it's behind
the policy of national isolation.
Japan's high-tech seclusion
is made possible
by an electro-magnetic network
named R.A.C.E.
It relies on 270 sea-based antennas
covering the entire archipelago.
As you know, it filters out
all waves and light reaching Japan
and scrambles outbound signals
to create a total barrier
to all transmissions
rendering even satellite
surveillance worthless.
Your mission is to penetrate
the electromagnetic field
then transmit a reverse beacon
to unscramble the diffusion barrier.
If successful,
this will facilitate
direct satellite surveillance.
The beacon transmission from Tokyo
must last at least 3 minutes
for the satellite to align.
One problem is your entry route.
All waters and airspace
are guarded by a warning system
on a technological par with R.A.C.E.
Not even a micro-recon craft,
much less a person,
can get through.
After you send
the beacon transmission
the infiltration team will press
further into Japan
to gain as much information
as possible about Daiwa Industries.
72 hours later you'll meet at a
predetermined extraction point.
Commander Leon Fayden
has volunteered
to lead this dangerous mission.
10 years ago
he was dispatched to Japan
leading an anti-terrorist task unit
helping Japanese security.
They suddenly shut the borders
but he was there
until forcefully repatriated.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want you to worry.
Not about volunteering...
the fact that you were in Japan.
I never had a chance to.
Is that the only reason?
Yes, it is.
Didn't want you involved...
Bring up the deck monitor!
This vessel is not damaged
or under attack.
A nearby US cargo ship
just exploded.
We are investigating the cause.
Just in case,
let's go to emergency status.
Freight inspections all complete.
Safely past border security.
We'll lose radio contact shortly.
3 minutes to analysis completion.
Receiving beacon transmission.
Please guys, just 3 minutes...
Analysis is in progress...
1 minute passed.
2 minutes, 30 seconds passed.
10 seconds to completion.
9,8,7...
What is it?
Signal's lost, sir.
- Find out why.
- Analysis not possible.
Scan again.
System alert...
Vexille, this way.
Zak!
In an entire decade,
you are our first foreign guests.
We've quite a welcome for you.
On my signal, rush for the water.
I won't go by myself.
You're the only one with a back-up
transmitter.
We'll join you later.
Leon...
Don't worry, Miss.
I'm alone. Nothing to be afraid of.
Maria changed your clothes, not me.
Maria?
Don't go outside!
Leon...
Do exactly as I say.
Maria...
Don't you dare go out again.
They're still looking for you.
Sorry, Maria. It was my fault.
I never thought SWORD would turn up.
So much food...
What about my colleagues?
- Go cool this.
- Sure.
What about Leon and the others?
What happened to Leon Fayden?
His whereabouts unknown.
We're still looking.
This is real.
It's really rare, y'know...
You slept for 2 days.
Get some food in you.
It was you who sent the messenger
to America?
One more question.
Where are we?
This used to be known as Tokyo.
Tokyo...
Captain, a second transmission.
Are you certain?
Certain, sir.
From the back-up transmitter.
It's still coming in.
We're counting on you this time...
Never used chopsticks before, Miss?
Tasty?
That's like magic.
Where did you hide it?
Saito's heading this way.
Most impressive...
On second thoughts, not.
5 guys for 1 girl?
That's kinda pathetic.
Where's the SWORD women?
Any chick would run
from a tacky tie like that.
The boss goes soft on you
but I don't have his problem.
I don't know what you're planning
but whatever you do
it's just a matter of time.
I'll see you at headquarters.
He's right.
It's just a matter of time.
Daiwa's serious about finding you.
What is it?
This place is so full of life.
I've never seen anywhere like it.
It makes me nostalgic somehow...
Bad news.
Come here...
Get in there.
Analysis completion...
Captain, 3 minutes completed.
Okay, let's run the analysis.
Run the feeds from satellites
JC17 & JD15.
Running analysis.
Analysis is in progress.
Nothing there...
No mountains...no rivers...
No human habitation...
What's going on in Tokyo?
Get it up there.
That's all that's left of Tokyo?
Daiwa Heavy Industries...
Captain,
we've got Lt. Commander Vexille
Serra's bio-signature in Tokyo.
Satellite JD14
is scanning for her now.
Any other survivors?
None confirmed.
Captain, look at this.
Put it up on screen.
The red dot is her.
She's being pursued?
JD14 is tracking her.
- Captain?
- What is it?
The bio-signature map...
it's unfiltered, sir.
Her bio-signature
is the only one down there.
How can that be?
They aren't human?
Scan the entire country!
Maria.
What's this?
Let's wait to see
if we're being followed.
They say everything
outside the city's a wasteland.
Daiwa escaped
to their island fortress.
Come here.
That's Daiwa out to sea.
It's their fault no people are left.
The Japanese race is extinct.
But you guys...
We're not human any more.
Not human...
Just fragments of humanity.
Fragments?
Fragments that will soon be gone.
You saw it, right? The final step
between man and machine.
No red blood left in our veins.