So what shall I bring
back for the mother?
What does a mother's heart yearn for?
Mother's heart? It only yearns
for her son's happiness...
no matter where he is... no matter
how he is... just happiness...
And a son's happiness is in
his mother's laughter... her smile...
something that he
isn't able to see.
I promise, mother.
The laughter will return...
that smile will return.
It's a son's promise.
And a brother's!
Your heart aches when your dear ones
go far distances, doesn't it?
And when dear ones create distances
in between, it aches even more.
Has your princess woken up?
- Oh yes... Pooja!
No one knows her by that name. Call
her what she is called by everyone...
Poo!
You have no right to
look so beautiful.
She has arrived, the cunning vixen,
to drop her daughter.
After seeing your face in the morning
how can I call it a lovely day?
Liar! Liar! Come here...
Who is it, Anjali?
- Your future daughter-in-law.
Come, let me serve you
some cornflakes.
Anjali... Anjali I need to talk to you.
- What?
This song that you sing every morning.
- So?
It feels very nice.
But the neighbours around
were complaining.
I don't sing for them do I? I sing so
that my son learns about our country.
Our Krish has learnt everything.
Say that you have!
Yes... I have learnt everything.
- He has learnt nothing...
he knows nothing about our country.
Our religion, our traditions...
our heritage... Move out of my way.
Our country has...
Oh stop it Mummy!
What country? Country!
Eh! The country best in the world
is our India... don't ever forget!
OK... I won't say anything.
He's already half an Englishman...
when he turns a full one
don't complain to me.
Yes... become just like her!
How do they say it? How do they talk?
Wouldn't it have been better
to have lived in Chandni Chowk?
Let me knot it for you, Jeej!
- Aaaah!
What happened?
- What kind of clothes have you worn?
It's become too long hasn't it?
What now?
Where's the back?
Didi, don't wait for me.
Anjali, Daijaan, come here.
How do you allow Pooja to
go out wearing such little clothes?
By the way even the two of you
are looking decent today, I think...
You had worn this even the
day before, hadn't you?
It suits you a lot!
Poo... the whole college
runs after Robbie.
He's not my type!
Who is your type?
And when will you meet him?
He might meet me anywhere... anytime.
He could be right here somewhere.
Oh God! Who is this... disturbing
Poo so early in the morning!
Who is this who hasn't turned to
give me a second look? Who is he?
Chandu's uncle fed Chandu's aunty
on a moonlit night in Chandni Chowk...
in a silver spoon,
some Chatni...
some chatni.
Do you know Rohan, Didi always says
that a married woman is the union of...
a wife and a daughter-in-law.
She is a good wife, but she hasn't
managed to be an ideal daughter-in-law
And your brother?
Not a day passes...
not a moment passes when he
doesn't remember his parents.
But he never says anything. He has
put up their photograph in the house.
But not once has he
turned towards it.
We have made a small world for
ourselves here, Rohan.
If you look from afar
it's filled with happiness...
but the closer you go,
you will find a lot of sorrow.
Why have you come, Rohan?
Why now?
I had promised bhaiyya that I will
never ask where he went or why he went
But today I have realised that
he doesn't think of us as his own.
That is a pain I can't bear...
can't bear.
I have left some broken
bonds back home, Pooja
that can only attain the status
of a family through my elder brother.
I have come to take my brother back...
take my sister-in-law back...
But I can't do this on my own.
I will need your support Pooja.
Will you support me?
No... No... never!
- He is Sonia's brother.
He's not my brother... And I didn't
even know that Sonia had a brother.
So Sonia, when was this
brother of yours born?
Brother? Who's brother?
My first brother from India
has come.
I mean first cousin.
He can't stay with me...
It's only a matter of few days.
At least meet him once.
My house isn't a charitable institution
that anyone can stay here.
Daijaan, please explain to her...
- Why are you troubling him? Why?
Oh stop it Aunty.
C'mon, In such a big house can't he...
- Can't stay.
This big house has you wearing
really small clothes... that's why.
I don't want any young man staring at
you... And I'm the boss of this house.
And I ring all the bells.
Gosh! What is it?
What is it? I was just
saving you from an evil eye!
Who's evil eye?
This whole family is mad.
All the mad people from Chandni Chowk
have moved in here.
Didi, Sonia's brother has just
arrived, he has no place to stay.
Can't we give him a
small place in this big house?
Pooja, You know Rahul, don't you?
Didi, he has come from India.
From India...
- My great India... remember?
Listen to me...
- No... no...
Just listen to me...
he has come from India.
So? Should I make him sit on my head?
Do you know the population of India?
If all of them shift here, where
will we sleep? Let me do one thing.
I'll go to Heathrow and stand there to
invite everyone arriving from India...
saying, 'Please come to my house.
My wife is mad!'
He is coming today,
he's coming now, right now!
He is waiting outside and
I'm calling him in...
Listen...
Excuse me...
"We shall never part,
through smiles nor through tears..."
"we shall never part,
through smiles nor through tears."
"How helpless are we,
what is this trial by fire..."
"we stand so close
yet we are so far"
"If you are the body,
I am the soul."
"I'm your blood..."
"we meet and yet we don't..."
"Oh what an illusion."
"It's all your blessings,
whether smiles or tears..."
"we shall never part,
through smiles or through tears."
My name is Rahul.
My name is Yash.
He will stay with us.
Take his luggage...
And this is your room!
And listen...
if you ever need anything...
want anything...
don't bother asking me for it!
Listen...
- What is it?
If you want to live in this house
you will have to follow the rules...
and regulations of the house.
No coming late and try and...
leave as soon as possible.
Dinner at 8 p.m. Or starve the night
And... stay away...
This is too much... Eh!
What are you staring at?
Say more, Please... it feels nice.
- Eh! Feels nice? Am I singing a song?
Why do you keep calling me
Eh'? I have a name...
I know, but I can't say it.
- Why can't you say it?
I said, that I can't say it. Didn't I?
- Oh!
So you don't want to take my name
as a sign of respect. That's great.
In that case I should return
the respect too.
Can I call you Bhaiyya?
- Call your father that!
Don't you drag my father into this...
actually you can... you have the right
He got scared! Poo,
I think this one's a little...
I'm mad? You wear this jacket.
Rohan, we were waiting for
your call for such a long time.
Seems like both of you
are right here with me.
Mad!
The campus is giving me
an accommodation after a week.
Right now I'm living with
an Indian family.
Why, an Indian family?
They are very nice people.
When I met them I felt like...
I have known them for years.
A laughing, happy and...
contented family,
like we are... we were...
Is he going to pay for the bill?
Go eat your food... even that's free...
There goes Madonna
early in the morning.
If you are here, who is singing
this prayer in the morning?
Goddess Saraswati herself
has incarnated in the house?
What has happened to
Saraswati here?
Look what we have done, Pooja?
We have woken them up so early.
Come on... take their blessings.
Salutations Didi... Salutations Jeejaji
- Salutations to you too... Who is this?
You are not able to recognise her
because...
You are seeing her fully clothed for
the first time. It's your sister-in-law.
You mean our Poo?
Have a laddoo!
Mother has sent them.
I thought I should
keep them as offerings.
Let me do the tika for you.
Won't you get your tika done?
Back home no one leaves
the house without a tika.
Mother says it's an auspicious
start for the day.
Mother says?
So then... do it.
Now who has done this?
- Me of course.
I enjoy puncturing tyres.
Was that a joke?
- It was... so?
No I don't want...
A guest is equal to a God. And you
can't refuse a lift offered by God.
Come on go now.
- I'll take a taxi.
Give me the money you would have
paid the cab.
That I am.
Listen... Please come back home
early in the evening.
Why?
- Just!
I have finished...
now let's leave.
By the way are you
interested in cricket?
Why?
Because there's a match.
India v/s England... at the oval.
It must be the last over.
Is it a stolen car?
- No.
Is it yours?
- Yes.
Then do what pleases you.
Don't say anything now. Anything
can happen at the last minute.
You can never bank on India.
Did you call me 'bhaiyya'?
- Why? Should I?
Why? Just drive the car carefully.
Hey! We won...
- We will win!
Like every year
Poo will decide on the boy...
who will escort her to the prom.
You will be given marks on ten.
To go to the prom with me...
you have to be brilliant in
three departments.
You are not so bad.
I wasn't talking about myself.
I was giving you points.
I will go only with
him to the prom.
Where will he go?
Just fell.
I'm leaving... I'm leaving.
Listen...
I want to say something to you.
Say it fast.
I don't have time.
Should I say it?
- Say it.
Should I?
- Please say.
You have...
- Yes?
- Say it please.
Both...
- Both of us.
- Both...
Both... Both of your
shoes are not matched.
That's the latest fashion.
I don't think you know.
Please tell Didi
not to wait for me.
Where are you?
"From the moment
I set my eyes on you..."
"I marked you to be mine"
"Don't turn your back on me,
you are mine, only mine"
"From the moment I set
my eyes on you..."
"I marked you to be mine"
"Don't turn your back on me,
you are mine, only mine"
"Please say it, you are my soniya"
"From the moment I set
my eyes on you..."
"I marked you to be mine"
"Don't turn your back on me,
you are mine, only mine"
"I accede, you are my soniya"
"I'm wounded by your love,
that's what makes me act the way I do"
"That's a nice line to fool me
But it won't work on me"
"It has taken years for us
to meet each other"
"Hope these moments last forever"
"this moment of bliss intoxicates me"
"Please say it once, you are my soniya"
"I accede, you are my soniya"
"Your presence drives me crazy,
I can't think straight"
"I place you on my eyelashes,
so you are in my dreams forever"
"I want to hold you tight"
"I am yours forever, I vow today"
"Let's both vow at this moment,
that we'll never love each other less"
"Please say it, you are my soniya"
"You, you, you are my sonia,
Hey you are, you are my soniya"
One minute, child...
one minute... What happened?
Mr. Vajpayee had called for you...
he wants you back in India.
It's his...
- What's the date today, dad?
6th September.
Pooja, Couldn't you wear
decent clothes at least today?
You came in these strange
black clothes.
Do you know everyone was
staring at us in the temple?
If everyone was staring at me instead
of God then it's not my problem.
Did you hear that, Rahul? She speaks
nonsense even on Bauji's birthday?
Today is father's birthday.
Today is bauji's birthday?
Look at her... From Poo to Parvati...
What happened to you?
Please take it...
it's the offering from the prayer
But aren't offerings on
birthday done for the...?
I know. But Bauji
was a very fun loving man...
he said even after I go
always remember me on a happy day.
That's why every year on his birthday
Pooja and I've a special prayer for him
If he had to see Pooja like this today,
he would've been unconscious.
You must feel sad that he
is no longer with you now.
Yes... we do.
It's important to have the warmth of
elders in a house...
or else a family always feels
incomplete... Isn't it?
Don't you miss him?
Don't you miss?
Don't you miss Bauji?
You guys haven't had
your breakfast... Pooja, Krishi...
Come on... Please come.
Even you are coming aren't you?
I forgot.
The one who is not here
is etched in my memory and the one...
who is right here,
I forgot about him.
What present should I give you?
Just return my Nandini back to me.
We have lost each other
in this big house.
Just get back my Nandini for me.
I want nothing else.
Nothing else.
Listen...
What's the matter?
Your affection is quite overwhelming.
Yes... That's because you are
looking extremely...
what do they call it? 'Sexy'.
Krishi will see.
By the way, that should have been
my line... Go now.
My bag and my coat.
- I'll just get it.
Listen, day after tomorrow
it's Karwa Chauth...
Wow! So what am I supposed to do?
You don't do anything. Like every year
there's party for indians
You are leaving?
What is it?
He keeps popping up everywhere.
So Karwa Chauth!
- Yes... it's day after tomorrow.
So you must have received the Sargi.
- Sargi?
Sargi... Don't you know what sargi is?
It's a ritual for karwa chauth...
it's something that every mother-in-law
sends for her daughter-in-law.
Hasn't your mother-in-law
sent it for you?
Some elder person of your family
must be sending it to you.
No...
Don't worry. This year
you will get your sargi.
My mother... she will
explain everything to you.
Greetings to you, my child!
- Greetings.
My son speaks so much about
your family that I feel almost like
I'm there with all of you.
He has become a part of
our small family.
I hope he is not
troubling you too much.
Dear child, Sargi is something that...
every mother-in-law sends
for her daughter-in-law.
Some sweets, a few almonds and...
signs of marital bliss...
and lots of love.
I'll send it to you.
I will think I have sent.
It to my daughter-in-law.
OK my child I'll hang up now!
- OK.
At times why do even strangers
seem like they are your own?
And why is it, at times...
that even our own people
become strangers?
Listen... Even I have kept
the karwa chauth fast today.
For whom?
What's going on there?
- Something that doesn't happen here.
Karwa chauth fast?
That too for me?
Why? Who am I of yours?
You don't have the guts
to tell your brother and bhabhi...
how you are related to them...
Trying to be a great tiger before me!
Let go of my hand.
Why has he held her hand?
- Let go of my hand.
I let go.
What if I tell them?
Today in the presence of everyone...
what if I tell them the truth,
what will you do?
I don't think you will be able to.
You are scared.
What if I do?
Then I will tell
everyone what's in my heart.
Really? Is that so?
- It's a bet.
Don't bet with me,
you might regret.
Maybe that's what I want.
But looking at you...
I wonder if all this is a dream.
Dream?
Yes... How can anyone
be so frightened?
Your turn.
"My trinkets tinkle...
they say I am yours"
"I can't spend a minute without you,
Oh I am yours"
"Take me away...
oh darling take me away"
"My trinkets tinkle...
they say I am yours,"
"I can't spend a minute without you,
Oh I am yours"
"Take me away,
oh darling take me away."
"Your trinkets tinkle...
they say I am yours..."
"can't spend a moment without you,
Oh I am yours"
"Take me away, oh darling,
take me away"
"I can't think of a life
without you,"
"I spend sleepless nights
counting stars in the sky,"
"my heart keeps calling out to you,
my bindiya makes a sign,"
"The shimmering bindiya,
shines like a star next to the moon,"
"My anklets call out to you,
try to make up to you as you sulk,"
"Oh my loved, my beloved.
Try and understand..."
"what I'm trying to say"
"Your trinkets tinkle,
they say I am yours"
"Can't spend a moment without you,
Oh I am yours."
"Take me away, oh darling,
take me away."
"May we be in
marital bliss forever..."
"may our soul mates be
with us forever"
"Now that you have entered my world,
never leave"
"Take my hand and ask me
to be yours forever"
"Oh darling you look so beautiful,
seems like you have been made for me"
"Your beauty shines so brightly,
that it shames the moon"
"Go away you liar, I'm not taken in"
"Don't flatter too much,
your giving yourself away"
"I wish from the bottom of my heart,
may your pair be forever"
"Oh my love, my beloved, wish
we spent our lives together forever"
"Your trinkets tinkle,
they say I am yours"
"Can't spend a moment without you,
Oh I am yours"
"Take me away, oh darling,
take me away"
You are mad!
My son has turned into
a complete Englishman.
No. Not at all.
Really, Aunty... Sometimes
I wish we were living in India.
And Krishi would sing the
same songs that I grew up singing.
But we are here and I have become
'mummy' from a mother.
Why do you think so, Anjali?
Whatever the tongue...
the culture is yours, isn't it?
Still... It's not the same, Aunty...
...Just see... Coming!
Mad!
By the way, D... j... Daijaan,
What are these children doing?
There's a function in Baba's school.
They are rehearsing for that.
All of us are going for it.
You will come with us, won't you?
I'll just be back.
What do I do with this?
What are you doing?
I'll manage myself.
Leave it Daijaan,
I'll do it myself... Daijaan...
Daijaan... DJ!
My little child! My child!
I knew it...
My heart kept telling me
that it was my Baba. Oh Allah!
How big you've grown up to be.
You hid it from your DJ too?
You didn't even tell me?
Why? My child, why?
Didn't I keep telling you, Anjali?
See, it's my little child!
It's my child.
You have come back to me.
My child!
Just coming!
Oh! Where is Didi?
Where's she gone?
Oh my God! Is this our table?
They do this all the time.
Look at this, Aunty,
They give the front seats to the
shining white army and seat us behind.
Why do they do it
always? No... Aunty,
Where is that silly principle?
She has arrived, the cunning vixen.
Is she the Queen of England that
she's got the table in the front?
Please go you silly woman...
Hope your table starts shaking...
hope your chair breaks to pieces.
Should we sit?
Already there have been a
lot of complaints.
Even last year at this function
you had created a ruckus!
Krishi is performing... Very nice...
what's the big deal?
You just shut up and stop
this Englishwoman act of yours!
Anjali, she's right!
- You keep quiet.
My son's on stage...
I will at least whistle once.
No... No...
- Just one whistle...
How sweet my son looks!
He looks just like you, sweetoo!
God, Please protect my son.
Eh! Your son is just performing...
not fighting a war on the border.
Just see!
- Just see!
My son! My son!
- Even mine.
Now sing your, 'Do Re Mi'.
Did you do this?
Now tell me something...
You must have been a little nervous?
I was a little nervous.
But someone said something to me...
and everything was alright.
What did the person say?
- Just a minute.
If you want to be someone in life...
if you want to achieve something...
If you want to win, always
listen to your hear.
And if even that doesn't
give you any answers...
close your eyes and
think of your parents.
And then you will
cross all the hurdles...
all your problems will vanish,
victory will be yours...
only yours.
Who said this? Papa?
- No. He.
Did you take care of mother?
Did you get selected
in the cricket team?
How did you manage
to lose so much weight?
Why didn't you tell me?
Come back home, Bhaiyya.
Please come back home.
Has Papa sent you?
Rohan, now this is my family.
These are my people.
This is my world!
And the home you are talking about
was never mine in the first place...
and will never be.
You go back now... just go back.
You...
I have seen you again,
that's enough for me.
Go back.
Do you know Bhaiyya,
you often said when I was a child
That mother loved you more than me.
I never liked it then.
I used to get angry.
But today, I would like to tell you,
that you were right.
Mother loves you more than me.
She loves you too much.
And she will always.
She will always
- I know.
He hasn't forgotten Dad's words.
He will never come back.
He will come Rohan.
He will definitely come back.
I know my brother-in-law well.
Just get him to meet
mother and father.
Will you be able to do that?
You know, dad...
I had a strange dream last night.
I dreamt that you and Mom had come
to London to surprise me.
Then?
- What then, dad?
The alarm went off... I mean...
why would you and Mom come to
London to surprise me?
I'll speak to you later
The work's done.
Guess where we are.
- Where, dad?
Is it ever possible that my son dreams
of something and I don't turn it true.
Tell me where you are right now,
we want to meet you just now...
You are meeting me
after such a long time.
Present? Now...
at this time... here...
You meet me at 5 p.m. At
the Blue water Shopping mall.
But tell me what
you want, my child.
You will find what
I want right there, Dad.
What's happening here?
- I'm looking for the receipts.
What receipts?
- To return the clothes.
If you have to return them, why do you
buy them in the first place?
The country best in the world
is our India... Right Mom?
Mother's stooge!
Did you tape that? That Indian serial,
Kyon Ki Saas Bhi kabhi bahu thi.
What a brilliant twist!
The son dies.
Oh God! Really? Oh No...
You have given away the suspense.
What are you doing?
- It's fine till the hugs
- but he keeps kissing me too.
- You have never kissed me so much.
Come home, darling... and see.
Lies! You lied to me.
Yes... I lied to you, Dad.
What would I have achieved even if
I had told truth.
I wouldn't be able to break
your ego.
What else is it if not ego, Dad?
That separates a mother from her child
that takes away...
a brother from his sibling... that
throws a father away from his son...?
He is not my son!
I don't believe that he is my son.
Has he fulfilled the duties
of a son? He didn't.
He did, Dad... he did.
He always fulfilled them.
He only made one mistake... Love.
If that is a crime according to
your law, so be it.
But isn't it your duty as an elder
to forgive him for his mistake?
But you came down to punishing him.
What kind of punishment is this, Dad?
What punishment is this?
Just look into my eyes and say that...
you don't feel the pain
of parting with him.
Say that you don't remember him.
Say that you don't love him.
Say it, Dad. Say it.
I don't love him.
I said it, didn't I?
God has blessed you
with everything, Dad... Everything.
I just wish he had given you a heart!
- Shut up!
You irreverent child!
You love him.
You love him a lot.
I have got my answer.
You really love him.
Let's go back, Rahul.
It's too much now...
This is not our country.
These are not our people.
We have set up a house here...
but have you ever wondered
what kind of a home is this...
that doesn't have a mother's
warmth or a father's blessings?
Let's go back, Rahul.
Mother and Father are here...
They are right here.
They are elders.
They are a little angry with us.
But we will ask for forgiveness.
Rahul... I know
they are as incomplete without us...
as we are without them.
We will ask for forgiveness, Rahul.
Let's go back.
You will never understand.
To turn a stranger into your own...
and then to turn him back
to a stranger...
you can never understand the pain.
I agree they are elders...
but even they don't have the right
to break a heart.
Even they don't have
a right to break a heart.
I think we should call him back.
Yash, It was her last wish
to have Rahul...
Just wait for a while... I
know he will definitely come.
We don't need to wait
for anyone... Rohan.
Rahul and Anjali are leaving.
They are leaving tomorrow from here.
They haven't even come home.
If you say to them...
Do you know mother always
says that...
a husband is God.
No matter what he says...
no matter what he thinks...
he is always right.
You brought Rahul home one day...
right.
We gave him lots of love... right.
He became a part of our family.
He became my life...
right... absolutely right!
Then... one day he left home
and went away.
Wrong
You let him leave... wrong
You separated a mother from
her child... wrong.
Our family shattered
to pieces... wrong.
Then how does a husband become God?
God can't do any wrong can he?
My husband is just a husband...
just a husband... Not God.
Not God.
Nandini!
I said it... Didn't I?
That's it!
Ever since the day you left,
Bhaiyya...
mother has only seen you
through His eyes.
He is the one who gave a mother...
the strength to stay away
from her son.
Please swear on Him, Bhaiyya...
that you will come home
at least once.
Just once, Bhaiyya.
Even if it is for a moment.
Even if it is for a day.
Let Bhabhi feel
at least once that
she is the daughter-in-law
of this family.
She is a part of the family.
At least let your shadow fall
on the photograph...
that has kept your memory alive in
mother's eyes for the last ten years.
Just once, Bhaiyya.
Then you can leave
No one will stop you.
On the strength of that one memory...
that one moment... Mother
can lead her entire life.
Can't you do just this
much for mother?
You took my words so much to heart
that you went away.
Didn't even look back once.
Didn't come back even once.
Didn't come back.
Where did you call
me back, Papa?
Did I have to call you back?
Am I not elder?
Do I have to call you back?
I thought you didn't love me.
I thought you didn't
think of me as your son.
How could you think that?
How could you?
I brought you into this house for
the first time with these hands.
You completed our family.
You fulfilled all our dreams.
How did you think...?
I thought you didn't love me...
didn't love me.
I love you very much,
my son... love you very much.
Just... just couldn't say it.
In these ten years I have thought
about you every moment every day.
I thought of you so much that,
I felt like embracing you and...
telling you how much I love you.
Just couldn't say it.
Elders' anger is a part of...
their love, my son.
You took it so much to heart that
you got angry and left home...?
And I didn't even call you back.
Why would you call me?
I should have come on my own.
Yes...
- I should have come on my own.
Why didn't you come?
Why didn't you?
This is your home...
You are the elder son of the family...
You are my son... my son.
And now I have grown old my son.
I have grown old.
At least forgive me now.
At least forgive me
now... At least now.
Come here, son.
Son...
At times the youngsters
in the house show the right...
path to the elders in the family.
I kept you away from your brother
for years.
Please forgive me if you can.
Forgive me... forgive me.