Ji-hae, know what this is?
An umbrella?
A very special umbrella
They're all the same
It's special because Sang-min gave it to me
He must know that I like him
Thought he wouldn't
when you stare at him everyday?
Go give this to Sang-min
No, you give it to him
I'm not going there
Why not?
Did you and Soo-gyung fight?
Remember when it suddenly rained that day?
Sang-min was drinking coffee here
He was looking out of the window
then suddenly turned to me and said
"Did you bring an umbrella?"
And then I said
"I was worried I didn't"
He placed his umbrella here
and said
"You can have it"
He said he was okay to get wet
And then he ran off in the rain
Did you bring an umbrella?
You can have it.
It's raining a lot outside
Sang-min might be getting soaked without an umbrella
This is a really special umbrella
I'll give it back to him
Did you bring an umbrella?
Of course, I did
Really?
But still, take mine
Is she crazy?
You have an umbrella
but why are you so soaked?
It's not mine
I came to return it to you
You left it at the store
I'm not the only one
who gets wet even with an umbrella, am I?
Don't go
You already know...
my feelings
Now, you know it all
Yeah
when I saw you run without an umbrella
I left my umbrella behind
Even on the day of the play
I wanted to give you a present
so I bought Soo-gyung's, too
And if fate was on my side
I thought you'd pick the gift with the card in it
I thought we'd grow distant
if I confessed my feelings
I wanted to say that I liked you,
but I couldn't
I'll come see the play
Look
I cut my wrists
I saw it all
Both of you whispering love
Do you really love her?
Is it really so?
I'm working out my feelings
My eyes were looking straight
but my heart was confused
Can I trust those words?
Can I think of it as a promise?
Yes
There's only one that I love
That one is me, right?
Yes, I love you
I swear that I love you
I love you, too
Sang-min
I love you so much
Sang-min!
What the hell are you doing?
I didn't even finish my lines
and then you call out my name?
You can't just change your lines like that
You ruined everything!
Sang-min, I wasn't acting
it was my true feelings
I love you
Love is more important than a play
After the play Sang-min and I went on a date
We decided to go to the river
where my mother's memories lay
Joo-hee?
No, I'm her daughter
My name is Ji-hae
Is that so?
I must've made a mistake
But you look so much like your mom
I delivered a lot of your mom's letters
Thank you, sir
I know well what happened to my parents afterwards
Students and citizens!
This is illegal demonstrations!
Eliminate corruption and establish a new state!
A new state!
Down with dictatorship and the military regime!
Down with the regime!
Down with dictatorship!
If you wipe on toothpaste
your eyes will hurt less
- Joo-hee?
- Tae-soo?
Put on toothpaste
It's been a long time
It has
Have you heard from Joon-ha?
Joon-ha!
Joon-ha
come back alive!
Joon-ah!
You have to come back alive!
Joon-ha!
Joon-ha
answer me!
Joon-ha!
Joon-ha...
come back alive!
Joon-ha
Joon-ha!
Joo-hee!
- Joon-ha!
- Joo-hee!
Tae-soo!
Joon-ha!
You have to come back alive!
Joon-ha
come back alive!
You have to come back alive!
Got it?
Medic! Medic!
Hold on! Hold on!
Breathe! Breathe!
Stop it!
He's dead! Retreat!
Get moving, you bastard!
Joon-ha, you bastard!
Where are you going?
Come back!
Corporal OH!
You haven't changed at all
Just like in the past
you're still pretty
I've aged a lot
- You had it hard, huh?
- Not really
How's Tae-soo doing?
I guess he's doing alright
Why didn't you get married?
Well, I did
I heard
I had so much to tell you
But now that we've met
I can't remember
It's a piano doll
We have one at my home, too
When I look at it
it reminds me of you playing the piano
It looks so much like you back then
Doesn't it?
We were so innocent back then
But the past has gone now
I think our feelings took the best of us
We cried and laughed at the smallest things
How do I look right now?
You look healthy
But I'd like to see you look happier
I'm crying right now
Can't you see my tears?
Why did you hide that you couldn't see?
It's late
Sorry, I have an appointment
I have to go
I'm sorry
It was almost perfect
I could've succeeded
I even came here last night to practice
You almost fooled me
You did a good job
I nearly believed you
Also...
I risked my life to return this necklace to you
Please don't
This necklace is yours
Afterwards, mom and dad got married
And I was born three years later
Then a few years later...
Mrs. Sung Joo-hee?
Joon-ha's last wish
was for you to spread his dust in this river
Actually
Joon-ha
got married right after you did
Poor guy had a son, too
And Joon-ha
wanted you to have this
Mommy, it's a rainbow
I still remember clearly the rainbow I saw that day
Until I finished telling this story
Open your hands