[birds chirping]
[children chattering]
(girl #1)
I'M ALWAYS INCLUDED
IN EVERYTHING.
(girl #2)
MY MOTHER SAYS
IT'S NOT HEALTHY
TO EAT SO LATE.
SO WHAT DO YOU DO?
I EAT ON THE CARD TABLE
IN MY ROOM WITH MY SISTER
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT
CHILDREN ARE SUPPOSED TO DO.
SAYS YOU.
(Nerlinger)
ALL RIGHT, YOUNG PEOPLE
I DON'T WANT TO HAVE TO
CALL YOU CHILDREN, OK?
SO LET'S START FINISHING UP.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
LET'S GATHER UP
OUR THINGS, BOYS.
OH, BILLY, WHAT A PERFECTLY
WONDERFUL PIG.
HOW DID IT GET
INTO CENTRAL PARK?
SEARCH ME.
[laughing]
LET'S PUT IT AWAY,
ALL RIGHT?
[swing creaking]
ELI, LET'S GO OVER HERE.
PETER,
LET'S PUT OUR PAPERS AWAY.
JUJU.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
AREN'T YOU DOING WELL TODAY?
[children chattering]
HOW COME?
THOSE ARE VERY STRONG COLORS.
I CAN'T DRAW ANY PEOPLE.
I BET YOU CAN.
I BET THEY'RE
JUST IN THEIR HOUSES
TILL THEY'RE READY
TO COME OUT.
HOW ABOUT IT
IF TOMORROW I HELP YOU
BRING THEM OUT?
OK.
LET'S GATHER UP OUR PAINTS.
(Nerlinger)
ALL RIGHT,
I WANT EVERYTHING PICKED UP.
LET ME SEE
WHAT YOU DID TODAY.
I MADE A PICTURE OF THE GUY
ON THE SKATEBOARD.
AND I MADE MY SKATER FALL DOWN
'CAUSE HE WAS SHOWING OFF
AND IT MADE THIS GUY MAD,
SO HE SOCKED HIM.
AND BUSTED HIS HEAD.
OH, HE DID NOT.
[swing creaking]
[creaking]
(Nerlinger)
I WANT EVERYTHING PICKED UP.
I DON'T WANT TO SEE
A PAPER TOWEL.
A GUM WRAPPER.
THERE ARE PLENTY OF
PAPER TOWELS FOR EVERYBODY
IF YOU TAKE JUST ONE.
JEANNIE GRIFFIN,
I AM TALKING TO YOU.
WILLFUL WASTE
MAKES WOEFUL WANT.
MISS PENNY!
MISS PENNY! MISS PENNY!
QUIET. QUIET EVERYONE.
HOW CAN YOU HEAR INSTRUCTIONS
IF YOU'RE MAKING
SUCH A HUBBUB?
[children chattering]
(Nerlinger)
QUIET! SILENCE!
DID YOU HEAR WHAT I SAID?
WHAT?
I SAID MAYBE WE OUGHT
TO LET 'EM BLOW OFF STEAM
BEFORE WE PUT 'EM
BACK ON THE BUS.
MAYBE A GAME
OF FOLLOW THE LEADER?
YES, FOLLOW THE LEADER.
THAT WOULD BE FINE.
MICHAEL.
ALL RIGHT,
EVERYONE PUT THEIR SUPPLIES
INTO THE BIG BOX
AND THEN LINE UP
BEHIND MISS DORSETT
FOR A GAME
OF FOLLOW THE LEADER.
(Sybil)
NO, NO. BACK THIS WAY.
[children exclaiming]
OK, EVERYBODY.
COME ON. PETER.
COME ON, GIRLS.
NOW, LET'S NOT SHOVE.
GOODNESS SAKES,
I'LL GET SQUASHED.
OK, HERE WE GO.
IS EVERYBODY READY?
LET'S GO.
[children chattering]
**[scatting]
[swing creaking]
[bell tolling]
(Nerlinger)
OH, MY GOD, SYBIL.
FOR HEAVEN SAKES,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN THE WATER?
SYBIL.
WHAT?
YOU WENT EXACTLY
THE OPPOSITE WAY
FROM FIFTH AVENUE.
THE BUS DRIVER IS VERY ANGRY.
NOW,
COME OUT OF THE WATER, SYBIL.
WE'RE GOING TO BE LATE.
ALL RIGHT. NOW, CHILDREN,
YOU FORM UP IN A LINE
RIGHT OVER HERE.
QUICKLY, PLEASE. COME ON.
(Nerlinger)
I COULDN'T FIGURE
OUT WHAT HAPPENED.
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
YOU WERE RUNNING
IN THE OPPOSITE DIRECTION.
I YELLED. I HOLLERED.
OH, SYBIL,
LOOK AT YOUR SHOES.
I--I--I DON'T FEEL VERY WELL.
I THINK I'D LIKE TO GO HOME.
MAYBE YOU OUGHT
TO SEE THE SCHOOL NURSE.
NO, I CAN COPE.
BECAUSE, SYBIL, I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN COVER FOR YOU.
I MEAN, IF WE'RE LATE
AND THE HOMEROOM TEACHER
ASKS ME.
I'M SORRY.
I-- I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW,
ALL RIGHT?
SYBIL.
ALL RIGHT, KIDS.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
[traffic rumbling]
[car honks]
HEY, YOU'RE GONNA
TURN INTO A BANANA,
YOU KEEP LIVIN' ON FRUIT.
HA, MR. DARWIN SAYS
WE'RE JUST A BUNCH
OF MONKEYS ANYWAY.
YEAH, BUT THEY EAT
LOTS OF PROTEIN, TOO, SYBIL.
THEY EAT ROOTS, NUTS, BUGS.
OH, I HAVE LOTS OF BUGS,
THANK YOU.
[chuckles]
HOW MUCH DO I OWE YOU?
THAT'S, UH, ONE NICKEL,
HALF A DIME.
I DON'T THINK SO.
OH, COME ON, WILL YOU?
IF THESE HAD
ANYMORE BRUISES ON 'EM,
I'D HAVE TO SEND 'EM
TO THE HOSPITAL.
GO AHEAD.
THANK YOU, MR. RIZO.
HAVE A GOOD DAY.
**[piano playing]
HI, MISS DORSETT.
SCHOOL LET OUT EARLY?
SO IT SEEMS.
UH, WHEN DID
THE PIANO MOVE IN?
TODAY, 2ND FLOOR, FRONT.
IT'S LOUD, ISN'T IT?
IT DON'T STOP
BY 10:00 TONIGHT,
THEY GET MY FOOT
THROUGH THE DOOR.
[baby crying]
**[piano playing]
**[piano playing loudly]
[Sybil in Hattie's voice]
HOW COULD YOU EMBARRASS ME
IN FRONT OF THEM ALL THAT WAY?
(Sybil as Peggy)
GET AWAY.
PLEASE, GET AWAY.
I WILL NOT GET AWAY.
I WILL STAND HERE
TILL YOU EXPLAIN YOURSELF.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT I DID. I DON'T--
DON'T YOU PLEAD IGNORANCE
ALOUD ON ME.
OUT, OUT, OUT.
I HAD TO GET OUT.
WHAT?
**[piano playing]
[screaming]
NO!
[sobbing]
[screaming]
(Hattie)
THAT'S NOT A CHORD.
THIS IS A CHORD.
YOU CAN'T SHARP A "G".
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
I'VE GOT MORE BRAINS
IN MY LITTLE FINGER
THAN YOU'VE GOT
IN YOUR WHOLE BODY.
[glass shattering]
[gasping]
(Hattie)
YOU DIDN'T CUT
DEEP ENOUGH, DID YOU?
NOW, WE GOTTA GET YOU
TO THE HOSPITAL.
(as Peggy)
I SEE
ONE EYE
AND--AND ANOTHER ONE
AND SOME GLASSES
AND
SOME RED KIND OF HAIR.
MMM-HMM.
NOW, TELL ME WHEN YOU SEE
MY FINGERS WIGGLE.
I SEE-- I SEE A PICTURE FRAME
AND A...
THERE'S A DOCTOR,
A LADY, IS IN IT.
OH, YEAH.
YOU SEE A CIRCLE, RIGHT?
THERE'S A CIRCLE,
AND IT'S DARK
ON THE SIDES OF IT.
I SEE A WHITE COAT.
IT'S A WHITE COAT.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
DOES MY WHITE COAT
BOTHER YOU?
I SEE SOME FINGERS WIGGLING.
YOU HAVE A RING.
A MARRIED WEDDING RING.
MMM-HMM.
YOU HAVE A LITTLE GIRL
ALL YOUR OWN?
NO.
YOU HAVE A LITTLE BOY?
MMM-MMM.
IS IT FUN TALKING
LIKE A LITTLE GIRL,
MISS DORSETT?
WHAT?
WHAT JUST HAPPENED? JETLAG?
I CUT MY WRIST.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WHY, DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
YES, OF COURSE.
I'M IN NEW YORK.
I'M IN A HOSPITAL.
MMM-HMM.
I'VE CUT MY WRIST.
AM I THROUGH? MAY I GO?
WELL, I'D LIKE TO FINISH
THE NEUROLOGICAL EXAM.
WHY IS THERE
A NEUROLOGICAL EXAM?
I'VE CUT MY WRIST.
I THINK YOU HAVE
THE CHARTS MIXED UP.
IT'S, UH...
NO, IT JUST SEEMS
THAT WHEN
THE SURGICAL RESIDENT
WAS PATCHING YOU UP
HE THOUGHT
YOU SEEMED KIND OF CONFUSED,
SO HE CALLED ME IN.
DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
AND I ASKED YOU
HOW I COULD HELP YOU,
AND YOU TOOK MY HAND.
YOU CAME RIGHT ON IN HERE.
DON'T YOU WANT TO STAY?
COME ON.
LET'S FINISH IT UP, OK?
HERE.
TELL ME WHAT YOU SMELL
IN THESE LITTLE BOTTLES.
CLOVES.
MMM-HMM.
I...
I KNOW I SHOULD
SMELL SOMETHING--
NO, YOU SHOULDN'T.
IT'S WATER.
OH! DISINFECTANT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WHAT'S THE MATTER? YOU SMELL
SOMETHING LIKE THAT BEFORE?
YES.
I'M SORRY.
YOU ASKED ME SOMETHING?
NO, YOU WERE JUST TELLING ME
ABOUT YOUR SYMPTOMS.
YOUR, UH, TUNNEL VISION
AND YOUR BUMPING INTO WALLS
AND...
YES. YES, I KNOW.
SOMETIMES,
WHEN I'M HEADING FOR THE DOOR,
BY MISTAKE, UH...
WHAT IS IT?
THIS IS YOUR OFFICE?
YES.
NO!
WITHOUT LOOKING AT YOUR WATCH,
TELL ME WHAT YOU JUST SAID.
IS IT SO IMPORTANT?
YES.
I SAID,
"IS THIS YOUR OFFICE?"
THAT WAS A HALF AN HOUR AGO.
IT'S NIGHTTIME NOW.
I DIDN'T...
I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO KNOW.
[sighing]
YES, YOU DID.
NOBODY KNOWS.
SOMEBODY KNOWS NOW.
ALL RIGHT?
DO YOU REMEMBER ANYTHING?
DO YOU REMEMBER
THE VOCABULARY TEST
OR SAYING
THE NUMBERS BACKWARDS
OR ANY OF THAT?
[sobbing]
NO, I DON'T. I DON'T.
NONE OF IT?
NO.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHETHER YOU'VE BEEN HERE
FOR AN HOUR
OR A DAY OR A WEEK, DO YOU?
I DON'T THINK
IT'S BEEN A WEEK.
HAS IT BEEN A DAY?
NO.
I--I CUT MY WRIST.
MMM-HMM.
AND I DON'T KNOW HOW.
AND THEN I WAS HERE,
TALKING TO YOU.
MMM-HMM.
HAVE I HURT SOMEBODY?
HAVE I DONE SOMETHING BAD?
NO.
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
HAVE YOU ALWAYS
LOST TIME LIKE THAT?
I'M SO AWFULLY
ASHAMED, DOCTOR.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
I'VE ALWAYS BEEN LIKE THIS.
ALWAYS.
AND I USED TO THINK
THAT EVERYBODY WAS LIKE THIS.
THAT THEY WOULD
JUST NATURALLY WAKE UP
AND BE SOMEPLACE ELSE
OR A WHOLE LOT OLDER
OR WEARING ANOTHER DRESS.
ONCE, I WOKE UP,
AND I WAS 2 YEARS OLDER.
AND...
IT WAS VERY HARD FOR ME
TO GET THROUGH COLLEGE.
I WANT VERY MUCH
TO BE A TEACHER.
I WANNA GIVE
SOMETHING TO SOMEBODY.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
SURE.
I SUBSTITUTE TEACH
BECAUSE I'M GONNA GET
MY M.A. IN ART.
IT'S IN ART.
[sobbing]
IT NEVER HAPPENED BEFORE
IN FRONT OF THE CHILDREN
BUT THINGS HAVE BEEN GETTING
A LOT WORSE LATELY.
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
I CAN'T STUDY.
AND THEN,
I WOKE UP,
AND I WAS IN THE WATER.
AND THE CHILDREN SAW ME.
SYBIL.
[gasping]
PLEASE DON'T TOUCH ME.
IT HURTS ME.
IT HURTS TO BE TOUCHED?
HERE, HAVE A CRYING TOWEL.
NO, THANK YOU.
I DON'T CRY TEARS LIKE PEOPLE.
YOU MUST HAVE
CRIED LIKE PEOPLE
ONCE UPON A TIME.
HERE. SYBIL, COME ON,
SIT DOWN.
YOU KNOW,
I THINK THE FEAR
THAT YOU'RE SUFFERING FROM
IS VERY, VERY DEEP.
AND I THINK
YOUR--YOUR SYMPTOMS,
YOUR--YOUR TUNNEL VISION
AND YOUR BLACKOUTS
ARE A RESULT OF THAT FEAR.
IT'S A KIND OF HYSTERIA.
YOU SEE?
YES.
YOU UNDERSTAND,
IF YOU ARE--ARE
TOO SCARED TO FACE SOMETHING,
THEN IT JUST MAKES
PERFECTLY GOOD SENSE
TO BLACKOUT
AND THEN YOU NEVER HAVE TO
KNOW WHAT YOU'RE SCARED OF.
NOTHING SCARES ME.
LISTEN,
WOULD YOU LIKE TO COME BACK
AND SEE ME AGAIN
ON, UM, THURSDAY?
UH, MY NAME IS DR. WILBUR
BY THE WAY.
IS IT EXPENSIVE?
NO, NOT IN THE CLINIC.
I THINK YOU CAN AFFORD IT.
I HAVE TO ASK MY FATHER.
HE'S HERE ON HIS HONEYMOON.
MY MOTHER DIED A WHILE BACK.
HE REMARRIED.
HAVE TO SHOW HIM
THE SIGHTS TOMORROW.
(Sybil)
IF YOU CAN CALL
LUNCHING AT THE MUSEUM
CAFETERIA THE SIGHTS.
WELL, I MUST SAY
THIS IS SURE
A DELIGHTFUL NOTION.
EATING BY A REAL ROMAN POOL
IN THE MIDDLE
OF NEW YORK CITY.
I BETTER NOT SAY
"ROMAN" OUT LOUD.
THE POPE MIGHT
JUMP OUT AND EAT DAD.
NOW, YOU QUIT THAT.
WELL,
WHAT'S THE NATIVE CUSTOM?
DO WE STACK OUR TRAYS
OR EAT RIGHT OFF 'EM?
WELL, I'M SETTING
MY PLACE PROPER.
WAIT, WILLARD,
TILL I SLIDE A NAPKIN
UNDER YOUR PLATE.
THERE, NOW,
ISN'T THAT MORE HOMEY?
HERE, YOU SEE
HOW SHE BABIES ME?
WELL, HE IS A BABY.
JUST A BIG, STRONG,
SWEET OLD BABY.
BUT HE'S JUST WHAT
THE DOCTOR ORDERED.
AREN'T YOU, LOVEY?
HOW DO YOU
LIKE CHICAGO, DAD?
OH, FINE.
UM, PLENTY TO DO.
OH, MY SPAGHETTI
LOOKS YUMMY.
NICE AND CRUSTY
AND TOMATOEY.
WHAT DID YOU TAKE, SYBIL?
JUST CHICKEN SALAD?
NO, IT'S TUNA.
OH.
THAT'S A PUNY KIND OF LUNCH
FOR A GROWING GIRL.
I DON'T WANT YOU
TO SKIMP ON YOUR FOOD.
WELL, I STOPPED GROWING
A LONG TIME AGO, DAD.
IT'S FINE,
A GRACIOUS SUFFICIENCY.
THANK YOU.
WE, UH, THANK THEE LORD
FOR ALL THY BOUNTIFUL
BLESSINGS. AMEN.
AMEN.
BUT, OH, THE PRICES
OF EVERYTHING HERE.
I NEARLY DIE EVERY TIME
A WAITER BRINGS THE CHECK.
(Willard)
THAT'S WHAT YOU GET
FOR LOOKING, HUH?
(Frieda)
OF COURSE, THINGS
ARE DEAR IN CHICAGO, TOO.
IT'S HARD TO MAKE ENDS MEET.
HMM.
WHEN WE LIVED
IN WILLOW CORNERS,
YOU COULD EAT
A MEAL LIKE THIS.
OH, I USED TO GET
YOUR MOTHER TO...
GOD REST HER SOUL.
TO GO DOWN TO
THE GREEN--GREEN COMET CAFE
AND ORDERED
A WHOLE COVERED DINNER
ON A SABBATH
SO SHE WOULDN'T HAVE TO COOK.
YES.
AND WHY,
WHAT WITH THE ROASTED CHICKEN
AND YELLOW GRAVY
AND THE FIXINGS
IT DIDN'T COME TO $1.50.
DAD,
I--I HAVE AN ILLNESS.
IT'S WHAT YOU AND MOTHER
CALLED MY MOODINESS.
AND IT'S GETTING
WORSE AND WORSE.
IT WILL BE
THE END OF EVERYTHING
UNLESS I CAN DO
SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
I'M SORRY TO BRING YOU
IN ON THIS, FRIEDA,
BUT YOU'RE NOT BLOOD FAMILY
AND I DON'T SEEM
TO BE ABLE TO GET DAD ALONE.
WELL, UH, I FEEL LIKE FAMILY.
GOODNESS.
DAD, THERE'S A LADY,
A DOCTOR,
AND I-- I'VE TALKED TO HER.
SHE CAN HELP ME
IN THE PURSUIT OF ME
AND SHE THINKS THAT
THAT'S A USEFUL PURSUIT.
WILLARD, YOU SAID YOURSELF
WE HAVE A PERFECTLY
GOOD SPARE ROOM
AND ALL HER THINGS WOULD FIT
IN THERE JUST PERFECT.
NOTHING WILL FIT PERFECT
ANYWHERE UNTIL I FIT PERFECT.
I'M SORRY.
I'M GOING TO THE RESTROOM.
I DON'T WANT IT SAID
THAT I INFLUENCED ANYTHING.
BETWEEN A ROCK
AND A HARD PLACE, SYBIL.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW
HOW THE CHURCH VIEWS
THE PRACTITIONERS
OF THE MIND.
I'M VERY FRUGAL.
IF I GIVE UP
MY LUXURIES, TELEVISION,
AND I DON'T READ AFTER SUNSET
AND I-- AND I USE
THE STOVE ONLY OCCASIONALLY
TO COOK 3 DAYS AT A TIME,
I COULD-- I COULD GET BY
ON WHAT YOU SEND ME.
THE DEVIL HATH POWER
TO ASSUME A PLEASING SHAPE.
SHE'S NOT THE DEVIL, DAD.
NOW, I--I KNOW THAT.
I DON'T KNOW THAT ABOUT ANYONE
EXCEPT THE PEOPLE
IN OUR OWN CONGREGATION.
SHE'S A REPUTABLE DOCTOR.
FIRST THING
YOU KNOW IT'S DRUGS,
THEN A HOSPITAL
FULL OF LOST SOULS.
THAT'S THE WAY
THEY BEGIN IT, SYBIL.
OH, LORD,
I THINK I'M TRAPPED.
THE FINAL PREPARATION
FOR THE HOLOCAUST.
IT'S ARMAGEDDON, SYBIL.
[groaning]
"AND IT SHALL RISE UP
IN THE EAST
AND THE RIVERS
SHALL FLOW AS BLOOD."
[grunting]
SYBIL!
I'M SORRY. OH, DAD,
I'M--I'M SORRY.
I CAN PAY FOR IT. IT--IT--IT
SURELY IS--IS ABOUT $2.
WHAT IS THE MATTER WITH YOU?
[groaning]
[Sybil groaning]
(Willard)
SYBIL. SYBIL.
SYBIL! SYBIL!
SYBIL!
[voices chattering]
[clock ticking]
[voices continue chattering]
[voices chattering]
[sobbing]
[children shouting]
NOW, TELL ME WHEN YOU SEE
MY FINGERS WIGGLE.
THE DEVIL HATH POWER
TO ASSUME A PLEASING SHAPE.
[children shouting]
I'VE CUT MY WRIST.
YOU KNOW HOW OUR CHURCH FEELS
ABOUT THE PRACTITIONERS
OF THE MIND.
[children shouting]
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
MY WHITE COAT BOTHER YOU?
[sobbing]
ALWAYS. ALWAYS.
I WAS ALWAYS LIKE THIS.
FIRST THING
YOU KNOW IT'S DRUGS,
THEN A HOSPITAL
FULL OF LOST SOULS.
[children shouting]
[groaning]
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S JUST DISINFECTANT.
THE FINAL PREPARATION
FOR THE HOLOCAUST,
THE ARMAGEDDON, SYBIL.
[sobbing]
I ALWAYS THOUGHT
THAT PEOPLE WOULD JUST
NATURALLY BE SOMEPLACE ELSE
OR WEARING ANOTHER DRESS
OR BE A WHOLE LOT OLDER,
LIKE WHEN I WAS
IN THE 3RD GRADE
AND MY GRANDMOTHER DIED
AND--AND I WASN'T ANYPLACE
FOR 2 YEARS.
I JUST WASN'T ANYPLACE,
NOT ANYPLACE AT ALL.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO COME BACK
AND SEE ME ON THURSDAY?
WHAT IS THE MATTER WITH--
[telephone ringing]
IT'S ALL RIGHT. I'VE GOT IT.
YEAH.
WHO?
VICKY WHO?
IT BETTER BE AN EMERGENCY
FOR "JUST VICKY"
AT 3:00 IN THE MORNING.
OK, PUT HER ON.
(Sybil as Vicky)
DR. WILBUR?
YEAH.
THAT WINDOW IS BEGINNING
TO LOOK AWFULLY GOOD TO SYBIL.
WHAT WINDOW? WHO ARE YOU?
I'M SYBIL'S FRIEND.
IT'S VERY HIGH, DR. WILBUR.
IT'S UP 4 FLOORS.
YOU'D BETTER COME QUICK
TO THE STATON HOTEL--
HOLD ON A SECOND.
HOLD ON, OK?
STATON HOTEL--
HOLD ON. WAIT A MINUTE.
WAIT A MINUTE. HOLD ON. YEAH.
ALL RIGHT,
IT'S THE STATON HOTEL,
136 WEST 125TH STREET.
OPPOSITE THE ROSLYN.
OK.
WHAT IS SHE DOING IN HARLEM?
[cars honking]
[door rattling]
(Dr. Wilbur)
VICKY?
(as Marcia)
LEAVE ME ALONE.
VICKY, LET ME IN.
IT'S DR. WILBUR.
THANK YOU.
SYBIL?
[gasping]
(Sybil)
OH, NO.
I DIDN'T WANT TO DO THIS
IN FRONT OF YOU AGAIN.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
LISTEN, WOULD YOU
JUST WAIT DOWNSTAIRS, OK?
[window closing]
WHERE IS THIS?
HAVE I MISSED THURSDAY?
DID I MISS THURSDAY?
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
WHERE'S YOUR FRIEND VICKY?
I DON'T HAVE A FRIEND VICKY.
SHE HAS A FRIEND SYBIL.
WHAT KICKED IT OFF THIS TIME?
I LOST MY JOB.
AND I--I TRIED TO ASK...
MY... MY...
YEAH? YOU ASKED YOUR FATHER
ABOUT SEEING ME.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT DID HE SAY?
SYBIL?
[sobbing]
(as Peggy)
THE PEOPLE. THE PEOPLE.
THE PEOPLE.
THE PEOPLE,
THEY'RE EVERYWHERE.
THERE, THERE, THERE.
NO, YOU KEEP THEM
AWAY FROM ME.
I WILL, I WILL,
I WILL DO IT. I WILL DO IT.
[sobbing]
HE DOESN'T CARE.
SYBIL.
I HATE SYBIL. I HATE HER.
WHO ARE YOU?
I CAN DO ANYTHING.
I CAN DO ANYTHING I WANT TO.
I CAN WALK ON THE FURNITURE
IF I TAKE MY SHOES OFF
LIKE THAT AND LIKE THAT
AND LIKE THAT.
AND I CAN WALK ON THE CHAIR
LIKE THAT AND LIKE THAT
AND LIKE THAT.
AND YOU CAN'T STOP ME.
I PROMISE YOU, SYBIL,
I WOULDN'T STOP YOU.
YOU CAN'T STOP ME.
I WON'T STOP YOU.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
[sobbing]
IT HURTS ME!
WHAT HURTS? WHAT HURTS YOU?
WHERE DOES IT HURT?
I HAVE TO GET OUT.
NO, WAIT!
I HAVE TO BREAK THE GLASS.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
NO, WE DON'T--DON'T
BREAK GLASS.
YOU WON'T LET ME OUT,
AND YOU WON'T LET ME
HAVE ANY PEACE
AND YOU LEAVE ME ALONE
AND IT HURTS,
AND YOU DON'T
LEAVE ME ALONE, IT HURTS.
WHO ARE YOU TALKING TO?
WHO AM I?
WHO HURT YOU?
OH, PLEASE, I HAVE TO GET OUT.
GET OUT.
I HAVE TO GET OUT.
WE'LL JUST GO DOWNSTAIRS,
WE'LL GET IN THE TAXI
AND THEN YOU'LL BE OUT,
ALL RIGHT?
NO, NO, NO, SHE'S THERE.
WHEN SHE'S THERE,
THE PEOPLE ARE THERE.
WHO'S THERE? WHO IS THERE?
THE PEOPLE.
I DON'T WANNA SEE THEM.
I DON'T WANNA FEEL THEM.
WHERE IS SYBIL?
I DON'T WANNA KNOW.
WHERE IS SYBIL? TELL ME.
I HAVE TO GET OUT.
I HAVE TO FEEL THE GLASS.
NO, NO. NO,
[sobbing]
NO. NO, NO.
I HAVE TO FEEL THE--
DON'T BREAK IT.
I SEE THE KNOB.
I SEE THE KNOB
ON THE WHITE HOUSE.
ON THE WHITE HOUSE,
I SEE THE KNOB.
AND THE SHADES
ARE PULLED DOWN.
I LIVE RIGHT THERE.
RIGHT THERE.
201 WEST 4TH STREET.
WILLOW CORNERS, WISCONSIN.
I LIVE RIGHT THERE.
RIGHT THERE. RIGHT THERE.
(Dr. Wilbur)
THAT'S HARLEM.
(Sybil as Peggy)
I DON'T KNOW
WHERE THE OTHER GLASS IS.
[sobbing]
IT'S IN DR. QUINONESS'
INSTRUMENT CASE,
AND IT'S ALL WHITE
AND SHINY KNIVES.
AND MY MOMMA SAYS,
"I WILL TAKE YOU
"TO PLAY WITH MONICA
AND CHERYL
"BECAUSE YOU LIKE MONICA
AND CHERYL."
AND MY GRANDMA SAYS...
MY GRANDMA SAYS...
MY GRANDMA SAYS,
"YOU--YOU GO
LIKE MOMMA SAYS."
MY GRANDMA'S GOOD.
SHE'S GOOD.
SHE LOVES ME.
I'M AFRAID! I'M AFRAID!
[gasping]
(Dr. Wilbur)
THERE'S NOTHING
TO BE AFRAID OF HERE.
(Sybil as Peggy)
THEY NEVER FORGET ANYTHING,
AND THEY LISTEN
TO EVERY SOUND.
AND THEY'RE EVERYWHERE,
AND THEY'RE EVERYWHERE.
THEY'RE IN THIS ROOM
AND THAT ROOM
AND EVERYWHERE YOU LOOK,
WHO?
AND EVERYWHERE--
THE PEOPLE.
THE PEOPLE. NO! NO!
NO, DON'T MAKE ME GO THERE.
[shushing]
I DON'T WANNA GO
UP THERE, PLEASE.
PLEASE DON'T MAKE ME
GO UP THERE.
[sobbing]
I WON'T GO UP THERE. PLEASE.
PLEASE DON'T MAKE ME
GO UP THERE.
GO WHERE? GO WHERE?
PLEASE.
IT'S NOT HAPPENING NOW.
PLEASE DON'T DO THIS.
(Hattie)
WELL, HERE WE ARE.
OH, LOOK, WHO ELSE GOT HERE.
DADDY'LL TAKE YOU UPSTAIRS,
WON'T YOU, DADDY?
WHERE'S CHERYL AND MONICA?
THEY'LL BE HERE LATER, SYBIL.
YOUR MOMMY'LL BRING YOU
SOME ICE CREAM,
WON'T YOU, MOMMY?
(Dr. Quinoness)
YOU'RE JUST GOING UPSTAIRS
FOR A LITTLE NAP.
WHAT KIND DO YOU LIKE?
YOU CAN HAVE
ANY KIND YOU LIKE.
NOW, HUSH NOW.
DOUBLE, DOUBLE.
EASY DOES IT. DOUBLE DIP.
THAT'S IT. THAT'S IT.
COME ALONG.
(Sybil)
NO!
NO! NO!
NOW, NOW, BIG BREATH,
BIG DEEP BREATH.
NO!
NOW, I CAN'T DO ANYTHING
IF YOU'RE GONNA TO FIGHT ME.
NO!
[gasping]
(Dr. Wilbur)
ALL RIGHT,
THERE'S PLENTY OF AIR.
NOW, THERE JUST SEEMED
TO BE NO AIR
BECAUSE YOU WERE BREATHING
AIR MIXED WITH ETHER.
(as Peggy)
THEY HAVE TO USE 2 CANS OF
ETHER TO TAKE HER TONSILS OUT
BECAUSE SHE'S A REAL
STRONG LITTLE GIRL.
RIGHT, RIGHT,
AND A MAD LITTLE GIRL, TOO.
THEY LIED TO YOU,
DIDN'T THEY?
YEAH, THEY GOT YOU THERE
UNDER FALSE PRETENSES.
[sobbing]
THEY'RE GONNA KILL HER.
THAT'S WHAT THEY'RE GONNA DO.
NO, THEY'RE NOT
GOING TO KILL YOU.
AND WHY DO YOU KEEP
REFERRING TO YOURSELF
IN THE THIRD PERSON, HMM?
BECAUSE SHE'S SYBIL.
[sobbing]
BUT MY THROAT HURTS, TOO.
AND WHO ARE YOU, SWEETIE?
WILL YOU TELL
DR. WILBUR NOW?
DR. WILBUR'S TOO FAR AWAY.
NO, NO.
DR. WILBUR'S RIGHT HERE.
DR. WILBUR JUST SEEMED
VERY FAR AWAY
BECAUSE ALL GOOD
AND SAFE THINGS
MUST HAVE SEEMED
VERY, VERY FAR AWAY.
DR. WILBUR, A WHITE COAT?
THAT'S RIGHT,
BUT I'M NOT WEARING IT NOW.
[sobbing]
HI. EVERYTHING'S OK NOW.
YOU JUST TRY
AND GET SOME SLEEP, OK?
I WANNA BE YOUR LITTLE GIRL.
PLEASE, TAKE ME TO YOUR HOUSE.
OH, HONEY,
YOUR MOMMY AND DADDY
LOVE YOU VERY MUCH.
THEY'D MISS YOU.
JUST TRY
AND GET SOME SLEEP, OK?
YOU TAKE ME, PLEASE.
HONEY. HONEY, PLEASE,
JUST--JUST TRY TO SLEEP, OK?
HELLO.
HERE'S YOUR MOMMY, SYBIL.
EVERYTHING'S ALL RIGHT NOW.
HELLO.
HOW'S MY LITTLE GIRL?
LOOK WHAT I BROUGHT YOU,
SYBIL.
SYBIL?
(Hattie)
DON'T YOU TURN
YOUR BACK ON ME.
I'M TALKING TO YOU.
SYBIL. SYBIL.
[groaning]
YOU'RE...
NO CUTS. NO BRUISES.
I BUSTED IT ALL TO PIECES.
YOU'RE ALL IN ONE PIECE.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S ALL RIGHT. IT'S EASIER
TO FIX WINDOWS
THAN LITTLE GIRLS.
(as Peggy)
LITTLE GIRLS ARE MORE
IMPORTANT THAN WINDOWS?
THIS LITTLE GIRL
CERTAINLY IS. SURE.
I GOT SOMETHING TO TELL YOU.
IT'S ABOUT SYBIL.
SHE PUTS GUCK
ALL OVER HER HAIR
'CAUSE SHE HAS GRAY HAIR.
[laughing]
I DON'T. I'M NATURAL.
YOU LIKE THE WAY I LOOK?
I HAVE A REAL PRETTY FACE.
SEE ME IN THE MIRROR?
AND A LITTLE NOSE
AND ALL MY FRECKLES
AND MY BANGS.
I'M ONLY 9.
DO YOU BELIEVE ME?
YES, I BELIEVE YOU.
MY NAME'S PEGGY,
AND YOU'RE MY DR. WILBUR.
(Dr. Lazarus)
TELL ME ABOUT YOUR PATIENT.
YOU THINK SHE'S REALLY
A MULTIPLE PERSONALITY?
ERNA, I KNOW SHE IS.
I'VE--I'VE MET
ONE ALTERNATE, I KNOW.
AND I'VE TALKED TO
ANOTHER ONE ON THE TELEPHONE.
SUCH A COMPLIMENT
THAT THEY SHOULD REVEAL
THEMSELVES SO QUICKLY.
ERNA, THE--THE WAKING SELF,
THE SYBIL PART,
IS VERY REPRESSED
AND--AND--AND VERY TROUBLED.
A GRIM--GRIM PERSON,
BUT THE--THE OTHER ONE,
THE--THE LITTLE PEGGY,
IS JUST ENCHANTING.
SHE'S--SHE'S, UH,
SHE'S JUST ADRIFT IN TIME.
SHE DOESN'T KNOW
THAT SHE'S IN NEW YORK
AND SHE'S--SHE'S ABSOLUTELY
FULL OF MISCONCEPTIONS
ABOUT EVERYTHING.
HOW ARE YOU
GOING TO TREAT HER?
PSYCHOANALYSIS.
WHICH ONE?
ALL 3.
THAT'S UNPRECEDENTED.
WHY ARE YOU
THE BIG PIONEER?
WELL, WHY DID YOU
TEACH ME TO BE?
[both laughing]
BE CAREFUL.
CONNIE, BE CAREFUL.
DON'T FALL IN LOVE
WITH HER ILLNESS.
OR SHE COULD BE OBLIGATED
TO SEEM JUST MORE COMPLEX
THAN SHE IS
JUST TO KEEP YOUR APPROVAL.
YOU KNOW,
THEY ARE NOT LITTLE GIRLS.
THEY'RE DEFENSES
THAT BELONG TO SOMEBODY ELSE,
PIECES, FRAGMENTS,
ONLY ILLUSIONS.
AND THEY ARE ACTING OUT
A DRAMA
THAT HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOU.
WELL, I KNOW THAT.
SO YOU MUSTN'T ACT OUT ONE
THAT HAS NOTHING TO DO
WITH THEM.
OH, FOR INSTANCE?
FOR INSTANCE,
YOU ARE NOT THEIR MOTHER.
(Dr. Wilbur)
IT WASN'T EASY TO HEED
MY FRIEND'S WARNING.
EVERY TIME PEGGY
LEAVES MY OFFICE
TO DISAPPEAR INTO THE CITY,
I HAVE THE MOST AWFUL URGE
TO CALL HER BACK
BECAUSE I KNOW THAT NEW YORK
DOESN'T EXIST FOR HER.
SHE LIVES
IN THE SMALL MIDWESTERN TOWN
OF HER MEMORY 20 YEARS AGO
WHERE THERE WEREN'T
ANY TAXIS OR BUSES
OR STRANGERS TO HARM HER.
AND WHENEVER
THE CITY SWALLOWS HER UP,
I WONDER IF I'LL EVER
SEE HER AGAIN
UNTIL, BY SOME MIRACLE,
SHE OR SYBIL
APPEAR ON MY DOORSTEP.
I WONDER WHAT SHE DOES
AND HOW SHE LIVES
OR WHO SHE SEES.
(Richard)
* HUSH-A-BYE *
* DON'T YOU CRY *
* GO TO SLEEP-Y *
* LITTLE BABY *
* WHEN YOU WAKE *
* YOU WILL HAVE *
* ALL THE PRETTY
LITTLE PONIES *
* BLACKS AND BAYS *
* DAPPLES AND GRAYS *
* COACH *
* AND 6 A-LITTLE HORSES *
* HUSH-A-BYE *
* DON'T YOU CRY *
* GO TO SLEEP-Y *
* LITTLE BABY **
**[Richard humming]
[snorting]
HEY, SYBIL DORSETT!
WANNA PET MY HORSE?
COME ON, MA'AM.
NOW, HAVE NO FEAR
OR TREPIDATION.
WE'VE FALLEN ON HARD TIMES,
HIM AND ME,
SINCE WE WERE
THE FINEST ROPING TEAM
IN ALL THE WEST
AND IT KIND OF
LOOKS LIKE IT'S GONNA BE
THE DOG-FOOD FACTORY
UNLESS SOME KIND SOUL
BELIEVES IN US ENOUGH
TO TAKE A RIDE.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
WOULD YOU TAKE
YOUR HAT OFF FOR A SECOND?
THINK YOU'VE SEEN ME
IN THE PICTURES?
OH.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU DID THIS.
I KNEW YOU DID THAT.
WHAT?
PAINT. THAT'S AN ART BOOK,
ISN'T IT?
"TURNER." YEAH, I KNEW
YOU WERE AN ARTIST.
I'VE SEEN YOU PAINTING
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
I DON'T DO THAT.
I HAVEN'T PAINTED
IN A LONG TIME.
YEAH, YOU DO. I WATCH YOU.
FROM WINDOW TO WINDOW,
RIGHT ACROSS OUR BACKYARDS.
EACH WINDOW A STAGE
IN THIS THEATER OF THE ABSURD
WHICH WE CALL LIFE.
YOU NEVER HAVE COMPANY.
YOU EAT BY YOURSELF.
YOU STILL PLAY WITH DOLLS.
AND YOU WATCH ME, TOO.
I'VE SEEN YOU OVER THERE
WITH THE LIGHTS OUT
SEETHING WITH PASSION
ON THOSE HOT SUMMER NIGHTS.
I DON'T HAPPEN
TO BE SEETHING WITH ANYTHING.
I'M JUST TRYING TO KEEP
MY ELECTRICAL BILL DOWN.
I HAVE TO GO.
WELL, WAIT.
WHY?
SAY, "W-A-T-E-R,"
AND I'LL TELL YOU
WHERE YOU COME FROM.
DO I HAVE TO?
YOU WANT YOUR BOOK BACK?
[sighing]
WATER.
ILLINOIS. IOWA.
IT'S WISCONSIN.
I--I REALLY HAVE TO GO.
OH, COME ON, SYBIL.
GET IN, I'LL GIVE YOU
A FREE RIDE.
OH, EXCUSE ME. I'M SORRY.
WELL.
WELL, THAT'S THE 2ND TIME
YOU'VE SAID IT,
SO I GUESS
YOU WANT ME TO ASK.
HOW DO YOU KNOW MY NAME?
MY LITTLE BOY MATTHEW
IS IN LOVE WITH YOU,
AND HE WANTED
TO WRITE YOU A LETTER.
SO I WALKED AROUND THE CORNER,
LOOKED AT ALL THE NAMES
ON THE BELLS
AND YOU'RE
THE ONLY SINGLE ON 5.
I NEVER GOT A LETTER.
NO, WE NEVER SENT IT.
WE BOTH FORGOT
HE HASN'T LEARNED TO WRITE.
[chuckling]
LOOK, I GOT
AN ITALIAN SAUSAGE SANDWICH.
IT'S REALLY TOO BIG FOR ME,
AND HE WON'T EVEN TOUCH IT.
WHO ARE YOU?
I HAVEN'T GOT A CLUE
BUT IT'S CALLED
RICHARD J. LOOMIS.
AND JUST LIKE MY HORSE HERE,
I CANNOT INFLICT HARM.
OH.
[speaking in French]
HEY, YOU'RE A LINGUIST.
I ONLY KNOW PIG LATIN.
[sighing]
YES, I WAS BILINGUAL
AS A CHILD. FRENCH.
THAT'S ALL I REMEMBER,
AND I'M SORRY TO SAY
IT'S ALL WRONG.
RAISED IN PARIS.
COME ON, PONY.
PARIS? OOH-LA-LA!
YES.
C'EST BIEN.
WE PLAYED HOPSCOTCH
IN THE  BOIS.
WE HAD CAFE AU LAIT
FOR BREAKFAST
AND PORRIDGE,
IF YOU CAN BELIEVE IT.
OF COURSE, WE HAD
AN ENGLISH NANNY.
YEAH?
YES.
DID SHE SAY,  "BOIS," TOO?
YOU GOT ME THERE.
HELLO...
[speaking in French]
OH, OH, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
OH, I'M SORRY.
YOU DON'T RECOGNIZE MY VOICE.
I'M VICKY.
VICTORIA, SYBIL'S FRIEND.
VICTORIA ANTOINETTE SCHARLEAU.
ALLO. ALLO.
HELLO.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
ALLO A VOUS, TOO.
WELL.
WELL, COME.
COME, RIGHT IN.
MERCI. MERCI.
OH!
QUEL JOLI BUREAU!
OH, THANK YOU.
UM...
ASSEYEZ-VOUS.
OU? SUR THIS COUCH
OU SUR THAT COUCH?
COMME VOUS VOULEZ.
JE CHOOSE THIS COUCH.
I DON'T BLAME YOU
FOR NOT REMEMBERING.
IT WAS MONTHS AND MONTHS AGO
SINCE I CALLED YOU
FROM THAT DREARY
LITTLE HARLEM HOTEL.
MMM-HMM.
WELL, TELL ME, UM,
WHERE'S SYBIL?
SYBIL IS A BIT EMBARRASSED
ABOUT THE FINANCIAL
ARRANGEMENTS.
SINCE YOU'VE BEEN SEEING HER
IN YOUR PRACTICE  PRIVEE,
SHE DOESN'T KNOW
HOW SHE WILL EVER REPAY YOU.
SHE'LL REPAY ME
WHEN SHE GETS
HERSELF TOGETHER
[laughs]
IF YOU'LL EXCUSE THE PUN.
[both chuckling]
YES?
DR. WILBUR,
MMM-HMM.
PEGGY IS VERY WORRIED.
SHE THINKS THAT PERHAPS
YOU THINK
SHE WANTS TO HURT YOU
BECAUSE SHE BREAKS
THE WINDOWS.
(Dr. Wilbur)
WELL, I DON'T.
NO, SHE WOULDN'T HURT ANYONE.
SHE'D BEEN SO HURT HERSELF.
I WOULDN'T HURT ANYONE EITHER,
NOT BY WORD NOR DEED.
I DON'T EVEN LIKE TO HURT
SOMEONE'S FEELINGS.
DO YOU KNOW?
IF SOMEONE CALLS ME SYBIL
BY MISTAKE,
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I DO?
I LOOK IN THEIR FACE
AND I SAY, "YES. YES."
OR,  "OUI. OUI.
YOU'RE SPEAKING TO ME?"
BECAUSE IT HURTS
TO BE EMBARRASSED,
DO YOU KNOW?
MMM-HMM.
[sighing]
SYBIL IS SUCH
A LAMENTABLE CREATURE.
(Dr. Wilbur)
WHY DO YOU SAY THAT?
SHE CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
SHE STARTS TO PAINT,
SHE CAN'T PAINT.
SHE WANTS TO PLAY THE PIANO,
SHE CAN'T PLAY THE PIANO.
SHE WON'T HAVE FUN.
THE WOMAN REFUSES TO HAVE FUN.
SHE'S AFRAID OF PEOPLE,
YOU KNOW.
I'M NOT. NO.
I SIMPLY ADORE PEOPLE.
DO YOU KNOW,
THE OTHER DAY,
SHE WANTED TO TAKE A RIDE
IN THE PARK
WITH THAT ATTRACTIVE
YOUNG MAN, UH, RICHARD LOOMIS
WHO LIVES ACROSS THE YARD?
SHE WAS AFRAID
TO TAKE HIS HAND.
SHE'S AFRAID OF HANDS.
SO IS PEGGY.
I HAD TO GO.
I'M NOT AFRAID OF HANDS.
I'M NOT AFRAID OF ANYTHING.
NO, SIR.
WHOSE HANDS ARE SYBIL
AND PEGGY AFRAID OF?
[in Hattie's voice]
DON'T YOU DARE TELL.
NEXT WORSE THING
TO BEING A FIBBER
IS BEING A TALEBEARER.
YOU TELL, AND I'LL FIX IT
SO YOU AIN'T GOT
NOTHING TO TELL WITH.
VICKY,
DID YOUR MOTHER EVER HIT YOU?
OH.
MINE? NO.
MY MOTHER
IS AN ABSOLUTE ANGEL.
SHE LIVES IN PARIS,
YOU KNOW.
SHE'LL BE COMING FOR ME SOON.
WE'LL BE TOGETHER,
ALL MY BROTHERS AND--
IS SYBIL'S MOTHER
NOT AN ANGEL?
DO YOU LIKE MY HAIR?
IT'S CALLED A FRENCH TWIST.
I DO IT MYSELF.
I LOOK A GREAT DEAL
OLDER THAN 13, DON'T I?
THAT'S BECAUSE
EUROPEAN CHILDREN
MATURE SO MUCH SOONER.
BUT I'M SO THIN.
THIS SUIT JUST HANGS ON ME.
MAYBE SYBIL
ISN'T FEEDING YOU ENOUGH.
I NEVER COMPLAIN EXACTLY.
BUT ALL SHE EATS
IS ROTTEN FRUIT.
THAT'S ALL SHE'S EATEN
ALL MONTH LONG.
HER DADDY FORGETS
TO SEND HER THE CHECK.
LOTS OF TIMES, HER DADDY
FORGETS TO SEND A CHECK
AND THAT MAKES PEGGY
VERY, VERY MAD,
AND SHE BARGES INTO THE STORES
AND SMASHES ALL THE CRYSTAL,
AND SYBIL HAS TO PAY FOR IT.
BUT I DON'T CARE.
(Dr. Wilbur)
DID YOU HAVE BREAKFAST
THIS MORNING, HMM?
SWEETIE, ARE YOU HUNGRY?
IF I STAND VERY, VERY ERECT
WITH A CERTAIN AIR OF DIGNITY
YOU CAN'T TELL
HOW THIN I AM, CAN YOU?
COME ON. I'M GONNA
MAKE YOU A SANDWICH.
I SEE THE WHEELS
GOING ROUND AND ROUND.
WHY DO THEY DO THAT?
WHY DO THEY GO
ROUND AND ROUND
AGAINST ME?
THEY'RE NOT GOING AROUND
AGAINST YOU.
THEY'RE JUST
MAKING A RECORDING.
REMEMBER PEGGY SAID
I COULD WHEN SHE WAS HERE?
YES, I KNOW,
TO HELP SYBIL.
MMM-HMM.
BECAUSE SHE SEEMS TO HAVE
SO MUCH MORE INFORMATION
THAN SYBIL DOES.
OH, I HAVE MORE.
I HAVE MORE THAN PEGGY.
I HAVE MORE THAN ANYBODY.
I KNOW EVERYTHING.
EVERY THOUGHT SHE THINKS,
EVERYTHING SHE DOES,
I REMEMBER.
SHE CAN'T REMEMBER.
SHE MUSTN'T REMEMBER.
THAT'S WHY IT'S VERY,
VERY IMPORTANT
THAT YOU DON'T TELL HER
ABOUT US.
IT WOULD BE TOO BIG
A SHOCK FOR HER.
SHE'S NOT READY TO TAKE IT.
HERE.
I HAVE A PEANUT BUTTER
AND JELLY SANDWICH FOR YOU
AND SOME BANANA BREAD
AND A BIG GLASS OF MILK.
NOW, I WANT TO SEE YOU
JUST EAT AND EAT AND EAT,
ALL RIGHT?
THANK YOU.
MMM-HMM.
MILK IS GOOD
FOR GROWING GIRLS.
THAT'S RIGHT.
LOTS OF MUMMIES
AREN'T LIKE YOU.
ARE REAL TRICKY.
VICKY,
DO YOU REMEMBER
SYBIL'S TONSILLECTOMY, HMM?
I SAW. I WAS THERE.
IT MADE, UH, SYBIL'S
THROAT HURT, DIDN'T IT?
YES, VERY MUCH.
MMM, HURT SO BAD
SHE HAD TO WHISPER
AND SHE COULDN'T TALK.
TALKED LIKE THIS
ALL THE TIME.
FUNNY THING IS,
IT MADE PEGGY'S THROAT
HURT, TOO.
NOW HOW COME
BOTH THEIR THROATS HURT
IF, IF ALL OF YOU ARE
DIFFERENT PEOPLE?
VICKY?
I KNOW. I'M THINKING.
DON'T I HAVE
LOVELY TABLE MANNERS?
NOTICE HOW DELICATE
MY HANDS ARE.
THE PINKIES,
IT'S CALLED CONTINENTAL.
HMM, YES, IT'S LOVELY.
TELL ME,
ARE YOU RELATED IN SOME WAY,
ALL OF YOU?
I KNOW WHERE I AM.
I'M IN NEW YORK.
LOTS TO DO IN NEW YORK.
MUSEUMS TO GO TO,
CONCERTS--
DO YOU THINK THAT
SYBIL AND PEGGY
SHARE THE SAME MOTHER
AND FATHER?
NOW HOW ARE THEY RELATED?
HMM?
ARE THEY SISTERS?
OR ARE YOU ALL PARTS
OF THE SAME PERSON?
DON'T BE SILLY.
IT CAN'T BE THAT.
NO, IT CAN BE THAT.
YOU CAN ALL BE ASPECTS
OF THE SAME PERSON.
ALL PIECES OF SYBIL.
NO, NO.
WE'RE ALL PEOPLE.
YOU CAN SEE US.
LOOK AROUND.
THERE'S NOBODY ELSE HERE,
JUST YOU AND ME
AND THE SINK
AND THE DISHES AND THE DOOR.
NOBODY ELSE HERE.
DO YOU BELIEVE ME?
SWEETIE,
I BELIEVE THAT YOU BELIEVE.
COME ON,
YOU HAVE YOUR SANDWICH.
QUESTIONS,
QUESTIONS, QUESTIONS.
MY GOODNESS, SO MANY.
LOOK, YOU EVEN HAVE
QUESTIONS IN YOUR EYES
RIGHT THIS MINUTE.
I'D LIKE TO ASK YOU
A QUESTION.
ASK ME.
WHAT'S LOVE?
SWEETIE, DON'T YOU KNOW?
NO, I DON'T.
PLEASE TELL.
WE ALL WANT TO KNOW,
ALL OF US.
WHO'S ALL OF US?
EVERYBODY
THAT LIVES WITH SYBIL.
(Dr. Wilbur)
WHO ARE THE OTHERS, VICKY?
ARE THERE MORE BESIDES YOU
AND--AND--AND SYBIL AND PEGGY?
VICKY?
(Sybil as Vicky)
I HEAR YOU.
ARE YOU SEEING THEM NOW?
YES.
I DON'T WANT TO,
BUT I CAN.
[creaking]
IT WAS SO NICE A MOMENT AGO
WHEN THEY WEREN'T HERE.
I NEED TO KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE SEEING,
SWEETIE.
IF I DON'T KNOW
WHO YOU ALL ARE
AND WHAT YOU WANT,
I CAN'T HELP YOU
AS EASILY AS I'D LIKE.
VICKY?
HELP, HELP, HELP, HELP.
WE ALL KEEP HOPING
THINGS WILL GET BETTER
BUT I, I DON'T THINK
SYBIL'S GOING TO LIVE
THAT LONG.
WHY, SWEETIE?
WHY DO YOU HAVE
THIS AWFUL FEELING OF DOOM?
BECAUSE OF MARCIA.
MARCIA'S GOING TO
KILL SYBIL SOMEDAY.
LET IT COME. LET IT COME.
WE'RE WALKING CORPSES.
WE START DYING
THE MOMENT WE'RE BORN.
(Dr. Wilbur)
WHO'S MARCIA?
WHY DOES SYBIL NEED MARCIA?
VICKY?
ONE OF THEM
PLAYS THE PIANO.
SHE'S THE PRETTIEST.
SHE'S THE ONLY ONE
WITH ANY JOIE DE VIVRE.
WHAT'S HER NAME?
NO.
MUSTN'T TELL YOU.
MUSTN'T TELL ANY MORE.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE EVEN
TOLD YOU ABOUT MARCIA.
WHY NOT?
WHY ARE YOU SO AFRAID
TO TELL ABOUT THE OTHERS,
VICKY?
WHO TOLD YOU IT WAS WRONG
TO TELL PEOPLE THINGS?
WHO SAID IT WAS DANGEROUS
TO TELL?
VICKY?
MUSTN'T TELL.
CAN'T TELL.
THERE ARE GUARDS
AROUND THE PALACE.
SWEETIE, EVEN THE GUARDS
AROUND THE PALACE
WILL TELL
IF THE QUEEN'S IN DANGER.
(Dr. Wilbur)
MARCIA APPEARED
FOR THE FIRST TIME
AT THE SESSION
THE FOLLOWING THURSDAY.
SHE ADMITTED
TRYING TO KILL SYBIL
IN THE HARLEM HOTEL
AND WAS SORRY
THAT VICKY STOPPED HER.
SHE ALLOWED ME
TO PHOTOGRAPH HER,
AS THE OTHER'S HAVE
SAYING THAT SHE WANTED
THIS PICTURE
PUBLISHED WITH HER OBITUARY.
WHEN I ASKED HER
WHY SHE THOUGHT ABOUT SUICIDE
SO OBSESSIVELY
SHE PRETENDED
TO LOCK HER LIPS
AND THROW THE KEY AWAY,
THEN PROCEEDED TO DRAW SCENES
FROM A RECURRENT NIGHTMARE,
AS THOUGH
THIS WERE A SECRET WAY
OF REVEALING INFORMATION
SHE COULDN'T GIVE ME OPENLY.
BY DRAWING
HER DREAMS IN SILENCE,
NOBODY COULD EAVESDROPS
ON HER,
AND THAT SEEMED TO BE
A CONSTANT DREAD
THAT SOMEONE WOULD FIND OUT
THAT SHE'D CONFIDED IN ME.
IN THE DREAM,
A CHILD COMES UPON,
UH, A LOST KITTEN
IN THE TUNNEL OF A GREAT PARK
AND THEN SHE DISCOVERS, UH,
A BOX WHERE OTHER KITTENS
HAVE BEEN ABANDONED.
THE CHILD IS--IS OVERWHELMED
WITH--WITH LOVE AND PITY
AND--AND RUNS OFF WITH THE BOX
IN ORDER TO SAVE THE KITTENS.
SUDDENLY,
SHE SEES A DEAD CAT,
WHICH HORRIFIES HER
BECAUSE IT'S BEEN BEHEADED.
BOTH THE HEAD AND BODY
COME TO LIFE AND PURSUE HER.
MARCIA SAID THEY ALL SHARED
THE SAME NIGHTMARES
BUT THAT SYBIL
DOESN'T REMEMBER ANY OF THEM.
THE DREAMS
ARE ALL OF ENTRAPMENT
AND RELENTLESS PURSUIT.
LARGE FAMILIES OF CHILDREN
AWAITING SOME
TERRIBLE RETALIATION.
LONELINESS,
THE HOPELESSNESS OF RESCUE.
PARALYZING FEAR
PERVADE EVERYTHING.
WHEN I SUGGESTED
THAT THE KITTENS
MIGHT BE
THE VARIOUS ASPECTS OF SYBIL,
THAT SHE'S TRYING TO
BRING ME FOR PROTECTION
AND THAT THE CAT
MIGHT BE HER DESIRE
TO DESTROY AGAIN AND AGAIN
SOME UNSPEAKABLE TORMENTOR
WHO WON'T STAY DEAD,
MARCIA BECAME SO FEARFUL,
SHE DISSOCIATED INTO PEGGY,
WHO WANTED TO ESCAPE WITH ME
TO AMSTERDAM TO GET AWAY
FROM WHAT SHE CALLS
"THE PEOPLE."
I LOOK AT ALL THE FACES,
FURIOUS, TERRIFIED PEGGY,
SEPULCHRAL LITTLE MARCIA,
VICKY WITH HER SOCIAL EASE
AND UNINTERRUPTED MEMORY,
AND SYBIL,
AND I WONDER,
WHAT THERE WAS BACK THERE
THAT COULD'VE CAUSED
SUCH A SHATTERING.
WHAT COULD'VE FORCED HER
TO THRUST ONTO CREATURES
SHE DOESN'T EVEN KNOW EXIST
ALL THOSE CAPACITIES
IN HERSELF SHE MUST DENY?
AND WHY IS IT SO VITAL
THAT SHE DENY THEM?
WHAT WAS THE TORMENT?
WHO WAS THE TORMENTOR?
(Richard)
HEY, SYBIL.
I KNOW YOU'RE THERE.
WHY DON'T YOU COME OVER?
WE CAN GO DOWNTOWN.
YOU CAN, UH,
SEE ME IN ACTION, OK?
I'LL BUY YOU A HOTDOG,
SAUERKRAUT, PICKLES.
YOU LIKE PICKLES?
I DON'T GO OUT AT NIGHT,
BUT THANK YOU ANYWAY.
OH, COME ON. LOOK, UH,
IT'S JUST FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
I ONLY GOTTA GO DOWN
AND PLAY THE INTERMISSION
AND IF IT DOESN'T RAIN,
UH, YOU KNOW,
I'LL CATCH THEM GOING OUT.
CATCH THEM FOR WHAT?
BY DAY,
I'M A CENTRAL PARK COWBOY
BUT BY NIGHT, A TONE-DEAF
WANDERING MINSTREL.
STREET MUSICIAN.
SAY YES.
(as Vicky)
SYBIL CAN'T SAY YES.
VANESSA, YOU GO.
YOU LIKE MUSIC.
YOU MAY GO, VANESSA.
RICHARD?
RICHARD.
RICHARD!
HEY.
OK, BUT LOOK,
I'M NOT ANY GOOD
AT JUMPING OVER FENCES,
SO WHERE DO YOU LIVE?
UH, THE GRAY HOUSE,
APARTMENT 5C.
OK.
HI.
GUESS WHAT I AM.
UH, A KUMQUAT.
NO.
A DONUT WITH EARS.
UM...
A SMILE THAT WENT
LOOKING FOR A BOY,
AND FOUND ONE.
NO.
I'M A CLOWN.
A CLOWN.
SYBIL, THIS IS MATTHEW.
MATTHEW, SAY HELLO TO SYBIL.
I KNOW SYBIL.
I WATCH HER
THROUGH THE WINDOW.
HE'S A LITTLE WOUND UP
AT THE IDEA OF COMPANY.
I REALLY LOVE YOUR APARTMENT.
IT'S, IT'S ALL LIT UP.
SYBIL BIBBLE DRIBBLE.
MATTHEW, SIMMER DOWN.
SIT!
MATTHEW.
NOW, DON'T LET APPEARANCES
DECEIVE YOU.
I AM REALLY NOT COMPANY.
YOU KNOW WHAT I AM?
I'M A PRINCESS
WHO'S BEEN ASLEEP
FOR 1,000 YEARS
IN A FOREST
CALLED SIMMER DOWN.
AND YOU KNOW WHY?
THAT'S BECAUSE A WICKED WITCH
PUT AN EVIL SPELL
ON MY ICE-CREAM CONE
THE VERY DAY I WAS BORN,
AND IF A PRINCE
DOESN'T COME ALONG SOON
AND BREAK
THE SPELL WITH A KISS,
I GUESS I HAVE TO
GO ON FOREVER
LOOKING LIKE SYBIL BIBBLE,
AND I WOULDN'T WISH THAT
ON A DRAGON, WOULD YOU?
[yawning]
OH, I'M GETTING SO SLEEPY.
[snoring]
[laughs]
SEE YOU BLINKING.
THAT'S BECAUSE
PRINCESSES ALWAYS BLINK
IN THEIR SLEEP.
THEY HAVE TO STAY ALERT
FOR THE PALACE REVOLUTION
WHICH IS LIABLE
TO TAKE PLACE ANY MOMENT.
[snoring]
(Matthew)
IF YOU WAKE UP,
I'LL SHOW YOU MY TOYS.
THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY.
[snoring]
[kisses]
OK. ENCHANTMENT'S BROKEN.
[Richard sighing]
(Richard)
SAY GOODNIGHT TO SYBIL.
THAT'S NOT SYBIL.
SYBIL STAYED HOME.
OK, BUT WE STILL
GOTTA GET YOU NEXT DOOR.
SO HERE'S BEAR-BEAR.
AND HOW ABOUT NIGHT-NIGHT.
AND DOODY.
CAN'T FORGET DOODY, OK?
(Richard)
AND WASH YOU FACE,
OR THERE'LL BE SMILES
ALL OVER YOUR PILLOW.
THAT WOULDN'T BE
SUCH A BAD THING
TO WAKE UP TO SOMETIMES,
WOULD IT?
WHAT?
SMILES.
ALL OVER YOUR PILLOW.
[trumpet blowing]
(as Vanessa)
I'VE BEEN WONDERING
WHY YOU WEAR
THAT OUTRAGEOUS SMILE
ALL THE TIME.
PEOPLE THINK YOU'RE SMILING,
THEY SMILE BACK
AND THAT MAKES THEM
FEEL GOOD.
SO THEY PUT
MORE MONEY IN THE KITTY.
SEE HOW CRASS.
CLEVER, CLEVER MAN.
OF COURSE,
MY FACE DOESN'T GET TIRED
SO I CAN KEEP
GRINNING AWAY ALL NIGHT
AND NEVER HAVE TO SMILE
AT ALL.
DO YOU MAKE
FABULOUS AMOUNTS OF MONEY?
I MEAN,
JUST TONS AND TONS OF MONEY?
WELL, OVER $5,000
LAST YEAR, TAX FREE.
AND THAT WAS JUST
ON THE SIDEWALK
IN FRONT OF CARNEGIE HALL.
THAT'S FABULOUS.
PLUS I GET COMPLIMENTS,
YOU KNOW,
FROM THE GREAT
AND NEAR GREAT.
I HAVE AN AUTOGRAPHED PICTURE
FROM LAWRENCE WELK THAT SAYS
"GOOD LUCK AND SUCCESS,
ALWAYS."
NOW, THAT REALLY
MAKES ME FEEL NEAT,
YOU KNOW?
LIKE ALL MY YEARS AT JULLIARD
WERE REALLY WORTHWHILE.
ONCE, I YEARNED TO BE
A CONCERT PIANIST.
WHAT STOPPED YOU?
I COULDN'T FIND
THE RIGHT PIANO.
I MEAN,
SHOULD IT BE A STEINWAY
OR A BECHSTEIN GRAND?
I DIDN'T KNOW.
YOU ARE 12 YEARS OLD
AT THE MOST,
AND I GOTTA KISS YOU.
2 GENTLEMEN IN ONE NIGHT.
FANCY THAT.
I GOT BLUE PAINT
ALL OVER YOUR LIP.
OH.
GOT IT. GOT IT.
OK.
(Sybil as Vanessa)
MY MOTHER WANTED TO BE
A CONCERT PIANIST, TOO.
YEAH?
YEAH.
THE BIGGEST
DISAPPOINTMENT IN HER LIFE
WAS WHEN HER SISTER FAYE
GOT MARRIED FIRST
AND LEFT HER BEHIND
TO DEMONSTRATE PIANOS
IN THE FAMILY MUSIC STORE
INSTEAD OF BEING
ALLOWED TO PURSUE
HER DREAMS
LIKE SHE'D BEEN PROMISED.
THAT WAS IN WILLOW CORNERS,
WISCONSIN.
THAT'S MY NATURAL HABITAT,
BELIEVE IT OR NOT.
WILLOW CORNERS, WISCONSIN.
YEAH.
MY GOODNESS.
AFTER THAT, MOTHER WOULD JUST
PUNISH THE MUSIC, YOU KNOW.
SHE'D JUST SIT THERE
AND BANG ON THAT PIANO
AND CALL OUT
THE TIME OUT LOUD
AND CALL OUT THOSE NOTES
LIKE SHE HATED THEM.
YOU KNOW,
JUST BANG ON THE PIANO.
YEAH, LOVE AND HATE.
PEANUT BUTTER AND JELLY.
I USED TO HATE
MY LATE WIFE
WHO I SPEAK OF
WITH A CERTAIN IRONY
SO AS TO KEEP A TOTAL
COLLAPSE AT A DISTANCE.
I WISH
YOU WOULDN'T MOCK YOURSELF.
YOU WANNA HEAR ABOUT IT?
'CAUSE I'D LIKE TO TELL YOU.
YOU WOULD?
I'D LIKE TO HEAR.
I JUST DIDN'T THINK
I SHOULD ASK.
BEEP-BEEP WITH THE HORN.
CHOO-CHOO WITH THE TRAIN.
CRASH-CRASH WITH THE CAR.
ALL BROKEN.
AS MATTHEW SAYS
WHEN I DROP A DISH.
ANYWAY, UH,
HER NAME
WAS JANIE.
AND SHE WAS 19.
AND, UH, I NEVER THOUGHT
I WAS GONNA BE ABLE
TO COPE WITH ANYTHING
AFTER SHE GOT KILLED.
AND I HATED HER
FOR FINKING OUT.
BUT ONE THING IT TAUGHT ME.
YOU'RE NEVER READY
FOR WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO.
YOU JUST DO IT.
THAT MAKES YOU READY.
[sighing]
IT'S NEW YORK. NOBODY CARES.
THIS IS US.
IT IS?
YEAH.
OH.
* HEY RIG-A-JIG
KISS A LITTLE PIG *
* FOLLOW THE BAND *
* HEY RIG-A-JIG
KISS A LITTLE PIG *
* FOLLOW THE BAND *
* JOIN IN
AND FOLLOW THE BAND *
* MY HUSBAND IS A CABBIE *
* IS A CABBIE, IS A CABBIE *
* MY HUSBAND IS A CABBIE,
IS HE *
* ALL DAY HE STRIPS GEARS *
* STRIPS GEARS, STRIPS GEARS *
* AND AT NIGHT HE COMES HOME *
* AND DRINKS TEA **
[all laughing]
* HEY RIG-A-JIG
KISS A LITTLE PIG *
* FOLLOW THE BAND *
* HEY RIG-A-JIG
KISS A LITTLE PIG *
* FOLLOW THE BAND *
* JOIN IN
AND FOLLOW THE BAND *
**[scatting]
(Richard)
GIVE ME A BITE.
**[scatting]
* HEY RIG-A-JIG
KISS A LITTLE PIG *
* FOLLOW THE BAND *
* HEY RIG-A-JIG
KISS A LITTLE PIG *
* FOLLOW THE BAND *
* JOIN IN
AND FOLLOW THE BAND **
[cars honking]
**[both playing guitar]
**[both continue
playing guitar]
[Sybil screaming]
(Hattie)
YOU STOP THAT NOW.
THERE'S NOT
A THING IN THE WORLD
THE MATTER WITH THOSE SHOES.
(Willard)
WHAT-- ARE THEY SO SMALL,
DAUGHTER?
MAYBE THEY PINCH.
(Hattie)
NO, I GREASED THEM MYSELF.
THERE'S PLENTY OF ROOM
TO GROW IN.
FEEL THE TOE.
THEN WHY IS SHE SCREAMING SO,
I WANT TO KNOW.
I CAN'T TELL YOU.
I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO TELL YOU.
[cars honking]
I CAN'T TELL YOU.
[in Hattie's voice]
NOW YOU JUST COLLECT YOURSELF,
YOUNG LADY,
OR WE'LL BE LATE FOR CHURCH.
WE'LL BE LATE FOR CHURCH.
BEG YOUR PARDON?
YOU JUST COLLECT YOURSELF,
YOUNG LADY.
(as Peggy)
I WON'T GO!
I CAN'T TELL YOU! I WON'T GO!
HEY, MAN, HOLD MY GUITAR.
TAKE CARE OF IT.
PEOPLE, WHY DO THEY DO IT?
WHY DO THEY DO IT?
[muttering]
NO MOSS GROWING ON THAT GIRL.
THERE'S NO MOSS
GROWING ON THAT GIRL.
I DON'T WANNA GO.
I WANNA GET OUT.
[Sybil moaning]
[tires screeching]
[cars honking]
DON'T TOUCH ME.
I'M GOING TO GO
RUN AWAY DOWN.
DON'T TOUCH ME.
SYBIL!
GET OUT.
[mumbling]
GOTTA BREAK THE GLASS.
I MUST BREAK THE GLASS.
[muttering]
GOTTA BREAK THE GLASS.
THE PEOPLE JUST GOTTA GET OUT.
GET OUT!
NO, NO, DON'T TOUCH ME.
I KNOW. I KNOW. I KNOW.
WRITE, THEN YOU CAN SEE.
I KNOW. I KNOW. HOLD ON.
I HAVE TO DO IT.
[in Hattie's voice]
I HAVE TO DO IT, YOUNG LADY.
YOU JUST LAY STILL.
JUST LAY STILL.
(Sybil as Peggy)
IF I LAY STILL, IT HURTS ME.
OH, IT HURTS ME.
[Sybil sobbing]
[in Hattie's voice]
I DID IT. I DID IT.
SYBIL.
WHAT?
[Sybil exclaiming]
[knocking on door]
(Richard)
YOU OK IN THERE?
SYBIL.
WHO'S THAT?
WHO THAT WHO SAY, "WHO THAT"?
(Sybil)
WHO THAT WHO SAY,
"WHO THAT WHO SAY,
WHO THAT'?"
RICHARD LOOMIS, HELLO.
HELLO.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
DO YOU NEED TO?
WELL, I'D LIKE TO
BUT I DON'T HAVE TO.
HAVE I MENTIONED DANNY?
NO.
WHO'S HE?
WE WERE CHILDREN TOGETHER.
HE WAS
AN OUTCAST LIKE ME, ONLY,
IN HIS CASE,
IT WAS BECAUSE HE DANCED.
I USED TO BE SORT
OF AN OUTCAST, TOO,
BECAUSE I COULDN'T
PRONOUNCE MY S's.
WHENEVER I FEEL ESPECIALLY
WARM TOWARD SOMEBODY,
ESPECIALLY GRATEFUL,
I THINK OF DANNY.
HE HAD KIND OF
A HOLY FORBEARANCE.
EVEN AT THE AGE OF 9 OR 10,
HOW HE GOT IT
IN THAT BENIGHTED TOWN,
I'LL NEVER KNOW.
(Sybil)
HE NEVER ASKED
FOR EXPLANATIONS.
NEVER. HE JUST ACCEPTED.
DANCE WITH ME.
I'D GET IN AWFUL TROUBLE.
I HAVE TO STAND UP IN CHURCH
AND TELL IT OUT LOUD
IN FRONT OF EVERYBODY.
* I WANT MY ARMS ABOUT YOU *
* THE CHARMS ABOUT YOU *
* WILL CARRY ME THROUGH *
* TO HEAVEN *
* IM IN HEAVEN *
* AND THE TEARS
THAT CROWD AROUND ME *
* THROUGH THE WEEK *
* SEEMS TO VANISH *
* LIKE A GAMBLER'S
LUCKY STREAK *
* WHEN WE'RE OUT TOGETHER *
[tapping]
(Danny)
* OUT TOGETHER *
* OUT TOGETHER
DANCING TO THE BEAT **
[siren wailing]
THANK YOU.
AM I GONNA SEE YOU AGAIN?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE POLITE.
I NEVER AM.
HEY.
UM, KISS A CLOWN,
GET A SMILE ON YOUR PILLOW.
I DON'T SLEEP WITH A PILLOW.
IT'S BAD FOR YOUR SPINE.
YOUR HAND AT LEAST?
[gasping]
BURNING KISSES. BURNING.
WHAT DID I DO?
(as Vanessa)
ISN'T THAT NICE?
MMM-HMM.
SOMETIMES, HE, HE PLAYS SONGS
THAT ARE LIKE HAPPY AND GAY.
ONE TIME HE PLAYED, UM,
WITH A SONG IN MY HEART.
YOU KNOW THAT ONE?
UH, IT GOES...
YOU KNOW. YEAH, RIGHT.
* I ALWAYS KNEW *
* I'D LIVE LIFE THROUGH
WITH A SONG IN MY HEART **
I CAN SEE YOU HAVE
A LOVELY VOICE.
ONE TIME, WE WENT TO THE PARK,
YOU KNOW,
'CAUSE WE WERE
GONNA PLAY CATCH
AND THEN ONE OF THE BOYS
CAME OUT
BECAUSE HE WANTED
TO PLAY CATCH.
AND RICHARD
THOUGHT IT WAS ME,
SO HE WENT OVER TO MIKE
AND HE KISSED HIM RIGHT
SMACK DAB ON THE LIPS.
HE WENT... AND MIKE WENT...
WHAT IS A BOY--
WAIT A MINUTE.
DO YOU MEAN
SOME OF THE OTHERS ARE BOYS?
I WASN'T SUPPOSED
TO TELL YOU THAT.
NOW VICKY'S
GONNA BE MAD AT ME.
**[playing piano]
VANESSA, I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IT HURTS.
WHEN RICHARD
KISSES SYBIL, IT HURTS.
WHY IS THAT?
WHY DOES LOVE HURT?
LOVE DOESN'T HURT, SWEETIE.
LOVE HEALS.
IT SMELLED
LIKE DISINFECTANT.
WHAT SMELLS
LIKE DISINFECTANT?
THE HANDS
IN THE GREEN KITCHEN.
LIKE THAT STUFF
YOU MADE SYBIL SMELL
THAT TIME, REMEMBER?
MMM-HMM.
[in Hattie's voice]
I JUST LOVE YOU TO DEATH.
BUSHEL AND A PECK,
A HUG AROUND THE NECK.
NOW, YOU JUST
COME ON OVER HERE.
LET ME GIVE YOU A HUG,
HONEY.
THAT'S A GIRL.
DON'T HANG BACK LIKE THAT.
NO. ISN'T THAT FUN?
JUST TICKLE, TICKLE,
TICKLE, TICKLE, TICKLE.
AND TICKLE, TICKLE,
[piano bangs]
(as Vanessa)
THEN THERE'D BE A BIG PINCH.
BUT I WASN'T HURT BY LOVE
BECAUSE I CAME LATER.
BESIDES THAT, I WAS QUICK
AS GREASE LIGHTENING
AND I COULD ALWAYS GET AWAY.
SYBIL HAD A DREAM
SHE COULD PLAY,
BUT I CAN REALLY PLAY.
**[Sybil humming]
**[playing piano]
* DREAMER **
YOU HAVE  EASTER...
YOU HAVE  EASTER BONNET.
I LOVE  EASTER BONNET.
PLAY IT FOR ME, WILL YOU?
OH.
YOU COULD DO IT.
**[humming]
OK.
I'M READY.
OK. OK, WAIT, WAIT.
OK. START AGAIN.
* IN YOUR EASTER BONNET *
* WITH ALL THE FRILLS
UPON IT *
* I'LL BE
THE GRANDEST FELLOW *
* IN THE EASTER PARADE *
**[scatting]
* I'LL BE ALL IN CLOVER *
* AND WHEN THEY LOOK ME OVER *
* I'LL BE
THE PROUDEST FELLOW *
* IN THE EASTER PARADE *
* ON THE AVENUE *
**[yodels]
* FIFTH AVENUE **
**[piano playing]
[crying]
VANESSA,
WHAT'S THE MATTER, SWEETIE?
(as Peggy)
I'M NOT VANESSA.
I'M SORRY, PEGGY,
BUT YOU POPPED OUT SO FAST.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, SWEETIE?
IT WAS MY IDEA
AND SHE STOLE IT.
I WANTED TO SING
EASTER BONNET
REALLY, REALLY BAD.
WELL,
YOU CAN SING  EASTER BONNET.
I DON'T WANT TO.
I WANNA DANCE.
WELL, FINE.
AND I WANT YOU TO WATCH ME.
ALL RIGHT. ALL RIGHT.
I'M ALL EYES, ALL RIGHT?
OK.
ALL RIGHT.
VANESSA WILL BE MY STAGE MAN,
AND YOU'RE GONNA WATCH ME.
OK. OK.
* HEAVEN, I'M IN HEAVEN *
* AND MY HEART BEATS *
* SO THAT I CAN HARDLY SPEAK *
* AND I SEEM TO FIND
THE HAPPINESS **
I DON'T, I DON'T FIND
HAPPINESS ANYWHERE.
WE'LL FIND IT, PEGGY.
IT JUST GOT LOST SOMEPLACE.
I--I WANT TO SIT
IN THE BIG CHAIR WITH YOU.
WELL, YOU CAN COME SIT
IN THE BIG CHAIR WITH ME.
OK.
DR. WILBUR, WOULD YOU HELP ME?
I--I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING.
WHY CAN'T YOU SEE ANYTHING,
HONEY?
THERE'S DISH TOWELS
AROUND MY EYES,
AND THEY'RE AROUND
MY WRISTS, TOO.
DISH TOWELS?
YES.
HERE, COME ON.
HERE. THERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHTY?
YEAH.
HERE. IS THAT BETTER?
THERE. OK.
WELL, NOW, HOW DID
THE DISH TOWELS GET THERE?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M SCARED OF DISH TOWELS.
WELL, DISH TOWELS ARE JUST
INANIMATE OBJECTS, PEGGY.
WILL YOU CALL ME "SWEETIE"?
I'M SORRY, SWEETIE, BUT, NOW,
DISH TOWELS DON'T JUST
JUMP UP AND
TIE THEMSELVES AROUND
LITTLE GIRLS' FACES
AND AROUND THEIR WRISTS.
THEY HAVE TO BE PUT THERE
BY SOMEBODY.
JUST HANDS, NOT SOMEBODY.
WELL, HONEY, THE HANDS
HAVE TO BELONG TO SOMEONE.
NOW WHO--WHO DID
THE HANDS BELONG TO?
JUST HANDS.
WELL, YOU WANT TO TAKE OFF
THE DISH TOWELS
AND LOOK AT THE HANDS?
WHY DON'T WE DO THAT?
WILL YOU DO THAT?
WILL YOU HELP ME?
SURE.
OK. NOW ZIP AND ZIP.
NOW,
THE DISH TOWELS ARE OFF.
NOW, WILL YOU LOOK AT
THE HANDS?
NO. I DON'T WANT TO.
I DON'T WANT TO.
WELL, TRY. TRY.
JUST TRY LOOKING
AT THE HANDS, OK?
CAN YOU SEE THE HANDS?
HMM?
NOW CAN YOU SEE THE ARMS?
UP TO THE ELBOWS?
AND UP TO THE SHOULDERS?
CAN YOU SEE THE NECK?
NOW CAN YOU LOOK AT THE FACE?
NO. THERE ISN'T ANY FACE.
[shushing]
THERE ISN'T ANY FACE.
THE HANDS DID IT OR
THE TOWELS JUST DID IT
ALL BY THEMSELVES.
I'M SCARED. I'M SCARED.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
I KNOW, BUT IF WE LOOK
AT THE SCARY STUFF,
IT'LL GO AWAY.
OH, IT HURTS ME.
IT HURTS ME.
I KNOW,
BUT WE HAVE TO FIND OUT
WHAT DID THE HANDS DO
TO MAKE THAT HURT.
[groaning]
OH, COME ON, PEGGY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
OH, MY GOD.
KEEP AWAY FROM THE WINDOW.
REMEMBER, YOU PROMISED
YOU WOULDN'T BREAK GLASS
IN MY OFFICE.
HANDS AND THE PEOPLE
AND YOU COULD SEE THEM
AND THEY WALK AND THEY TALK
AND YOU CAN HEAR THEM
AND, AND "A" SHARP AND "C".
OH, OH, IT HURTS ME.
WHO ARE THE PEOPLE, SWEETIE?
WHAT HURTS? WHAT HURTS?
I WILL. I GOTTA GET OUT.
I GOTTA GET OUT.
PEGGY!
I WILL. I WILL. GLASS BREAK.
WHERE ARE YOU?
WHERE ARE YOU, PEGGY?
TELL ME.
THE KITCHEN,
THE KITCHEN, THE KITCHEN.
IT'S ALL GREEN.
AND THE SINK AND THE TABLE
AND THE LIGHT,
YOU CAN SEE IT.
AND THE SHADE, AND THE SHADE,
AND THE PIANO
IN THE LIVING ROOM,
IN THE LIVING ROOM.
AND THE PEOPLE,
AND YOU CAN'T GET AWAY
FROM THE MUSIC,
AND IT DOESN'T
MAKE ANY DIFFERENCE.
OH, DON'T HOOK ME.
DON'T HOOK ME.
HOOK YOU WITH WHAT?
DON'T HOOK ME. DON'T HOOK ME.
I KNOW. YOU GOT A BIG HOOK.
YOU GOT A BUTTON HOOK.
YOU'RE GONNA HOOK ME.
NO. NO. NO.
PEGGY,
WHO ARE YOU TALKING TO?
NO, YOU WON'T LET ME OUT.
YOU WON'T LET ME BREAK GLASS.
YOU WON'T LET ME DRAW.
AND YOU WON'T LET ME DRAW.
YES, I'LL LET YOU DRAW.
YOU WON'T LET ME DRAW.
I'LL LET YOU DRAW.
YOU WON'T LET ME DRAW
BECAUSE I'LL DRAW MY WAY OUT.
I'LL DRAW MY WAY OUT.
AND ALL THE PEOPLE
AND THE COLORS.
AND THE PEOPLE
YOU WON'T BE MAD.
NO, NO. DRAW.
I'LL DRAW MY WAY OUT.
YOU WATCH. YOU COULD WATCH.
VICKY WOULD SAY "MAY,"
BUT I CAN SAY "CAN"
IF I WANT TO.
I CAN SAY "CAN" IF I WANT TO.
THE PEOPLE, THE PEOPLE,
THE PEOPLE.
IT'S ALL PURPLE. AND IT MOVES
AND YOU WATCH THEM
AND YOU SEE THEIR FEET.
AND YOU HAVE TO GET AWAY.
AND THERE'S ANOTHER
AND ANOTHER AND ANOTHER.
AND THE MUSIC,
IT GOES AROUND AND AROUND
AND AROUND AND AROUND
AND OVER AND DOWN LIKE THAT,
AND THEN LIKE THAT.
AND YOU COULD SEE,
YOU COULD SEE,
AND THE PEOPLE HAVE HANDS.
PEGGY, WHO ARE THE PEOPLE?
I DON'T KNOW. I DON'T KNOW.
THEY'RE JUST PEOPLE.
AND IT'S LIKE THAT
AND LIKE THAT AND OVER
AND AROUND AND LIKE THAT
AND LIKE THAT.
AND YOU CAN HEAR IT,
AND YOU CAN HEAR.
AND IT GOES SHARP, SHARP.
IT GOES SHARP. "A" SHARP.
"A" SHARP AND "F" AND "F"
AND--AND--AND "B" AND "D"
AND--AND--AND--AND--AND
BRAHMS AND BEETHOVEN.
AND--AND--AND--AND--AND--AND
BRAHMS AND--AND--AND
THE  NEW WORLD SYMPHONY
AND DVORAK.
AND DVORAK, YOU CAN HEAR IT.
YOU CAN HEAR IT.
OH, OH, MUSTN'T WASTE PAPER.
MUSTN'T WASTE PAPER.
PAPER IS VALUABLE.
YES, IT IS. YES, IT IS.
IT'S VALUABLE. IT'S VALUABLE.
[Sybil sobbing]
YOU CAN SEE NOW.
YOU CAN SEE THE PEOPLE.
YOU CAN SEE THE PEOPLE NOW.
YOU CAN SEE THEM.
YOU CAN SEE.
OH.
(as Sybil)
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
OH, GOD,
HOW DID I GET UNDER HERE?
HOW DID I GET UNDER THERE?
YOU HAVE TO STOP ME
FROM DOING THIS.
I CAN'T GO ON.
SYBIL, HOW DO YOU FEEL?
RELIEVED, A LITTLE.
HMM, I'M NOT SURPRISED.
YOU'VE ACCOMPLISHED
A GREAT DEAL.
SYBIL, COME AND SIT DOWN.
I WANNA SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
COME ON. SIT DOWN.
NOW, YOU TOLD ME THAT
THIS WAS A PICTURE
OF THE PEOPLE.
WHO DREW THAT?
THAT'S MY MOTHER.
THAT'S A PICTURE
OF MY MOTHER.
LOOK, THE LITTLE WISPS
OF HAIR THERE AND,
AND YOU CAN'T SEE HER EYES.
HER EYES ALWAYS SCARED ME.
DID YOU DO THAT?
NO. NO, I DIDN'T DO IT.
LOOK. LOOK,
THE LITTLE BOW AND HAIRPINS
SHE ALWAYS WORE IN HER HAIR.
AND--AND THERE'S
THE BUTTON HOOK.
I--I DON'T REMEMBER.
BUTTON HOOKS SCARE ME.
LIKE THEY'RE GONNA GET ME.
BUTTON HOOKS ARE GOOD THINGS.
WHAT ABOUT DISH TOWELS?
DO DISH TOWELS SCARE YOU?
HOW DO YOU KNOW
ABOUT DISH TOWELS?
DO THEY SCARE YOU?
YES.
BUT NOW DISH TOWELS ARE GOOD
AND USEFUL THINGS, RIGHT?
SYBIL,
LOVE IS A NECESSARY THING.
BUT NOW IF A VOICE SAYS,
"C-COME HERE, I LOVE YOU"
AND THEN A HAND REACHES OUT
AND PINCHES YOU
LIKE THAT, HARD,
THEN--THEN LOVE IS SPOILED
BY THAT HAND, ISN'T IT?
AND--AND--AND MUSIC,
NOW THAT'S SOMETHING
THAT--THAT YOU LOVE VERY MUCH
AND YOU MISS VERY MUCH
BECAUSE SOMEHOW
THAT WAS SPOILED FOR YOU,
TOO, BY THE HAND.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW,
BUT--BUT WE'RE GONNA FIND OUT.
AND THAT HAND
BELONGS TO THE PEOPLE
AND THE PEOPLE
WAS YOUR MOTHER.
(as Peggy)
THE PEOPLE,
I CANNOT SEE THE PEOPLE.
OH, PEGGY, STOP THAT!
(as Sybil)
WHAT?
OH, DR. WILBUR,
IT'S GETTING WORSE.
THIS IS GETTING A LOT WORSE,
ISN'T IT?
HOW DO YOU KNOW
THOSE THINGS?
I DON'T TELL YOU THEM.
AND WHO DOES THOSE DRAWINGS?
YOU DO.
OH, BUT YOU DO THEM
AS OTHER PEOPLE.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
MMM-MMM, MMM-MMM.
YOU DO THEM AS OTHER
PARTS OF YOURSELF
NO, I DON'T.
...WHO ARE STILL CHILDREN.
IT'S TRUE.
NO, IT'S NOT. IT IS NOT
SYBIL, YOU'VE GOT TO
UNDERSTAND. IT IS TRUE.
THIS IS NOT POSSIBLE.
IT'S POSSIBLE.
MMM-MMM.
IN FACT,
THROUGH MOST OF THE ANALYSIS,
I'VE BEEN TALKING TO YOU
THROUGH THEM.
THEY ALL HAVE NAMES
AND THEY COME HERE
AND THEY PROTECT YOU.
THEY KEEP YOUR APPOINTMENTS
AND THEY'RE THE ONES
WHO POUR OUT THIS INFORMATION
THAT YOU'RE AFRAID TO FACE.
OH, NO.
YOU'VE GOT TO
UNDERSTAND THAT, SYBIL.
NO, IT'S NOT TRUE.
IT'S TRUE.
IT'S NOT TRUE. NO, IT'S NOT.
NO. IT'S NOT TRUE.
SYBIL.
EVERYTHING YOU CARE ABOUT
SURVIVES IN THOSE PARTS OF YOU
THAT YOUR MOTHER
WASN'T ABLE TO REACH.
YOUR MUSIC, YOUR PAINTING,
EVEN YOUR ABILITY TO LOVE,
THEY SURVIVE THERE.
SYBIL, I WANT YOU
TO HEAR SOMETHING.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
I'M GOING TO LET YOU
HEAR YOURSELF
PLAY THE PIANO.
I--I CAN'T PLAY
THE PIANO ANYMORE.
I USED TO PLAY IT.
I--I CAN'T PLAY IT ANYMORE.
WELL, THIS IS A PART OF YOU
WHO CALLS HERSELF VANESSA,
AND SHE CAN.
SHE PLAYS BEAUTIFULLY.
I DON'T WANNA KNOW ABOUT HER.
SYBIL.
WE'VE GOT TO MAKE
THIS REAL FOR YOU.
[crying]
DOCTOR, I DON'T THINK
THAT I CAN TAKE IT.
MY HANDS ARE GOING NUMB.
THERE'S NO DANGER FOR YOU.
THERE IS NO DANGER.
THERE ARE NO DISH TOWELS
TYING YOUR WRISTS NOW.
MY HEART. MY HEART.
THAT'S ONLY ADRENALIN.
THERE IS NOBODY HERE
TO HURT YOU,
I PROMISE.
NOTHING BAD
IS GOING TO HAPPEN.
IT'S GONNA MAKE IT BETTER.
PLEASE, SYBIL,
JUST RELAX AND LISTEN.
**[piano playing]
THAT'S VANESSA.
AND SHE'S GOT ALL YOUR MUSIC
FOR SAFEKEEPING.
**[piano playing]
THAT'S ME?
PLAYING MOZART?
MMM-HMM.
AND YOU PLAYED SIBELIUS, TOO.
YOU PLAYED  FINLANDIA.
[clicking]
[Sybil in Hattie's voice]
DON'T YOU DARE TELL.
NEXT WORSE THING
TO BEING A FIBBER
IS BEING A TALEBEARER.
THAT'S MY MOTHER'S VOICE.
THAT'S MY--
THAT'S MY MOTHER'S...
THAT'S MY MOTHER'S VOICE.
SWEETIE, THAT'S NOT
YOUR MOTHER'S VOICE.
THAT'S YOU IMITATING YOUR...
SYBIL?
SYBIL!
[moaning]
WHAT THE HELL
DID THAT MONSTER DO TO YOU?
WHAT HAPPENED
IN THE GREEN KITCHEN?