In the year of King Tai, Ming Dynasty
The eunuches held the real power of
the development
They built up different departments
to reinforce their power
The whole country was under their control
East Chamber was the most powerful
and arrogant intelligent bureau
In order to get rid of those opposing power
They recruited many heartless
and cruel soldiers with high pay
To form a cold-blooded Black Arrow Troop
They were under severe training secretly
There was an arsenal under the East Chamber
It is responsible to design new
killing weapons
They used the prisoners for test
Let me go!
You shameless bastards!
God will punish you
Come out
I'm a government officer
you can't kill me
And you
Let's go
Plum Blossom Sun Shooting Arrow
Dogs Teeth Arrow
Phoenix Tail Arrow
The head Eunuch Tsao Siu Yan
After appointing himself
the head on the East Chamber
He controlled the Emperor
and the whole government
He tried every means to get rid
of those who went against him
What he wanted was a kingdom of himself
He set up a court and collected Information
from many different sources
Those who were against Tsao
Would be arrested and executed
with terrible punishment
Everybody was afraid
of the East Chamber
The whole country was covered
with frights and anxiety
You Excellency, he is the Military Secretary
Yang Yu-hin
What secret do we know about him?
On the 4th of April
he and the secreataries of 3 other department...
wanted to submit an impeachment against
the East Chamber
He pleaded the Emperor to close
Your Excellency
please give your judgement
Your Excellency, here is his impeachment
Secretary Yang
Damn
You've misunderstood us
We're faithful to the Emperor
Your frame to us would scare our Majesty
Aren't you afraid of death?
It's a royal order that eunuches
aren't allowed to involve in politics
So as to avoid you freaks
to mess up the country
Now you slaugher the officials
You're the one who should be dead
How dare you?
Execution
Yes
Yang, I don't think you know
the situation well
Give me the military power
Then I'll let you live
It's so ridiculous that
the government of Ming dynasty
is controlled by you dogs
No one can take over military power
without imperial permission
Stop dreaming
Officer
Give Officer Yang a permission as he wanted
Tsao, because of you bastard
Ming Dynasty is hopeless
He committed suicide
Although Yang was dead
I'm afraid his fellows
would go to his right hand Chow Wai-on
Protect Yang's children to the frontier
I'm sure Chow'd try hard to save them
Yes, sir
This is the Royal Order
The traitor Ex-Military Secretary
Yang Yu-hin
Is to be executed at noon
Tsao Siu Yan killed
the whole family of Yang
but the son and daughter
of Yang were interitionally left
In the Autumn of the same year
they were exited
Tsao orderd the Black Arrow Troop
to tail them secretly
What he wanted was to kill
Yang's right hand, Chow Wai-on
So as to terminate
the remained power of Yang
Kiddo, are you fine?
What the hell it is? Not even a tree
It's so hot
My holy God, I, Yau Mo-yin
swear in front of this sword
I must save Yang's children
All is ready, let's go
Go!
To get out of the boundary
we'd pass Tsi, Turk, Hai-ku 3 places
You divide into 3 teams
I will give order in the central
They can never escape from us!
Your Excellency, the troops are all ready
What shall we do now?
From here to the boundary,
we'd pass Tsi Turk, Hai-ku 3 places
There are steep atopes and cliffs!
I think, Tsao must hide his troop here
to trap us
There is a dried river bed at the West
Let's take risk, to give him a raid
OK, let's go this way
President
nothing happened in these 3 days
Chow has been the right hand of Yang
He could be the coach of 800,000
imperial soldiers
Because of Yang's recommendation
Thus, thinking of such relationship
Chow would come to save the kids
I am thirsty
Drink it
Uncle, can you give us
something to drink?
Get lost, get lost
Come over... open your hands
Thank you
No hurry, drink it slowly
Sister, drink it!
No, you drink it
The president really knows everything
Set them free, now
No, we can't defy government's order
If not, let's kill him
We come to save
But not to kill
If you want to kill
let's kill the dogs of the East Chamber
Set them free and leave with us
Otherwise, those bastards won't let you go
Stop puzzling
You've no choice, hurry up
Sister
Kiddo
Enemies
Protect the kids
They are small potatos only
our large hasn't shown up yet
Kiddo
Your Excellency, Chow finally comes
The twins Sword
Sister, I'm so scared
The Black Flag Arrow Troop?
Sister, where are you?
Just follow me
The arrows are like a storm.
Save the kids and leave at once
Shit! The soldiers are coming towards us
Stay where you are
Your Excellency,
it wasn't Chow who came
They seem to be rascals
Brother, we are safe!
Chow Wai-on is such a wise man
The people come for the children
are trobbers only
Let them go first
I want to make a deed set at them all!
This is the Dragon Gate
I've made a date in the Dragon Inn with Chow
We'll leave the frontier together
We're carrying the kids
and the soldiers are after us
I think
We'd go to the Dragon Gate
along the river bed
Just do what you said
Yang Kwan is a main road
Shang, take 500 soldiers
to guard this gate
Yes
There are many lanes to Yu Mun Kwan
Send the best soldiers to block all exits
Although the Dragon Gate is heavily armed
I think Chow'd take this risk
And leave from the Dragon Gate
with the rascals
Go there by taking the path
I'll follow with the Black Flag Troop
It's wise of you, Your Excellency
Let's go
Yes, sir
Spicy Meat Bun
Three-taels
why don't you send me the wine?
It's coming...
Damn weather, the wind made me so dirty
Good morning, sir
What? You don't want to serve me?
No, if it's not you guarding the border
We can't even do business here
Fetch me some wine
OK, I'll go right now
Sir, here comes the wine
See, your nickname suits you well
Exactly 3 taels of wine per cup.
Not a drop less
My grandpa gave me this name
Spicy Meat Bun
Come here
Where is your boss?
She is dealing some business upstairs
You want to leave the border
through my secret tunnel...
Or want to sleep with me?
Tiger, you can only choose one of them
Choose carefully
I've made it
Men are all sex-oriented
You want it whenever you want it
and leave whenever you finish it
Cut the crap
Just relax
Come on
I want the answer, tunnel or me?
I want both
It's too greedy of you
I've checked it. I'm not interested at all
The Willow Dart?
I'll get 100 taels by sending you
out of the frontier
But I'll get 400 taels by sending you to hell
I really don't know what to choose
Here is fresh meat for the buns
The boss's coming.
We're waiting for you to extinguish our fire
Eating mutton will make you have more fire
It'll make you hot. Bastard
Maybe you can help us with this?
Damn you
I don't eat mutton
I want to eat you
Go to hell
Why not eat me? I'm bigger in size
Damn you
Who is he?
You're always interested in men
How about me?
I always treat you as well as I can
Good looking
He is Chow, a wanted criminal.
He was a coach of the Imperial Army
He doesn't look like a coach
Yes, he doesn't
He's in big trouble with
the East Chamber
They want his head
East Chamber?
Yes
It's nothing
Mind your tongue
Tiger's head worths 500 taels?
Meaner, ask the chef, Duo
to keep the head of the lamb
You just care about lamp but not me
How dare you do this
in front of your fellows?
You'll give them a bad example
Why is there blood on your dress?
No. There is no blood
Look
Really?
You're having period?
Haven't you seen it before?
Ask your mother then
She passed away long long time ago
Go ask your sister then
Come over here,
I'll teach you a good lesson
Come over here...
Come if you have guts
Damn you
Welcome.
How many rooms do you want?
We want 3 of your best
Okay, take a rest first
Your period doesn't seem to be regular
Tell me earlier next time
Time to go back, we're just here
May I help you, sir?
Thanks, I'll do it myself
This way please, this is clean
With less wind and sand
What do you want to eat?
Give us some bread
Why not some wine?
OK, give us 3 catties
I'll get it now
Listen
This is my place, everything is mine
If you violate the rules
You can never
trade your pilfered goods here again
Damn you
I'll do it
The Dragon Mountain is famous for its rain
Why?
How can it rain in such a sunny day?
I think you're a stranger here
Where are you from?
We came from the south
To the north
How long will you stay?
We'll leave tomorrow
Spicy meat buns...
Beautiful
How sweet of you
We don't know where they are from
Watch out for them
One is soldier, one is wounded
The one in black should be their leader
- She's a woman
- A woman?
I can tell she is female because...
She didn't show interest in me
There is something wrong with the meat
Don't eat
What is it?
There is something wrong anyway
Not showing respect
Go
Let's go
Do you have any medicine?
No
It's getting dark. Light up the candles
Mistress, what meat is it?
Spicy Meat
What is spicy meat?
Haven't you heard of it?
The name of spicy meat appeared in a novel.
Mrs Suen sold it
Mrs Suen opened an inn which robbed
But mine is Dragon Inn
But you don't look like a jinx
Really? My name is Jade King
What a pity that it's hard for
a stone to turn to jade
In this world
There're many things unworthy of the name
and many people got empty brains
You're pretty
You too
But I'm sure I know you better
So you should let me know you better
I don't think it's a big deal actually
Why not ask some men here
that'd be fun
What! You think I'm afraid of men?
I've messed with more men than
you've seen
Just look at you, you're still a virgin
Aren't you?
Where is the hen hurrying to?
Let's see how you light up
a candle on the roof
Who are you? Why are you laughing?
May I know where the Dragon Inn is?
Here it is
Are you the boss?
Just call me Jade King
Jade! What a good name
Beautiful name
How about me?
Any room?
Handsome guy
Are you a businessman?
I want a room
How long will you stay?
Do I look like I've no money?
I'm just afraid that
you'll leave without saying goodbye
You know,
Dragon Mountain is famous for its rain
Even the most
vigorous animal scares of it
So we're the same people
we should keep in touch
Glad to make friends with you.
I may need your help some day
It depends on how smart you are
Miss Yau
He is here
This is my inn, please make yourself at home
Wearing foreign dress for
foreign customers tonight?
I've told you to wash that flag
See, I got mud all over me
This must be a woman
How do you know?
As you said
only women won't be interested in you
But he is different
His eyes didn't show interest on me
but his heart did
I don't think his heart
is interested in you
I can listen to your flute again
Go to work
Don't just play that song
Uncle Chow
Poor kids, you suffered a lot
He is Ho Fu
Thank you for your help
I really appreciate for all your kindness
Don't mention it
This is called Dog's teeth Arrow
It's produced by the East Chamber
I'd seen when I worked for the government
So you'd better pay much attention
to it in future
When can we get out of here?
As soon as possible
Chun, take the money
Hide up and meet your family later
Sir, I can't take this
This inn is so complicated
Pack up and leave here
as soon as possible
Mistress
I know you will come
You're really clever
I don't need you to flatter me
I just want to know about the weather here
Come inside
This room is nice and quiet
No room is nice
in a deserted place like this
What tea do you want to have?
Tuckanhoe or something else?
What kind of flower is this?
It's beautiful
You think it's white lotus?
It's turnip flower
White lotus can only be found
on Snow Mountain
Try the tea
When will you leave?
Tonight
I'm afraid you can't
Why?
Don't you know
the weather of the desert?
Please advise me
This's raining season
the weather is unpredictable
It'll rain cats and dogs even
the sun is on
This's the only hotel here
You can't reach the gate even
you can leave here
I think you know
whether it's sunny or rainy day
It depends on who that asks
The rain'll keep you here
just stay for a few more days
Though the weather is unpredictable
we can't stay forever
Seems we're connected in some ways
Please help us
You're leaving?
- I've two children with me
- They're hostages?
Mistress, please lead us the way
It depends on which way you want to take
The general of the border is my friend
I think I can help you with my reputation
But if you want to leave secretly...
Let me think...
I'm okay. Weapons are ruthless
We're friends now. And I'll repay you
Come again tonight
I have to leave tonight
You can't. I'll wait
Block the gate
Damn you. Fool
The latch is useless, move the table
Open the door...
Who is it? We just closed the door
Don't open it, let him die in the rain
Open up, quick
Stop knocking, bastard
If you knock again, I'll...
What's the matter?
Are you deaf?
Why didn't you open the door?
We're in trouble
3 branch heads from
the East Chamber have come
Damn you
My books are all wet!
Are you blind? Just close the door!
Go and shut the door
Boss
He is calling you
Can't you see I'm busy?
Any good room?
No, all full
Please ask them to move out
I just do whatever I like
Not tall enough
I don't do things I don't like
Take it back
You bitch
What did you say?
Money isn't my concern
Most important of all
I want a comfortable accommodation
I'm doing business too
I don't care about the money
You've messed up my place
So what to do then?
Count the loss
And I'll pay you by triple?
Good room? There is one, come on
It is raining cats and dogs
we can't leave now
We'll wait
Take the luggage in
We have limited rooms but numerous guests
How long will you stay?
The weather is unpredictable
See how long can this gold pay for?
You must be tired
Sir, please have some tea
Any strangers checked in these days?
Are you looking for someone?
We businessmen should be careful
and get rid of trouble
I just want to know
if there is any trouble around
Have some tea
If there is any, I won't open an inn here
Sorry
This is a very special tea
The taste is nothing special
But you have something special
on your mind
Don't you think Chow Wai On
will take this route?
Go and check
Meaner...
Boss
Why you acted before my order?
Shadows are found everywhere
But they're not our men
We haven't taken any action yet
Go and check carefully.
Watch out for the money box
Yes
What a troubled world it is
Thieves'd watch out for other thieves.
Damn it
What is he singing?
He is barbarian.
He is humming barbarian song
I'll dig your eyes out
So you can't see
I'll peel off your skin
so you can't wear
I'll chop your head off
so you can't live
Don't make any trouble
Somebody is on the roof
Forget it
We'll leave right after the rain stops
Who was killed by the thunder?
We are all here
Good job! Kill your tribe
Thank god
Where are Bill Chow and Shao Tong?
I'll go and find them
No! It'll alarm our enemies
The rain is so heavy, we can't leave
Neither can they
Right
Look at the sword under the lamp
after drunk...
When can we live in peace?
I don't want to wait anymore!
Just stay calm
Anxiety won't help
But waitng won't help either
Lower your voice
If the eunuches come
we'll be in danger
What'll we do
if we are trapped in this inn?
Ho, I didn't pay a penny less
There are rules that
we all should follow
Miss Yau, my buddies and I...
make money by risking our lives
To save this two kids...
we've missed many business opportunity
and money
Now the government knows who we are
Damn, we've given all
we have to be a good guy
Well, I'll pay your loss
It sounds reasonable
Make it clean
Sir, did you sleep well last night?
Bull shit
Have a seat
- Shun, clean the tables and chairs
- Yes
Give us some tea
Still didn't get any news
from Bill Chow and Shao Tong?
It's strange!
We can't even find their bodies
There must be something strange
Tony, give them some bread
We don't want bread this morning
Give us a roasted lamb
Roasted lamb
- Do you have roasted lamb in desert?
- Yes
They're fat lambs!
We just killed two last night
Give us one
You too? Ok, coming...
The fight last night was tiring enough
And now we've to work this morning
Go and get the weapons
You are good looking
From your forehead
There is florid
I can tell you're having good luck
Thank you.
Hope your fortune telling comes true
If you don't mind,
can I see your hands?
Sure
From your influence line
you were a government officer 2 years ago
What're you working now?
Anywhere! When there is rough road
I'd make it flat
When there is tree blocking the road
I'd remove it
That's why
your influence line isn't that smooth
I don't think I've the luck
to be gov't official, but I think you have
Why?
In such a desert
Ordinary citizens won't wear
officer's boots
Don't be nervous! You're an officer
So you should know
something happened in town
Which one are you talking about?
The Secretary
of the Military Dept. Yang was killed
His corpse was hanged and his
whole family was killed too
Pal, do you know who did it?
I don't know
Really?
The water is boiling
Sir... oh no...
Mister
Can you tell me is he a lady killer?
Yes! His eyes attract women
Really?
The ones who killed Yang
are some ruthless bastards
It's hot, let it cool down
Mistress
This is for the broken table.
Buy a new one
I don't think it's enough
Give us the food! We're starving!
Pal, you are a man
of righteousness and guts
May I know your name?
I'm a wanderer, name is meaningless to me
Let's cheers for this nameless world
OK! I'll drink this wine with you!
Cheers!
- Please
Here's the roasted lamb
Mistress, how about our lamb?
It'd be roasted one by one
But first come first serve
Make it half then
Dao
Cut the lamb in half
How? Straight or cross?
As you like, just make it half
I wonder what relationship Chow has
with this inn?
I think we'd better take action
as soon as possilble
Let's ambush them tonight
Bravo! The rain has stopped!
We may go now
Don't panic, they will discover it easily
The larget is so great
We are not clear about the outside world
We have 2 kids too.
We can't go as fast as they can
Once this inn is owned by thieves
there must be some secret tunnel
Let's search it tonight
It was dangerous!
Quickly I fixed up the mess
otherwise I'd have lost if there're a fight
No, some hocus is put!
Drink this
Tonight, why no we...
What shall we do tonight?
What?
You are all fools!
If we want to leave here
We must get rid of those bastards first
Ho Fu, Iron, you two'll attack
from both sides
Mo-yan will attack in the midle
Cha's room is at the corner
and has just one door
Okay, let me do it
Mr Chow, have you fallen asleep?
I come to serve you
Jade, why do you come here
in the middle of the night?
Why do you come here then?
Stop bothering my business
This is my inn
Who'll responsible for it
if someone get killed here?
But there were many people got killed
in this inn before
I tell you, I know your story very well
Don't push me to make a dead set at you
What are you?
Officers and thieves have their own ways
And our own duties
But I'd ask your help
How?
Be frank, they are kidnappers
That's none of my business
$1000 taels, deal or not?
To kill him?
No, just delay them.
Make them stay one more night
And forget everything, what say you?
Guess
Fantastic
Promised?
If you can't sleep, get something to eat
Sister
Take care of the kids
Where is Uncle Chow?
It's fine
Yuk Bo
You went for a walk so late?
It's freezing
- Here is too hot
- Hot?
But I feel cold! Am I so sick?
The logner we stay
the more danger we'll have
We can't wait
Let's take a risk! Go!
Ho Hu, Iron
I'll stop the enemies with Mo-yan
Just take the kids away
We'll meet at the Dragon Gate
Wai-on, cover them
Leave the inn to me
Mo-yan
Who is it?
Chun
- Brother Ho
- Come in
Miss Yau
Chun, don't worry
We'll protect you
Mo-yan
Wai-on, take care of Yang's kids
Wait
Can I have this flute?
Don't waste time
The rabbit in the trap is always
anxious to escape
But it can never make it
Yes
We'd move this time!
My inn would be jacked up
Pack up now
No matter how, we'd move
Damn it
Why do you shut the door?
Don't you know the wind is killing me?
No business today?
Thank god! Our savior comes
Don't let them fish in the trouble water
Just tail them
Thank god
You bring us peace
Even fire has to go off
What peace?
There is sand-storm outside
You said there was a fire?
Here! Here!
Where is it?
Here
Where is the fire?
What were you doing?
You should smell it!
Damn it! Can you see the fire?
I want them to show up
What's wrong?
Who are you?
Why do you bring so many weapons?
For business
Trade with knives?
Sir, businessmen should be careful
In this troubled world
we've to protect ourselves
You look familiar
Who are you?
I'm talking to you
Sir
Watch the opera
we don't have to do anything
Just wait and see
Where are you from?
Are you the general guarding the border?
How dare you talk to me like this?
We are...
Secret agents from the East Chamber
This is our identity proof
It's confidential
Our identity proof
Damn it
We become thieves in return
Where are you going to?
Going out of the border
Don't you know the gate is closed?
No one can get out without the order
from the President of the East Chamber
I know
You look like
the wanted criminal Chow Wai-on
You look almost the same
You should be him...
I don't think so
Look! There is a mold on the man's face
But he hasn't
But I don't remember there's any mold
Look at that guy
he has a mold when he came
Now, only a scar is left
Look, they pretend to be calm
You can tell there is something wrong
with them
Take them to your camps for questioning
Maybe they're the people we want
If you get any merit from it
don't forget us
Sure
You, come over here
The one with a scar
Hey, I'm talking to you!
Why do you stare at me?
Not happy with it?
You are just like a thief
And you're a businessman?
You can never cheat me
Don't get angry, it's their trick
I don't like you since the first time
I saw you
Take them to the camp
Yes, sir
Drink with me
Go
You two get up
They are all here
Watch over the general.
I'll look for another exit
Three taels, give me wine
Sir, take care...
The reward from
the government is just $1000 taels
See, these cheques cost $1,000 taels each
I'm a reasonable man
Drop the knife
There is trouble in the frontier.
No one can go in or go out
You'd better stay few more days
When the order is cancelled
I'll let you go
Thank you, sir
You'll have a share too
Let's drink
Chow Wai-on disappeared
Lu Siu Chuen
Sir, he doesn't seem to be here
Dao, the stuff is here
It is the first time...
you stare at me like this
Boss
Go
He came from the secret passage
If you are willing to stare at me
because of the passage
How about I open all the passages...
So you can stare at me for
the rest of your life
You're in this business for
such a long time
You should know what I want
and I like most
I want to buy a road to leave the country
I'll offer $1,000 taels
$1,000 taels?
If I want $1,000 taels
I wouldn't have added the...
So you don't want money
No
I want $2,000 taels
and you
What? Scared?
Hero always goes with beauty
But I do want to try...
a special one like you
But on one condition
What is it?
I want a formal wedding
What? Scared?
Forget it!
I just want to have one night stand
I'm a righteous man
Sleeping with you...
may bring me a notorious name
OK, let's have formal wedding
I'll take this as present
Give it back to me
Come on, go ahead
Move your hand downward
then we'll save the wedding
Come on
I'll take it back on our wedding
Your Excellency,
we'll be at Dragon Gate soon
A wedding? Do you mean it?
Jade's secret tunnel is
the only way out
Only you believe her
I don't trust that bitch
You are a triad member too
We can be brothers
So why can't I trust her?
Dragon Inn is a place
only talks about interests
It has its own way to survive in a desert
The wedding is to confuse the East Chamber
I want Cha to be the master of
the wedding so as to hinder their act
Then I'll force Jade to tell me
where the tunnel is
When you see I put the candle on the sill
you all rush our from both sides
Mo-yan'll take the kids to Jade's room
Then we'll escort Jade to lead us
out of here
There is no righteousness in politics
Mo-yan, do you understand?
How can a man come out
after entering the bride's room?
Don't you think...
I'll give you all up for having sex?
Just follow his instruction
Even Miss Yau can't understand him
The more confused we are,
the easier it goes
Dragon Inn
I hope I won't see you here again
How is it going on outside?
The set has almost done
Did the geanny promise?
There won't be any problem!
Of course!
Just only you stay...
The granny will promise anything
How can I be the master of wedding?
If it's not your reminder
on the other day...
I can never marry Jade
You deserve it
Right, their parents are not here
and you are old enough...
You're the only choice
Okay, I'll do it
Congratulation
Thank you
Today is my wedding
Enjoy yourselves and let's get drunk!
Make yourselves at home
You men look sad
Give a speech
I've been a homeless
and lonely businessman before
I'm so glad to be a match maker
in a desert
I really feel honored
Why are you standing here?
Today is Jade's wedding
Why don't you congratulate them?
Smile
I know it's nosy of me...
but it's hard to find a good man
If you find one...
just keep him by any means
Perfect couple
They're made for each other
Great! Have my toast
Don't get drunk on this big day
But it's a big day! We should get drunk
Sir, don't drink any wine
that is not ours
It may be poisoned
Cheers
Fine
Great!
Go to the bride's room.
Don't let them delay us
What are you doing?
Going to bed so early?
It's good time
We want to play with the couples
If you can defeat me, I'll let you go in
OK! Come on
It's a big day, don't fight
Let's drink
Give us wine
Sir, it doesn't matter
We've more men! We are having advantage
Water is filled into these 2 pots
Don't worry, you won't get drunk
Let's make it five
Don't waste time.
Tell me where the tunnel is
Light the candle first
But in case you're fooling me...
Here it is
See if you are capable to go in
Mr Ngai, the 4th one
The last one
Tell me now
It's not funny to fool you
Do you have weapons on your wedding?
Where is my flute?
Search it
Baldy, cheers
Ok! Let's finish a pot each
Useless! Get lost
Come on
Be careful
I have brought some fruits for you
Thank you
Isn't it delicious?
The moon is beautiful tonight
Sister, tell me why...
it's not the same moon as in our hometown?
Mom said the moon
is always more beautiful in hometown
So this is less beautiful than
the one in our hometown
But, we have no home now!
We can see the moon here safely
it's the mercy of God indeed
How do you feel this place?
Good, cause you are so kind
to treat me fruit!
Come and eat together
There may be some changes
If anything goes wrong, I'll drop the cup
Once you get this signal, take action
Think some ways to send me out
Sure
But not tonight
This is the only chance, I must go
I tell you, once stepping in my room
you have to listen to me
I say yes, then yes
Jade, please help me
I'll marry you when I return
So we won't owe each other
Haven't you fooled me enough?
Sir, the President's army will
arrive soon
Miss Yau, this is water, not wine
Forget me, just watch out for the signal
They seem to be serious
I think so
Cut the crap! We've bet our lives on it
You're a man of the world
Inform me once you get any news
There is a secret passage in Jade's room
Chow'll leave through this tonight
He's smart
No one can leave here
How about going up there and check?
Will it help?
Check? Okay
Don't waste time
Yes! Time is running short! Come on
Mistress, open up
Who is it?
It's Cha Ting! Open up please
What's the matter?
My servant is hurt
Do you have any medicine?
What's up?
You're trouble
My servant's head is hurt
Please have a look
Today is my big day.
You should know what to do
Give me the medicine
Come over here, this way
Let's talk
What's up?
Don't you think you can go that easily?
Why do you act in such a hurry?
Let's take action after this night
Don't ruin my wedding
But I'm afraid you'd ruin my plan
What does that mean?
I know Chow is planning to leave
through your secret tunnel
He gives me much money
and accompanies me
What can you pay?
Give me a price
$100,000 taels
Money isn't a problem, we can talk about it
Give me the money, I'll give you the man
Be careful that you'll lost
both money and man
You're back
2 more injured?
I tell you, you've to pay for my medicine
Have you finished your business?
But our affair is not ended
You can't go
Mr Ho, where are you going to?
Come on! Have some more wine
Get lost! I want to piss
What a coincidence, I want to piss too
Then you go first
The candle is blown off
Bitch
Shall we wait for the signal?
He is enjoying himself
but forget about our lives
Broken cups
Nothing... this is for protection only
Let's keep on drinking
These bastards are well prepared
We've to fight anyway, let's start now!
I'll help you
Take the knife
You want to escape?
Go with the kids
Ok
Let Chung chase after them
Our target is Chow Wai-on
Shall we wait for Chow?
Stop waiting, let's get out of here
Get up, let's go
Where is Uncle Chow?
Don't ask, quick!
Let me go, what have you got from
the East Chamber?
They've given me much more than you have
Stop him!
I won't let you go
I can't believe you work for
the East Chamber
Damn you
Don't frame me
Chow, you're going to lose
Meaner
Who told you to take action?
We didn't, that old man...
The old bastard?
Meaner
Damn you
Jade, we've paid you
Take it back to buy your coffin
You're good
There is a sand-storm ahead
It isn't sand storm
Someone is riding a horse
The troop from East Chamber is coming
Let's go separately, we'll join later
Okay
It's Tsao's black Flag Arrow Troop
I'm your man
Iron, Ho Fu
Yuk Ying, Yuk Bo
Yuk Bo
Sister, I am here
Where is Yuk Bo?
Sister
Don't be afraid, I will take you away
Are you mad, Jade?
Siu Chuen
You two bastards, you are beasts
I'll take your skin off!
Sister
Mo-Yan
Hold it
Tsao is here
What? Tsao is here?
She fainted, it's useless
Take her to my room
Dao
Tell the general I'm in trouble, go!
The medicine
We've been through all adversities...
and we'd escaped from every danger
But it's an ever changing world
We can't be sure if we can escape this time
Mo-Yan
Wai-on, I should have faith in you
That flute
I didn't mean to give it to jade
I really don't know...
you'd be so upset
Luckily I can explain to you
People said: Love is not secured
in a messy world
Actually, love is more valuable in
such a troubled world
You can't get the flute back
It's nothing
Nothing is more important than our love
Damn it
Why don't you leave?
This is my inn, why should I leave?
I've nearly forgotten
You're as cool as a desert
You're so mean
The people in desert are always selfish
They only care about themselves
So you open this inn
You travellers
leave when you reach your aim
I just learn this from you
And I'm cool and mean?
Who is it?
Dao
Are the helpers coming?
He's not coming
Damn it, they're all heartless beasts
After killing those bastards
I'll come back and teach them
a good lesson
Why are you back?
It's out of my expectation that
the one who stays behind with me
is a barbarian
Watch out for the arrows
Dao, take the kids to the tunnel,
Hurry up
Damn it
Hold it
Hurry up
Your flute
I don't want anything that
is given out of pity
Your excellency, the inn is surrounded
Mo-yan, go down first
Hold my hand
There are many soldiers
Forget it
Go
There are people behind the hill
Still chasing?
Go to hell!
Go...
The desert is huge, I'll follow you
I will stop him
Jade, take the kids away
Wait for me at the Dragon Gate
Don't think about it now!
Wai-on, we'd live or die together
Me too
Why don't you leave?
Block his way
Are you okay?
Wai-on!
Get lost!
After killing you
my kingdom is as solid as steel
We'll fight you together
But you fight alone
Damn you, we can kill you any time
Come on, eunuch
Shit, we are trapped inside
the drift sand
What should we do?
We can't move
It's your end
Mo-Yan
Don't close your eyes
I'll help you to chop him
The Willow Strike
Destroying stance
Mo-Yan
Go to hell
It's useless
I will kill you
Stop
Be careful
Chow, you are a man
You have to take the kids out of here
I'm the most powerful man in the world
You choose the way to hell
Oh, my leg
My hand
Where else can you go?
Wonder sword
Push me over there, hurry up
Chow, can you hear me?
Mo-Yan
Will you come back to the Dragon Inn?
When other guests come
you may have already forgotten me
I can't face the desert as brave as you
I want to leave now
The Dragon Inn
Give me some wine
Let's leave this heartless place
to go after Chow