We've also made 2,500kg
of morphine,
700kg of heroine
and 300kg of cocaine.
Apart from reserving some for our own use
it's all exported for fund-raising
or for preaching purposes.
The new tranquilliser we've had under
research has been successfully made.
Chief, Asian Hawk and Alan are here.
The agents of many countries
are interested in it.
- We must mass-produce it.
- Take care of this.
When the plant at hillside
starts production
we can cope with our needs...
Friend, could you
cut short your report?
My report's over.
Brothers, after 30 days hard work,
today is festival once again.
The Goddesses are now here.
We should thank our true God.
Supreme Creator.
Thank you for bringing us
to this world
for creating the sun, moon and stars
to shine on our life.
Thank you for creating animals,
plants, everything
to keep us safe from starvation...
health and for creating sickness.
We also thank you
for creating the two sexes
to enable us to have pleasure.
Thank you, Lord for your grace.
The happy hour begins.
Quiet!
Enjoy yourselves.
May has been captured.
Never mind. Let's go.
- We must act gracefully.
- Right.
Let her try being a whore.
Cut that out.
Do you know where Laura is?
Don't keep thinking of her.
You never cared for May. Now...
It's all right. She's now...
It's her own doing.
Women are a nuisance.
You're a nuisance.
- What are you doing?
- I'll exorcise your spirits.
Spirits? I've no spirits.
Now tell the Llama.
The Asian Hawk is here.
Let them do anything they please.
Don't stop them. Understand?
How long will it last?
Three days.
During this time
she'll be totally in my power.
Good.
Pledge upon death
allegiance to the Chief.
I pledge upon death...
You must go with Alan to get
the 3 pieces of the Armour of God.
I must get...
Inject the Asian Hawk
to make him loyal to us.
Let's drink to our meeting.
Don't drink too much,
it's very strong.
Are you afraid of getting drunk?
I'm not afraid of strong wine.
Great, isn't it?
Don't waste any time.
What are you doing?
I've already paid.
I want to talk.
There's nothing to talk about.
You're the most beautiful little whore.
- What are you up to?
- I want to give you more wine.
- Who are you?
- I'm a prostitute.
- No, you're a well-bred girl.
- I'm not, I'm a whore.
What are you trying to do?
Who on earth are you?
I'm really a whore, believe me.
What is it?
The Chief says this girl is a spy.
Never mind.
- You promised to bring me wine.
- OK, I will.
What now?
- Ask someone the way.
- What?
- Ask him.
- Who?
Buddha be praised.
That was easy.
He's following us. Keep calm.
Don't laugh.
Where's the Chinese girl?
- Who?
- The Chinese girl.
Downstairs, in a guarded room.
- What are you doing here?
- Your job?
I'm in charge of storerooms, the garbage rooms,
kennels and the dungeon.
Let's talk in bed.
Get up, don't sleep.
I can't get away if you're in bed.
Get up.
You're drunk as a Lord.
I can only cope with two.
And the other one?
You want me to persuade him?
My hand still hurts.
It's up to you.
Pick up your robe.
This is for you.
Violence? I sang in a Peace Concert.
Violence is disgusting.
It's up to you. I'll fix these two.
Don't talk about this
when you return to Hong Kong.
Close the door.
Only a nut would rely on you.
I didn't ask you to come for nothing.
She hit me.
I didn't know it was you.
They... Everything OK?
- What do you want to know?
- I wish everything was OK.
See if there's a key.
Would a nobody have the keys?
Right you are.
Girls are great sometimes.
Help tie them up.
Laura...
I had so much trouble
finding you, Laura.
Laura, it's Jackie.
Are you all right? You're scaring me.
I'm scared.
Don't worry.
I'll get you out of here.
Maybe she's in shock.
Let's talk after we get out.
Get her out of here at once.
Hurry up.
Bye...
See you next time.
Thank you.
The earliest flight's tomorrow.
Let's spend the night here.
OK.
Anyway, Laura's unfit to travel.
She'll be all right tomorrow.
Make yourselves at home.
We still have to keep
our promise to your daddy.
What?
- What?
- Never mind. Go to bed early.
I'll see what I can do.
- Good night.
I'll go up with them.
I'm really grateful.
It's nothing much.
It's been unexpectedly easy.
Of course, with me here.
I am a lucky charm.
- Good night.
Good night.
Let's go.
I'll take them to Frankfurt airport
for a flight to Hong Kong
before coming back.
Is that necessary?
I like to keep my promises
but more than that, I want to do it.
Want to play whore again?
Sorry. Good night.
You want to see
the Armour of God now?
How about seeing it tomorrow?
I really want to see it.
OK...
I'll show it to you.
What are you doing?
- You act as if Laura were kidnapped again.
- It's nothing.
Why do you need me then?
Can't I just pay you a visit?
Go and see Laura then.
She won't do anything.
So you come to see me?
What do you want?
Sorry, I don't know how to put it.
What is it?
Did you notice
anything wrong with Laura?
It's natural
after a long confinement.
She looks funny to me.
She's no longer as young as she was.
She wants to see the Armour of God now.
Isn't that a bit fishy?
Fishy yourself.
She's always been curious.
And she was kidnapped for it.
Let her see it.
Borrow it from May then.
She just slapped me in the face.
Slapped you in the face?
Why? Tell me about it.
Are you sure you want to borrow it?
Come on, but you ask her.
Knock at the door.
No answer. She must be
taking a bath or changing.
Just see for yourself.
May.
- She's not in.
- Wait till she comes back.
Laura's waiting.
I'll show her and put it back.
Hurry up.
Jackie, why are you at my door?
I...
You standing at my door when
I'm not here. What are you doing?
Trying to take the Armour of God?
No.
Get out at once.
I hate intruders or those
who do not respect others' privacy.
Listen.
I'd like to apologise.
I know I was wrong.
You do?
I don't.
- What?
- I know I should watch my language.
- And?
What else is there?
Why didn't you kiss me?
I wanted to, but...
What is it?
I've something to show you.
Something to show me?
But I can't show you here.
Where then?
Come to my room.
Come, I'll follow you. Go now.
Why show me in your room?
I'll tell you there.
I thought you had
something to show me.
Show you?
I'll show you some children's photos.
Laura.
Is that what you wanted me to see?
May, listen to me.
- What are you doing here?
- Waiting for you.
I wanted to see you.
What for?
Don't you know I missed you?
Don't, Laura, don't!
Don't let Alan see.
Don't mention him.
Laura, don't.
Wait a minute.
Jackie.
- Has Laura been here?
- No.
- Isn't she in the room?
- Anybody in?
- No.
No?
What a liar.
Who is it?
May.
Don't be shy.
I didn't want to embarrass her.
Let's go out and let her stay.
OK.
I'll be back right away.
When did that start?
Just now.
Frankly, that slap was good for you.
Good?
- Your bathroom?
- My bathroom opens onto hers.
Pretend you know nothing
when she comes out.
You've been to his room,
you've seen it.
- I didn't see anything.
- Stop acting.
I don't have to see it to know.
- You don't mind then?
- No, times are different now.
This brings us closer.
So you're more than friends,
you share everything.
- Right, we're better than friends.
- Right!
Friends.
You're worse than beasts.
You're accusing me again?
She seems to have
suffered a big shock.
I didn't do anything.
I'll give her a piece of my mind.
No need. See if Laura's in.
- I have a way with girls.
- Go ahead.
May's a good girl.
- I know.
- She's good for you.
Go now...
Go.
You again?
I'm arranging for a couple
to make love.
- What?
- Not you.
Why are you packing?
I don't want to see you anymore.
I'm leaving.
- What are you doing?
- Helping you pack.
May...
That room is linked to this one?
Nonsense.
Laura.
What is it, Jackie?
Alan and Laura have taken
the Armour of God.
How come?
I must go up.
What about me?
You help me arrange something.
What's wrong with the dogs?
Let's go and see.
Calm down.
Snookums.
Don't be afraid.
It's all right. I'll help you.
- What did you call him?
- Snookums.
- Only she calls me that name.
- Disgusting.
What took you?
- Don't you know what you did?
- I do, but we couldn't help it.
Luckily we're both all right.
I believe you too.
Otherwise, she wouldn't have
called me Snookums.
Disgusting.
How are we going to get out?
Laura and I escape.
You try to escape by yourself.
- You have so much confidence in me?
- I only promised to help Laura out -
not you.
Bravo, Snookums.
Now you've a chance
to even things up.
He always accused me
of taking away his love.
You're great, I can't get out.
- Go and take good care of Laura.
- You don't have to tell me that.
- Let's go before it's too late.
- We can't leave him behind.
Laura, forget me, an unlucky man.
Good luck to you both.
Why won't you rescue him?
I had a wish when I was a kid -
to save every man like Jesus does.
When I grew up,
I realised one man's strength is limited.
If he comes we won't all get away.
Right, Laura, don't be emotional.
Jackie's kung fu is limited.
If he tries to save me too,
then we'll all be captured.
Leave me, follow him.
Nothing would please me more
than to see you both happy and free.
Go now.
Alan, you're so nice to me.
I was right about you.
You go, I've decided to stay.
You don't mean what you say.
I've been wondering
why I lost Laura to you.
Now I've learnt your trick.
I must rescue you, come what may.
As I said, you're the bravest man.
But girls only fall for sweet talk.
- I must thank you then.
- Never. I won't help you for free.
They're demanding a ransom
of $5 million.
- Give me at least half that.
- Don't be so mean, it's not you.
He always acts the good guy.
So I'm forced to play the bad guy.
Teasing me?
I'm not afraid.
Remember, be alert.
I know. What nonsense.
I'm all right.
This way looks better.
You go that way then.
It makes no difference.
Let's split up after this.
I'll take care of the guards.
- What about you?
- Me?
Forget me, an unlucky man.
Never mind him, he never changes.
He's only thinking
of the Armour of God.
Don't kick off
the ladder after going up.
- Why are you giving me this?
- To make coffee.
- A knife? I don't like violence.
- Take it to kill yourself.
Be careful, this path is dark.
Don't worry.
I'm used to it.
I grew up in the country.
Mud, stones and ponds...
Come on.
Help me, Jackie...
One word and I'll stab you to death.
Quiet!
Why is he here?
- Find the other one.
- Yes, sir.
Get him.
Come out.
I'm not fighting. Don't pull.
Stop pulling...
Well, you've provoked me.
Brother, my pants are coming down.
No more pranks.
- Take Laura.
- Keep them here.
- Go now.
- Need help?
No.
Keep it up...
Jackie, watch out!
- I really must go.
- Go then.
- Kuang Sheng!
- Come on!
Goodbye.
- After them!
- Yes, sir!
Come on.
Put out the fire.
Wait, we meet again.
Over there.
Give me that.
Fly...
Give them to me.
Get down!
There's a door behind you, go now.
Don't come back.
I won't.
When I count to 3, run.
Ready, 1, 2, 3.
Go now.
A man?
Come on.
Split up.
Jackie, we're really leaving this time.
Take care.
Over there, follow him.
Don't go.
There's something you don't know.
I'm no fool.
Who are you?
Get him!
- Go out and block all the exits!
- Yes, sir.
Are you Asian Hawk?
Yes.
This is Europe.
To a hawk's eyes,
there's no difference.
Stealing a piece
of the Armour of God?
Not a piece, the set.
I'll take it, if you don't object.
What gave you the nerve
to come and get killed here?
I always obey my God's order.
He provides board and lodging for me.
I never say no to him.
What's the name of your religion?
What's the name of your God?
I believe in a powerful religion.
The name of my God is Money.
Now sacrifice yourself for money.
You'll die for sure.
I'm being easy on them
because they are girls.
So a money-worshipper has heart.
These girls have no feelings.
They only know that
if someone is against us,
they will kill them.
Risking my life for myself is better
than you brainwashing the masses.
You cause so much fighting
and killing. What for?
You bring misfortune to the world.
I'll take these, if no one objects.
No one objects? If we each give you
a punch, you'll be finished.
You can't scare me.
- Tear him in two and offer him up.
- Yes.
He's bluffing.
Try me.
- Get him.
- Yes, sir.
I knew you were bluffing.
This time I'll give you a chance.
Next time I'll let it blow up.
At worst we'll perish together.
We're ready to sacrifice
for the true God. Right?
Yes.
Let me see how great you are.
Why make unnecessary sacrifices?
I'm only taking a few things.
Yellow smoke, over there.
- Fly over at once.
- Help me.
Fly closer.
Coming.
Jackie, how are you doing?
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine. Keep up the speed.
Watch out!