- Hi, Cary.
- Hello, Sara.
As usual, Cary,
you're way ahead of me.
I haven't even had time to think
of my trees, much less get them pruned.
Oh! I can't take
credit for that.
Martin always made the arrangements
with the nursery.
After his death, the service
just automatically continued.
Not that i haven't the time. With
the children away except for weekends,
- I've got nothing but time.
- Yes, i know.
That's enough about that.
Let's have our lunch. It's all ready.
- Darling, I can't have lunch.
- Oh?
I would have phoned, but i wanted
to bring back the dishes i borrowed.
Sometimes i think you're smart
not to be a club woman.
Sometimes i wonder,
but it's just not for me.
- I hope you didn't go to trouble.
- I didn't.
It's George. He just phoned.
He's bringing out a weekend guest.
Last-minute notice, as usual.
What with a hundred other things to do,
i've got to dig up a date tonight...
- For this Mr. Allenby.
- A date?
Look, he's 40, which means he'll
consider any female over 18 too old.
We might as well face it.
I've got to be off.
Oh, how about joining us tonight
at the club for dinner?
Well, no, Sara,
I don't think I'd better.
Don't be silly. I'll phone Harvey.
Pick you up around 7:30.
- Harvey?
- Oh, well, at least he's available.
- Bye, darling.
- Good-bye.
- Could i help you, Mrs. Scott?
- Well, yes, thank you.
- Just put it right there.
- All right.
- Would you like some hot coffee?
- Yeah, thanks.
Perhaps you'd like
to share my lunch with me.
My friend couldn't stay. I have plenty
of food. Chicken, salad and rolls.
- Just a roll and some coffee will do.
- All right.
- Won't you sit down?
- Mm-hmm.
I was just wondering
if there's much to be done.
- Everything looks so wonderful.
- Not much.
Do you think you'll finish today
or will you have to come back?
Well, probably will.
I often wish I knew more
about gardening.
Do you think
I ought to take it up?
Only if you think
you'd like it.
- I'm Mrs. Scott.
- Yes, I know.
- I'm Ron Kirby.
- Oh, you're Mr. Kirby's son.
Mm-hmm. I took over the nursery
three years ago when my father died.
Have you been coming here
ever since?
Mm-hmm. Every spring and every autumn.
This may be my last year.
At agricultural school, I got interested
in trees. So I started growing them.
- What kind of trees?
- All kinds.
White fir, Douglas fir,
silver tip spruce.
- Do I have any?
- [Chuckles] No.
But you have some
just as interesting.
Like this Koelreuteria.
In china where it comes from,
they call it the Golden Rain tree.
Beautiful, isn't it?
They say it can only thrive
near a home where there's love.
- It's a beautiful legend.
- Mm-hmm.
Well, I'd better
get back to work.
Thank you for the coffee.
- [Girl] Mother?
- [Boy] Hey, Mother!
Here I am!
Hello, darling!
- Hi!
- Ned
- Hi, mom.
I didn't expect you home
until tomorrow.
I didn't have a class today
so I phoned Kay from Princeton...
I was catching up on some case
histories... bane of the social worker...
- So I brought them along.
- When's dinner?
I've been invited out
for dinner.
- Where are you going?
- Sarah's giving a party at the club.
I'll have to get dressed. Harvey's
going to pick me up in a little while.
Harvey?
Oh, that's all right.
I'll go fix the cocktails.
- Harvey likes my martinis.
- Ned, the martini wizard.
- Have you been seeing much of Harvey?
- No, dear, he's been out of town.
- Florida, I think.
- I like Harvey.
He's pleasant, amusing,
and he acts his age.
If there's anything I can't stand,
it's an old goat.
As Freud says, when we reach
a certain age, sex becomes incongruous.
I think Harvey understands that.
- All in all, he's remarkably civilized.
- ????[Orchestra]
And the only bachelor
around here.
I'll admit,
he does have his drawbacks.
He talks too much
about his health,
but when you get to be his age,
it's understandable.
Of course, it's normal to
fall apart as one grows older.
But I can see
it might be hard to accept.
Although naturally it doesn't matter
as much with men as it does with women.
But, I guess Harvey's
intelligent enough anyway to...
Are you reading this?
- What, dear?
- [Wolf Whistle]
It's about time you wore something
besides that old black velvet.
- Is it?
- Of course.
Personally, I never subscribed
to that old Egyptian custom.
- At least I think it was Egypt.
- What egyptian custom?
Of walling up the widow alive in the
funeral chamber of her dead husband...
along with
his other possessions.
The theory being that
she was a possession too.
She was supposed to journey into death
with him. The community saw to it.
- Of course, that doesn't happen anymore.
- Doesn't it?
Well, perhaps not in Egypt.
- What do you mean?
- Oh, nothing. Let's go downstairs.
Holy cats, Mother.
I've had it for quite a while.
I just haven't worn it.
- Do you like it?
- I guess it's all right.
- But isn't it cut kind of low?
- [Doorbell Ringing]
Hope it doesn't
scare Harvey off.
- A typical Oedipus reaction.
- A what?
A son subconsciously resents his
mother being attractive to other men.
We call it an Oedipus complex.
- Happens all the time.
- Good evening, Harvey.
- Cary, my dear! Well!
- And Kay!
- Hi, Harvey.
- You'll have a cocktail before you go?
- We have time.
- He's mixed it especially for you.
- Thank you.
- We've missed you.
- I'm glad.
- Did you enjoy Florida?
- Perfect, Kay, perfect. Cary!
I discovered one of the most
wonderful doctors down there.
Cured one of my eternal colds,
like that!
- Mom, Harvey, the Scott special.
- Thank you, Ned.
- Thank you.
- Mmm!
Excellent, my boy! Excellent!
I'm not sure the gin is as good
as the brand i usually use,
but the vermouth is fair.
[Kay] You mean
those two little drops you put in?
Kay, I hope for the sake
of my liver you've miscounted.
Cary, you're looking
lovely tonight.
- That color becomes you.
Well, thank you, Harvey.
Ned was afraid the dress
might frighten you.
It would take more...
perhaps I should say, less to scare me.
No, thank you, Ned.
One cocktail is my limit.
You know,
my reform started...
the night your father
won this trophy.
He filled it with champagne
and made us drink it.
[Sighing]
I can still remember it.
- How many of you were there?
- Not enough.
- I think we better start, don't you?
- Yes, Harvey.
- Cary! Hi, Harvey.
- Hello, Bill.
- We never see you anymore.
- Cary, dear, it's been ages.
Ann and I were laughing
the other night about the time Martin...
Here you are. You can have her later.
Come on, darling.
[Man] Cary!
My favorite woman. What'll it be?
- We had a martini at the house...
- Never switch the pitch.
- Same for you?
- Nothing for me. I've had my quota.
You'll need more than one to see you
through this party, all my fault too.
- And i've got him for the whole weekend.
- George! Hush.
Tom, Cary. I want you to meet
Miss Frisbee, Mr. Allenby, Mrs. Scott.
- Mrs. Scott.
- How do you do?
Hello. I've been telling
your Mr. Allenby...
He's awfully hard to resist.
Seems to be mutual.
- Sara!
- Hello, Sara, Cary.
Did you see? The Nortons
are here together. After all the talk...
- What talk?
- You know what everyone said.
- No, but i'm sure you do.
- [Clearing Throat]
Cary, oh, darling! How wonderful
to see you. I hardly recognized her.
It's indecent to have two grown
children and look as young as you do.
There's nothing like red for
attracting attention, is there?
I suppose that's why so few widows wear
it. They'd have to be so careful.
- Hello, Howard.
- Hi!
- How about a dance?
- [Sara] Go ahead, Cary.
All right. I'd like to.
That was a horrid thing to say, Mona.
What do you mean?
I was only trying to cheer her up
by telling her how lovely she looked.
- But she didn't seem to need it.
- Shall we have a drink?
- How are mary and the children?
- Everybody's down with the flu.
- I'm sorry.
- House is like a hospital.
Now i'm glad i did.
[Chuckles]
You're beautiful, Cary.
Too beautiful to be lonely.
I can never decide whether Howard's
wife is a saint or just not very bright.
She stays at home alone
night after night.
- Yes, but she has the children.
- Even if she hasn't got Howard?
- What does that mean?
- Don't bristle. Did i mention cary?
I'm beginning to think
you have an evil mind.
Now, really.
- It's much nicer out here, isn't it?
- Yes.
That's where they're going
to build a new swimming pool.
- Oh?
That's a wonderful place for it.
When do you think they'll...
Why don't we meet in new york?
I know a place.
Howard, let's forget
you said that.
I'm sorry, Cary.
I don't know what got into me.
I know you're not like that.
I apologize for what I said.
That's all right, Howard.
- But I don't apologize for wanting you.
- [Sighs]
Why didn't Ned tell me
about you before?
Think of all the time
we've wasted.
You're off on a tangent.
Your values are confused.
I don't get it.
The basic values of the sex attraction
between man and woman are...
Oh, Mother and Harvey.
Well, i'll try to explain,
but not here.
Here you are.
- Would you like a nightcap?
- No, thank you, Cary.
It's way past my bedtime.
It's been a wild night for me.
I've enjoyed every minute of it.
I always enjoy being with you.
Thank you.
I feel the same.
- Have your key?
- Yes.
Now do you understand that much?
Frankly, no. But...
All right, I'll...
I'll try again.
Cary...
I don't know whether you're ready
to think about marrying again.
Well, no, l...
I don't think I'm ready.
Of course I realize I'm not
very romantic or impetuous...
But then, you'd hardly
want that sort of thing.
I'm sure you feel as I do.
That companionship and affection
are the important things.
I could give you those, Cary.
Well, I won't press you
for a decision now.
- Good night, dear.
- Good night, Harvey.
You really didn't want to be
a football captain. You wanted love.
- Yes.
- No, not the romantic nonsense.
I mean, basic love,
the desire to be liked.
Football was merely
a means to the end.
Of course,
you do have the build for it.
How can anyone so little
be so smart?
And yet so pretty?
- I'll see you Tuesday.
- Well, how long does this go on?
Oh, you mean the pruning.
He was supposed to come back
a couple of weeks ago and finish up.
- I almost gave him up for lost.
- The independent type, huh?
- Good-bye, darling.
- Good-bye, Sara.
Hello there.
Hello.
I thought you deserted us.
- I've had a busy week.
- Busy two weeks.
- Have you been buying more trees?
- How did you guess?
Well, l... I was just going to make
some fresh coffee.
- Would you like some?
- No, thank you. I'm all finished.
That means we're not going
to see you again until next spring.
I won't be coming back
next spring.
I'm giving up
my maintenance work.
Growing trees
is a full-time job.
At least the way
I want to do it.
Don't worry.
I'll find you someone.
Thank you.
Well, I guess this is good-bye.
I wish you luck with your trees.
- Remember the silver tip spruce?
- Yes?
I was wondering,
if you're not too busy,
you might like to come over
to my place and see them.
Well, I'm sorry,
but I'm afraid I can't today.
Oh, well, of course,
if you can't.
- Oh, Mr. Kirby.
- Yes, Mrs. Scott?
Well, I was just thinking
that maybe if...
You've changed your mind?
All right! Let's go!
It certainly is
out in the woods.
- Not what you expected?
- I thought you lived here.
I do.
I can see that a woman might not
like it, but it does very well for me.
If one likes to live
in a glass house.
At night when I'm in bed
I can see the stars in the sky.
- And you have your plants.
- Mm-hmm.
- What a lovely color.
- That's a coleus.
The one on the other side
is a dracaena.
Grows into sort of a tree.
- Oh, where are the trees?
- Right outside.
After you.
Of course, they're only
five year olds, but...
Five years to grow that?
Don't you ever get impatient?
If you're impatient,
you have no business growing trees.
Someday I'm gonna tear down the old mill
and put in more silver tip spruce there.
- What's in the old mill?
- Oh, nothing.
Could we go in?
I love to poke around old buildings.
[Door Creaking]
That's the old millstone.
Grandpa used to grind his flour here.
Watch the cobwebs.
That's the loft where
he used to store his grain.
Oh!
Oh, look.
Oh! Wedgwood.
If we could only find the pieces.
- What would you do with it?
- I'd steal it. I love wedgwood.
It was probably thrown there
because the pieces were missing.
Better leave it.
Seen enough?
No, I haven't even started.
I suppose these old beams
are rotted.
No, they're oak.
They're good for another hundred years.
And the stairs?
What's up there?
I don't know.
I haven't been there since I was a kid.
- It's pretty dirty... full of cobwebs.
- Oh, I don't mind.
Did the bird
frighten you, Mrs. Scott?
Well, it...
it would frighten anyone.
A fireplace.
Why, that makes it perfect.
Perfect? For what?
Why, a perfect place
for you to live.
It would take a lot of work,
but it'd be worth it.
- I've got a place to live.
- Oh.
You don't intend to live
in that room all your life.
- I hadn't thought about it.
- You'll have to one of these days.
- You'll meet a nice girl...
- I've met plenty of girls.
Nice and otherwise.
Well, not the right one.
And when you do...
Or do you think you're not susceptible?
No. I don't think that.
Well, it's getting
a little late.
I'm sorry. I wasn't
trying to arrange your life.
After all, it's
none of my business.
[Dove Cooing]
[Door Creaking, Closing]
I'm going upstate to buy some trees
for some friends of mine.
I'll be gone a couple of weeks.
I'll see you when I get back.
- No, l...
- I'll see you.
- Hello, Cary!
- Hello, Sara.
I dropped by to invite you for dinner
tonight. Mona and Mark are coming.
- Mona?
- I know, but I owe them a dinner.
Besides, Mona can be amusing
unless you happen to be her target.
I suppose I should say yes. I haven't
been out since harvey left town.
But mona...
I didn't mean that the way it sounded.
You can't sit around here
with nothing to do.
You should at least
get a television set.
- Oh, no!
- Why?
Because it's supposed
to be the last refuge for lonely women?
That's very sweet of you,
but I don't want a television.
All right, but I've already spoken
to the local television man about you.
- That charming Mr. Weeks.
- [Doorbell Ringing]
- You really should get one...
- Excuse me.
- Hello.
I was just going to drop in
on some friends of mine.
I thought you might like
to come along.
Well... won't you come in?
Thank you.
They'll probably ask us
to stay for dinner.
I have a guest right this minute.
Could you wait?
- Cary?
- Yes, Sara?
- Mrs. Warren, this is Mr...
- Kirby.
How do you do? I can't stay.
I'll see you tonight.
Would you be terribly disappointed
if I didn't come tonight?
Of course not! I understand if you're
not in the mood for Mona's gossip.
- We'll make it next week. Bye.
- Good-bye, Mrs. Warren.
You are coming.
Well... Yes.
It'll be cold by the time we get back.
Better take a warm coat.
Hey, Mick!
I'll be right back.
- Hi, Ron.
- Hi.
- Hi!
- [Ron] Hi!
- I'd like you to meet Mick and Alida.
- How do you do?
- Hello.
- Hello, Cary.
What a nice surprise.
Come on upstairs.
- You're just in time for the clambake.
- Good!
- Come on in.
- Thank you.
- It's a little chilly in here.
- I'll have a fire in a moment.
I'll take your coat.
- Say, Ron, why don't you start it?
- Okay.
I'll make an anderson special, a talent
I developed on the ulcer circuit.
Freely translated,
the advertising business.
You wouldn't believe it,
but he was once a v.i.p. In New York.
No, you're the one that taught him
to be a very independent person.
The only thing he ever taught me was
how to open a wine bottle with my teeth.
To hear them tell it,
you'd think they spent the war...
crawling from
wine cellar to wine cellar.
- [Ron] We did!
- Make cary comfortable, will you, Ron?
All right.
Sit down, Cary.
- What did you say about me outside?
- When?
When he looked at me
and laughed.
I told him you had the prettiest legs
I'd ever seen.
- Here is the Anderson special.
- Oh, it's heavy!
Put the cauldron on the fire,
will you, old man?
- You're in for a shore dinner.
- Hope you like it.
- I do.
- Good!
- Here you are, Cary. Alida.
- Thank you.
Here's to those who wish us well, and
those that don't can go to hackensack.
Salud.
- How do you like it?
- Marvelous. What's in them?
First you get some ice, two jiggers
of clements, a little twist of...
Mick, stop it!
- You can help me bring up some wine.
- We'll be right back.
- How many are coming tonight?
- You never can tell.
That's so true.
You never know with that boy.
Which means I better get busy.
- Can I help you?
- Oh, no, make yourself comfortable.
''The mass of men lead lives
of quiet desperation.
''Why should we be in such
desperate haste to succeed?
''Lf a man does not keep pace
with his companions,
''perhaps it is because
he hears a different drummer.
'' Let him step to the music
which he hears, however measured...
or far away.''
- Why, that's beautiful.
- That's mick's bible.
He quotes from it
constantly.
- Please let me help.
- All right. Come on.
Kind of heavy.
- Is it Ron's bible too?
- Hmm?
I don't think Ron's ever read it.
He just lives it.
- Put it in the middle.
- All right.
Thank you.
- Alida?
- Hmm?
What did you mean when
you said that ron taught Mick?
Well, it's kind of
hard to explain.
I guess all of us
are looking for security these days.
You see, Mick thought...
Well, like a lot of other people...
that if he had money and an important
position it would make him secure.
Then when he met Ron who didn't have
either one and didn't seem to need them,
He was completely baffled.
The answer was so simple it took
Mick a long time to figure it out.
What was the answer?
To thine own self be true.
That's Ron.
You see, Ron's security
comes from inside himself.
Nothing can ever
take it away.
Ron absolutely refuses to let
unimportant things become important.
That's what Mick
and I were doing. We were.
In fact, things got so bad
between us that...
right before he went to Korea
we were thinking of a separation.
Oh, no.
You seem so happy.
Not then.
We weren't happy then.
Our whole life was devoted
to keeping up with theJoneses.
But when Mick was wounded
and had a lot of time to think,
He decided to get off
that merry-go-round.
When he came back,
he put it right up to me.
- [Woman] Alida!
- Yeah?
My room's a mess,
but don't bother. I'm off!
- Wait!
- I can't, I'm late. See you tomorrow.
- Mary Ann! What time?
- I don't know. In the afternoon.
- [Mary Ann] Ron!
- [Ron Chuckling] Mary Ann!
- I didn't know you were coming.
- Why, sure.
- [Mary Ann] Now I'm disappointed.
- Why?
I thought it was just another
of Mick and Alida's get-togethers.
- If i'd known... I want a rain check.
- Name it.
- To go swimming with you again.
- It's too cold.
- How about sailing then?
- Fine.
- Before it gets too cold for that too.
- I have a windbreaker.
- What about me?
- You'll be warm enough.
You never take me seriously.
[Alida]
Drive carefully, Mary Ann!
My young cousin.
She's spending the winter with us.
She thought our party sounded dull, so
she arranged to stay with a girlfriend.
- Think this will be enough?
- Yes.
Mick, would you give me a hand,
darling?
What have you been doing? I thought
you'd have the heavy work done.
- Put the bottles down.
- Think 16 will be enough?
- With this crowd? Thanks.
- You betcha.
Oh, no, thanks, honey, but there's some
tablecloths in the right-hand drawer.
- Lobsters have arrived!
- Look, I got 'em!
Hey, Manuel! Thank you!
I caught myself
this morning!
- This is Manuel, the lobster king.
- Hello!
My pleasure.
She's beautiful! My wife Rozanne.
! Que bonita!
! Tanto gusto!
- Mi hija, Marguerita.
- How do you do?
Marguerita is a very good cook.
She makes this corn bread...
Hey, hey, hey!
Get your paws off!
- [Rozanne] Alida!
- It's so good seeing you.
You will love the lobsters.
Mick, let me help you.
Well, Grandpa! How are ya?
Let me take your coat.
Cary, this is Grandpa Adams.
He's a beekeeper and artist.
- You must see his one-man show.
- Why, I hope to.
Of course, Miss Cary, I'm not
an abstractionist. Strictly primitive.
- You know everybody here.
- [Alida] Come on in, Grandpa!
Edna, what a beautiful cake!
Meet Miss Pidway, head of the Audubon
Society and an outstanding bird-watcher.
- How do you do?
- Glass of wine, Manuel?
- Two glasses of wine for Manuel!
- A dollar says you can't.
- Why, put it on your bill.
I've never seen this
done before.
- I wouldn't try that with my new teeth!
- Oh, no.
? My, my, my
I have rovey eye ?
? How he fly
all around the town ?
? Eye, eye, eye
every passerby ?
? He look-a her up
he look-a her down
ooh-hoo ?
?? Ooh-hoo ??
- ??Lady, what a pleasant view ??
- Thank you.
? I make the flirty eye
at you ?
??My, my, my, no more rovey eye
No more fly ??
? All around the town ?
? Not since I find
a passerby ?
? She look-a me up
Me look-a her down ?
? She and me we go to town ?
Hey, Mick, take over.
- Hey! [Muttering]
- [Laughing]
- Faster, mick!
Hey, everybody!
The lobsters!
[Alida]
Get 'em out of the way. There!
- Mrs. Scott?
- Yes?
I'm Mr. Week. Mrs. Warren told me
you might be interested in television.
Most of my ladies tell me
tv gives them something to do.
Mrs. Warren has made a mistake.
I'm not interested in television.
I'm in a terrible hurry.
Will you excuse me?
May I call again, Mrs. Scott...
When you called me
to hurry, I hurried.
Did you have anything better to do
of a Saturday afternoon?
No, as a matter of fact, the children
aren't coming up this weekend.
After you.
Oooh!
What you've done to it!
And the fireplace!
Oh, it's so friendly.
And you put in
this big window.
What a beautiful view
of the pond.
- Why, you can see for miles!
- Mm-hmm.
- The sun comes up right over that hill.
- Oh!
- Do you like it?
- Why, it's unbelievable.
Let's take your boots off, huh?
Of course, there's a lot of work to
be done yet, but it'll be worth it.
- Your feet are cold.
- I know. They're frozen.
- The teapot. You found all the pieces.
- Mm-hmm.
It took days and days.
[Chuckles]
These stairs are
moving to the loft.
I'll add the bedroom up there.
The old millstone
I'm trying to make into a table.
You know why i've started
to fix the place?
I didn't want to say anything until
I knew I could make it livable...
for us.
Do you understand
What I'm saying, Cary?
Yes.
I'm asking you to marry me.
I love you, Cary.
L... I just hadn't
thought about marriage.
Why do you think
i've been seeing you?
I didn't think.
- Can't you see it's impossible?
- No.
This is the only thing
that matters.
No. There are
other things that matter.
The children... How could I ask them
to give up their home?
Home is where you are, Cary.
But the kind of life you lead,
l... I don't know that life.
How could I make sure
it would work out?
You can't, Cary.
You can't!
Don't you see I'd be turning my back
on everything I've ever known?
- Isn't it enough we love each other?
- No, cary.
It isn't.
It isn't enough for either of us.
You're running away from something
important because you're afraid.
- Afraid?
- Mm-hmm.
- Of what?
- Many things.
Perhaps you're right.
It's absurd
to think of marriage.
- It's out of the question.
- Cary!
The hours
you've spent mending it.
Doesn't matter.
Cary.
Don't forget your boots.
I'll help you.
You mustn't catch cold.
Darling, don't cry.
Oh, Ron,
I love you so much.
What are you
thinking about?
That I love you.
It won't be easy.
There will be
a lot of things that...
You'll have to help me.
I'll help all I can.
- It's getting late.
- Mm-hmm.
Does it matter?
I'll take you home.
[Man] I sent the boy up
with the roast twice on saturday.
I kept phoning
up till 9:00 in the evening.
I'm sorry,
but I completely forget.
- Hello, Mrs. Plash.
- Hello. I was just thinking about you.
- Pleasantly, I hope.
- Of course.
I was telling Mrs. Scott
I couldn't figure out where she was.
- I even phoned the club.
- Oh?
The children weren't coming up so
I decided to go away for the weekend.
- I'll take my roast now.
- Glad you had a chance to get away.
- Where did you go, darling?
- Upstate.
Good-bye.
Good-bye, Mona.
It's comforting to know
she's not lonely, Mr. Gow.
Mona Plash is such a gossip.
It'll be all over town
by tomorrow, I'm afraid.
I hate to have the children learn
about us before I tell them.
Then you'd better tell them.
It should be so simple.
Two people who are in love
with each other, want to be married.
Why is it so difficult
all of a sudden?
It isn't,
if you're not afraid.
That's what Mick
learned from you, isn't it?
No. You can't learn that
from anybody.
Mick discovered for himself that
he had to make his own decisions,
that he had to be a man.
And you want me to be a man.
Only in that one way.
Mona certainly didn't
waste any time, did she?
I suppose the whole town's
talking about it.
Well, she phoned me.
That's why I rushed over.
Of course,
I didn't believe a word.
You should.
You can't be serious.
Your gardener?
He isn't my gardener.
He did work on the trees.
You met him.
And even if he was,
I'm in love with him.
And I'm going to marry him.
Well, all right,
maybe I'm a snob.
But it isn't just a question
of whether he's a gardener.
The talk won't stop at that.
They'll say he's
younger than you are.
- And the fact that you're a widow.
- What does that got to do with it?
- With money.
- Ron isn't interested in my money.
And that he worked at your place
while Martin was still alive.
People will say that all this started
before your husband died.
- But that's not true. You...
- I don't!
But Mona? Ha!
Mona will have a field day.
Before she gets through,
the whole town will believe it.
You know, Cary, as well as I do
that situations like this...
bring out the hateful side
of human nature.
Remember you have
Ned and Kay to think about.
At their age,
what people say matters terribly.
Have you stopped to think
what all these rumors will do to them?
You're asking me to give up Ron because
of something in people that's mean?
- I didn't say that.
- Do you think it would be good...
if I were to let myself be
beaten by such hatefulness?
Well, I'm not gonna do it.
Let them say what they want to.
And that goes for you too, Sara.
I must say, Cary,
you've got stubbornness.
And courage.
If you want to throw me out,
I won't blame you.
I apologize.
At least I can do that much.
You don't have
to apologize, Sara, just...
just go on being my friend.
I'd be a fool not to do that.
I've got to give a cocktail party
this weekend for that moron Jo-Ann.
She bagged Tom Allenby.
You bring Ron.
Maybe if people see him,
maybe if they get to know him,
they'll accept him.
Well, I'll call him.
Good evening, Mrs. Plash.
- Hello, ned. You home for the weekend?
- Yes, I am.
Just wait until you see your mother.
She's never looked so radiant.
- I wish I knew her secret.
- Thank you, Mrs. Plash.
- Lf you'll excuse me, I've got to hurry.
- Mm-hmm.
Yoo-hoo, Mildred!
How was New York?
Mother?
I'm home!
Where are ya?
I'm in the basement, dear.
I'll be up in a minute.
- Ned?
- Yeah.
- How are you, dear?
- What were you doing in the cellar?
I was putting some things
away in the storage closet.
Everything was getting
so cluttered.
Where's Kay? She and Freddie
were supposed to drive up together.
She's upstairs.
We've been waiting for you.
Why all the mystery when
you phoned? Who's coming?
Oh, mother, I hope you don't mind
my borrowing your manicure set.
Which is better?
Crimson snow or traffic light?
[Ned] Oh, dig you. Since
when have you joined the female ranks?
- All right!
- Now, Kay, Ned.
I want to discuss something with you
that concerns you as much as me.
You're going to get married.
Why, yes.
How did you know?
Oh, it had to happen.
Anyone as attractive as you.
Besides, you know what I think
of widows being walled up alive.
Egyptian fashion.
I knew you felt that way in theory.
Theory and action should be one.
Don't worry, Mother.
We're all for it.
Oh, darlings.
Hey, save that for Harvey.
Harvey?
Well, it isn't Harvey.
It... It's Ron Kirby.
You know him.
At least you've met him.
The only Kirby I know
is old Kirby the gardener.
- Last I heard, he was dead.
- Ron is his son.
Mother, is this a joke or something?
- No, it isn't a joke, Ned.
- But, Mother, you can't...
There's no point in approaching this
emotionally. Let's try to be objective.
This isn't one of your
case histories. This is us!
Just the same. Now, Mother, have you
introduced him to any of your friends?
[Ned]
Yeah, what does Sara think?
Well, Sara's invited us
to a cocktail party tonight.
I wanted you to know him first,
so I asked Ron to come early...
for a drink,
one of your special martinis.
This is no time for martinis.
Mother, why did you keep
this whole affair such a secret?
Because subconsciously
you were afraid he wouldn't fit in?
Why, Ron has no intentions
of fitting in, Kay.
He's quite content
with his life the way it is.
- Mother, the whole thing is impossible.
- You don't know him.
- We know the type.
- And we know you, Mother.
- [Doorbell Ringing]
- Suppose that's him now.
You must realize how
important this is to me.
I'm relying on both of you
to be fair and... give Ron a chance.
All right.
I'll make the martinis.
Won't you come in, Ron?
- You know Ned and Kay?
- Yes, of course. Hello.
- It's nice to see you again.
- Thank you.
Shall we go into the living room?
Kay, as I told you, Ron,
is doing social work in New York.
- You like it, I understand.
- You learn to deal with all sorts.
- NNed, you make a very good martini.
- Not too strong for you?
- You still have the nursery, Mr. Kirby?
- Oh, yes.
He's going in more
for tree farming now.
- Is there any money in growing trees?
- There can be.
The only thing I know about trees
is they make good logs.
- Now's your chance to learn.
- Mother?
- What happened to dad's trophy?
- Why, nothing happened to it.
Is the trophy part of the clutter
you were putting away?
Ned.
I suppose from now on,
there'll be lots of changes around here.
Ned, if you mean because of my marriage
to your mother, you needn't worry.
I have no intention of living here.
We'll be leading quite a different life.
But this has been the family house
for I don't know how long.
This is the place
we were born!
Ned, I wish you'd treat this matter
in a more detached fashion.
You don't know Mother as we know her.
She's really much more conventional...
than you seem to think she is.
She has the innate desire for group
approval, which most women have.
Never mind the $10 words.
And where, if I may ask,
do you expect our mother...
and, I suppose, us too to live?
- My place.
- In a greenhouse?
Oh, no, no.
He's going to remodel the old mill.
Mother, if you'll excuse me, I'm going
to a lecture. I'd better get ready.
Good-bye, Mr. Kirby.
Mother, I've got some
studying to catch up on.
What happened? I've never
seen them act like that before.
It's natural, Cary.
I'm not like their father.
What does that
got to do with it?
It would be different if you were
marrying the same kind of man.
Successful businessman,
pillar of the community.
I can understand it.
Perhaps you're right.
But once I make them see that...
Shall we get started?
Cary, do we really have to go?
Well, Sara said that...
And anyway, I want to show you off.
- We can take my car.
- Mine's right here.
- Does it matter that much?
- It shouldn't.
Jim, get me another one, will you?
I don't want to miss the arrival.
- How about you, Mrs. Taylor?
- Well, I really shouldn't, but...
Excuse me.
If you see cary before I do,
let me know.
It'll be easier for her
if I took them around.
- Count on it, Sara. Got a light?
- I may need to.
Hold my drink, dear.
A gardener?
Why doesn't he find himself
a decent money-making vocation?
You think material success is the only
end worthy of pursuit of man?
- What's wrong with money?
- You have to have it to have contempt.
Excuse me.
Thank you. Do you really think
she'll have the nerve to come?
- Oh, there they are now!
- They're here!
- Just look at that car.
- Just look at that man.
Daughter!
It's always the quiet ones,
isn't it?
But she's certainly the last person
you'd expect to...
Always pretending
to be so prim and proper.
Why, Howard,
did she turn you down?
I'm so glad you could come.
I'm Cary's best friend.
- I'd like to be your friend too.
- Thank you.
Come on, darling. George.
- Cary, my favorite woman.
- George, I want you to know Ron Kirby.
- Used to know your father. Fine man.
- Thank you.
Shall we say hello to Romeo
and his Juliet? Come on, darling.
So that's Cary's nature boy.
- You know the doctor, Dan.
- Hello, Cary.
You know Miss Frisbee,
Mr. Allenby. Mr. Kirby.
- How do you do?
This was kind of
supposed to be my party,
but looks like Mrs. Scott's
getting the attention.
I guess it is more unusual
when someone your age gets married.
But I think your friend's
awfully lucky.
You see, no one in my family's
had a dime since the civil war.
So, Tom won't get anything
but poor little me.
- Don't bother, Cary...
- My dear. What's this i hear about...
Oh. Haven't I seen you
somewhere before?
Well, Mrs. Humphrey,
probably in your garden.
I've been pruning your trees
for the last three years.
Oh, yes, of course.
- Ah, sara, I really must be going.
- I'll be right back.
Come into the bar. You've earned
yourself a good strong drink.
- Go ahead, Ron.
- I'll be right back.
All right.
- Howard.
- Hi.
How are you?
- Mona, Mark.
- Oh, my dear, he's fascinating.
And that tan!
I suppose from working outdoors.
Of course, i'm sure
he's handy indoors too.
Mona's sure got your number, Cary.
So have I.
Well, excuse me, Howard.
Guess you played me for a prize sucker
that night at the club, huh?
Goin' into that perfect lady routine.
Makin' me apologize.
If I'd known then
what I know now,
- would have had a different ending.
- Oh, Howard.
Never too late, huh, Cary?
Line forms to the right.
- Howard, you're drunk!
- Why, Cary!
Isn't one man
enough for you?
Maybe you'd better stay
right where you are.
[Sara]
What is it, Cary?
- I never would have believed it.
[Sara] Believed what?
[Mona] That Howard was the earthy
type. You seem to attract that, Cary.
- Shall we go?
- Yes.
- Excuse us.
- Oh, george!
Why, that man was
positively murderous.
- Did you see that, Fred?
- What's the commotion?
He might have
killed poor Howard.
- And in Sara's lovely house too!
- Well!
Nothing's important except us.
Will you remember that?
Yes.
- I'll take you to the door.
- No, Ron.
Thank you, but... good night.
Good night.
Ned, you're still up?
Don't forget to put the screen around
the fireplace before you come up.
Mom...
I've got a few things
to say to you, Mother.
All right, Ned.
I just want to tell you, meeting him
hasn't changed my mind one darn bit.
We did what you asked.
I asked you to give Ron a fair chance.
I don't think you did.
Just because we didn't agree
with your choice?
Listen, Mother, somebody in this
family's gotta think straight.
And you don't think I can?
I think all you see is
a good-looking set of muscles.
Why, Ned!
That's the way it looks,
doesn't it?
You're planning to give up a home that's
been in the family for I don't know...
There's a certain tradition.
Aand for what?
Don't you realize
what people are gonna say?
Haven't you any sense
of obligation to father's memory?
What does that
got to do with it?
How can you think of marrying Kirby
when you've been Father's wife?
- It's against everything.
- Nonsense, Ned.
Mother... are you really
intending to go through with this?
Yes, I am.
Well, don't expect me
to come visit ya.
How could I bring my friends?
I'd be ashamed.
Ned!
Ned, we mustn't let this
come between us.
If you mean Kirby,
he already has!
[Door Slamming]
And then Ned
on top of everything else.
No, I haven't heard a word.
I've got a call in for him.
Well, Kay stayed over.
- I didn't sleep a wink either.
- [Door Closing]
Do you really think
the talk will die down?
Kay?
Sara, I'll have to call you back later.
All right.
- Kay, darling, what is it?
What's the matter?
Well, tell me.
Nothing. It...
It's about me, isn't it?
Freddie and I
were at the library.
One of the kids
made a crack about you.
What did they say?
That you and Mr. Kirby were...
even before Daddy...
Now, you stop that, Kay.
You know that's a lie.
Of course I do,
and I told them so!
They went on and on
and I got mad and...
We were asked to leave.
Oh, darling.
And on the way home
Freddie and I had a fight.
I told him that i didn't care
what people said.
But, Mama, I do care!
I care terribly!
Oh, Kay, l... I don't know what to do.
I can't bear to see
you and ned so unhappy.
But, you see, Kay, I love Ron.
You love him so much
you're willing to ruin all our lives?
- You can't really think that.
- What else can I think?
But, Kay, you've talked
so much about people...
and why they do
the things they do.
- You say you understand.
- But I don't!
I don't! I thought I did.
I don't understand anything.
Cary?
- Oh, Ron, l...
- What's the matter?
Well, Ned's left home and l...
I left Kay in tears. Some of her
friends have been dreadful to her.
Because of me?
Ron, we're gonna have
to wait to get married.
- Why?
- Well...
To give the children
a chance to get used to the idea.
They'll feel differently
when they know you better.
- You don't want to marry me?
- I'm not saying that.
I'm asking you to be patient.
It's only a question of time.
Only of time?
Right now everybody's talking about us.
We're a local sensation.
Like Sara said, if the people get used
to seeing us together,
then maybe
they'll accept us.
You mean, we'll be invited
to all the cocktail parties.
And, of course, Sara will see to it
I get into the country club.
Dear Howard and I will
shake hands and forget.
- And Mona won't be malicious.
- That isn't what I mean.
And ned and kay
won't mind so much...
because we'll be living
just as you always have.
- Probably in your house.
- What's wrong with that?
It's only for a little while.
It would make things so much easier.
It wouldn't change you.
You couldn't be changed.
Yes, I could.
I'm learning right now how easy
it would be to let myself be changed.
- By whom?
- By you.
I'm sorry, Cary.
But it wouldn't work.
I can't live that way.
You knew that from the beginning.
But I can't ruin
my children's lives.
I have a responsibility to them.
Are you sure it's just that?
Well, what do you mean?
- You don't think I care what people say.
- Yes, I do.
You're not even trying
to understand.
- How can you say you love me...
- God knows I love you.
But I won't let Ned nor Kay
nor anyone else run our lives.
Don't you see we could never
be happy if we did?
I can see that you don't want to listen
to anybody's ideas but your own.
I can see that you're trying to make
me choose between you and the children!
No, Cary, you're the one
that made it a question of choosing.
So you're the one
that'll have to choose.
All right.
It's all over.
Cary?
I admit, after meeting him,
he's a darn nice guy, but l...
But I still say
you did the right thing.
Oh... I suppose so.
Everyone will welcome you back
to the fold. I'll see to that.
I don't know what i'd do
without you, Sara.
I know what you've been
going through.
I know it hasn't been easy.
But at least you have the children.
You don't have to fiill your life
with club work and parties.
- Oh, Sara.
That must be Ned.
I have a call in for him.
- You've told Kay?
- Yes, she's very happy.
- Hello?
- Mrs. Scott?
- Yes.
- I have your party now.
- [Ned] Mother, you called me?
- Yes, Ned, I did.
I wanted to talk to you.
I, um... I've decided that...
Well, I'm not going
to be married.
- Oh, great.
- You will be up this weekend?
You bet, Mom.
I got a class now, so good-bye, huh?
- Well, Ned... Ned?
Was he pleased?
Yes, he...
He seemed to be.
- Hello, dear!
- Bill! I thought you'd never get here.
- What's for dinner?
- Good night. Say hello to the children.
- Hello, Cary. Nice to see you.
- Hello, Doctor. Nice to see you.
I've been meaning to call you
about a checkup.
I don't think it's serious, but
I've been having miserable headaches.
- Any time. Can I give you a lift?
- I'm waiting for the children.
- Let me hear from you now.
- All right.
Oh, Mrs. Scott.
Seems the kids couldn't make it.
Guess they're pretty busy
with the holidays coming on.
Something in a christmas tree,
ma'am? Oh, hiya, Mrs. Scott.
- Merry christmas!
- Merry christmas, Tom.
- Like this one?
- I need one bigger than this.
- How about this?
- That's not very pretty.
I'll show ya another one.
Hello, Cary.
Well, hello.
I, uh... I have to get a tree
for the children, and I saw these.
How are you?
- How about this pine, Mrs. Scott?
- Oh, I'm fine.
No, not that one. L...
I didn't know
they were your trees.
No, they're Mick's.
I'm helping him unload.
- How are Mick and Alida?
- Fine.
Will you say hello
to them for me?
They'll be right back.
They're doing some christmas shopping.
Here's a medium-sized fir,
Mrs. Scott.
Or maybe you'd rather have a spruce?
- A silver tip spruce?
- Oh, i've got a beauty!
You remembered.
Oh, Cary...
Ron! Ron?
Mick and Alida sent me
to get you.
Oh, I didn't know
you had a customer.
How about this one,
Mrs. Scott?
No. Send this one to me.
Ron? Shall we go?
Yeah.
??Let heaven and nature sing ??
??Let heaven and heaven ??
? And nature sing ?
- ?Joy to the world ?
? The Lord is come ?
? Let earth receive her king ?
??Let every heart
prepare Him room ??
? And heaven
and nature sing ?
??And heaven
and nature sing ??
and heaven ??
??And nature sing ??
??Joy to the world
the Lord is come ??
??Let earth
receive her king ????
- Hello, Mama! Merry Christmas!
- Merry Christmas!
- Thought we'd never get here.
- I'm so happy to see you.
- Oh, it looks gorgeous!
- Hey, look at all that loot!
- Is that for me?
- Where's our present for you?
Nothing's come.
But don't worry about it.
- Just having the two of you is enough.
- I better phone.
- Not here. It's a secret!
- Don't open anything until I get back.
- All right.
Mama!
Look!
Why, that's lovely, Kay.
Freddie and I
are going to be married.
In february,
after he graduates.
Well, aren't you a little young?
You were 17 when you got married.
But... it's so soon.
Soon?
Oh, it seems like forever.
Oh, Mama!
Remember the afternoon
that Freddie and I had the big fight?
That's when we found out we loved
each other. Mama, he's so wonderful.
Yes, I remember.
That was the day you told me your life
would be ruined if I married Ron.
I was being childish. You shouldn't
have let me get away with it.
Of course, that was different.
You didn't really love him,
did you?
Mother!
Your present's on the way.
Hey, this is Christmas.
Let's enjoy it.
After all, it'll probably
be the last one we spend in this house.
What do you mean?
Kay's getting married.
And if I'm not called up right away,
I'm in line for the Walker Scholarship
which means a year in Paris.
After that, onto Iran
with the Dayton Company.
I didn't want to tell you till
I had it pretty well cinched.
Hey, Mother.
Thank you.
Yes, with Kay and I away,
I think we should sell the house.
The house?
It's too big for one person.
What with taxes...
There's your present now.
- [Door Opening]
- Mama?
- Mama!
Don't you see, Kay?
The whole thing's been so pointless.
Oh, mama, I'm...
I'm terribly sorry.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
Mama, it still isn't too late,
if he loves you.
- Please, Kay, it...
- Mother?
Merry Christmas!
Merry Christmas, Mrs. Scott,
and Happy New Year.
Kay and I couldn't afford
anything but a table model.
It's got a nice-sized screen
and it's easy to operate.
All you have to do is turn that dial and
you have all the company you want...
right there on the screen.
Drama, comedy, life's parade
at your fiingertips.
Fetch, go on!
Fetch, old boy!
Ha, ha!
Boy, are you slippin'.
Why don't you try
using shells in that gun?
- Doesn't seem to help.
- Ha, ha!
Can't shoot straight anymore,
I guess.
I don't seem to be good
for anything lately.
You haven't been good for anything
since you and Cary broke up.
- What's that got to do with it?
- Everything, and you know it.
You're not the same anymore.
You're no good to me,
yourself or anyone.
All right,
so what do I do about it?
- Call her up. Go see her. Apologize.
- Apologize for what?
I don't know for what.
For anything. Make up something.
- But do something.
That's a boy. Good boy.
Hey, nice, huh?
Look, Mick,
I told her that I love her.
I asked her to marry me. I can't force
her. She has to make up her own mind.
She doesn't want to make up her
own mind. No girl does.
She wants you
to make it up for her.
- Come on, let's go.
- No, I'll be along later.
Gotta catch one pheasant
at least.
Hey, uh...
Well, uh... You know.
Well, Dan,
what's the verdict?
I was just going over
the findings.
There's nothing organically
wrong with you, Cary.
Why do I have
these headaches?
It's not my imagination.
And they're getting worse all the time.
- You're punishing yourself.
- For what?
For running away from life. Headaches
are nature's way of making a protest.
Will you give me
something for them?
Do you expect me to give you
a prescription to cure life?
Sit down.
I want to talk to you.
Forget for a moment
that I'm your doctor.
Let me give you some advice
as a friend. Marry him.
Well, there's no point
in discussing that.
- It's all over.
- Apparently it isn't.
- You still have the headaches.
- But that's silly.
And anyway,
how could I marry him?
The whole thing was impossible
from the beginning.
You know, Dan, in a place like
Stoningham, you can't ignore convention.
So you gave up a man you were
in love with because of others?
And you had the great satisfaction
of being taken back into the fold.
I was thinking of my children.
You're just as lonely as you
were before. Lonelier, in fact,
with kay married
and ned abroad.
Sso what good
was your noble sacrifice?
Cary, marry him.
Oh, it... it's too late.
And maybe he's
found someone else.
Anyway, if he'd really loved me,
he would have come to me.
No! If you'd loved him,
you'd have gone to him!
In spite of the town,
the children, everything.
Let's face it. You were ready
for a love affair, but not for love.
Good-bye, Dan.
- Cary!
- Hello, Alida!
- It's so good to see you!
What were you doing in the doctor's
office? Nothing wrong, is there?
Oh, no. Just a checkup.
He couldn't find a thing wrong with me.
- Would you have a cup of tea?
- I'd love to, but I'm late.
- I have to pick up Mary Ann.
- Mary ann?
- She's getting married, you know.
- Married?
Very nice boy from new jersey. They've
been going together for a year now.
- I thought...
- I don't think you've met this one.
I have to dash. Come by and see us,
We miss you!
- I appreciate that. Good-bye, Alida.
- Bye!
Cary!
- Alida?
- Hello, Cary.
- Come on in.
- I thought i should come over.
- There's been an accident, Cary.
- It's ron.
- You better come with me.
- How bad is he?
Don't know yet.
Dr. Hennessy and Mick are with him now.
- Oh, alida.
- Get your coat first.
- I'll tell you on the way.
- [Footsteps Running]
Mrs. Scott.
Please, Mrs. Scott.
- How is he?
- We don't know anything yet.
- Where's Mr. Anderson?
- He took the doctor back to town.
- Well, didn't he...
- Nothing that he could have done.
He'll be back
in the morning.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Scott.
I have strict orders.
He can't be disturbed.
He must be kept quiet.
Let me take your coat.
Why don't you sit down?
I'll get some coffee.
Wish Mick had waited.
But I'm sure the doctor wouldn't have
gone if he thought there were...
Alida.
This room.
The beauty that
Ron's put into it.
And the love.
He never gave up hope
that you'd come back, Cary.
You told me once that
Ron was so secure within himself.
Because he refused to give importance
to unimportant things.
Why did it take me so long
to understand it?
Remember I told you it took us
a long time to find the right answer?
It doesn't happen overnight.
I feel like such a coward.
I was so frightened.
I let others make my decisions.
Alida, I've let so many people
come between us.
Friends, neighbors, children.
And the strangest one of all, myself.
Don't worry about things
in the past.
Isn't that
unimportant too, hmm?
If only I haven't
waited too long.
Mrs. Scott?
Your coffee.
Thank you, but I really
don't care for any.
Why don't you go upstairs
and rest a while? Try to sleep.
I couldn't sleep.
I want to stay here in case he wakes up.
May I sit over there?
Well, all right.
- Well, Dan?
- He's got a concussion.
- Of course not.
- Otherwise, I'd get him to the hospital.
It's gonna take time
for him to recover.
Dan, what can I do?
You plan to stay?
Yes. No more running away.
He'll need rest and care.
And he'll need you, CCary.
Nurse.
Cary.
Yes, Ron.
You've come home.
Yes, darling, I've...
I've come home.