Why is that bitch so mean
to me?
Why'd she go through
my clothes?
I won't let her
get away with this
Missing Child
Snowman-shaped birthmark on the back
No way
Then again, why not?
Yeah, why not?
This could be her
Until when
are we doing this?
You think
I'm enjoying this?
Shut up and
keep your eyes peeled
Check out her legs
They're awesome
Mine are prettier
By the way
why'd you
hit me that hard?
Where'd he get these snacks?
I bet he can make noodles
out of newspaper
His pockets are like
trash cans
Look me in the eyes
when I talk to you, punk
- Look at me
- Look! That's him, isn't it?
- Him! Him, over there!
- What?
Him!
- Hide!
- Heads down!
Bitch!
What's up with those jackasses?
How fast can you run
100 meters?
- 10 seconds
- Is he superman?
You've got some nerve,
showing up here!
I'm on the run from them
Who?
Why'd you come here?
Don't worry, I've lost them
You sure?
Did you call the cops?
What's the point?
They do nothing but
tell you to wait
Why didn't you run
to your place?
- I needed to see you
- What for?
Mi-young, I don't want
you to get me wrong
- for asking this
- Get to the point
Let me hear what it is first
You're an orphan,
aren't you?
- Out
- Huh?
Get the hell out!
If not, fine
I knew you weren't
Get out!
- When we were drinking
- You're insane!
You said your mom
might be a step mother
Whatever Get out!
Wait, look at this
This is from that old man
Oh, Mi-young!
Let me tell you
I was on fire, girl!
I wish it were like this
everyday
What's wrong?
- Hey!
- Nothing
Something's bugging you
What is it?
- It's nothing
- You!
You lost all my cyber money,
didn't you?
You're so dead!
Okay, spill the beans
What is it?
Mom, I want you to
tell me honestly
What?
Am I your real daughter?
Am I?
Dad and you are my
Wait, wait a second
I have to go back out
I think that bitch
cheated me
She didn't give me
all she owed me
She always does that!
I should kill her!
He must've gone drinking
Thank God
I can't believe
we lost him again
That short-legged ass was fast
Keep your mouths shut
about this
Look who's talking
If he finds out, we're through
I'm hungry
Order some Chinese food
- Spicy noodles for me
- I want the plain ones
And fried dumplings
They're hard to chew
Get steamed ones instead
Sweet and sour pork
for me
Hey!
Wake the hell up!
You got a call
Hello?
Damn!
You've got videos
to return?
- No, I don't
- It's for you
Hello?
Are you nuts?
You shouldn't be here
They're out looking for us
What if they see you?
What's wrong?
Chang-sik
Let's go to a motel
Now?
Can I trust you, Chang-sik?
Trust me
Just try to relax
Leave your body to me
so I can work you freely
I'm so nervous
Never done this before
If my body
Mi-young, I'll get you
through this
I'll count to three
And you'll fall asleep
One, two
Redsun!
If not, why would you see
an orphanage?
And what about the zoo?
Those images are real?
How come
I have no recollection?
Those with childhood trauma
tend to suppress those
painful memories
In many cases, it develops
into multiple personalities
- I'm beat
- What are you doing?
- I'm going to bed
- With me here?
I said no!
Get out of here
This is my place! Hey!
Come on, get out
What are you doing?
Get out! Now!
What's she doing?
It's Showtime, bitch
Our company has won
the Presidential Award
Don't let $1,000 in cash
slip away
You're holding this event,
aren't you?
What'd you get the
Presidential Award for?
Beat it, boy
How old are you,
calling me a boy?
Go deliver Chinese food
Get out of here
You're asking for trouble
You fuckers!
I deliver Chinese food,
so what?
That doesn't mean
you can talk shit to me
Get out
Make my day, fuckers
Get your ass out
I take shit from no one
Don't play with knives
My stomach!
I don't have to buy anything?
Of course not
This is fraud, isn't it?
Don't tell me this is free
Fill out the form
It's so free
Watch it, pal
- Name and phone number?
- And address
- Get out! Out!
- What for?
He's giving his number
Oh, that's right
- Is this it?
- Right
Let me put it in for you
Have we met before?
It won't work, mister
- What's going on?
- Fill this out
Free ginseng
and $1,000 in cash
What's the matter?
It's just don't think
I can do this alone
- May I help you?
- Gosh!
Was there an orphanage here?
Until 7 years ago
I see
Why is she crying?
A snowman-shaped
birthmark on the back
Tell him it's the same year
and place as on the flyer
Same year and place
as on the flyer, sir
Oh, will you?
Yes, sir
Have a good trip back
What'd he say?
He's coming back
on the first flight tomorrow
He sounded very nervous
I bet!
It's been 20 years
This is all thanks to you
Don't mention it
I'm just so happy that
I can help my best friend
We're the hands and gloves
that go together
Nice! It's for her own good
For mine, too!
One more beer!
So hard to spend money
God, still too long
before it gets dark
Hello?
I won free gifts?
Dude, long time no see
How are you doing these days?
Did you eat?
- Fuckers
- Get back here!
Upstairs!
Why are we chasing him?
What am I gonna do?
I'm so fucked!
Bastards!
What am I gonna do?
Hello?
What the fuck do you
want from me?
What have I done
to you fuckers?
What?
What wife?
I'm not even married!
I don't give a damn
what you do to her!
Do whatever you want with her!
Who are you guys anyway?
You're messing
with the wrong guy
To the parking lot?
Bastards
How the fuck
did I wind up with her?
I'm screwed now
Yeah
That's right
Getting used to that, aren't you?
The camera is ready to roll
I was sick to my stomach
because of you two
What have we done?
Sons of bitches!
Why don't we bury them?
What do you think they are,
a couple of pots?
Who wants to do it?
I haven't banged a girl
in 4 and half years
- You do it
- Okay, I'll do my best, boss
Wait! Wait!
Won't it be better
if I do it?
Think about it
If I'm in the video, I won't
be able to rat on you
Right?
I love that girl
What do you think this is?
A honeymoon video?
Think about it, man
Even though
You're a cold-blooded gangster
I'm sure you're warm at heart
She won't be able to do it
before the man she loves
Let me do it
It smells
What do you say?
What smell?
I smell nothing
It smells!
Let's check it out
Let's go!
Come on
I've got a dinner date
Not until we solve this case
Dinner's after
Let's go
Come any closer,
and I'll kill you!
It's better for me to do this
than these people
Over my dead body!
Step aside I'm doing it!
No, I'm doing it!
Shut the fuck up!
Or let them do it!
These kind of videos
Better with some resistance
Don't you think?
Fucker
Just do it!
Nothing we can do
It'll be over before you
even know it
Make yourself believe
what I said earlier
This is the only way
Sorry to bother you
We're from the station
Oh, you guys are drinking
Drink with us
Sit down
We're not allowed to Drink
on duty, but
It's about a car outside
You own that car,
Seoul Da 1338, right?
- Potentia?
- Right
Where were you on the 12th?
Around midnight
I'm sure we were Drinking
Were you two together?
Yes
How much does it cost
to Drink here?
Depends on what you get
Let me pour you a shot
- I didn't know you had customers
- No, they're friends
Why aren't they singing?
Sounds like they're fighting
Don't mind them
Come on, Drink
We gotta hit the road
after this
Look, detective
I was just wondering
Do I have to turn myself in
if I run someone over?
Do you know?
The insurance boys know
better than us
That's right
Help!
- Turn off the mike!
- The insurance boys
I only did what I was told to do!
He can't talk
This boy is a mute
He's a poor kid
He's from this Island
- What island?
- Detective Oh
- Where's that videotape?
- Right by the camcorder
Find it!
It's criminal evidence
Please, detective
You have to believe us
We're innocent
Save your breath, punks!
Sir, can you make it look like
I turned myself in?
Drink this
What a lousy day it's been
His son, he wants to
see you tomorrow
Who?
Your brother
Sorry I didn't ask you first
But eventually
You'll have to meet him
Hi
How are you?
- Glad to see you again
- You, too
- Where?
- Outside
Let me tell you
It wasn't an easy decision
- I had to...
- If he were alive
He would've been
so happy
I'm so sorry
He jogged every night
to stay in shape
so he'd live long enough
to meet his lost child
Now
Meet your sibling
You've been separated
for a good 20 years
Here's the child your father
looked so hard for, Hwang Mi-young
Look at your brother
Come on
Brother
Brother!
Oh, God!
Mr. Choi, we gotta talk
This is a boy?
He looks like a girl, though
Who made these holes?
See you later
- Get up
- I'm tired, leave me alone
Get up!
Boy, life wears you out
I can understand now
why you're so bitter
I never imagined it'd be
at a place like this, but
let me tell you
everything
What is it, mom?
It's kind of complicated,
but simply put
You and your sister have
different fathers
What?
Your sister's father was
a friend of your father's
I remarried your father
Soon after
your sister's father died
I'd known him, though
People spoke ill of me
They almost stoned me
for remarrying
a friend of my late
husband's
But I never loved your
sister's father
It was your father that I truly loved
and I still do
Up until now
I've had so many guys
after my beauty
But I've remained faithful
When I miss him
so much
I stare into the air, and
You know why I'm crazy on cards?
I play cards to stop myself
from missing him
Otherwise, I would've gone
insane long ago
So
My father's dead?
They say daughters carry
on their moms' fate
I hope you don't
What's going on?
Watch your back, asshole
Why do you let her
torture you like that?
We're all dying here
tonight
Help!
You two don't deserve to live!
Come here!
She's found out about
the account
Chang-sik, get your ass
over here!
Make yourself useful
and do the laundry
You shouldn't work
on Sundays
Get a cup!
I'm working my ass off
to feed you brothers
Can you put this on for me?
Just like your brother!
Don't know how to wear a tie
- When's it due?
- February
I can't believe that little girl
I knew is becoming a mom
I was taller than you
back then
I know
Closing the barn door
after the horse is stolen
Be sure you brush up on
what you learned today
OK, that's it kids!
What's your name?
Shirts...
Am I missing anything?
- My sunglasses!
- On your head, fool
Oops!
Let's go
- Where are you going?
- We're going on a trip
Oh, for your 2nd anniversary?
Don't forget you have
a bun in the oven
He looks tired
Make sure you get him
a souvenir
Did you get the camcorder?
Forget it
We're late
We need that!
Let's rent one there
- Chang-sik, we're leaving
- Okay Have fun!
Wait! Wait!
Won't it be better
if I do it?
Think about it
If I'm in the video, I won't
be able to rat on you
I love that girl
I'd rather die than see her
have sex with another man
I'm in love with her
Hello?
Jang-mi!
- That'll be $2.8
- Can I buy another snack?
Anything less than 20 cents
- It's $3 then, right?
- Thanks
Excuse me
Can I go through?
It's been a while
Buying anything?
No, selling something
Look, back then...
I was just
Dad, buy me this
He's justjoking
He likes to call me dad
What a sly player!
That's not it
Why am I your dad?
I'm not his dad!
Go explain it to her!
Why am I your dad!
You make me crazy!
I've become a giraffe
waiting for you
Been away?
I didn't order anything
Not here on the job
Be nice to me cause I've got
something nice for you
Movie tickets!
I'll take them off your late fees
What? Wow
This kind of attitude
often takes me aback
I don't want them
Take them and get out
How can you be so
Hey, Mr. Bum!
Long time, no see
I notice you haven't
changed your part yet
It's getting dark outside
and we're Ionely
Let's go hit the movies
You really wanna see
a movie with me?
I'd like to do everything
with you, babe
Meet me at Teddy Home
in an hour
- For real? You're notjoking?
- You don't believe me?
Of course, I do!
I'll be waiting for you
You're really going
to a movie with him?
I bet he'll buy you
noodles on the date
Don't go
Please, don't go
I said, don't go!
Or I'll
put that video up
on the Internet
Who do you think you arer?
Are you threatening me now?
Do you know what a fool I became
because of you?
You made a complete fool
out of me!
And you never even call
You never even brought
around your ugly face!
Put what on the net?
I didn't mean it
Do whatever you want with it!
Why don't you sell it
to a porn site?
The instant that you do that
I'll make sure you rot in jail
You freaking psycho!
You didn't have to hit me!
I did call you!
But you never answered it
That's not my fault!
Hey, Video!
I'm talking to you!
You never answered
the damn phone
Why is that my fault?
Get a life, bitch
Jang Mi-young!
I'm sorry, damn it
Are you coming today?
What the...
I know you won't win
Why don't you model for us?
- For panties?
- Yeah
You really want your sister
to get naked on TV?
I'm your only sister, you know?
Be there, okay?
Be there!
- The answer is number 4
- Isn't it 5?
That's right
What?
- You said it was 4
- I did? I'm sorry
- Miss Jang Mi-young, get ready
- Okay
Let me introduce our
next contestant
Come on out!
I Love Quiz
Welcome to the show
We have a beautiful young
lady with us today
Miss Jang Mi-young, how are you?
Good, thanks
Could you tell us
what you do?
I... um...
In short
I collect late fees
Okay
Video...
And I act
- You act?
- At home, I mean
I suppose
you do a lot of things
Okay, are you ready?
Cappuccino rocks!
What kind of coffee
do you like most?
I hate coffee
I totally get you
I hate Chinese food more
than Osama Bin Laden
Tell me, babe
I'm free after 8 tonight
Wanna go out?
That's correct
I've been wanting to ask you
Who are those ladies over there?
Oh, my mom and sister
Oh, I see
I can see you got your looks
from your mom
All of you are so beautiful
Okay, let's move onto
the next question
You call this a drawing?
Don't be so hard on me
Why don't we eat and
Is that all you think about?
You're as cheesy
as someone I know
Here are some hints
Chinese poet, poem
King Hyunjong, Yang Kuei-fei
You're wearing a big smile
That means you're confident
You know the answer,
don't you?
Or not
Give us your answer to level 8
- What is...
- Yes?
- What is 'Cicinnurus Regius'?
- Correct!
- How much so far?
- I think it's $3 K
No, I heard him say 5 K
- Why'd you even ask?
- Shut up!
Each bird has one wing
they can only fly as a couple
That's right
- Who am I describing?
- I'm home
You've got 5 seconds
So difficult
- Who is Mendel...
- You have to be specific
Who is Mendeleev?
Mendeleev
Correct!
Level 10
Only one question left
If you get this one correct
you'll be the Quiz Master
I'll give you the clue
Look at the monitor
It's 'Freud'
Will you challenge it?
You haven't used your chance yet
Either phone or Internet
Your mom and sister are
going wild back there
Have you decided?
Should Ichallenge it?
Don't ask me
- Sorry, nerous...
- It's the first time
that a contestant has asked me that
You have to decide for yourself
What's it gonna be?
- I will
- She's challenging it!
She's not the only girl out there
I'm not calling her
No way
No fucking way
He established the concept
of the social character
Who is he?
It's the final question
You can be the Quiz Master
The smile is gone
She looks rather nervous
You have a chance left
You can use either the phone
or the internet
- I'll use the phone
- Sure
Who will you call?
- Just...
- You don't have a person in mind?
The phone is right
in front of you
You've got 30 seconds
Make your call
- Hello
- Hello?
It's me, Mi-young
Hello? Hello?
Chang-sik, are you there?
- What are you calling a psycho for?
- No swearing, please
Is this some kind ofjoke?
I've got a question
for you
Why didn't you
answer my calls?
- Think about it
- Now I'm in
You think I meant to
make a fool out of you?
I don't have much time
Neither do I!
Don't yell at me!
I'm not a bum any more
I even got a job now!
Hello?
Let me finish before you
hang up on me!
Come on, listen to me
- I mean...
- What should I do?
- Hello?
- I know very well
I often say things
that I don't mean
We don't have time for this
Just answer my question
- Who established...
- Things got crazy
All I'm saying is
Let me talk!
I realized later
what I'd done to you
What's wrong with you?
I was so worried about you
that I couldn't sleep
What
I staked out your place
at night
Hang up!
What's your point?
I'm just...
Can we go steady?
What?
Or we can talk about it
some other time
Some other time?
No, tell me now
I'm in love with you
What did you say?
I couldn't hear you
This is so embarrassing
I know you heard me
You heard me!
I love you!
Miss Jang Mi-young?
I...
We'll meet and
talk about it, okay?
Now?
Where?
At theconvenient store
Hello? Hello?
I didn't mean for this
to happen
What was the question?
At the convenient store
I can't believe these people
It's a quiz show for Christ's sake!
Crazy!
Where's the remote?
Every guy named Chang-sik
sucks!
Mi-young! Mi-young!
Taxi! Taxi!
- Get in
- Us?
Where's she going?
- Good heavens...
- Drink this, mom
Does she know how many panties
I have to sell for $30 Grand?
She was amazing, though
Knowing all those things
- How did she do that?
- Excuse me
We'd like an interview with you
- For TV?
- Yes
I'm so proud of my little girl
You don't see that kind of romance
these days, how beautiful
Pull over
Stop the car!
Chang-sik! Chang-sik!
- Chang-sik!
- Mi-young!
Stay right there
I'm coming across
Not here
Come to the crosswalk!
What are we doing now?
It feels so weird
- Have you had dinner?
- Not yet
Let's eat
What would you like?
- What?
- Sushi?
Stay there
I'll come to you
Ok, you stay there
I told you I'd come to you
I thought you told me
to come to you
God! I told you to stay there
It doesn't matter
We're here together
Yeah, in the middle
of the damn road!
Tell me
What?
- There you go again!
- What?
I told you how I feel about you
on the phone
And you said
we would talk about it in person
You did, didn't you?
Chang-sik
What?
Hug me
Come on, this is too embarassing
There's people looking
and cars passing by
Oh, boy!
What the hell is she doing
in the middle of the road?
Mom, don't!
They look great
I bet you did the same
with dad, didn't you?
Not like that
Shit!
I told you to hug me
not grope me
I thought it'd be okay
What the hell are you
talking about?
I never told you it was
okay to grope me!
What's wrong with you?
You guys are all pigs
They can never
What a picture!
Get a room!
I'm sorry
Are you nuts?
There are people watching us!
- I wasn't going to, but...
- But what?
I got aroused
Did you have to put your
damn tongue in my mouth?
I'm sorry
We could've done it later!
Why'd you hug me?
It's your fault
You got me horny!
I can't believe this!
God, we're stuck again!
It's your fault!
Come back!
Get up now!
Fuck! I'll save up and
buy out this restaurant
Not in a million years!
You're too lazy
The early bird
catches the worm
Who knows?
I might find my parents
who are loaded
And get a load of money
Get up and bring back
the empty plates!
Okay! Okay!
Get the lion
It's head's big, you know
Once you get a hold on him
It won't fall
Make a lot of money!