KOREA PICTURES presents
a CULTURE CAP MEDIA PRODUCTION
Executive Producer Soma H.Z. Chung
Producer Choi Soonsik
Co-producer Park Dojun
Co-executive Producers
Lee Dongjoo, Lee Seokjun
starring
Kim Raewon
Moon Geunyoung
Director Kim Hojun
MY LITTLE BRIDE
Honey~
Hey, you can't kick that...
Jeez.
You haven't changed one bit.
It's you, Boeun.
You're a big girl now. Great body!
Nice curves.
Drop it, okay?
Hey, you little girl!
Hey, give me a break!
They look so nice and shiny...
Stop staring. You'll sprain your eyes.
No, it's just that they look familiar.
Anyway, what brings you here?
Missed me so that
you had to skip school?
No, it's the school's anniversary.
I was forced to come here.
I'm wasting my time
when I really have to study.
Yeah, there's only 2 years left
to the national exam.
But people like you really make
college look undesirable.
What do you mean?
You're a pervert and a playboy.
I may be a playboy,
but not a pervert.
Here's your present.
Just for you, keep it
a secret to the family.
Okay.
Pretty, isn't it?
It's padded. Real thick.
You're a pervert!
Should I help you put it on?
- Should I?
- Want me to punch you?
- My son! My son's home!
- How have you been?
- Welcome home.
- Thanks.
- How was your trip?
- Fine. How have you been?
- Grandfather's waiting. Hurry.
- Okay.
- Mom, it's heavy. I'll carry it.
You've changed.
What was all the rush?
And is grandpa really sick?
Son, brace yourself, okay?
Delicious, isn't it?
I made it myself,
just for you, grandfather.
Really tasty.
No one but you can take
such good care of me.
Of course, I'm your
only granddaughter.
You've really grown.
Now you look like a lady.
She may have grown,
but she's still a child.
I'd be married in the old days.
Right grandfather?
Absolutely. A married woman.
- Sangmin, come sit here.
- Yes, grandfather.
You two, hear me out.
You may have heard this story
before,
Sangmin's grandfather was an
old friend and war comrade
When we were young, we made a pact.
To marry our kids.
But you two had only sons.
So, our pact was passed down
to the next generation.
I hope you two can
keep this promise.
What are you saying?
You idiot! Grandpa wants you
to marry Sangmin!
Marriage?
You must be joking grandpa!
Marry Sangmin?
Hey! Your grandpa's not kidding!
I can die peacefully after
you two get married!
This way I can face Sangmin's grandpa.
How can a high schooler get married!
Anyone over 15 can marry
with their parent's consent.
I haven't much time left, you know?
No, I won't.
Never!
Sorry grandpa but I'll forget
what you just said.
He hasn't finished speaking!
I'm speechless myself.
It's me. I'm back.
I'm back in Korea, standing
in front of the dept. Office.
Hey, there's new blood in the dept.
- How are you?
- Oh, yeah.
The chicks are great!
Let's get together after class.
Hey, Sangmin!
What a surprise!
Has it been a year already?
No, family business.
How about you?
Great. My looks...
- keep me too busy...
- Come on...
Come back when I'm the TA.
It'll help when you skip classes.
Would I, a model student, do that?
Besides, it's my last year...
Friend, my good friend!
- How have you been!
- Great dude!
Look at him! Life in the West
has done you well!
What brought you back?
Problems at home?
- Yeah something's up at home...
- Huh? What?
- I'm getting married... damn.
- Huh? Bastard!
Hey, is it a black or white girl?
Pounding!
Only you should know about it~
I'm just 17~
Come, come silently ~
Here and there~
Hey!
They're making such a fuss.
Losers...
- Shh! They'll hear you.
- Why? You think you're different?
My doctor said I have
20 more years to go!
Really?
Change of plans. I'll make my move.
Just back me up.
I understand.
Good!
They switched it.
Isn't he the guy?
They switched it. Remember?
Yeah...
I really wish they wouldn't play
those things on TV.
I guess the wedding's really on.
What am I going to do, mom?
Be strong, son.
Grant your grandpa this one wish.
Let's call it a day!
You're Suh Boeun, 1st grade,
right?
You were so funny, don't you agree?
Hey, what?
Come on!
Who's he?
He's just a guy I know.
That's what they all say.
I'm telling the truth!
I really thought about it,
and I'll speak first.
- Let's just do it.
- Are you crazy?
I'm kidding.
You think I'd want to?
I don't want to do it with you!
Even if I did,
it's insane. I'm just 15!
Okay, I got it.
Anyway, I'll buy you dinner.
Or anything else you need.
Mister, you're a sugardaddy,
aren't you?
- Boeun.
- Huh?
How can you do this to me?
I may be pretty, but
into something like this.
Hey...
Hyewon, stop it!
- I'll leave you two to talk.
- Huh?
See you later, Boeun.
- Remember, it's a secret.
- I know.
- Bye.
- Good bye.
- What's her problem?
- It's understandable.
Hello? Yes...
What!
Good, good.
Grandpa!
- Grandpa!
Grandpa, we're here!
Grandpa, Grandpa!
Wake up, Grandpa!
- Uncle, something's wrong!
- What?
Grandpa!
It's doing it again.
We should've gone
to another hospital!
It almost gave me a heart attack!
I was out of myself again.
Are you okay, grandpa?
- Let's have a word outside.
- Okay.
Be by your grandpa's side, okay?
Yeah.
I'm really worried.
I know. With the kids like that,
he's getting worse.
Come on... marriage is
out of the question!
They... you have to think about
Boeun's future.
Come on, let's just marry the kids.
Let go.
Come on...
This is Sangmin's grandparents.
Soon after this picture was taken,
war broke.
Want me to tell you a secret?
Secretly,
your grandpa had feelings
for Sangmin's grandma.
She was quite a beauty.
However, after Sangmin's
grandpa's death,
I tucked those feelings away.
That's why I took care of Sangmin's
father like my own son.
Your father may not have been
so happy about this.
- Boeun!
- Yes?
Keeping this promise is the most
important thing for me.
- Grandpa!
Grandpa, wake up. Grandpa!
You can't die!
Open your eyes, grandpa!
Grandpa, I'll get married
so open your eyes, grandpa!
I'll keep your promise, grandpa!
I'll get married...
Are you crying?
Stop crying.
You may be behind in your grades,
but you're the nation's first
to get married.
Congrats, missus.
Right.
Scared that Sangmin will
discover your lop-sided butt?
A butt that needs cushioning
to keep it on balance?
- Hey, get out!
- Ouch, it hurts!
I'm sorry Boeun,
for not being much help.
Mom, am I really getting married?
What about school?
I have to go to college...
Marriage won't change anything.
Marriage, accept it with grace.
It's nothing.
Just consider you're getting
a new brother.
I'm scared that they'll
find out at school.
How will I face everyone?
Don't worry.
Grandpa will take care of it.
Your grandpa was your principal's
military senior.
Really?
Behold the face of a wolf who'll
eat up a 15 year old virgin.
- Is it satisfaction or disbelief?
- Satisfaction, of course.
Shit, are you really my friends?
I can't be married at this age.
- To Sangmin!
- Cheers~
The chicks here are hot!
Let's go out on the floor!
Hello.
You're here. Thanks.
You're here.
- Sir!!
- Yes, come in. Over here.
I won't forget this.
How could our field trip
be at the same time?
I know.
You shouldn't keep it from
your other friends.
If they found out,
the whole school will know.
Then I'd have to quit school.
Anyway, you're so pretty today.
I wish I could get married too.
Look here!
Hey, smile!
- How are you doing?
- Hello.
- Don't take my picture.
- Okay, okay.
Good luck!
I'm convinced that
grandpa scammed me.
- Boeun, it's just a wedding, okay?
- I can't do it, mom!
Now, don't be a baby.
I'm nervous myself.
I'm telling grandpa.
"I can't do it!"
Do you want your wedding
turned into a funeral?
I don't know.
I'm scared, mom.
What am I going to do
with such a baby?
Now the groom will enter.
Welcome him with a big applause.
The groom, please enter!
She's so beautiful!
Respectable guests,
family and relatives.
We are all gathered here to
congratulate the new beginning of
groom, Park Sangmin
and bride, Suh Boeun...
- Dad, we'll be okay.
- Yeah, yeah.
Remember, she's only 15.
- What's your point?
- I know I can trust you.
You forced me into this marriage,
so I'll do as I wish!
Boeun is still in high school!
I don't care! I'll do as I wish
with my wife.
Boeun, don't worry. Your father-in-law
has had a word with Sangmin.
About what?
- That you... shouldn't do it...
- What?
I can't say...
- Call us when you get there.
- Yes, auntie.
Stop calling her that.
It's mom from now on.
Yes, mom.
Hey, mom! Can I keep the bouquet?
It was so pretty...
Forget the bouquet...
She's such a child.
What am I going to do with you?
Stop, you promised to be cool.
- Bon voyage~
- Yes, yes...
- Bye~
- Follow right behind, okay?
It's time to board, where is she?
Boeun.
- Boeun? Where is it?
- Over there...
- Okay, we'll go inside, thanks.
- Okay, go.
- Thanks for everything.
- Don't overdo yourself.
- Have a safe trip.
- Yeah, give me the suitcase.
Have fun, Boeun.
Don't worry, dude.
Be good, okay?
- See you later!
- Bye. Bon voyage.
- I've never boarded on time...
- Wait.
- What?
- I need to go to the bathroom.
Again? It's your first time on
a plane, isn't it?
Don't worry. It's only an hour
to Jeju Island.
It won't take long.
You're making such a fuss.
Hurry back.
- I'll be at our seats. Hurry.
- Okay...
Shit. Where is she?
- Sir, you must be seated.
- The plane's leaving. Open the...
Sir, please seat yourself!
Mobiles are prohibited in the cabin.
Thank you for your cooperation.
He must think he owns the plane.
It must be his first flight.
I don't believe this.
Wait sir.
- We're in a hurry.
- Sorry.
Hey!
Did they arrive safely?
Yeah... they did.
I need to be clear about one thing.
Listen.
Until Boeun graduates from
college, no grandchildren!
Make this clear to your father as well.
Yes, of course.
When she was little, she would fall
and break things,
but she seemed to hold herself
well at the wedding.
It's a relief.
Why? Are you disappointed
that she didn't fall?
Yes, a little.
Come on...
Not those idiots again!
Having fun?
Hey!
Hey, do you have a place to stay?
Just this once.
Press anything. Wind it and press.
Say cheese.
Take your best shot.
Uh, Sangmin?
I can't believe this!
What brings you here?
Boeun's on her honeymoon
and we're on our fieldtrip.
- Don't you remember?
- Of course I do.
- Where's Boeun?
- Well...
- Hey! Who's the mister?
- He's just a friend.
- He's cute.
- See you later!
- Hey, stop it. Wait, come here.
- Oh god...
Hey!
What are you doing on top of her!
You pervert! You chase after young
girls, don't you!
It's not like that.
- I'm not...
- Really.
- Really?
Then what are you doing?
- Uh?
- Huh?
Look at him running off!
Aren't you supposed to be
on your field trip?
Yes...
Then why are you here?
What are you doing today?
Nothing.
Do you have a boyfriend?
No... I don't.
The mobile you have reached is off.
You will be transferred to a voice mail...
Pest, how can you do this to me...
Our parents shouldn't find out.
We'll talk later. Bye.
Then, from now on we're dating.
Okay!
Hey you! Come here!
Wow! Looks so fun! Isn't it?
- Where are you from?
- I'm from Canada.
Canada? I know Canada!
Who am I kidding?
I've never set foot on Canada.
Teacher!
Hi, how are you?
Uh, Hyewon?
What brings you here at this hour?
It's individual time.
Haven't you ever been on a field trip?
Of course I have.
Anyway, where's Boeun?
Why're you alone?
I don't even know where to begin?
It's like this...
Yes.
Boeun...
You're a serial pervert, aren't you!
Hey! Come back!
Feels good, doesn't it?
It's been a while... together.
Sit here.
Stop.
Rest your back on this.
I feel great.
It's too late for this
but I'm sure that we did
a horrible thing to Boeun.
She's only 15, and going through
her 1st year of high school.
Come on! Be more positive.
You were considering him as
your son-in-law anyway.
She's not going far away.
Let's have some faith, okay?
Besides, our in-laws love Boeun
like their own daughter.
But, she's not their own daughter.
I can understand dad and you,
but I still can't forgive you for it.
Okay, okay, that's enough... enough...
Without Boeun, it seems like
there's a big hole in my heart.
Everyone looks like Boeun,
that one too...
Candy, sir? Thank you.
Candy, sir?
Boeun, help him.
Honey, honey, here.
Thank you very much.
- Grandpa!
- Dad, come on out.
- Sit, sit and eat.
- Okay.
So, how was your trip?
Good grandpa. We had a good time.
Yes, Sangmin was kind to me.
I really had fun.
Stop, I didn't do anything.
I'm glad you had fun.
Since you're officially married,
love one another
so we can see the fruit of your love.
But you don't look so happy, Sangmin.
Are you sick?
Of course I'm not sick.
They're definitely a great couple,
aren't they?
Your room's been cleaned,
go get some rest.
Yes sir.
Stop, we should have a drink
with the new groom.
How about it dad?
Right. My grandson-in-law
should pour me a drink.
As you wish.
Grandpa, I'll go to bed now.
Yeah, yeah.
Go to your room...
Careful!
Honey!
Let's go!
- Hey! Boeun's not a thing.
- Good night!
Hey! Be careful.
Hey! Hey!
- Have a good night.
- Good night!
Honey!
Ah, you're heavy!
You stink of liquor!
Hey! Hey!
- You're tearing my dress. Stop it!
- Keep still!
He's coming on real strong.
This is the right place.
Come in. Look at this tree.
Come in dad.
Close the door behind you.
What do you think? Huh? Okay?
Look at this, great huh?
It's a great place.
Great place Boeun.
- You put up that picture.
- Nice, isn't it? Great huh?
Look at the balcony. I chose this.
Boeun.
It's so clean.
Hey, look at this picture.
This picture.
Where should I put this picture?
You're having the time of your life,
aren't you?
- What's this, Arabian Nights?
- Goodness!
- What's with the pillows...
- Goodness...
Separate rooms until you graduate,
okay?
I am so pissed!
I like it...
What's this, a flower garden?
What am I going to do?
Stop it!
Language is part of culture...
Language is... a part of... culture...
When we learn of foreign language
We should also learn about
that country's culture...
Ah, great!
Hey, stop! Put something on!
I always take everything off.
Even my underwear.
Get out!
Out where?
This is my room.
What do you mean?
Yours is over there.
Get out!
I don't feel like it.
Let's sleep together.
What, you're crazy!
You sleep together
when you get married.
Boeun...
What?
- I think tonight is the night.
- What?
Listen to me.
Stay away from me.
Come on. We're married. Boeun,
do as I say!
Hey, stop it!
We're married! Do as I say
and stay still.
Shit... I was just playing with you!
Oh my god!
Good morning, Boeun.
Your eyes are quite a sight!
Morning exercise?
What? You disappeared from the airport?
Then what did you do
during your honeymoon?
Who, me?
Can you keep a secret?
You have too many secrets.
I'm dating Jungwoo.
Jungwoo? What about your husband?
Husband... are you kidding?
I was forced into it.
Then does Jungwoo know
you're married?
No. But I'm sure he'll understand.
Let's go.
If I call her, she'll
be here in an instant.
She'll come if you call her now?
Of course. "Yes master"
and she'll come.
You're such a liar.
Stop, she'll be studying anyway.
- Wait. I'll show you.
- Dude, that's impolite.
- Tell her to come.
- Wait.
Wife! It's me!
Your husband commands you to come!
Wow.
- Hurry!
- Wow.
- Hurry!!
Bye!
Now she'll fly here like a bullet.
Guys... let's drink!
I'm Sangmin. I'm a man, ain't I?
Of course you're a man.
I'm just teaching my wife a lesson.
Like a real man.
A man of all men.
A real man. Have a drink, men!
Men!!
Men, drink up!
Drink till we drop!
There'll be an inspection today.
Go home and study.
Wife!
She's my wife. Come here wife!
- We're married!
- Not today.
He's really her husband.
Welcome, Boeun.
You saw her at the wedding.
My wife, Boeun.
How could you call me over
to a place...
like this.
Your husband says okay.
Another beer please!
Don't. Would you like a soda?
Yes...
A soda over here.
You're so adorable.
Thank you.
Of course! My wife's adorable.
She's a horrible cook,
with a bad temper.
And a bad student.
- She also snores.
- Sangmin! You're drunk.
- Stop drinking, okay?
- No.
I am jealous. I have no one
to worry about me.
- Wow, I feel great. Bottoms up!
- Bottoms up, bottoms up!
I never introduced myself.
I'm Sangmin's senior, Han Jisoo.
I'm Suh Boeun.
Boing, boing, Boeun.
She goes boing boing
every morning!
Jisoo, know what she did to me
on our honeymoon?
Hey, Park Sangmin!
Get off your butt!
Pretty please...
I'll see you again, Jisoo.
Yes. I'm sure we'll be good friends.
Treat me like a little sister.
But you're my senior in life
since you're married.
Stop joking.
Stop joking, stop joking.
You know, you two are
made for each other.
We were always at each other's
throats when we were little.
Hitting and teasing each other.
He's the first boy to flip my skirt.
Funny. Boys are mean to
girls they really like.
Jisoo, Jisoo, kiss me.
At least you could've fixed me
something for my hangover.
You deserve it.
Besides, I'm still in high school.
You always use that line
when you're cornered.
High school is not a crown, you know.
It is too, so there!
Okay, then I'll show you
my cooking talents tonight!
- Hey, Suh Boeun!
- What?
- Let's go.
- Come.
You wanna get smacked? Come!
What do you want?
I heard you were telling everyone
you were Jungwoo's girl?
Fucking unbelievable!
She's boasting that
she's slept with Jungwoo.
The bitch thinks we're shit.
How dare you, bitch.
Listen up. Watch your mouth.
If I hear about this again,
you're dead meat!
Jungwoo and I are in love!
Have you lost your senses!
Hey! Didn't you get the message?
I didn't do anything wrong.
I'm leaving!
Hey! How dare you...
Lose your attitude!
What are you doing!
Fuck off.
What?
Hey, Lee Jungwoo,
you can't treat me like that!
You're in no position to say
that to me.
Listen up. It's true that Boeun
and I are dating.
Don't mind them.
They think they're princesses.
But you're the real princess.
Sesame oil, sugar!
- A small bottle of oil?
- Yeah!
- This sugar?
- Hurry, hurry.
Okay!
Vinegar, spaghetti, ketchup!
There's the vinegar...
And there's the spaghetti!
Here?
Here, the ketchup's here. Okay...
Hurry, hurry!
- Olive oil, pickles!
Boeun!
Are you okay, Boeun?
Boeun, Boeun, Are you okay?
Are you okay?
Ow, my leg!
It hurts?
- Does it hurt bad?
- No. Why? Get off?
Stay put before I change my mind.
Don't touch me there!
I'm not doing it on purpose.
Why should I?
My hand just went there naturally.
What a great excuse!
Now walk straight.
You slant to the right cause
your butt is lop-sided.
Don't start with me.
I'm not kidding.
Your right butt has grown bigger.
Hey, stop it!
Stop it! Hey, stop it!
Lop-sided butt~
lop-sided butt~
- Stop it, stop it!
- Okay, okay!
- Ladies and gentlemen!
- Shut up...
Boeun has a lop-sided butt!
Lop-sided butt~
Look at how you're cutting.
You should put your heart into
what you're cooking.
Just be quiet!
- Be quiet? I'm older than you...
- Stop it!
Stop what? I'm older...
Hey... You little...
- What?
- Take my sword.
- Pest... aim at what you can take.
- Hey, come here.
What are you going to do with that?
- Hey, stop it... it's hot. Hot! Hey...
- Hey...
Hey... that's not fair!
Ouch!
- It's delicious.
- Yeah.
You got something on your mouth.
The same with you.
Rock, paper, scissors!
Yes!
Make sure everything's spotless.
It's more important than cooking.
Give me a break!
Hey, is it this side?
Hey! You pervert!
If I were you, I would help!
This picture's great.
I look so handsome.
Gotcha!
Sangmin... Don't come near!
Stop it!
Don't come near!
Stop it, stop...
- Now, I'm taking everything off!
- Stop!
- Thanks, the Kimbap's delicious.
- Really?
The baseball field's empty.
Aren't people coming to watch the game?
No one comes to watch
high school baseball anymore.
It's pro-baseball or the major league
they go to.
I hope you'll play in the major league
some day.
Hey, Lee Jungwoo!
Good luck!
I'm starved.
Double crust seafood...
This is pretty good.
Lee Jungwoo, hurrah~
Give us a break.
Great pitching and now good batting?
She's quite a chick.
Why don't you share? Shit.
Yes, that player's Lee Jungwoo.
An upcoming star in high school baseball!
Huh? It's Boeun's high school.
Was I too generous?
That's doesn't look good...
Youngsters with raging hormones.
Something to do without.
But, I guess they'll
grow out of it.
One cute student is quite
passionate about a player.
- Ah, it's the Kimbap girl.
- Excuse me?
They were sharing a Kimbap lunch
before the game. Nice picture.
I see.
Can't you be more early?
- Were you still up?
- I've been waiting for you.
It gets dangerous at night. Go to bed.
Okay.
- Sleep.
- Go to sleep.
- Yeah.
- Night.
- What's wrong?
- Don't you know?
What?
The whole school knows about
you and Jungwoo.
- What's wrong with that?
- Do you think it's right?
You're married.
Just by law!
You know how things are!
What if Sangmin's and your parents
found out? How can you be so selfish?
Why are you crying?
I like Jungwoo too!
There you are. We're having a
meeting at our place tonight.
I know.
You look great. Your hubby
must be treating you well.
- Hey!
- Yes?
- You live in apt. 106, right?
- Yes
There's an important meeting tonight,
so tell your mom to come, okay?