What'd you say?
Are you going
through menopause?
I'm not going
through menopause.
I'm not gonna go through
menopause for like 20 years.
I'm pregnant,
you little bitch.
God damn it!
I'm going out with Desi
to find out if
she's stealing from us.
I've got
the Graham Parker concert.
Who's gonna watch the kids?
I don't know.
Figure it out.
I kind ofjust wanted to talk.
I thought maybe we could go
to a coffeehouse or something.
You want coffee?
This place has coffee.
They have
all kinds of drinks.
Um...
But someplace
quiet, maybe.
This place
can be quiet.
There's a spot in the back.
It's pretty quiet.
What sport
do you guys play?
We play hockey.
Oh, I like hockey.
Who do you guys
play for?
We play for
the Philadelphia Flyers.
So, you guys are
all from Philadelphia?
No.
Actually, none of us are.
Do you guys still
have all ofyour teeth?
Well, I got all my
teeth except these ones.
Do you want to
try them on?
Yeah, I'll do it.
Go for it.
Do I look sexy?
Yeah!
Do you want to
make out with me?
Oh, yeah.
Wow.
They definitely look
way better on her
than they do on you.
Here we go.
Thank you.
So, should we go
to the quiet area?
No, no, no.
Where are you going?
We kind of have to have
a little business
meeting tonight.
Business meeting?
Girls, you gotta celebrate
because we won tonight.
Let's go.
I want to party
with these winners.
Come on, Deb.
Just come to the stage
and dance with us.
Yeah.
Okay.
Yeah!
Okay, let's fucking dance!
Don't be shy,
feel free to come down
and fill up these empty seats.
Thank you so much for coming.
This is so exciting!
For the first time
in over 30 years,
Graham Parker & The Rumour.
Where are his fans?
I mean, where are they?
It's hard to watch a band
when you know all of
them remember D-Day.
What was
the press turnout like?
Oh. You're serious?
Nobody came. Nobody.
Nobody is here?
The guy from
Green Day is here.
Yeah, Billie Joe,
I emailed him. He's a fan.
You gotta get a photo
of the two of them.
No, he says he doesn't
want to do any press.
He's just watching the show.
Oh, how punk-rock of him.
"l don't like photographs."
Grow up, Green Day!
Shut the fuck up, Tom Selleck!
You don't have, like...
I wouldn't call them
classically good dance moves,
but you left it
all out there.
You're a blast
to dance with.
Thank you.
We're having a little shindig
at the hotel after this.
You should come by
and hang out at the hotel.
You want me to
come to the hotel?
Yes, I want you to come
by the hotel with me.
Well, what would we
do there?
Maybe we can find somewhere
quiet and have fun and kind
of see where it goes.
Do it like adults
do sometimes and...
Like, sex?
I mean, if you want.
If that's on the docket,
but I'm not
trying to force that.
So, you would
do sex with me?
"Do sex"?
What are you, Borat?
Are you hitting on me?
Yes, yes,
I'm hitting on you.
You're hot and cool and nice
and you have beautiful eyes.
I'm sorry.
I'm married,
I have two kids
and I'm pregnant.
That is what we call
the hat-trick. Wow.
I'm sorry
I didn't tell you.
I was just really enjoying
you being so nice to me.
I hope this doesn't
come off as super-cheesy,
but I think you're
a very rare find.
Thank you.
And I would totally
"do sex" with you.
That was
spectacular, guys.
Really well done. Amazing.
Thank you.
Good, good.
Hey, Graham.
Pete. How are you, man?
Well, the first numbers
came in.
Yeah, right, yeah.
Happy? How's it looking?
About half of
your last record.
Ah. So, you were
expecting it to sell?
They never sell anymore.
They used to sell,
but now they don't.
I'm not a sexy
16-year-old girl.
But I wanted to sell it.
It's such a good record.
I feel like I let you down.
No, I'm gonna be fine, man.
My overheads are so low.
I just got a song in Glee.
The guy in the wheelchair
is gonna sing it to
the Asian girl, I believe.
I don't know,
I've never seen the show,
but that's what I'm told.
The secret is,
make sure you
have a small nut.
That's the key to life.
Graham, I don't have
small nuts, all right?
I have big nuts
and I need to
provide for them.
Graham!
Hey, what's up?
Billie!
Graham,
how are you doing, man?
Great fucking show, man.
Good to see you.
Thank you.
Fuck.
Yeah, I'm inspired.
I want to write
a fucking song right now.
Inspired.
Yeah.
That inspires me.
Let's go get a drink.
Let's get a drink.
All right. You coming?
No, no, I'm fine.
You guys go.
Congratulations on Glee.
Oh!
Yes, thank you.
All right.
See you, Pete.
All right. So long, guys.
Later.
Yeah, yeah.
You got a song on Glee?
Yeah.
That's killer, man.
That's so much money.
It's great.
It's good for all of us.
Why did you put that
guy's teeth in your mouth?
That's so gross.
I was drunk.
He was dirty.
No, he was wearing a tie.
That's true.
He wasn't dirty.
When I kissed him,
I felt his little tiny
teeth nubs with my tongue.
You did?
Yeah.
It was like kissing a baby.
French-kissing a baby.
Can I ask you
something stupid?
Uh-huh.
Do you know why we're
missing money at the store?
Are you guys missing money?
Yeah. Like, $12,000.
Do you think
that I took it?
No. I mean...
Well, no.
I did and I don't now.
It's not me.
Why do you live in
such a nice apartment
and have such a fancy car?
Yes, you're right.
Um... Look...
I am an escort.
I get paid
to go out on dates.
You...
Oh.
But only three to
five times a year.
Ten times, max.
But it's not technically
prostitution, because I don't
have to sleep with them.
Oh, well, that's good.
But I always do.
That's why I only do it
four to eight times a year.
Fifteen times, max.
Huh.
One year, I did it 20.
Well, as long as
you think it's safe.
It's safe.
I only do it 10
to 30 times a year.
So, who do you
think is stealing money?
It's fucking Jodi.
No.
Yeah.
She's a pilled-out whore.
Huh.
Since you told me,
I want to tell you something.
You're pregnant.
How'd you know?
Wow.
Maybe you should tell Pete.
You didn't tell Pete yet?
I haven't told Pete.
Why?
I don't know why.
I just want him to want me.
I don't want him to want me
because I'm pregnant.
Go home and
fucking suck his dick
and tell him then,
and he will love it.
You think?
He'll be so excited.
Or even better yet...
Better yet,
you should tell him
while you're
sucking his dick, like...
"I'm pregnant."
What are you doing?
Um, returning some emails.
What time do you
have to go to work?
Like, 10 minutes ago.
Do you wanna be late?
No, I can't be late,
not today.
Do you see me standing
here in front of you,
half-naked?
Yeah.
And does that
make you feel anything, or...
Come on.
Are you trying
to start a fight?
No, I'm not trying
to start a fight with you.
I'm trying to fuck you.
Oh, God, you know what?
Today, of all days,
is the day you need to
cut me a break, all right?
Whatever.
Oh, God.
What?
I didn't realize
it was intentional.
I didn't say anything
because I didn't want
you to be embarrassed.
I thought I was being gallant.
All right, fine.
I'm an asshole.
God.
You know
what your problem is?
You're never,
ever in the moment.
You're never, ever present.
You're never in your body.
That's not true.
I am in the moment.
You know how I know?
I want to get
the fuck out of the moment.
I swear,
I can't win with you.
I just can't do it.
You can't just walk away.
Oh, God.
Hey! How's the record
company going, Pete?
What? Not great.
I'm still waiting
for numbers to come in.
What have you heard?
A couple numbers
have trickled in.
It's lower than we expected.
Then why are you
giving Larry money?
What?
I know everything.
I talked to the accountant.
You know what?
I don't wanna get
into some nasty fight
so can we please
talk to each other
the way the therapist told us
to talk to each other?
Fine. Fine.
It makes me feel sad
when you are dishonest.
I understand it
makes you feel bad
when I am dishonest with you.
It hurts my feelings when
you treat me with contempt
and corner me,
and try and
trick me into lying.
Okay.
It makes me sad
when it's so easy to
trick you into lying,
because you're
such a lying shit-bag.
That's not...
You can't do that,
you can't do that.
The therapist said you're
not allowed to judge me.
That's not a judgment,
that's just a fact.
Fair enough.
Sometimes I withhold truth,
that is true.
But it's only because
I'm scared to death
of your crazy-assed,
illogical overreactions.
Well...
It hurts me
inside and triggers me
when you're such
a dishonest shit,
that you're lending
your father money
without telling me
while your record
company's going bankrupt
and we're on the verge
of losing our fucking house!
What else are you
lying about?
I've taken
Viagra for two years.
I ate six muffins
downstairs a while ago
and my
cholesterol level is 305.
My heart could
explode at any second.
These might be my
very last words.
Oh, and I gave Charlotte
antibiotics when
you weren't looking.
That's why her ear got better.
So, go fuck your witch doctor.
What are we even doing?
What are we doing?
This is not
making me happy.
You're not happy.
You don't like me.
I can feel that.
I'm not blind.
Jesus.
We're like
business associates.
brother and sister.
There's no passion there.
We're not like
brother and sister.
You know what we're like?
We're like Simon and Garfunkel
and, somehow,
you turned me into Garfunkel.
I don't even know
what that means.
Art Garfunkel.
What's wrong
with Art Garfunkel?
He has a beautiful voice.
He's got an amazing voice!
He could put
a harmony to anything!
But what I'm saying is that
you turned me into him.
What the hell are
you talking about?
Simon controls him!
That's because Simon
writes the fucking songs!
He's the better one!
You know what?
I see the way you
look at our kids.
You have so much
love and compassion for them.
You never look at
me like that. Ever.
Would we even
still be together
if I didn't get
pregnant 14 years ago?
You know what?
I'm not gonna go
down that road.
Would we?
Okay.
You know what?
I don't want to
have a party here.
You need to cancel it.
No, I'm not.
I already paid
for the catering.
I've put down deposits.
And I sure as fuck
am not gonna call
everybody back in two days
when you change your mind.
Your girlfriend is not ugly.
Actually, Larry,
she's not my girlfriend.
She's just a...
It's cool, buddy.
You don't have to explain
your girlfriend to me.
Can you please stop
licking your fingers?
Do you know how many
germs are on your hands?
And you're putting
them into your mouth.
That's gross. Stop.
Stop it!
I'm gonna kill you!
Hey! Sadie,
enough, all right?
She isn't hurting anyone.
You want to say something,
just keep your mouth shut.
You have never
been nice to her
and now she's getting
aggressive with you.
I told you
this would happen.
I'm sick of
everybody fighting.
What do you think
you're gonna be like
when you grow up?
I don't know. Um...
I don't know.
Do you think you want kids?
Mm-hmm. Just one.
Just one, why?
Because if I have two,
then the other will
fight with the other one.
Does it make you
sad when you fight?
Mm-hmm.
I don't want
anyone to fight.
I love you.
Why isn't anybody talking?
Why is it so quiet?
It's the Sounds of Silence.
Will you stop, Dad?
How many of those
are you gonna eat?
As many as I want.
I'm gonna tell Mom on you.
Try it. See what
you get for Christmas.
Nothing.
Snitches wind up in ditches.
Remember that.
Hey, Peter.
Hi.
Hiya.
All right. See you.
Have a good one.
Peter.
Peter!
Hi.
Catherine.
I'm Joseph's mother.
Oh, right.
No, I know.
Hi, Catherine.
Our kids have gone to school
together for eight years.
Sorry.
Hello, Joseph.
I hear our kids have
been chatting online.
Yeah? I heard that your wife
has been screaming at my son.
And I don't appreciate it.
Excuse me?
She screamed at my son.
Right? She threatened you.
She screamed at you.
She cursed at him.
He's 13 years old,
for God's sake.
What the hell is
the matter with her?
Okay, you better check
her meds and get 'em right.
Okay, you know what?
Why don't you
back the fuck off?
Because that's my lovely,
sweet wife
you're talking about.
Oh, I need to back off?
Yeah, you need to back off.
Because your kid
is an animal.
He's a fucking animal.
Why don't you
put him on a leash?
Turn around,
turn around, turn around!
If he insults my
daughter again,
I'm gonna hit him
with my fucking car.
Got it?
In fact,
ifyou insult my wife again,
you know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna show up
at your house
when you're sleeping
and I'll take your iPad
or your iPod or your iMac
and I'll shove them
up your fucking iCunt.
I got nothing to lose.
Your kid is the problem.
My kid is a fucking angel.
Turn around.
I don't have
time for this shit.
So I'm keeping it together,
but if I wasn't at
school right now...
Touch my... Touch me?
I didn't touch your...
You touched my upper breast.
I didn't. I didn't.
I got right
below your shoulder.
You got right here.
You actually...
He hit my nipple.
You what?
You're insane.
Why would you do that?
Did you just
touch my mom's nipple?
He just touched my nipple.
Why would you do that to me?
I poked you
on the shoulder.
I have very high nipples.
I touched your shirt.
What do you think
is under my shirt?
I just...
My breasts
are under my shirt.
Your shoulder.
He just touched my breast.
Well, that's a funny
place to put a shoulder,
on my boob.
Hello? There are
children around.
This isn't over.
This is not over.
You're gonna be sorry.
Let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
And why the fuck
would you believe Desi?
You just admitted it.
Did l?
You stole $12,000 from me,
Jodi, and I need
you to pay me back.
Could you at least
give me a referral?
You babysat my kids
while you were on OxyContin.
Oxycodone.
Well, oxycodone.
Oxycotton.
OxyContin?
Oxykitten.
What's Oxykitten?
Meow.
Jodi, you put me in danger.
Me and my family.
It was a cry for help.
Help. Help.
Why don't you help me?
Just help.
You didn't help me.
Are you high right now?
Help me.
Is that about me?
Is that the cops?
Is this a set-up?
I need to go.
Okay, see you later.
Fuck you, Debbie.
Fuck you.
Joseph was very upset
when I spoke to
him about this.
So I thought it
was important that we
join together and
work this through.
Absolutely.
We're gonna work
through it,
but Debbie told my son
that he looked
like Tom Petty,
in a negative way.
Who's Tom Petty?
You know who
Tom Petty is.
And she said that if she
had to come back
that she was going to...
"F" up his pussy-ass,
which is what she said.
Oh, my...
Are you serious?
I didn't.
I would never.
To a child?
Your son has been
defiling my daughter's
Facebook page now for months.
These people are liars.
He said that my
son was an animal
and that if I didn't
keep him on a leash,
that he would hit
him with his car.
Did you say that?
That's ridiculous.
Who talks like that?
You do.
He didn't say that.
He said it to me.
No. What I said
was that we need to keep
an extra eye on our kids
because with all
the technological advances,
they need to learn to
use them responsibly.
No. What he said to me was...
He called me an iCunt.
A what?
Language, Catherine!
Language.
I'm quoting!
How am I gonna relay
what these two nutballs
said to me, unless I say it?
Can you please not
talk like that, Catherine?
Music Man is
rehearsing next door.
Sorry, fucking Music Man.
Maybe if I looked
more like this
fake bullshit couple.
Looks like they're
in a bank commercial.
That's what you
look like.
Like you're a bullshit
bank commercial couple.
None of this
talk is productive.
I would like to rear up
and jackknife my legs
and kick you both
in the fucking jaw
with my foot bone.
You're just really
scaring me.
This is what happens
when you corner a rat.
You corner me,
I will fucking
chew through you.
I'll chew through you.
Catherine,
you're better than this.
Fuck you, Jill.
You're a horrible
fucking woman.
This is why everybody
hates you, Jill.
This kind of shit.
Ineffective.
Fucking bullshit hair.
And I'm glad
your husband died.
Because you're
a fucking asshole.
He probably killed himself.
Okay, Catherine,
I think we know
what's happening now.
Now you know what
we're dealing with.
I'm not gonna
eat that chicken.
Why not?
Because I feel
like I'm gonna be
a vegetarian.
Can you become
a vegetarian tomorrow?
Uh-uh.
You guys
have been reading my texts?
No, we haven't.
Yes, we have.
We're supposed to
keep an eye on you.
How did you find out?
Joseph told me
that you flipped out
on him and his mom.
And you guys are nuts,
and I agree.
All right, you know what?
Don't be disrespectful.
You're the ones
who are disrespectful.
Reading my texts is like
reading my diary.
And you were really
sweet on your iChats.
We were really proud of you.
Yeah, we were going to
give you your computer
and phone back.
Fuck you!
Okay, there's the first
official "fuck you."
Okay, that is not
how we talk to each
other in this house.
You guys talk to each other
like that all the time.
And to Joseph and his mom.
You made Joseph cry.
Joseph has a crush on you.
You like a boy who cries.
Shut up, Charlotte.
You guys so desperately
want me to be so perfect
and to make no mistakes.
Well, you two
are fucking insane.
Okay.
All you do is fight,
or you don't fight,
which is even worse
because it looks
like you hate
each other for weeks.
You obsess over
every little thing I do,
and you don't trust
in me or believe in me.
Well, I'm fucking sick of it.
Yeah, I said "fuck."
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Ground me forever,
I don't care.
I don't care about anything.
I hate everything.
Everyone's going crazy.
I don't care if I have
no friends.
Are you still
upset about Lost?
Of course I'm
upset about Lost!
You guys took away my shit
before I could watch
the last two episodes.
And I don't know
what the fuck happened!
She's becoming
just like us.
I hope I never get my period
if this is what happens.
Where did you find this?
I stole it.
Thank you.
No big deal.
Our kids are fucking crazy.
And it's our fault.
Do you think there's anything
we can do to turn
it around, or...
Sadie's 13.
She might be
a lost cause.
Where did she learn
that kind of language?
We don't talk like that.
I have no fucking idea.
Do you think Sadie
is this crazy because of us
or is it hormones
and Lost?
J. J. Abrams.
He's ruining our daughter.
Yeah.
That fucking geek.
I feel bad for us.
All of a sudden,
we're like a magnet
for negativity.
Why do people
keep attacking us?
What did we do?
We're just doing our best.
Should we talk
about our fight?
I think we're
under enough pressure.
Let's just let
it go, this time.
Yeah.
We can give
each other a break.
All right, great.
Thank you.
And I'm sorry about my dad.
You're right.
I'm sorry that he's just
an endless mooch.
The truth is that
this isn't about us.
It's about our parents.
We're not even
mad at each other.
We're mad at them.
Exactly. Exactly.
Let's just take away
our parents' power
by loving them.
Can we do that?
Yes.
Thank God.
I kind of feel
better already, do you?
Do you?
I do.
I love you.
I love you, too.
It's not us,
it's them.
Totally.
What are you doing?
We have to get
ready for the party.
I just watched
the last episode of Lost.
Okay.
You know what?
We don't have time
for this right now.
We have a lot of
people coming over.
They're all dead.
What?
Jack, Kate, Sawyer...
I don't care about
the show right now.
Jin, Sun...
Okay? I need you to
just get in the shower,
get dressed.
Let's just put it on hold.
Walt, Juliet...
All those people.
Don't think about Losttoday.
Tomorrow, Lost, all day.
I can't wait to hear about it.
Jack? No way, really?
Right now, shower.
I don't make fun of
your stupid Mad Men.
First of all, I don't get
worked up over Mad Men.
That's because
Mad Men sucks.
What Don Draper
has gone through
beats whatever Jack
is running from on
some fucking island.
Bunch of people
smoking in an office.
It's stupid.
You're getting me off topic.
Just, please, get dressed.
Hello.
Hi.
I'm glad you're here.
I need a buffer
in case it gets weird.
Oh, well,
I'm ready to buff.
Grab these napkins.
Let's buff. Okay.
So, that's the girl
who works for you.
Yeah. That's her.
Works for Debbie.
She seems nice.
My wife would
never let me have
a hot employee like that.
Yeah?
No.
Every woman
who works for us
Iooks like they've
been in some kind
of horrible accident.
I'm taking control,
and now you're my slave.
Are you comfortable with that
around your husband?
Oh. Pete wouldn't know
what to do with that.
Do you think
our wives are looking
at us right now?
Oh, definitely.
Yeah.
They look
like pedophiles.
Thank you.
The girls are so
excited you're here.
They're all outside.
Hi.
Hey, how are you?
How are you, man?
Good to see you.
Happy birthday, Pete.
How wonderful to see you.
Thank you, Grandma Molly.
You're wonderful.
And look at my gorgeous,
gorgeous, gorgeous.
No, I get that.
I'm just wondering
why I should do it.
Pete, Jason's here.
Peter, hi.
Hey, how's it going, Jason?
You look well.
Thank you.
How do you like
what I've been
doing to your girl?
How you like
Debbie's "after" body?
It's nice.
Come on. Show him.
Look at this.
It's beautiful.
Look at that "after" ass.
Now, it starts here.
But it used to start here.
And I brought it up.
You're welcome.
So, are you a trainer?
Yes.
Oh.
But not just physical.
Spiritual.
I'm sort of a guide.
Mm-hmm.
You guys should talk.
I think you'll get along.
Come here, honey.
I gotta tell you something.
Yeah.
Who's that in the pool?
Mine.
Hello.
Hello, Debbie.
How are you?
Good.
Remember my husband, Pete?
Oh, right.
I didn't recognize
you with the long hair.
Oh, yeah.
I've been growing it.
Happy birthday.
Thank you so much.
Very old Scotch.
Wow. You know...
I hope it hasn't expired.
No, Scotch doesn't expire.
It improves with age.
Yeah. No, I know.
Thank you so...
That's nice.
Come on in.
Sure.
Sorry.
So, what do you do
in Chino, Oliver?
I'm a surgeon.
Wow. What kind?
That's great.
Mainly of the spine.
My specialty is
scoliosis surgery.
My mom used to talk to me
like I had scoliosis
because I'm a little hunchy,
but that's a different thing.
Well, you definitely
don't look right.
Hey!
Sorry we're late.
I was in the lab,
cloning myself.
We're gonna have
another seven tomorrow.
We cut their hair differently,
so we can finally
tell who they are.
You like
the new haircut,
Travis?
I'm Jack, damn it!
Oh. Of course.
Larry, this is my father.
Really? How are you?
Oliver.
Oliver?
"Can I have some more?
"Please, Oliver?
I need a little more, sir."
I love that movie.
You must get
that all the time.
Not really.
My nose
itches right here.
I'm sorry, excuse me.
I'm Claire and
I'm Larry's wife.
Very nice to see you,
but I'm gonna go get the kids.
We won't see her
now for the whole day.
I'd help, honey,
but you know I got
the blood pressure,
and I don't want to.
Can I get you a drink, Dad?
Yeah, a little white wine.
White wine?
Yeah.
Heavy stuff.
So, who knew that
Debbie had a dad?
Where have you
been for 15 years?
Never seen you at Hanukah
or Christmas or Ramadan,
nothing.
How you get out
of all that stuff?
Do you have a wife?
Yeah, my wife's at home.
Why didn't she come?
Uh, construction.
They're sanding our deck.
You let the woman
sand the deck?
She supervises it. Yes.
Okay.
Hey, guys.
Hey! Look how big
the kids are!
Sadie!
Hi, Larry.
Hi, Sadie.
Mom. Who's Oliver?
What do you mean?
Is he your dad?
Is he my...
He's my biological father.
What does that mean?
It means that my mom,
Grandma...
He and my mom had a baby,
and that was me.
Oh, so you're
our grandpa?
Well, why don't
you ask your mother?
Yeah. I guess so.
Then that would make him
your grandfather then, yes.
Do you want him to be?
Yes, then we get
another grandpa.
Come on.
Well...
Another grandpa.
Trampoline time.
That was deeply
uncomfortable.
At least that pretty girl
was here to divert
our attention.
Oh, my gosh. Hi.
Me, oh, my.
I did not see you there.
Hi.
I saw you there.
Did you guys come together?
Are you a couple?
No, we didn't come together.
No, absolutely not.
I'm sorry, I thought...
The moustache is a little...
- Mmm. That's fair.
- I just assumed.
This is
a straight-man moustache.
What is the difference between
a gay man's moustache
and a straight
man's moustache?
The smell.
Uh, excuse me.
So, spinal surgery.
It just seems to me
to be at the top
of the surgery chain.
Well,
we're not cardio,
we're not neuro,
but I like to think
we're an important
part of the spectrum.
Do you operate
every single day?
Most days.
Multiple times a day?
Three, four times.
So, what's the price range?
Like, if I wanted a...
I'd rather not say.
It's so big,
you're embarrassed to say.
I wouldn't say "embarrassed."
Are there hunchbacks today?
Of course.
I've never seen one.
Well, that's because
there are spinal surgeons.
That's because of you.
Each time I don't
see a hunchback,
you're getting
that much richer.
You like The Beatles,
don't you?
Who doesn't like The Beatles?
Nobody.
No, nobody.
So funny. You're so funny.
What is your sun sign?
Libra.
Oh, boy.
That's not good.
No, sir.
Not for me,
that's not good.
Sexually, we're
completely incompatible.
That's not true.
Right?
That's such a shame.
Yeah, it's as bad as it gets.
You don't know.
What is yours?
I'm a Cancer.
Really?
Is that good?
Wow.
What does it mean?
That's kind of strange.
Well...
Taurus and Cancers are,
sort of, soul mates
of the Zodiac.
We're, like,
perfectly compatible.
And I balance what
you lack and you
make up for what I lack.
And a quiet Cancer
almost always
has a huge penis.
You're making me embarrassed.
Thank you.
No. Fantastic.
Oh, I wanted
to make a toast.
Thank you guys for coming.
Thank you so much.
Pete's turning 40.
Weird.
And we're ready to start
this new phase of our
lives with open hearts.
Ready to just choose joy
and forgive everybody.
So, thank you all for coming.
Wait. Forgive who?
I think she just
means in a general sense.
You know, just put
the past behind us...
And live without resentment.
But, specifically,
who are you forgiving?
I just like to know
the details before
I make a toast.
Right. You and my dad
and, you know, others.
I see.
Well, I know you have
some issues with me,
but I'm curious,
what's he in for?
Before today,
nobody even knew
he existed.
Well, my parents divorced
when I was really young
and we don't spend
much time together
and I'd like to work on that.
Just like we
would like to work on
how you have
financial issues.
She's talking about
all the lending and
the borrowing and...
I know what she meant.
You are a beautiful woman,
but you are not
totally maxed out.
I would say,
honestly, you're a six.
Oh.
A six-and-a-half.
I could make you an 11.
Really?
When I found Deb, she was a 7.
And now she's a 12.
I wanna be a 12.
You can't be lazy.
I don't wanna be lazy.
Look at me.
You cannot be lazy.
I won't be lazy.
Do you know how
she got her body?
How?
Bodies by Jason.
Wow.
Say it.
Bodies by Jason.
Say it again.
And now just say, "Jason."
Jason.
Again.
That sounds right, doesn't it?
Yeah.
What the fuck is
happening right now?
When was the last time
you two saw each other?
I'm curious.
Actually, we had
lunch together last week.
Uh-huh.
And before that?
It's been about seven years.
Seven years?
That's a joke, right?
That's like two Olympics.
But I'm the bad guy.
All right, Dad.
What Debbie doesn't
understand is it's not bad
to help out a parent.
And it's certainly
not bad for a parent
to help out a child.
I'm sure Oliver would agree.
Well...
Are you really
doing this right now?
Am I doing what?
I didn't start the toast.
Are you really
about to hit up
my dad for money?
What? He does four
operations a day.
It's perfect.
It helps everybody
and it relieves
his guilt from all
the abandonment issues.
You can't buy forgiveness.
Right, Pete?
I don't think anyone
is looking for handouts.
I mean, you know...
We'd pay him back.
If you two are in a bind,
I'd be more
than happy to help.
No. It's not good
to borrow money
from family members
because it
causes resentment.
Remember?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What do you
want me to do? Okay.
Admit that my life is shit?
Is that what you want
me to say? You happy?
Aren't I allowed a little joy
with these children I never
wanted to have?
You have never
once stopped
asking us for money.
Family helps family.
It's true.
Look, I don't expect
you to fully understand.
Your dad left.
You're broken inside.
It's not your fault
you can't feel love.
There's something
that you can't...
This is coming out wrong.
You know what?
I would rather have
my dad than your dad.
Because he
doesn't drive me crazy.
You know what's
the best quality
my father has?
Is he asks for nothing.
I don't know what the fuck
he's thinking right now.
Look at that.
Nothing. Nothing.
I don't even know him.
And I turned out
perfectly fine
without his input, okay?
I just figured out
what your problem is.
You hate Jews.
Which is so odd
because your
children are Jewish.
Don't play
the Jew card, Larry.
I'm not playing
any Jew card.
Seriously, it's used up.
You can't use up a Jew card.
That's the whole
point of a Jew card.
That's right.
You can't use it up,
it goes forever.
You know what?
I have to go.
Yeah, great.
What a big surprise.
Bye, Oliver. See you later.
See you in
another seven years.
Make sure and say goodbye
to the grandkids
who you met today.
You know, nothing I do
is right because of you.
Nothing. No matter
how hard I try,
I'm just the asshole here.
But you know what?
You know what I realized?
It's you. You're the asshole.
Good luck
working that out.
Happy birthday,
and go fuck yourself.
Hey, see you when
the Cubs win the pennant.
I'm gonna go
light the candles.
Just get it going, okay?
Maybe we should
try the toast again.
You know, can you be quiet?
You just threw
me under the bus.
No, I don't...
You threw me under the...
You threw me under the bus.
We agreed to let go
and forgive,
but then you started
ripping into my dad
like a crazy person.
I'm not ripping into
your dad.
I'm just saying to him
what you say to me.
Don't be
such a ball-buster.
I am not a ball-buster.
You make me one.
I am a fun girl.
I am fun-loving.
I am a "Good-Time Sally."
I dance hip-hop.
I cannot believe l
have wasted my whole life
busting the balls
of people who have
no balls.
I'm the only one
here who has any balls!
God damn it.
Mom?
Mom? What are you doing?
What?
You're smoking,
and in the front yard?
No! No, they're Barb's.
Mom!
Since when have
you been a smoker?
I'm not a smoker.
I thought you
said smokers die.
I'm not smoking.
I wasn't smoking.
I saw you.
No, I wasn't.
Mom, you're smoking?
Deb, you can't smoke,
you're pregnant.
You've been doing so well.
You're pregnant?
No effing way.
I don't want
another sister.
I don't want her
as a sister.
I'm sorry, I'm so sorry.
It just slipped out.
Are you pregnant?
Since when
are you pregnant?
Since when do you care?
You don't even
want another baby.
You have no idea
what I want.
I want an Asian baby.
We're not gonna
have an Asian baby.
Yes, we are.
They're not Asian.
Sadie.
We'll buy one.
Shut up, Charlotte.
You shut up.
Shut up, Sadie!
Shut up, Charlotte!
Shut up!
Okay, Sadie, shut up.
Shut up, Charlotte!
Shut up!
Okay, stop saying "shut up"!
You're pregnant?
Since when are you pregnant?
When did you find out?
Will you stop
eating cupcakes, please?
Stop eating cupcakes!
Hey, we just heard.
You're having a baby?
See, it can happen to anybody.
That is so wonderful.
Let me give you a hug.
Fantastic, congratulations.
It's wonderful.
I'm so happy for you.
This is too adult for you.
Let's go outside.
Congratulations.
Well, I guess
we're stuck together
then forever then, right?
Weren't we always?
You didn't even
want a baby.
Of course I do.
I never said that.
I didn't want one
if I could choose.
I should put that
on a Hallmark card.
That's beautiful.
Debbie...
Good luck with
the pregnancy, Debbie.
But please,
take care of yourself.
It's a much riskier
pregnancy after 40.
I'm not 40.
Of course you are.
You were born on
December 5th, 1972.
I'm not 40.
How do you know?
I was there. I'm the one
who took your mother
to the hospital.
Well, that's not
what she said.
Your mother was in labor
for only about 20 minutes
You couldn't wait to meet me.
Can you imagine that?
I don't even know you.
You can't just
come into my house
and reminisce.
Look, maybe we're
just not meant to be
in each other's lives.
I'm not sure this
was such a great idea.
Wait a minute.
Hey, wait a minute!
You did leave and
you didn't come back.
My first life was ruined.
I did my best with my second.
So, I ruined your life?
I was eight.
People do better
when I stay out
of their lives!
That's what
my son tells me.
You think my
life is so perfect?
I've got a 13-year-old
who's a pothead.
I've got a wife who's
keeping Zoloft alive.
You never said that before.
You don't think I wanna
talk to you about this,
to share it with you?
It's just not our way.
We don't talk to each other.
We don't know each other.
And I thought that's
the way you wanted it.
How do I get out
of this?
How do I get you all
to just help me
down off the cross?
You sound just like Sadie.
Who's Sadie?
No, your daughter.
Your younger?
The big one.
Your older.
I know, I know that.
A wonderful girl.
Hey, guys,
some of us need to leave.
Would this be a good
moment to sneak out?
Where is Dad going?
Best birthday ever!
Oh, shit!
Bike lane, asshole!
Fuck you, you Twilight
pimply-ass motherfuckers!
Your dad's still here.
I know.
It's kind ofweird.
Where the hell is Pete?
Um...
Is it okay if Joseph
hangs out here for a while?
Mm-hmm.
Hi, Joseph.
Hi.
Do you want a piece of cake?
Oh! Yeah, sure.
Thank you.
All right, then.
They are so cute.
So cute.
He looks exactly
like Tom Petty.
Go around.
Watch it, watch it!
Hey, Pete! Great party!
Yeah.
The best!
And then we shake it.
And then
a restaurant comes up.
Dad, excuse me.
I'm gonna go look
for Pete right now.
Would you mind staying
with the girls for
just a little bit?
Well, ifyou want me to.
Ifyou don't mind.
You don't have to.
Sure.
Can I let Sadie
show me the last
episode of Lost?
She asked me if l'd
seen it and I haven't.
Yeah, that would be nice.
Thank you.
She said we could watch it.
Come on.
I'm gonna let you
watch Lost. Come on.
Is it scary?
I'll cover your eyes
if it gets too scary.
Are you mad at me?
Did I say something?
Shh. Larry, please.
Are you fucking kidding me?
You opened your door on me.
I didn't open my
fucking door on you.
I opened my door!
Aw, fuck.
I was right there!
You're supposed to look
before you open your door!
I was in a fucking bike path!
That's a blind spot.
There's no fucking bike path.
It's a residential section.
Get your head out of your ass.
Pay attention!
Open your goddamn eyes.
What are you doing,
sleepwalking?
You're supposed to look
to see if a biker's
coming through.
You're supposed to look!
It's not my job to
look out for you.
You look out for yourself.
I don't look out for you.
I don't see you.
I don't know
where the fuck you are
or what you're doing.
No one is ever
looking out for me!
I need your name
and your number.
Why?
Because you're
gonna pay for my door.
Fuck you!
Why don't you pay
for my bike and my face,
you fucking prick?
Don't disrespect me.
Are you sure
that's him?
I don't think that's him.
I gotta write down
your license plate.
"Range Rover of Sunland."
What are you doing?
Ow.
I guess the party
didn't turn out
like you planned.
It wasn't a good party.
Hi.
I'll bring you in
as soon as his
X-rays are finished.
Okay. Is he okay?
Okay.
Yeah, he has a broken rib
and he's been crying
a little bit.
But he'll be fine.
You know, Pete was
never a real fighter.
But that's why he married you.
That's why he loves you.
Because you're
the fighter.
And you need that.
One person
in a relationship
has got to punch.
Do you mean
that in a good way?
Oh, it's a high compliment.
Thanks.
Listen, I know what
you're worried about.
You think he's
gonna turn into me,
but I don't think
it's gonna happen.
He's smarter and
probably a little cuter.
A little less Jew-y.
Although after 50,
that's all gonna change.
Be prepared to wake up
one day with a rabbi.
But the good
news is, you know,
he'll love you forever.
That's in our DNA.
We stick around.
He worries
about you, you know.
It puts a lot of
pressure on him.
I know, I just don't have
anyone else to
talk to about it.
Why don't you
talk to Claire?
If I open up to her,
she'll leave me.
No, she won't.
Mmm.
Larry, she loves you.
I know, but there's
a certain point at
which you just can't stay.
I guess it's hard
to forgive somebody
if they don't
formally apologize to you.
Are you apologizing?
I'm very close.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I'm glad everybody's okay.
Okay, thanks.
Oh, thank you.
All right, I'm off.
Okay.
This is awkward.
What?
I need $40 for a cab.
That's funny.
No, I'm not kidding.
Oh, yeah.
You drove me, honey.
I wasn't prepared.
I know.
I only have a hundred.
It's okay.
I'll bring you the change.
All right.
Give him a kiss for me.
I don't get it.
See, it's not sad.
It's happy, because
they helped each other
achieve their destiny.
Great. I'm gonna have
some freaky-ass nightmares.
Hi.
I really liked our
life so much better
before we tried to
change everything.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
I don't want to
keep anything from you.
I love you, you're my wife.
I just didn't
want to let you down.
Are you mad
that I'm pregnant?
No. I'm not mad,
I'm thrilled.
You don't feel trapped?
I sometimes feel
like I trapped you.
I don't feel trapped.
Really?
No.
You should,
because I have trapped you.
You can't go anywhere.
I'm gonna get you pregnant
every 10 years for
the rest of your life.
You can never leave me. Ever.
I never feel trapped
by you.
I'm so happy
to be with you and
I love you so much.
You're my favorite person
in the whole world.
God damn it,
why am I crying
like this?
Something is wrong
with me.
You're pregnant.
Oh, yeah.
Shit.
I was just outside
telling your dad
that I liked him.
What if he
thinks I like him now?
No, he won't think that.
I don't want him to think
I like him that much.
No, it will never happen.
Can you believe it?
This is the craziest
thing ever.
What are we gonna do
with a third baby?
I have no idea.
How are we going to afford it?
We'll sell the house.
We don't have to.
We kind of do.
We'll make new memories
in a new house.
I love you.
Is there anything
you want to do
for your birthday?
It's been the worst
birthday ever.
There is one thing,
but I don't
think you'll like it.
What?
I wouldn't mind
going to see some music.
Would you want to do that?
Yeah.
Really?
I don't believe you,
but you're sweet
for saying that.
How do we break
you out of here?
I can just leave
on my own volition.
It's not a mental institution.
Can you?
Yes.
It's not like
One Flew Over
the Cuckoo's Nest.
Please don't put
a pillow over my face.
Let's get outta here,
McMurphy.
You got it, Chief.
Will you carry me?
You've been carrying me
all this time.
Thanks.
I like this song.
Really?
Why?
Why don't you sign him?
Ryan Adams?
No, he wouldn't sign with me.
Why not? You're the best.
He is in between labels.
Let's go try and talk
to him after the show.
Thank you.
I'm sorry if I'm not
all fancy pants
and wealthy
and showing it all off
with my Vidal
Sassoon haircuts.
Sorry.
Quit slow-blinking at me.
I'm sorry.
Okay...
I would like to rear
up and jackknife my legs
and kick you both
in the fucking jaw
with my foot bone.
That's what l
would fucking love.
I wish my fucking foot
would go right
through your skull.
This is what happens
when you corner a rat.
I will fucking kill you.
You corner me,
I will fucking
chew through you.
I'll chew through you!
Slow-blinking eyes.
I will chew off
your fucking eyelids.
You won't
slow-blink at me,
will you?
Did you drink
before you came here?
No, but I'm gonna
start drinking.
I'm gonna slit somebody
open like a fish
and drink their blood.
That's what I'm gonna drink
ifwe don't start
getting to
the fucking point here.
Probably I'm gonna start
with Karen Carpenter's head.
I'm gonna rip her head off
and I'm gonna drink her blood.
And then I'm gonna come back
and light you on fire.
I'm gonna light
you all on fire.
But I'm gonna
start with you, Jill.
I'm gonna
fucking torch you.
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna go buy
a fucking pickup truck.
And a cord of rope.
And I'm gonna string it
around all three of
your fucking necks
and then drive
around town, dragging you.
That's what I'm
gonna fucking do.
That's completely
uncalled for.
Really, Jill?
Do you think it is?
Fuck off, Jill.
God, everybody
fucking hates you.
God!
That isn't even nice.
Go suck a big
fucking dick, Jill.
That's totally
uncalled for, Catherine.
You're a fucking asshole.
Everybody hates you.
They hate your fucking bob.
And I'm glad
your husband died.
Because you're
a fucking asshole.
He probably killed himself.
I would. Kill myself.
God, I'd kill myself, Jill.
Cut!