Cinema Service Presents
In Association with
Tera Venture Capital & iPictures
Produced by Fun & Happiness
and Seasun Film
We sincerely thank people
in the film industry and
Korea's very first parody feature
(March 2002, The Blue House)
Mr. President!
Just a few winners from the
state youth invention competition
I thought you might
want to take a look, sir
Why don't you just leave it there
Yes, sir
CQCQCQ,
this is DSI, ABO,
Delta Sierra one
Alpha, Victor, Oscar
CQCQ,
this is DSI, ABO---
Hello?
Thanks for picking up
QSA is BSI---
- ARG is---
- Hello?
What do you mean hello?
What is this your first time?
It sure is
Don't worry
You'll get used to it
- May I ask your name?
- What?
I guess you can
just call me Kim
Oh yeah? My last name's
Kim too, you know
- Nice meeting you
- Me too
Guess you've been doing this
for quite some time now, huh?
Yeah I really enjoy it
It's a good way of
relieving your stress
I like to get on
it from time to time
Excuse me, but may I ask
how old you are?
42--- born in 69
You're a lot younger than I am
I see how you're new to this
Age really isn't that important
Why don't we just be friends?
A Funny Movie
(March 2002, Japan)
Mission complete!
Director / KIM Sang-jin from
Director Debut/
JANG Kyu-sung
As there has been some diligent
peace making efforts throughout
the peninsula, fear has ignited
among the Japanese extreme
rightists for their minimizing
power in Asia
Especially the million men
patriots led by Hanako---
has been prevalent throughout
Sang-chul Kim, the victim of
earlier murder as you know---
He was the guy that ran---
In Dok-do we stand' website
He was a great guy
As the Japanese history textbook
fiasco was gaining worldwide
attention---
I believe they assassinated the
man to show Japan resistance
Maybe they were trying to tell
us to stay our of their business
Sir!
Don't we know that already?
You're right
But, uhhh--- anyway,
Our No 1 priority is---
getting Hanako in our hands
Hey shithead!
I said not to fuck around
during meetings!
Listen when I say shit
You fuck! You fuck!
Come here, you piece of shit
Come here!
What does your father do?
- He's a gangster, sir
- What?
A gangster?
Are you trying
to fuck with me?
You're fucking with me,
aren't you?
So are you happy now that
your father's a fucking thug?
Are you happy now?
Stupid fuck!
I never said
I was proud of it
Let's go Gabdu
Hey, you Fangbo!
Stop right there you---
- Sir
- What?
I think you made a mistake
His father really is a gangster
What?
You serious?
He's the KP lead and---
I'm the vice lead
Hey!
I thought you were kidding
You're right, I was
What the---
Are you guys trying to
fuck with me here?
You think this is a joke?
You fucking shithead!
Don't ever fuck
with me like this
- What is this?
- Pardon?
This isn't what I wanted
This here is what I wanted
How can you do this to me?
Why do you think I paid you?
I was much better off before
You're making things rather
difficult for me here miss
How is this better than now?
How do you cut it like that?
I'm a doctor, not a sculptor
What?
Why couldn't you?
Please take a careful
look at the angle here
To hell with this
In any case, this surgery
doesn't count It's bull shit
- UhhhUmmm---
- I'm out fuck
- Philosophy
- Yale
- Economy
- Yankee
Yankee?
Those suckers
- Buffalo
- October
Wait!, You were supposed
to use E, not B
You're right, I'm sorry
Okay
- Escape!
- Integrity
Give me a break here
What's wrong with integrity?
Whatever---
Enough of that!
Guess I won
You want to go for
one more round?
- I'm good now
- What do you mean?
Isn't this great? Playing
games I never played before---
There are tons of other
games out there you can play
You know, there's Beer-pong,
Bull-shit, Waterfall
There are plenty of'em
Really?
How do you play them?
Well---I can't exactly teach
you over the radio---
Why don't I teach you when
we meet up in person?
Okay!
- Are you sure this is the Okryu's?
- Yes sir It's Okryu's Seoul
Why didn't you show up?
Hey, Mr. Kim
I do understand---
how you'd be
ashamed to meet me,
but you still should've
kept your word
What are you talking about?
I waited two hours
in the rain
What do you mean, rain?
Come on, Kim
You owe me
an apology here
You're the one
that should apologize
Were you waiting at Pyongyang's
Okryu's or something?
Of course, I was at Okryu's
in Pyongyang
Where the heck else?
What did you just say?
Pyongyang instead of Seoul?
Seoul?
Oh my lord!
Your voice sounds rather familiar
from that South Korean news
You know what, your voice
sounds familiar as well
Chairman Kim, why
don't we meet up for real?
It's such a shame to throw
this opportunity away
I mean---the talks
we shared so far---
Didn't you mean them?
You're right
After all, we share the
same blood, don't we?
- Let's meet!
- Let's do that
(October 2002, Seoul)
I think our man Kim Jung-ho
here is acting too tough
I mean--- the Japs are go to get
pissed, What are you doing?
Man---that's awesome
Try that again---
A little harder this time
Right on
- I think she saw me
- Fuck, what do we do now?
You guys are from the KP, right?
Jung-ho Kim here
I came undercover
for reasons of my own
Sir, what did you say?
Coke, juice, and iced tea---
is it that hard for you to get?
Did you get hit in the
head when you were little?
- What happened?
- He's gone Where's Kim Jung-ho?
The fucking guy had to make
us pay for his juice and die---
Honey!
Are you okay?
- Don't worry. I just had a nightmare
- What?
I'm so sorry honey
These scissors must be cursed
- What are you doing awake late?
- Just doing some cross-stitching
- Just go back to sleep hon
- Okay
Identification Confirmed
KIM Jung-ho,
who has been brutally---
murdered by Hanako,
heavily---
criticized Japan's rightist stance,
felt compelled to call us
Hanako's not the only Japanese
extreme rightist terrorist,
How can you make such
a shallow judgment?
The first shot is supposed to hit
No 2 neck vertebrate and
the second,
No 3 neck vertebrate
Hanako is the only terrorist to
always fuck up on the first shot
Also,
Hanako was responsible for
the earlier restaurant massacre
So, if you know
her so damn well---
Why the hell did you lose her?
And---
What the hell are you?
What is this, nap time?
It's been over a year since
we took over this case
For crying out loud,
I worked my ass of to---
get to where I am today
So just go out there
and go find Hanako
Get out and go get her now!
Go fucking get her!
Go get her you fucks!
Don't you find it strange?
What do you mean?
We got there right after we
received a call from Kim Jung-ho
So how in the world did
she get there before we did?
Maybe there's an
intel leak within the KP
That's a possibility
Yeah---but it's the KP
we're talking about
Guess not then
Are you joking around?
Yeah
That was so lame
Even the fish here agree
Aren't you going
to marry Sang-mi?
Marriage?
Does that word get your
heartbeat going or what?
I don't know man---
I don't think I can trust her
Man--- she acts all
suspicious sometimes
What are you talking about?
I mean---
I think she got a nose job, and
got her neck line done as well
But I'm not exactly into
the whole plastic surgery thing
Chill out man As long as
she has a nice personality---
Come on man--- you know
what I'm talking about
She goes ape shit on me
sometimes when she's drunk
- Shut up man
- You have to appreciate her
you tell her to come out with us?
Let's all go catch a movie
- Movie my ass
- Did she really get plastic surgery?
- You can tell man
- For real?
Oh---this patient's for cleaning
You're not supposed to take it out
Talk to me now
Can you tell my eye lashes?
- No No Not at all
- Can you tell my nose job?
- The neck line's terrible!
- What?
If he dies, I will too
- Jin-ha!
- Sully!
I'm so sorry for
leaving you here
Sully---
I won't let go
Every two weeks, I'll be
wating at the Ohwa in Sohung
On a crescent moon,
go wait at the Uksu
When the lunar eclipse starts,
come to the Rose garden
Please form a line here
Everyone gets one each
On a half moon, Fang-gum,
on a solar eclipse, Dong-nam
For Halloween, Yong-goong,
and for Thanksgiving, Song-pyun
For New Year's---
For New Year's, come on home
Jin-ha! You should've
known that this is the real me
What's with the rain all of a sudden?
It's impossible to catch a cab
- How are we go to get home?
- Good point
- You want to just run?
- Fuck that
Are you go to pay for
my laundry? Sang-mi,
I'll catch a cab for you
Oh my god
- Think he'll be okay?
- Gabdu?
Yeah I wouldn't worry
Do you remember the
first day we met?
It rained just like today
- Yeah---it's already been a year
- True
I'm ok, please keep
your seat sir
Damn, What the fuck
Honey!
It's not me
this lady over here---
- I don't know her
- What's wrong baby?
Get your hands off---
Come on---hands off
- Come on---hands off
- Honey---
- Darling! Darling!
- What the heck!
- Darling--- Darling!
- Come on---hands off
You know I'm really not her
honey or anything
It's okay--- she's just
sort of out there
- Off! Off of me you---
- Honey!
- Just get your frigging hands off!
- Honey--- Honey!
- Off! Off of me you---
Please--- Jesus--- get your stupid
hands off of me please
Please--- off of me------------
leaders, Chairman Kim's visit
to Seoul has been confirmed
The schedule visit---
will focus on dialogue involving
a united team at the 2002 Worldcup
to be held in Korea and Japan
They'll arrange the event so that
the Japanese emperor could attend
The emperor will apologize
to the Koreans---
Stupid fucks
We're at war!
Great Japan Forever!
The soldiers have worked day
and night trying to secure---
the Japanese honor
However,
the corrupt and scandalous
Emperor has pledged---
to apologize to the Koreans
Us Million-men brotherhood
will not compromise and fight
Japanese Empire forever!
Rebuild the great East!
Fuck the joint Worldcup!
Shouldn't we call captain first?
I worked for this---but it's obvious
that some didn't have to
Just suck it up
Now we speak Korean
There! There she is!
Shoot her! Come on! Shoot her!
Ms Bang!
Please answer this!
Just one comment please
That piece of shit
Stop the car for a sec
You my son of a bitch!
It's me dog
- What's up man?
- What's up my friend?
- What's up dog?
Roll down the window
Hey friend!
You want to go for a few drinks?
Why the hell not?
What about the customers though?
Friends don't wait man
- Okay, right on
- Hey Mr.
Let's hurry up here
Who are these guys?
- Throw these guys out
- Yes, sir
PPX?
Conspiracy fund?
You stupid fuck
Yes, we have the PPX
But---there's a slight problem
with the fund here, sir---
I mean--- the cab drivers
here are sort of rough
Hello? Hello?
Why are the million men patriots
trying to attack the gas station?
To come up with
the conspiracy fund
- Give me the money!
- I don’t have any money
Just give me what you got
Takeshima is online
Long time no see
Good seeing you
My family is---
Everybody's okay?
I miss them
You got---
What?
Come on--- what?
You got really pretty
- They did a good job
- What do you want?
What are you trying to say?
Stop mumbling
You didn't practice
typing, did you?
Stupid---
Hey Hanako!
Next one's sort of long
Watch before you leave
Emergency situation!
Totally bankrupt!
Help needed!
Mone---
Why are you doing this?
What do you want me to do?
- Lend me some money
- I don't have any money
I spent it all on my surgery
come on--- lend me just a little---
The guys are starving
Did you at least bring the PPX?
Don't tell me you forgot
That's been taken care of
Just do as planned
Can you give me some more?
Do whatever you want then
And next time, just call me
Don't ever page
me to the PC cafe
You can't even type
- Who's this?
- Anyone order beef LoMein?
Do you have to
order so damn late?
Jesus fucking Christ
What do you think we are?
Seven fucking eleven?
You always have to
order when I'm sleeping
Shit Forgot General Tso's
Whatever---
that comes to ten bucks
Man, the food's not sitting well
I think it's because we've been
eating shit food all day
If you're go to work,
you need to eat well
If you ain't go to eat that pickle
and onion, let me get that
Speak Korean you fuck
Sorry
Chopsticks
Great Japan forever!
Can I get those
chopsticks please
I have a question, sir
Why do they say chopsticks when
when you barely do any chopping?
That's true---
Just like you don't drum
anything with drumsticks
Tough question---
This is why I never
liked English classes
boys are struggling
living on chinese and all---
But if we complete this mission,
we're talking
some serious dough
Alright boys,
number crunching time
Today, I would like to talk
about the 'Hungry Spirit'
HUN---Uhhh---
That's right
It means you're fucking starving
That LoMein you boys just had---
That's actually symbolic of
the Korean 'Hungry Spirit'
Of course there are others
like Wonton soup
Listen!
Why all the Korean actresses
are on a roll these days?
It's all about the 'Hungry Spirit'
Hungry---
What' s that chick' s name---
Choi (Beep), right?
They call her wonton soup
That girl worked her ass off
since she was little
She practically lived on
wonton soup all her life
And mommy, mommy!
- I won the Oscar
- Good for you
But now that she' s successful
she married that baseball player
Cho (Beep) from Junichi Dragons
I heard she's pretty happy
And still keeps her tits perky
It' s not Junichi,
it' s Yomiuri Giants, sir
Listen!
Listen to me fuckheads
From now on,
you' re all fucking
dead if you talk back to me
Get the hell out now
Except for you boy
Just stay still assneck
Hey, fuckface
Koo' s Yomiuri
you fucking moron
Last month,
there was an incident---
involving a theft
of PPX liquid gas
That's a great terrible
At the same time,
there was an intel that said---
The Million Men Patriots have
successfully moved into Seoul
I'm definitely smelling
something here
In about an hour,
the Japanese
will send over
Detective Watanabe
I believe that the detective
will brief us on the details
And by the way,
one of you---
was ordered to go greet
the detective at the airport
Hey Gabdu,
Why don't you go?
What?
Welcome, Watanabe
Are you Detective Watanabe?
Umm---
I didn't know that they'd
send a lady to greet me
I'm the only one that
speaks Japanese
Let's go!
Did they catch Hanako?
They're still investigating
It's going to be quite
challenging actually
Just watch
I will find that ugly chick
And when she's mine---
She's dead meat
You knew from the
beginning at the airport
Do you want to touch me?
What are you talking about?
Man---this popularity thing---
Everybody wants
a piece of me
I want---
to spank you!
What do you want?
Anywhere you want
Get up! Now make
an isosceles triangle!
Isosceles triangle!
This is a fucking rectangle!
I said a triangle
Oh yeah?
Let's go!
Does that hurt?
Well---I'm okay I guess
This one's going to hurt a bit
How about that?
Better than you thought, huh?
Yes, I like it
Wish I could do more---
but it's my turn now
Hurry up now
Hurry up!
Make me go crazy!
That's not how it's done!
Much harder!
Harder, and harder
Oh, baby!
Spank me hard baby
I love it baby---
Now slow down a bit
No way---
I'm starting to like it
Oh baby, l---
Any leads?
His buttocks have been bruised
and anus heavily damaged---
But I think it was
poison that did the job
I think this is one of
the AT poison needles
This is definitely AT60
The Japs use these though
- Oh yeah---did you have lunch?
- No, did you want to eat?
Maybe some Kimchi soup?
How about some spaghetti?
- Maybe some curry?
- Sure, why not?
We were the only three to know
that Watanabe was coming
That means---
One of us had to have leaked---
it certainly wasn't me
Was it you?
You?
Let's really focus on
confidentiality this time
We really need to
tighten up the security
I think he knew
God He might be the one
Maybe---
Follow me!
I think we know who it is
This man here is another
high profile member of the MMP
He's an extreme rightist
Murakami Hideo
He was a former navy officer
And later joined the MMP
This guy was responsible for
a number of terrorist acts
Hold on--- Didn't Mr. Yoo
serve in the Coast guards?
Hey!
Watch your shadow
- Who are you?
- It's me Gabdu