Buster 19.
Here is Rubber Duck.
Does anybody love me?
Godklere.
Damn.
Log please.
- You have the wrong.
That girl passed me with 120.
When she slowed down
to comb her hair.
She let me not pass.
You have exceeded the
speed limit by 16 km.
It costs one hundred U.S. dollars.
- That's right.
It was worth it.
- What?
That girl has no panties on.
I looked down and there it was.
That was what?
You understand me?
She has no panties on.
Look, she's just waiting.
No panties?
Absolutely nothing.
Ok, I leave it with a warning.
But watch out now.
Breaker 19, bear east
at the l-40.
Approximately 243 to pole.
Thanks, buddy.
Where are you exactly?
I drive east on the same spot.
Where are you?
Mile behind you.
I see you. Nice car you have.
Yes we can.
Spider Mike is behind me
and I am Love Machine.
You know why?
I have a color TV ...
...a full bar behind
me and a waterbed.
All comfort, friend.
Got a bunch of dancers on board?
Yes, he has. A nice couple.
Nice load cattle, you mean.
Quiet here.
Any idea who is there for you?
No idea. Who then?
This is the Duck, old thief.
Jesus, Mike.
It is Rubber Duck.
We have the best first.
I've heard more stories about
you than about Jesse James.
You are now a real
desperado to move.
Love that old machine takes
what he can get.
We will ride his name
into pigsty?
That name has cost me
a lot of money, boy.
Can be honest, but
my fan does not.
So I do it to calm down.
Go ahead.
I'm not going anywhere.
Breaker 19, Cottonmouth
Rubber Duck.
I hear you, Cottonmouth.
Not bear to see.
Everything is green, so get it.
You have me and two others
behind you, over.
It is a pleasure.
The stench here is not to keep.
Who is that? About.
This is the handsome Love Machine
Mack with the fastest available.
Maybe so, but I have heard
that you are a limp rag.
Does he mean me?
I turn you on your alligator.
Mack is my everything that
is on the road rolls.
I do not get behind you, pig.
Slow down, there's
a bear's nest.
Holy shit.
Damn.
You kicked him well on
his tail, h boys.
Hi, RD.
Guys, this is Papa Bear.
It is long since.
- Six years.
Six years.
I should have known it was you.
- What do you mean?
On your cup, Cottonmouth.
- Can not, I have no cup.
Moreover, I lok no offenses committed.
- That'll do, asshole.
I can summon you because
you are 120 reasons.
But I will make you well.
Let's say you 110 reasons.
That will be about ...
- $35.
And insurance does
at one hundred.
Maybe something more.
- Come on, Lyle ...
If you want to avoid it,
I have a nice cell ...
...and your car seized.
How much, Lyle
- Fifty the man.
Dirty bastard.
- Sixty.
Calm down, it is not an auction.
- So what?
I deserve more than him.
I'm broke.
It's my job to my stretch
of road safe.
From me you can rot in the ditch.
- Seventy.
My ass.
- Keep your calm.
Now let's go for something
else he invents.
Lyle, soon hear from us.
- Why?
Our association will
organize the police.
Not me.
I need you rotvakbond not.
Not my league, Lyle.
I'm my own boss.
Then we have one thing in common.
- Two. We begin to die.
What a joker.
What do you know him?
Another of my first parking fine.
And he wants to give me my last.
Would not it about time to eat?
Yes, I do not want.
- You have to treat me.
Raphael's Drive lnn,
here's Rubber Duck.
What is this?
Do you love a sale?
I try to get everything
in one bag.
They sell this?
No, this bird feathers
gives her away.
I'll tell Violet.
- Roger.
Three dollars and a salad.
The Duck is coming.
- The year comes.
He gives you a ride.
- Maybe, as my taxi is not.
2000, I do not go higher.
All the wiring must be renewed.
Take this.
I would not give away.
I lose it.
- I guess.
Want to see my papers?
My driver's license?
Go, baby.
Ok, who wants it
- I prefer.
How much?
- Five dollars.
Ten.
- Twelve.
Fifteen.
- Come on. But is fighting.
Hey, Duck.
How you doing, Jack?
Throw it full.
That red thing is you
probably better.
Did you miss me?
- Yes we can.
Do that somewhere else.
How is it with my black widow
- I can not complain.
How you doing here?
- This is the Duck.
She needed a ride.
And then the XKE?
- I sold.
You know each other?
He told the officer that
I rode around naked.
I might know.
I have sent him to a motel.
He will still wait for me.
Ever ridden in a truck?
Would you like to?
Maybe.
Come, I have a surprise for you.
- That you will. Do not go away.
Are you mad at me
- I mad at you?
Note how this approach.
Is that my elevator
- that's him.
Do not be, baby.
My heart belongs to you.
- Yeah, for one second.
That's not my fault.
When are you going away from
that loser of yours?
He is not a loser.
It's you against him
only one bite.
Yes, especially you, Mr.
I Love Machine.
No, he called pigsty.
- That is temporary.
Wait, I'll call you.
I hear that you are looking for a lift.
- That she has al The Duck.
I'll take you to his truck.
Pigsty ...
Sorry, Love Machine, he's birthday.
Leave him here.
Let's go get that salad.
She likes me though.
- Yeah, that's clear.
It is finished. Come on.
Will you help me unpack
your gift?
What should I do?
Look outside.
What would that vetbuil like
- check insignia, I think.
You should also watch out.
- I am in for a joke.
What will he do?
- Bullying policeman.
How do you know my birthday
- I know so much.
Buster, I receive one?
Yes, I hear you.
- There is a cop on the check.
You know who the bear is? Dirty Lyle.
A really big bag.
Yes, a real fatboy. Like a pig.
When he got out, he bounces
like a ball.
He bounces like a beaver eyed.
He was determined so greedy because
he saves for a brothel.
Here he comes.
It was nice talking to you.
- You're welcome.
Where is the Duck
- Duck What?
Lyle is here.
And he is looking moth.
Pigsty.
How much money do you have?
I have enough, thank you.
I do not know what you run,
but come the hell here.
I'm sorry, I gotta go.
H, boy. How about you?
The bastard.
I'm broke, you know it.
Then I will arrest you for
vagrancy, young man.
Stand up and lean
against the bar.
Stand up.
You heard me.
Thanks, friends.
You know how you can
ruin a birthday.
Let's go. Pack your stuff.
Wait.
They have not done anything
What do you do?
He's crazy, man.
He wants to get me for vagrancy.
But I'm not going to jail.
My wife having a baby.
I must go home.
Really, Lyle.
She goes on everyday.
Does anybody know who
the father is?
Go there.
Dirty bastard, which
I did not pick.
Arizona can now be forgotten.
Go to your car.
- You too.
Stand still.
I've been waiting for you.
- My car broke down.
Excuse me
- Reverse.
Did you see that?
Put it on their behalf.
I just rebuilt everything.
I can not work.
This is my business.
Come on, get out.
Grab him.
- As far as I am.
Come on, Pat.
- Rear, you.
I'll bite your ears
off, big lout.
That's not a cop, but a
donkey with a uniform.
Good fight, Duck.
Help me here. Hurry.
Come on, get out.
Ram it together.
Pull the wires but rather loose.
Pull them out.
- The spark plug wires.
Here he comes close to it.
Unpack the distribution.
- Drag the whole lot out.
Where you going?
- The border.
Why not?
They can make us anything.
Happy birthday.
Best.
Do not stand there stupid.
Give me my gun.
Here it is.
- Give over.
Where were you? Help me.
Give me an ax or something.
I have a nail file.
You know what you can
do with your nail.
Wait a minute.
You say I do.
From the road.
Does anyone have a car?
Do not stand there so stupid.
Wait. I need your car needs.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
- What do you mean, nothing?
What do you have in your mouth?
What are you doing?
Out. Hurry the fuck.
I get you later.
How is my nose after that
collision with that cop?
Yes, I was rather slow.
He is not broken.
It was just as good.
- Yeah, they were
bored to death.
To the widow his knockout kick.
- Yeah, look out.
Where are we going?
It's getting unhealthy.
Do you remember when
we used road names?
Here we come safely to
the state border.
Ok, that I will.
Who else is more with us?
This Old Iguana.
I am a sex-crazed lizard.
I have to get the
plane to Dallas.
What?
- Wedding Pictures.
That plane will not
currently get.
H, get away from.
Where is your direction?
Get the fuck aside.
Give me something to that
crap from my face wipe.
Would you like coffee?
Well, I still remember him.
We go sharp left at
the next junction.
Get her out.
You okay?
She all right?
Pack my stuff.
You okay, ma'am?
- Yes, thank you
White fucking thing.
I had to buy a black truck.
Come on, get out.
I get next to you.
All right, widow
- Yes, apart from
a bruised butt.
One less.
That is ridiculous cop
out that Natoosha.
Give me a T-shirt.
Watch out.
All Jesus, I was Lyle Wallace.
Rubber Duck here.
Was that you, Lyle?
Can you hear me?
I hear you.
You okay or should I
send a meat truck?
That will you need later, bitch.
You go first such exercise
for your back stunt.
I get the State Police there.
And then we will sit behind
your rag, you bastard.
Sorry Lyle, I receive you badly.
In addition, he must
first deal with us.
Ten years.
At least ten years, even
with good behavior.
Here is Lyle Wallace, sheriff of Natoosha.
I've needed assistance.
I'm at the old farm road 109.
I've had enough.
I grab my stuff and get out.
If you want to stop here.
I probably get a lift.
Ok, I'm ready.
Can you hear me? I want out.
Would you like?
We are haunted.
If you look like, you can jump.
Would you also for kidnapping?
That's for teenagers.
...I am well into his thirties.
I'm Bob Buckman, and I
hate truck drivers.
Lyle Wallace County
Sheriff Natoosha.
Get away from me.
It must be here somewhere.
An old achterafweg
to New Mexico.
We're here.
Get ready for a sharp turn.
This is not a road but a path.
- Not even that well.
Do me a favor ...
Is that window shut.
- Is broken.
An invisible escape route.
Now we never find them.
Exactly.
This is the plan: we will
soon draw to suit ...
...Vaseline and I share and
an extra ration of rum.
There they are.
Take that road to the right.
My god, what a dust.
- Close your windows
shut, idiot.
Here at the Duck pigsty.
Are you still there?
My waterbed sloshes
around in tatters.
The heaviest blow that ever
since I've decorated twins.
I follow your smell, pigsty.
A curve.
Watch what you do.
- Shut up. I drive.
Leave it to one side
of the road.
Stay on one side of the road.
Why does he want?
We can not wait.
Watch out, we store for later.
- Shut up.
Word now is not bad.
- I'm not angry, I'm terrified.
I got them.
What is he doing?
- No idea, it is stopped.
These cops can not drive.
Another one of the road.
It's not them.
Here Spider Mike.
The kit sits behind me.
I will slow down some.
You fucking ...
They deserve a windfall.
Shall we let them through?
That seems like a good idea.
They are wise.
Close the door. It starts tours.
Jesus, they take the sheriff
in the sandwich.
There's a bear in
the fall, pigsty.
Here you have certainly
practiced.
Well done, Sheriff.
See ya, cop.
Here Sheriff Lyle Wallace for the sheriff of Natchez.
You read me?
Sheriff Stacey Love here.
I get you
I'm in the 109 behind a convoy
of truckers fugitive.
They are led by a certain
Rubber Duck.
They can be any time over
the state border.
Thanks.
You have our cooperation.
We would like to get
another car ...
...and a clean pair
of trousers.
Attention all cars.
Sheriff Stacey Love You.
Report u.
New Mexico, here we come.
New Mexico?
I have to go to Texas.
Do that again.
This Love Machine to the
boys on the hill.
I receive you. Say it.
What are you doing?
Waiting on you.
We already half hours listening
to what you do.
Congratulations.
Especially the Rubber Duck.
That was good work.
We're famous.
Thanks, guys.
Bald Eagle, Big Nasty and Sneaky Snake
would like to ride with you.
Why not? Join it to.
Thanks.
It is an honor to be driving
behind the Rubber Duck.
And we also have some long-haired
friends of Jesus to us.
Hi, this is Reverend Robert Sloane
with his church moving.
The Bible says nothing that you
can not run full throttle.
Welcome, Reverend.
We could use some
spiritual support.
With pleasure, brother Rubber.
Rubber brother?
Who is this guy?
It is no pastor.
Why do they call you the Duck?
- Because it rhymes with luck.
My dad always said:
Be like a duck.
Calm above the water and paddle
furiously underneath.
What are you looking for?
- A beer. You too?
No, I try to quit.
But give me one of
those T-shirts.
Please.
I lived with a man I
could not really.
He let me do something I did not want.
Paragliding.
Speak louder.
Hang gliding. I've tried.
And it was terrible.
A whole convoy, and they
like racing, but by ...
Luckily it worked.
And your boyfriend
- that was nothing.
Children?
I was married.
I have two children in Spokane.
You see them sometimes
- if I get the chance.
They have a good mother.
Do you have space for Rioolman?
We already have some rats.
But must come.
Pigs, cesspools and nasty
odors ride back.
Welcome to the convoy, guys.
But close.
Here is the Mississippi Flash.
The only things that count in
life are fast trucks ...
...fast women and fast food.
You know how big this is?
Look out, man.
Duck, We have a very convoy.
Check it out.
Incredibly, where do they come from
- everywhere.
Unbelievable. Why?
You should not ask me.
I run for my life.
But they follow you.
No, I happen to front row.
Duck, there's a bear in the air.
Attention, all trucks.
This is federal agent Hamilton.
I immediately ordered
your car to a halt.
You violate federal laws.
Attention, driver
Martin Penwalt.
Sounds crazy, h.
You're under arrest.
Immediately stop your vehicle.
Unbelievable. What is this?
You do it wrong, Hamilton.
You have to say ...
Rubber Duck, you get me?
Rubber Duck.
Rubber Duck?
That is his name-CSF.
Otherwise he does not listen.
Attention, Mr.
Rubber Duck.
Bring your vehicle to a stop.
You're under arrest.
Apparently she told me.
Yes, I have the
quipment checked.
This is a gentegreerd system with
crystal-controlled stage.
We know they are on channel 19.
They are ready.
Sheriff Wallace, we are
down here ready.
Have you pressed the button?
They have their own language.
You try it once.
Buster 19.
This is the bear in the air,
Sheriff Lyle Wallace ...
...Rubberzak to your filthy
black rattletrap.
Use such language in
the ether, Lyle.
You're talking about my
beautiful black truck.
That thing you call a truck ...
...is the most disgusting piece of scrap
that I ever got thrown on the voucher.
And Martin, look for you.
We have a roadblock with
twenty armed men.
Get ready, here they are.
They have orders to you and that piece of junk
to shoot full of holes if you do not stop.
Listen, Lyle.
Go for yourself that
are blocking.
But first look what
is on my trailer.
Chemicalin, Lyle.
High Explosive substances.
I was not around when I want
to ram your barricade.
Are you serious? You're crazy.
Why did not somebody tell me
- he is bluffing.
Here he carries 40,000
liters nitromehanine.
Jesus, he carries explosives.
It's official.
I want to talk the
person in charge.
Go off the road.
There will be a terrible explosion.
Join instantly.
Are you deaf?
Is there someone who
can answer me?
Wait, my mother wants
to talk to you.
Fuck your ass up.
Come again gasp.
My god, they go to my town.
Put all traffic stopped.
Let them through.
Warn traffic. And hurry.
See? Nothing wrong.
They go right to the city.
Damn, that water carriage.
What does that guy?
Here Eighteen Cycling, I would
like to ride with your convoy.
Let them all just drop dead.
With pleasure, eighteen wheeler.
Come on.
Duck, did you see that?
They are on our side.
Residents of New Mexico, has done something
unheard of in our state.
Six trucks were on the border, followed
by the police of Arizona.
Soon more came from.
They are not stopped
by roadblocks.
My God, you see that?
There are not more a dozen,
but 25, 50 or 100.
Ladies and gentlemen, as I can see.
There is no end.
I'm going to find out who they
are and where they go.
So far, no one hurt, just
the pride of the police.
Buster 19, Rubber Duck.
Breakers 19, Rubber Duck.
I'm Chuck Arnoldi, press assistant
to Haskins governor of New Mexico.
He bears the truckers for
years a warm heart.
I can help you solve problems.
What example?
Is this a kind of
protest convoy?
And if so, to what end?
Our goal is to continue driving.
Reverend, you will see this as a convoy
of spiritual or political issue?
Life is a spiritual matter.
Crusher 19, the Rubber Duck.
Arnoldi Here. Can I have a word?
What have you learned, Chuck?
A lot.
The governor would meet
with you personally.
He is willing to talk
with everyone.
He has to establish an area in
Albuquerque for the night.
The police order to
leave you alone.
Bullshit.
Can I frank?
- Go ahead.
This is unofficial.
It may not be on TV or
in the newspaper.
Translate me?
The governor has asked the
National Guard to deploy.
But this is an election year.
And the governor wants the
Senate to find out.
Do you know who they
are along the side?
Do you?
- Voters.
What will they think if the governor
lets shoot you to pieces?
Help him, he can help you.
Do we have a choice?
Spider Mike the Duck.
My wife is about to explode.
I'm almost fucking father.
That is good news, Mike.
I must go now. Best.
We will miss you.
Give my regards to your wife.
This Love Machine.
Good luck with your baby.
It was fun, Mike.
- Bye, baby maker.
Keep the gas on the shelf
until you get home.
Good trip through Texas.
Put the Alamo greetings from me.
Next time I will propose
you my son.
Keep it up for me.
I hope he saves.
They seem to have no blacks.
A wonderful opportunity
to get the headlines.
Liberal, humanitarian headlines.
Truckers. Gear, just gear.
No, normal people.
- Harness.
I think that is more popular
than we convoy.
Let sheriff in Wallace.
Sheriff Wallace was rushed
to Texas left.
What is he in Texas?
It attracts up to 2100 rpm.
Then switch.
He drops back to 1800.
This is good for 18 to 21 tons.
You love this truck, h
- I do not like this truck.
I know someone who really
takes his truck.
He even has his dog
named Kenworth.
For me it is mainly driving.
Where can we find
the Rubber Duck?
Give him a chance to
dry himself off.
I want pictures.
- No, you make no pictures here.
Thurs with your money.
You have ridden fast, Lyle.
- Yeah, but I am tired.
What are you stupid
black bastard.
You're too late for the party.
You had firmly enjoyed.
You know where to strike.
- You offered resistance.
All right, if you
do not save me.
I have not beaten.
I helped you on your feet.
Thanks, but I no longer
need your help.
If I hear about your child,
you let me know.
For now you stay with us.
- Why?
As bait.
Suppose they all come.
- No, that's not his style.
We offer a lot of money
for a story or photos.
What a lot of money
- $500 for good pictures.
For $2500 you get the first
exclusive series.
This is no time to do business.
- I will get dressed.
You're the Rubber Duck.
- I'm in a hurry.
I want to do business.
- I.
You're wet.
- Oh yeah?
Suits you.
Guess, I'm going squander.
Are you the convoy?
Do not worry.
I make sure you get help.
I do not sell story.
Of course. You have to bleed.
That will be best.
You'll need it for the lawyers.
I am concerned.
- Is that so?
Where?
Stop this nonsense.
I try to help.
I know.
I mean, I want to know where
you feel your question.
Because I'm really not.
We can talk it in my car.
Breaker 19, SOS.
Riding a 18-wheelers heading
west that I receive?
Funny Fly Here, I receive you.
Enter a message to Rubber
Duck of the convoy.
Bobby, your timing is perfect.
I'll come back.
- No, wait. What is it?
Buster 19.
Spider Mike's in the cell
in Alvarez, Texas.
He was half beaten to
death and needs help.
Here Mother truck, emergency.
Spider Mike needs help.
I do not know, Bobby.
I've been thinking about all those
people that we welcome ...
...and join us.
They follow us just because
they have no one else.
And that guy in the helicopter
we believe he can use.
Otherwise, he saw us standing.
And so we talk with him.
The less you have, the less
you have to share.
Breaker 19, this is
Midnight Mover.
Spider Mike's in Trucker's
Hell in Alvarez, Texas.
I should only speak
to him first.
Keep everyone away.
Jerry Haskins.
Glad you have time for me.
I know how busy you have it.
Here you have a nice cross-section
of the population.
I know most of you were
well founded ...
...but the question
is what we can do.
I know that your case
must be made clear.
Welcome, Governor. The press is waiting al
- Well, I come.
I first want to talk with
our hero, the Duck.
It's about more than
speed limits, right?
Spider Mike's in the cell.
He was beaten up.
Spider Mike's in Alvarez.
You must get him out.
His back is broken.
- And his skull is
completely open.
Governor, it's nice to have
you here in Albuquerque.
Yes, you're doing
a great job here.
I need to ...
Wait, you know better.
I need to talk alone
with the Duck.
Then we see each other again.
Everybody out.
I think he needs help.
Yes, come.
I promise I will exert all possible pressure.
And that's not enough.
But if I were you I'd just
stay away from Arizona.
Black or white
- What do you mean?
Coffee.
Black. And what would you go?
I want to take you to Washington.
As elected leader.
Because that you are now.
I need you.
Come on, Reverend.
And you need me.
Spider Mike Lyle is stuck in Alvarez.
They have beaten him half dead.
What does Alvarez in Lyle
- I go get him.
Will you guys grow up again?
Would you help us?
- I try.
But I can not always get
criminals out of prison.
Sometimes you sacrifice the individual.
- Bullshit.
He's right.
It can cost months.
You have something nice,
do not destroy.
I'll do what I can, but he must himself
provisionally to survive.
Is that all?
- Yes.
Well, I must go now.
Take over.
You know what we need and
what we fight against.
Take out what's inside.
It helps you.
Are you going away? Why?
Why do you always do
- I do not know.
It was just as good.
Can these people
you do not care?
Do me a favor and help Bobby
find out this thing.
You can do better than
him your word.
You coming back?
Why did not you at that perslui?
They can you.
I did not want.
Can I sell you something?
No, thank you.
All of that loneliness is
a sentimental cowboy.
Windows.
But here I go back.
You said he only would come.
Bye, Lyle.
- Where are you going?
Come back.
Central ...
Where are the keys
- but look back.
I knew you would come, but not
that you would need help.
I did not ask.
They came by themselves.
This is something between
you and me.
Look what you did.
You're a criminal,
lying carrier.
And what are you?
Yourself look at that.
An old piece of
iscarded rubbish.
Say on, what virtues
you doing before?
I am the authority.
Do you understand that?
I represent the authority.
I got shit on you and
your authority.
I'm glad to see you.
They'd have to shoot.
If I had a gun, I did it myself.
And that badge would
you entitle?
Throw him in jail
and get a doctor.
No, he had nothing to do with it.
It was Alvarez.
Forget it.
- I forget anything.
This is not over.
For me.
I'm sorry, man.
Does not worry about it.
I'm really sorry.
I do not like my other
debts to pay.
Crusher 19, to all trucks.
Who does not want them to
Mexico, may now say.
Meeting here. Okay, they agree.
Let them but the tequila ready.
I'm right behind you.
Bald Eagle joins.
And you
- I love Mexico.
Bobby, about 400 meters
to the river we turn.
Did you hear me, Bobby?
Ok children to school.
He wanted me dead drive.
Where are you, Bobby?
I have a problem, Duck,
but I can handle it.
No time for trouble.
We're almost there.
We are behind you and
see you in Mexico.
What's going on?
We save us now. Drive through.
My papers are in the car.
He is coming.
Buster 19.
Here is the bear with his gun.
Front of your door.
Get out of your truck with your hands
up or you go into the air.
Martin, can you hear me?
This is Lyle Wallace.
You can not go along.
Get it out.
I remain.
Get out, I said.
Take the door away.
Duck, can you hear me?
Go ahead, Colonel.
Duck, you're dead. You're dead.
Get out of here.
Ready to fire.
Ready.
Focus.
Fire.
You poor wretch.
A lonely breed.
Loud and proud men.
But not too proud to cry.
Embodies the tradition
of American cowboys.
Ladies and gentlemen, we
are gathered here ...
...to this great American
honor ...
...who gave his life for a cause that
is so important for us all ...
...like many great Americans
before him.
These truckers will now pass ...
...the last tribute to
their fallen comrade.
Can I have an amen
for our sister?
In their Macks, Jimmy's, Caywalkers
fruit trucks, garbage trucks ...
...and even limousines.
All truckers.
From old cars to 18-wheelers.
They keep this country alive.
This controlled individualism
is so important ...
...I was in Washington
the Senate will submit.
You too can contribute
your ideas ...
What are you doing? It is not over.
- They sell tickets.
Write to the White House ...
...and I will support you.
Do or goes with it.
- Bullshit.
Ladies and gentlemen, we will ensure that
Rubber Duck's voice will be heard.
Bastard.
Ever seen a duck that
could not swim?
Stop the truck at.
Ladies and gentlemen, the true
spirit of America ...
Take the FBI man.
I did not warn you.
It is getting out of hand.
He uses the truckers in the
White House to come.
What should the government do?
- What do you think this is?
A parade?
What is he laughing?
Dutch Subtitles by: nonkelwim