It's too little.
What are you saying?
- Nothing
- Go away
You are in charge this time.
My men will do what you say
Your boy is arrogant,
you tell him yourself.
You think who you are? You are so late
Wah Dee hurry,
Big Brother is waiting for you.
It's to get money for
godfather's litigation.
Trumpet wants you to be the driver.
I haven't done it for a while.
But if you Brother Seven wants me,
I'll do it.
If you don't like it, don't do it.
If Big Brother asks me, I'll do it!
O.K. then, wait for my call!
Don't put on airs, little brother!
Let's go!
Wah Dee, I know you don't want to do it.
But Trumpet biases towards us.
After all, he is one of us.
You know...
Favors can never be repaid fully.
Godfather's affair concerns us all.
Trouble again,
if nothing else leave quickly.
- Brother Seven, I'm leaving, good night!
- See you.
Ambulance and police are coming!
It's been ten minutes.
Wait...
I'm leaving first!
Bye Bye!
Manger!
Don't move!
Open the safe! Hurry!
Get up quickly!
You bastard, get up!
- Be quick!
- I'm getting up.
- Open it!
- I'm opening it.
Two cups of coffee and tea.
- Three egg sandwiches.
- Hurry!
Go after him!
Calling control...
Stop!
Don't move!
Stop! Don't move!
Get off! Go!
Let go of the hostage!
Stop! Stop the car!...
Stop the car!
This should be enough for us to enjoy.
Put it away!
Big Brother, he's coming!
What are you doing?
Stay low and keep quiet, it will be O.K.
How did you manage to get away.
Where's the money?
Give it to him!
Police are looking for us.
First, get a place to hide.
Not the right amount.
This is it.
We risked our lives for this.
If you don't want it, fine.
You are taking advantage of me.
So what?
Not happy,
tell your Big Brother to see me.
Don't bother her, she's out of this!
Go away...
What's happening? Who is she?
I used her to get away.
She recognizes all of us now.
Do you want all of us in trouble?
I brought her here, I'll be responsible.
Good, you're responsible.
It's your man, don't leave any trace.
Do it clean.
There are no cars here,
I'll give you a ride.
"The booze sinks in."
"When will it block out my sadness."
"The past will all calm down."
"Unable to break through."
"Unable to see clearly ahead."
"Conflict and coercion still present."
"Treading on a grey path."
"Like the reflection is the abyss"
"Shouldering my sufferings and regrets."
"Your eyes are filled with tears."
"The world is unknowingly filled
with emptiness."
"Woo... please don't leave."
"Thinking of you again."
"Who will cover up for me."
"Want to know you wherever I go."
"Unable to remove the trace."
"Unfortunately we each have to face."
"One's own destiny and goal."
Try to stay home.
Why are you so dirty all over?
Nothing!
Come again when you are free.
Having a late night snack!
Wait! Ah Lin!
Today is your Mom's death anniversary,
go up and burn this for her.
What happened to your hand?
Never mind him, he's always like this.
Are you O.K.?
Let's go in!
Bar girl kills herself for love.
Jumps in the middle of the night.
Moon in the sky, shining on me.
Lost it all at the tables.
Lost all my money.
Why do I have nothing, I'm not a hooker.
Madam, give me some face.
You haven't written the ticket yet!
You better be earlier next time.
Yes, I'll be earlier next time.
I'll be earlier tomorrow
and every other time
Thank you Madam,
I'll be earlier tomorrow.
Interfering with my area.
Hey, who's this?
Wah Dee, don't play.
I've got some important things
to tell you.
Be serious, listen.
The police and the gang
are looking for you.
What you and Trumpet did is out.
The police got hold of Trumpet.
Rumour has it, you sold them out.
Go find a place to hide.
Informer...
Don't run!
Hit, I dare you!
You'll know when we get back.
Get the car!
Turn around, go!
Kong Sir, this is my nephew!
Please give me some face, Kong Sir!
Who respects you? The police or the gang.
- Which side respects you?
- None...
You only look after people's car.
Lean against the wall.
Yes, Kong Sir, he's young...
Do you want to enjoy the air-con
in police station?
Lean against the wall.
Bastard, you dare play games with me!
Don't think you're so great to this man.
Shut up, go away!
Tell me, what have I done!
You'll know later.
You bastard, still putting on airs.
Just because you're police.
My grandfather was also a police.
He didn't put on airs, he cared for me.
Kong Sir!
Go and take a look!
Go nearer if you can't see well!
Told you to get rid of her.
Do you want to see the end of us?
If she wanted to,
she could have identified us!
She might say it
after further questioning.
I don't have time for this everyday.
If you don't want to do it,
I'll get my men.
Get out!
Is it this one?
Too big.
What about this?
Too small.
We've done this so many times.
How about this one?
Too big again!
Say it clearly, then I put it on.
Get on!
Bastard, I'll get you wherever you go.
I'm coming, Boss!
They were welding up there.
- So I placed the papers on.
- As if I owe you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Boss, your car is the most current model.
Good on gas and smart looking, let's go!
Slowly, Boss, slowly! So happy.
Another business.
Wah Dee? Are you OK, out already?
Did Big Brother come?
No, haven't seen him!
Yes, fresh.
Tell Big Brother I'll be at Bamboo Hill.
Good Bye!
What happened?
Did 4336 call back? Try again.
Call 9333, Wah Dee calling.
Call me once he gets Brother Seven.
What time can I get home?
I didn't call the police,
they found my purse,
so they found me.
May I call back home?
They don't know
where I am or what I'm doing!
They will be worried.
I won't be coming home tonight, Ah Sang!
I'm staying with my classmates.
She's leaving for the U.S. tomorrow.
O.K. I know.
Alright, alright, Bye!
Is this your first lie?
Second, the first time was
at the police station.
I'm going to bathroom.
Let's go!
How about one more man, Miss!
Open the door!
Get hold of the girl.
Where are you going? Don't you dare
play games with me.
Cut his hand off.
Trumpet doesn't get this any bigger.
It's his own fault, protecting the girl.
Don't move!
I promised her she will be alright.
Who is responsible if she identifies us?
I'll be responsible.
What are you saying, you wounded my man,
I haven't settled the score with you yet.
Trumpet, I'm his Big Brother,
I assure he'll be responsible.
Wah Dee, let's go!
Go? What about wounding my man?
Now this is settled.
Get away!
- Big brother
- Let's go!
You've bleed a lot!
- Are you alright?
- Leave me alone!
Go home!
Don't follow me!
He comes home only when he's hurt.
Stop nagging such unlucky words.
Did I say it wrong?
Please stop it! It is very irritating!
How is it?
O.K., but a bit lower
and that will be it.
Who's paying me?
Money, follow me! Ma Ma Mia!
Those bastards, we should pay them back.
Yes, stab them back.
Let him sleep down here.
Let's go buy some stuff for soup.
Snakehead soup will help the healing.
First throw this out.
Why is there so much bleeding this time?
You just try letting someone stab you.
Good morning!
Please call 98!
Who's calling 98? Hey, who's calling?
Ah Sang said you're not eating properly.
Hello JoJo, it's getting cold now.
Remember to put on more clothes.
Ah Sang said
you missed the dancing lessons.
You have to continue the lessons.
There are a few universities here.
I think they're not bad.
Aunt Mary's daughter has just arrived.
She knows quite a few boyfriends already.
We've already bought a house here.
- And be good!
- Bye!
Moon in the sky, shining on me.
- Mister!
- Who are you?
What is it?
Do you remember me?
Are you crazy!
There're thousand of girls
passing by daily,
who will remember you.
You called me 'fresh'. Do you remember?
Oh 'fresh', you're something.
He's never been stabbed for a girl.
How is he now?
I've brought him some soup.
Wow, you even brought him soup.
Good, let me have a sip.
- Stop it!
- Shit!
Do you know where he is?
Even if I know I won't say it.
What do I have the gain?
What? $100 for the information? Save it!
Why do I have nothing, I'm not a hooker.
Sorry to bother you!
Allah Ah Tor. Nah mor allah a tor.
Holding a big banana.
Hey Miss, have a drink with me!
Alone? Let's dance!
May I invite you?
Elope...
What? Pretending to be a lady!
Don't stay if there's nothing else.
Go away, why are you following me?
I'm returning your jacket.
And the lighter.
Get on the bike!
Hey! Amigo!
Wah Dee, she's not bad, let's compete.
Alright, bring out your best girl.
Strawberry!
How do we compete?
You in front, I follow,
between 2 lamp-post.
I will pass you.
You're putting money in my pocket.
$10,000! Bring me the keys!
- As you like.
- Bring me the keys!
Clear the field!
Get on!
Get on and don't fall off. Understand?
Are you scared?
Get off if you're scared, get off!
If you're that good, don't fall off.
Ready! 1,2,3.
What are you looking at?
Are you pissed off?
Hold on!
Are you O.K.? Isn't it fun?
It's my birthday,
that's why I looked for you.
- What is it?
- Excuse me!
Hey, we're closed.
- What do you want?
- Buy yourself a drink!
Hey, what are you looking for?
- 17 years old? Are you telling the truth?
- It's true!
Better add more, I don't believe you.
Alright, shall we leave it like that?
When's your birthday?
I don't know!
How can you not know?
I don't know, what's unusual about it?
Why not treat today as your birthday.
We can celebrate together from now on.
Good!
Let's blow together!
From now on, we share the birth date.
- Today, let me celebrate for you.
- OK!
You're terrible.
Go in now.
Wah Dee, wait, this is for you.
It's raining hard, Sang!
Why are you soaking wet, Miss?
And you smell gasoline all over.
It's nothing, Ah Sang!
Take your shoes off and go in.
- Quickly change your clothes.
- I will.
- Be careful you'll catch a cold.
- I know!