Western grip?
Correct.
Just like holding hands.
Holding hands?
Like this?
- I don't know how.
Yamete kudasai.
Ah?
Please stop doing that.
- Can't hear you.
- Ha ha, idiot.
This person must be mute.
Saa, who knows.
I'm just too ignorant.
Hey, you guys are noisy.
Na?
What did you say chibi?
The one you were talking about just now
was the Eastern grip.
Eastern grip?
It's really common...
...just for people like you.
Did you said something wrong?
How old are you?
- Junior High student?
- Middle School student?
Looks like you know a lot.
Get off the next stop.
Mada mada da ne.
Who's that?
Good afternoon!
Thanks for the hard work!
Oi chibi.
We are not recruiting.
Wait chibi.
What is your name?
I'm asking you for your name.
Could it be you are that transfer student...
...named Echi something?
Answer me.
Echizen Ryoma.
So it is.
The prodigy from America.
Show me what you've got.
And you are?
Seigaku regular,
second year student, Kaidou Kaoru.
You'd better not regret.
You will lose.
What did you say.
Well he looks quite cute.
He's really good!
You alright, senpai?
Such beautiful spinning ball...
It's my first time seeing something like that.
Hey, hey, hey, ah Kaidou?
Who's he playing with?
That must be the transfer student
Ryuzaki-sensei was talking about.
Heh, you can even spin the ball
into such an angle.
Snake shot.
Game Kaidou. One love.
Court change.
So it'll be like this.
If it continues like this, he will...
My reaction is getting slower.
I can't be losing to this chibi?
This is a match of perseverance.
I won't lose.
Heh...
This person...
...even knows the Snake.
That is a Buggy Whip shot, right.
It's quite difficult to use...
...since this is my first time trying it.
First time?
Senpai, you sure are sweating a lot.
You'll wet that uniform.
The weather's so hot yet you're dressed so weirdly.
It's not over.
Come!
Mada mada da ne.
That'll be all.
Good afternoon!
Captain...
Playing a match without approval,
twenty rounds around the court.
But I-
Forty rounds.
Yes.
The rest of you start your high-intensity training.
The first years pick the balls.
Yes.
You're the team captain.
Please give me your guidance.
I will join next semester.
First, hand up a registration form.
Ah, okay.
Oyaji.
Oh, Ryoma.
Gave me a scare there,
what're you doing here?
Is your mother doing fine?
It's outrageous.
What were you thinking leaving our hometown?
It's called Seishun Gakuen.
Nothing spectacular.
Why, don't like it?
Don't tell me that to get me into that school,
you brought me here all the way from the States?
Well, you can say that.
How about it?
Let's have a game.
Here then.
I'll crush you.
Ready. Start.
Don't look down on me!
Damned guy.
Mada mada da ne.
Go home.
Ku'so!
Ugh! What the hell? What you doing?
When did you come here?
Anyway, get out.
Scared you, didn't I?
Get out.
It's been a long time
since we were in the bath together.
That's disgusting.
I feel like getting out of here right now.
You're blushing.
You're shy?
Your skin's so thin?
Who's the one that wants to get out?
- Tell me clearly.
- Shuddap.
When we were bathing together while you were young...
...didn't you like to put your legs like this?
- What kind of joke was that?
- It hurts, it hurts.
You're early.
The English test turned out bad.
- No doubt about that. It was horrible.
- I thought it was okay.
Echizen Ryoma...
...National champion for four years running...
...never lost a single game in the championships.
- No defeat, that's impressive.
- Ah that's more.
Ryuzaki-sensei.
What kinda guy is that Ryoma?
Playing with the world's top masters...
...with 37 consecutive wins.
People said that as long as he wasn't injured
during the Grand Slam, he wouldn't lose.
Japan's greatest player.
It was also because I looked up to him
when I was young that I began playing tennis.
Even now he's still my most respected senpai.
Nitouryu no Samurai Nanjiro.
Exactly.
That boy is Samurai Nanjiro's junior.
Even if he's famous,
I still won't give him preferential treatment.
I will treat him fairly.
Now it's just to ensure
that we will achieve victory in the Nationals.
Only these.
As expected, it's here.
We are the same group.
Ah, o-xhibi.
Come to see the groupings?
About the tournament to decide the regulars...
First years aren't allowed
to take part in the ranking matches.
Why would there be your name?
Saa...
...because I am strong.
Don't be so arrogant.
Kaidou.
Give me your guidance.
Tennis is about hitting the ball back fast.
Let's have this practice first.
Don't want to.
How cute.
Jackknife.
That technique isn't too bad.
All the different smashes in tennis...
...sure benefit you guys.
Too bad your ball isn't high enough.
Sorry but I've checked your data.
The data won't lie.
If not for the data...
...you would have played better.
- What are you doing?
- Woot? Ugh.
What was that?
Doing that by yourself.
Makes one so nostalgic.
This Seigaku regular uniform,
- Not too shabby.
- Heh?
Let's have a game at the usual place, okay.
Let's go.
When did he come in...
- Everybody gather.
- Hai!
- Good morning.
The opposing team is Seishun Middle School...
...finally we get to play.
I still haven't accepted you.
Ah, I see.
Hey, look at that.
What's this?
A chibi here.
How come even a chibi can become a regular.
Oh, it's Hyotei!
Hyotei is here!
- Yo Tezuka.
- Atobe.
Where did this kind of manners come from?
How are you doing, players of Seigaku?
Hoi?
You even send Junior students
when your own players aren't good enough.
Hmm.
Who are you?
Really cute.
Tezuka.
We'll see you eat dirt today.
All the best.
You are?
Higaki Shioin.
The next player on the court is...
...Seigaku's Tezuka against Gokuin's Nakano.
Finally, he's playing.
Oi, Echizen.
Why aren't you watching the match?
You're Seigaku's regular, right.
Watch the match? Why?
What why?
Kaidou.
I'm just saying.
Anyway, I don't like these kind of things.
Tennis is just a game for solo players.
There's also doubles.
Is it that fun? Doubles.
It looks like
you still don't know much, o-chibi.
Two persons together can be like three people.
That's doubles.
Just joking.
Have some food first.
Milk and bread are all here. Here.
I don't like milk.
Echizen, it's your turn to play.
I'll be going first.
Oi, have you eaten?
Seigaku! Fight! Fight! Fight!
- Ike, ike, ike, ike, ike, Seigaku!
Oi, oi, is that kid really going to play?
One set match. Seigaku's service. Play.
Ne, umpire, you haven't counted...
...the points.
15 - Love
That guy's really good.
It's hard to believe he's a first year.
- Medic. Hurry.
- Ah!
There doesn't seem to be any problems with his eye.
Just a cut on his lower eyelid.
The match can't continue.
It's fine.
Stop joking.
Captain Tezuka is worried too.
I want to play.
Ten minutes.
If you don't win in ten minutes,
I'll substitute you.
Tezuka.
Alright?
No problem.
Sorry for the wait.
Still playing on?
Just a little cut,
no reason to make a big fuss.
That guy's left-handed.
No way.
You'd better admit defeat.
Nitouryu.
Note: This name refers to Ryoma's ambidexterity.
Seigaku Tennis Team.
Congratulations on your victory.
Thank you.
Players of the tennis club.
Today, my idiot son lost his game...
...sorry to bring you guys trouble.
It's okay...
...we won in the end.
- It's my treat today.
- Thanks.
Eat, eat.
- Everyone, let's toast.
- Okay.
Okay, cheers!
Cheers!
Let's eat.
Hey, no.
- No, don't.
- Stop it!
Delicious.
- Delicious.
Sensei, sorry to trouble you.
We brought you quite a bit of trouble.
Ah er, I have some good wine here, have a little.
I am the team captain, Tezuka.
Captain?
- You're mistaken.
- Tezuka is a third year student.
Yo Tezuka-sensei.
Tezuka-sensei.
- But that o-chibi was quite good today.
- Yes, he was.
- He scared me a little.
- Um.
Ah, that was the Nitouryu.
That Nitouryu was not natural.
Not natural?
He learned from his father.
His father, you said...
...Echizen Nanjiro?
- You're bothered because of this?
- Eh?
What do you mean?
What is it?
What? What? What?
Ah Eiji, sorry to keep you waiting.
That Echizen sure is slow.
Get someone to bring him here.
Why don't you go?
Why me?
Damn late, Echizen!
Ah, my apologies. You see...
...we are not open for business today. Ah, dozo.
Sorry about it.
- Come back tomorrow.
- But they're eating... But they're eating...
No, no, no. That is...
...just a minor incident. Don't worry about it.
Carry on. It is okay. It's okay.
- Taka-san.
- Yes?
Good accuracy.
What about Higaki?
Don't worry.
There's a reason to make Higaki lose.
To control him better.
If this carries on...
...it might lead to the damage of your whole body.
Rest for a year without playing tennis.
Concentrate on your therapy.
Wait till the National Finals.
Please let me play till that match.
If it's tennis...
...you can still play in high school.
No matter what, I want the team members...
...to go to the Nationals together.
Swing the racket for me to see.
Your Zero-Shiki Drop Shot.
(Zero Degree Drop Shot)
Stop.
Being your therapist...
...I can tell you that this is your limit point.
That move of yours...
...will add on to your injuries.
You must not use the Zero-shiki Drop Shot
under any circumstances.
Alright?
Hi.
What's the matter?
Have your injury recovered?
All thanks to you.
Recover well.
Competition is one week away.
Up or down?
Up.
- Up.
- I will serve first then.
Let's have a proper match.
As the captain,
you'll lose face if you don't win.
Give me all you've got.
You sure?
Echizen, you're strong...
...but if you don't get better,
we will not win in the Nationals.
Give me your best shot.
I won't go easy so give me all you've got.
Give me all you've got
and improve yourself, Echizen.
Why did you transfer schools?
Didn't it cross your mind...
...that the Nationals
are filled with the best players.
- Even stronger than yourself?
- Think about it.
Think about it on your own.
You're Seigaku's pillar of strength.
Stop kidding around.
Echizen's not coming again today?
What did you hear about it?
Don't worry about it?
Looks like he came to school though.
What happened?
Is it a cold?
It is a cold.
- Ne, ne, ne, did something happen to the chibi?
- Ah...
What do you mean something happened?
- It wasn't easy coming here.
- Then what do you want me to do?
At least help me a little.
The age of Kanto will continue tonight.
Ryoma, let's have a game.
- Don't want.
- Good. Heh?
Oi, Ryoma.
I'm bored. What's up?
Why?
Ya, they want those training camp.
Sure.
See you then.
Mum...
...there's still one more week, right.
I understand.
Bye.
What are you trying to do?
Mind your own business.
How long do you intend to stay here?
Don't try to change the subject.
Captain, please play another round with me.
Just concentrate on practising
for the upcoming competition.
I wish to start immediately.
I'm about to leave.
What are you talking about?
I don't have much time already.
What do you mean?
We'll talk about it later.
Hurry up, go for practice.
Tezuka.
For next week's Kanto Meet,
the playing members have already been selected.
The first team we're up against is Hyotei Gakuen.
Heh... Hyotei...
No way, it'll...
...definitely be a blood bath.
- We lost last year but this year,
we'll definitely win!
- Yeah!
These are the Kanto's meet regulars' uniforms.
- Tezuka's choices are Oishi Shuichiro.
- Yes.
- Fuji Shusuke.
- Kikumaru Eiji.
- Yes.
- Kawamura Takashi.
- Inui Sadaharu.
- Yes.
- Kaidou Kaoru.
The last one is, Echizen Ryoma.
Momoshiro, even though I can't put you down this time
you still have to work hard in the future.
Yes.
Captain, I can't take part in the Kanto Meet.
Can I be dismissed?
What?
I have to represent in the Youth Cup.
I'm going back to America.
Then, what about the Kanto's meet?
That's why I'm giving
this regular's uniform to Momo-senpai.
What the hell are you saying.
- Stop fucking around!
- Oi! Oi!
- Stop.
- This is a rare opportunity to come by for any Seigaku player!
What kinda joke is this, bloody idiot!
Oi, Momo.
Leave him alone.
Don't brood over it.
So, you guys are the players
of Seishun Middle School.
- Higa-san...
- Yes that is Higa-san.
I brought you a nice present.
Hora, who should I aim?
- Eh? Dangerous! Everyone is dangerous!
- You! You!
- What the hell are you!
- Oi Kaidou! Kaidou!
Wait, you okay?
- That bastard!
- Wait, calm down. Calm down. Stop this! Stop it!
Let go of me!
It's been a while, Tezuka.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Leave here at once.
- Don't waste anymore of your energy.
- Why is he here for?
Why is he here?
You bunch, I'll accompany you.
Play a game in Samurai Nanjiro's meet.
Come on out, if you dare.
- Ano saa...
- Echizen!
Don't associate yourself
with that kind of people.
Isn't this chibi your opponent in the game?
Game?
Oh, you didn't know?
He didn't tell you?
Hold on.
Echizen Ryoma, remember that.
Brat.
Hyotei Gakuen.
Egate Mcleod Higaki.
- Hyotei.
Leave at once.
I will not tolerate this.
Are you troubled?
Sensei.
Ryoma's going back to America, right?
Is that alright?
Whether he wants to leave or not, is not up to us.
If it depends on him,
I guess there's nothing we can do.
Will the participating schools
please report to the court now.
It's starting soon.
Momoshiro that idiot,
didn't come in the end.
And so is the chibi.
- Let's go.
- Oh!
Kanto District Meet is about to begin.
Seishun Gakuen and Hyotei Gakuen match
is officially begun.
Please exchange your lineup.
I've waited for a long time, Tezuka.
Sorry,
but we will be the champions.