Keep guard here!
That way
Run up to the back of the hill
and don't turn back.
Don't stop or I will shoot!
Run for it!
Who told you to come in?
We are helping the General
to catch the prisoner.
Damn it!
The prisoner has run away
to the back of the hill.
Mount the horses and chase!
Run!
I've heard King Li Shih-Min
went to visit
enemy's place by himself.
Is that you?
Thank you, Madam.
You've not taken food for two days.
Eat the food!
As you are a monk,
can you take meat?
With Buddha in your heart,
wine and meat are nothing.
Monks always have Buddha
in their hearts.
Take it!
Your life as a monk is too simple
and poor.
Right.
Wang Jen-Tse's soldiers
have searched everywhere.
You better stay here for a few
more days.
- I will send you food.
- Okay.
Thank you, Madam. I've a job to do
must cross the river at once.
Do you know if there is a shortcut?
Well, we can escort you
to cross the river.
There are many check points.
How can you pass them?
Put down your hand at once!
You're born to be a couple.
It's a pity you're monk.
Dont' be shy.
- What now?
- Let's go!
You've got a lot of romance, Kid!
It's a pity you are a monk.
Sir, it's late now.
The bridegroom and
bride must return to their room.
Will you please let them go.
Damn it! Stop pretending.
How can we fool you?
Don't play that!
I'll buy you a drink.
Will you give me a favor?
Alright, you may go!
Thank you, Sir.
Don't be too cautious, brother!
Let's go and have a drink!
Is it hurt?
No.
Tear it off quickly.
Oh! It's bleeding!
What are you laughing for?
You really look like a sweet little wife.
Thanks for saving my life.
I'll repay your kindness.
- Li Shih-Min, you can't get away.
- Shoot.
Stop it! The general wants him alive.
We'll get promotion
and fortune this time.
Capture him alive!
Will you take him cross the river?
- How about yourself?
- Hurry.
They are running!
Shoot!
Master!
Bald-heads,
don't you want to betray us?
I guess they don't have guts
to do that.
Buddhists do not kill. Let's move!
Master, what shall we do now?
We need to defend ourselves.
Buddha will not give mercy to devils.
I understand.
Chueh Yuan, kill him!
Don't you dare to kill?
Buddhist and thief
won't live together. I'll kill you!
Chueh Yuan, kill.
Chueh Yuan, kill him!
Amida Buddha! My holy Buddha,
please forgive us.
Chueh Yuan is only taking them
to the heaven.
Buddha will forgive us.
Yes!
Chueh Yuan is doing it
you goodness sake.
Master.
I know I have committed sin again.
But, they would have killed me
if I didn't do it.
Yes, he is right.
Your mind can never he purified
and stay with Buddha.
You are leaving Buddha from now on.
Master!
Go far away from us!
Master! Wang Jen-Tse is still
waiting in Temple for him.
You can't be responsible
for letting him go.
Let's go back.
Why don't you mount the horses?
Master,
the buddhists are always merciful.
I know I'm wrong.
Please give me another chance.
Go away!
Don't come back to Shao Lin Temple!
Master!
Master...
Stop him!
Don't let him come into the Temple!
Master!
Hurry and go.
Wang Jen-Tse is waiting to catch you,
run quickly!
I don't want master and brothers
to be blamed.
Please let me in!
Master!
- Master!
- Tie him up and take him down hill!
Master, you have saved my life.
And abbot has helped me
in reincarnation.
I can't cause disaster
to Shao Lin because of me.
Let me have the suffering. Master!
Sorry for not seeing you off.
The monk has gone
but the temple still remains.
If you don't hand over the monk
and Li in three days,
I'll destroy Shao Lin Temple.
It's really a big trouble.
I've said he would get Shao Lin
into trouble.
We should have not let him stay.
Amida Buddha.
Buddhists are all merciful,
As Chueh Yuan is my disciple,
we must help him.
Being a Buddhist for years,
how can you say this?
You are wrong!
I'm sorry.
General!
Have you found Li Shih-Min
and the monk?
I've found them.
Where are they?
The Shao Lin monks have helped Li
to escape.
Chueh Yuan has killed
all our soldiers.
Traitors!
Let's march into Shao Lin Temple!
There'll be a disaster
in Shao Lin Temple.
- Master, let's fight with them!
- Yeah, fight with them...
We are trained in kung-fu.
We must protect Shao Lin.
Master, please let me go out.
I'll be responsible for everything.
To take the responsibility alone
be yourself?
How can you fight against
Wang's army by yourself?
I...
You are too eager to take revenge.
You better unfrock
and join Li Shih-Min.
Master,
I have not repaid your kindness.
I'm a buddhist monk
and have nothing to worry.
Only my daughter worries me.
Father!
If you can
take care of her in future.
- I'll have no more to worry.
- Father!
Master!
You go with him.
No matter what happens to us,
protect him and don't come back.
You may go!
- Father!
- Master...
Abbot! It's no good!
Wang Jen-Tse's army has passed
the Shao Shih Shan.
They'll reach our main entrance
very soon.
If we don't worry anything,
nothing will worry us.
Then we'll have a sound mind.
Why are you still so afraid?
Buddha bless us!
Tell the monks not to start any move.
Yes!
Let's lay siege to Shao Lin.
Bowmen to a ambush in hide-out!
Don't let any monk to escape.
Kill...
Amida Buddha!
Abbot...
Why do you want to
attack our temple, General?
Because Shao Lin monks conspire
with Li Shih-Min.
There is evidence
to prove the treason.
I'm ordered to punish the monks
and burn the temple.
Burn it down!
Hold it, General! I have a request.
Say it!
This is a historical land.
If there's a crime,
it should not involve the temple.
And the punishment shouldn't extend
to the monks.
As a temple abbot,
I'll take all responsibilities.
Alright, I'll kill you first.
Light up the fire!
Abbot!
If anyone tells me the whereabouts
of the traitors,
I'll keep your temple in peace
and abbot alive.
Abbot!
Abbot! Amida Buddha.
Kill him!
Oh, you!
If none of you speaks,
I'll kill you all.
Abbot!
No killing!
Abbot,
kindness results nothing to evil.
Kill the devils and enter Buddha.
Let's release their souls
and bring them to death.
Abbot!
Brother
Pan K'ung!
Master, you start killing now!
Let's kill them. They deserve it.
Shoot the arrows!
General...
Master!
- Master!
- Father!
Shoot the arrows!
Let's charge into the temple
and burn it down!
- Master!
- Father!
Li Shih-Min has crossed the river
with his army.
They are heading for Tung Tu.
You must defend Shao Lin
and uphold the justice.
- Master!
- Father!
Let's kill them!
General!
It's a bad news. Li Shih-Min
and his army have crossed
- the river heading for Tung Tu.
- What?
Kill them!
Kill!
Chueh Yuan, watch out for the sword!
Thou shall not kill. Can you do that?
I'll stop killing but not stop
to uphold justice.
Secondly, thou shall not steal.
Can you do that?
I've determined to enter Buddha,
Thirdly, thou shall not covet,
can you do that?
Master, I've determined to enter Buddha,
to defend Shao Lin
and uphold the justice.
Thou shall not covet,
Can you do that?
Yes.
Fifthly, thou shall not drink.
Can you do that?
I suggest this vow should be exempted.
Your majesty!
Since your majesty has given an order,
this vow of drink
shall be exempted forever.
To show appreciation,
King Li of T'ang Dynasty awarded
the Shao Lin monks
many fortunes.
The monks only accepted
a gown for each,
a tea set, and forty acres of land.
The King permitted Shao Lin
to form a defence force.
Such legend was recorded
on a temple stone
with the royal signature
of King Li Shih-Min.
The martial art of Shao Lin began
to prevail.
The fame of Shao Lin kung-fu was
everlasting.