This time it's a martial arts film.
The heroine is a bounty hunter.
The villain wears rain slippers even on clear days.
The worst of his kind.
What happened? His name's Gyeon-woo?
Gyeon-woo?
The story's setting is a mess.
Japan invades during King Sejong's reign,
and the king's father is the tyrant Yeonsan.
In the end,
the heroine fights the villain in a field.
Heavy rain pours down on a sunny day.
Yup~!
The heroine becomes a king. King Jung-jo.
She's from the future, of course.
It's fun, huh?
Why is the heroine always from the future?
Science is advanced then,
so they invent a time machine.
And people go to the past to travel.
People from the future could be here now.
I think UFOs are time machines.
Someday, I'll meet someone from the future.
I have to.
If you do, ask him to take you.
What?
If it's possible...
Give this to Shin Cine.
Tell them to cast Han Suk-gyu and Shim Eun-ha.
Jeon Do-yun is okay, too.
Excuse me, we talked on the phone, right?
Well... this is "The Warrior's Sad Love Story"...
It's going to be a hit.
Shin Cine didn't
call back.
Hey!
Hey, kid.
Is the subway your sketch book?
Don't scribble on it. Wanna die?
My lipstick!
I always take her home, even to Bupyung station.
It's something a man must do.
On the way, we play fun games, too.
Left foot over the line, I win.
With the right foot, you win.
What's the prize?
Let's see...
How about a kiss?
A kiss?
Wanna die?
You choose.
Hitting each other.
Again?
You can hit me, too.
Okay.
Someone's coming.
I think this is unfair.
I'm a girl, so I'll slap the cheek.
No. Then I'll change it, too.
- But I'm a girl.
- Men and women are equal.
Okay, then. You slap, and I slap, too.
Go easy on me, and I'll kill you.
Better slap me on the cheek.
If you don't, I'll kill you!
All right.
You slap, and I'll use my finger.
Right, that's fair.
Saw that?
See that guy step over with his left foot?
I had my eyes closed.
Plus he came the opposite way.
I thought it was this way.
Shut up. Here they come.
Left foot. Left foot.
It'll be the right foot.
Left! Left! Switch to the right.
You have to hit me?
You know why the sky is blue?
'Cause the reflection of the sunshine.
Nope. It's for me!
I want it to be blue. So, it's blue.
You know why the fire is hot? It's all for me.
I want it to be hot. So it is.
You know why we have four seasons here in Korea.
- Because of you.
- That's correct!
And why you were born here?
- It's for me as well.
- What?
That's nonsense. I was born before you.
You know the word of "worship"?
"Peter came first in order
to prepare for the birth of Jesus." huh?
Well... Yeah, I know.
So, get ready!
Come here. Stay still.
When I'm with her,
I never know how the day will turn out.
What?
What are you looking at?
I quit!
Is your face a racket?
Why does the ball always hit my face?
It's strange.
I never want to lose a game.
So I play until I win.
Wait long?
Just a teeny bit.
My mom bought me these heels,
but they're killing my feet.
Want a massage?
No, it's okay.
Instead, let's exchange shoes.
Don't wanna?
How can a guy wear heels?
It'll fit.
But, I can't...
Yeah? I see.
Come on. I'll buy you some sneakers.
Forget it.
Then wear mine, and I'll carry yours.
You don't understand women.
Okay! Let's exchange.
Really?
Wanna know a secret?
What is it?
I don't wear panties on exam day.
But I had one today.
Catch me, honey!
Hey. If you don't, I'll kill you.
Stop right there!
Stop!
Out!
It was just a second,
but I felt something in her eyes.
That's my house.
Wait. I'll bring you an umbrella.
I'm okay. I'm already wet so I'll just leave.
Eh?
Are you my daughter's boyfriend?
Yes, sir.
How much do you know about my daughter?
Not much...
Next time, don't hang out till late.
You don't understand me.
Why'd you stand him up?
What's wrong with him?
Why do you stand guys up?
And what happened to your heels?
What's wrong with you?
I told you not to meet Gyeon-woo.
He's dumb and has no future.
It's none of your business.
Why is he stupid?
You're stupid so you don't know.
What has gotten in to you?
Let me live my own life!
Afterwards,
I didn't hear from her for a long time.
- Hello?
- Gyeon-woo, it's me.
Long time no see.
Her voice sounds cheerful
as if nothing happened to her.
Our 100th day celebration is soon.
It's 100 days already?
When do you think a girl's the prettiest?
When a sexy woman is naked.
Where are you now? Stay right there.
No, I'm just kidding.
The prettiest is when she's playing the piano.
What's your favorite song?
That George Winston song.
Pachelbel Canon?
Yeah, that song.
You're not gonna ask me?
When is the guy the prettiest?
Just give me a rose.
Still have your high school uniform?
Yeah. Why?
Bring it on our 100th day,
and give me a rose during my class.
Do it yourself, okay?
What? What did you say?
How can I during class?
Hey! Just hung up on me! Damn it!
I don't wanna get beaten by her,
or get humiliated at a women's college.
Oh my God!
A burglar!
Help, a burglar!
Eh? Are you crazy?
You're gonna break into where?
What on earth are you doing in broad daylight?
And you...
Why you didn't drop by an aunt's
coming and going Bupyung for the girl.
You never know how much hard time
I went through for you.
She even intends to introduce a girl to you.
Gyeon-woo!
Where are you going?
I'm cleverer than I look.
These girls sure love Chinese food.
Hey, you! Where you headed? Come here!
I'm delivering Chinese food.
I ordered it. Bring it here.
Really?
Bring a lot of radish?
Oh, I forgot something!
Give me the food first!
That's the wrong way!
There's another customer.
Hey!
But that wasn't enough for her.
We relived our old high school days.
Drink!
Drink till die!
I've never had anything like this. Gee!
Sorry, I'm gonna drink it in my way.
Feeling so good!
Have a smoke, too!
Wow, I've never had a smoke, either!
Gonna be a big deal. I don't smoke well...
What are we supposed to do if caught by teacher.
It's a suspension!
You've already had your ups and downs in life.
Not to worry.
Go ahead and smoke!
Hey, you are such a tough cookie!
You go to a very good school!
These clothes are so tight!
After we visited that club,
a school uniform party was held every month.
But she got wasted again.
Oh, wild teens! Here's a condom.
Let's prevent AIDS.
Taxi!
She's having a happy dream.
Compared to when I looked at her
in the motel the first time,
She looks so different.
Could her pain be cured now?
Maybe it means that she doesn't need me anymore.
Excuse me. Can you drive slowly?
Here.
Have any plans after graduation?
Actually, I've never thought about it yet.
Can I see what's in your pocket?
Sir? Right.
It's a condom.
What is this for?
Oh, right. I learned that it prevents AIDS.
But I haven't used it yet.
- Actually, on the way here.
- Forget it.
"Chicks Hen"? What does this mean?
Oh, right. It's a chicken soup restaurant.
"We'll satisfy all your wishes"?
I think it's to satisfy our tastes.
"Hurry and tell him."
How do feel about our daughter?
Oh, right. We're just friends now.
Please don't worry.
If we get closer, I'll let you know, sir.
Don't see her any more.
After that day, she never calls me.
It was sudden, but that's how we broke up.
We've broken up. Now, I'm free.
It's me. Come to the cafe by seven o'clock.
Why?
What? I have a blind date today.
Come in 45 minutes.
I have a blind date, too.
Are you on your way?
I'm on a date with a girl.
Hurry up.
I have to go to the bathroom.
'Gotta go to the bathroom.'
Eh?
Nice to meet you.
I'm Cha Seok-won. Nice to meet you.
- Same here.
- Have a seat.
Were you really with a girl?
No, I was with a guy.
Can I take your order?
Coffee, please.
You can drink coke.
I'll drink coffee.
Gyeon-woo. You're very lucky.
I heard a lot about you. That you're a close friend.
Friend...
I need to go to the bathroom.
How is he?
No idea... but he looks nice.
He is not the man you broke up with, is he?
How do you know?
When you see a new man...
Forget about the past, all right?
How the hell do you know?
This necklace is given
from your ex-boyfriend, isn't it?
You wouldn't wear it
if you just broke up for nothing.
Considering your temper... and you...
used to say that you couldn't get over him.
Does that means he isn't here anymore in this world.
That man is the one my mom introduced to me.
She kept pushing me to meet him...
...Doesn't look bad, does he?
Yes.
Hey, listen!
I'm totally ok, but you should be obedient to man.
Man likes something more feminine.
And... don't drink a lot.
Some of the guys target intoxicated girls.
And it's all right with me, but to the other guys
try to surrender for just once.
...not try to win. Good luck to you.
Where's Gyeon-woo?
He left already.
He told me ten rules to follow.
I have a good memory. I'll recite them.
First, don't ask her to be feminine. And don't...
Second, don't let her drink over three glasses.
She'll beat someone.
At a cafe, drink coffee instead of coke or juice.
If she hits you, act like it hurts.
If it hurts, act like it doesn't.
On your 100th day together,
give her a rose during her class.
She'll like it a lot.
Make sure you learn fencing and squash.
Also, be prepared to go to prison sometimes.
If she says she'll kill you,
don't take it lightly. You'll feel better.
If her feet hurts, exchange shoes with her.
Finally, she likes to write.
Encourage her.
Ladies and gentlemen, please pay attention...
Gyeon-woo.
Step back behind the yellow line...
Gyeon-woo!
after passengers getting off, take in order...
please use the next train.
What's his name?
Gyeon-woo. I'll do it myself.
Gyeon-woo. Where are you?
I looked all over for you.
Gyeon-woo.
Come to the escalator. Okay?
You're dead if you don't. Hurry up.
Who told you to hug me?
Dummy. You're supposed to dodge.
Sometimes I feel like I know her and sometimes I don't.
We're definitely standing at the crossroad now.
What's going on between us?
Can this relationship last forever?
Who is it?
It's me, Dad.
She told me to write a letter and bring it.
To write it on paper.
To express my feelings,
I tried hard to find the right words.
When I first met her,
I wanted to cure her grief,
but now I can't give her up.
I wish we can get serious.
I'm writing about these feelings.
She's probably writing about me now.
This is how we're preparing to split up.
Gyeon-woo.
See that mountain top?
Yeah.
Could someone hear me from there?
Yes, probably so. Or probably not.
Then go over there. I'll shout here.
If you hear, answer me.
You want me to go over there?
Yeah.
Gyeon-woo?
Can you hear me?
Gyeon-woo!
I'm sorry. I really can't help it.
Gyeon-woo.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry... I can't help it.
I thought I was different, but I'm just a helpless girl.
Gyeon-woo!
I'm sorry.
Did you bring your letter?
Yeah.
What's that?
A time capsule.
We put our letters in it and bury it here.
And two years later, let's meet here again.
We'll read the letters that day,
and maybe we can find an answer then.
This was her way of saying good-bye,
and I kept repeating in my mind
that two years isn't long.
Let's open this exactly two years later,
at two, Okay?
We can meet two years later.
When we meet then,
we'll be different from what we are now.
We may become closer,
or stay forever apart.
We can only choose one.
Gyeon-woo.
You go first.
Let's separate here.
Should we go together?
No, I'll take the next train.
I think that's better.
See you two years later!
Okay, in two years!
Two years!
Bye!
Gyeon-woo!
That's how we broke up.
Over time
I couldn't endure the loneliness after we broke up.
Thinking of those memories,
I started to write about our stories on the Internet.
Then I made up my mind.
If I meet her again, I'll show her a different me.
Got to make use of my time.
For her and my future's sake.
Why does the ball I hit keep hitting my face?
I wrote our stories on the Internet everyday,
and I kept myself busy for two years.
Yu~p!
Excuse me. I wrote 'My Sassy Girl'.
Shin Cine saw my writing,
and offered to make a movie out of it.
I made her dream come true instead.
I wanted to tell her right away,
but I can only wait till that day.
She didn't come.
It's our only day to meet.
No one knows when she will come.
Wow!
How did he get in here?
It's a mystery.
Gyeon-woo!
How are you?
I was so happy while being with you.
I'm not sure if you knew,
but the person I loved passed away.
The day when I first met you
was the day he died a year ago.
Actually, I tried to look for him in you.
I know it was wrong. I'm sorry.
I also met him on the subway like you.
I was really sick at that time.
He did everything I wanted.
Like you did to me.
Under this tree, we planned our future together.
But he suddenly passed away.
While I was dating you, I met his mother often.
She wanted to introduce a nice man to me,
but I couldn't.
The day I first met you, I came under this tree,
and I prayed to him.
To let me free.
When I met you, this occurred to me.
That maybe... he introduced you to me.
But the more I met you,
he seemed to grow jealous of you in me.
The more I liked you, I felt guilty inside.
While the two of us are apart,
I want to forget him alone.
After that day, I went often to this place.
If I'm not with you after two years,
it means I still lack of courage.
How much will we change after two years?
I feel like you live in the future,
and I stay in the past.
I want to meet you soon,
so I can read your letter.
Why are you staring at me, sir?
Because you're so pretty.
I thought an angel came down.
Do you come here often?
Sometimes. This tree has a secret.
I have a secret here, too.
Really?
Three years ago,
I buried a letter here with my boyfriend.
What's your secret?
So what happened?
We promised to read the letters a year ago.
But I couldn't come.
I guess you're a year late.
But two years didn't seem that long.
I haven't made any decision yet.
I just wasted my time on stupid thoughts.
Like what?
If we were destined to meet,
I thought we'd meet by chance somewhere.
Know what fate is?
Building a bridge
of chance for someone you love.
To be honest, I read you guys letters.
I said this tree had a secret, right?
Yes.
Look closely. Does this tree look the same as before?
Well, it looks like it changed a bit. But I'm not sure.
People are dead or alive.
There's a dead tree and a living tree, too.
This tree was struck dead by lightning last year.
It was split into two.
But this young man felt sorry for it.
During this spring,
he planted another tree that looked the same.
When he planted the tree,
he asked me if it look the same.
He said that someone would be sad if it died,
so no one should know.
Gyeon-woo...
You call a wrong number or the dial is not in service.
Please, call again.
Hi.
It's been a while. You've gotten prettier.
You still look young. How have you been?
You were in England?
Yes. For one and a half years.
So I can forget him.
I see. Feel better?
Yes. A lot better.
Is it true now?
My son might be sad.
He won't. He'll like it this way.
Good, that's what I really hoped.
Auntie! I was getting my photo taken.
You naughty boy.
Know how long it's been?
Sorry I didn't tell you before.
This is Gyeon-woo. Doesn't he resemble him?
When you had a hard time,
I tried to introduce you to him for several years,
but he kept getting out of it.
Heard you came to Bupyung often,
but you never visited me?
Go out with him.
I thought he'd make things easy for you.
Oh, yeah. Gyeon-woo,
you're going to England, right?
She's already been there,
so she can give you some tips.
I don't have to go now.
Why? You two know each other?
You may not believe it,
but I think I met a man from the future.
From your future.
This is how I met her again.
Think it's too coincidental?
It's building a bridge of chance for your love.