1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2...
Hui, any plans after discharge
next week?
What? The first thing is
to fix that batch
Because of it, I've had to suffer for 5 years
Right. Let's have a good time, when we dig it out
Would you care to eat?
No, sir
1, 2, 1, 2, 1, 2...
Get going. Don't take yourself for big brother
The same food again
That should be donated to Ethiopia
Even they wouldn't care for it
Don't eat then
Even if I fast now,
I won't die in a week
Eat
Brother Sheng, brother Sheng
What is it?
When you check out next week
please tell my wife to see me
Okay, give me your address
To see you? Your wife has run away
Damn you. How do you know?
Your miserable looks show it
Hey, my food
They've taken it away
Who's taken away my food
It has been donated to Ethiopia
They've got so much food.
They must've taken mine
Don't bully us because you're permanent
Who did bully my friend
It's me, Piao
The doctor says I have malnutrition
Right, right
Forget it. It's been given to Ethiopia
Even the starving ones there won't care for it
Hit my friend
Stop, everybody! Stop
Sheng, come and lend a hand
Stop! Stop
All crouch down here
Crouch down, crouch down
Stop!
One more month's sentence for fighting
One more month
We don't even mind to be permanent here
You don't mind
Friend, you've dropped something
Thanks, thanks
How careless
Sorry, sorry
It's alright
Do you need my help
For such heavy work I can do it myself
Sir
Is this purse yours
Thank you
Don't mention it
Take this
Sorry
An honest young man like you is rare
You're right
Such heavy work is unworthy of you
I don't mind
How about joining my Tourist Agency
Can I cope
Yes
Thank you, boss
Don't mention it. Excuse me
Bastard
My leg hurts
It hurts badly and is getting numb
Of course, it's mine
I've difficulty in breathing.
My heart's going to stop beating
Artificial respiration at once
Not this way. Hold me and
massage my muscles
How
I'll show you
Put your hands on my neck. 1, 2, 3
Let us try
Massage, massage
I feel good at the back
What has it to do with your back
You won't understand
Why didn't you warn me
You have no more breathing trouble
If you do, I'll take you to Casualty
No need, no need
Better take you home
Okay
Sorry, I've something urgent to do
What is it?
To talk business
But I worry about you
Give me your address.
I'll see you when I can
Are you serious
I live at No. 3 fat Kwong Street,
3rd floor
If I happen to be out
come to Chuan Chi Teahouse to see me
Are you sure you're alright
Yes
Goodbye
Goodbye. Be sure to see me
Good bye, goodbye
Detective work requires experience
First, fingerprints
Slender fingerprints mean you're pretty
Let's talk about this at dinner tonight
Do you have to talk about this at dinner
It's outdated to fool around during office
Yes, uncle
No, Director
Come in with me
What's so funny
Do you mean I'm clumsy
No, Uncle
No, Director
I knew you did it deliberately
Bastard, are you taking me for a moron
You knew I couldn't aim well
and you pretended to praise me
You've no judgment.
You can't be a private eye
Uncle, I only meant...
How long have you been here
One and half minutes
How long have you been
with that Detective Agency
Seven years
Aren't you ashamed of sporting your books
No
It's a detective story
What have you learnt? Tailing?
No
Snapping
Eavesdropping
A little
Stealing
I dare not do it
What have you learnt then
English
Damn
If you're not my nephew, I should've fired you
How about the loot of Hang Pao Gold Shop
I've told Bonnie to investigate
Bonnie to investigate
When have you been promoted
Bonnie's new, you should work with her
I wanted to
But she insisted on acting alone
So she's quite smart
Commissioner, brother Kuang, want to see me
Yes. How's the Hang Pao Gold Shop's loot
I met one of the discharged robbers
That won't help
You must make friends with him
Most important of all, get his address
Stop acting for a while
Bonnie, don't worry.
A novice has difficulties. Take your time
Next time try to get acquainted with him
I've already got his address
Look, how efficient she is
Bonnie, don't you know I admire your efficiency
Let me stand you dinner to tell you my experience
This will be helpful to you
We can talk about it during office
What's so funny
It's alright now. Back to work
Yes
Hold it. Come back
Remember to give me a report every day
Note down carefully the characters
time and place of the happenings
That report is on the desk
Okay
This is the file
What do you mean by that? Feeling swell
Why are you dressed like that
To imitate Holmes
Take it off
Any new clues
Okay, I'll keep an eye on him at once
Listen, I'm going out to investigate
Work with Bonnie to get back the lost. Understand
How come
Impossible
Rocks? Why no trace of diamond at all
What? Why have you dug such a large hole?
Faster. We still have a lot of digging to do
Faster, faster
5143, 5144, 5148, push the wheels
Are you here on leave?
Coming
Harder. Chin Ta-chi is mad
Sure. Harder, or the wheels may turn back
Don't be lazy
Aren't we pushing now with all out strength
Sheng, damn you, you fought in jail
and got us involved
Push quickly. Don't relax
Let's endure for a few days
Sheng must be waiting for us with money
I endure it only for the sake of the future
When I go out, I must fly to
Pattaya to lap up the sunshine
Maniac, the sunshine's dazzling us here
It's okay here. Let's dig overthere
Over there
YES SIR
Don't be lazy. I'll be back soon
See how things are
Silk Road
Cheer up, cheer up
Sheng will get a Rolls Royce to pick us up
Level it first
How's the situation
Hold on
Hold on, hold on
Brother Hui
Come and help
Harder, hold it
Sheung, have you dug them out
Why? Have you disposed of them
Take gold, not cash to avoid counterfeits
Right, take gold
I've dug them out
Splendid
How much shall we get each
At least $3 million, right
$3 million
I've dug them out
But they've all turned into rocks
Sheng, you're tops
You really have a sense of humour
I'm serious
I'm not easygoing
Stop joking
I'm serious
How dare you make fun of me
They're there. Show them
They've really turned into rocks
Hell with you
I can't hold on
Get out ofhere
Sheng
Sheng, have you swallowed up my share
No, no
Follow him
Stop, stop
Let's go
Brother Hui, brother Hui
Where's Piao
I'm down below
I won't forgive you
Hello, whom you want to speak to
Is Sheng in please
Who's speaking
I'm Bonnie
Bonnie, speaking
Sheng, sorry for that accident.
Are you alright
Yes, but my back still aches
Can you come out to dine
I'd like to host steak dinner for you
Yes, the doctor wants me
to walk and eat more
Splendid. See you at the Flagpole in 30 minutes
Okay
I can escape after dinner
Help! I'll kill you
Right. Sheng lives in here, go in
What are you doing? Were's Sheng
How careless
Bitch, are you blind
She's charming. Let's rape her before killing
Okay
Will it work
Come on, come on
Go away
Want to test me
Bitch
What's wrong
Impossible. Lighter
It's wet, damn it
I'll try again
Take a bath first
Take a bath
Let me
Strip
She's shapely
Sure
Strip
Watch Enjoy Yourself Tonight
Enjoy Yourself Tonight
How can a blind person watch TV
Right
Miao-maio, come and see
Enjoy Yourself Tonight
Who's Miao-miao
Who cares
So it's a cat
Don't tease it
Come here, Miao-miao
It's more important to find it
I've found it
Help! I'll kill you, damn cockroach
You're not bad in acting
The gems are yours, the girl's mine
Small coins
Where are the diamonds
What an idiot,
I forgot to put on cologne
Go into hiding
Why is the door unlocked
I can't get the cologne without light
What a mess
Who is it
Your brothers of course
Sheng, hand over the diamonds
or we'll be nasty
I really haven't got the diamonds
Don't lie
Where's that girl
Follow her
Don't! Piao's more important
The bill
$5, please
What will you have?
Milk with cream and egg
Brother Sheng
Chuan
Where have you been these years
I've had no news of you
I was in business overseas
Why didn't you write? I missed you
Mexico is a large country
I don't even know the Post Office there
Have you been there all these years
No, I've been to Bengal and
Moscow to talk business
That's most inconvenient then
No, one hour's flight will do
Bengal is in Asia and Moscow is in Europe
One hour's flight is incredible
Why don't you eat
I prefer to watch you eat
Let's eat together
Is the food okay
Okay. Over...
Overthere we seldom tasted such good food
If you prefer, I'll cook for you everyday
No need. The food outside is better
So you have someone to cook for you
Don't get the wrong idea
I mean foreign foods in foreign restaurants
Let's go out to try them sometime
Come on, have some soup
Thank you
Sheng, let me do it for you
Okay
How's business lately
So so
How's your business in Mexico
Don't talk about it
Alright, if you prefer
I might as well tell you
How's it
It used to be okay
but recently we've had cash trouble
If we don't tide it over,
my years' effort
I'm going on 30
I decided to build up a career
to settle down, but
Have you got an objective
She was my childhood friend
But I know she looks down on me
Excuse me
Here's $10,000. Take it
If not enough, I'll borrow some for you
No need. I'll try to raise more myself
You took much time to save this. I...
Don't worry. We're friends
I wish you could succeed in your career
But somehow I can't understand
You've just been out of jail.
Why do you need so much money
How do you know that
Don't shilly-shally
Anyway, I'll lend you the money
Eat
Want to travel, sir?
Why not? Isn't yours a Tourist Agency
Yes, yes
Please come here. Come on
Please sit down
Where do you plan to go, sir
The farther the better
South Africa, Brazil -two tours next month
Next month? Sorry
What's the earliest flight to leave HK?
Earliest?
In 5 minutes. Cross the street to take it
What flight?
A helicopter to Kowloon
I don't mean that
I want to go abroad
It's now the boom season.
All flights are booked up
Even to take a bath in Thailand,
you've to wait one week
One week? I'll be finished then
Can't you wait to take a bath
I am not going to have bath
but to find shelter
Spain is best then
The cost of living there is low
The earliest flight for Paris
is the night after tomorrow
Thence you change flight for Spain
What's the earliest flight
for France, sir?
The night after tomorrow
He has been asking me the same question
So it's you
What a coincidence
Are you going to France
Yes, to visit my parents. And you
He hasn't made up his mind
I have. The night after tomorrow. And you
Okay
I'll go the night after tomorrow
I'll arrange that for you at once
The cheapest return ticket for Paris is $8,400
US$8,400
Lily, count them
Yes
Thank you
Don't mention it
I'm sorry about last time
Did I hurt you
It was only my fault
Why are you going to France
I...
To take shelter
Nonsense. I go wandering. It's now the vogue
Reading is now the vogue
It makes no difference
Your receipts
The plane leaves at 10:30 p.m.
Day after tomorrow
Be at the airport before 9:30 p.m.
If you need any further info., ask me now
No
No, no
I must be off
Me, too
Thank you
Modern girls have no taste at all
Write me often when you get there
It must be snowing now. Wear more
Keep these 2 bottles of medicinal oil
Apply it when you feel sick
Even a doctor won't be much help
And turtle soup is nutritious
They say it's dry on the plane
Remember to drink it
What are you looking for
The counter
Counter
Bonnie
Where are you going
So you're here
Yes
Have you completed the check-in
No, let's do it together
Okay
Sheng, you know her
We joined the same package tour
My cousin Chuan
Your name, please?
I'm Bonnie
The counter's overthere.
Let me hold it for you
No need
Show me the ticket. I'll fix your seat
Good
Do you know what seat she prefers
At most I'll give her my window seat
Sheng
What is it?
When you fix everything there,
come back to pick me up
Don't put it this way,
people may misunderstand
I'm speaking the truth
Miss, what happened
Let me go and see
Please take a close look
I've checked it, sir.
Your ticket is not confirmed, and invalid
Miss, I bought it at Chieh Tung too
So your situation is the same
What? It's hell
That Tourist Agency has cheated us
We've all been fooled. Let's contact them
That lady said our tickets are invalid
What then
Let's join them to take the matter up
Hurry up
The Chairman said the checks were paid in late
You'll get your pay tomorrow
Have tea, sir? Can we get our paid today?
Tomorrow, tomorrow
Tomorrow
Drink it tomorrow
There are clients. Keep busy
Who's the Manager here?
Tell him to come out.
We must settle with him
Excuse me
Miss, this is our Manager
What a hectic day
So it's you
Let's talk it over
We want a refund
The Airline says the tickets are invalid
There's no such flight
The Tourist Association says
it's not registered
Right, we want a refund
Quiet! Quiet!
Hurry up! Many people are here
Listen, I guarantee on my character that...
Bastard, you've taken away our money
Friends, I didn't cheat
Refund us the air tickets
Two
We'll break your bones if you don't
Buddy, be reasonable
I'm only an employee working for the Company
How dare you cheat me?
Right
Miss, when have I cheated you
He bought the airtickets
What do you mean?
Why scandalize me in public
I don't mean to
Bastard, go away
Open up, open up
So high
Retreat. I'm breaking it open
Break, break
Don't jostle, don't jostle
Bastard, stop
You can't get away
It doesn't concern me
Don't run, don't run
It's not my responsibility
Don't run
It really doesn't concern me
I must get hold of you
What's wrong? Don't do it here
You may ruin other people
Keep away
What's it
Nothing
Maniac
What's it
Do you know him
You're rich.
Make a call and you'll get $5000
Okay
Sheng, the Tourist Agency wants to see you
This is Chang Chin-sheng
You're Mr Chen. The money can be refunded. Pi Ching Bar
Okay, I'll be there
How's it
The money can be refunded tomorrow
When?
I forgot to ask him
Listen
Hey, three o' clock, idiot
What?
Three o' clock
And
Idiot, he said
Idiot
Chuan, I can take care of it
Buy some underwear for me
I want you to go in with me
Be nice. We must fight for time
When I get the money,
I'll go to another Tourist Agency
Oh, no
Go ahead
Have you made reservations, sir
I'm looking for someone
Please go in
Sheng, here. Come up
Sheng
Sit down
The money
No hurry. Drink something.
I'll be the host
Thank you
Waitress
What will you have, sir
He wants
One mixed fruit fleecy, one French Toast
Good
You promised a refund
Yes, the cashier promised
to bring the money
I must call him. Wait here
There's a telephone overthere
This telephone stinks
What?
Couldn't be
He'll pay you when he sees you
He's coming, he's upstairs
Sit down
Buddy
It could be fatal
Don't! Listen to my explanation
No more nonsense. Hand them over,
or I'll take your life
As he's giving us the location,
be easy on him
I really didn't take them
You still want to take them all
for yourself
Let me
There's a fight
Hui, stop him
Where's my money
Stop that
Stop acting. Refund me $5000
Let's go, Chuan
Let's go. We're not their match
Let's go
Follow them
Pay me. Don't go
Who say no
The things are broken and they're gone
Am I to charge them to your account
Sure, sure
Don't let me see you again here
I really have got no money
Going away
Bastard, you dared to fool me
I lured you out to collect the reward
The reward
Yes
I'll give it to you now
Sister, have mercy! You may kill me
You asked for it. You nearly ruined me
I didn't know it was so serious
I won't dare to do it again
How dare you talk
To get the reward,
you may sell me out again
Once again? Don't
Let's go
Where's Sheng
How I won't be taken in
Pay me or I won't be taken in
What if I don't
Forget it. Let's have tea
some other day. Bye
Stop that, or I'll shout
Several men assaulting one?
Here's a $5000. Take us there
That's better. Follow me
It's up above there
Go up
See if you can get away now
Keep away! Keep away!
Keep away, or I'll jump
Sheng, let's talk it over
Go on. Excuse me
I've locked the door. He can't get away
Sheng, don't try anything foolish
Keep away
Sheng, come down first. Come on
Stop pushing me
Come down, you may tumble to death
Watch out
Pull him up
Sheng, take care
Why is it so heavy?
Harder
What are you doing?
Bonnie, lend a hand
Harder
Can I let go? I've acrophobia
No, or they'll pull us up
What are you doing there
Lend a hand at once
I can't make it
Cut off the rope
Where are you doing
My pants are falling. Let go
Don't, or I'll get you
Oh, no my pants are dropping! Let go
What are you doing? My clothes
Chuan, are you alright
Yes. And you
I'm alright
What happened
You're damned, you took away my pants
Sheng, how are you doing
They're coming soon. Run!
My car's in a next street. Let's go
Hurry up
Come in
Sit down. I'll bring you coffee
Thank you
You're beautiful and you've taste in decor
Right, it's better than
my Chuan Chi Teahouse
What has beauty to do with taste?
Why not?
The taste of the interior decoration
shows your own taste and beauty
what did you say
The decor here is beautiful
Is this flat yours?
It's my uncle's, but his family has emigrated
I'm watching the house for them
Are you sure the decor is okay?
He must be out of his mind
He thought the flat was yours
Damn you
Taste my coffee
Drink it
It smells good. Chuan, smell
I have nasal congestion
Two spoonfuls enough
No sugar. I must keep fit
No one has put sugar into mine
Let's change. I don't have to keep fit
Sheng, did those men bear you a grudge?
No, they're my friends
They looked so tough
I don't think you're any good
Why did they push you so hard
Don't talk nonsense or I'll get you
They only wanted to see me
We missed each other for a long time
The way he looked
he was trying to take your life
Right, right
Take my life? Never
You know better yourself
There are usually three reasons
For honor, for girls or for money
None at all
Confess it
Lie again, and I can't help you
I didn't
Don't deny
The way you put the sugar shows
you were hiding something
Sheng, tell them the truth
Okay, I will
You're late. Is there any clue?
Is the clue reliable?
Yes, but not as useful as yours
Chang claimed he didn't get the gems
So much the better
What do you mean
This is a normal phenomenon
Ho won't admit of course
Do you think it's true?
Absolutely, according to my observation
Have you observed Sheng?
You're responsible for tailing Hui
I mean I've observed you
What?
It's true on observation of both you & Chang
Could Ma Hui & his men have done it?
Have you discovered anything about them
Much
What
Ma Hui's looking for Sheng
Then they mustn't have done it then
Who then
What's on your mind
Chest
My mind is all blank
I've got an idea
What?
Let's deliberately provoke Ma & his men
So they'll settle it with Chang
Then we can sit back & watch them flight
and see who's got the goods
You see what I mean?
Perfectly
We're rich. I've long waited for you
No, no
A small fry swallowing a big fish
Show me. I didn't see it
How crafty you are
Are you still in the mood for fun
My money's all spent
As of today, we'll each go our own way
are we to let Sheng go like this
No, he's even cheated my ma out
of her funeral money
I'll never let him go
Since last time, We've been unable to find him
Don't forget we must eat
Don't blow up because you've lost
If I see him, he'll suffer
Why has he become so sly after 30 years
It shows he has brains
You mean we have no brains
Not us
If not us, it means myself alone then
You said that
How dare you to taste me? Damn
Let go
It's no concern of mine
You want to know where Chang's hiding
Yes
He's now at 17 Hsiao Lik Yuan
Village, Shatin
in his cousin Chuan's shop
Understand
Such a good job? Reserve it for me
I'll come right away. See you then
Hui, where are you going?
I'm rushing to have an interview
Here's $1,000. Try your luck
50/50
You're smart
Have you noticed Hui's enthusiasm for work
Right. When in jail, we did everything
And he was so generous today
Right, we always had to ask him for it
Is he really going for an interview?
There must be something fishy
What shall we do
Tail him
Go then
he should be downstairs by now
Want bras, miss
Crazy
What's there to see
You need psychiatric help, sex friend
What are you doing
You think you can get bras of your size
Go and buy a pair of parachute
Taxi
Follow that red car in front.
Here's $100
Is that red car? Yes, yes
I haven't got in yet
Taxi
I envy you, you have no worried
Why don't you leave Hui and his men
and start all over again
I can't. They won't let me go
Do you expect me to hide here all my life
You want to hide? Never
Stay where you are
Calm down. I'm only trying to help Sheng
Me
Don't say that
You'll be doing him a favour
to leave him alone
I've come only by myself
Maybe. See what he has to say
Sheng, it's hard to find your place
Why is the atmosphere so tense here
Why are you here
To see Sheng
There's lots to eat
I'm both tired and hungry
I haven't prepared your portion
Take my portion
What on earth do you want
I'm really trying to help Sheng
Sheng, let's go out for a chat
Oh, no
That would make me lose face
Let's go!
- Go on with eating. I'll come right away
- Okay
I found you
Sheng, you'd better hand them over
Hui, I didn't take them
I can't help if you deny it
I'll let you go, but Chiang and Piao won't,
and Chiang can do anything
Especially Ah Chiang, he will do anything
You can't hide all your life
Hui, you've known me long enough
to doubt me
Go back and tell them the truth
They won't listen to me
What then?
The only way
Hui, what is it
I shouldn't help you
Please, Hui, I beg you
I really am innocent
Hong, go and clean the groove
The only way is to get out of here
and go as far as possible
But I have no money
Help
I'm afraid
What are you doing there
Let's try the Water World here
There are still two overthere
Okay, let's go
Try them yourself. All ruined
Bonnie, are you alright
Yes
You said you had no money
Sell the goods
and you'll have lots of it
I already said I haven't got it
Alright,
I'll raise travel expenses for you
Are you serious
I'm not sure if I can get it
Wait for me at Chung Ta Timber Mill
I really don't know how to thank you
Don't mention it
Hello
Where are you now?
I'm following Chiang and see Hui's car
But now there's no trace of Hui
He's now going out. Follow him
Never mind Huo Chiang
Okay. Goodbye
Ma Hui couldn't have come here
Right. How could he be here?
Must be that fellow
That fellow
All eaten
I'm not too hungry. You eat
Whom were you talking about?
Whom?
Well, whom?
I mean her
Don't talk nonsense. What's your proof
Proof? Here are four persons
Not you, him or me
Who else, if not her?
You're being unreasonable
Never mind her. She's joking
You cover her up because you like her
Look, what pretty chest she has
Keep your mouth shut, will you?
Ain't I speaking the truth? Cut it out
Don't fight because of me
Bonnie, Bonnie
I'd better go. We'll keep in contact
Goodbye
Are you happy now?
Sheng, in fact I
Actually Chuan did that for you
Thank you.
Luckily she's broad-minded
Is she
Quiet. Why did Ma come to see you
We're after all brothers
Ma trusts me and has even promised
to lend me money to go abroad
Is it true
Sure, we'll meet at Chung Ta tomorrow
He'll bring me money then
Isn't he friendly
Would he be so broad-minded
He did that to harm you.
He meant to mislead
Piao & Chiang into belief
you've taken the loot
No more nonsense, please
Once you go abroad, they'll surely believe
you've run away with the loot
It seems Ma's really trying to frame you
Right, you're smart
After you leave, Ma Hui may
say anything against you
And you've no way to prove your innocence
Don't judge with a little man's mind
The truth is once you're away
he can say anything against you
And you've no way to prove otherwise
Thanks for reminding me of it
Think carefully and you'll see
Why did he date you for such a quiet place
He must be up to no good
Don't try to be smart
Not everyone's as obstinate as you're
You meet everyone at star Ferry
lf he's up to no good, you'll be
in danger in a desolate place
The right place should be
the flagpole at Star Ferry
It's crowded and much safar
Glad you understand. Think it over
Shut up
Think it over
You're right
You 're my good friend
What's the matter with you?
He's fight and I am wrong?
Don't be biased against me
I'm not only biased but
highly preiuiced against you
Because you irritated Bonnie
You've gone too far
What's now?
Never mind her. It's her shop. She'll come back
Does your dog bite, old man?
My dog never bites. He's meek
You side he wouldn't bite, old man?
This dog is not mine
You're crafty
Where's Sheng? Speak up
or I'll be nasty
He's at my home. I'll take you there
Don't play tricks
Overthere
It could be a trap
I won't walk into it so easily. Follow me
It's for you
Sheng? Liang
Tell Sheng Huo Chiang's caught me
It's Chuan. She was caught by Chiang
Isn't she going to help to hang herself?
What a new gimmick she's got
She can't fool me
Tell her to go to the old garage or
He may disfigure me
That's what I'm going to say
Wait
He threatened to disfigure Chuan
Did he?
Chiang, don't hurt Chuan. I'll come at once
Wait for me
Get going
Go and rescue Chuan now
Don't think I'm as dumb as you
It was only a trick
Let me play along with her and keep her waiting
They didn't sound like lying
You'd better go and see
I have no time. You go yourself
No, I must buy a newspaper
Go now and you'll see
Idiot
Go
Lighter
Shut up
Why should I talk?
Sheng's coming. When he's here,
you'll be finished
With you here, I'm not afraid of him
Overthere
Chuan, I'm hungry
Liang, here
Are you alright
Why is Sheng not coming
Did he know Chiang's caught me
Yes, but he has no time
He wouldn't care about my safety
I'm here to help you
Why is he not coming himself?
He doesn't care for me
He does
Why is he not coming
He said only an idiot would trust you
What? Did he say that
He didn't mean it. Why is it so hard
You indeed are an idiot
What are you doing? Enough
Chuan, I'll protect you
Liang, are you alright
Calm down. I'm here
Enough. Put me down
or I won't give you face
Go now. You're not his match
Calm down. I'll get you out for sure
I'll count three and you put me down
1, 2, 3
Liang, are you alright
I'm alright. I can hold on
Don't hit him anymore
Quiet
I bet you to put me down to fight with you
Don't hurt Chuan
Liang
Liang, go at once
You're not his match, Liang
I won't let him hurt you
Let me go, and I'll take you to Sheng
Let me go
Liang, Liang
Liang, Liang, are you alright
Yes. Don't be afraid of him. I'll hit him
Liang, Liang
Can you beat me?
Had I known sheng's so heartless
I wouldn't have played along with you
Liang, are you alright
Chuan, let's run. Chiang's powerful
Don't be afraid. I'm here
How's Sheng overthere
Don't be worry. I'll finish him off
Too early
Sir, I'm here to fix the room
Will you speak Cantonese
I'm here to fix the room
No need, no need
A de luxe room is cleaned 3 times daily
Hurry up
Thank you
Here you are
Let me
Whom are you looking for
Mr Chen, come and sit down
So you're Mr Chin's friend. Have a cigarette
Our boss doesn't smoke
Have a cigarette
You may go out
Boss
Mr Chen
Mr Chin
None of you cares to smoke
Right, right. Go out
Thank you
Please sit down, Mr Chen
Mr Chin, our boss wants to see the goods
Okay
We accept your price. We'll contact in few days
Don't plaster it
It may bruise without plaster
Brother Hui brought me that
It doesn't concern him
No? Maybe he colluded with Sheng
I met that bitch after we parted
That couldn't be a coincidence
Don't you know your boss tried
to double-cross you
Who told you that
Never mind
He lured Sheng to talk at Chungg Ta
Go at once
Is that so
Brother Hui
Sheng, I've raised $5000 for you.
Go tonight
Since you're so friendly, I can't go away
I've decided to follow you
Okay, I'll think it over
Lend a hand
Sheng, Sheng
I'm here
Why are you doing that
You won't understand
Let me
Trying to kill yourself
Are you alright
Yes Watch out
Come up, come up quickly
He's trying to run against me
Don't hit him
Go away. Let me
How do you feel
Well, does it hurt
Try
It really hurts
Good, I made it
Liang, are you alright
It hurts
Hui, don't be afraid. I'll help you
Stop
Follow him, quick
He fooled us. Why are you on his side
I fooled him too.
He fled because he's guilty
Right, he's exposing himself
What trick are you playing with Hui
I'll tell you for sure.
He told me to run to frame me
Why should he do that
Unless he's taken away the stuff himself
We were in jail and discharged the same time
He couldn't have taken it
Of course he could
He colluded with another man in jail
Why are you here
The same coincidence every time
You can't convince us you're innocent
I've come to see Sheng
Is that so
Can you support what you said
Of course. My partner will show you the proof
Where are you
I came to the timber mill without seeing you
Turn around
You're all here
He's my partner Fu
This is my card
So you're a private detective
Yes, yes
You're his partner. How about Bonnie
The Underwriters appointed us
to investigate the case
So you've been spying on me
Yes
I sensed something was wrong
You're pretty and you helped me
In fact, you're a good man
Repeat it when there's a full moon
I feel the heat now, if you don't
Show us the evidence
Evidence? Sure
Hui colluded with the jailor to double-cross us
Can't I see it myself
Who's the man who followed them
Someone who bought the loot
His name is Cheng Chung-pai
You recognized him
He's my ex-boss, a con-man
He has his own means
to buy loots
What is it?
Cheating
See what Chen is up to
Don't let him swallow up the loot
You must help us
Sure
The Underwriters want to recover the loot
We have no reason to help
There's a reward
How much
10%
The reward is going to be handsome then
They've got to make a move. Let's watch him closely
What now?
What are they doing
Why have they taken so many police uniforms
Well, why?
Nonsense
Where are we going
On analysis of the data gathered by us
this crafty old Chen Chung-pai obviously
What are you trying to imply
He wants to double-cross us
What do you mean? Put it more plainly
He wants to swallow up our share.
That's all
Nonsense
I won't let him go then
Not so hard! It's my Uncle's table
Bonnie, he's rude,
don't talk so loud to him
Yes
Forget it.
Sit down
Crazy, you think I'm rude to everybody
Sorry, Bonnie, next time I won't do it
Sit down, will you
Okay, sit down. Calm down
Since we know Chen's double-crossed us
let's try to take care of them
I know. We should try to rob too
Nonsense
Don't be afraid.
At least Liang dare to speak out
Yes
Right. Is it guilty to talk
How dare you? I'll get you
Quiet! We meet to work out a counter-measure
Be free to express your views
Do you accept Liang's proposal to rob?
Yes
What a good plot
No one dare to touch because they play police
What have we got
You're smart, you're right
What have we got? Force
Right
Well, why not
We're outnumbered
We can only win by stratagem
It makes sense
You always say 'yes'. You're a yes man
Right, right
Yes
Right again
If you don't say 'yes', and I don't either
we'll get at nothing the whole night
At least we now know force alone is impossible
Let's play along with them
I knew you'd say that
- Want another glass of beer, sir?
- Okay
Do I look like a policeman
Yes, but a short one
Am I that short
Come and contact us in time
Let's go
Go forward and watch
This seems to be a small place
I see
- Let's go out first
- Yes
Please sit down, Mr Chen
Your goods?
Overthere
Let's go and have a look
Scatter them
Overthere
Why have we no assignments
Who cares? We'll rob when the time's ripe
- Hope we can cooperate
- Yes
Boss, we're being surrounded by police
You fooled us. Let's go
Stop! We're police
Keep us covered
Make way, make way
My Diamonds. Return me the gems
Stop! Police
Stay where you are
We've surrounded the place. Give up
Keep me covered when I break out
That case
Going to hell
What now?
What shall we do
Break out. I'll keep you covered
I give up
Stay where you are
Stir and I'll shoot
Okay, let's return
Let's return
Have you a light, sir?
Yes
Where's that beauty?
Are you going to lend me
No
Let's return
It's the right time
Thank you
Thank you, thank you
Did we act well, boss?
Where's that case?
That case?
Overthere. Follow them
Stop them
It's here. Come up quickly
Hurry up
Go back
How's it?
Boss, they've got away
Hong, have you seen our police van
Yes, we saw it just now
Let's proceed as planned
Hey...
You turned brilliantly. Let me get out
I must stay alive to enjoy life
Don't drive so fast
Let's overtake his car
Don't regret
Go on
What now?
Sound the police siren
I know
What does that mean
They know we're imposters
Open up, open up
Back out at once
No, there's a truck behind
What now?
Go up and run against it
Help
Chuan, Chuan, where are you
Don't make advances
Don't touch, don't touch
Don't touch
Nonsense. Let's try to get out
How about this
They ran against our car
We can reverse it to
break it and get out
If no one dares, I'll do it myself
You're a girl. You mustn't do it
How stubborn. A girl's as capable
Anyone who can drive, raise his hand
So you can't drive then
I've never learnt it
Here's three toothpicks. Each draws one
Anyone getting the longest one
Stop talking. Draw now
You've finished drawing
See whose is the longest
The longest one needn't go
See which of you has got the shortest
Yours is the shortest
How even God knows who's the bravest
Catch them
Get back that stuff
There's still 4 there. Take them
Let's go
Hide under the car
They're hiding under the car
Follow them
Take him
Quick
What are you doing? Get in quick
It can't be opened
Follow them
Go over at once
Go ahead
Go and get it at once
What now?
Let's scatter
Let's overturn the car
Fling the case
Overthere
The case is overthere
Have you got it
Bastard
Go now
Get back the case first
Chuan, help me
Bring in quick
Sorry, it's blocked
Overthere
It's here
Come over, come over
Chuan, help me
Are you alright
Let me give you a punch and see
Get that case. I'll go and see Bonnie
Okay
So you're smoking here
You
What? Whoever you are
you mustn't be hiding here
You're paid all the same.
Aren't you ashamed
Sorry
Back to work
I'll go at once
Go now
Stop
You know what desperation is
They don't
We must be tough then
I give up
Toss the case over
Go up
Go now
Toss the case over
The case is overthere
Come up
Go up and follow him
Overthere
Go down
Watch out
I'm afraid
It's dead, don't
Still alive
Sheng
Chuan, run
Chuan, I'm here to help you
Bastard
What are you doing
Come and help
Can you fight? Come out when they finish
Right
Chuan, don't be afraid.
I'll vindicate you
Liang
I'm here to provoke a fight
Chuan, stand still
Stop now and get back that case
- Fix it yourself
- Come and help
Where are you going
Can't go up
Give me that case
We can't possibly find it out of so many
No more nonsense. Go on
Open it and see
It's worth the pains we've taken
No, we must hand it over to the police
We go to jail and you go to get it
No, it won't work anyway
Watch out! They're armed
Listen, you've been surrounded
It doesn't concern me
- I give you 3 seconds to give up with the loot
- What now?
1, 2, 3
We give up
Give up
What are they doing
We're giving up. Don't shoot
Lay down your arms
Stay where you are
Stop! What are you doing
Stand still
Let's go Let go
Let's go
Get back that case
Often I dream of the foamy sea
Of the boat, of you and me
Afore day break comes along
I am the prisoner of your eyes
which light up, like thunder, like fire
The very eyes I have been seeking
My heart is swollen with love
It goes out to you, to you
I live in memories sweet as honey
I shall find the nets meshed so fine
To keep the memories so divine
Hand in hand we look at the moon
I shall be with you all my life
Like the drone to the queen of the hive
Together, all our lives
Come what may, ebbs ortides