There have always been
conflicts in the martial arts world.
Some people think they can avoid conflict
by suppressing their earthly desires.
In fact, 'love' is the most
difficult thing to suppress.
So many heroes have lost their
nerve because of the women they love.
I am on a secret
mission for his Majesty.
I shall be gone for a few months. If you tell
anyone where I am, you will be killed.
Keep on going.
Who are you?
Are you going to rob us?
No. Your head is more valuable
than any of your possessions.
I can't believe I just saw that.
Some sweets for my Husband,
from Butterfly.
- Sister, did you see anything?
- Everything.
Don't worry, I've seen it before,
it hasn't changed in 10 years.
It's got bigger.
It's just like a mushroom.
It hasn't grown any bigger.
You're honest, but cruel. That's why
you can't get anyone to marry you.
How dare you talk to me like that?
I took care of anyone
who wanted to marry me.
I was just kidding. Are you angry?
You've become so heartless
since you met that Bee.
It's not Bee, she's called Butterfly.
You never come to visit me.
Isn't it delicious?
Butterfly cooked it.
That's why it tastes so awful.
I don't know why you're so fond of her.
A whore would be better.
Does she know our secret?
Of course not. She doesn't like
men from the martial arts world.
Her father was the Master
of the Vlll Divine School.
She comes from
the world of martial arts.
Her dad killed too many people
and asked her to stay away
from that world when he died.
Now she treats me like a merchant -
someone who knows nothing about kung fu.
So, just keep pretending you're a
common merchant and forget all about me.
What? But I care about you.
I've done everything
you asked me to do.
OK, I haven't visited you
as much as usual. I'm busy moving.
A new home in beautiful surroundings
will be good for stargazing.
Will Butterfly move there with you?
What is Li Shu Tin from the
West Chamber planning to do?
I don't know,
I am only a security officer.
You're not just a
a security officer, you're also a spy.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Tell her quickly.
The one down here is suffering.
Don't you want him alive?
Eunuch Tsao wants his head.
Give me the ball.
That's not fair.
Hey, this way.
Give it to me.
This way.
Your Excellency,
here is Lu's head.
But he refused to tell us
Li Shu Tin's plan.
Good job. Your help will bring
luck to our kingdom.
Thank you for the reward.
Be careful.
My body is getting weaker and weaker.
The royal doctor said I am very weak.
I might die before the
Mid-Autumn Festival.
Ko, I have a wish.
A wish I've had for a long time.
I hope, before I die...
Your Excellency,
do you want me to kill Li Shu Tin?
Li's collaboration with Suen Yuk Pa
has increased his power.
They want to control the world
of martial arts after my death,
together they will plan a coup.
Li Shu Tin gave Suen a secret letter,
in it are the details of the rebellion.
I want to get hold of this letter
and use it as evidence.
This way, once his Majesty knows their plans,
we won't be blamed for anything.
Your Excellency, do you want me
to destroy Suen's power?
Ten years ago, my Happy Forest
School fought against his Elite Villa School.
Don't ask me to do that now.
I know I have to destroy him one day,
but there are only 2 months
before the Mid-Autumn Festival.
It will be difficult to kill him
in such a short space of time.
But this is my wish.
I have to pay a high price for this.
I might have to sacrifice my life.
Wait. Then decide OK?
Do me a favor please.
This is a difficult mission.
But not impossible.
Do it before the Mid-Autumn Festival.
I'll wait for your good news.
I'll try my best.
You won't be disappointed.
The owner of this ball
must be very important.
It belongs to Prince Cha. He is the relative
and playmate of His Majesty.
His Majesty thinks he is clever.
I told him to learn
about internal affairs.
Soon you will have an excellent assistant.
But I am dying.
And he is too young
and not eager enough to learn.
What a pity.
Are you going to give me the ball?
You are smart. But what a pity
you love playing games so much.
How can you take on any responsibilities
if you aren't good at these games as well?
I have to thank you
for giving me the ball.
Where are you?
Come out I've got the ball back.
How is he ever going to be successful?
Master, there are a lot of great
fighters in the world of martial arts.
We've invited them all, but how
can we find the most powerful one?
Why did I recruit you?
Because I killed Hung,
the Master of the 12 Allied Swords.
Exactly. To find the real hero,
see who kills whom.
Why did I send the invitations?
Because I want a massacre.
Guess, go to Han's Forest.
Find no more than 10 heroes.
You are wise.
Master Suen, Ko of Happy Forest
will attack you at any time.
You must be careful about
the secret letter I wrote.
Look after it carefully.
Don't let the men of Happy Forest find it.
We'll be finished otherwise.
Li Shu Tin.
Dad, he...
I've told you before not to mess
around when I'm in a meeting.
But, I've reached
the 9th Grade of the Wonder Fists.
I want to practice with Brother Lui.
That's fine Suen Kim.
Call me by my nickname -
The Saint of the Sword.
OK, Saint of the Sword.
You lost this time, you owe me 50 taels.
Get lost.
Brother Lui, I am challenging you.
Tomorrow I'll wait for you.
Dad, I'm coming.
Brother Sing, be careful.
Isn't this fun?
- Take my hand, I'll help you over.
- Fine.
Brother Sing, be careful.
- You're not that bad.
- This is my home.
As a child, I was always
in the trees stargazing.
- These are for you.
- Thank you.
Let's go over there.
Do you like it?
Did you make it?
You deserve a kiss.
It's pretty.
When the house is built,
let's put the bed right here.
Then we can look
at the views everyday.
And then we could put in a skylight
so we could look at the stars at night.
Great.
What a lot of rain.
Please sir, give us shelter.
- Please give us shelter!
- Don't bother me.
Get lost.
Let's go here.
What a lot of rain.
Brother Sing I want his candy.
I'll get it for you later.
What are you doing there!
Go away.
Why did you kick her?
This is my doorway.
- Don't do that!
- Let's get him.
Who cares if it's your house.
Go to hell Fatty!
Don't think you can bully others like that.
You deserve a good lesson.
From now on,
we are Brothers and Sisters.
We will share the good and the bad.
We ask you to witness this.
Sister Ko,
I found the ones who beat me up.
Good. Ask Fatty's Gang
to come here. We'll kill them all now.
OK.
Go in.
Search them. Hurry up.
Are they the ones
who beat you up?
Sister Ko, they're the
ones who beat me up.
Hold it! If you've got guts,
let's fight one against one.
Who is going to fight with you?
Beat him!
Are you scared?
Have you finished?
Let's call it quits, OK.
Are you telling us his parents
wasted money on keeping him fat?
Correct.
So why not beat us to death?
What a hero, but I won't
be so stupid as to kill you.
Help us do one thing
and we'll forgive you.
Shush!
Don't go, you bastards. Stop!
- Brother Sing, I want to pee.
- You'll pee later.
I'll kill you!
Go Fatty!
Damn you bastards. I'll kill you.
How dare you!
It's not fair.
Don't go there.
Throw him to his death!
The sword!
Go to hell.
Hurry up, let's go.
You've got what it takes. From now on,
you can be in my gang.
I'll treat you to a feast tonight.
Great!
Here comes the food.
Great.
- Isn't it good?
- It's great.
Don't eat too much.
You know, fat people
shouldn't be in gangs.
So, why don't you go on a diet?
Eat less. Why don't you listen to me?
Damn you bitch.
You take my food and
treat those little bastards.
I wanna kill you. Don't run away.
He wants to kill us. Go now.
I want to burn you to death.
Yip Cheung, this way, come quickly.
Fatty how dare you.
Let's go.
You deserve it.
Put out the fire.
I'll get my revenge, you bitch.
Help! Come and put the fire out.
You naughty boy,
watching people bathing.
- Have you been here for a long time?
- You've been sleeping for ages.
You watched me bathe
when you were small, didn't you?
But now you're grown up and
you're scared of me.
I didn't watch you bathing.
I know you watched once.
Actually you have grown up.
Just tell me what you want.
Don't get me wrong...
Here you are!
Hey, I'm helping you now.
Don't tell her the truth.
You're useless.
Only fit for drinking.
Tell her you love her.
Today is a good day.
If you don't, don't blame me.
If we're friends,
keep you mouth shut.
As you're a friend
I'll tell her for you.
Sister Ko.
What's the matter. Shy?
No.
You are getting worse,
you always get hurt.
It's getting more and more serious.
You won't stay with me otherwise.
What did you say?
There is a rumour about the Evil Claw.
It kills a person in a thousand seconds.
Have you heard of it?
Lui Heung Chue's got it now.
You're really lucky.
The Evil Claw has hurt your left hand.
When you recover,
your left hand will be useless.
It is the fate of every killer.
Don't you feel sad?
I am pleased.
I prepare for death with every mission.
Do you know who I do this for?
You're always like this.
Just tell me honestly,
what is on your mind.
Suen's a great kung fu master.
He is difficult to handle.
What we have now
is sufficient for our future.
Have you ever
thought about your future?
Future?
We'll be the masters
of the martial arts world.
What then?
After that nothing else is important.
You are still a woman,
you should have a husband.
You should be able to
understand me after all these years.
I don't see myself as a woman. I don't
want you to treat me as a woman either.
Remember that.
But you won't tell Sing this.
Tench, pomfret, loach,
silurid fish, sole and carp.
It'll be funny if I can fish any of these.
Brother Sing, time to eat.
How's your fishing going?
I have to cheat again.
What are you doing?
Fishing is... really... difficult.
It's cold.
Time to eat.
So many dishes. Let's drink some wine.
No don't. You always make me drunk.
Now I will make myself drunk.
Hey...
If you're drunk,
you can't stop me leaving.
If I don't leave, how can I do business
and provide for both of us?
You know I always worry about you?
You're a straightforward man.
You don't know how horrible
the world of martial arts is.
My dad was a kung fu master.
He was killed.
You always come back safe.
It's thanks to my father's blessing.
Don't you agree?
Sure.
What's that smell. Did you fart?
See.
Smelly bean curd, I love it.
It stinks, but it's delicious.
It proves you can't judge
on appearances.
- Where is the fish I caught today?
- Here it is.
Oh, it smells good.
Be smart in business and you
won't end up a dead fish like this.
What should I do then?
You should be vicious.
But, most important of all
you should have this.
It looks like bean curd.
It's pigs brain, that means
you should use your brain.
That's right.
My God, please bless my husband
so he will be smart and make more money.
Then all women will be fond of him
and be seduced by him... Oh, no!
No, forget the things
I just mentioned.
I'll start from the very beginning.
My God, please bless my husband. Be safe
in this trip. Don't be framed by rascals.
Have a nice trip and come back soon.
Most important of all, don't be courted
by other girls and stay loyal to me.
Butterfly, what have you put
in my luggage? It's so heavy.
Why are there so many books?
These are the secret books
which you forbid me to see.
You said, you depended
on them for business.
I never said that.
You're right, these are the
books I need for business.
If you feel it's heavy just leave it.
No, it's not too heavy.
Where is my sword?
Where did you put my sword?
What's the use of
taking the sword with you?
It's for the sake of appearances
and it's useful to carry something.
It can be used as a stick.
I can cut fruit with it, and...
maybe fight with it as well.
Let me think, what I should
buy you as a souvenir?
- Cosmetics?
- No.
- Silk garments?
- No, too kitsch.
Any hints?
- This new product...
- A shovel?
No, it's for women.
Foreign women love it.
Thousands of Chinese
women find them attractive.
That's great. It must be wonderful.
Look.
This is called a bra.
And these are called underpants.
Bra and underpants.
Let me tell you. These two things give
ladies the perfect figure.
Men find them so attractive that they
are loyal to the women who wear them.
Ko has a nice figure...
She must use these.
That's great.
Remember to buy me these.
What a pretty moon tonight.
I don't want the moon to go.
Because when it goes, it means
it's time for you to leave me.
Can you cancel this trip?
I don't want to leave you.
But this is something we
have no control over.
It is confusing.
Like when we wake up and can't
remember a dream we've just had.
- Do you understand?
- Sure I do.
Don't think I don't understand.
Are you not leaving?
You're really smart. But wrong.
But I promise you
I will come back soon, very soon.
Keep you promise.
Butterfly, I am leaving now.
Try not to miss me. I'll miss you a lot.
And don't worry about me, or else
I'll end up worrying about you.
You should remember
not to treat Ko as your maid.
Learn how to sew if you have time.
Don't bother her.
Also, don't ever offend her over
silly things. Never offend her.
Get up early in the morning.
And make sure you eat properly.
You should control your diet.
I don't want to see a pig when I'm back.
And don't be such a big mouth.
Stop lying.
Don't trick Brother Yip.
Always remember
to wash every day.
You are a girl, be good
and don't sit like this.
Don't talk to your doll,
they'll think you're mad.
You have a lot of bad habits,
but don't hate yourself.
I have a lot of bad habits too.
We are two of a kind.
It's dawn. I have to go now.
I have been writing this letter all night.
Love you always, Sing.
Here it is beautiful, here is great,
How peaceful and prosperous it is here!
What a dangerous and messy world.
A swordsman was killed.
He was a great kung fu master,
from the Happy Forest.
He is called Meng Sing Wan.
I am scared to death.
You are supposed to be dead.
From now on,
you are called Tsun Wai.
You are a swordsman from
the South - a Cantonese.
Don't worry, I will get the
secret letter off Li before the autumn.
I will find out
about Suen Suk Pa.
We can kill him
this time if we join our forces.
On the first day of each month
Suen will book a room at a brothel.
The swordsman will spend one night
there with the best whore, Miu Siu Siu.
There are lots of performers from
the North there at the moment.
They perform by the shore each night,
I believe Suen will go there soon.
Sir, how about fortune telling?
- How much?
- 5 cents now, 50 taels next time.
Why are the prices so different?
If you don't trust me this time,
5 cents will mean a lot to you.
But if you think it's worth coming here
a second time, 50 taels isn't expensive.
- What do you want to know?
- Just tell me anything you know.
You are on a secret mission.
You're meeting a friend.
Have I ever seen this friend before?
Yes, and you will meet this friend again.
You haven't seen each other in 10 years.
5 cents is too expensive.
- Is my friend a man or woman?
- Woman.
I shouldn't ask
a blind man my fortune.
You are so arrogant.
Stop.
Sister Ko, I have reached the Elite Villa.
Suen Puk Pa trusts me.
I am now investigating
Li Shu Tin's letter.
Besides Suen, I've found
a hooker called Miu Siu Siu.
She looks like Ho Ching -
the one who disappeared 10 years ago.
I wonder if she is Ho Ching?
I'll carry on investigating.
How is Butterfly?
Why didn't you mention her?
I'd like to know what she is doing.
Please reply as soon as possible.
Meng Sing Wan.
- Who is it?
- Sister Ko, it's me.
I've come to visit you.
Hello Butterfly.
You are mistaken,
I am Little Butterfly.
Sing has had so many girlfriends,
I can't remember all their names.
Please forgive me.
- I made some dim sum for you.
- You know how to please people, don't you.
That's why Sing fell for you.
What do you want me to do for you?
Sister Ko, you're smart.
Sing wants you to teach me how to sew.
And I think I should dress like you.
You look so beautiful.
No one would believe
you're 10 years older than me.
You are wrong.
I am only 6 years older.
- You know I have a bad memory.
- Hey, you haven't returned my hairpin.
But you took the scarf which Brother Sing
sent me. Do you remember?
You can take anything
as you are so mean.
I don't want anything.
Brother Sing asked me not to argue you.
- He knows you are mean.
- Me?
I have made some clothes for Sing.
- I wonder if they will fit him.
- No?
We grew up together.
I know everything about him.
Grew up together?
I thought you were
just his babysitter.
What did you say.
Nothing, just kidding.
What an awful colour.
Sing loves these two colours.
I've never seen him
wearing this colour before.
How long have you been with him?
We lived together for over 10 years.
I know his loves and hates.
- It's too sweet.
- Sing loves sweet things.
I thought you understood Sing.
I won't eat anything,
I'll save it for Yip Cheung.
Sister Ko, you like Yip.
Actually, you two are a
perfect match for each other.
Stop it,
if he hears that he'll misunderstand.
You know he is a serious man
and you always make fun of him.
Yip is serious, but he treats you well.
Hey, he can't cope with Sing anyway.
I agree.
Lots of girls love Sing.
I've worried so much about his trip this time,
but I tell myself not to.
He has a secret weapon.
Just tell me, or forget it.
I'll tell you, but just because it's you.
I'm pregnant.
- Are you sure it's Sing's baby?
- What do you mean?
Why are you so serious?
I'm joking.
I'm going to look for Yip Cheung.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
You're lying. Your mouth is dirty.
Really? What is it?
Are you drunk again?
Why did you kiss the picture?
I didn't.
Give it to me.
Stop teasing me.
Who is she? Your lover?
I'm not teasing you.
I've brought you some dim sum.
Master Suen, how is our plan going?
It's going smoothly.
We have sent out all the invitations.
On the 8th day of August, all
the heroes of the martial arts world
will gather at Han's Forest.
Then,
the Yellow Dragon Horse Troop will pick them.
We will set out at once to destroy
Ko and her Happy Forest.
If I chop the claws off a crab,
how far will it go?
Tsao Sau Ching,
how well can you cope with me?
Master Suen, our mission
is going to be successful.
The title of Master of the martial
arts world is reserved for you.
Thank you.
But be careful.
Many great kung fu masters
are found in the Happy Forest School.
Don't worry.
I have something to report too.
Last month, I recruited a
great swordsman from Hai Fung.
He is as great at martial arts
as Lui Heung Chuen.
You mean Chun Wai.
You are well informed.
To get the title of Master
of the martial arts world
everyone wants to recruit
great swordsmen.
It is easy to recruit,
but much harder to make a man loyal.
Your Excellency.
I know what you mean.
We should find out what your opponent's
weakness is, so we can control him.
All Lui Heung Cheun wants is money.
Chun Wai wants my lover.
Only believe it if you have
seen it with your own eyes.
Remember,
you should be careful.
I will always remember your words.
Sister Ko, Suen Yuk Pa
is now arranging the moves.
On the 8th day of August, he'll send
the Yellow Dragon Horse Troop
to bring some heroes to his villa.
You should try your very best to stop
him otherwise we will be in deep shit.
I will inform you straight away of any news.
If I get any. Meng Sing Wan.
How dare you.
We are the guests
of the Elite Villa.
Well, that means
I haven't made any mistakes.
Sir, what's happened?
Miss, we found this corpse.
We found this letter in his luggage.
We sent it to the address written on it.
Go and check whether the
dead man is your relative.
Go.
Butterfly.
Yip Cheung,
what's wrong with Brother Sing?
Round them up.
Master, we've found something.
Ho Ching.
What did you say?
What do you mean?
You look like one of my friends.
What did you say?
How old are you?
Where do you come from?
Are you...
Chun Wai, how dare you
be so rude to Miss Miu.
Suen Kim.
Dad, he was rude to Miss Miu.
Stop. I have some good
news to announce to you all.
In three days, I will marry
Miss Miu to Chun Wai.
Miss Miu, congratulations.
Master, in fact I...
I know what's on your mind.
You won't blame me for not
informing you before, right?
I...
You're lucky.
You'd better keep your mouth shut.
Bravo.
Give me the arrow.
Master, will you
give us more luck?
Ha ha, so what, I love it.
- Monkey!
- Yes.
Bring the wine.
Go and pay.
See, it overflows.
Look.
You lost, so you're paying for it.
You should drink some, young master.
Damn you.
Master Suen, please don't.
Go away.
We haven't held such a
big party in a long time.
I envy you.
The Master has placed his
trust in you very quickly.
Actually, I am happy,
but I do have some worries.
I am afraid
that I would disappoint you.
I've never made any
bad judgements.
You two are a great help.
Just work together
without arousing suspicion.
It'll be the end of that bitch.
Ko, who wants to challenge me?
When will we set out to
destroy her Happy Forest?
I want to have fun...
You've messed up again.
Get lost, now take him away.
Let go of me.
What a jerk.
- Master, may I be excused?
- Yes.
Hands off me,
I want to have fun.
Good night.
It's you.
- Master!
- Kill her!
Get her.
Are you Ho Ching?
Why are you doing this?
This is Sister Ko's mission.
Suen always keeps the letter with her.
I will no longer be his woman.
I won't stand a chance if
I don't do anything now.
You are Ho Ching.
Ho Ching.
I failed. I can't face Ko again.
Take care.
Don't. Ho Ching.
Brother Lui, I'm mourning.
I can't take on any jobs for a few days.
I'll report for duty in a few days.
Please inform Master Suen.
Ho Ching didn't disappear.
She has been staying with the Elite Villa.
Why did you cheat on us?
How else have you deceived us?
I've always treated you as my family.
I want to know why you raised us?
To kill? To get rid of your enemy?
Or do you want to be the leader
of the martial arts world?
Have you got any feelings.
You are heartless.
Have you tried to understand me?
I have to cope with so
much in order to survive.
Don't make excuses!
You are so selfish.
I don't know what you're thinking.
But I know you're after money.
Have you had enough?
I have never shed any
tears in front of anyone.
I can't believe you
would blame me like this.
I do feel sad about Ho Ching's death.
Do you think I love killing?
That money is my only reason for killing?
Ever since I entered the world of martial arts,
I've never had the choice.
I haven't smiled since I was born.
I am not happy,
I am always scared.
What makes me feel good
is that I am still alive.
But I have to pay
such a high price.
Do I look like a woman?
Am I not attractive?
I understand.
You don't know what I am thinking.
I don't want to be a puppet again.
I want to choose my own path.
It's too late to say that.
You know, if we or the
Happy Forest want to survive,
we should compete with others.
The Happy Forest and the
Elite Villa can't live side by side.
This is the rule of the martial arts world.
I don't care about rules.
I just want to know if it's the last time.
Stop asking.
I'd never hurt you, I am not your enemy.
In fact, I'll always protect you.
You have done everything well.
Have you ever thought
about the pressure I bear?
Sometimes I ask
myself what I am doing.
I am not related to you.
But when I see you so happy,
I know it's worth it.
I have realised
that I am only a woman now.
I promise this is the last time.
Thank you.
Meng Sing Wan!
Aunt Sans' daughter was
pregnant before her marriage.
The Master of the village said
she should be drowned.
It's a punishment. We should
get her as soon as possible.
Damn it, how long
should I hide up here?
Sing is missing.
But my baby is growing
bigger and bigger.
What should I do?
Tell me.
I'd better not talk to you.
Brother Sing asked me
not to talk to dolls.
I have to get rid of this
habit before he comes back.
Brother Sing!
You shouldn't jump.
The roof might collapse.
You always tease me.
It's time for revenge.
You're not in a good mood.
I'm not in a good mood either.
I have brought you
a bottle of wonderful wine.
Sing said that you like to get drunk.
You have company tonight.
We can forget all the bad stuff if we drink.
Fine.
Tell me the truth, is Sing dead?
If he is alive,
why didn't he come back?
Did he talk to you?
I always treated you as my family.
You should believe me.
I will bring him here, no matter what.
Why don't you let me go to the
Happy Forest? Is Sister Ko our family?
You'll understand
that this is a complicated world later.
It's the same story again.
You always use the world of martial arts
to explain difficult things.
I don't understand.
Sing and I don't belong to the world of martial arts.
Why do we have so many problems?
The world of martial arts has no boundaries.
The living can't escape any problems.
Please stop saying such confusing things.
You mean someone wants
to hurt me and Sing?
Sure.
When he finds out you're an obstacle
on his road to success, you'll be in trouble.
Who am I bothering?
You don't even understand.
So stop asking.
I won't ask again.
You're not answering my question.
Hey...
What a big pack of herbs.
That's why he is so upset.
Fire...
It's not a fire,
I am boiling the herbal tea for you.
You might look funny, but you won't
make me laugh. I am still angry.
Drink it.
- Are we friends again?
- It's good for the baby.
I don't want to drink it.
It took four hours to make.
You should drink it.
I did this for your family.
Are you going against them?
I love it.
You can't handle the woman you love.
Why should you bother my family?
What woman?
Sister Ko.
I know you love her.
Don't drink it then!
Careful, the house will collapse.
Oh, I'll drink it!
I knew it was you. What are you doing?
It's two days from the Mid-Autumn Festival.
I brought you some treats.
Why didn't you come in
through the main gate?
I am a great kung fu master,
you know.
Stop pretending I'm still mad at you.
I'm not that mean.
I went to the temple to pray for you.
I am not angry. I wish you good health
before Sing's return.
You mean, Sing is coming back
before the Mid-Autumn Festival?
Maybe.
It's a promise.
Remember to keep your promise.
And to bring Sing back to me.
That's good. I won't be so lonely then.
It will be a family reunion.
But you must be sad
not to have anyone.
I'm so serious.
I don't know how to please girls.
I've so many faults,
I am destined to be a monk.
Don't be so upset,
you can improve yourself.
How?
You should learn how
to express yourself.
Just tell others
what you are thinking.
Most important of all, smile.
Learn how to smile?
Yes, smile now.
You look awful. You'd better not laugh.
You'd scare everyone.
I haven't finished yet. Your biggest
problem is that you are too mean.
Also, keep your promises.
According to Sun's Military Advice, it is wise
to act as quick as lightning in any attack.
We should attack suddenly.
You are gathered here.
What I want to tell you is that
this is a critical moment.
We are going to attack
the Happy Forest tonight.
The swordsmen of the Yellow Dragon
Horse Troop will go with us
and attack those bastards.
Suen Kim!
My son...
You bastard!
Sing Wan!
With this armour on
how can you hurt me?
Where's the Evil Claw that
you attacked me with last time?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I never attacked you.
Your Excellency.
We have destroyed Suen Yuk Pa.
We also have Li's secret letter.
Good, well done.
You haven't disappointed me.
Opening the secret letter
will reveal their plan.
Be careful.
I was pretending
to be Eunuch Li!
I killed the real Li Shui Tin
a long time ago.
I knew there would be a battle between
the two most powerful forces if I did this.
And that then I'd be able to control
the entire martial arts world.
But you can help me
to fulfil one more wish.
Tell the King of Hell this good news!
You bastard,
I already know your plan.
I'll take the opportunity
to watch your moves.
In two months time,
you will show your real face to us.
Bullshit, why are you so arrogant?
Licence to kill.
Bullshit.
How dare you betray me.
The magic ball.
The Whirlwind Kick.
Lightning Kick.
Super Strike.
You are so stupid. It's an iron ball.
The real ball is here.
The Flying Arrow.
Fatal Kick.
Thank you so much.
If it wasn't for your help,
we wouldn't have killed Tsao.
His Majesty will be very happy.
I won't go back to the capital.
I love these games, I'd hate to
do a normal job. Take care.
Little Whirlwind.
From now on, the martial
arts world belongs to us.
I hope you can stay with me.
Brother Sing.
Look out!
Butterfly.