Lau Man-chai from Shandong,
Moun Chun from Shanxi
Dai Nan-gai from Shensi,
Shun Do Wong-bat from Hunan
and Ga Gung-gung from Beijing
all bought their guns from me.
Everybody makes friends with me.
What about Fok Lo-dai from Kunming?
We've gone through a lot together.
But my grandfather retired
20 years ago.
Oh, you are Fok Lo-dai's
granddaughter?
Why didn't you say so?
You'll make a fortune
transporting my goods.
Let's worry about this deal now
and we'll talk later.
Baldy!
I know him really well. I remember
when he had a full head of hair.
They're coming!
Everybody, I'm here again.
How are you all?
Long time no see.
Low Sai, you've put on weight.
Chow Pei, your skin is so smooth.
How Tow, you fought with Dan Nan-ying
and lived to tell the tale.
- Are you OK?
- I'm fine.
Brother Wang!
How are you, brother Wang?
- I haven't seen you for a long time.
- It's been ages.
I'm glad to see you today, brother.
Are these your goods?
The goods you want. I'd go through
hell's fires to bring you this.
There is a story behind this,
everybody.
The Japanese were able to conquer
Manchuria all because of this weapon.
You can do anything with this gun -
including killing that Dan Nan-ying.
Cut the crap and give us
a demonstration.
OK.
Don't judge it by its size. You can
kill from one hundred feet away.
Stand back.
It makes a really big bang.
Let me try.
What are you laughing at?
I don't know how to use it.
It's really easy-open it, put
in the bullets, close it and lock it.
That's it.
OK.
Stand in front.
Dan Nan-ying is gonna die!
Hey, don't get me wrong,
I don't want revenge.
But you killed him, so how will I
collect the money he owed me?
Of course you'll get your money.
OK, hand over my 20 quid, please.
There's more than a hundred in here.
Come and get it.
You are a pain in the neck.
Get rid of her!
Will you pay me now?
I will.
Fuck you!
I will, I will!
You could have paid me earlier.
Now we're quits.
After her!
Fuck your grandmother, you bitch!
Bitch!
Fuck your ancestors!
"United East Asia!"
The Japanese are serious trouble.
Son of a bitch!
Are you mad?
What about that Chinese guy?
He's gone.
Thank you. Bye.
My Lord.
Turn around! Quickly, turn around!
- Why?
- Do I have to explain my order?
Count to five hundred, quick.
OK.
One, two, three, four, five...
Do you want to get me killed?
You could be recognised coming here.
My identity has been exposed.
What?!
Then I'm finished.
Don't worry,
they don't know you're co-operating.
That's better.
Aren't you going
to a council meeting?
Shit! I almost forgot.
You must postpone it.
- Postpone it?!
- As a favour to me.
Someone's flying over to get you.
What, again?!
I've never seen so much as a fly!
Don't tell anyone you eavesdrop.
...ninety-two, ninety-three,
ninety-four, ninety-five...
So many people!
What should I say today?
Regarding imperial Japan's
development of this city Kaa Yi,
I wonder if you have made a decision.
I'm still thinking about it.
We already agreed to co-operate
with the Japanese.
Did we?
It seems we did.
Yes, yes.
I've talked about the development. We
are going to build a chemical plant.
- Do you mean a poison gas plant?
- Yes.
If you have no objections, I'll start
sending in the raw materials.
There's no need to hurry.
Don't worry, My Lord, everything is
arranged, it shouldn't be a problem.
Well, in that case, the materials
will be shipped here in four days.
Come on!
Are you going to tell
the truth or not?!
I'll chop it off!
- Are you OK, Grandpa?
- I'm fine.
What happened, Grandpa?
Lung, didn't I tell you
there's no need to test her?
Now do you believe how good
my granddaughter is?
Not bad, not bad.
Come and say hello to Uncle Lung.
He is a pillar of our community.
I do look like some Mafia boss.
We're not just playing with you.
It's a matter that concerns
the whole country, all of us.
This here is Puttan.
There's a city there called Kaa Yi.
The ruler of the city is Youda.
He's got some information
on the Japanese,
but he's scared to death of them.
If we fly him to Guangzhou City,
he'll tell us what he knows.
So...
Ming-ming, we're doing this
for our country. Don't get mad.
I should be mad.
You make a simple matter like this
so complicated.
Why don't you just tell me to go?
- When do I leave?
- Tomorrow morning.
Right, when you get to Kaa Yi City,
look for our agent Sky 001.
But I've never met him.
No problem.
Just remember this watch.
OK.
- The pigeon.
- Yes.
Pigeon, pigeon,
what do you need a watch for?
There is a Chinese plane ahead.
- Shoot it down.
- Yes, sir.
Have you seen this man?
Have you seen this guy?
- Have you?
- Have you seen him?
- Well, have you?
- Have you?
Asshole! I bet you everything
you've got!
No problem. Come on.
Yours is heavier.
For telescopic sight.
A wonderful torch.
This is America's newest toy,
the yo-yo.
It's almost there.
Let's play.
Is it loaded?
Use another one.
- Use this.
- No problem.
It's gone.
I'll go and get it.
Why did you throw it away?
I don't trust you.
Stay here, I'll be right back.
Who are you?
You must have the wrong guy.
A lot of people look alike,
don't you agree?
Stop it!
Who dares to make trouble
in Kaa Yi City?
Those three big guys over there.
Mind your own goddam business, bitch!
Come on, fight back.
You stay out of it.
Good... You are really fantastic.
Thanks for helping out.
That should teach you guys a lesson
for cheating.
He cheated us and beat us up.
Our reputations are ruined!
- They're completely unreasonable.
- Who said we're unreasonable?
You started all this trouble!
He cheated us.
We should teach him a lesson.
- Am I right?
- I can't say you're wrong.
I bet with them, I won.
That's not wrong.
You're not wrong either.
But he's a swindler.
Then you're wrong.
We played Numbers.
He threw 2, I threw 6.
- So I win, right?
- Right.
- He threw 5, I threw 6. I win, yes?
- Yes.
- He threw 6, I threw 7. I win, yes?
- No.
The biggest number on a die is 6,
you cheated!
Stop it!
Everybody said you're wrong,
so you must be wrong.
If you're wrong, they must be right.
I helped you, so I must be wrong.
Yes, you are wrong.
If you help a guy to correct
his mistakes...
- Are you right?
- Right.
Cheating is wrong,
but you helping me was right, right?
Right.
Wait, wait, let me think.
You cheated, you're wrong.
I helped you, I'm right.
You are a cheat. You beat him up.
You're wrong. You're right.
You're causing trouble,
you're wrong!
It's too complicated. I quit!
Why don't we have a drink?
Come on, guys, let's talk about this.
No more fighting, OK?
Do you think I will run away
or something?
Help! Help!
If you get a kick out of beating me
then beat me.
Hey, hold it, guys.
Sky 001, I'll help you.
- OK, help me get rid of them.
- OK.
I want that one. Hurry up.
Don't you want this?
Thank you for saving my life, lady.
- Eat something.
- Don't waste your time, Sky 001.
What's this Sky 001?
So you know I'm Sky 001, now what?
Go save Youda.
Excuse me. Why should I save Youda?
I've got my money,
my job is to take Youda away.
Money? Do I get paid?
You two want to save Youda?
What if I say yes?
I certainly hope so.
Why is that?
You are...?
I am Sky 001.
I am 003, he's 004.
We are disguised as Japanese.
No wonder I've never seen you before.
I am your superior.
- We're leaving.
- Where to?
Didn't headquarters tell you? We're
to take Youda's jewellery as well.
Of course they did.
Let's go.
Please, it's just around the corner.
Really?
It's quite near.
We'll be there soon.
Don't move
or I'll blow a hole in you.
Don't move.
You're Japanese?
But you're mistaken. I'm not Sky 001.
We knew that.
What's the problem?
It's none of my business.
What are you doing? Can we talk?
Yes, why don't we talk?
We'll talk inside, move!
Thank you.
Don't move!
Come on...
Back to headquarters with me.
Don't chase him. Let's go.
Why did you save us?
Because I'm Sky 001.
I just found this.
- Where are you taking us now?
- To save Youda.
You two please go ahead. I've got
some urgent matters to attend to.
Leave him.
If the Japanese go into the palace,
Youda's co-operation
will no longer be secret.
It will be difficult to save him.
Why is it difficult?
At worst, we'll have to fight.
Come on.
This way.
Thanks for saving my life.
But you saved me twice,
I still owe you.
But don't worry, I'll pay you back.
I'm beginning to understand
why Headquarters sent a girl.
To quash your chauvinism.
Now we'll do a test.
This is the result
of a joint experiment
between the Japanese Empire
and a neighbouring country.
But General Toga,
he only drives the sheep.
This can of gas is small
but it can kill more than ten men.
His family depends on
this one man here.
It only takes five seconds.
Five seconds?
If you want to test it,
test it on a dog.
- Is it really that powerful?
- Try it if you don't believe me.
I'm going to take a bath.
Come on.
Come with me.
Don't be afraid,
I'll give you another chance.
If you can hold your breath
for five seconds, you're safe.
One... two...
Five!
Damn Japanese!
It's important to save Youda.
OK, you look for him,
I'll watch the Japanese.
OK.
Stay cool, I still owe you one.
If you die, I can't pay you back.
Congratulations, General.
With this gas,
the imperial Army is invincible.
Even without it,
we are still invincible.
I want this war to end quickly.
General, General!
General, there is a Chinese woman
here looking for Youda.
Youda is...
Spread out!
Who are you?
You look so nervous.
You must be Youda.
- What are you?
- Chinese.
You're all right. It's probably
just Sky 001. I'll get it.
You'll get me
in serious trouble, woman. Hide!
Why should I hide?
If you don't hide, I'll...
Youda...
Keep it down.
Are you decent?
Of course! I'm no exhibitionist!
There's a woman here looking for you.
- I know.
- How did you know?
Aren't you a woman?
You finally see me as a woman.
Youda...
Stop fooling around. I think
that woman wants to rescue you.
You're so bad,
you should have told me.
I don't even have enough time
to pack.
What are you talking about?
You fooled me last time
at the temple.
I heard you talking to Sky 001.
You said if I didn't tell my dad,
you would take me with you!
So what!
You're having second thoughts?
I'll tell my dad!
Chin-chin!
It's my dad, what should I do?
Shit!
What took you so long to answer?
I thought you'd been kidnapped.
I was just bathing.
I didn't hear you.
A woman came into this palace.
She may be hiding in here.
I was bathing. I didn't see anyone.
For your safety,
I want this room searched.
Your daughter's in there.
There was a spider.
- Who are you?
- The Chinese woman.
Our city does not welcome Chinese.
You don't? Well, I'll go, then.
Not so fast!
Youda.
You want to kill me.
Shit.
If you want to help me live,
stop your father.
If you go, then what about me?
OK, I'll meet you at the temple.
Help!
Are you all right?
I'll help you, Dad.
Please get Youda out of here.
I'll stop Dad for you.
Fine.
- Murderer!
- Don't stop me!
- Kick me.
- OK.
Hurry up!
Over here, woman.
I'm just a wanderer.
It's none of my business.
Why did China send you here?
Send me here? What for? China?
General, test your new product.
Please.
I remember,
China sent me on a mission of peace.
No. To do business?
I wasn't sent
to test the poisonous gas!
I was lucky to get away.
Should I save him?
Why should I risk my life?
He seems to be able to handle them.
I'd better go.
But this is too cowardly. No!
- You're just in time to rescue him.
- I'm used to it.
So I don't owe you any more.
- Let's get out of here!
- Go!
What are you trying to say?
I am the ruler of Kaa Yi City.
The Japanese want to build
a poisonous gas plant.
So for everyone's sake,
I should tell him everything.
Since he is a Chinese spy,
he will be grateful and he will send
a plane to take me somewhere safe.
So you are the Chinese pilot,
sent here to fetch me.
And you... you...
This is nothing to do with you?
Why not?
Defeating Japanese imperialism,
uniting the Chinese people for future
generations, establishing peace.
This has nothing to do with me?
- Is that so?!
- You're nuts.
What? Is it wrong to fight for peace?
Since we all have the same goal,
if you leave, I'll support you...
and we'll leave together.
Go? How?
Your plane.
It's out of fuel.
How come?
On my way here, the Japanese hit
my fuel tank. Now it's empty.
Don't worry. I know where we can find
fuel. The Japanese supply station.
Right.
Then hurry. Go and get it.
We'll be home in no time.
Have a nice trip back.
What do you mean?
Aren't you going with us?
I'm staying here to get rid of Toga.
Once he's dead,
there'll be no more plant.
Don't worry, you go back first.
I'll see you in China.
How are you going to get rid of Toga?
He's got so many men.
If necessary, I'll die with him.
He goes to the supply station
every night. I must take this chance.
Why didn't you say?
We can kill two birds with one stone.
Get the fuel and kill Toga.
I want to make sure we can get away.
Since everybody's agreed,
it's a deal.
- You really would help me?
- We'll help each other.
We help you kill Toga,
you help us get the fuel.
It's settled.
Thank you.
Wait!
You two are lovers.
You two are business partners,
but you will become lovers soon.
But I have nothing.
So tell me, will you desert me?
Don't worry. We're in this together.
And we won't leave anyone behind?
No!
- Miss, what is it?
- Dad said to keep a tighter patrol.
I want to look inside.
Miss, no one is allowed
in without a permit.
- Where's the oil?
- The Lieutenant knows. I'll ask him.
Bring him here, let me ask him.
Lieutenant!
They threatened me...
- Where's the oil?
- In the barrels with the red line.
- I'll get Youda.
- Wait, where's Toga?
He didn't come.
No more talking! Move!
Hurry! Where is he?
We said we wouldn't leave
until we killed Toga.
Don't be such an idiot.
We can move the oil first.
No.
Stop!
Stop or I'll shoot.
We're waiting for Toga.
Why are you pointing a gun
at your friend?
I never looked on you as a friend.
- You...
- Don't move, or I'll shoot.
I'm doing this for everyone's good.
What are you doing?
Leave him alone, he's crazy.
Let's move. You watch him.
I hope you're not as crazy as him.
In that case, let's vote.
- Do you want to go?
- Of course.
- And you?
- I'm following Youda.
How about you?
My job is to take Youda away.
Meeting's over. Let's move.
I said they'd come.
Take them away.
Dad, don't shoot! I was kidnapped!
- Don't move!
- Hold your fire!
Move and I kill her.
Chin-chin!
Hold your fire!
The lighter!
Get in the car!
Get out!
Get in! Hurry, get in!
Get in and go!
Bring him with us.
Go!
An imperial Japanese Officer
will never be taken alive.
Leave him! Come on!
No! I must kill him tonight!
You go!
- I will die with him!
- Don't be a fool.
Come on!
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
Lady, save the love song
for later, OK?
Mind your own business.
- I'll distract them.
- Be careful.
Shit!
- Follow me.
- OK.
I'm free!
We're back!
I've come to rescue you!
We didn't desert you!
- Are you all right?
- Yes, thank you.
Hop in!
Jump!
We're finished. We can't go home now.
Are you happy now?
The Japanese are here
to develop Kaa Yi City.
We are all in favour of Kaa Yi City.
For a better quality of life,
we should give our full support
to the lmperial Japanese Army.
So the Japanese...
Woman, I don't even
know your name yet.
Her name is Ming-ming.
Her grandfather defeated
Dai Do Gow Mei Wu single-handedly.
Ten years ago, your dad was betrayed
by General Geung Cheu Lam's man.
Your dad was killed by the guy
who betrayed him.
Is that true? How do you know?
That's none of your business.
Are you family?
If you want to know the whole story
don't interrupt me.
So then you lived with your granddad
and two years ago got your revenge.
- What happened next?
- Well...
Then she broke up with her boyfriend.
But she hates men that wear leather
jackets and silk scarves
and who put on the charm.
That's not true.
You've given in so soon?
She's just trying to embarrass you.
Embarrass me?
Let's see who's got the better life.
- I think I do.
- We'll see.
You were an orphan
so you had to rely on yourself.
Then you became a swindler
and lots of people hated you.
In order to avoid them
you became a wanderer.
- Am I right?
- How did you know?
You wanderers are all the same.
So what's special about you, then?
I'm a bit more special than you.
I've been a spy for five years
and they call me Sky 001.
My real name is Wong Siu-fong.
What a girlie name!
It sounds all right to me.
You're giving in again.
He hasn't finished.
I was adopted by a robber, then...
Then you destroyed
your foster father's gang,
but you felt really bad about it
and you let him go.
Now he's a businessman in Hong Kong,
and you really want to be a doctor.
- Then...
- Then you could become a doctor...
once you were reincarnated.
You were in your boss's good books as
you had destroyed your father's gang.
You went from strength to strength
to become Sky 001 in two years.
You don't need to ask me how I know,
I got it all from Granddad.
My granddad wouldn't allow me
to work with a stranger.
Your story is very touching
and yours is legendary.
You're a perfect match.
If you don't die now,
and you have a child one day,
call him Touching Wong if it's a boy
and Legendary Wong if it's a girl.
If you have a second child,
call it Wanderer Wong.
It seems as if our chat
is disturbing someone.
...so whoever comes between
the imperial Japanese Army
and Kaa Yi City will be executed!
Don't you all agree?
Now I know you're so reasonable,
I've decided to betray them.
I'll let you in on
some secret information.
The secret news is...
Come on.
What secret?
You have foul breath,
did you just eat shit?
I want to find Youda.
Youda!
General Toga.
The execution starts in ten minutes.
Memorise it
and say it at the execution.
I, Youda, ruler of Kaa Yi City,
sentence these three people to death
because they sabotaged
the order of United East Asia.
Loyalty to the
Imperial Japanese Empire.
Bullshit!
I, Youda, ruler of Kaa Yi City,
sentence these three people to death.
Chin-chin, Chin-chin.
Youda.
Everything's OK.
You will be well soon.
What about the others?
Gone, all gone.
Why?
- I set them free.
- The Japanese agreed?
Of course not, so I gave them hell.
I stood up and said to them...
I am the ruler of Kaa Yi,
I order you to set them free.
If you don't,
I'll kick you all out.
The Japanese were scared shitless,
and set them free.
Really?
I've never lied to you, have I?
They are all good people.
They deserve to be happy.
You'd better rest
and not think about this.
I, Youda, ruler of Kaa Yi City,
sentence these three people to death
because they sabotaged
the order of the United East Asia.
Imperial Japan...
You can't make me do it!
They injured your daughter!
Don't you have feelings?
The Japanese are armed to the teeth,
what can we do?
I don't care! I want to rescue them.
You are risking your own life.
Even if you want to do this, you
still cannot save them, so why do it?
If they were really your friends,
they wouldn't want you to die.
My Lord, you have to do this.
Executioners, get ready!
My Lord, please be ready.
I, Youda, ruler of Kaa Yi City,
sentence these three people...
to be set free.
Release them!
Whoever sabotaged relations between
Kaa Yi and the imperial Japanese
is committing a severe crime.
Even though Youda is your ruler,
he is as guilty as the others.
Every man should be equal.
So in order to preserve fairness
and justice,
I sentence Youda to death
along with the others.
Am I a friend or what?
One...
Two...
Three...
You cannot kill Youda!
Ready!
One, two...
No! You can't kill Youda!
- No!
- One...
- No! You cannot kill Youda!
- Chin-chin!
You can't kill them, you can't!
You can't kill them!
Stop!
Dad!
Chin-chin!
No more delays.
Ready, take aim...
One...
Fire!
Rescue our ruler!
Quick! Quick!
Quick!
How can you fight the Japanese
with this?
Maybe they won't come back.
I want to avenge my father's death.
They'll be back.
If you're afraid, leave now.
I'm not that kind of person.
I'm afraid they might make mincemeat
of you.
Then we can eat mincemeat tomorrow.
Youda, please give the order.
OK, I'll summon everyone to the city.
I...
ruler of Kaa Yi City,
Youda, now call for full
force protection of our city.
- This is war!
- War!
War! War! War...
You're dead!
War!
Fire!
Get ready!
- You stay here, I have to go.
- OK.
Forward!
Quick, they're coming!
One, two, three, fire!
Put it there... fire!
Knock the gate down!
Son of a bitch!
They're bombing the gate! Jump!
Find them!
Spread out!
- Forward!
You traitor!
- No sign of them, sir.
- Continue the search!
Yes, sir.
Lieutenant, your orders?
What the hell is going on? Damn it!
You son of a bitch!
Throw them!
Everyone, retreat! Quick, hurry up!
Come on, come on!
Faster!
Not a bad watch.
What are you doing?
Sorry, sir.
If you people have any guts,
come get me!
Kill him!
Come and get me!
Everyone stop!
They're all dead!
Move that body out of the way.
Come out.
- Are they all dead?
- Yes.
Retreat.
Move.
Watch out!
General, it's too much,
we can't continue.
As an officer,
you should set a good example.
Follow me.
Take these guns.
- How's it going?
- Fine.
Let me.
Put down your weapons
and your families will be OK.
Mum! Mum!
Siu-bo!
Surrender now
or more people will die.
I surrender, I surrender.
Don't kill my people.
Put down your weapons.
OK?
Youda, don't surrender!
Duck!
I want to kill him!
Don't, don't!
Two wrongs don't make a right.
You can go now, but tell your people
that we're a peaceful race.
The invader always loses.
Everyone, I've got something to say.
Reinforcements are on their way.
This time we are going to succeed.
If you continue resisting,
you will lose.
But I have a solution.
Your orders, sir.
What happened?
- We did our best but...
- Nonsense! What really happened?
They made a strong stand and set fire
to the city to try and wipe us out.
Such a fine city going up in smoke.
What a pity.
I'd rather see this
than my people suffer.
As long as there are people,
we can build a new city.
Without this city, there's nowhere
for their gas plant. I need a break.
Do you have time for a break?
I'll take you out in my aeroplane.
Are you flying to China?
I really want to go back home.
Sorry, I've only got room for two.
Really?
But there's a cargo compartment,
if you don't mind.
I don't mind. I don't mind at all!
I really don't mind.
This city is practically useless!
Retreat.
Yes, sir!