Evening, handsome.
Hi, Lucille.
How you've been?
Okay.
- Evening, Hank.
- Hey, Betty, how's your mama now?
She's good.
Here you go.
So...
How you been?
- Pretty good, and you?
- Pretty good.
How's Sonny?
He's all right, I guess.
Vera, how are you doing?
- I'm good, how are you?
- I'm good.
Here.
It's all right.
- You want a drink?
- Oh yeah, thanks hon.
Wild Turkey.
I'm sore,
so go easy, darling.
Yes ma'am.
- Thanks, Vera.
- You're welcome.
Yeah.
What's the matter, hon?
You look so sad.
I'm fine.
Hey?
You wanna... You wanna get something to eat?
- Talk?
- Take care, Sonny.
Morning, Pop.
This shit's cold.
I'm gonna get some more.
What the hell are
those niggers doing out there?
I said something to you.
Did you hear me?
Yeah.
Damn porch monkeys.
Be moving in here soon.
Sitting next to me...
watching my TV.
There was a time
when they knew their place.
Wasn't none of this
mixing going on.
Your mother,
she hated them niggers, too.
Tell them to get
the hell off my property.
- You put that thing down.
- We came by to see Sonny.
I don't give a damn
who you come by to see.
Get them out of here
right now.
Tell them. They're your buddies.
Tell them to get out of here.
What are you standing there for?
You watch your ass, all right?
- You got everything you need?
- Yeah.
- Be careful walking around.
- Yeah, yeah.
You see these two boys here?
They're my sons.
They were on my property.
No need to be scared of no little boys.
They ain't come to hurt you.
No need to be letting off no shotgun
to tell them to leave, either.
You understand?
Then keep 'em off my property.
They're friends to your son, okay?
He invited them here.
They ain't trespassing,
they ain't hurting nobody.
Next time you wanna play cowboy,
I'm over here all the time.
Well, you keep them
off my property.
- I think you heard me, sir.
- I think you heard me too.
All right?
Come on boys, let's go.
Aw, shit!
- You're all right, Dappa.
- Yeah, I'm all right.
- You're sure?
- Yeah. It was loose.
Yeah.
Did you see what you did, Sonny?
Yeah, I'm sorry.
It was my mistake.
- Yeah, it was.
- It won't happen next time.
Let's just keep going
till we get it right.
That's none of your goddamn business.
Woo!
I'm surprised you're
talking like that to me.
- You being a woman, you know?
- I'm a liberated woman.
Better watch out,
Georgia Ann,
Tommy's gonna sue you
for sexual harassment.
Oh, that's okay.
Booter, how you doing?
Just give me the $2.50, Sonny.
I got it, Booter.
- You keep the rest of it.
- Thanks, Mr. Grotowski.
Just like I said,
no more mistakes, all right?
I wanna make damn sure nobody
makes any mistakes, especially you.
So when it gets time for us
to do it, you know...
you can't mess up.
That goes for me too,
and the rest of them.
You ain't no different then us,
you can't screw it up.
Yeah.
- That's Hank's boy.
- It's in the genes.
Yeah, but he's a boy.
- Yes, he is.
- He will be a man tomorrow.
In England, they give
the guy a party the night before.
They call it the Monster's Ball.
They don't want no lawyer, no preacher,
or anything like that around...
So, it's just you and me.
Like I said, we can't think about what he did
or anything else about him.
It's a job.
We have to do our job right.
I've been drawing a lot.
What about you?
Yeah.
Look here,
we ain't got a lot of time.
I'm going to give you
all my drawings...
all my clothes.
When you get older,
they may fit you and you may
want to wear them.
I'm not gonna
see you again after this?
No.
Why?
- 'Cause I'm a bad man.
- Who says?
I do.
But I want you to know something.
What?
You ain't me.
- Yes I am.
- No, you're not.
You're everything
that's good about me.
You're the best of what I am,
that's what you are.
This man you see sitting
here today, you ain't.
Hey, babe.
You look nice, today.
You always look nice.
Tyrell, did you tell your daddy
what you won at school?
Oh yeah, right.
My drawing's getting used
for the school magazine cover.
- You know what I did?
- What did you do?
Go on, just tell him.
Don't be playing no guessing game.
I made a picture of you...
sitting alone...
in jail.
The theme was solitude.
Way to go, Ty. Way to go.
Put it there, boy.
Not too bad.
What's going on with the car?
It's leaking radiator fluid.
Take it in right away.
Have them check the hoses.
The car get too hot,
you're gonna be in trouble.
The house?
I'm losing it.
I can't afford to make
the payments no more.
Not no more.
I'm sorry, babe.
Ty, let me and your mama
talk for a second.
Okay.
Come on, now.
Only reason I'm here,
so you can say goodbye to your son.
Okay.
I been coming here
for damn near 11 years, Lawrence.
And I'm tired.
I'm tired of coming here.
- Time.
- So soon?
I got to get going, babe.
It's time for me to go, Ty.
I'm gonna call you.
You wait by the phone, okay?
Come on now.
Come on Ty, you got to let go.
Come on, Tyrell.
For every time
I hurt you, I'm sorry.
Come on.
Ma'am, let's go.
Let's go.
I know my way out of here.
Come on.
Well, he don't have
any outstanding appeal, so...
looks like we're definitely
gonna do it tonight.
Everybody okay?
- You all right, Georgia Ann?
- I'm okay.
Dappa, is that hood ready?
Yeah, it's fixed
and ready to go.
All right.
Anybody got anything to say?
Tommy?
He likes to draw.
It calms him down.
Draw?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Phil, will you make sure he's got
whatever it is he needs to draw with?
Yes, sir.
Tommy, why don't you
lead us in prayer?
Okay.
Open cell 13!
I'm here for your stuff, man.
...that the Lord
save us his anointing.
He will hear Him
in His holy Heaven,
and the saving strength
of His right hand.
Be careful with this.
Don't worry about it, man.
Close 13!
Worry's all I've got.
...some in chariots,
some in horses.
But we remember
the name of the Lord, our God.
They're brought down and fallen,
but we are risen and stand upright.
Save us, Lord. Let the King
hear us when we call Him.
"Sky surfing is when you skydive,
with a board attached to your feet,
and try to do different maneuvers."
"A camera flyer flies
with a camera on top of a helmet,
filming the sky surfer...
and flies with the sky surfer
for capturing the moves."
"My camera flyer is my husband,
Craig O'Brien."
I'm gonna put
these on nice and loose.
Everything's gonna
be okay, right?
Yes, sir.
What about my last phone call?
Warden says it's a bad idea.
Turn around.
Maybe you could call my son
and tell him that I tried.
I don't think so.
Okay.
Open 13.
"Our freefall
is usually around 60 seconds,
and the normal altitude
we jump from is 12,500 feet."
Let's go.
Close 13.
"Starting to feel a little
cramped by your present surroundings?"
"Maybe it's time
to expand your horizons."
to think about ReMax."
"ReMax Associates
lead the real estate industry..."
I'm going to be right back.
Stay right there.
"ReMax can help you find
a new home that meets all your needs,
while selling your current house
to someone who will find it
absolutely perfect."
"If you're looking for results,
look for ReMax."
"Nobody sells more real estate."
Where... Where's my paper and pencil?
It's my right to have
my paper and pencil.
I know.
Your paper and pencil's
on the way.
I promise you it is.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Here you go, Lawrence.
Is that done?
Let's see.
Wow.
That's nice.
It's real nice.
I don't look
this good in person.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
You're welcome.
You all right?
Sonny.
- Just breathe.
- Sonny.
Sonny, sit down.
I said, sit down.
Sit down.
Come on, Lawrence.
Come on, buddy. Come on, buddy.
Let's go.
It's all right. It's all right.
Just let go. Let go.
Let go. It's all right.
Let go. Come on.
Come on.
I've always believed that a
portrait captures a person...
far better than a photograph.
It truly takes a human being
to really see a human being.
Wait a minute.
Come here.
What the hell is this, Tyrell?
What did I tell you
about eating this shit?
Didn't I tell you
don't be eating that shit?
Look at this.
Look at all this fat!
This fat ass!
Look at all this nasty fat!
Where they at?!
Look at all this candy!
You ain't eating all this candy!
You crazy?!
Look at this room!
It's a mess!
Why is it a mess, Tyrell?
'Cause a fat little piggy lives in this room!
Get your ass on this scale!
Get on the scale!
What does it say? What does it say?
- 189.
- 189?!
You ain't lost no weight!
Come on.
Let's go wait
for your daddy to call.
It is ordered and adjudged
that the judgment
pronounced and set forth in this order
sentencing
the defendant to death
in the manner and by the authorities
as provided by statute,
shall be executed
at this time.
Lawrence Musgrove,
do you have anything
you'd like to say?
Push the button.
Hey.
Do you know what you did?
Are you listening to me?
Do you know what you did?!
You fucked him up!
You fucked up that man's last walk!
How would you like it
if somebody fucked up your last walk?!
You're like a goddamn woman,
you're like your fucking mother!
You shouldn't have done that,
you son of a bitch!
Get up,
you fucking pussy!
You are a piece
of fucking shit!
Do you understand me?!
- Easy, easy!
- Get your fucking hands off me,
- you fucking nigger!
- Hank! Hank!
- This ain't you!
- This is me, Phil! This is me!
And I'm the man
who could have your goddamn job!
Don't you ever let me catch you touching
anybody that outranks you again!
- Do you understand me?
- Yes, sir!
"Yes, sir"?
- I don't want to hear you.
- I just keep the peace.
You piece of shit!
You got... bleeding.
Sonny.
Get up!
You get out of my goddamn house, right now!
You get out!
Come on!
You lousy piece of shit!
Get up!
What are you gonna do, huh?
What are you gonna do?!
See? How do you like that, huh?
C'mon are you a tough guy now?
Are you tough?
Say something.
Say something!
Get up.
You hate me.
Answer me.
You hate me, don't you?
Yeah, I hate you.
I always did.
Well,
I always loved you.
Hand me the scissors.
Hold on a minute.
- Where are you going?
- I want to put these up.
- How much?
- That'll be $2.85.
Hey Billy, I'm moving
as fast as I can.
I'll put this dress on
and I'll be right out there.
- You don't need to get dressed.
- Damn car still acting up.
Leticia listen. It's not just your car.
You've been late every day this week.
Billy, I've been trying to get here.
I need this money.
- I'll lose my house.
- Look,
go home, relax.
Take some time off, you know.
You shouldn't be here
right now anyway.
I know that. That's why you should have
given me the week off.
- With some pay.
- Hell, Leticia! We already got a new girl.
Hank?
- Let's get this over with quick.
- Is there a passage...
- ...you'd like me to read?
- No.
All I want to hear is
that dirt hitting that box.
He was weak.
You can say something if you want,
once we've covered him up.
- How are you doing?
- All right.
- You want to see a menu?
- No, I know what I want.
What you gonna have?
A bowl of chocolate
ice cream...
and a cup of coffee.
- Black, sugar, cream?
- No, black.
- That's it.
- Is that it?
Hey, Vera, it's Hank.
Is it too late?
Chocolate ice cream.
Here you go.
I wanna... I wanna a plastic spoon
for the ice cream.
Oh, Goddamn!
Sorry about that.
- It's all right.
- Shit!
I didn't mean to do that.
I'm sorry.
Bring me some napkins
or something.
I'm sorry about that.
And you said a what...
Plastic spoon.
- Where's Lucille?
- I'm trying to fill in for her.
- I'm ready to pay this.
- Yep.
What's the deal here?
I don't know.
I just overrang this thing.
If you can't get that thing open,
just tell me how much it is,
and I'll pay you for it.
$3.92.
Here's $4.00.
Keep the change.
Thanks.
Hey, cowboy,
feel like some late-night pussy?
I guess so.
Haven't seen you in a while.
Yeah, well...
I ain't been
feeling too good.
Busy with this and that
and the other, you know.
- How have you been?
- All right.
Good.
So how's Sonny?
I can't do this tonight, Vera.
- Are you sure, hon?
- No, not tonight.
- I'm sorry.
- No need to be sorry. Some other time.
All right.
You can keep that money.
I'm going to.
Adios.
- Have a seat, Hank.
- Thank you, sir.
I appreciate you seeing me.
What brings you here, Hank?
Sir, I'm resigning
and I wanted to come by
and tell you personally, you know.
I appreciate that, Hank.
Why don't we wait a few weeks
before we submit the paperwork?
That wouldn't do anybody
any good to wait on that.
I've got my mind made up.
All right.
We're gonna miss you.
I brought my badge in and...
- Why don't you keep it?
- I ain't got no use for it.
There you are, Pop.
We got each other...
son.
- Remember that.
- Yes, sir.
I quit the team.
That was a mistake.
I can't do it anymore.
You're reminding me
of your mother.
I guess that's bad, right?
Your mother wasn't shit.
That woman failed me.
I got more pussy
after she killed herself...
than I did when
she was living as my wife.
The point is...
she quit on me.
You're doing the same.
Goddamnit!
Let's go.
Hand me my purse.
Come on. Get out!
- Why, Mama, what's wrong?
- We've got to walk.
Tyrell,
get off that street!
You'll get yourself killed.
Don't do that!
This is jim-dandy.
This is just what I'm looking for.
At the same time,
it's the most expensive one.
But if you're willing
to talk price a little...
We put quite a bit of work into it.
We could talk about it.
Let me think it over.
You got my number.
- All right.
- It was a pleasure.
- Nice seeing you.
- Nice talking to you.
See you.
Come on, T.
Let's go.
That's what you think
your mama looks like?
Yeah, sort of.
- See you in the morning?
- Yeah.
- You too, young man.
- Bye.
Bye-bye.
Come on, T.
Get up!
Help me!
Help me! Wait!
Wait!
Come back here!
Help us!
Please, help us!