- Why am I different?
- I didn't mean it that way.
Why?
Why am I different?
Go!
I don't want you here.
Sorry.
The day you came here,
Mt. Holy cried.
I didn't know what it meant then,
but I do now.
The shaky ground,
the evil spirit in the air...
...Mt. Holy was warning us
of a disaster.
Did you know?
I think you couldn't tell us,
but you did know.
Mt. Holy is afraid of you
cause you're to destroy it.
That fate of yours is a disaster,
damaging our tribe.
Hold my hands.
Mt. Holy will talk through you.
As the black moon appears
after the 3-day-long sun...
...two angry dragons will kill
all the living things on earth.
Trees will sooth the dragons...
...but the sword of the spirit
won't be stoppable.
When the sword shines...
...the world will quiet down
with sadness...
...but the chains of sadness
will last forever.
Mt. Holy wants me.
If I sacrifice myself to it,
the tribe will be safe.
I know now why my father
wanted to go to Mt. Holy...
...and why he left me here.
It was to protect the tribe.
Haeah!
I was born to be a sacrifice
for the tribe.
Can't you change my fate?
Haeah! You can do it,
can't you?
Do I have to die?
Can't you save my life?
I will make more paper
and stay outside the village!
I won't break my words
until the moment I die!
Save me!
Help me live!
Haeah!
Does Dahn know?
Have you told him yet?
Not yet.
Vee wants to do it herself.
Dahn won't buy it.
He won't let her go.
But there's nothing that
Haeah can do.
Mt. Holy has decided it,
- and it was predicted long ago.
- She knew?
Haeah believes in the prophecy
of the mural painting.
Don't go!
Give them time alone.
Let me.
- Anything wrong?
- No, it's just the paper.
Are you sure?
The paper looks so heavy today.
Cause everybody feels down.
It will be okay
when the fury of Mt. Holy subsides.
I hope so.
Juk and Yun will get married
in a few days.
Will you stay with me?
I don't know.
The life has never worked
in favor of me.
It made everything I wanted
turn away from me.
Because I wasn't with you.
It'll be different from now.
No matter what happens...
...I'll stay by your side
and help you out.
You can lean on me.
Okay?
Your ancestor painted it.
I'm the new patriarch.
Tell me everything about it.
It's the holy sword you saw
in the painting.
Long ago, Hwasan and Mae
went to a severe war.
Having been exiled from Mt. Holy...
...Mae tribe tried to make
the holy sword...
...with blood and bones
of a 1,000 alive people.
...in order to kill Mt. Holy
and exterminate our tribe.
To do so,
they needed the seed
of Hwasan Royal Family.
Soo, the chief of Mae, tempted
the King of Hawsan, Han...
...and gave a birth to Vee
who's to complete the sword.
But it wasn't easy.
Han brought
her here...
..to protect our tribe and Mt. Holy..
If Vee is here to protect us,
why sending her to Mt. Holy?
When the black moon
appears in a few days...
...it'll be the last chance
for Mae to perfect the sword.
They'll try to get hold of Vee
and complete the holy sword.
So Mt. Holy is using her
as the sacrifice.
It's the wisdom of Mt. Holy
to protect our tribe.
Can't we save her?
Does Vee have to die
for the tribe?
We have to live up to Mt. Holy?
What are you talking about?
Leave.
The time has come.
- Out of the way!
- Be reasonable.
I won't let you stop me.
It's for the tribe!
How can you do this?
As the patriarch,
I have to protect the tribe.
For the safety of the tribe,
I'm willing to die.
I bet you wouldn't do this
if you were in my place.
You made a big mistake,
refusing the position.
Why didn't you tell me?
We could've run away.
Sorry
Don't go.
Don't!
I'm begging you.
Don't go.
Lock him up.
I'll punish him later.
Open it!
Let me out!
What did you just say?
We're not going to Mt. Holy.
I'm taking Vee.
I've made up my mind.
Go back.
I'll ask you who are the patriarch.
If you let Vee live,
our tribe will perish.
Don't you know that?
I don't care about the tribe.
I'm no longer the patriarch.
I changed my mind.
Don't try to stop me.
I won't let you!
You've betrayed the tribe...
...and deserted your friends
including me and Dahn.
You'll be sorry.
Change your mind, man.
It's not too late.
Come with us.
Sorry.
We're friends!
Quit it!
- Give it up.
- I won't regret it. Go ahead!
Why?
- Don't do it!
- Out of the way!
It's the only and last thing
that I can do for the tribe.
I'm the only one
who can do this!
I'm coming
And you're ruining it!
If you care about me,
don't do this.
Nothing ever happened.
Consider it as a dream.
To Mt. Holy...
Take me there.
Will you?
Come with me.
Go!
You've betrayed the tribe
and killed your friends.
Wasn't it for Vee?
Get her out of here.
Save her!
You deserted me
and that's painful enough.
I can't hold them back long
with only 6 arrows.
Consider it as a farewell gift!
Nothing to be done now.
Mt. Holy will bring a disaster.
Juk knows it very well...
...that the holy sword of Mae
is the only thing to save Vee.
He'll go to Mae for it.
You've got only 3 days.
If you fail to take Vee
to the Mt. Holy...
...the sword will be perfected
and used to harm Mt. Holy.
If that's the case,
it'll be the end of our tribe.
The density of our tribe is
in your hands.
Find Vee and go to Mt. Holy.
Any other ways to save Vee?
The curse of Mt. Holy is
already hitting her.
She'll eventually bleed to death.
The fate of the tribe should
come before her life.
Dahn!
I know how painful that is.
But you'll meet her again
for the pain you're in.
That's the nature's way.
I put dews from Mt. Holy on it.
Good luck.
We've got only 2 days.
I'm worried Mae might
find Vee before us.
What are you thinking about?
Would I do the same
if I were Juk?
Then he would be after you.
- You hate him?
- I did.
Not any more, though.
I forgot about him.
Sorry it didn't work out.
Stop taking about him.
Think only about the tribe.
That's what counts.
If not, you can go back.
I'll let you go.
I've chosen this way,
and it was me who Juk go.
And I failed to protect Vee.
It's still warm.
- Don't come closer!
- Don't move!
- Take me to Mt. Holy.
- You'll die if you go.
That's the fate that
Mt. Holy has given me.
It's my fate to protect you.
You won't die!
Don't be silly.
Soon after I'll get the holy sword.
Then, Mt. Holy can't kill you!
I can save you!
If you save my life with it,
what about others?
They're sacrificing you
for their own lives!
They are deserved to die!
That's where Dahn is.
If I live, he dies.
The day you showed up,
you occupied my mind.
But I had to give up on you
for Dahn.
Why? He's my friend.
Returning from Mt. Sunghwa,
I thought I could have you.
But, unfortunately,
Dahn came back alive.
I tried to forget about you,
but I couldn't.
The more I tried, to forget you,
The more I wanted you.
I won't do that any more.
I will save you. And it will be me,
not Dahn, by your side!
Let me go.
Wait...
Wait!
Stop looking for Vee.
Mae has nothing to do with her.
You're desperate, aren't you?
If you want to beg,
do it right.
I guess the hunting won't be
as boring
I'll let you live this time.
If you get in the way again,
you will be sorry.
Let them live.
We can use them as bait.
Vee is nearby.
We'll find her soon.
When we first met,
we became good friends.
You were brave, warm-hearted,
and loved the tribe.
Let me remember you
as the man I know.
That's best for all of us.
You can't satisfy everybody.
It's dog-eat-dog out there.
Nothing's more important
than my love for you.
Even if you save my life,
I will never forgive you.
Send her.
No, not so fast.
- You've got more to give me than Vee?
- Why don't we become friends?
- What do you want?
- Vee!
I don't care what you do
with the holy sword.
Cause Vee will resurrect
after you get what you want.
So?
Promise me you'll let her go.
Then, I'll help you.
You know what my wish is?
It's killing every single soul
from the Hwasan tribe.
And you're one of them.
- What are you doing?
- Aren't you going to run?
- Not with your head.
- Is that right? Here's your chance.
My baby...
You have grown up
beyond recognition.
You look just like your dad.
Do you know who I am?
No.
You're not the person I missed,
and I won't ask who you are.
All I want to know is
why you're doing this to me.
You have no idea
what curse Mt. Holy put on us.
For hundreds years..
In the land of hell
where no weeds grew...
...our ancestors had to eat
their own flesh to survive.
We worked very hard with our bare hands.
They couldn't die
with their bodies festering...
...and had to endure the pain
of bugs eating them alive.
It was all due to the curse
Mt. Holy put on us!
But, with the holy sword,
we can destroy them.
We're giving them back
the pain they gave us.
My baby...
You can sooth the pain
that our ancestors had.
That's your fate.
Consider it as an honor.
Don't be scared.
You'll sleep for a short time.
Then, you'll be reborn
as a daughter of Mae tribe.
Go!
It's no use.
She can't get away!
Hadn't you saved me then,
Had I died then...
...this wouldn't be happening.
l have to die.
I'm too much burden on you.
If there's anything left
that I can do for you...
...I'll be by your side.
- Can we meet again?
- Sure. I promise.
I'm sorry.
I can't take you with us.
Let's go back to the altar.
He wants the holy sword.
He will come to the altar
to save Vee.
We have to get back
before him.
Stopping the holy sword is
the only way to expiate my sin.
So I stuck around Vee
and got to know you.
It was you who saved me
in Mt. Sunghwa.
You protected Vee.
The moonlight is dimmer.
The black moon will be up soon.
We've got to hurry.
Wake up! Wake up!
If the black moon is ours,
it will bring Vee here.
We'll see
Can you hear it?
It's calling the holy sword.
The curse of Mt. Holy can
no longer torture you.
Hang in there.
Just a little longer.
The girl of a fate, the spirit of Vee...
...will bring the holy sword to us!
The spirit of Vee!
Destiny!
Mt. Holy...
You have to go there.
Dahn is waiting for you.
Be strong. You can do this.
Where's Vee?
Where is she?
With the black moon up,
the holy sword will appear.
It will be useless, though,
if you don't have Vee.
You and your tribe will die.
How sad!
It's only the holy sword
that can save her.
I'm taking it with me.
You think I'll let you have it?
You'll have to.
Either to save her or your tribe,
one of us has to kill Mt. Holy.
- And I have Vee.
- Say it! Where is she?
Right here.
Inside me!
Don't mess up with me.
I'll tear you apart
and find Vee!
Go ahead.
Thrust it in me!
Why?
Are you afraid?
You want to see the holy sword?
I'll tear your heart out.
At last, you're back.
Bring it!
Bring it to me!
Or you'll kill her?
Can you do that?
I don't think so.
But I can
cause that's my fate.
Kill him!
It's over.
Should I kill you
with this holy sword?
Or should I let you have her?
You listen to me.
I'll let you have this sword.
- On one condition!
- Say it.
You become one of us, Mae.
Anyway, destroying the Mt. Holy...
...is one thing we have in common.
I'll let you live to take revenge for our tribe...
...and you can have Vee.
Can you do it?
With the black moon gone,
the holy spirits will kill me...
...but you'll be protected
...cause you'll be the last
descendant of our tribe, Mae.
As the descendants,
if we wreck vengeance...
...we won't be breathe as alive
and close our eyes as dead.
Forever, Mae!
You'll come back to me.
Stop it!
You think you can stop me?
Let Vee rest in peace!
That's our only help for her!
How dare you say that,
you two-faced prick!
When you let her go...
...when you tried to get her
for the tribe...
Vee was with me!
Everybody wanted her dead,
but I protected her for my life!
That's how we're different!
Nonsense!
Vee didn't want any of this!
You cheated yourself
and left yourself dream!
No way. Dream isn't painful.
It's over when you wake up.
But there's something that
you can't get yourself out.
That's love!
I can't let that love die.
How can you love a ghost?
- That's all I want!
- I don't want to let her go, either,
but that's her fate!
Her fate my butt!
I won't let her go!
Kill me and let Vee go,
or die to let her live!
I'll be with her!
No matter where she is,
That's how we're different.
And you didn't love her.
You were obsessed with her.
It wasn't an obsession!
Vee wanted you, but it was me
who loved her! lt was me!
Stop right there.
I'm begging you.
Don't let me kill you. Please...
There's something
I always wanted to say to you.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I wanted to see you
once for all. Goodbye.
- Let me go with you.
- No.l don't want you to.
I promised you
that l'd always be by you.
Remember?
You said you'd help me
live a life that I choose.
Please let me.
Play it when you feel down.
It'll cheer you up.
It worked for me.
When the black moon rises
after a 3-day-long sun...
...a dragon with its soul lost
will look for a hidden tree...
The tree greeting the dragon,
a golden snow will fall.
And the soul trapped in the tree...
...will meet the dragon again
with the blessings of God.
Then, nothing on earth can
separate them again.