Stop with the groveling.
I'm the one who needs
to thank all of you guys.
You're going to make me
filthy stinkin' rich! Thank you!
We're the losers.
But please give us the opportunity...
...to join your team!
Please!
Please, give us a chance.
Well, that was a pretty
good sized explosion.
The Evil Team will be
the world champions for sure.
Yes?
Who is it?
The cripple?
- Why not?
- I'm sorry.
Look, I played professional
soccer for years,
- you want to stop me?
- The person in charge isn't here right now.
Golden Leg!
What are you doing?
- Hung!
- Hung, heh...
Okay...
Hung, my team wants to sign up
for the soccer tournament!
It's an open competition,
everyone has the right to sign up.
You're wrong.
I'm the chairman.
I have the right to decide
who can sign up.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
What's the name of your team?
Come over here!
This is Hung.
Hung!
Get a load of this soccer team!
I'm dying to watch them play!
What's the name again?
This is Shaolin...
OK...
Hurry and sign them up.
I really want to watch these guys.
If you'd like, I'll even pay
your application fee.
Thank you!
No problem! You, my lame friend,
are like a brother to me.
Ah, look at that.
My shoe is dirty again.
White gets dirty easily.
So...
I'll help you clean it up!
I'm good at cleaning.
Let me do it!
This is a job for me!
Hey! Let me do it!
What a pack of idiots
Hi!
What are you doing?
Who are you?
Where are we going?
Why are you so quiet?
I need to go home.
Hey, we've been waiting
a long time for you.
I'm sorry.
Please, give me just a few minutes.
Try this one.
No. I just want to see the quality of it.
Touch it.
I'll get it dirty.
- No problem. Go ahead.
- No...
- Touch it.
- No.
- How's that?
- It's so smooth.
- I promise I'll buy one for you.
- I touched it already. That's enough.
Tomorrow, I'm going to start
playing in the soccer tournament.
Really?
I'm going to become
a famous star player.
But if you hadn't
helped me to repair these...
I'd never have been able to play.
You know, you're so important to me.
Tell me whatever you want.
I'll be able to pay for it very soon.
If you become rich and famous,
please buy me some sneakers.
No problem!
But you should have more confidence.
I mean, really, you're a beautiful
girl, you're good at Kung Fu.
You know, you're perfect.
You shouldn't let your hair hang
down so it covers your face like that.
Come on.
- Come on. Look at me.
- No...
Look at me!
You're so beautiful!
Really?
Yes, of course.
Was it a fly?
Yes. But I didn't get it.
Did you get it that time?
I did.
I'm sorry. I got your hand all dirty.
No problem.
You know, you're a real beautiful girl.
Don't you know that?
Yes. I do.
Thank you! Thanks so much!
Don't you forget it!
Hey, where are you going?
I let you bring a girl in here because
you promised me you'd clean the store.
Hurry up! If you don't finish
the job on time, I'll get in trouble.
Go on home. I'll call you later.
Okay?
Remember! You should have confidence.
You're the best!
That's a nice shirt.
I like your socks, too.
- Let's switch clothes.
- Good idea...
Come on, guys! Haven't you
ever done this before?
Just pretend it's training as usual.
There'll be hundreds of reporters
and spectators outside.
You guys need to keep smiling...
...and let the reporters
take pictures with us.
You also need to say hi and
thank the fans for their support.
Thank you!
Thanks for your support!
They're just the cleaners.
Cleaners are part of the audience too.
Thank you!
Shut up!
This auditorium is so small and empty.
You said...
This is just the first round.
So we need to play well
and get into the finals.
- Great! Get into the finals!
- Shut up!
Shaolin Team?
Look at this guy!
Look at that guy!
What's wrong?
No smoking here?
What just happened?
That's impossible! Just an illusion!
What are you doing?
It's okay, just an illusion.
I think we should
show off our real power.
Great!
What's wrong?
Please don't play like that!
I really want to play soccer!
Hung, call for you.
I'm not scared. It's just an illusion.
What? Forty to nothing?
Is this a joke?
Yeah!
Goal! Yes! Iron Head!
Yes, we use Shaolin Kung Fu
to play soccer.
So Kung Fu is great, wonderful!
- We lie low...
- And...
I want to thank my parents
and my Shaolin master.
Even though they've already passed away.
I also want to thank my good friend, Mui.
Mui... How are you?
Did you have dinner already?
Hello! Can I help you?
I want...
Say no more.
Let me take care of you!
Would you mind
showing us your Kung Fu?
Yes, of course. Sixth Small Brother?
1, 2, 3!
Awesome!
Can you show us something else?
- Sure!
- Big Brother, one more please.
Hey, hey, take it easy!
My Brothers,
Today we say goodbye
to our old sneakers.
Don't throw stuff around here!
Sorry...
Hi.
Mui?
What's up?
Wow, you look so different!
Not really.
No, you're really decked out.
Do you like it?
I've got some good news for you!
You know my soccer team
won our matches hands down.
I know. I watched you guys on TV.
Congratulations!
Uh, this is for you.
Thank you.
Come on. Let me introduce
my friends to you.
Wow! How great is this!
This is my friend...
Are you human or a ghost?
Oh, no! She's just a woman.
Ah, she's your girl, eh?
No, no, she's my friend, Mui.
She uses Tai Chi to make steamed bread.
Oh! It's her.
She's an unusual girl.
Yes, she's one of a kind.
I can see that.
It looks like she's carrying a log across her
shoulders. I've never seen anything like it.
Hey, hey, I spent two whole nights
making these two pieces.
Two pieces.
Sing, you really shouldn't
be bringing her out at night.
She could scare someone to death.
That wouldn't be a problem.
Then you could do the wake for them.
Hold on! We could tie her up
and toss her into the ocean.
What, and you want to give up
eating seafood forever then?
Okay, okay, knock it off! You all
shouldn't be treating a girl like this.
It's okay. I don't mind.
Yeah, she's a soft and gentle girl,
but she's got a great sense of humor.
Hey Mui, give us a sexy pose.
How about another one?
- What's wrong?
- Don't touch me!
Are you upset with me?
No, I'm not.
So you're...
I'm sorry.
I'm only kidding.
I know, you just think I'm a joke.
I'm sorry. Really, I don't care.
Don't be like this.
Wh... why did you do this?
Don't touch me!
Boss...
What's wrong with you?
I can't even go out to play Mahjong...
without finding you looking like
you're not even human or a ghost.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Enough already!
Mui has the right to decide
how she wants to look.
Can't you respect her decision?
I think she looks quite nice today.
Don't you think she looks beautiful?
You talk too much!
This is none of your business.
What makes you think you
can talk to me like that!
They're my friends.
What they're saying
is how I really feel.
I think I'm very beautiful right now.
I love my new look a lot.
If you don't like it,
you can get lost.
Hey! Who do you think
you're talking to?
I'm talking to you.
My cruel, cold boss.
That's it!
You... do you think you're tough
enough to fight with me?
You trying to rebel against me?
Who are you?
It's me.
I'm Mui!
I'm going to tell your Mom.
Mui, you're awesome!
Mui, we were just joking.
Please don't get mad at us.
Actually, your poses were great.
Really?
I think...
I think I've changed a bit.
You'd better believe it.
You've got confidence now.
I want to tell you something.
What's that?
I like you!
I like you, too!
Is this love?
You...
You're kidding, right?
No. I'm serious.
Absolutely not. This isn't love.
We're friends, forever...
Don't you think we're good together?
Sure! We're fine.
So, you'll come to see me often?
If your shoes get broken,
I'll help you fix them again.
No, thanks. If my shoes get broken,
I'll just throw them away.
We should look forward to the future.
I'll never wear broken shoes again.
Don't be like this.
What's wrong? Why are you crying?
Don't do this.
I understand.
Goodbye!
Hey, come on over!
Mui, you're looking nice today.
Cheers!
After we win this game,
we'll be going to the finals.
Going to the finals!
But we can't underestimate our opponent!
Underestimate our opponent!
We're the more powerful team.
We won't let you get into the finals.
Holy cow! How'd they do that?
Must be special effects...
Good morning, Hung!
Good morning!
Come on over here and sit down!
You're a lucky man.
Very lucky to have such a great team.
Thank you.
Looks like Iron Head and Iron Shirt
have even become quite popular.
It's been amusing watching your
guys use Kung Fu to play soccer
and get all the way to the finals.
You've done a good job.
Hurry up, don't waste our time!
Give up the finals
and join my Evil Team!
It's not a dirty bribe.
You can get the money
before you sign on with me.
This is a lot of money.
I could probably break my left
leg and retire on this.
Why not! We're brothers.
Thank you.
But I don't think I can't accept this.
What? Do you think I'm
trying to intimidate you?
I think your team has great potential.
Maybe we could join together.
Don't get upset so easily.
Think about your future.
Forget our rivalry. Okay?
Hung, I wasn't thinking
of our rivalry.
I know it was all my fault.
I can't blame anyone else.
You're lying!
I know you too well.
You're too greedy!
You're right!
I am greedy. My team is greedy, too.
But we don't have an
insatiable greed for money.
We have an insatiable greed
for the championship.
See you on the soccer field.
Stop! Wait just a minute! Thank you!
Mui!
She died already!
How come?
I killed her!
What!
Mui is the master-hand of Tai Chi.
She must not be treated unjustly!
What do you want?
Revenge!
Don't be silly! I'm just joking!
She's still alive.
She just doesn't work here anymore.
Why?
You know, my little store
is well-known for sweet steamed bread.
But now the steamed bread...
she makes has become salty and bitter.
She's been ruining my business.
I didn't have another choice.
Salty and bitter?
Yes.
What's your name? Can I help?
No, thanks.
Come on, we've got to go!
Boss, how many goals
do you expect to score today?
Scoring goals isn't the only way to win.
I've got a great plan for winning today.
Impossible.
Those American drugs are
absolutely incredible!
And with the referees, linesmen,
soccer association, soccer federation
and soccer committee...
all in my pocket.
How can they fight against me?
No problem!
- Great!
- Way to go!
Wonderful!
Throw-in?
He did that on purpose!
How can you call that a throw-in?
Hung, are you fighting,
or playing soccer?
Yes, we are. So what?
I ought to break all your legs
and turn all of you into cripples.
Cripples! Cripples!
How are you gonna fight against me?
I'm sorry I have to leave the game.
It's okay. You're just
leaving us physically,
but your spirit will stay
in our hearts forever.
Move over! It's my turn.
Sixth Small Brother!
What's going on?
Why don't you stop them?
It's only halftime, and all
your guys are badly injured!
How are you going to
play the second half?
Go home! There's no way you
guys can play the second half!
There's nothing
interesting going on,
Maybe I should go down there
and dance to give them a show.
No! It's not your show. It's mine!
Damn you!
Break it up!
You guys must not
want to play anymore!
Who did that?
Who saw that?
Hit me in the face,
if you're brave enough!
Rub gently.
I can't believe they're even
more out of control than I am.
I can't believe that...
my reputation has been ruined.
I figured they'd try
to do something to us,
but even I can't believe
how cruel they've been.
The Evil Team isn't that great.
They must have taken drugs
or some kind of injection.
Call the police!
Look,
We've got to try our best
to keep going.
We'll win in the end!
My house is on fire, I've gotta run!
I'm sorry. My mom is
giving birth prematurely right now.
I need to go home and take care of her.
Can't you ask her to wait
until the end of the game?
You can't give up now!
They're not playing soccer.
They're killing us!
I'm begging you.
Please don't leave us!
I'm begging you back.
Please let me go!
Calm down!
Yes, he's right!
We have to keep going.
Now, we only have eight players left.
If one more player gets injured,
we'll forfeit.
We have to try our best to
defend against their killer kick.
Why should WE? If YOU defend one
killer kick, then I'll play defense for three.
What are you talking about?
Calm down!
Shut up!
I'm not sure if I can
defend against it, but...
Shaolin Lu Han Array!
Array?
Can't stand against a shot like that!
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine!
Hello, Chun.
- Tin?
- Yes.
There's something I haven't
told you in many years,
but I really wanted
to tell you right now.
Chun, I love you!
Do you think we're being too cruel?
- I don't think so!
- Really?
So we can be harsher!
Brothers! Go!
What the...?
Be careful!
Watch out!
Give me a break!
Hurry and get up!
Quit acting like you're hurt!
Yeah, you're a genius!
I'm just fine.
The game's almost over!
Use the final attack!
Final attack?
Yes! That's it. Now you guys...
...can't even stall for time.
Game over!
Shaolin Team.
You've only got seven players left.
If you don't have any
substitute players,
I'll stop the game...
and announce that the game's over.
Any substitute players?
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
I'm ready!
I'm the substitute player.
I'm the goalkeeper.
What are you making out
like E.T. For?
I didn't know how to cut my hair,
so I thought it'd be easier to shave it.
What for?
I want to help you.
How can you help us?
Go back to Mars,
Earth is too dangerous.
I really want to help you.
Trust me! Let me try!
- No way!
- Look,
your shoes are broken.
Put these on.
The OTHER side.
Go!
Alright!
Watch out!
What happened?
What just happened?
Boss, watch out?
Damn it!
Boss!
"Shaolin Team Wins
the Championship"
"Evil Team Gets Permanent
Suspension for Drug Use"
"Coach Hung gets sentenced
to 5 years in prison"
Wait! Stop the bus!