# Faithless lover's kiss #
# Is written on the wind #
# A night of stolen bliss #
# Is written #
# On the wind #
# Just like the dying leaves #
# Our dreams we've calmly #
# Thrown away #
# Now they've blown away #
# Softly flown away #
# The promises we made #
# Our whispers in the breeze #
# They echo and they fade #
# Just like our memories #
# Though you are gone #
# From me #
# We never can really be #
# Apart #
# What's written on the wind #
# Is written in my heart #
Hello.
- What happened to Mrs. Black?
- My predecessor? She was paroled.
So you're the new
executive secretary, huh?
Don't let that title deceive you.
I do everything but wipe windshields.
- I'm Mitch Wayne.
- Yes, I recognized you.
- I'm Lucy Moore.
- Recognized me? From where?
Oh, come now.
Surely you realize...
how often your photograph
has graced our tabloids?
But the captions usually read, "Kyle Hadley,
Prince Charming of the oil empire, and friend."
The dashing Kyle Hadley.
I saw him dash through
the office recently.
Seems he misplaced
his money belt.
- Again?
- A hat was passed, and I contributed $16.47.
Well, for that, you ought to get
an oil well named after you.
- Your boss in?
- No, Mr. Ryan's out of town.
- I guess you'll have to pinch-hit for him.
- What can I do for you?
Kyle Hadley's at 21,
in the mood for a conference.
- Business, of course.
- Look, I'm only Mr. Ryan's secretary.
- I don't think it'd be proper to...
- Would you rather wipe windshields?
All right.
Kyle and I flew in
from Texas this afternoon.
- Sounds urgent.
- Very.
- Kyle said he felt like a steak sandwich.
- Steak sandwich?
And who serves the best
steak sandwich in the world?
- 21?
- Simple, isn't it?
Or should I say
simpleminded?
1,380 miles for a...
- Then you were fooling me about
a business conference.
- No, that was my idea,
you know, in case Mr. Jasper Hadley
should ask why we came to town.
Oh, the big boss. Well...
Cheer up. You might
get your picture in the paper.
Is that all you live for?
- Guess again, Miss Moore.
- I'm sorry.
I just wanted you to understand
how I feel about such things.
- Know something?
- What?
Maybe we're two of a kind.
Harry, put it on my tab.
- Of course, Mr. Hadley.
- Who's this friend we're waiting for?
Mitch Wayne, my sidekick.
Mmm, where do his millions
come from?
He's eccentric...
he's poor.
- I'll bet.
- Honey, you would lose.
Mitch is just a country boy. The kind of assets
he's got you can't buy with money.
Sorry, kids.
I'll have to make this some other time.
- He's not eccentric.
- No, he's as rich as Rockefeller.
- Hello, I'm Kyle Hadley.
- I'm Lucy Moore.
Lucy Moore.
Your taste is improving.
Miss Moore is Bill Ryan's
new executive secretary.
A member of the happy, happy
Hadley Industrial family.
This is sure cozy.
There are rare moments when only
champagne will do. This is one of them.
Like the lyrics say,
"Are you from Dixie or where?"
Indiana. Small town
you probably never heard of.
Any time you ask me,
I'll put it on the map.
What shows
in your crystal ball?
Oh, I'll probably walk down an aisle
and wind up in a suburb...
- ... with a husband, mortgage and children.
- That's not for you.
- Why not?
- Got too much beauty and brains
to fall into a trap like that.
Just what sort of trap
do you suggest?
How would you like to join the Kyle Hadley
Society for the Prevention of Boredom?
What would my duties be?
- Not duties.
Pleasures, such as Kyle Hadley's
guided tour through the gossip columns,
around the world
in 80 headlines.
- I'm afraid that'd bore me.
- What wouldn't bore you?
My career... advertising.
Bravo...
as they say in Texas.
- Where did you learn the advertising game?
- With the Sheraton Agency.
- Top drawer?
- One of Madison Avenue's finest.
Good enough.
I'll buy you the agency.
What if I took you up on that?
A phone, please.
Yes, Mr. Hadley.
- You're really serious, aren't you?
- Sure I am.
- What's the number?
- The agency or my apartment?
- Seriously...
- Very seriously, forget it.
I'm only following the advice of a Texas
philosopher who said, "Give the little girl a big..."
I think it's time we heard from another county.
What do you do for the Hadley Oil Company?
We're troubleshooters.
Wherever they want trouble, they send for us.
I, uh, have a sheep skin
that says I'm a geologist.
- That adds up.
- I was kicked out of the same school.
They found rocks
in my head.
Shouldn't you be going back
to the office?
Apparently,
I never should have left.
- We haven't finished our champagne.
- Remarkable, isn't it?
I think we need cigarettes.
Get a carton.
We'll get a cab, meanwhile.
Thank you, Mr. Hadley.
Carton of Mullhall, please.
Thank you.
Don't look now,
but you've dropped your friend.
You advertising people...
so clever with words.
Guess I've fallen
from your grace.
Does it really matter?
Change your course.
Teterborough Airport.
Look, if you don't mind, I'd like to get off
the merry-go-round.
I can't quit now.
I want you to meet
another fellow... a real one.
- Some other time, perhaps.
- Some times, like now,
I can get you
in the terminal.
I want us to be friends
when we say good-bye.
Well, then let me
give you a tip.
- Drop me at the office.
- And if I do, I lose you.
Look, Lucy, once we're up in the blue,
I'm a different fellow...
a lot different
from this character.
All right.
Maybe I should meet him.
No stunts now, like buzzing
the Empire State Building.
The only stunts I do
are in nightclubs.
May I ask why?
I wouldn't admit this
to anyone but you,
but I drink too much.
- Here's your change.
- Can't shake you, can I?
Goes both ways.
Am I safe in this crate?
I guess so. The tanks are loaded, and
the pilot isn't, for a change.
Lucy.
You know, I've seen you before...
at the office.
- A fleeting glance, wasn't it?
- How much did you contribute?
Enough.
How long have you known Mitch?
My dad introduced us
when we started the first grade.
- That must have been before
your father struck oil.
- Dad was worth 100 million then.
He had no use for private schools, and
he wanted me to grow up with Mitch.
Why Mitch in particular?
Mitch's old man is my dad's boyhood pal...
his idol, I guess.
A small rancher...
kind of a legend in our county.
Great hunter, sort of
a throwback to Daniel Boone.
I used to wish
he was my father.
Is your father aware of this?
Dad's a big man... so big that he and I know
I can't fit his shoes, or even come close.
- Can anybody?
- Yes.
Mitch.
When I was kicked out of college,
Dad gave up hoping...
Mitch's qualities
might rub off on me.
It's easy to talk like this when you're 6,000
feet above the big poker table.
- Poker table?
- Sure. The big one... from Maine to California.
Down there, I'm a guy
with too many chips.
I throw 'em up in the air,
and a few land on my shoulders.
They'd be disappointed if I didn't behave like
a playboy... didn't end up like my uncle.
- How did he end up?
- Joe Hadley?
Lived hard and he died hard.
He survived a few duels over some European
duchesses and countesses,
only to be done in by a jealous Turk who hired
assassins to cut out his heart.
- He was only 30.
- Black sheep?
- One of three.
- Well, I take it you include yourself,
but who's the third?
My kid sister Marylee.
She's got enough devil in her to put
Uncle Joe and me in the shade.
What's the matter?
Your ears burning?
Just came to tell you
we're off the Carolina coast.
- North Carolina?
- Uh-huh. Are we turning back?
Can't. Automatic pilot's
set for Miami.
- And then what?
- I feel like a swim. How does Miami Beach sound?
Better ask your guest.
Just say the word, and
I'll make a 180-degree turn.
Reluctantly?
Uh-huh. Something
is happening to me.
I find myself talking to you like
I never talked to anyone before...
not even Mitch.
Please, Lucy. I think we're past
the point of no return.
Flight 498...
now arriving from Havana
at Cubana concourse.
Kyle's probably arranging
to buy you the hotel,
a stretch of the beach
and a slice of the Gulf strip.
Why are you so sarcastic?
Do you resent our being here,
or are you just disappointed that
I didn't ask Kyle to turn back?
The first surprise
came at Teterborough.
I underestimated Kyle's charm.
Perhaps you've always
underestimated Kyle.
Or maybe you're
overestimating me.
- Could be.
- Nothing like this has ever happened
to me before.
It's an adventure.
It's exciting.
Are you looking for laughs?
Or are you soul searching?
The latter, I guess.
I think I'm beginning
to know Kyle...
and to like him.
Well, in that case, I'm glad.
I really am.
Tell me something.
This hooky-playing...
when does it end?
I don't know.
For me,
it never seems to end.
Okay, kids.
Let's beat it to Miami Beach.
Found us a boarding house with
built-in black-eyed peas and grits.
This way, please.
I'm certain, Mr. Hadley, you'll find everything
to your satisfaction.
- Everything?
- Yes, sir.
Nice little boarding house
you have here.
This is Miss Moore's suite.
- And we're right across the hall?
- Yes, sir.
How do you like it?
What's not to like, huh?
Come on.
I'll show you around.
Anything missing?
Open the closet.
Look over here.
Great invention,
the telephone, hmm?
See you in an hour, okay?
Sure floored her, didn't it?
- Me too.
- Sounds like a crack.
No, just a dent in my armor.
- What does that mean?
- Nothing much.
Except I had Lucy
figured wrong.
What did you expect?
I figured she'd be different
than all the rest.
- She is.
- No, she's not.
If she were, she'd have spit
right in your eye.
Lucy?
Lucy, you decent?
Lucy, are you dec...
Guess she was.
- Yes, Mr. Hadley?
- Did you see Miss Moore leave?
Yes, sir, I did...
about, uh, 30 minutes ago.
Yes, sir.
- Remember the girl who arrived
with me an hour ago?
- Yes, she left alone.
Took a cab to the airport.
The airport.
Please step on it.
Last call.
National Airlines,
flight 46 to New York,
gate number five.
- All aboard.
- Hello, Lucy.
Hello.
Please let me talk to you.
I left, didn't I?
Didn't that say enough?
Yes, more than you know.
Please give me an hour...
just till the next plane leaves.
All right.
Pan American World Airways Clipper,
flight 701...
for Buenos Aires
and intermediate cities...
now boarding
at Pan American concourse.
- Cream?
- Never use it.
Shows how I ittle I know you.
Why'd you run out?
I took a sudden dislike
to the suite.
Did I... overdo it?
Oh, it was beautiful
at first glance.
Then I thought how ugly
it would be... in the morning.
You mean, the idea of...
having fun?
Wasn't that your intention?
Guilty as charged.
I was tempted.
Was it easy to overcome?
Yes. You made it easy.
How, by throwing
my money at you?
- No. No, it wasn't that.
- What, then?
It was the ride.
"Up in the blue,"
as you call it.
Talked too much,
didn't I?
No. It was good talk.
Only... something happened
to me...
something unexpected
as the things you told me.
I tried to tell myself
it was, I don't know,
sympathy, compassion.
But it was more.
Let's...
let's get out ofhere.
Cigarette?
We'll put you on the next plane
to New York.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, Lucy...
sorrier than I've even been
in my whole sorry life.
I hope you believe me.
- Is it important that I do?
- Very,
because I...
I want to start
all over again... with you.
How?
Suppose...
Just suppose I came
to New York again.
Not to play,
but to work, to behave like...
like Tom, Dick and Harry.
L- I'd ask you for dates,
take you to lunches,
to the movies.
I'd be... happy
with a good night kiss.
I'd think seriously about all
the things I used to laugh at,
like having a wife
and a home...
and kids.
Right now there's one thing
you don't have to suppose.
I'm in love with you.
So much so that...
I want to marry you.
- Mitch Wayne?
- Yeah.
Jack Williams, Miami Press.
- Uh, care to say a few words about the wedding?
- What wedding?
We know that Judge Ross issued a marriage
license this morning to Kyle Hadley...
and, uh, Lucy Moore.
- So what?
- Who is Lucy Moore?
- That's a good question.
- You don't know her?
- Not very well.
- What is she? A show girl, model, what?
Just a girl... a lady.
- A beautiful lady.
- I got news for you, Mr. Wayne.
Your torch is burnin'.
- Wedding took place two hours ago.
- Yeah? Where?
- Right under my nose. St. Mark's Church.
- Oh.
St. Mark's Church.
Uh, Mr. Wayne.
Hey, now wait up, Mr. Wayne.
- Pull up a chair.
- Thank you, sir.
- How does it look to you?
- Promising.
How much
would you gamble on it?
I thinkwe ought to go
15,000 feet.
What do you hearfrom Kyle?
The gossip columns say
they're in Acapulco.
When do you think I'm going to
get a chance to kiss the bride?
Six months from now? Ayear?
- It's only been five weeks.
- Is that all?
It's about time you got hitched,
isn't it?
No, I... I have trouble enough
finding oil.
I sure wish you felt different
about Marylee.
We grew up together,
like brother and sister.
I just can't see it
any other way.
Yeah.
It's a shame, though,
in a way.
It's a real shame.
- All right. 5,000 feet. No more.
- Okay.
- Hi.
- Hi!
Mitch. Mr. Hadley,
meet Mrs. Hadley.
Welcome to Hadley...
the town and the family.
Thank you.
Well, son, I...
I just couldn't be happier.
- Did all right, didn't I?
- You sure did.
Nowyou vamoose for a few minutes.
I want to talk to my daughter-in-law alone.
Sure, Dad.
I'll be in Mitch's office.
- Would you like a soft drink?
- No, thanks.
Just had one
in the drugstore.
- Have you been out to the house?
- Yes, it's beautiful!
And it's home.
- Did you meet Marylee?
- No, she was out.
Oh, that's too bad. L- I know she's gonna
like you just as much as I do.
I was afraid you might
be wary of me...
that, perhaps, you'd regard me
as a gold digger.
Now, look.
I'm gonna be honest with you.
That's just what I figured,
until I talked to Mitch.
Mitch? Interesting.
Yeah. I wasn't easy
to convince,
but Mitch sold me.
In other words, you trust Mitch's judgment
more than Kyle's.
Well, I wouldn't put it
that way.
- May I ask you a favor?
- Anything at all.
Please give Kyle a chance.
You may have to change your opinion ofhim.
How much liquor
has he been puttin' away?
I haven't seen him drunk yet.
Does he still...
Well,
I better not ask about that.
You mean, about the pistol
he keeps under his pillow.
- You know.
- Yes.
I know all about his anxieties
and fears.
You can forget
about the pistol.
Kyle threw it in the ocean.
- I tell you, I'm still up on cloud seven.
- And sober too.
Yep, even in Mexico. Remember how I used
to go on those Tequila jags?
How could I forget?
- Yeah?
- A Mr. Willis calling. He says it's urgent.
Okay, put him on.
Dan Willis.
- Mitch.
- What is it, Dan?
The Hadley gal's here
with Roy Carter.
Thanks, Dan.
I'll be right over.
- You got a gun here?
- Stay here. I'll handle it.
Dan said the Hadley gal.
I'm the Hadley boy, remember?
That's a hot one, ain't it?
Notvery.
I've heard better.
What's the matter, honey?
Are you insulted?
Not yet.
Just bored.
The afternoon's wasting away.
I'll be right back.
How's the chances
of some privacy?
Are you crazy, Roy?
If old man Hadley ever found out,
he'd have you sent so far away, it'd take
ten years for a telegram to reach you.
- Give me the key.
- Forget it. You're stepping out of your class.
You wouldn't like to have this joint of
yours catch fire some night, would you?
Give me a couple of minutes
to clean up.
Don't overdo it.
If I ever catch you
with my sister again, I'll...
- Where do you want her to play, in a sandbox?
- Honeymoon over?
Are you forgetting where you are
and who you're with?
Oh, be polite.
Answer the lady.
Tell us all about...
Marylee, come on.
We're getting out ofhere.
Wait outside, Marylee.
- Step aside, Wayne, before I cut you.
- I would like to see that.
Hold it, Roy.
You bigmouth beer slinger.
You phoned Wayne, didn't you?
This gun's got a hair trigger.
Okay.
So I'm persuaded.
- Some other time, huh?
- You've had it.
- You take Kyle and get out ofhere.
- Thank you, Sir Galahad.
You do care about me,
don't you?
- Let me have the gun, Dan.
- Forget it.
Forget it.
I'll kill him.
A whiskey bottle's
about all you'd ever kill.
Sorry, Dan.
Mitch, let's go down to the river,
to our old haunt.
We used to be happy there.
Our own private world...
mine and yours...
and Kyle's.
Then you grew up and left me...
you and Kyle...
the rover boys.
I guess that's why
I hate him so...
for taking you away...
from me.
I love you, Mitch.
I'm desperate for you.
So desperate, I run
to the likes of Roy Carter.
All right, blame me.
I'm not talking about blame.
About love.
Do you love me, Mitch?
Like a brother.
I don't want you
as a brother.
Can't be any other way,
Marylee.
Don't... Please don't waste your life
waiting for me.
I'll wait,
and I'll have you,
marriage...
or no marriage.
I'm Marylee.
Welcome to Hadley, Sister-In-Law.
Thank you.
Nice of you to come in and greet me.
Oh, please.
I'm allergic to politeness.
By the way, your darling husband should
be taught to mind his own business.
Should I apologize for him?
You should have seen him...
on the wrong end of every punch.
And on thewrong end of town.
It isn't 21, but...
it can be exciting.
What do you think of Mitch?
You changed the subject.
Oh, there's a man for you...
or for me, rather.
Kyle starts something,
Mitch finishes it for him.
Kyle falls on his face,
Mitch picks him up.
Kyle steals,
Mitch takes the blame.
And there you have
the secret story of Kyle Hadley...
and his electric personality.
I've heard it
from Kyle himself.
Anyway, about your marriage,
you have my condolences.
Pardon me if, uh, I seem to be
brushing you out of my hair.
Darling, I'll send you some of my towels.
I believe you're still wet behind the ears.
What was the matter
with you today, son?
You were supposed to be
huntin', not broodin'.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Sit. Sit!
Anything we can talk about?
- Did you ever hear of Iran?
- Africa? Asia? Asia, I guess.
- What about it?
- I'm thinking of going there.
- For Hadley?
- No.
Trans American Oil.
- Got a bellyful of the Hadleys?
- I guess so.
I sometimes wonder
ifl did right by you...
puttin' you with Jasper
and his kids.
Meant it all forthe best... wanted you to have
the chance I had and didn't take.
I better level with you, Dad,
about why I'm leavin'.
I'm in love with a woman
that happens to be Kyle's wife.
- Is she in love with you?
- No.
Strictly one-sided.
Bet you can't throw that far, Mitch.
Mitch can do everything
better than you, Kyle.
Shut up, Marylee.
- Throw it, Mitch.
You did it, Mitch!
Last one across is a rotten egg.
Hey, what's that purple stuff
on your lips?
Mulberry juice.
Looks like lipstick, doesn't it?
Yeah, sure does.
Mitch, am I beautiful?
- Uh-huh.
- Do you love me?
Sure. You're my girl.
When we grow up,
you'll marry me, won't you, Mitch?
I love you so much.
I t's gonna be a great football game.
Could put us in the Cotton Bowl.
Putting me in Dallas
is what I like about it.
I never know who's got the ball.
A drink...
for your thoughts.
Congratulate me.
I've just been voted the life of the party.
Your old room.
All those wonderful afternoons
we used to spend here.
And it rained.
Well, it was too cold for us
to go down to the river haunt.
Yes, those wonderful
lost afternoons.
That's a nice dress...
real flattering.
I've changed since we
last swam in the raw, haven't I?
A long, long time ago.
I was an idiot boy then.
Yes, you were.
The other idiot boy's downstairs
having himself a big party.
It's a happy occasion, isn't it?
Unbelievable.
Married a whole year
and still sober...
and still faithful.
It can't last much longer.
Don't sell Lucy short.
There's only so much
a woman can do, and no more.
I speak from...
personal experience...
with you.
You know,
you're remarkable.
You've got your axe buried in Kyle's head,
and you're grinding it at the same time.
- I can think of much better
things than making small talk.
- Oh.
All right. Let's dance.
Still the idiot boy.
Oh, thank you, Dad!
Oh, it's beautiful.
Thank you, Lucy.
What about the poor struggling husband?
Don't I get anything?
- Well, what more do you want, son?
- Another big party.
Only next time,
we'll invite the stork.
- Beats prescription liquor, doesn't it, Doc?
- It sure does.
Just a second, Doc, please.
- Do me a favor.
- Just name it.
Ask Lucy to pay you a visit.
- She's been visiting me regularly.
- She has?
Look, why don't we have a powwow in my office
about 10:00 in the morning?
It won't keep.
Tell me, is, is Lucy all right?
Well, what I mean is...
can she have children?
- Tomorrow we'll sit down and...
- Now, Doc.
Please.
There's nothing wrong with Lucy.
Well, your wife's
a wonderful dancer.
Kyle, what's the matter?
- Come on. Dance with me.
- Can't.
Somebody just stole my...
magic dancing slippers.
Anyone for lunch?
Don't tell me where.
I'll find my way.
Glory be. Maybe you finally
see the light in my eyes.
Oh, there's nothing
like a picnic,
and I've brought everything
but rain and ants.
Oh, correction.
Everything but rain.
Anything happen at the house
after I left the party?
Didn't miss a thing,
except the sight of me
sleeping in your old room.
Did Kyle have a spat
with Lucy?
That's why you gave in and came here with me...
to play 20 questions.
Well, did he or didn't he?
I don't know. All I know is he bit
my head off this morning.
Why?
What'd you say to him?
That he looked sick. All I said was,
"I trust it's nothing trivial."
- Do you...
- Oh, please. No more questions.
Let's eat,
drink and be merry.
We'll eat, drink and run.
If Lucy were here with you,
I bet you wouldn't say that.
I once washed your mouth out
with soap. I can do it again.
I knowyou, Mitch.
No one will ever know you
as I knowyou.
Good morning, Doctor.
- What's the story?
- I believe we'll have to make
some further tests...
What is it?
Yes or no?
Kyle, it's not that simple.
No apologies. Facts.
- What'll you have, Doctor?
- Oh, just a limeade, Sherry. No ice.
Yes, Doctor.
The tests we took show a...
Well, let's call it a weakness.
Believe me,
you're not sterile.
And there is hope, real hope,
that, in time,
we'll be able to correct
that weakness.
- Hello?
- Marylee, it's Mitch.
Oh, yes. Brother Mitch.
Kyle just phoned me.
He wants us, you and me,
to join him and Lucy
at the country club for dinner.
Look, I'll pick you up
at 6:00, okay?
Don't bother, Mitch, not unless you have
an exciting evening in mind.
And you know exactly what I mean
by an exciting evening.
- Good evenin'. Fill her up?
- Yes.
You're Biff Miley, aren't you?
Nice of you to recognize me
without my shoulder pads.
Your number's
in my program.
I recognized you too,
Miss Hadley.
You do?
What do we do now?
Break into a chorus
of "Hail, Alma Mater"?
I close up
in half an hour.
You mean, usually.
All right.
Just keep the motor running.
- Good evening, Jack. Is Mr. Hadley here yet?
- Oh, yes, ma'am.
Hello, Lucy.
What's up?
I was hoping
you could tell me.
I haven't seen Kyle since
he left the house this morning.
He phoned me about an hour ago and said
we were having dinner at the club.
Well, he phoned me too.
Kyle.
Howdy.
Good evening, Mrs. Hadley,
Mr. Wayne.
Good evening.
- Set 'em up, Ben.
- Yes, sir.
- Where's little sister?
- Couldn't locate her.
She'll never, never be missed.
- Will she, honey?
- Will she what?
Be missed. Haven't you learned to hate
Marylee as much as I do?
A toast to...
to beauty...
and the truth,
which is anything but beautiful.
Come on.
Let's have some dinner.
Honey, this is an occasion.
We must proceed with,
with quiet dignity.
What, um...
what are we celebrating?
The end of a drought...
a year long drought.
We drank a toast to truth.
- So?
- You ought to let us in on what
you're really celebrating...
or mourning.
- Ben, quick. The potions.
- Yes, sir.
So you'd like to know
my secret.
The secret is...
not to pour the vermouth, just
to pretend you're pouring it.
Those lousy cops again.
I'm sorry, Ralph.
I didn't mean to blow up like that,
but I'm getting a little sick and tired
of your efficiency experts.
They ought to get off their chairs
and out in the field for a change.
All right, Ralph. I'll see you in New York
Thursday morning. Bye.
I thought I'd seen
the last of this.
I wish I could,
but I can't explain it.
- Where have you been?
- The country club.
- Did you have a spat?
- No.
Nothing as simple as that.
We let him drink, hoping he'd talk
and tell us what was on his mind.
Butwe learned nothing,
except that
he's terribly tormented.
What are you
going to do now?
Go to him and try to help him.
Kid. Kid stuff, Mitch.
I want to buy a new car,
the first flashy car.
To hell with college.
I wanna have fun...
with some girls.
Nice overin Dallas.
To hell with college.
Wanna make some money, Mitch?
Over at the bottling plant.
Old man Daley's place.
No, I haven't got any bottles.
Old man Daley has.
Don't touch me.
Touch me, I'll tell my father.
That's what I'll do.
My father.
We weren't stealing,
were we, Mitch?
We were just stacking
some bottles up for you.
That's all we were doing,
wasn't it, Mitch?
Mitch? Mitch.
Wait forme.
Wait forme!
I remember I stopped the surgeon just
before he went in to operate.
I said, "Doctor, I'll write
a check for a million dollars,
but just don't let my wife die."
But I failed.
I failed them all...
my wife
and my brotherJoe.
Both my children.
I think you're being
too hard on yourself.
Where did you first meet
my daughter?
I never met her before, not till
she picked me up tonight.
- She picked you up?
- Sure.
- That's how she operates.
- What do you mean, "operates"?
I never heard of anybody
pickin' her up. That's all.
It's always
the other way around.
How would you know?
Why don't you just walk up and down
Main Street and ask somebody?
I'm asking you!
Look, I don't like
to shoot my mouth off.
I also don't like
being on the carpet.
I didn't take her to the motel.
She took me.
Your daughter's a tramp, mister.
If that ain't plain enough, I could put...
- Get him out ofhere.
- Should we hold him?
No. Let him go.
Keep it quiet, if you can.
Thanks.
Thanks a lot.
- Kyle?
- Hmm?
When is it going to end?
You never know.
Things have a way
ofhappening so suddenly,
unexpectedly.
- What's wrong?
- What isn't?
Me and my darling sister...
we pushed Dad
down the stairs.
You started drinking
before your father died.
Yeah,
I was 14 years old.
- Kyle.
- Hmm?
Do you love me?
Love you?
I don't even love myself.
Kyle, what is it?
Is it something I've said...
or something I've done
or should have done?
I can't tell you.
I'm afraid.
It's like I was deep
in a mountain pass,
snowcaps hanging
over my head.
If I make a sound,
snow might all come
tumbling down.
Bury me... alive.
- Good morning.
- Good morning, Lucy.
- Would you like some coffee?
- Yes, thanks.
You look ill.
It's been a long week.
Yeah.
About time for me
to clear out.
Bored?
Disgusted.
Mostly with myself.
But I...
I need you here.
That's the only reason
I stayed... to help you.
Not Kyle?
I made a resolution last week.
It goes like this:
To hell with the Hadleys.
I'm a Hadley.
Not to me, you're not.
- I respect my marriage.
- Haven't I?
Where are you going?
Going to see my dad. Why?
Would you drop me off
in town?
What's the matter
with your car?
Nothing.
All right.
That was no lady.
That was your wife.
Where are they going?
I don't know.
Where would you take
your best friend's wife?
You're a real sweet kid.
Now be nice to me, brother.
One morning we'll wake up,
and we'll be all alone together.
Go on, sister.
Tell me another pretty story.
- Once upon a time, there was
a poor little rich boy.
- Kyle Hadley, by name.
- Who pickled his tiny brain with gin and bourbon.
- Not so. Scotch.
Till he got so stinking blind, he couldn't see
what was going on right under his big red nose.
But his charming, righteous
little sister did.
Yes.
She saw the end
of a marriage...
and the beginning
of a love affair.
You're a filthy liar.
I'm filthy... period.
But you don't have to take
my word for anything.
Just try keeping your head clear
and your eyes open.
Why should you care?
You've never cared about me.
- Or your wife.
- Why are you putting your two cents in?
Only because of Mitch.
Because I've never had him,
and your wife has.
Will you pick me up at the drugstore
in about an hour, please?
Better take a taxi.
Am I that much trouble to you?
You don't know how much.
I'll be waiting for you.
When you figurin' on leavin'?
Monday morning.
Flying all the way to Iran?
No, I'm gonna take a tanker
out of Baltimore.
Places don't seem so far away
if you take a plane.
Used to feel that way
about motor cars.
What'd Kyle have to say?
Nothin'.
Haven't told him yet.
I'm waiting for him
to sober up.
How's Kyle's wife?
Goin' through hell.
Did she ever find out
just howyou feel about her?
Yeah. I about told her
this morning.
How strong does she feel
about you?
I don't know.
In about another hour or so,
I'm gonna find out.
The car's over here.
Stopped at the gun shop.
Picked out a rifle
for my dad...
for Christmas.
What's the matter?
Well, I'll tell you
what's the matter with me.
I'm leaving for Iran
next week.
Trans American Oil.
I can't keep holding back
how I feel about you, Lucy...
how I've felt ever since
the first day we met.
I'm in love with you.
No. L-I have
to tell you something.
- I've found out why Kyle's
been drinking so heavily.
- Forget Kyle.
- I'm talking about you and me.
- Mitch, you've got to listen to me, please.
You know how much Kyle's always talked about
having children... how badly he's wanted them.
Dr. Cochrane told him
he might never have any.
Poor guy.
Mitch, it was a medical opinion,
not a fact.
I'm going to have a baby.
That was for good-bye.
Well, it's a beautiful day...
for something or other,
isn't it?
- What's Kyle doing?
- You mean, right this minute?
- Yes.
- Well, right this minute, Kyle's out.
Did he say
where he was going?
All I know is he hopped
into his car and he flew.
- And I mean flew.
- Was he drunk?
If he wasn't,
he was well on his way.
You ought to take it
with you.
Well, with you chasing me...
Can I level with you, Kyle?
Mr. Hadley to you.
Well, it seems to me,
Mr. Hadley,
if I were one of the richest
men in the world,
I wouldn't be sitting in a place like this
drinking raw corn.
- Whatwould you be doing?
- I'd be at the country club,
drinking bonded bourbon.
- Nothin' but.
- I like bootlegged corn better.
It's full of memories.
Each swig takes me back,
far back.
You know, good ol' days, when a fellow
knew nothing and cared less.
Hello. It's Mitch.
No, sir. He ain't here. I haven't seen him since
that last time. You remember.
Yeah. Well, buzz me at home
ifhe drops in, will you?
Yeah, Mitch.
Surewill. Bye.
Excuse me, sir.
Dinneris served.
Thank you, Sam.
It's rather pleasant here
without Kyle, isn't it?
Well, ifit isn't
SmilingJack himself.
Hark, L-I think I hear the master's kiddie car.
I hope the drawbridge is down.
My, you're a dandy group.
Bring me a cocktail
I can drink.
Yes, sir.
- I don't mean tomato juice.
- Yes, sir.
I suppose you're wondering why
I brought you all here tonight.
Now ifhis lights
would only go out.
Kyle, would you please
come upstairs?
- You wish to confess?
- Please, Kyle.
- Don't leave the country.
- Please.
Amusing, isn't he?
Very.
Let's throw a party.
Call up everybody we know.
No party, huh?
What do you say to a plane ride?
We'll go to Acapulco.
What do you say to Palm Beach?
- We'll decide about it in the morning.
- It'll be fun,
like turning back the clock.
Palm Beach.
I like that.
It's got meaning.
It's got signif...
Are you sure
your husband's out of town?
Sit down, Kyle.
You said, "Sit down, Kyle."
That means bad news,
doesn't it?
No, it doesn't.
The news couldn't be better.
You know howyou look now?
Like you did that night
at the Miami Airport,
when I took you
off the plane.
Kyle, I went to see
Dr. Cochrane this morning.
He told you about me,
didn't he?
I said the news was good.
What's goodabout it?
We're...
we're going to have a baby.
You mean, adopt one.
No. No, ourbaby...
yours and mine.
No. No.
No.
Kyle, it's true.
You shouldn't
have done that to me.
You shouldn't have.
What are you talking about?
Mitch.
You and Mitch.
Don't say that, Kyle.
Don't even think it.
What did you think?
You think I was just
a drunken idiot?
That I'd believe you?
That I'dlet you use
myname? Take my money?
You all can rot in hell!
- You, Mitch and your little...
- Kyle, I've had nothing to do with Mitch.
You dirty tramp!
Mitch.
Get out.
Get out before I kill you!
He hit me.
Dr. Cochrane, please.
It's very urgent.
She's asleep now.
Give her one of these when she wakes up.
- How bad is she?
- She's weak, too weak to move
to the hospital till morning.
She's had a miscarriage.
- Good night, Marylee.
- Good night, Doctor.
- Your coat, Doctor.
- Thank you.
Mind ifl ask you
an impertinent question?
Kyle had no cause.
- Thanks. Where is he now?
- I don't know.
He'dbetternot come back here
tonight. I'll tellyou that.
Call me if you need me.
- You been in an accident?
- Get me a bottle of corn.
- Maybe you ought to go see a doctor.
- I said a bottle!
You know who that is?
Kyle Hadley.
The oil family.
Well, what do ya know?
I thought he was a bum.
That's five bucks.
- I said five.
- I'm buying something else.
- Like what?
- That gun you keep.
Put it in another sack.
No sale.
What's with you?
- Somebody tried to kill me.
- Who?
My best friend.
- What are you doing?
- The liquor's on the house.
I'll give you 100
for the gun.
I got business
to attend to.
Take your courage
and leave me be.
Oh, don't go!
- I'm just gonna get you some water.
- Oh, not yet, please.
I don't wanna go to sleep yet.
I just want to talk to you.
Take me away, Mitch.
Take me out of this house.
- I will, in the morning.
- No!
No, now. I'm afraid.
I won't leave you.
Where is he?
I don't know, but wherever he is,
he'd better stay there...
because ifhe comes back here,
I'll settle with him.
Oh, no, Mitch. Please.
Shut up, woman!
There's gonna be a killin'!
- I heard talk! I heard him!
- You heard nothin'.
You lousy white trash.
You no-account,
two-faced dog.
I'm gonna watch you cringe.
- Then I'm gonna put a bullet in your belly.
- For what, Kyle?
My best friend,
my lifelong pal.
What a laugh!
You crawlin' snake.
You crept in here,
sponged off us Hadleys, stole everything
I ever wanted, everything I ever had.
Like what?
You made me small
in my father's eyes.
You made my sister
spit at me.
Then...
you stole my wife.
- I didn't take anything from you.
- Lousy white trash, say a prayer.
You know who you sound like?
Oldman Daley.
Remember old man Daley
and the bottles?
It was your idea
to steal them.
I couldn't talk you out of it,
so I went along.
But when he caught us, he didn't
blame you, he blamed me.
And he grabbed me and he
kicked the tar out of me.
I remember him saying,
"This is what Hadley gets...
for letting his boy
play with trash like you."
He had you pegged right.
You are trash!
I took the blame for stealing those bottles,
just like I've always taken the blame,
but I'm not gonna take it
for this.
Kyle, we've never lied
to each other.
And I'm telling you now,
I never touched Lucy,
only because she's your wife.
Get this straight.
The child would have been yours.
Not mine.
Yours.
- Lousy white trash!
- Kyle!
Kyle!
Mitch?
Yeah?
What are we doing here, Mitch?
What are we doing?
Let's go down to the river...
where we belong.
Operator, rush an ambulance
to the Hadley estate.
I'll be down at the river,
waiting.
Waiting.
I was just thinking.
You know,
you threatened to kill Kyle.
The servants heard you.
Also Dr. Cochrane...
and Yours Truly.
So what?
I could tell the police...
that I sawyou kill
my dear brother.
You could.
On the other hand,
a wife wouldn't...
and couldn't testify
against her own husband.
You know, for a beautiful girl,
you can look real ugly sometimes.
Ask yourself this:
Would I ever be enough for you?
I can talk you right into
the state penitentiary.
You're sick, Marylee.
Your sickness won't be cured
by marrying me.
Before it's too late,
you'd better face up to yourself.
Look how far we've come
from the river.
Raise your right hand, please.
Do you swear the testimony
you're about to give in this inquest...
is the truth, the whole truth and nothing
but the truth, so help you God?
- I do.
Dr. Cochrane,
wouldyou tell this inquest
about the threat, please?
When I asked Mr. Wayne
where Kyle Hadley was,
he said, "I don't know, but he'd better not
come back here tonight."
Thank you, Doctor.
Next witness.
My wife. She said to me,
"There's gonna be a killin'.
I heard talk. Mr. Mitch said
he's gonna kill Mr. Kyle."
Thank you.
Next witness.
That's what I heard...
Mr. Mitch yellin'
and sayin' to Mr. Kyle,
"Get out of here!
Get out
be-before I killyou!"
- Thank you. Thank you
very much. Next witness.
Well, Kyle looked all beat up.
I said, "What's with you?"
He said,
"Somebody tried to kill me."
I asked who, and he said,
"My best friend."
Did he mention a name?
No, he didn't have to.
Why not?
Well, everybody knows that Kyle's
best friend was... Mitch Wayne.
- Thank you, Mr. Willis.
That'll be all. Next witness.
Canyou tell us if, at any time, you heard
Mitch Wayne threaten to killyour husband?
Mitch Wayne did not kill
my husband.
That wasn't my question.
I asked you if, at any time, you heard Mitch
Wayne threaten to kill your husband.
- Yes, but...
- Thank you. That will be all.
Will Miss Hadley
step forward, please?
State your name, please.
- Marylee Hadley.
Do you swear the testimony
you're about to give...
is the truth
and nothing but the truth?
- I do.
- Be seated.
You can refuse to answer any question
you may regard as incriminating.
What was your relation
to the deceased?
He was my brother.
Exactly where were you at
the time Kyle Hadley was shot?
I repeat, Miss Hadley,
exactly where were you at
the time Kyle Hadley was shot?
You refuse to answer
the question?
Canyou tell us anything
about the shooting?
Yes. My brother,
he was killed.
By whom, Miss Hadley?
By whom
was your brother killed?
Mitch Wayne.
Stop those men!
No one will leave this chamber
till after this inquest is closed.
Miss Hadley,
you named Mitch Wayne.
Are you here and now
testifying...
that Mitch Wayne shot
and killed Kyle Hadley?
Mitch Wayne was there...
in the study
with my brother.
Kyle had a gun in his hand.
He was raving mad...
raving about things
that weren't so.
Mitch tried
to talk to him,
to make him understand
how wrong he was,
to stop him
from using the gun.
Afraid he might even use it
on himself.
I made a grab for the gun.
Kyle and I struggled.
The gun went off.
Miss Hadley,
five persons under oath...
have testified that Mitch Wayne
threatened to kill Kyle Hadley.
They don't know Mitch Wayne
as I know hi m.
Whatever he may have said...
means nothing.
Except he was worried
about Kyle...
as a brother for a brother.
Why would Kyle Hadley
want to kill himself?
He was depressed...
by Father's sudden death,
and he'd been drinking.
Heavily?
Yes.
My brother always drank
too much.
He was sad...
the saddest of us all.
He needed so much...
and had so little.