"With pride, I write down."
"The poem of my life."
"Passion and love, tears and follies."
"Honesty an end in itself."
"Life something to gamble with."
"When epic stories are retold."
"Hail the hero with will of steel."
"Who watches the world like a lion."
"Forward we go."
"As consequences are known
to one's own self"
"On the double."
"I must soar over the clouds."
"Forward I must go."
"As consequences are known
to one's own self."
"On the double."
"Must soar over the clouds."
"Forward I must go."
"As consequences are known
to one's own self."
"On the double."
"Man must stand sky high."
The law has duly punished
the drug king Chu Tao.
But we've paid a heavy price.
Aer you damaged the
squatters' camp,
the government had to
resettle them.
It paid $1 million for one
ceiling lamp,
and the whole shantytown was damaged
by you.
Taxpayers must pay for
social security.
But they shouldn't pay for
individual heroism.
Why the lamp instead of the stairs?
Because you were so nimble.
Right, we don't need star policemen.
We only need disciplined policemen.
I never expected promotion
for capturing Chu.
Our success was the result
of everyone's efforts.
Not you alone.
You're lucky not to have
been demoted.
Top brass wanted to discipline you
for holding me hostage,
But I talked them out of it.
I should thank you then.
I feel you're too individualistic.
You forgot you're only an
ordinary cop.
As of today, you're back in
uniform again.
Go to help where you're needed.
That means being an
all-round reserve?
You'll be busy as hell.
Thank you, sir.
Issue tickets, yes.
Catch robbers, no.
Attention, all on patrol.
An accident has caused a
big jam at the Crossroads Motel.
Hurry to the scene.
May, you better go.
I'm on duty.
Just regard me as another citizen,
and not your girl friend.
A common citizen who wants to
talk to a policeman.
What is it?
I feel that you make a
dashing traffic cop.
I'm on duty, Miss.
I've brought you some cold drinks
Thank you.
Thank you, Mister policeman.
I don't drink, Miss.
Have a sip. You never know
when you can take a break.
That's why I must avoid
drinking too much.
Don't worry.
Do you want me to be demoted?
Hey, Big Hero! Big Lover!
Still a lowly traffic cop?
You're lucky not to have
gone to jail like Chu.
Jail?
Three Swiss doctors certified
I only have 3 months to live
I've come out to wait for death.
Three months is a short time.
My boss may still be alive after
you're dead.
That's a threat against my life.
Is that so? Sue me then.
Take care.
Let's go!
Ka-kui.
That policeman
brought me so much hardship.
As long as I live,
I won't forgive him.
Boss, I don't know how to
do any good things,
But I'll stitch up that
policeman good and proper.
I'm very excited tonight.
Of course,
they have a live show and steak.
But I can see you're not happy.
Me? No, I'm looking forward to it.
Wish you were as happy as I am.
Are you afraid of Chu Tao...
No, but I'll be more careful
with him out of jail.
Maybe next week...
Detective.
Finished so soon?
Why are you here?
This is no place for a
traffic cop.
Block B, 1st floor, it must
be comfortable.
You go up first.
How do you know she lives in
block B, 1st floor?
With money, you can get
people to do anything.
Let alone getting someone's address
What do you mean?
The staircase of this old
building is very narrow.
If there's a fire in the corner here,
there will be no way out.
Fire engines can't get close
as the street's too narrow.
Kid, watch out for this beautiful
lady carefully.
Don't let her get scarred
or scalded.
You bastard!
May.
Auntie.
You're on your own?
Why isn't Ka Kui helping you?
He's still on duty.
I can manage.
I'm not against you
dating a policeman.
But he's too dutiful and stubborn.
A man should be committed to his work,
But a dedicated policeman
may have many enemies.
That's why you
have to face all this trouble.
In fact, I'm not worried.
I'm doing it to save him
from worrying.
He has reason to be worried.
Who are they?
Those same rascals.
Why is the detective not here?
Wait for me at the cafe
across the street.
Excuse me.
Why are you here?
I promised to
fix him for good.
I came to check
if you're running away.
It's not her faults.
She must be your mother,
she's so charming.
You scumbag!
Scum? You're wrong.
I'm the scum of the scum.
I'm not afraid of you.
Don't pay any attention to him.
Let's go.
Auntie, your daughter's
in love with a policeman.
I really worry about her.
I worry about you too.
You live on a high floor.
You may fall down by accident.
You dare hit me?
Don't!
Take her away.
Let go!
Creep!
Don't pull my hair.
It hurts!
Stop! It hurts!
Don't get mad, she's only a girl.
Let's go.
If you weren't a woman,
I'd have killed you by now.
Let's go. Forget it.
Take care.
Are you alright?
Auntie.
May got beaten because of you.
I told May not to date you
Did that lackey
and his henchmen hit you?
No, I used force first.
So they hit back at me.
They knocked me down.
My bottom hurts.
How did they know you'd be here?
He followed May back.
They're in the cafe over there.
I wonder why else they'll get up to?
Don't do anything foolish.
Kid, you looking for a beating?
You only know how to bully girls.
I have to admit I enjoy doing that.
Sorry.
Kill him and blame it on me!
You've studied the law.
Arrest them
if you've sufficient proof.
I couldn't control myself.
That's not a logical reason.
It was just a natural reaction
A policeman should have more patience.
You're a disgrace to the force.
I don't think so.
If a law enforcer daren't
respond to threats.
That's an insult to law.
You started it all to attract
attention to yourself.
It reminds people of your past.
How am I to answer to my superiors?
I've still a way out.
I quit.
Can your resignation solve the problem?
It's best when there's
no other way out.
I'm going.
Thanks for your support.
Goodbye.
Ka-kui.
Okay, if you have to quit,
Find a better job outside.
Bye-bye.
I will.
What's so special about
being a cop?
Don't you know the law?
Can the police use force at will?
Can they kill people?
Cut the crap. Sign it.
Damn you, I won't.
I'll sue you 'til you bleed.
I can afford a lawyer.
I'm not afraid.
Hit me! Go on, hit me! I dare you!
He hit me, you saw it!
Kill me if you dare!
My eyes are damaged!
I'm blind, pay me back!
Hit me in public if you dare!
Why are you just standing there?
Afraid?
Shoot me dead! I'll sue you!
Youngsters nowadays
have no tolerance.
Uncle Bill, I told you to
dissuade them.
Why didn't you say so before?
I thought you gestured for me to
throw him out.
Next time I know what to do.
What happened?
You don't want me to be a
policeman, do you?
I do, I'm proud of you.
I've got nothing
after all these years.
Just a lot of enemies who put
you in danger.
A good policeman has enemies
If he has none, it means,
he can't catch thieves.
In fact, I'm happy to see you hated.
It shows you're a good policeman.
Don't try to soothe me.
I'm already fed up and
I've quit.
Have you?
Are you disappointed?
Are you really quitting?
Thank God!
Don't!
What an exaggeration!
It's $5,540. Thank you.
I'll look around outside.
How about my credit card?
Sure.
This copy is for your reference.
Thanks.
What clothes should I bring along?
It's Bali,
you don't need any clothing.
That's what you think!
I'm so happy we're going
on this trip.
I hope the travel agency is honest.
It looks decent,
like a proper one.
Registered, paid, and no nonsense.
Ah Fay!
Ka-kui.
Long time, no see.
Is your beat?
Right.
What's the matter.
Got a report there's a bomb
in the arcade.
A bomb in the arcade?
It's right up your alley. Help us.
I'll try.
Ka-kui.
I'll just take a quick look.
Ah Sun!
You came at the right time.
Somebody reported
a bomb being planted.
Could it just be an hoax?
No. He told us to
disperse the crowd.
Said it'll explode in ten minutes.
Tell HQS to disperse the crowd.
So many people!
How do we do it?
Now, if it's a hoax,
who's to take the rap?
Facing the music is nothing new.
But a real bomb could prove fatal.
Right.
What should we do?
Treat it as if it were real.
Disperse the crowd.
Report to HQS.
Where's the fire alarm?
Over there.
Ka-kui!
I'll leave after sounding the alarm.
Give me something to smash it with.
- Ka-kui, this doesn't seem...
- Let's share the blame.
Follow me.
It's nothing!
Don't leave without paying!
Have you paid?
It's nothing at all.
Don't go, Miss.
It's impossible.
They just don't care.
Ka-kui!
Get out! Quickly!
Attention, everyone!
Please leave here at once.
Everybody,
I mean everybody must leave.
Central coding on fire, I guess.
Leave immediately, please.
Attention, leave in an orderly
manner, but fast.
Take care.
Why the hell is the alarm ringing?
People have business to do.
Ah Fay.
What's that?
Tell them to beat it, fast.
Please evacuate now,
for your own safety.
What's that?
I'll fix it. You go out first.
See if anybody else is inside.
Yes, sir.
We are done for!
Who's your commander?
You handle them.
Evacuate first.
The police will help you.
Ka-kui.
It's nothing. I'll take care of it.
You go home now,
Chief.
Who said there was a bomb?
It was phoned in.
Could it be a hoax?
Who sounded the alarm?
Me, sir.
You can go.
Yes sir.
Why the dispersal?
I was taught that,
when handling emergencies,
civilian's safety comes first.
So I dispersed them.
So you're indispensable
to the force.
No, sir.
Sir, there's no fire.
Your man suspected a bomb
and dispersed the crowd.
The demolition team's here.
Thanks.
Are we being made to look foolish?
Uncle Bill.
Quite possibly.
They want to see the man in charge.
May I go and pacify them?
Where are the demolition people?
They're coming.
This is getting messier.
Was I right or wrong?
Depends if there's a bomb or not.
Right now, we have to wait and see.
Tell them to stand way back.
Yes, sir.
Wait until after
the search is complete.
My ball!
How much longer must we wait?
What's the situation?
When it's fixed,
you'll be given the all clear.
Here you are.
Thank you!
Get set.
The ammunition people are here.
If they find nothing,
Raymond will be chewed out.
I didn't mean to embarrass him.
Nobody would cause this
mess on purpose.
Connect the hose over.
Smoke squad, stand by.
Bring in the water jets!
Spray that area!
Luckily no one got hurt.
Have you assessed the loss?
The insurance co will pay
for the loss of goods.
But our company's image
matters most.
We've asked the press to
play it down.
Who has a grudge against
our company?
It could be a simple case.
Possibly a mentally disturbed man.
Someone has called and claimed
responsibility for the bombing.
Tell her to put it through.
Put it through.
Speaking.
We are responsible
and we want $10 million.
If you don't pay, watch your
other properties go up in smoke.
Let me talk to him.
Let me think it over, sir.
It's a lot of money.
I must meet the board first.
We'll give you 24 hours.
Don't call the police.
Raymond, you're lucky.
It was a miracle no one was
hurt in that complex explosion.
You should thank God.
You did a good job regarding
Chu Tao too.
It was not me alone, sir.
Right.
Raymond, don't be too modest.
We leave the case to you.
Do you agree?
Yes.
Uncle Bill.
Morning, sir.
It looks like a tough case.
That's why we've got it.
Who do you think can handle it?
None other than you.
Think it over.
It can't be me.
How about someone who's on leave
You mean Chan Ka-kui?
He's quite competent.
He's too impulsive and unorthodox.
With him involved,
we'll feel the heat for sure.
He's rash, but a good cop.
I don't agree.
Go and find him, then,
if you feel he's the one.
Want to make fun of me?
Over there.
Which seat?
Did you get your passport
when you were a student?
Please find Chan Ka-kui
among your passengers.
Attention, passengers.
Mr Chan Ka-Kui.
Don't, don't.
Let me take a look.
It's ugly, don't look.
Mr Chan Ka-Kui,
please contact information.
You're wanted.
Yes.
What is it?
I don't know.
Let me go and see.
Are you Mr Chan?
Yes.
There's something wrong
with your passport.
My passport?
Only routine, it won't take long.
What happened?
I'll be back right away.
Be quick.
Ok.
Bye.
Oh, it's you!
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
What is it?
I'm in a hurry for a flight.
That bombing has turned out
to be an extortion case.
We've found it rather tough going.
What has that got to do with me?
It's a challenging case.
Raymond feels that...
I hope you'll cancel your leave.
Impossible,
I've already boarded the plane.
Besides,
I've left the police force.
I know how you feel.
I sympathize with you,
being under pressure,
but avoiding responsibility
is no solution.
I am not...
Uncle Bill, he said he's
not avoiding responsibility.
Raymond is impressed
by your performance.
What performance?
All I've got is impulsiveness...
Impulse means vitality.
But I can't control my 'heroics'.
An heroic man is usually
quick-thinking.
But the police need disciplined,
rather than quick-thinking men.
A quick-thinking man is
unconventional...
...to the point of being
irresponsible.
Only slow-thinking men have to
respect discipline, right?
Yes.
I must board the plane.
Time's up.
Goodbye.
How much ransom are the
bandits demanding?
$10 million, but the mode of
payment was not mentioned.
Any idea who may be responsible?
No clue. Could it be
a psychotic former employee?
Who knows?
Have you tried to locate the source
of the dynamite?
Why?
Simple.
Dynamite is a controlled item.
Dynamite for the bombs
must either be smuggled in,
or stolen from a local company.
Right, I hadn't thought of this.
We must find their
bomb-making and storage facility,
before payment is made.
Once the bombs are found,
they can do nothing.
So you solve the problem
right away.
Who can handle this case,
apart from you?
You take it over.
Do it your own way.
Yes, sir.
I must board the plane.
You can go to Bali any time.
It won't sink.
But the bomb case can't wait
Take your trip afterwards.
I must tell May about it first.
Go on then.
Hurry up.
Miss.
What is it?
This plane...
It has just taken off.
Taken off?
Well, it's already in mid-air.
Why is it so punctual?
May's passport is still with me.
Shit, now we're in real trouble.
Uncle Bill, it's too late.
What now?
Have I done something wrong?
Over there.
Thank you.
We're from Homicide,
here to see Miss Wong.
30th floor.
Thank you.
A bug.
Bugging? It took Nixon out of office.
Want to crack the case?
Know your enemy and you'll win.
Hide it.
Miss Wong, two policemen
here to see you.
Where is the toilet, please?
Go straight and turn right.
Thank you.
25th, please.
24th, please.
Please wait.
Uncle Bill, I'm worried about May.
I'll call Jakarta Airport
on my return.
Uncle Bill!
It stinks!
You've no manners!
Let me take the other lift.
I'm a policeman.
Miss Wong is expecting me.
Please wait.
Thank you.
You're used to being the scapegoat.
Don't tease me.
Two.
I'm Inspector Chang,
he's Sergeant Chan.
We've made an appointment.
Please follow me, gentlemen.
We are...
Mr Fung's in a meeting.
The power of attorney is ready.
Sorry.
Where's the toilet please?
Go straight and turn left.
Thank you.
Sorry.
Never mind. Where's your friend?
He's went off because
he's impatient.
The President is back.
This lot, if bought for under $300M
will be profitable.
Mr President.
You want me?
Inspector Chang's here.
Thank you.
Thank you for your
co-operation with the police
Who told you to build the
building so fast?
Please sit down.
Directors, shareholders and
department heads.
We have called this meeting...
to review the past 6
months' property situation,
before fixing the coming
year's sales policy.
As you know, the local stock
has now risen...
...two-thirds before last
year's market collapse.
Let's see the trends of the
local Blue Chip.
Judging from today's stock market.
Hotels and Manufactures
futures are good.
Good for all of Hong Kong.
Summing up the performance
of Banks & Properties,
the chance of rise & fall
for the next half is even.
So small investors may
invest in properties.
We must finish the new
houses soon.
Miss, you're beautiful.
The boss said when someone
comes for this coat...
...tell him to pay $500 for it.
Really?
Yes. Bye-bye.
How was it just now?
The meeting went ahead.
Did you bug the conference room?
Yes.
And the office?
Did he say "yes"?
He didn't say "no".
What else did he say?
Buy flats later in the year.
Buy flats?
Where are you going?
I'll take the next lift.
Ka-kui, it's May.
May, so you're back.
Oh, you're so great!
May, listen.
Ka-kui, you didn't want me
to return?
You slipped away after
luring me onto the plane.
You even took away my passport.
I was expelled on arrival at Bali.
And I was detained for over 10 hours.
I must finish it.
Would you even leave a dog behind?
Wouldn't you take it back home?
I now fare worse than a dog.
They're all staring at you.
I'm only talking to him.
What has it got to do with you?
Tell me in front of everyone,
what are you taking me for?
A girlfriend, ok?
Girlfriend?
Girlfriend? Am I your girlfriend?
You're nicer to common citizens!
Listen.
It's all over between us
Chan Ka-Kui, I hate your guts!
Uncle Bill,
did you send the cable for me?
I was going to do it
when I left the toilet.
You've ruined my life!
May!
Don't be so hard-hearted.
Go away!
Calm down.
Don't hold my bag! Scram!
Don't touch me. Out of my way.
May, listen.
I've already finished what
I wanted to say.
I won't see you any more.
May
May, are you all right?
Keep away,
don't touch my motorcycle.
Keep away.
May, listen to my explanation.
Won't you come and help?
Keep away,
I won't see you any more.
May
Go back to work.
Tell Ka-Kui to come in.
Ka-Kui, he wants you.
Sorry, sir.
Sorry.
Calm down.
You want to call May to explain?
No point in explaining now.
Don't explain.
I said the same to my wife.
A man is working
when not at home.
Sorry, I must go to the toilet.
Don't copy Uncle Bill's
male chauvinism.
Go and change now.
Sorry, sir.
May
So you're leaving.
A whole day wasted for nothing.
I'm off.
Let me escort you back.
No need.
Don't do anything foolish.
I'm serious.
It's no concern of hers.
Don't do anything foolish.
You're both in trouble.
Don't try anything!
I'll kill you.
I'll have some fun with you at last!
Ka-Kui!
Over here!
Detective, you're so outnumbered.
I shouldn't have brought so
many against you.
You've over-rated me.
My boss did it.
He wants to ruin you.
I took his money
and must do the job.
I give the orders and
my men deliver.
Make your move.
We are human too.
If you beg for mercy from John.
We won't shatter your feet.
We'll just break them half-way.
Stop dreaming.
Shoot if you have the guts.
It's a serious offence to
kill a policeman.
My boss wants to ruin you.
Breaking your limbs will be enough.
Get him.
Follow him.
He's here. Cripple him.
Beat him to a pulp.
Get up.
Let me do it.
Let me beat you so you're
permanently disabled.
It's not my fault,
I was paid to do it!
Keep away! I'll kill you,
I'm serious!
Fire at me!
I'll shoot!
Fire at my chest!
I'll shoot now!
It's not my fault!
Next time, I'll finish you off!
May!
May, are you alright?
Yes.
Take care of yourself.
Where are you going?
It's dangerous.
I wanted to even up the
score for you.
What if it was acid, not ink?
My face would have been
scarred for life.
Or, what if he lured you away
to get me.
What should I do then?
I want my boyfriend to be
gentle and considerate,
not a savage. Please understand.
Come in.
Good morning, sir.
'Detective on duty involved
in park scuffle'! Who? Look!
I must meet The Dogs first.
It's me, sir.
Sorry, sir.
YC Chu is vengeful but you
mustn't take it personally.
Sorry.
Do you need my help?
No, I think they're only
troublemaking.
I don't want it to spread.
Anyway, be alert.
The Dogs have been sent
to help you.
They're highly efficient.
Talk with them.
Thank you, sir.
Did he scold you? He must...
Let's go over there.
Any news?
Press said Fung's stock
may rise to $8.40
We've no cash to buy in.
And the new Miss Beach is
his girlfriend.
Mind your own business.
I'll take it. You call May.
Go on.
Ka-kui, some news.
I already reported this
to the board,
and they've agreed,
in principle, to pay.
Get to the point.
Is the money ready?
Almost. $10 million is not
a small amount.
Check the source of the
phone call.
Tai Po District.
Trace it.
Ting Kok Road, Tai Po.
Headquarters calling, any
officers in Ting Kok Road?
Any officers in Ting Kok Road?
Over.
Yes, I'm PC12674.
What do you want? Over.
Listen, PC12674.
Check any man leaving
a phone booth. Over.
Roger.
Have you tipped off the cops
Don't stall for time.
No, we won't do anything stupid.
We now want $20 million.
$20 million?
No bargaining.
PC12674.
Speak up.
I've found a suspect.
Stay alert. He could be
armed and dangerous.
Don't cause any panic.
Roger.
Sir, it's an offence not to
use the zebra crossing.
Go on,
Give me a break, sir.
Your ID card, please.
Calling Headquarter.
We need more men at that
phone booth.
Officers in the area,
please come to help at once.
Sorry, I can't identify.
Don't say "sorry",
it's no fault of yours.
How long have you been
in the force?
I left school two months ago.
You're excused, then.
Will I be punished for
having my gun stolen?
Have I lose any chance of
ever being promoted?
Not necessarily. You've learnt
from the experience.
A cop has to have his gun
stolen at least once.
It'll make him more careful in
the future.
Could you identify the suspect if
you saw him again?
Yes, dead or alive.
It's for you, boss.
Join our team and work with us.
I've already applied to join you.
Please fix that file for me.
Who is it?
Joker.
Speak up.
There's some news.
What news?
A Crazy Fai is dealing in dynamite.
See you at Hoi Wong Bar
at 9 tonight.
You know what to do?
No
You don't?
Hey, buddy.
Fai, I want to talk to you.
I don't know you.
We'll get on over time.
Well, let's talk over there.
Take your time.
What's your name?
Lo
Can I help you?
I want to buy a fish bomb.
Fish bomb?
Fai, I was introduced by a friend.
What do you need it for?
To catch fish.
You don't look like a fisherman.
Do I have to tell you I need it
for some serious business?
The profits are high.
I'll cut you in.
Ok, I'll make enquiries for you.
The goods don't belong to me.
Wait.
Thank you.
Sorry, my friend has already quit.
But he's making enquiries
for you. Wait here.
I'll come back when it's finished.
Wait.
Ok.
Hey, you. Stand up.
What is it?
CID, stand up.
Hands up.
Listen,
I've just come here to drink.
Drink? Someone said you
posses contraband.
Don't look.
Don't move. Throw it with
the holster, quick.
Stand together.
Don't do anything foolish.
Stand up. You have it?
Come out.
Keep away.
Bastard, you don't have to
sell to me.
Help.
Please, stop! You may kill me.
Why did you play that trick on me?
I wanted to make sure you're
not a spy.
So I got two CID guys
to check you out.
You can get the stuff easily.
Where is it?
Have you got the money?
It's cash on delivery.
Watch it for me.
Is it powerful?
Why not?
It's for blowing up rocks.
Any more?
Plenty.
Enough to blow up the
Empire State Building.
I don't know him. I just met him
for the first time.
I really don't know him!
You think you can get away?
Have some coffee.
Smoke?
Cooperate, and you'll go free.
Ever you ever got any confession
with this method?
It's never failed.
Well, what's the charge?
Come on! I've seen everthing.
But I'd rather play along.
You won't get mad so easily, right?
Have you never seen a girl use force?
Stop that!
Stop it!
Have you ever met such ruffians?
You promised to play along.
I'll sue you bitches.
Don't talk big. I could kill
you with one shot...
...and claim my gun misfired.
Who'd pity you even if you
were dead?
Come on!
I'll talk.
Why didn't you do so earlier?
Come on and have some coffee.
Have a smoke.
No, thanks.
Someone's peeping.
What's there to see?
I sold some sticks of dynamite
to some people recently.
One is a boatman.
He blasts the water to kill fish.
The second one picks up
empty shells...
...and he bought our stuff to
make bullets for resale.
The third is Polar Bear,
a big dealer.
He usually hangs out
at a Yaumatei poolroom.
Let me go and have a look.
Hung
Shopping?
Have you been followed?
No. What about you?
Don't look. Open up.
He was seen entering a storehouse.
There's a man waited for them.
We're sure there are three inside.
We'll wait here for them.
Keep up the surveillance.
They're coming out.
Check their car licence.
488, follow them.
You stay here.
I'll go down and see.
We're setting off now.
Ka-Kui, where are you going?
I'll go in to have a look.
Be alert.
I will.
Received.
They're tricky.
They've shaken off 488.
Don't worry, they'll return for sure.
Tell them to come back.
Yes sir.
Come back, 488.
Don't. It's me.
Quiet!
You scared me!
I slipped!
There's somebody else here.
Stay where you are!
Turn around!
Police, what are you doing?
He must be dumb.
Did you see three men over
here just now?
Question him.
Do you work here?
Do you sleep here?
He's gesturing
but I can't understand him.
You get what you can from him.
Take him to the police
station first.
Come along. It's okay!
I only want you for questioning.
Come on.
No need to handcuff him.
Are all these things yours?
Don't go away.
He can't hear you. Follow him.
Help me get back my gun.
Mr Chan.
Let's scatter! Find that
deaf-mute. Take care.
Yes, sir.
I didn't expect that
guy to be such a good fighter.
Neither did I.
Help me find my gun first.
If our plan to acquire
Indian Ocean Bank succeeds.
We've a better method to raise
funds from shareholders.
President Fung, it's for you
I told you I won't take any calls.
It was the same man as last time.
Jimmy.
Sorry.
You lied, you've reported
us to the police.
Don't misunderstand.
We didn't...
Stop acting.
We knew you'd call the police.
I knew we couldn't stop you
from doing that.
If you still think it pays to pay
$20 million.
Publish an advertisement in
a best-selling paper...
...in the name of your group
tomorrow afternoon.
Broadcast it once again.
Where did the call come from?
It can't be traced, maybe a
remodelled radiophone.
We knew you'd call the police.
I knew we couldn't stop
you from doing that.
We'll show you our power
tomorrow noon.
We won't waste any more time
bargaining with you.
Don't worry,
they're only threatening.
We've sent more men to your premises.
It's going to be alright.
Listen, we can't let them
cause any more chaos.
Yes, sir.
Honestly, I didn't rat on you.
You didn't, eh?
The cops came after they got you.
They wouldn't let you go
if you hadn't squealed.
It's a simply lack of evidence.
I didn't squeal on you.
Anyway, we're not afraid of you.
Where now?
You've no choice.
Miss Wong, what's the matter
The letters have been examined.
Thanks.
Flowers for you.
Plant this and we're even.
You've no choice.
Hold it tight.
Where shall I put it?
You'll see later.
Start the car.
Roger, keep the alert going.
Police, what's this?
What's that?
Nothing
Nothing.
Sorry. CID. May I take a look?
I'm CID. Show me your bag.
Looking into the red bag.
Sir, I'm CID.
Come back now.
Seems like no problem.
These letters have been examined.
Roger.
Could it be a bluff?
I hope so.
But it's better to be cautious.
Good, keep in touch.
Tell him to wait.
Roger.
May is downstairs.
She has something to tell you.
Thanks.
What's it, May?
This letter's for you.
I must leave.
You brought me down just for this?
It's important. Keep it safe.
Where's your motorcycle?
As the bike and I are incompatible,
I sold it.
I'll follow that girl.
I've got everything prepared
Relax. It's only a bluff.
We depend entirely on the police
Ok.
What happened?
How come?
Find out what's happening!
At once!
Let's all keep calm.
Ka-Kui, let's go down and
take a look!
Get someone to investigate!
Yes sir!
Bring a fire extinguisher!
Help put out the fire!
Quickly!
Has the ambulance arrived?
Call them at once.
Get more men to help!
A call from President Fung.
Uncle Bill,
a call from the developers.
Ka-Kui, I'll go and deal with it,
you follow.
What's wrong with you people?
What happened?
The President's secretary
got her arm blown off.
How's the secretary now?
Surgery went smoothly.
The doc says there's a 95% chance.
Her facial wound was covered
using skin from her leg.
We'll know the result later.
They've now decided to pay.
What am I suppose to tell Raymond?
We've no choice, Uncle Bill.
Obstacles are inevitable in anything.
Remember, we're facing real bandits.
I'd rather be blown up myself...
...to save the lives
of everybody else.
Don't worry,
I've deployed everything.
If one of them comes to collect,
we'll nab him.
Raymond would complain
if I told him about this.
No point
in saying anything right now.
Sir
They want to pay. How am I to
tell my superiors?
No way, we've no choice.
Obstacles are inevitable in anything.
Remember, we're facing real bandits.
I would rather be blown up myself.
To save the lives of everybody else.
Don't worry,
I've deployed everything.
If he comes to collect,
we'll handcuff him.
All words, no action.
This is bad,
Raymond's going to be in trouble.
We don't want that to
happen either.
In fact,
frustrations are inevitable.
Remember, we're facing real bandits.
I'd rather be blown up myself.
So that no one else will suffer.
But don't worry.
If they dare try to collect,
I'll arrest them.
I understand your situation,
and I'll report it accordingly.
I hope you'll solve it quickly.
Come with me.
Why are you depressed?
Quarreled with Ka-Kui again?
It won't, it won't happen anymore.
Wait.
Hold it.
An important call for you.
Put it through.
Ka-Kui.
Yes.
May was abducted.
When was that?
When we returned from
the supermarket.
Do you know who did it?
No, it could be your enemies.
Those ruffians again?
Chu Tao!
Ka-Kui
Ka-Kui, what happened?
You don't need to know.
I going after a real scumbag.
Ka-Kui
What's he doing?
He left without saying a word.
Don't die yet, sign it first
Our henchmen...
Don't, sir, he's a patient.
Let me finish first.
Our men deserve credit for
what they did.
Are you taking the money
into your coffin?
Chu Tao!
Hand May over to me!
I didn't know he did this!
I didn't do anything!
Hand May over to me now!
That's no way
to treat a patient, sir!
Where are you hiding May?
Speak up.
I didn't do it.
Who did it then?
I told him to get out.
I'm now sick and poor.
How can I make fun of you now?
Any money he has.
He's spend it on treatment.
It's no concern of ours.
He dictated everything.
We got paid, that's all.
Who is it?
There's a phone over there.
Answer it.
Old man, don't die,
sign this first.
Is there be anything more between us?
I couldn't care less,
he's dying.
Maybe there would be,
if he was still alive.
Who's calling 1478?
Ka-kui.
May.
You can recognise her voice.
Come immediately to
Hung Fung Industrial Building.
Who are you? What do you want?
Come alone, or be ready to
collect her body.
Sun Fa Road
May, are you alright?
Don't yell.
Are you alright?
Yes.
Why have you taken her hostage?
Ka-Kui, when you read this letter,
I've decided to leave you.
Please don't read it.
I won't see you any more.
A love letter.
One loses weight if her
lover leaves her.
There's more, listen.
You scum!
At first I thought you were sincere.
And I could put my life
in your hands.
Now I can't stand your
excessive passion for your work.
I asked myself:
Why has the reason for my loving you...
...turned into reason for leaving you?
How would we part over
something trivial?
You said you wouldn't
involve me in your work.
But I don't mind.
I only mind that you have no
time to spend with me.
I'm happiest in your company
But waiting alone,
without seeing you.
Becomes the cruelest thing
in the world.
This is your fault.
It means, if I didn't leave you,
I'd be waiting for you all my life.
Don't read any more.
She's crying.
Cry!
Go on.
Because you are a policeman
who never relaxes
You're a policeman
who never relaxes?
We're in trouble then.
Leaving you means suffering
once and for all.
Please forgive my selfish decision,
May.
What do you want?
Nothing but your help
to make us rich.
You know we're blackmailing the group.
Collection is always the
hardest part of a blackmail.
So I need your help to
collect for us.
Stop dreaming.
You've no choice.
He won't help us to collect.
Inflict the Thunder Palm on him.
Stop!
Don't!
Don't, I beg you.
Stop!
Don't!
Ka-kui, are you alright?
Yes.
Acting like a hero!
It'll be your turn next.
Stop!
Get the car in right position.
You son-of-a-bitch!
Well done, Dumby!
Kill me if you have the guts
You can bear it.
Is that so? Let me see how
his girl friend does.
What are you doing?
Can you stand it?
Stop!
Are you going to do it?
Speak up!
Let her go,
I'll do anything for you.
You'd do anything for her?
We can't set her free.
What do you want?
Collect the money for us
and we'll release her.
You've no other choice.
Ok!
Splendid!
Don't try to get out
of your clothes.
Break one wire and it explodes.
The same thing happens
if I press this button.
Be careful now.
Ka-Kui
Take care!
I'll come back!
What now?
- We've got something!
- Check the source of the call
I'll go and find Uncle Bill!
Is the money ready?
I'll get someone to collect
it in 10 minutes.
It's ready!
Notify the police!
We didn't!
Where's Ka-kui?
I can't find him.
Impossible. How could he be
so irresponsible?
I won't wait.
Listen, don't move unless
you're 100% sure!
Stand by to move!
Yes, sir!
The trip takes 15 minutes.
Just in time.
Don't play dirty jokes!
If you don't get the money here,
the bombs on you will blow up.
We'll wait here for you.
Go now.
Good luck!
Sir, you...
We're here to investigate a case.
The Chief is looking for...
Ka-Kui!
Ka-Kui?
Ka-Kui, what are you doing?
Keep away!
Keep away! Don't get in my way!
Don't get in my way!
Ka-kui!
Sir, you...
Ka-Kui!
Ka-Kui, where have you been?
Never mind, I'm here to
collect the money.
Collect the money?
Your men?
Men?
Ka-Kui, are you alright?
Time's running out.
Where's the money?
What are you doing?
Ka-Kui
I'll do my duty if you move.
Don't shoot!
Raymond, don't!
I'll shoot!
Shoot, and you and
Uncle Bill will die!
You'll all die!
Break a wire and
my body explodes!
Ka-Kui, what on earth has happened?
Calm down, let's team up
and deal with it.
If I can't get out in 10
minutes, it will explode!
Don't follow him!
You go back first!
Listen, don't stop Ka-Kui
when you see him.
He's back!
Right!
He seems to be followed!
Let's go!
Start the car!
Get him over!
Give me the case!
I'll come back after I shake
off the CID.
Believe me!
The cops are following?
Stop there. Don't come over!
Why are you stopping here?
What's up? What are you up to?
What the hell!
A bomb's exploding. Run!
A bomb. Run!
The cops are following?
Trying to fool us! Blow
him to bits first!
And the money too?
Radio signals go dead in the tunnel!
What then?
Anyway, we've the girl!
Lets go back first!
So you'll wait him!
Kill her if something goes wrong.
May!
The car's back!
He dare not play any tricks.
May!
Quiet!
Freeze, you're under arrest!
Why are you arresting me?
Come over here!
Don't be foolish!
I'll shoot you down!
Can you shoot so fast?
One shot to kill three!
Think it over. A few years inside
And you can start over!
Sure, we'd like to try your way,
But, those would be our best years!
Don't force me to shoot!
Don't shoot.
There are explosives all around.
May!
I'm here!
You're alright, aren't you?
Ka-Kui, take care!
Good job, Dumby!
Come up here!
There's a conveyor belt.
Don't touch it! It's dangerous.
Go!
It's so high up here!
High enough for you to jump.
What's happened to you?
May, go as far as you can!
Take care!
Papa! Papa!
Beat you up! Papa!
Papa, papa, still calling for Papa!
Papa, papa. Mama to you!
Papa!
Papa, Papa, Mama to you!
Papa? Mama?
Papa?
Goddamn!
Ka-Kui!
Stop crying!
Look at the beautiful fireworks!