Oh, shit.
Duffy split.
Yeah, wasn't that Duffy?
Duffy rolls outta here
in a brand new Cadillac.
The lad has the nerve to ask me
to clean up his fucking locker
and save it for him.
Probably has dirty
pictures of his wife.
I don't know what
the fuck is in here.
Uh-huh.
He does have dirty
pictures of his wife.
Yes. He does.
Lucky man.
Look at her hooters.
You like that, huh?
All right. This is
what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna keep them.
Well, no, I gotta
answer to Duffy
for that.
I'll answer to him.
He is a duffus but
he's not a bad guy.
Fuck Duffy.
Just fuck him.
Fuck all of them.
Five copies of
an arrest report.
If the prisoner was
transported, there wouldn't
still be five copies here.
Duffy might've left him
downstairs. What's his
name? Chavez.
Let's go find him.
[door bangs]
Who's there?
It's strange, 'cause
the manifest says the
prisoners all evacuated.
Anything's possible
in this storm.
I feel a bet coming on.
Shall we open the casino?
Please.
All right.
Up to his
nose by 4:00.
What the fuck
took you so
long, man? Please.
Please what, shitbird?
Get me the fuck
outta here, man.
The water's rising.
It's been rising for like
three hours. It's already
up to my neck.
I'm not gonna be able to stay
here long, man. I'll drown.
The water doesn't stop.
Get me the fuck outta here.
There's fucking snakes and
shit in this water.
Twenty bucks
and the Polaroid he
says nothing before five.
Twenty bucks. What the fuck
is that? Let's make it worth
our while, at least. A dime.
I'm not betting
you $1,000.
Five hundred.
Get me the fuck
outta here, man!
The water keeps rising.
Two hundred
and the Polaroids.
Please, motherfuckers.
Please what, shit turd?
Got a broke leg.
Please, get me
out of here.
Wait a minute.
You want me to get
wet on account of you?
Think the world
owes you a living, huh?
I'll drown.
Hey, man, I got on
Swiss cotton underpants.
Yeah, that's right.
Cost me $55 a pair.
You think I wanna get
all this brown water
and shit all over?
That don't come out.
You got underwear on
that cost $55?
My girl gave them to me.
[mumbles]
Come on, we get
the time of death
from autopsy.
What are you doing?
Hold this.
Oh, come on, man.
Let the Fire Department
get him out. What
are you, crazy?
He ain't worth it!
Come on, man.
[laughing]
You are crazy.
[laughs]
[voice echoing]
You okay, man?
You okay?
The good news, Terence,
is I'll okay you to return
to full duty.
The bad news is
that in all likely
you'll be experiencing
moderate to severe
back pain.
How severe?
You'll wanna be taking
something for it.
Gonna write you a
prescription for Vicodin.
For how long?
From now on.
No. For how long
am I gonna have pain?
We're gonna try to manage
this as along as we can.
For the rest
of my life?
Probably. But they're
making advancements
every day, so,
just work with me
on this, all right?
Now, when this runs
out, call the office.
[applauses]
Thank you for
helping me honor
our fallen heroes today.
We will now move on
to the awards
and promotions.
Among those
being promoted
to lieutenant today,
it gives me
great pleasure
to additionally award
the Distinguish
Service Cross
to Sergeant
now Lieutenant
Terence McDonagh,
in recognition
of extreme valor
in the line of duty.
Congratulations, Lieutenant.
[applauses]
[Police radio chatter]
There's three more.
You don't wanna look.
It's execution style.
What did you
come up with?
Scale in the closet,
bundle of glass
in envelopes.
Dob been around?
I thought he went away.
He's out.
I saw him
the other day.
Let's get him in.
His baby mama is over
by General Taylor
and Annunciation.
You have informers
doing the canvass?
The duty captain
sent them out.
Whoever they talk to,
I want followed up by
a member of the squad.
You'll see to that
personally, Armand.
Are they pulling
security cameras?
Yeah.
Every license plate
in the area.
Got it.
My Friend
by Babacar Ndele.
«My friend is a fish.
«He live in my room.
«His fin is a cloud.
He see me
when I sleep.»
Couple's name: Dauta
and Yasin Ndele.
Dauta's mother's name:
Ramatullai Ndele.
Children's names:
Animata and Babacar.
Family's from Senegal.
Immigration status: illegal.
From what we know,
Dauta had been dealing
heroin to supplement his
income as a peddler.
Now, I want
every drug dealer,
every junkie within
a five-mile radius
hassled into giving up
who his supplier was.
Due to the nature
of this crime,
you've got full
authorization for
overtime if you need it.
Lieutenant McDonagh's
gonna be heading up
the investigation,
so coordinate with him.
That's it.
Let's see
some results.
McDonagh, see you
in my office
for a minute.
You up to this?
Why wouldn't I be?
I know you're still
having problems
with your back.
Dealing with being
in pain a lot
of the time.
I'm managing.
You still taking
medication for it?
Only what
the doctor prescribes.
Ordinarily there'd be
somebody with more
time on the job
handling this kind
of investigation.
But I'm gonna go out
on a limb with you 'cause
you got good instincts
and do nothing'
but work.
But if I find
that you needed help
and didn't ask for it,
I will be mad.
Yes, Sir.
How is your
old man doing?
He's drinking himself
into an early grave.
Give him my best,
would you?
I will.
Lieutenant, no more
unnecessary jumps, huh?
Yes, Sir.
Good morning,
Mr. McDonagh.
Hi, honey.
You bring me something?
You're out already?
Yes.
[telephone rings]
Mm.
[man on answering machine]
Frankie, hi. This is Andy.
Hey, hey, hey!
Hoping to see if you
have any time tonight.
I'm at the Monteleone.
You need to call him back?
No.
You know I'd rather go
to the Monteleone with you.
I can't afford it.
I can.
I can afford it.
[cell phone rings]
Yeah?
Who brought him in?
That's who's
questioning him?
I'll be there in ten
minutes. Tell him
I'm on my way.
Tell him if he puts his
hands on this guy, he's
gonna have a problem.
I don't give a shit, Armand.
You tell him to take
a fucking break!
Excuse me. Could you
tell me how much longer
that's gonna be?
Hello, Miss?
I'm a Lieutenant
in the Police Department.
I'm in the middle of
a homicide investigation.
Can I get my
prescription, please?
Do you see
I'm on the phone?
Hey, you can't
come back here.
You got me waiting 40 minutes
so you can make a fuck
personal phone call!
Security. Security
to Pharmacy. Security
to Pharmacy, please.
This is it.
Police emergency.
You're no cop.
What's that look like?
Why are you acting
all crazy for?
This is, uh, $23
with my copay, right?
There's 40. Give
everybody a drink.
Get the fuck
out of my way.
(detective)
Dob, look at me.
Okay?
Two hours.
That's enough.
Tell me something
I don't know.
Man, you gotta
get me outta here.
Get you outta here?
Are you crazy?
I got you on possession.
You're on parole.
Maybe but one
skinny ass joint.
That joint's gonna
get you back.
I've got five
dead people, man.
You understand?
I don't know
nothin' about it.
Tell me something.
What do you
want me to tell you?
I want you to tell me
something I haven't heard.
I don't want you to tell me,
look at me, I don't
want you to tell me
that you don't know nothing.
But I don't know nothing.
Did you tell him
what I said?
You understand
what that means?
I'm entitled to whatever
I want in this room.
That means Guantanamo
Bay. You believe
this motherfucker?
I've busted my ass
for yambos and this
yambo tell me shit.
Detective, can I see you
outside for a second?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Two minutes.
Think about it.
Uh, not a great time
to take a break.
What are you doing?
He's about to go.
Bullshit.
He's scared out
of his mind.
You and your partner made
a spectacle out of
picking him up.
Everyone in Central City
knows he's in here.
No, just shush.
You think he's gonna go out
if you keep insulting him
like that?
You trying to tell me
how to do my interrogation?
Yes. I'm gonna tell you
when you're doing
something wrong.
Go fuck yourself
I'm gonna treat
you respectfully.
You treat me respectfully.
I'm looking at some bullshit
pot busting. Because
you're on parole
you wind up back
in Angola. Why
would you do that?
I ain't the one
doing it.
Who did have
Kingard piss off?
I never said two
words to him.
I don't know.
But you knew he
was selling dope.
Come on.
Shall I call your parole
officer? Stop wasting
my time.
I knew he was selling.
Okay. Tell me
where he was selling,
whose neighborhood was it.
Man, look. I got
me a good job at
a cleaning service.
I check in when
I'm supposed to.
I smoke a little
weed, but that's it.
Tell me whose
neighborhood it was, Dob.
Man.
You know Fate?
Big Fate? Yeah.
Ain't nothin' moved
that part of town.
He ain't got a piece of it.
Where can I find him?
Shit. I'm saying
all I know.
If you want me
to lead you to him,
you well just lock me up.
Check Stevie's arrest
report on Dob.
If it mentions marijuana,
make sure it gets lost.
What do I tell Stevie?
You can tell him
to go fuck himself.
I'm gonna go upstairs
and crash an hour
in the crib.
What do you want, Mundt?
Internal Affairs
is checking the
property room vouchers.
So?
That means they're
gonna find out
the shit missing.
Not if you don't
tell them, they won't.
I can't do it
anymore, Terence.
Oh, fuck.
I'm-I'm really sorry.
I just can't.
Mundt,
whatever drugs might've
been taken out of
the property room,
you will have a
voucher, you understand?
They won't turn up as missing,
'cause there's no record of
them being there
in the first
place, okay?
They're installing cameras.
So then you
don't do anything
where the cameras
can see you.
I can't.
When it was me doing
paperwork to cover the
cash you misplaced,
that was all right.
That was entirely
fucking reasonable.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Mundt.
Hey, Mundt?
[woman laughing]
[woman laughs]
You bad boy.
(woman)
Oh, yeah.
[moans]
Stand against the wall.
Come on! Stand
against the wall.
You're too busy
making out with
your girlfriend
you don't know
when you've done
something illegal?
What are we
hiding tonight?
Nothing.
You passed drugs
in that club?
No.
The two of you match a
description. Empty your
pockets and the handbag.
Why?
I said you match
a description.
Somebody seen
passing drugs.
I wasn't passing drugs.
What does that
even mean?
Empty your pockets.
Dump out the handbag. I'm
not gonna tell you again.
This is bullshit!
Just do what
he says, okay?
What you got there?
Nothing.
I'm not gonna
get stuck, am I?
No.
I get stuck, I'm
gonna be very
fucking angry.
You're not
gonna get stuck.
Where's your badge
if you're a cop?
This is what
I'm looking for.
Here's where it
says I'm a cop.
Sir, it-it's obviously
just for personal use.
I mean,
I'm not a dealer.
That's for
the DA to decide.
You're gonna
dump that bag
or I gotta do it?
Sir, is-is there any way
my parents don't have
to find out about this?
I mean, can we,
can we just
handle this?
I'll go to jail on weekends
or something like that if
I have to do that.
My father has a
heart condition, okay?
This would kill him.
Please. Just let me
keep this from him.
You think he want
might to know?
Yeah. I'd wanna know
if you were my child.
Here.
This fur is nothing,
but this is my
grandmother's.
It's worth $60,000.
You can give it
to your girlfriend.
If You don't have
a girlfriend,
you can give it
to your mother.
It's bribery.
Excuse me!
This is worth $60,000.
Doesn't that
get us passed?
Where's the rock?
Come on, come on,
who's got the kibble?
You wanna hit?
Yes.
Jesus Christ.
Again.
Yeah?
[whispers]
Are you fucking
kidding me?
[groans]
This what's
gonna take?
Yeah?
You're worried about
your father finding out?
No.
What about your mother?
I don't give a shit
about anyone of them.
Did they beat you?
No.
Molest you?
Didn't buy you
any clothes back
to school, huh?
Didn't see you in
the high school
play, huh?
I wonder what'd they
say if they saw you now.
Smokin' crack.
[groans]
Going out with
no panties on?
No pain?
[moans]
I bet they think about
you when you were
a little girl.
What the hell
happened to ya?
Don't fucking move!
You stay and watch!
You watch her! Watch
your fucking girlfriend.
[train whistling]
Fuck!
I need the coke back.
What happened?
I snorted what I thought
was coke. It turned out
to be heroin.
I gotta be at
work in a hour.
Oh, baby, okay.
I'm not alone.
Just get the coke.
I'll get out of here.
You didn't break it
out for your client?
Nah. He brings his own.
Uh-huh.
Who are you?
I'm the last person
in the world you
want me to be.
He's just
an old friend.
Come on, missy,
we've had you under
surveillance for weeks.
Do you have any illegal
substances on you?
Like what?
Asshole.
Cooperate with me,
I'll let you walk
outta here.
You play games,
come with her.
I got some coke.
Get it.
Get out.
[laughs]
That was fun.
Hey.
[both laugh]
Come. Come!
Are you a policeman?
Yes.
Do you know
who do this?
I don't know, yet.
Look here.
This dead.
Babacar.
This little girl,
no more.
He's dead, dead.
Older man.
Oh, my angel,
she's dead. All
my whole family.
How are you related?
Yasin. She were
my sister.
When was the last
time you saw her?
I see her dat morning.
I go by in case she
need anything.
But dat morning
she says she needs
something from the grocery,
and she called there
and had it delivered
by a boy to her home.
Help me, please.
Please, help me find
the killer of my family.
Please, sir.
Help me. Help.
Are you the manager?
No, sir.
The manager's
over there.
New Orleans Homicide.
You got people making
deliveries here?
We get different guys making
deliveries. Different days,
different guys.
What about Tuesday?
Different times a day.
Different guys.
Late afternoon.
We don't keep track
of who takes what
to who.
A delivery boy
hasn't shown up
in a while?
Excuse us. Hello!
Police Department.
We're looking
for Binnie Rogers.
I'm Binnie Rogers.
We need to talk to you
for a second. Do you mind
stepping in the hall?
No, I can't step
into the hall.
Can't you see this
lady needs me here?
We're looking for your
grandson, Miss Rogers.
What are you
looking for him for?
Just to talk.
We just wanna
talk to him.
He do somethin' wrong?
He might've been
a witness to a crime.
I don't know
anything about that.
Where can we find him?
Young man, what do you
think gives you the right
to come into my room
and have a conversation
without even acknowledging
my presence?
We're terribly sorry.
It's very important
we talk to this
woman's grandson.
And she told you
she doesn't know
where he is.
Actually, she hasn't
told us that.
I don't know.
I'm sorry, Grandma.
What do you
wanna know?
Did you make a delivery
Tuesday on Josephine
and Danneel, son?
Uh-huh.
What did you see there?
This is a 15-year
old boy, sir.
We need you to tell us
what you saw, Daryl.
He don't get involved
in drugs, in gangs.
He go to school.
He hold down a job
and he come home.
A family was
murdered, ma'am.
And I feel very
bad about that.
But I don't want my
grandson involved in it.
Maybe your grandson has
some feelings of his own.
Well,
the lady told me
to set the grocery
bags in the kitchen.
Uh, as I was setting
the grocery bags down,
I heard screaming.
And I heard gunshots.
So I hid in the closet.
When I came out,
everybody was dead.
Did you see
who shot them?
Say yes or no.
This is who we're
looking for. Name
is Donald Godshaw.
Street name «Big Fate».
You should familiarize
yourself with his record.
It goes back
to '91. Did time
for rape, sodomy,
aggravated assault,
narcotics, and possession
of automatic weapons.
We believe he's also behind
at least three homicides
including the Ndele family.
Lieutenant, wanna show
some of those victims?
All three were
possible witnesses.
Godshaw has two flunkies
that he runs with.
Deshaun Hackett,
street name «Midget».
Has a girlfriend on Burgundy
and Mazant. We'll set up
surveillance on the block.
Maybe we'll get
lucky he'll turn up.
Gary Jenkins,
street name «G.»
His grandmother lives
in the Iberville Projects.
If his laying low
chances are, that's
where we'll find him.
Let's bring him in.
Give me a minute.
I need access to the
apartment next door.
Do you mind?
Oh! It's okay, baby.
[laughs]
Why you need
access for?
We had complaints
about disturbance,
not answering the door.
[baby cries]
[dog barks]
Don't fucking breathe.
I love it.
[laughs]
I just love it.
I've told you
everything I know.
This is your
lucky day, son.
You're the first person
we've picked up. You're in
a position to help yourself.
Help myself do what?
You know something
about this family
that got murdered.
I don't know nothing.
You were in the apartment when
the Africans got shot. Who was
with you? Midget Donald?
Donald Godshaw,
«Big Fate». Where is he?
Where can we find him?
I don't know
no «Big Fate».
We don't need you no
more. There's gonna
be five homicides
and Donald's gonna
hand them on you.
He gets eight to ten.
You get for life.
I don't know nobody
named «Midget».
named «Big Fate».
Renaldo Hayes!
Oh. Man!
That's bad luck.
I keep hope that once
in a while this kid throws
to somebody on his own team.
I love the guy. By the end
of the fucking game, I'm
starting to hate him.
What do you want
for the weekend?
What's the spread on
Louisiana-Arkansas?
Four.
Louisiana.
Minus to four
for a dime.
You got it. I got
a favor to ask.
My kid got
a speeding ticket.
I'll take care if you
give me half a point.
You're gonna grind me
for helping out
my kid?
Grind you?
You're funny guy,
you know that?
There's guys getting half
a point on the street
for nothing. Grind you.
All right.
But you take
care of it.
Hello. Hello!
I'm Lieutenant McDonagh,
New Orleans Homicide.
What can I do for you?
A friend of mine's daughter
got written up for speeding.
She was doing 75
on the way to the hospital
to visit her grandmother.
Has a couple of minor,
minor violations
in the past.
She's in danger
of losing her license.
What do you
want me to do?
I'd like you to take
care of it for me.
You come to the scene
of an accident to
ask me that?
There shouldn't
be a problem.
Are you asking me to break
the law? Is that what
you're doing here?
I'm asking you
one cop to another
to do me a favor.
The answer's no.
Just like that?
Just like that.
Is this the same Police
Department my father was in?
You'll excuse me.
Great.
Guardian of the Flame,
right? Fucking ass.
Get back in you
car, Lieutenant.
Or else what?
Hey there.
Hey, what are
you doing here?
You know the Lieutenant?
Yeah. We used
to work together.
Why don't you walk him
back to his car?
I could've told you
not to bother with
that asshole.
You needed a ticket
fixed, why didn't
you come to me?
I didn't know
you worked here.
They only let me out
on patrol when they're
short handed.
Mostly they got me
in the property room.
Property room?
What are you
doing tonight?
You asking me out?
Yes, I am.
[laughs]
Hey.
You like these
boots, don't you?
Only on you,
you know that.
Yeah?
You're horny?
Oh, yeah.
No, you're not.
You're high on dope.
Not true.
Whatever I take
is prescription.
Except for the heroin.
Hey! Wake up, McDonagh.
Yeah, there's times
I can't get what I need
with the prescription.
Really?
Yeah. When my back
hurts sometimes.
Well, maybe there's
something I can do
to make that pain go away.
You definitely can.
What's that, baby?
What do you want me
to do for you?
Check out your
property room
and see if there's
any Oxycontin
or morphine
you can sneak
outta there.
Just make sure
you get rid of
the voucher copy.
You're nuts.
Hey.
The ticket's gonna be a
little more complicated
than I thought.
You're kidding me.
The best thing to do
is to have her plead
not guilty.
By the time a court day
comes around, I'll talk to
the cop who wrote her up.
I thought that's what
you were gonna do.
I went straight
to the Lieutenant.
He wound up being
a hard on.
It'll work out.
It's just gonna take
a little longer. Come on.
Kinda calls into question the
half-a-point-for-nothing
concept, don't you think?
You're some cheap
prick, you know that?
You say you're gonna
do something and you
don't do it.
Good! Charge me
for the half point.
And after last weekend,
you're down $3,000.
You might,
I mean, might
have thought to bring me
a little something.
Two dimes!
On Louisiana
against Georgia.
Okay, you got it.
[flushes toilet]
How long has he
been in there?
About 20 minutes.
Who else?
His girlfriend.
At least one. That's
as far as we know.
What are these fucking
iguanas doing on my
coffee table?
There ain't no iguana.
Yeah, there are.
What the fuck is that?
Fucking iguana.
Are we set up?
SWAT's around
the corner.
No! No, just,
just no SWAT.
Let them stay there.
The duty captain said
he wanted to coordinate
with us when we--
Is that what you're fucking
doing now? Reporting back
to the duty captain?
I'm telling you
what he said.
If we need SWAT,
we'll call 'em.
Let's go.
Who else is in here?
Nobody.
We're gonna come back
every day, you understand?
More times we come back,
more chances that child
getting shot.
Ain't nobody here.
[whispers]
He's hiding back
there in the armoire.
You all stay
with her. Armand.
Get up.
I said get up!
Damn, man.
It's always nice to see
an intact family.
A father who honors
his obligations
as far as his
children are a concern.
You're here.
That's important thing.
You may be hiding in
an armoire, but your
child knows you're here.
Are you tripping, man?
Armand, give us
a minute.
You're tripping.
You want that shit.
Shut the door.
Shut up. Shut
the door.
Sit down.
Sit down, sit down.
[exhales]
Now we can talk.
You don't mind
if I light one
up, do you?
Fuck, man.
I find it relaxes me.
What the fuck, man?
You know we got
your boy, «G.»
Right?
Man, I don't know no «G.»
He knows you.
It's amazing how much
you can get done
when you've got
a simple purpose
guiding through life.
My purpose is
to find out
who shot up this
apartment on Josephine.
I know the guy who
was living there
was from Senegal.
I know he was
selling heroin.
I know whose territory
he was stepping on.
And I know who went
over to the apartment
to straighten him out.
I found out all that
in the past few days.
Where is
«Big Fate», son?
I don't know
no «Big Fate».
You see, I know
that's not true.
'Cause everybody who comes
from where you come, knows
who «Big Fate» is.
The fact that you're lying
to me, tells me you're
hiding something.
You know my only reason for
being here is to find out
who shot up the apartment.
I know that's what
you're hiding.
See? It all,
all comes back
to that same
simple purpose.
Man, I ain't
telling you shit.
[dog barks]
Hey.
What's wrong?
Your father's mad at me
'cause I can't take care
of his fucking dog.
Why does he need you
to take care of it?
'Cause he's going
back into AA.
He says he can't
do with any more
responsibilities.
Besides that he,
he's gotta stop drinking.
I mean, ain't like
I don't wanna take
care of it,
but I leave at 7:00
in the morning
to go to work!
Oh, let me
talk to him.
I try to be a good
wife to him, Terence.
I do. But you know,
I got a limit, too.
You know, he's got a
drinking problem. He says
he's got a drinking problem.
He wants to so something
about it. That's good.
You know, he's been
down this road before
and it didn't take.
He wants to
try it again.
Good!
But I, I say to him,
why don't you just take
the beer the way that I do,
but he says
he can't do that.
Hey, Pop.
How are you doing?
I thought you said
the meeting was at seven.
I gotta get there early.
Set up the chairs.
I'll take you.
She can do it.
I came over to see you.
Let me take you for
a ride, at least.
You feed the dog?
I can take
care of him.
What are you
talking about?
Genevieve told me
a little about what's
going on.
I'll take the dog
off your hands
for a while.
How are you gonna
take care of a dog?
I got a friend.
She just loves animals.
All of them. Dogs, too.
Let's go.
[dog barks]
Have a good time!
No. No!
Fuck you.
Did we not discuss
this on the phone?
How come you only
call me when you
need something?
You're fucked up,
aren't you?
What? Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fucked up.
What are you doing?
I'm going to work.
I have to go to
Biloxy tonight.
Go to the hotel casino.
How are you gonna
take care of the dog
if you're fucked up
and you're going
to Biloxy?
All right. The doorman's
gonna walk him in
the morning
and I get back
in the afternoon.
Oh, he's sweet.
What's his name?
I don't know.
You don't know
his name?
I'll ask my father.
You are unbelievable.
I gotta get going.
Unbelievable.
You don't know.
Baby, be nice to me.
He smells.
You need a bath.
Try to understand.
It doesn't matter that you
were just along for the ride.
It doesn't matter that
you didn't actually
shoot anybody.
You're playing the prices now.
The price of «Big Fate»
getting off,
it's gonna help the DA
convict you and
your boy «G.»
I guarantee you that's
just what he's gonna do.
Why don't you
smoke, man?
What are you
talking about?
I gotta listen
all this bullshit.
Break out
to smoke, man.
Flipping out on us?
No, man.
Your partner lit up
a motherfucker blunt
before he put
the cuffs on me.
I love this guy.
[laughs]
You say I smoked
marijuana in your
presence? Huh?
Cannabis? Is that
what you're saying?
Right. Your word
against mine,
so they fuck won't
believe me, right?
(detective)
Lieutenant.
Lieutenant, can you
step out for a moment?
My name is
Eugene Gratz, Lieutenant.
I'm an attorney.
This is my client
Donald Godshaw.
I understand you've
been looking for him.
[Godshaw laughs]
How can I help you?
I just wanna talk
to these guys
for a second.
Why don't you
wait there?
Gentlemen.
Can I get you
a glass of water?
Um, no, thanks.
I gotta turn over the
names of my witnesses
to Godshaw's lawyer.
As soon as I do that,
Godshaw will look
to scare the kid.
He can't scare him,
he'll kill him.
He'll never get to him.
Since Godshaw
turned himself in,
I've authorized
24-hour protection
to start immediately.
Just remember,
we have no prints,
no DNA, no weapon.
We lose the kid,
we lose the case.
Understood?
[siren wailing]
He's a nice dogs.
I just can't keep him.
She said she'd
be back at 1:00
this afternoon.
I'm off at 4:00,
and I got another
job I gotta be at.
She didn't call?
No. And the night guy ain't
gonna go walk him.
I can't leave the animal
in her apartment. It
might do damage.
How did you
get my number?
Miss Frankie
gave it to me
in case of emergencies.
Emergencies?
This is what I'm talking
about. Doesn't pick up
the phone.
She isn't where she's
supposed to be. Not
showing up.
Terence, think they're
gonna put me on the witness
stand by May 15?
Don't know, why?
So my mom goes
for the parole board.
I'm sure we can get
people to put in a
good word for her.
[cell phone rings]
Hello?
Where are you?
I'm about an
hour from there.
I'm on my way.
Frankie, I'm on my way.
You ever been
to Biloxy?
Now, you stand there.
Don't move.
I'll be back
in five minutes.
Baby.
Hi, baby.
What are you doing?
You all right?
Yeah.
You okay?
Who did it?
Do you have
anything for me?
Some coke.
That's it?
And Vicodin.
I'll take both.
What the fuck is
going on in here?
[door closes]
Who's this?
Hey, hey, hey!
Take it easy.
(Frankie)
Just get my money.
What are you,
jealous boyfriend?
Just get me
my money.
I'm using to paying
when I'm done.
Done smacking her around?
It was erotic shit, man.
I didn't hurt her.
Didn't that hurt?
Did I hurt you?
Terence, let's just go.
We don't hit
women down south.
You just made
a big mistake.
My father is Andy Winnick,
you ever hear of him?
One of the biggest
developers in the
gulf coast.
Congratulations.
Tommy Leonardi is one
of his best friends.
Listen, scumbag. Don't try
to impress me with you-father
knows-some-guinea hood.
What you gotta take away from
this experience is that if
you ever see that girl again,
you turn around
and you walk in the opposite
direction. You got that?
Yeah, man.
So much looking
at that girl,
you're gonna wish you
were born without a dick.
Oh! Whoa, whoa,
whoa. Oh, whoa.
Whoa. Big mistake.
Oh, yeah.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Big mistake.
[laughs]
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
[whispers]
Whoa.
Oh, yeah.
Daryl, this is Frankie.
Frankie, Daryl.
Hi, Daryl.
Hi.
I gotta go talk
to someone.
You go ahead
and take Frankie
to the coffee shop.
And you stay with her.
You can do that, right?
Yeah.
Do you have
to do that now?
I'll be with you
in a minute.
Let's go?
Take care of me.
How'd Louisiana
go off that?
Three-point underdogs.
What are they losing by?
Eight.
Eight? What
the fuck is that?
There's still two
minutes left to play.
Louisiana ain't got
this passing game.
Good point.
You wanna get my picks
for the Pac-10?
Do I look like
I wanna hear 'em?
Where is the kid?
He went to the bathroom.
Hi. Are there any
other bathrooms
beside that one?
Yeah, on the other side.
[voice from machine]
Hey, man, insert
more coins.
Insert more coins.
Play again.
What's going on?
What did he say
when he left?
He asked me if I'd be
okay waiting here
by myself.
I said yeah. He said he
had to go to the bathroom.
What is going on?
He's a witness
to a homicide.
To what?
To five homicides.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
To find him.
Where is he?
Binnie, call security.
Nobody's calling anybody.
Where's your
grandson, Binnie?
I don't have
to tell you anything.
Yeah, you do.
I haven't done anything.
My grandson hasn't
done anything.
If he doesn't wanna be
a witness, he doesn't
have to be a witness.
This is bigger
than one, two.
This was a massacre.
Children
were executed.
Maybe you should've
thought of that before.
I need to know
where he is.
Young man, I would like
to know the name
of your superior.
Right now I'm working
on about an hour
and a half sleep
over the past
three days.
And I'm still trying
to remain courteous.
And I'm beginning to think
that that's getting in the
way of my being effective.
What are you doing?
What--what
are you doing?
I wanna know
where Daryl is.
My God.
Nobody saw me
come in. Nobody
knows I'm here.
This old woman's
gonna run out of air,
and you're gonna have
a tough time convincing
people that it wasn't you
who did it to her.
And even if, and even
if you do convince them
that you didn't
kill her on purpose,
you're still gonna have
a tough time selling
them that you
took care of her
with a fuck!
Now, listen to me.
Where the fuck is he?
I said where
the fuck is he?
He's on an airplane.
Miss Antoinette
bought him a ticket
and send him to live
with her family in England.
[whimpers]
All right, it's okay.
That's okay. That's a
good girl. Suck it up.
There you go. That's it.
Take it in. That's a
good girl. Take it in.
Good! Good.
Good.
That's it. Breathe.
Maybe you should drop
dead, you selfish cunt.
You ever think
about your kids or
your grandkids? Huh?
Sucking up their inheritance
through that fucked
oxygen tube?
And Binnie's fucked
intensive care?
You fucks, I hate you.
I hate you both.
I should, I should
fucking both,
right now,
I should fucking
kill you fucking both.
You're the fucking reason
this country's going
down the drain.
Watch out. He's not
in a good mood.
Come in.
Have a seat.
Scotland Yard called.
The kid's in England.
Make him a material witness.
Maybe Scotland Yard
will hold him.
Can't do that. He had no
involvement with the crime.
He don't want testify,
we can't compel him.
Well, we could still
try flipping one
of the three.
You can try
all what you want.
Nobody flipping
on Godshaw. They're
scared to death of him.
As of now, all are
persons of interest.
You gotta let him go.
Oh, come on!
Five homicides and
you're letting him go?
You weren't supposed to let
the kid out of your sight.
Be glad he didn't
turn out dead.
This is bullshit.
Get the hell outta here.
You're not the one
on the street-—
Get out of my office.
Risking our lives
on the street!
You know what's
involved, right?
Maybe if we get a prosecutor
worry about something, we
could stand a fucking chance.
What happened when
you went to see
the grandmother?
I told you.
She said the woman she takes
care of, bought a plane ticket.
He was on his way to England
to stay with
her relatives.
Any incidents took
place over there?
What kind of incidents?
Any kind.
No.
Whatever it is,
you're gonna have
your story down.
Public Integrity is
waiting for you
back at the house.
Oh, come on. Public
Integrity into this?
What for?
That old woman,
her son is a United
States congressman.
I asked where
Daryl was.
His grandmother told me.
You didn't, at any time,
threaten his grandmother?
No, I did not.
You didn't, at
any time, threaten
Antoinette Fahringer?
No, I did not.
You should know a formal
complaint's been filed
alleging you cut off
Mrs. Fahringer's
oxygen supply.
Who's saying that?
Mrs. Fahringer?
Is it true?
I think she might
be suffering from
a little dementia.
Lieutenant, we're
asking if it's true.
Absolutely not.
Lieutenant.
You know, I saw five
of those driving into
work this morning.
I want you
to clean it up.
Clean it up.
Ned, excellent.
You got my message.
Good. Come on.
What message?
You get the flowers
I sent? How's Jenny?
What the fuck are
you talking about?
Okay, that's good.
Stop it!
Cut it out.
What are you
doing here?
What do you think?
I don't have
anything for you.
Then this is
a problem.
Yeah, who
needs a problem?
You owe me
five large, Terence.
I haven't got it.
Then, you gotta
give me something.
Give me goods if
you don't have cash.
Give me a gold Rolex.
Ned, I look like
I got a gold Rolex?
Don't pine me for
a fucking stooge.
Keep your voice down.
Just keep it down.
Don't play me
for a fucking stooge.
Are you done?
Do you think these guys
care you're a cop? They
will fuck you up
just like
everybody else.
Let me get something
down with the Texas game.
'Cause that's where
the season turns a lot.
No.
Nothing. You pay
what the fuck you owe.
I'm a little late on
my rent, that's all.
Lieutenant.
Uh, somebody named
Frankie called.
What's going on?
All kinds of things.
Come closer. I'm Dave.
Who are you?
Andy.
Jeff.
What do you want?
What I want right now
is to get this behind
position right.
He wants money.
Who are you?
Sit down.
I told you,
I'm Dave.
And the guy you robbed,
I know told you he was.
You make a date
with a pretty girl.
You gotta pay.
Dear. Like this.
You want the schwantz,
not the prosty.
See? That's it.
When you engage with
another human being, we remind
ourselves we're not alone.
Plus, who knows,
maybe we even learn
a little something.
How much?
You took 10 off.
To make it right, you
gotta come up with 50.
No, that's bullshit.
No, it's punitive
damages. What can
I tell you?
I don't get it.
She kept up with
the bargain.
He says no.
He's a fucking liar.
I did everything he
asked me to do.
Which was what?
(Frankie)
You want details?
You sick people.
Oh, listen to her
stand up for herself.
The indignation.
I love it.
Where's the money?
In my bag.
It's all here?
Okay. Here are
five thousand.
There's ten
in change here.
Why don't I give you
this, call a day.
We could do that.
Alternatively, I could
tell Jeffy to shoot the dog.
Do you want me
to shoot the fucking dog?
Or put my calling card
on this gorgeous
punum here.
I don't give a shit
about the dog.
But you mark her up,
I'm gonna have a tough
time getting you your money.
By my money you
mean $50,000.
I'll need a
couple of days.
By a couple
you mean two.
Yeah.
Good.
[whispers]
Hey.
I know. Relax.
The boys wanna saddle her
up just in the spirit
of friendliness.
You mind?
Well, let her get
cleaned up, put on
something hot.
She looks like
shit right now.
Beautiful.
What are you
waiting for?
I don't wanna put
any pressure on you,
but she has a client
coming over in 15 minutes.
You boys can be
done by the, right?
The both of us?
They'd had been done
in 15 seconds you
hadn't mentioned it.
My mistake.
You'll hit her
when we come back.
Two days, same time,
same station, yes?
Okay. You got it, baby.
Don't make me look
for you, Terence.
They're gone.
I'm gonna take you
to my father's house.
Buy some time at least.
Frankie.
They're gone.
I can't take her.
I just need a place
where she can stay
for a couple of days.
Why can't you put her
up in your place?
I can't take a chance
these guys find out
where I live, Dad.
Christ!
They gave me the job
of bringing cookies
to a meeting.
It takes me half
a day to get it done.
You want me to
baby-sit a pros?
You don't have
to baby-sit her.
She's very
self-suficient.
Well, I'm not in any kind
of shape to take on
something like this.
Look, I get home
from one meeting.
I lie on the couch
and I wait till it's
time for the next meeting.
That's all I
can do right now.
Let your wife
deal with her.
They'll get along
like sisters.
Get away from me, you rag.
[grunting]
My husband is trying to quit
drinking and you bring this
shit into our house?
Give it back or I'll swear
to God I will stab you
in the heart.
I will stab you
What kind of trash
you're bringing
in here?
She's going
through my bag!
My personal shit!
Everybody calm down.
It's hard enough
for your father.
He's gotta put up
with narcotics under
his nose.
Oh, God. It can't be any
worse than you being shit
face on beer all the time.
Enough!
You tell her I'm
shit face all the time?
Oh, it's pretty
fucking obvious, lady!
Oh, yeah?
You fucking whore.
Watch this.
Come get it.
Come fucking get it.
Get her outta here.
I can't deal with
this shit.
You cunt.
Hey, the neighbors!
You're a cunt,
you whore.
I'll fuck you up.
We come in
or you come out?
Alright, come on,
let's go.
So, uh,
Francesca Donnenfeld.
Do you know her?
Just cut the bullshit,
Yasco, and tell me what
you're here for.
I'm Yasco.
Here's the thing, tough
guy. You keep fucking
with the wrong people.
First the old lady,
now your prostitute
friend's customer.
The old lady, you might've
written out. She, uh, doesn't
remember so good.
The colored nurse,
she's covering for
the grandson, whatever.
But why I get a call
from the chief D's office
that you've
shaken down your
pros friend's customer
whose father's hung all
the way from here to
fucking City Hall.
You're done, Lieutenant.
What do you want?
Your gun, for starters.
Come on.
Until the outcome
of the hearing,
you're on modify duty.
Better call your
delegate. You got
an ass kicking coming.
You have a good
day, Lieutenant.
[jumbled voices]
A man without a
gun is not a man.
Oh, well, I know.
Look, you cut the
best deal you can
and you get the hell out
of the Police Department.
'Cause if you stay in,
it's gonna get worse.
Can I talk to you
for a second?
I can't stay here.
I didn't take this
shit from my own mother
and I'm not gonna
take it from her.
Can I get a minute alone
with my girlfriend?
Just give her a day or two.
She's gonna calm down,
I promise.
I'm so, I'm so happy
you're here.
And I got something
else somewhere.
I'll show you.
She's really mean.
I wanna show you
this place.
I spent a lot
of time here
when I was a boy.
That doesn't
work anymore.
I was here
alone a lot.
This was my
special place
as a child.
My, my castle.
And I would imagine
things here. Pirates,
a buried treasure.
And my dad didn't
like that so much, but
my mom, she, she got it.
And, uh, and
before she died,
she bought me a metal
detector. Come on, let
me show you something.
Look at that.
Right out there,
I thought that pirates
came up the Mississippi
and that they buried
a treasure right there
by that tree next to the house.
So I, I took the
metal detector
my mom gave me
and I went out there
waiting it would
start beeping.
It was like beep-beep,
beep, beep, beep.
And I started digging,
and I-I-I dug and
I dug and I dug,
and I found a, a
Sterling silver spoon,
and I was so happy.
I started screaming
and jumping and laughing.
And I went, «Hey, man,
this is treasure.
This is pirate treasure.»
And I came back
in here with it.
And I hid it somewhere,
this Sterling silver
spoon.
I still can't find it.
It could be anywhere.
I-I know it's here.
I don't know what
to tell you, Terence.
Not a lot I can do
under the circumstances.
I know.
I tell you guys all the time,
you cannot get away with that
cowboy shit anymore.
You don't listen,
now this is where
were at.
My best fucking detective,
I gotta put him in
the property room.
Terence, come on.
Man, I-I don't wanna
you get jammed off
for all of this.
You're doing all this wrong
shit and I'm here. They're
gonna think I'm doing it, too.
So, go to the store
warehouse in Metairie
that way you're not here.
And while you're there,
get me my .45 Magnum and
bring it to me. Okay?
Hey.
You're working here?
Looks like.
What you got there?
Nine, ten grams
of heroin and
a Glock nine.
Yeah. You see that
scale over there?
It's broken.
See? useless.
I sent for a new one.
As soon as it gets here,
I'll weigh the drugs
and I'll get you
your voucher, okay?
All right, bye-bye.
Can I help you, sir?
[jumbled voices]
[laughter]
Can I talk
to you a minute?
Excuse me?
Mind stepping outside?
I'd like to talk to you.
You interrupted my meal.
I'm gonna pretend to be polite,
so you look a big man in
front of your friends.
You give me a hard time,
I'll put the cuffs on you
just like any
other shitbird.
I'll be back.
You a'ight?
Motherfucker wanna
talk to me.
You ain't gonna shoot me,
are you, motherfucker?
Why would I do that?
I got something for you
I think you're gonna like.
Let's take a walk.
Be crazy for
coming down here.
I'm gonna give you a chance
to make some money the
old fashion way
with a cop protecting you.
What I need
protection from?
The cops.
[laughs]
A cop will protect
me from cops?
You'll know when a supplier
is under surveillance.
You'll know when it's
safe to make a pick up,
when it's not.
What I gotta give you?
Fifteen thousand
a shipment.
Oh, I'm sorry,
am I being unfair?
How I know you ain't
looking to set me up?
Tomorrow I'll bring you
some information.
Small shit.
You decide if you wanna
go to the next step.
What about the murders?
You don't give the fuck
about them no more?
Look at me.
Now look at you.
I never did.
Hey, I got the weight
on that dope finally.
Thanks.
That's all there was?
I'll double check it
if you want.
Don't matter.
Still got enough
for felony.
What are you guys
got going on today?
Buying bust on Fourth
and Ferret on Andre's
outfit.
Happy hunting.
[cell phone rings]
Undercover just busted
one on Andre's. Fourth
and Ferret.
What do you know?
Man of your word.
Are you running me
back to my car?
Yeah. I need
to make a stop first.
Is that all right?
Yes.
This, this is prime
real estate.
Doesn't look prime.
See, that's the point.
Now is the time
to get in.
Two, three years from now,
all this we'll be river
front condos.
Marble floors,
health spas.
By that time,
another motherfucker
made all the money.
Don't be going legit
on me now, «Big».
Money's money.
Tell you what.
You'll be the
front man,
I'll be the power
behind the throne.
It's like we're working
for a greater good.
Yeah, you're right.
This is a good spot
to build condominiums.
See? I know I
likes you, man.
Come on.
[siren wails]
May I ask you to step
out of the vehicle?
What'd I do?
You bought dope.
I watched you
buy dope.
Now stand the fuck up.
Put your hands
on the car.
I didn't--I didn't
buy nothing, man.
No? What's this?
Officer, please, let--
Please what?
I don't know how
that shit got in there.
Did I put it there?
No, sir.
Just some
freaking currants?
Yes, sir.
That's what you
tell the judge, then.
Maybe you'll get lucky
and he will be a
football fan.
You know who I am?
Oh, I know who you are.
Then why you wanna
fuck my life up for?
That's gonna knock me
out the draft.
I'm sure you'll get
a contract of some
kind eventually.
You run the 40
and what? What's
that, four-three?
Why do you do
this to me?
For some motherfucking
marijuana, man.
I was gonna by
my mama house.
So, you're going off
for six points favorites
against Texas.
You win by five or less
or you lose altogether,
none of this ever happened.
Sir, I can't do that.
A fumble, a missed blocking
assignment. You can
absolutely do it.
Sir, please. Please,
don't make me do that.
Listen to me, Renaldo.
I dumped a lot of
money this year
on you.
I got the chance to get
some of that back, I wanna
take advantage of it.
You're gonna tell me the
integrity of the game is
too much to you, fine.
I wouldn't dream of
trying to convince you
to go against your conscience.
Turn around.
I'm placing you
under arrest.
You--you won't
tell nobody.
You ain't gonna
tell nobody?
[men laughing]
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
This that Taliban shit.
That's what's this is.
That shit Osama give
a motherfucker before
they blow themselves up.
That's money.
Money.
Shut up!
Where's the 15,000?
You'll get it, man. Relax.
Did I not do
what I said I
was going to do?
Yeah, man.
Relax.
Tell me again to relax.
I'm not looking
to beat you, man.
Where's my money?
I'll get your money.
When?
Tomorrow.
Where?
My place.
Give me a cut of
the uncut dope.
Look, I'm gonna
pay you in money.
This is interest.
That's bullshit, man.
What's that, little man?
Midge, chill out.
Here.
Now, put that gun away
before you kill somebody.
I'll kill all of you.
To the break of dawn.
To the break
of dawn, baby.
(Terence)
Wassup, wassup, wassup
wassup, motherfucker?
No fucking
bets, Terence.
What's the matter?
You don't like me?
You don't pay your debts.
I don't wanna know you.
I can't afford it.
Ten grand!
Five I owe.
Yeah? Five
for Louisiana.
Right there. Wassup?
Where did you get this?
What, are you my priest?
Right there, here.
You got it.
It's a six-point spread.
No shit.
Frankie?
[thundering]
Frankie!
Hey.
I got something for you.
I need to get
my clothes.
Don't worry about your
clothes right now. This
is uncut dope.
Just a bunch of stuff
from my closet and then
from my dresser by the bed.
I'm not gonna give you much
until we know how strong it is
'cause it's pure, you know?
Baby, I've been talking
to your father a lot
and I think I'm gonna go
to a meeting with him.
What does that mean?
You don't want any?
I mean, of course
I want some but I,
maybe when I get back.
Frankie. Frankie,
we gotta go.
Okay? Right.
Thank you.
This the way
to do business.
This, this way I ain't
gotta worry about what
I'm walking into.
I got you.
Yeah, let me hit
that shit.
Yeah.
[laughs]
You hitting this shit?
Hey, Midget, light
the Caucasian's rock.
You're my kind of
motherfucking cop, man.
You're a crazy,
motherfucker.
What did that Ki run you.
What do you care?
I'm guessing 60,000.
Very good guess.
Will you shut
the fuck up?
You owe me 15 thousand.
I'll take 25% of the
dope uncut.
That means you're
getting my price.
It's one way
of looking at it.
The other is, you get to
keep 75% and not go to prison
for the rest of your life.
Yeah.
Go ahead.
Make sure you cut
that shit before
you sell it,
unless you wanna kill
the motherfucker
who buys it.
Did I ever tell you
the story about
nigger Elk?
I was watching TV,
the game, right?
Reynaldo Hayes,
He got tossed the ball.
He was running with it.
He jumped over three
linebackers in midair.
He sprouted antlers
like a gazelle.
Like an elk.
He landed again.
He ran, ran, ran.
He scored a touchdown!
Crack talking.
Listen, I'm not worried
about you, so don't be
concerned about me.
'Cause I'm not concerned
if you're not concerned.
I'm not really concerned.
I'm worried 'cause
if you drop dead,
I'm the motherfucker
they come looking for.
And then I gotta
end up having a
nigger from Africa
trying to move in
on my shit.
And I don't wanna shoot
no more purple ass
niggers from Africa.
Easy, easy, easy, easy.
'Cause I'm not Eazy-E.
Fucking god.
Hey. Hey. I need
to go to the store.
So?
So I need you
to watch him.
Fuck, no,
I can't watch him.
Don't be yelling.
There ain't nothin'
to eat.
Get the fuck
outta here!
Get the fuck outta here!
Hit me again
with another one
on them rocks.
What the fuck's that?
It's my lucky
crack pipe.
You crazy motherfucker.
You don't have
a lucky crack pipe?
No, I don't have a lucky
motherfucking crack pipe.
Then, Donald, you're
gonna take a hit
of mine.
Why I gotta do that?
'Cause it's lucky.
Shit.
Lucky crack pipe.
[woman screams]
Sorry we're late, fellas.
I hope you didn't
wait dinner.
Who the fuck are you?
Third party beneficiary.
Your friend here
can fill you in
on the details.
I'm working on getting
your money, Dave. That's
what I'm doing here.
I don't know about you,
but the hardest part
of collecting debts
is having to listen
to the stones.
Terence owes you
some money?
$50,000. Plus my two
young friends here
were supposed to have
a sexual experience
of their choosing
with an attractive woman.
Nothing. He came across
with none of it.
That's wrong. That's wrong
you don't do what you say
you're gonna do, Terence.
The dope's worth
more than 50,000.
Take it.
Why don't I take
all the dope?
Why are you gonna take
what belongs to me?
Well, there was a time
when I wouldn't have.
I would've taken what
was mine and left the
rest on the table.
But, you see,
I never got rich
enough to retire.
I'm stuck
doing this shit.
And I'm not
young anymore.
So now I don't leave
nothing on the table.
Pick it up.
Shoot him again.
What for?
His soul's still dancing.
(Terence)
Shoot him again.
[gunshot]
Good night, Lieutenant.
What are you
doing tonight?
I'm getting outta
here and go to bed.
Just for fun, why don't
you stop by the apartment
on Josephine?
For fun?
You might find something
interesting there.
Like what?
These bushwhackers
might've hit a crack pipe
while they were there.
You know? The odd chance is
he dropped it under the bed
where the kids were.
And we missed it.
The DNA'd place
them at the scene.
You had a vision, right?
Deoxyribonucleic acid.
(Terence)
Frankie? Frankie.
Where's Frankie?
She's not in the house?
Frankie's on her
way to rehab.
Rehab?
What about her clothes?
Someone will
bring her her clothes.
Anything else
you wanna know?
[mumbles]
You don't have
to hide it from me.
We're birds
of a feather.
We both like
our poison.
You just drink
beer, I thought.
Do you mind if
I watch the game?
Mh-mh. Be my guest.
(reporter)
I cannot believe
what I'm witnessing.
Louisiana up
by 18 points in
the second quarter.
For another score.
You wanna share?
Back to pass.
He scrambles.
Hobbs builds his
way to another--
I don't know.
And all this without
Renaldо Hayes.
We still don't know
the nature of his injury.
Just that he's taken
himself out of the line.
I'll kill him.
Renaldo Hayes being out,
the freshman Johnson has
really stepped up
for this football team.
You're in the land
of miracles, my boy.
I'm looking right there
at Hayes, and I'll
tell you what.
The guy just does not look
like a happy guy. He's
on the sideline.
He's obviously suffering
from some sort of injury.
Hey, guys.
Good to see you.
Listen.
This stuff, this
thing between us,
it's gotten way
out of hand. Got
way outta hand.
Okay?
Those gumbos, couple
of fucking assholes.
They disappeared because
of something you
did to them.
Whoa, man, I got
no beef with you
whatsoever.
Everything between me,
right as rain.
And I want
you to know
that my father
got in touch
with his guy
and he told him
whoever it is,
that complaint has
been withdrawn.
Finished.
Oh, yeah.
Okay?
Okay.
Oh, yeah?
Uh, phew.
Okay.
That's the way out.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no. Look, Ned,
if you'd called first,
I would've saved
you the trip.
I'm guessing
that you didn't
see the game.
How did this happen?
Louisiana by three.
Hayes ended up playing?
Nope.
Worked out anyway.
What are you
talking about?
Nothing.
Oh,
and my daughter's
tickets, speeding tickets,
thank you,
thank you.
This female highway
patrol officer calls up,
says they're
taken care of.
It's $10,000.
Sure you don't
wanna count it?
I trust you.
All right, man.
You take care
or yourself.
All right.
Great news.
Our man came up with this
at the crime scene
on Josephine.
I just got lucky.
The lab found
Godshaw's DNA on it.
[all laugh]
That is fantastic!
Yes!
Oh, look at that.
I found the spoon.
It's not silver.
It went rusty.
I wanna give it to you.
It's yours.
It's for me?
That's so sweet.
It's beautiful.
(Godshaw)
Yeah, I need
eight of them.
Yes, eight.
Uh-huh. It's
going down, baby.
Yeah, I got some help.
I'm telling you.
Police Department.
Stand up. Keep your hands
where we can see them.
What the fuck is this?
We got it.
Check the outside,
check the backyard,
check upstairs,
check his car.
We got this. it's okay.
Good. We're good.
Upstairs.
(Terence)
Cuff him.
No.
What do you
mean no?
This is what happens.
Before we can cuff him,
he goes for this weapon,
we shoot this prick
and steal his shit.
Fuck. Terence, what—
What are we doing?
I thought we had
our thing going.
You're wrong, baby.
He acts like he likes you
'cause he likes to get high.
Huh? That don't mean
he stop bein' the police.
Cuff him, Stevie.
No. Can you draw
a line of murder?
It's interesting
where to wreck its fun.
I said cuff him, Stevie.
This is about money.
You want my fucking money?
Take my money! You won't
kill me for this shit.
Go for it, son.
Go for it.
Got for it.
Go for it!
Yeah, yeah.
Next time.
Now fucking cuff him.
I said cuff the
motherfucker, Stevie!
[United States anthem]
[people singing
the anthem]
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is an honor to conclude
this year on a positive note.
In recognition of his
leadership and tenacity
in the investigation
of the Ndele family murders
resulting in the successful
apprehension and prosecution
of the three
individuals responsible,
I'm proud to include
Lieutenant Terence McDonagh
among those being promoted
to the rank of captain.
Captain McDonagh.
[applauses]
Woo!
Excuse me.
Would you care
for some wine?
No, thank you.
We're all gonna stick
with our sparkling water.
I would like
to make a toast.
To the new Captain.
To new life.
I'm probably
gonna start to
cry right now.
Oh, that's okay.
To my new family.
God bless.
Here, here.
You still gonna be working
on night shift when I get
closer to the due date?
I'll make sure I'm
not. How is that?
I could get to the hospital
and all, but I like having
you home at night.
I like it better
that way, too.
[women laugh]
Thank you, darling.
(guy)
All right.
There we go.
Where are your keys?
Did I give them to you?
No, I don't
think you did.
Stand against the wall.
What'd we do?
Hey, stand
against the wall.
What are you doing?
The two of you match
a description. Passing
drugs in the club.
Don't say anything.
Do exactly what
I tell you to do.
So, what are we
high on tonight?
Nothing.
Empty your pockets.
Dump out the handbag.
[knocking at the door]
Room service.
I didn't order
any room service.
Oh. It must've been
a mistake again.
Holy shit.
I'm Evaristo Chavez, man.
You saved my life.
I was in the prison
that was flooding.
Oh, yeah.
Do you remember me?
Are you still with
the Police Department?
Port of call
still New Orleans.
Okay.
What happened with you?
The judge remanded
to a drug treatment
program.
November 14th
I have a year clean.
Congratulations.
Are you all right?
Sometimes I
have bad days.
Listen,
you saved my life.
I'm almost done working.
I'm gonna get you out
of here, okay?
Okay?
Do fish have dreams?
You know, Chavez,
I still hate
that I ruined
my underwear for you.
[laughs]