And now it's my turn
I'm leaving this world
I'm leaving my memories
I see...
I see the kid
kid that I was
I see...
What are you doing out here?
Oh, I've been hired to escort
this one out to his uncle's
Parents can't handle
him no more
You ask me, he was left too long
to suckle on a negro pap
His uncle's got a ranch
in a town called Palomito
Maybe he can put some
starch in the boy
I'm the uncle
Give me the money, sir
The money...
Here's your damned money!
- It's all yours
- It's not damned money
- It's money blessed by God
- Go to hell!
-
What took you so long?
Well I'm in charge at the ranch and
my uncle...
What's your name?
Where are you from?
La Louisiane
Oh... Louisiana!
This is your first time
Yes, it is!
Yes, it is
No
Do you believe in God?
I don't know
Do you?
Today I do
My Mama gave it to me
Madeleine
Come here
We can go just the two of us
You and Me...
Sorry to break up the party
Leave me alone, Wally
I ain't working tonight
Doing virgins now, are we?
Don't be that way
I've been riding
all day long darling
just to get here and see you
Wally, please
Go. Go away!
You wanna see
how a man does it?
Go Go, Mike
He'll kill you!
You don't wanna die over
no whore, Mikee?
- Now get the hell out of here
- I stay
- Please, no, stop it!
- It's time to go!
Do you believe in God?
Madeleine
would you come with me?
I have money
Runi
Hey, Rolling Star!
You'd better feed him somehow
- Got time for a drink?
- Yeah, you know me
- Billy!
- Don't worry Billy
I'll take him
Do you mind building me one?
Here. How do you think your
little chat with Sullivan will go?
Well, we'll see
You know, the town's starting to
hum
They say there's more gold in them
mountains than in all California
Yeah, that's what I'm afraid of
Damn Jimmy!
- Goddamn butcher!
- Help!
Damn Jimmy, what the hell
do you think you're doing?
You're my deputy now
This dentist prick tried
to kill me!
Put him down!
Put him down, I said
Please
Do it
What do you think you're doing?
You can't go throwing people
through windows!
We're the damn law
I quit, 'cause he deserves it!
You'd better rein in
that temper of yours
Where's my tooth?
- Sir, you're all right, sir?
- I'm all right, it's a miracle
Don't worry, you'll be paid for
that busted window
Ok, Thank you
Cause I'm docking it
out of your pay
- Well Now, what about that drink?
- Yeah
Sounds good to me
No sir, you're gonna simmer down
and you're gonna keep a watch
on things now!
- Can you put that back in?
- Yes
You couldn't take
this one out, could you?
I think we have to
climb that hill
You go on ahead
I ain't fixing to die
Pleased to meet you
Looking for those damned
Sacred Mountains, huh?
Father Del Rio, may you be
blessed in heaven!
What was that?
Prosit
What was that again?
Woodhead, I said you are
a pessimist and I am an optimist
You've got to have faith, my friend
I don't have faith in
no one but me
me and old Betty
I promised you gold
I'll give you mountains of gold
They're so close
I can almost smell it
Well, let's get a move on
Yeah well today is
maybe not a good day
What do you mean not a good day?
Well, you know
tomorrow maybe we come back
What do you mean tomorrow?
I've got to
Anyway one of us must live
Mike the Conqueror!
I told you that horse
won't listen to anybody but me
Easy. Easy
Easy, boy
Hey, hey! You're not gonna
win him like that
- Wait, you're stuck
- What?
You're stuck to me
I'd thought you would've done
better than that
Boys, finish them gates!
Marshal!
Sullivan
That's a hard ride
What are you doing
round here, Marshall?
Interested in one of my horses?
I heard back in town
that your hand Woodhead
and that Prussian
are crossing the border
on to Chiricahua territory
I don't know anything about that
I'll tell you though that
I've send Woodhead up to Riata
to sell some of my horses
A pair of mules
holding digging tools?
You're accusing me
of something, Marshall?
I know about the Prosit's map
to them damned mountains
And believe me
it ain't nothing but bullshit
Well people around here talk
you know that
I know that
But what you should know
is that anyone crossing the border
is breaking the law
Is that a fact?
You shouldn't get caught up
in this nonsense, Greg
You don't wanna
loose what you got
Father, we should get going
What you want?
Well right now, all we want
is somethin' to eat
Where's the manuscript?
The Del Rio manuscript
Don't have it
Don't play dumb with me, because
I know your magic, Indian Witch
Prosit took it
Don't be afraid
I don't kill animals
Where did you get this?
My Mama gave it to me
And this one here?
I bet a pretty Indian girl
gave it to you
How do you know that?
Why else would you spend
so much time in the mountains?
Hey Mike!
Hi Pete!
What are you doing here?
What does it look like I'm doing?
Now you two are starting
resembling an old married couple
Mr. and Mrs Marshal!
Why don't I take you upstairs and
show you what kind of woman I am?
Too much of a woman for me!
Come on here
Playing good tonight, boys?
How about a song?
Chiricahuas!
What happened?
Where's Woodhead?
He is dead!
Look what they did to me!
You were told not to go
on their territory
We were on the road to Riata
They attacked us
Well, they've killed
one of our own!
What are you gonna do
about that, Marshal?
We can't just sit around here
with our tails between our legs
while they try to fence us
in from all sides!
You're a southpaw, huh?
what?
Ain't you left handed?
You say I'm lying?
You think I sit on a horse
and do this myself?
And it must have hurt
I am a Prussian Officer!
The Von Luckner family is well
respected in Germany for many years
I'm a man of science
a geologist
I make maps
I've never seen
anything like this!
The whole world's gone mad!
Maybe...
but I'll find out what happened
You can bet on that
Maybe you're not the right man
for the job, Marshal
It's our land!
You ruined my song
A round of drinks on the house
in Woodhead's memory!
She's got cojones
as big as a bull's!
To Woodhead!
May God grant you vengeance!
Sullivan, I found the mountains
I can...
Sullivan, you still need me!
Maybe not
What are you looking at?
Move!
Who did this?
You, tell me
What happened?
- Tell me, you son of a bitch
-
which side are you on?)
Are you sure you don't
want me to go with you?
No. I need you here
You know if Woodhead and that Prussian
did travel into their territory
you may not get the welcome
you're used to
Jimmy
I'll be back in a couple of days
And Jimmy
you better keep your eyes peeled
till Rolling Star relieves you
Yes, sir Marshal
Sir Marshal, Marshal
Damned Cajun!
Go back to your squaw, boy!
Get out of here, Indian!
Bye, you Indian lover!
It's a hot one
ain't it, Sheriff?
Yeah
I'm looking for
a good friend of mine
His name is Prosit
I reckon you'll find him
over at the Venus Hotel
All right
Many thanks
Prosit, huh?
Come on Billy
get me over to the saloon, quick!
Hey sheriff
we got a wounded one!
Holy Mother of God!
Woodhead?
Prosit
Where's Prosit?
- what did you say?
- Prosit
I saw the mountains
you have the manuscript...
Sullivan's got it
I'll have a drink
Now Woody, look, come on
don't make me do anything rash
Come on, take me
back to the office
Come on, come on!
Let's get Jimmy. Let's go
And keep it straight!
I was there
He was my partner
We were like
blood brothers
Woodhead
Howdy Pete
Yes?
I'm looking for a man
named Prosit
Woodhead!
It's a miracle!
I know what you're gonna say
but look what they did to me
They scalped me
and left me to die
I begged
I prayed to God to give me
the strength to make it back
so I could kill you
Drop the gun!
I said drop the gun!
You heard the man
You can't leave me
in the same cell!
He's a killer
you're breaking my heart!
And I thought that
we were partners
Wally, my friend!
I thought you were dead
It seems
you've been very busy, Prosit
What matters is that
you're alive, partner
Where's the manuscript?
- Manuscript?
- the manuscript
Ah, that manuscript!
Like the Del Rio manuscript?
Eh, I don't have it
But I know who's got it
Yeah, I can take you to him
We can find him right now
Well, we can't get out but...
You know we can...
We are partners
We are partners?
It's good to see you, Wally
Likewise
The Marshal is here
Yes
Riata, was it?
Yeah, Woodhead's dead
But it wasn't the Chiricahua
that killed him
Some shooter came into town today
and finished the job
He's sitting over there in your jail
That man shuffles his feet
What's wrong?
Well nothing's wrong, darling
Nothing
Here, I'll take that
I'll take it
What was that all about?
Oh, just a friendly conversation
between two men
Is that so?
Well he sure left in an awful hurry
for it being so friendly
You're in love with him,
aren't you?
Whose side are you on, darling?
I didn't know I had to choose
Well, I'm on my side
Been real busy
Got a full house in there
I heard
You gonna paint my portrait?
Hey, what's your name?
Wallace Sebastian Blount
Hey, stranger
You got a light?
Most folks used to call me Wally
Wally
No, Wally!
Please no, stop it!
Back off!
Stop it!
It won't be like it was before
You want to see
how a man does it?
Go. Go, Mike!
You don't wanna die over
no whore, Mikee?
You son of a bitch
I thought you were dead
I'll be damned
You're fixing to shoot me
with my own gun!
That ain't right
You're the son of a bitch, Mike
I guess maybe
you never got over
that thing what I did
In fact
you did me a favour
I died, but I came back
And now, I'm heading for
the Sacred Mountains
But first
some truth,
the same way
that you've done for me
Ok
you want what's real?
And I won't deceive you
You wanna know
what I saw in the fire?
I saw
funny shapes
funny little black tongues
licking my soul
I'm going to learn to kill
To kill
with my spirit
It's nice to see you again
Mike, Mike
Come on, come on
I think you'd better go
and find your mummy, OK?
Follow us
Take me to Runi
We get out of this, I'll take you
anywhere you want to go
Follow me!
Billy, Billy
No! no Billy
Billly, no!
No! Billy
Billy!
Papa...
Don't do that
You can't shoot me!
Look at the manuscript!
- what for?
- the last pages
I ate them
Wait, you need me
We're partners
I guess I'll have to
cut it out of you
Wait, Wally
We're partners
Hey, this is madness!
We'll pass through now!
Think! Think... Wally
We're partners, Wally
Let's go
Schnell!
Ja ja, Schnell
You tried to kill me
but the map is in my head
Well I hope so
for your sake, partner
Father
Father?
No, no, no
Come on, boys!
Get some water on that thing!
Get that through the window here!
Come on! Pump, boys
Hey, Jimmy! You sure you boys
don't want to wait till sun up
get a good night's rest?
You want to tell him
that we wait till the morning?
I've enough shit already
I sure I wish
I could ride along with you
- you gonna be OK?
- We're gonna be fine. Billy and I
Sure sorry about Billy
See you down the road a bit
Come on, boys!
Pump it up there! Come on!
Horses are ready, M'dam
We've got guns
and supplies for a week
Let's go
Runi
You ain't gonna drink
that shit, are you?
Runi! Runi!
It's the drink
It must be the drink
I don't know why you're
going back to kill them
We should leave them
to the Chiricahua
Can't you see how hard
he fights to survive here?
You have no respect for life
What was that?
Just a couple of coyotes
We'll never catch up with them
We don't even know
where we are
Well you can turn back
if you'd like
They only killed your uncle
So, anybody else want out?
You're free to go
You and Charlie take first watch
Sweet Jesus!
Maria!
Maria
I'll kill the man responsible
I promise you that
He's ok, he's ok
Don't worry
He's a friend
It's all right. It's all right
I'm sorry
Well, I promised you gold, partner
I'll give you mountains of gold
Don't even think of trying
anything funny, Prosit!
You know the difference
between you and me?
You are a pessimist
I am an optimist
Julio!
Chiricahuas
We must head to the canyon!
They won't follow us there
- Which way is it?
- It's that direction!
Well I'm happy here
Most men think this here mountain
is just full of gold mines
But I know different
I know the truth
I wish I was a spider
I love these creatures
Yes, it must be great to be a spider
If I was a spider
you would squash my head
It is not what I...
Yes, you would squash my little
black head, wouldn't you?
Animals are beasts
but men are monsters
You are right
Men are
monsters
Father Del Rio
You're a saint amongst sinners
I'm trying to save my animal spirit
Why do I have to be stuck out here
with a pathetic human like you?
You know, that tooth's got to
come out one way or another
Easy. Easy
You should have let Runi
take a look at it
No way in hell
I don't want any of his Indian magic
I'll end up as crazy as Mike
My goldmine
And now
the gold
Get up
Get up!
We've known each other
for quite some time now
mighty Mike
It's time to go!
You're a dead soul
You're not welcome here
Why do you say that?
You're so lucky
that I owe you so
very much, little boy
I was in many shapes
before I was released
And I see...
I see...
I see why I'm here now
To bring you with me
I see why we met the first time
To come here
in this world
together
Mike, Mike
Come on
Mike, Come on, Mike
My love
Hey, how are you doing?
You see where love
leads us
Time to see the truth
Come with me, brother
Take my hand
Speak with me
in deep tongues
the language of the dead
It was you Mike
who killed that girl
Sweet little Madeleine
It was you, Mike
It is you who must go
and I must wait
You're free now
I love you so. I love you so
I feel her through love
And you will bend
and tell me
that you love me
He's dead
And now it's my turn
I see
I see my memories
But I don't want to die
Runi! Help! Runi!
I... I love you
I love you too, darling
You've been a little rough on me
this last while
She's waiting for you
My mouth's feeling a lot better
Real good baccy this!