Five hundred dollars
for the death of Chen kuo-wei
Friend
Please stop, you're wasting your energy
Are you Chen kuo-wei of Quadruple Door?
Yes, who are you?
I'm Yen Tieh-hsin
So you're the Hades Kick
The kick which has never been beaten?
You're right
Someone pays me to kill you
You and I haven't met before
Who wanna kill me?
I can pay you double to kill him
You can, but killing is my profession
I've to keep my words
So I must kill you first
You're too arrogant
I've never lost before
You may not win
I don't care who you are
I'll break your hands first
Hsien
What's the matter, master?
I'm going out, keep an eye on them
Sure
Stop it
We won't practise this today
Let's practise the Fist of Five Styles
which I taught you few days ago
Dozing again
Cheeky
Pointless
Start now
Appearance of Dragon & Tiger
Two Tigers, White Snake
Panther & Fire, White Crane
Hold it
Your wrists are too weak
You can't learn it well, understand?
How dare you fool me?
Fooling me... Not me!
Who's he?
Say it
Naughty Panther
Though Mentor Wong is your father
you should never cause trouble here
All because your kung-fu is too vague
You mean that my kung-fu is very bad?
Not too bad but useless
How useless is it?
Your Panther & Fire
It isn't bad
You've exposed your body
easy to be attacked
Your foot-work is too loose
Just a kick
and you'll fall
Naughty Panther
you've taught Hsien a lesson
We all feel very happy about it
He's too arrogant, I can't stand it
You've vented our anger
That's great...
Eat more then
No, I'm talking about that girl
What a charming face
very pretty indeed
How much? 30 cents
Not bad
Too good if I can kiss her
That's easy
I'll make her hug and kiss me
Liar I won't believe you
Let's take a dinner to bet then
Deal
Be careful!
You'll be sent to jail if she sues you
Just watch out Don't worry
Just watch
He's dead man
This flower is beautiful
Trust me, try it on
I'm sorry, sir
My eyes hurt
What can I do?
Something got into my eyes
Help me get rid of it, miss. Please, hurry
Not yet
Yes good
Thanks
Snake
Snake?
Don't be afraid...
I'll kill it. Don't be afraid
It's great
I'll do the same thing on your sister
My sister?
How dare you flirt my daughter!
I didn't, she hugged me first, bitch
Mother
Save it, I saw everything over there
Who'll flirt an ugly duck like her!
Time to teach you a lesson
Good, not bad
You're good fighter
Watch out
What a fierce woman
Come on
You're all ruthless bastards!
Man won't argue with bitch, excuse me
Give me back my jade
You broke my jade! Pay me back!
Pay? No way
Father...
You must pay me
What happened?
He's broken my jade
but refused to pay me
Beast, go away
Who're you talking to?
You
Pay him immediately
Pay? I don't know how to pay
Good, I'm just looking for someone
to vent my anger
Let me teach you how to pay
Get up
Wanna kill me?
I'm doomed, I'm dead
Don't be afraid, it's just the back
I won't kill you, don't move
Please spare me...
Not yet...
Got you now
Fainted that easy?
Sometimes my attacks
aren't very accurate
Watch out
I chop... I chop meat
I hit... I hit a cucumber
I twine... I twine a garlic paste
I wouldn't know how good I'm
if we didn't fight today
It's been ages, bro
You still look great
Your bro is old now
What a beautiful niece I've got
She's still a kid
Where's Hung?
This naughty guy always goes to play
He's a young man now
I think you may not recognize him now
This time, stay longer
Hung, don't go away
Come to greet your auntie and cousin
Come here, now
Coming...
Shit!
Come to greet your auntie
Auntie, cousin
Cousin
Hung
What happened to your neck?
I... I slept without a pillow
Without a pillow? Let me help you
No thanks, auntie
Come on, relax
Auntie
Feel better now?
Yes
Brother, Hung really looks smart
He's quite tactful and clever
Brother, you're really a good father
Yes, I'm very strict to him
No wonder I heard people praising him
as soon as I came here
Really? What did they say?
The son of Huang Chi-ying is very smart
He's also a man of justice
I'm very proud of him
Come here my son, come here
Sit down
But there're many sex maniacs
in this village
A bad guy harassed your niece
on the street just now
he beat me too
Who dare do this to my relatives?
Can you recognize him
if you see him again?
Sure I can
Good, let's find him now
I'll teach him a real good lesson
Hung, come with me
Uncle
You don't have to go out
Why?
That guy is here
Who?
He's your son Huang Fei Hung
You...
Son-of-bitch...
Kneel down
Father
You bastard, I'm so angry
Huang Chi-ying
I'm doomed
Mentor Li, is someone looking for cure?
I'm looking for your son
Why?
Your son beat my son irrationally
You see the bandages? He hurts so badly
It's just a waste to heal him
Huang Chi-ying, we want your son?
You beast, I must kill you
No, Dad... no...
Brother, you'll kill him
Yes, because I'm too angry
But they'll think that
you won't have your son tortured
Mentor Li doesn't come to witness
how you punish your son
but to punish him with his own hands
Don't move...
It's all me
I'll let your son beat me back
Take this
I've given you a chance
It's you who let it go
You dare say this at this time
Huang Chi-ying, you indulge your son
I'll just abandon him
Just do anything you want
Mentor Li, how about let Hung
stand this mentor's 10 strikes
without any resistance?
He deserves it if he dies
If not, just put it into an end
I don't need 10 strikes to kill him
Young Master
I'll take the revenge for you
Mentor Chao
beat him to be as badly as I'm
How many strikes in total?
You want to cut off my posterity?
Stop it
It's already 10 strikes
You said you'll kill me within 3 strikes
A Crane & a Snake
A Secret Attack
I'll fight back if you don't stop
My clothes get dirty, take it
You comes for the revenge?
It's me
You hit your master
Young Master, are you alright?
Young master, are you ok?
My baby, are you alright?
Young Master Go to hell
Young Master
I hurt as badly as you now
Huang Chi-ying, you're somebody
but I ain't ordinary person
just wait and see
Let's go!
You watch out!
Take Young Master home, hurry
Do come back
Be careful
Now two of them are badly hurt
Are you very proud of yourself?
I'll kill you now
Brother
It's useless
to beat this naughty panther
Let's punish him by practising kung-fu
You really piss me off
From today, you can't go out
and do 6-hour foot-work everyday
Don't move
Be careful, this water is hot
So, feeling good now?
You're trembling, I feel very happy now
So happy...
You feel itchy? Let me help you
Stop, don't go too far!
I don't, your father asked me
to keep an eye on you
You'll have to stand 2 more hours
if you break one single bowl
You deserve it
Master, you come back
Your foot-work is fine
Did he slack off?
No, I've been watching him
Really? Yes
Show progress finally
Yes, I'm very tired
Are you really tired?
But you got a chair Yes
What? A chair, let me see
Damn it, a chair
You dare cheat me
when I'm punishing you
I really can't do anything about you
I'll ask your uncle to come tomorrow
and fix you
Who's he?
Beggar Su
It hurts!
Eat
Master's asked Beggar Su to fix you
Yes
You're miserable then
Why?
Do you know anything about Beggar Su?
He's very cunning
All his students have become cripples
Really?
Well, you can try
Nau was his student
and you know what happened to him?
What?
He lost all his teeth and hair
His nose is twisted
even his father can't recognize him
That monster likes torturing people
Sick guy
What should I do then?
You think about it yourself
Shit! You got to help me
The 36th Method
Run
You're clumsy
Run hurry
I leave now Just go
Leave so soon, my friend?
Eat buns...
Come in please
Can I sit here?
Yes...
Are you Chaochowese? Me too
Friends... please Please...
The food is very good
They all look good and taste good
Really good
Good
Sir...
Why you're alone? Where's Old Shang?
You eat first, eat
What would you like to eat?
A bowl of shark's fin as appetizer
Sorry, we got no shark's fin
It's too bad
Then I want a roasted left goose leg
Left leg...
A chicken and a steamed grouper
Sorry, we got no grouper
Then any fish will do
Also a stewed abalone
and big shrimp noodle
Yes
Half catty of Shaoshing wine, hurry
Half catty of Shaoshing wine
You have a big stomach
Of course, or I won't be so fat
Here's the left goose leg, chicken...
Half catty of Shaoshing wine
Yes... no thanks
Cheer... just feel free
Eat... very delicious...
We're friend... feel free to eat...
Drink...
Go ahead
I eat...
Drink..
He must be starving
Very nice
I mean the food is really good
Really good
I'll pay the bill, don't refuse me
I'll pay it now
Buy me lunch tomorrow. I'm leaving
I'll pay there
Let me pay, just enjoy it
I've to go, see you tomorrow
Take it easy, goodbye
Excuse me, goodbye... Enjoy
Sir, 1.99 dollars please
Someone will pay the bill
Who?
The old man who's eating with me
You know him?
He's my father
Your father?
How many fathers do you have?
He's the boss of this inn
and I'm his son
So you're his illegitimate son?
So you don't want to pay now?
Look there
No
I've just forgotten to bring the money
I'll come tomorrow and I'll pay you then
Kingkong, beat him
Tiger's Claw
Stop it, let's talk
Stop it
Don't fight, we're friend, don't fight
It's okay to beat friends
I'll get back what you've eaten
Get him!
Roasted goose's leg
One on the left
Soyed pork
Damn it
Also half a catty of Shaoshing wine
No... I'm dying
Stop it. That's enough
I've thrown all up
Enough
Enough? He's to do the toilet cleaning for us
I can't stand it anymore
Thanks
You dare interfere with our affairs
Just watch, I can jump
Take it
It's hot, isn't it?
Stop eating
We're friends Who's your friend?
You're nimble but stupid
Go away, kid
I must beat you
Go...
Old guy, you're really tough
Certainly, or how can I survive?
Just look at you
you're weak and useless
It's just an accident
If I hadn't fallen into the trap
I'd have beaten them
It's just an excuse
How come you're so miserable?
couldn't pay the bill?
That's a long story
May I know your name?
I'm Su
I feel very angry
when I hear the name Su
It's all his fault
Who're you talking about?
It's that Beggar Su
My father asked him to come
and fix me up
So you're afraid of him
Afraid? Of course not
It's heard that
he's vicious and cunning
That old bastard...
I'll teach him a lesson someday
You'll have the chance
Well, where do you work?
Me? I have no work
So you're beggar?
Yes, I'm Beggar Su
I see...
Beggar Su
Exactly
Better go now
You can't go now
I've received your father's money
I've to do my job
You can't go away
How long do I need to learn from you?
A day?
A year
I'm doomed then
I quit and you've got the money
Profits are all yours
You wanna quit? I wanna teach you
You old bastard
Do you dare release me?
don't ever underestimate me
Let me show you Tiger-conquering Fist
This is Tiger-conquering Fist?
Tiger-like Fist
It's great, isn't it?
Tiger-conquering Fist?
I think it's Conquered Fist
Crane Fist
Crane's Beak
Fed-up Crane
Crane Waiting for Shrimps...
Shrimps... Flying Crane
I'm coming
You scare me
You're scared to climb up a tree
What? I'm just using the Monkey's Fist
Wanna follow me?
Answer me. Answer me
Please stop
Answer me, now!
Okay...
Nobody will find a student by force
Wanna escape?
I wanna piss
Do it there There
From right to left
Then back to right
Back to the front
Left to the right
Right to the front
Left to right, right to left
I can never finish it
Just go on
So harsh to me? Fine
Hung...
Old guy, wash yourself
Go away, kid
Do you hear me? Go away
Can't you see I'm busy
What a stubborn bastard
Is this your place?
How about if I don't leave?
You're so cheeky
and so naive about the world
Comfortable?
No, you're a wicked person
I'm good at fixing wicked people
Come on...
You shouldn't be too arrogant
with such bad kung-fu
Who's your master?
My father teaches me
Then
your father mustn't be a good fighter
Maybe I'll let him be my follower
I think you'd better call me father
Go to hell
Sit down
Get up
Sit down again
Good boy
Go to hell
Take my shoes
Oh...
Don't come here
You've become a turtle now
I'll surely beat you now
You can never beat me
with this bad kung-fu
Killing a nobody like you...
would only defame my reputation
Crawl between my legs
and never return
Crawl
Wait, is this your trousers?
You shouldn't be too arrogant
with such bad kung-fu
Then
your father mustn't be a good fighter
Take my shoes
I'll surely beat you now
You can never beat me
with this bad kung-fu
Killing a nobody like you...
would only defame my reputation
Crawl between my legs
and never return
Crawl
You idiot, this wine is very expensive
It smells good
Master, I'll dry your clothes
Why are you so sexy?
The clothes got fire...
On fire...
It's my only suit
My backbone
My wrist
You're not strong enough
There's no good dish
and the tea's too cold
Cold...
My head hurts, master
Have your meal
You're so tired
that can't even use your chopsticks?
Master, all the stuff is done
So quick?
Take it back from upstairs
Hurry
I shouldn't have made it so full
Oh my god
Hung, help me to break walnuts
You break it like this
Like this
Master, it's too hard even for a monkey
Let's go for a walk outside
Good...
Stack...
Master, you're smart Of course
Don't miss it... I'll take this
Old guy, you should leave now
Leave?
How can I buy good wine with so little money
I have to win more, I stake on this
Come on, stake... believe me, stake
Open it... What?
Don't dare
Open it...
Scared? Shut up
Open it
You're amazing, master Sure
That's great
Put down your bets...
We're getting rich. It's easy
Lucky you
I'll play with you
in one go
Alright, we'll make a good fortune today
Come on
Stake
Good
Open
I'm sorry
What's it?
You're nimble
but I got good eye-sight too
So you're a swindler
Police is here, run!
You filthy thief, give me back the money
You can never get back your money
from a swindler
Do you know who I'm?
Do I have to?
You'll be surprised if I tell you
I'm the Iron-head Rat
Really like indeed
Very hard indeed
Scared?
Don't go
Give me back the money
no matter who you're
I'm not afraid of you
No one dare say this to me
You don't want to live, do you?
I'll let you try my iron head
Your heart
Your lung
Master, his head is too strong
Don't give up
Now you know how good I'm
It's fun
Good, very good
You've knocked into my trousers
Watch out...
A hammer for an iron head, alright?
How can you bear?
It's unbearable!
Master, I can't bear...
Lazy No...
My hands' gonna break
Let's stop now, buy me some wine
Buy some wine?
Waiter Coming
What do you want?
Give me three...
Three catties of wine?
No, 3 taels of Shaoshing wine, hurry
3 taels?
Hurry up, don't just stand here
Right
What takes that kid so long
to buy some wine?
Idiot
That's him
Old guy, who are you?
Who are you then?
I'm King of Stick Hsu Ching-tien
Do you know me?
Yes, I have
You ever heard of Beggar Su then?
Beggar Su?
It's me
Go
Don't go, he doesn't look like Beggar Su
What?
Look
He's trembling
he isn't the real Beggar Su
Well, how dare you cheat me
What's for? I'm the real Beggar Su
Still so stubborn?
Master
Give me the wine
It's water
Idiot, you harm yourself
Master
If I meet you again
I must kill you, go
What? You're beaten too seriously?
Master, it's all my fault
It's all because of you
You've made me lose my face
I've never had such humiliation before
It's not because you couldn't beat him
just you didn't drink enough
Now you know
But I'm so useless
or I'll surely
kick the King of Stick out
Then you're blaming me
for not teaching you?!
You've taught me minor things only
and how to stand beating
Your father Huang Chi-ying is an expert
of all kinds of kung-fu
How can I teach his son?
He wants you to torture me
Your father's given you to me
because he knows
I have good kung-fu skills
What skills?
The 8 Drunken Gods
It's nothing special
You won't understand how great it is
Many people asked me
to teach them in the last decades
but I turned them all down
Don't ever think that
I can't stand still
In fact
I'm trying to beat my opponent with surprises
How?
Why don't you teach me then?
Didn't your father tell you that...
foundation is very important
I do this because I want you to have
a good foundation
It's really the right time now
Really?
You should be a bit drunk
to learn the Drunken Fist
Have a drink first
One more
Hung, have you ever been to school?
I've spent a few years
in a private school
In with the wine
May our cups never rest
For I'll sing you a song
Please listen with your ears open
Power and wealth are no avail to us
Eternally drunk may prevail
Enough
Sober men and sages are lost
through the ages
But great drinkers never die
Shing Fung produces fine wine by the ton
The best solders of Shien Yang
are always so young
Though the king calls
I wouldn't alter one sip
For I belong to the drunken immortals
your lordship
With uplifted cup
I invited the full moon
Bring forth my shadow
may three of us swoon
Fine wine in a radiant cup is necessity
Put down that cup
the horses are awaiting there
Fallen on the battlefield
who will remember me
Remember me?
Lu, the sober drunkard
Li, the cripple with a powerful leg
Han, holding a pot in his arms
Lan, a sudden attack at the waist
Chan, the superior double kick
Tso, the desperate throat lock
Han, blowing his flute
Auntie Ho, swinging her body around
Be more serious
This style is so sissy
Miss Ho is a woman
Watch me
Do it yourself
Okay, I'll
Practise hard
Only women practise this, not me
Huang Chi-ying
Why do you stop the natives
from selling me the Bull Head Hill
You can't hide anything from me
What do you mean?
Li Wan-hao, I think you just want
the thing hidden on the hill
What are you bullshitting?
Coal
You secretly deal with the Coal Company
to make profit from selling of coal
You can hide your guilt
before the villagers but not me
Since you know it, I won't deny
If you don't interrupt my work
I'll give you 20% of the profit
20%? You spend so much on me?
Listen, the hill belongs to the natives
No one can take it away, get out of here
Huang Chi-ying
you're trying to go against me
I'll find someone to handle you
A 1000-dollar warrant
to kill Huang Chi-ying of Fushan
Huang Chi-ying?
Master
Is the food for tonight ready? Yes
Hurry up
there'll be many guests tonight
Master Hsu
Funeral?
You want me to beat you
Haven't you suffered enough last time?
I just wanna have something to eat
and someone to beat
Alright
I'll make you an extra dish tonight
Master, what's it?
Bamboo shoot and pork, give me a rod
Yes
Pork?
I'll have a piece first
Good, it tastes good
Master
One bowl
Your teeth are so strong to break a bowl
Well?
Watch out for the teeth
Well? He's considerate
Sit still
I knock
Ass against the stick
This is 'Hungry Dogs Snatching for Food'
Not accurate enough
Got it
Are you drunk?
Master, there's wine
Master, the King of Sticks gave us wine
It's free of charge
Master
We've been together for a whole year
It's time for us to separate apart
Master can only teach
You've to work it out
practice makes perfect
and make the Drunken Fist
becomes part of your body
I live nowhere, don't miss me, go home
I'll come when you need me
Beggar Su
Master
Higher
Come on
Mentor Huang
Mentor Huang... what's it?
Li and his men
are digging Bull Head Hill
Really?
Tell them I'm going there. Quick
It's just at the front
You really deserve
the name of Founder of Hung's Fist
Who are you? I don't know you
Why did you ambush me?
I kill for money. I'm Yen Tieh-hsin
I'll do my best
when having a good opponent like you
So you're the cold blood killer
Yan Tieh-hsin
Yes
But I'm no ordinary person too
Then you must show me your best today
The hands are just the doors
but the legs to fight
30% for the hands
and the rest for the legs
Huang Chi-ying, I must kill you today
Master
Father, how are you? Are you alright?
Idiot, you're back
It's alright. I'm here
You dare attack my father?
I'll give you a good lesson
You again?
So you come to bury your father
You...
Mentor Huang
it's too bad you've such disgraceful son
You can't live in peace
for the rest of your life
Good guy
go back and clean the stools up
or I'll kill you too
No way, I'll kill you
Okay, you both have to die today
You first
Wait... wait for me
Master, why you're here?
How can I miss a great fighting?
It's none of your business, Su, go away
No, I'm bossy
but don't worry
I don't need to fight you with my own hands
He's good enough
Drink first
This wine is strong
Which kind of wine is it?
San Pien Wine
It's good
Lu, the sober drunkard
Li...
the cripple with a powerful leg
Lan...
a sudden attack at the waist
Han...
holding a pot in his arms
That's great... the 8 Drunken Gods...
Thanks... there's more
Han Hsiang-chi...
blowing his flute
It's amazing
Even the flute would twist
Tso, drinking wine lock...
Throat Lock
I lock...
Lock...
Bow...
I'll make you bow
Shadowless Hand
Yes, you're very smart
Chang
I must kill you
And Miss Ho? Show it now
Miss Ho... Ho...
Wait
Master, I can't stand it anymore
Why?
I haven't learnt it yet
Can you teach me now?
Of course not
Hung
It seems invisible but it's visible
Combine the other 7 styles, and relax
Well, I'll create another Miss Ho
This is Sexy Girl's Fist
Twisting the ass
You don't sit right
Putting on cheek blush
and facing the mirror
Is it the 8 Drunken Gods?
Everyone has different styles
Even they learn from the same master
The goddess wants a drink
Come on