Say no more.
It's time for the competition. Let's go!
Okay.
The Roller Skates Obstacle Race
is now commencing.
Your turn to get embarrassed. Go now.
Let me kiss you first.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
The first contestant, No.8.
Be careful!
Not a chance!
The second contestant, No.37.
Looks like something big.
Let's get him.
Why are you robbing my stuff?
Robbery! Someone just robbed me!
Hurry! Get them! Robbery!
Robbery! Get him!
Robbery!
Can't give yourself away.
I'm CID.
I'll be responsible for any damages here!
It's too late! Split!
It's in the van!
Faster!
Monkey! Do you know how to drive?
I'm a cop.
Help me catch the car up ahead!
Faster! Pass, pass!
Faster, faster! He's right behind us!
Why is your car so slow?
You can't even overtake a truck!
I'm a cop...
Stop the car!
Or this bullet will go through your head,
then through his!
I'm going to shoot!
Stop! Stop the car!
No!
How lucky!
Do you know how to drive?
Drivers are so careless nowadays.
Oh, shit!
Chai! Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Father-in-law,
I've already chased after them.
Boss, they've transported
the merchandise to Five Stars Cleaning.
Good. Send some guys to
search Five Stars Cleaning.
Yes!
You!
You're good for nothing, except in bed!
- Get out of my sight!
- Yes.
Get me Housekeeper Chan.
From now on,
I forbid you leave your room!
Father, don't be so mean.
Housekeeper Chan, use this name list
to send out invitations for me.
I understand.
Bring the equipment in.
Got it.
You all should already know
what to do here.
I won't say anymore.
Which one of you is in charge?
I am. My name is...
There are a few more points
I want you to take note of.
First, don't bring in any tools
that you don't need.
Leave the ones you don't use outside,
by the door.
Second,
these stairs lead to the second floor.
Bullshit.
"Weather today's Ha Ha Ha".
He said I was talking crap.
You guys are absolutely
not allowed to go upstairs.
Third. The toilet is over there.
But you can only clean it, not use it.
Smoke?
Thanks.
Thank you.
Fourth.
You can smoke, but you can't light it up.
Nothing annoys our master more than
all those ashes flying around.
Does your hair fall out constantly?
Not as much now.
You should wear a cap.
It's a health hazard
to have hair flying around.
Fifth. Our contract states that...
you'll get paid
after I deem your work satisfactory.
That's for certain.
Alright then, you may start working.
Finally! After hearing garbage spilling
garbage, it's time to pick up garbage.
Go faster, faster!
Go after him! Quickly!
Go after him!
7086 reporting.
Good afternoon, sir!
Sir.
7086 be seated!
Yes sir.
You were quite heroic this morning!
Thank you sir!
Do you know how many cars you smashed?
I didn't have time to count, sir.
It was more than 50 vehicles!
Thank you sir.
Still "thank you"?
No, no thank, sir.
Did you know what happened
to those two muggers you caught?
They escaped?
That would've been better!
They're out on $500 bail each.
You have neither witness nor evidence.
How are we going to prosecute them?
Charge them for racing with a cop?
Do you know you are a big spender
when it comes to solving cases?
I'm now considering
where to send you next.
You are more suitable in places
where there are more trees than people!
Sir, I was just doing my job.
Doing your job?
Get your dirty hands off!
Where are my two tortoises?
Hold it!
Sir, luckily I have quick reflexes.
If you've stepped on Rose, you would be
guarding the reservoir for sure!
Albert?
Luckily it's just a pencil sharpener.
Sir, how many sharpeners do you have?
I've only got one sharpener.
Albert...
Sir, might as well
send me to the reservoir.
Reservoir? You better have
your traffic uniform ready!
You'll get to taste the scorching sun
and the pouring rain.
That was a red light!
Really?
You just crossed a red light.
Sir, please give me a break.
Sure I'll give you a break.
Let me see your license.
I know him!
Let me. Sir!
It's you, Chubby!
Yeah. Luckily it's you.
I've always said it's good
to have connections.
My principle is to separate
personal from official business.
Next time,
tell your friend to drive more carefully.
Sir...
Sir no more. This is my job.
Sorry if I can't help.
Let him then!
Cops only know how to write tickets,
not catch thugs.
I was good at catching thugs!
Otherwise I wouldn't end up like this!
I'm pissed!
No use getting pissed off.
Let me sit down and think of something.
Pack up the stuff.
Didn't you say you'll think of something?
It takes a brain to think.
Do you have one?
Of course!
Of course? Let me ask you.
What are the five grains?
Rice, oat, wheat, wheat...
large wheat... small wheat...
cornflakes!
For you to eat?
I can't think of it.
That means you don't know them.
Do you want your limbs to get numb?
No.
Then hurry up and pack the stuff!
Actually, what are the five grains?
If I knew, I wouldn't have asked him!
I should know. Rice, wheat...
I'm beginning to despise myself
more and more.
Once upon a time,
others clean the toilet seat for me.
Now I'm the one doing the cleaning
and getting sneered at.
I wouldn't call it sneering.
But, that old hag was a little too picky.
That's how the rich people are
when they host a party.
I don't think so! If they invite me...
Would you go then?
Of course!
You wish! All the guests are rich.
So do we have to show
our savings books to get in?
Right.
We look like rich people at a glance.
Just a glance for you.
No matter where you look, I still have
the appearance of an achiever.
In that case, let's all go then.
That's not right.
Are you scared?
Didn't you say you know a lot of VIPs?
We may even solicit some business!
Right.
That's true. I'm sure I'll bump into
many old buddies there.
- I got it!
- Teapot.
Coming!
I've got it! The five grains are rice,
wheat, barley, oats, and rye!
So now you know.
Let's go.
Where to?
To borrow a suit for you.
What for?
To show off!
Get the door.
Hey. Where's the stuff?
You sure they will work?
Why not?
I even know how to make an atomic bomb!
Light them.
Go ahead.
Please.
Hi, how are you?
Those cigars are strong. Who are they?
Don't know.
Guests.
Stop smoking. Put them away!
"Wow" what?
Such ordinary scenery is no big deal.
Your brother knows a lot of people.
Well said, but God knows
whether they know who you are.
Isn't that Chan Chiu?
How are you?
I'm fine.
Thank you for coming, Mr. Chan.
Acting like he's the host.
This is his house!
How come I didn't know?
You don't know a lot of things.
Come on.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Sis, let me introduce you
to some friends.
Same old trick again!
I'm declaring a truce with you today.
Let me give you a hint.
No need to stick to one vegetable
when you're at the market.
I still don't understand.
That means no need to bring
your own lunch box to a restaurant.
I get it! Vaseline!
Courting along with Vaseline
will get you nowhere.
You should find a partner that
has weight and makes you stand out.
Teapot!
Don't count me in.
I know.
Nobody is telling you to go after girls.
Your job is to embarrass yourself
as much as possible.
You can't go wrong with that!
Just be yourself.
Let's go!
The gold just keeps going up nowadays.
Excuse me.
Master, Mr. Ho is here.
Take him to the library.
Yes.
Please.
Brother Chiu, congratulations.
Thanks.
Quite a party.
Thanks to everybody.
Sir, where are you going?
I... want to go to the restroom.
Follow us.
This way.
The restroom is
downstairs and to the left.
Thanks.
Mr. Leung, if there's anything
you need help on,
just give my secretary
Susan a call, thanks.
Very well.
Brother,
when did my name become Susan?
Have some class!
Can't just call you Sis.
You need face to do business.
Once you've got the tricks,
then it's smooth sailing.
Business has been tough lately...
Miss, has anyone told you
how beautiful your eyes are?
Really?
And,
no one else here
has such a figure like yours.
I can't go to bed with you.
I have a husband.
Tell this to someone else.
But you said it pretty well.
You'll get a chance.
I'm no longer available. Sorry.
Miss Chan...
Good evening. How are you?
Thank you.
It's her!
Do you know her?
Not yet, but I will soon.
See how feminine she is!
What do you mean by feminine?
You want to grab her
the moment you see her!
Enough said. Show your stuff!
Which one?
Playing dumb!
Come!
The floor sure is slippery!
Miss.
Brother Chiu. I hope nothing happened
to your merchandise.
Of course not.
You just get the money ready.
Money is no problem.
When are you going to deliver?
In three days.
This is my business card.
Hope we can do business.
Five Stars Cleaning?
How are you, Mr. Chan?
How do you do?
No problem then.
Brother Ho, we'll proceed as agreed.
Thanks for coming.
I'm going now.
- Bring him up here.
- Yes.
Wait for me outside.
Yes.
Your business must be pretty profitable.
Not bad.
Mr. Jack So, our brother Chiu
would like to talk business with you.
Brother Chiu?
Hold my glass for me. Excuse me,
I have some business to attend to.
No problem.
Please.
Teapot, shall we dance?
Sure.
Shall we dance, Mister?
No, thanks.
Boss, this is Mr. Jack So.
Brother Chiu, we've actually met before.
How are you?
Really?
I've heard you were pretty tough.
Not as tough as
my two previous partners.
Scarface Wing and Cat Shit Keung.
They like to slash people.
Then what kind of a company is
"Five Stars Cleaning"?
Awesome! Our cleaning company
is strong and muscular.
We have a staff of more than 100
and 5 board of directors.
Brother Chiu, even your place here
is under our management.
If you need any assistance from us,
just give me a ring.
In other words, "Five Stars Cleaning"
has one bright future!
Then, where did you hide the briefcase?
What?
Bring it back now,
or something's going to happen to you.
What do you mean, "something"?
I don't know what you're talking about.
So you are not talking?
I said, no!
Well?
Well? You kicked me for no reason.
I should ask you why!
Are you talking?
If you don't talk,
maybe your partners will.
Take him down
and round up all his partners.
What's going on?
That damn Chiu! He said to talk
business, but he asked for a briefcase.
I said "I don't know".
Then he pointed a gun at me...
and beat me so hard,
I couldn't even scream for help.
It's alright. Don't panic.
It's just a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding? You even ordered
your men to round up my partners!
But don't worry.
I didn't expose you guys.
Now all my partners are here.
Come and get me! Kill me!
Bugging us for no reason. Let's go!
Please make them stay here.
What? Try to stop me?
Go to hell!
Let go!
Sorry. My apologies. Goodbye.
Father, what is going on?
Go back in. Go in!
You bastard!
As my master said, "It's all
or nothing. Fight or die." Come on!
That's all you can do? I can take that!
Come here!
I'm stronger!
Better not use your leg,
or I'll break it!
I know that.
Freeze frame?
What the hell is going on?
I don't know
what led to all this either.
Looks like it won't be easy to get away.
Teapot, light!
Teapot, you hold the fort!
If you killed him,
how am I going to get my stuff back?
We'll wait for you outside!
Hey! Don't just leave me!
Get them!
"Get them" your ass!
Put out the fire first!
Put the fire out!
Step on it!
I'm no longer scared.
That's what you think.
Don't move!
Stop the car! Wait for me!
Don't try anything funny. Stop the car!
Are you crazy? Just leave me like that?
Luckily I got away, or else!
There're no real friends after all!
Sorry, I hopped on the wrong van.
Couldn't be wrong, right?
Good.
You young ones are quite impressive.
You even dared
to touch Chan Chiu's stuff.
I'm a chivalrous man.
Bring back the briefcase,
and I'll give you $200,000 as reward.
What briefcase?
Don't act dumb anymore, or I'll get mad.
We really didn't take it.
Don't know what you're talking about!
Boss, let us interrogate them.
Looks like they need a few cuts
before they'll talk.
Good. They are all yours.
Save me the grief.
Hey, wait a minute.
By now we shouldn't be greedy anymore.
Actually,
it's much better to deal with him.
At least he's straight to the point.
That's more like it.
Then let's settle this...
at Peak Park tomorrow at 9 a.m.
Okay. Let's go.
Be careful, man!
You think I'm an idiot?
The lady will stay as hostage.
No way! Brother, don't leave me here.
Brother and sister! That's even better.
Sorry, Boss.
Don't worry, Sis.
We'll come back and get you soon!
If I don't hear from you by dawn,
I'll kill the hostage!
You...
No problem. Let's go.
Remember.
Got it. Let's go.
Boss, should we tail them?
No need.
It's not good if Chan Chiu finds out.
There is no briefcase!
How could you say there is one?
That's right.
How are we going to find one?
Now what?
Yeah!
Yeah what?
If I didn't say we have one,
will we be here now?
I mean...
I know what you want to say.
You want to find just any briefcase.
This trick no longer works.
Not really. As long as
they're convinced it's the real thing!
Are you crazy?
Do you know how big it is,
what it looks like, and what's inside?
No.
Then how can we forge one?
You're always right.
What briefcase is this?
I think this is the one they want.
Why didn't you say so earlier?
You guys won't let me speak
when I wanted to!
Why wouldn't you let him speak?
Be quiet. Open it first.
Wow what?
Nothing. Just wowing in advance.
All U.S. bills! Look at this!
Money!
We're going to be rich!
They all new!
Smells good too!
All 100 dollars bills!
We're rich!
Look! There's a lot more!
They smell better than perfume!
Right,
they do smell better than perfume.
Can't you guys tell
these U.S. bills are counterfeits?
Stop joking!
This is the plate
for printing the counterfeit bills.
That's even better!
We can print them ourselves!
Do you know how?
No.
These things are useless to us.
You are all money-crazy.
We need these to save Sis.
That's right. Put them back.
All of you are heartless.
You forget Sis the moment you see money!
Let's go then!
Wait. There's no hurry.
Let's change first.
Do you see them?
They're not here yet.
Then let's go!
Go where?
Once we move, they'll find us!
We have to divert their attention.
You three lure Chan's men
to the warehouse,
so we can buy some time.
Curly, you take the two plates
and lure Ho here.
That's just like sending me to hell!
Don't worry. They won't kill you
until they get what they want.
I'll go get help.
Help? Do we have any?
No, but don't you worry about this.
I feel we have a dark future.
Relax.
Chan Chiu won't kill us
before he gets the plates.
And he won't kill us
if he only gets one plate.
They're approaching.
All yours.
Go look! Don't slack off!
Yes.
Remember, be careful.
Will they trick us?
How would I know?
Doesn't matter to me.
I'm used to being tricked.
Over there!
We're here!
Move!
I saw nothing! I don't know anything!
Did you kill him?
No. Just blasted off the lock.
Don't shoot for nothing!
Go!
Teapot, do you know how to drive?
Of course!
- Get up there.
- What for?
Charge out of here!
By myself?
Have you heard of "one against many,
many against one"?
Not me.
Go. I have to conserve my strength.
Fight further! Don't involve me.
Go away!
All you know is shoot.
What else are you good at?
Kung-fu.
Put the guns away!
You two have been acting cool all night.
Get to work!
Where have you been?
You're sweating all over.
I was looking for you guys.
There's one more here!
Behind me!
I'm nervous.
So am I!
It's safe here.
Why do you think I came here for?
You're a nuisance to both the living
and the dead!
Don't mind me. You go ahead!
Just these three.
Bring the briefcase over.
You can go over and finish them off.
Hold it!
Thank God!
Where are the other two plates?
We used it to buy life insurance.
What?
We gave it to our Big Brother.
Big Brother? Who's your Big Brother?
Vaseline, don't say it!
Talk! Or I'll kill you all.
You would if you could.
Our Big Brother will be here soon.
Windpipe, we have to think of ourselves.
If Big Brother has any honor,
he'll come and share our pains.
Otherwise, let him fall into the trap,
or go through our troubles with us.
Maybe he knows what's coming
and bailed out on us.
That's right.
Big Brothers are like that nowadays.
Alright. I'll wait for him here!
Big Brother! Don't come here!
Big Brother, this guy is nothing
but trouble. Let's kill him.
No. It's hard to find
such a loyal subordinate.
They're coming.
Ho Man?
Are you jerking me?
How would I dare, Big Brother?
I am not your Big Brother.
Teapot, Windpipe, Vaseline, we're here!
Big Brother.
Don't mention "Big Brother" again.
Whoever says them will die.
What?
They were right.
So you are the one behind all this.
Brother Chiu, you misunderstood.
Big Brother, you should step out
to take responsibilities.
These two plates for you,
and he has the other one.
You two settle this yourselves.
Brother Chiu, let's discuss this!
What's there to discuss? Men!
- Yes!
- Get ready!
Charge!
Ho Man, we'll see who'll come out alive.
When two tigers fight,
one of them will die.
And the one that's alive will
finish us off.
Big Brother, the cops are here!
Let's go!
Go!
We're going too!
On your knees!
Wow! Feels like an epic.
Ranks!
Be quiet! You all stand aside.
Get the evidence.
Yes sir.
Do you think he's for real?
Sir, all the evidence is here.
This time we have enough evidence...
to keep you in jail
for the rest of your lives.
Take them away.
Yes sir!
Get up, get up!
Take them all away! Move!
Sir, can I ask you a question?
Go ahead.
Are you real or fake?
Of course I'm real.
I used to be
in the Royal HK Police Special Force.
I specialized in organized crime
undercover work.
Thank you all for your help
in this operation.
But I still need you to go back
with me for statements.
All the people I know are VIPs,
and you're no exception.
No wonder you're so vulgar,
cause you're a cop! You're good!
I knew you were not a fake
the first time I saw you.
We're heroes among heroes!
My master said that police
are the most hated of professions.
I'm glad I never listened to my master.
Ranks, you look so handsome
in that uniform. I like it!
I'll apply for police cadet tomorrow.
Let's go.
Sit down! What's the matter?
Don't know why, but I feel like...
I'm about to meet my mother-in-law.
You have a mother-in-law?
No. It's just a metaphor.
I don't feel comfortable.
You again, Chubby!
That's right, sir.
What're you here for this time?
Don't know.
Maybe it's for some unfinished business.
Let me help you.
Sir, are you high in rank?
Do you know what three stars mean?
I don't know.
Three stars mean Chief Inspector.
Teapot, give me your hands.
Turn them over.
For me?
And here's $20,000 reward.
Thank you sir.
We have money to get married!
7086.
Sir!
You're partially responsible
for this case's success.
This is to reward you.
Thank you, sir!
Sir, just a gift?
Will there be a raise?
Sure.
Really?
Not now. Wait until the government
adjusts the wages.
That means never.
MADAM!
Ceci.
Well?
Gave me this little dingy.
That's good! It's to encourage you.
Getting a raise
will be more encouraging!
I've something to tell you.
What?
I'm going to marry you.
Really? Sorry, Chubby.
She's willing to marry me!
I've been waiting for this!
Congratulations.
Can't you shake my hands
after I've kissed her?
I'll treat you two to dim sum.
Good! Let's see who runs the fastest.
Okay.
Wait!
You have to carry your girlfriend,
and I'll carry mine, Okay?
Sure!
1, 2, 3!