One early morning
Lifting the dark misty veil
of the night
From its pillow of its mountain peak
the Sun rose and saw...
The valley is filled with the
season of love
and the branches of memories
have sprouted...
innumerable blossoms of moments past
Unspoken, unheard yearnings
Half asleep, half awake
Look out sleepily at life
as it flows in wave after wave
at once new. Also the same
Yes the very same life
Which encompasses love and desire
Meeting and also parting and a sense...
that time is flowing like a river,
whispering as it flows...
that the valley is filled
with the season of love
and the branches of memories
have sprouted...
innumerable blossoms of moments past
"Why is the wind singing today?"
"Why is the wind singing"
"Why is the season raining colours"
"My heart wonders What is going
to happen today"
"Why is there moonlight in the day"
"Which way is life moving"
"My heart wonders what are these
events foretelling"
"Why is the wind singing today"
"Whose face am I seeing
in every flower"
"Whose face do I see in every flower"
"Whose unheard voice is in my ears"
"Whose are these sounds..."
"vibrating in my dreams"
"My heart wonders
Whose arrival is awaited"
"Why is the wind singing..."
"singing, singing"
Today your dream is coming true papa,
today your daughter begins her first case
You devoted your entire life
for truth and human rights
Today I am taking my first step
into the same battlefield
as always, I'm taking your faith
and blessings with me
Karim Khan do you know how to cook?
No Sir the wife cooks
Better start learning. Now women have
started doing men's jobs. Never know...
when you'll have to sleep
on an empty stomach
Now may I meet the Indian prisoner?
Most certainly! Now you have
the right to, Madam Lawyer
come, I'll escort you myself
That way I'll get to spend a
little more time with you
Shall we?
Excuse me Madam, but you're
wasting your time
This man is here for 22 years but
no one's heard him utter a single word
We think he is very happy here,
never fights, never complains...
seems like he doesn't want
to be free at all
Freedom is every man's birthright and
it's my duty to see that he gets it
You do your duty and let me do mine
Hey Seven Eighty Six...
Oye, look who's come to meet you
You imbecile, Madam Lawyer is here,
at least greet her
The State of Pakistan has decided to
reopen cases of some Indian prisoners
So find your lost voice quickly
and start blabbering
This opportunity won't come again
What did I tell you?
- Open the cell
I want to speak to him alone
Well, you've signed the papers,
what do I care
aye Karim Khan keep an eye on her
There
I've done my duty now
it's up to you and your God
Let's begin with names
I'm Saamiya Siddique and you are...?
Do you want me to call you?
Seven Eighty Six like the others do?
Your name can't be so unpleasant
that you prefer a number to it?
Veer Pratap Singh
It's ages since you've heard
your name, isn't it?
Please talk to me Veer Pratap Singh,
I've come to help you
Twenty two years ago you remained silent
and no one could defend you
Today God is giving you another chance.
Talk to me...
and I promise to get you
back to your country
please talk to me
I don't know why you don't want
your freedom. But I want you to know why...
your freedom is important for me
and other girls of this country
My father fought his entire life
for women's empowerment in Pakistan
But he could not do
as much as he wanted to
Today, after years of hard work,
I have earned my first case
But everyone knows it's impossible to
win this case. They want me to lose...
so that no woman will tread into
this male domain again
But I'm not going to lose
I will not let down my father's dream.
Or the women of my country
I just need your help.
Talk to me...
Please talk to me
Talk to me Veer Pratap Singh
That's an F 16
flying at the speed of 1200mph
When a plane tears through the skies,
plays with the clouds...
no one but a pilot can
understand that feeling
I can still feel my hands throbbing,
the blood rushing and the winds lashing...
when I used to take my helicopter...
into the mountains
ahead... left...
Help...
Let's go get them
This was me and this was my life
Squadron Leader Veer Pratap Singh,
a rescue pilot with the Indian air Force
I loved my work
Flying was a childhood fantasy.
And saving people's lives...
was my father's legacy.
He was an army officer...
who gave his life for the country
I was alone and free
and I lived every moment
as if it were the last
Little did I know that
three days later...
my life was going to change
because of a girl
a girl who was then sound
asleep in Pakistan
Wake up, zaara.
It's seven o'clock
Seven! I've never woken up this early
- Whatever has not happened till now...
will begin from today.
Yesterday your marriage got fixed
Now you're just a guest here
for some time
Soon you'll have to go to
your husband's house
Your mother wants you to
change your habits
Wake up every morning at seven,
make your own bed
Then learn cooking from Iqbal chacha...
- I'm not going to change for anyone
I am who I am, tell them that
aahaa, your cool attitude
won't work anymore
You're lucky they've chosen you
because of your beauty
I hope your manners won't turn
them away. Or you'll be a spinster for life
"I am the way I am and I will always be"
"Whether someone is happy,
Or even if they are unhappy"
"I will never change my style"
"Whether they understand or
they don't I will keep saying"
"I am the way I am
and I will always be"
"I am the princess of my feelings
and the queen of my mind"
"Why should I wear a veil
If the scarf drops, so let it"
"Whether they smile of they pout."
"It does not bother me if
What I say causes a rift"
"I am the way I am
and I will always be"
"I have no desire to adorn my palms with
henna"
"Or to hear the wedding flute play."
"I am quite happy
in my own home, thank you"
"If you can hear me O priest,
let me clarify"
"I don't know that
I will ever agree to marriage"
"I am the way I am
and I will always be"
dr Yusuf, is everything all right?
Just pray. Now there's no time
to take her to the hospital
She's repeatedly asking for zaara
Yusuf, I'm zaara's mother
but it's Bebe who brought her up
Where is zaara?
She's gone to the temple
to get holy water for Bebe
I'll break this news to zaara,
no one will say anything to her
zaara, is that you?
Yes Bebe, your zaara has come and look
what she's got for you. The priest...
sent special holy water for you and...
I know little one...
no holy water will
help me now. - Bebe...
Since you were a child you have been
chattering non stop
and I have been listening. Today I'm
going to speak. And you'll only listen
You know that I've been here
ever since the inception of Pakistan
I was 16 years old when your
grandfather left India...
and he came to Pakistan
and he brought me along with him
Your family, this country has given me lots
and I took it all with all my heart
But today I've this one last wish,
will you fulfill it?
Lmmerse my ashes in my India,
dear child
I may be an orphan but I am an Indian,
that's my only identity
I told you about Kiritpur haven't I?
For us Sikhas...
it's a very important pilgrimage.
All my ancestors are there.
Just immerse me there.
I will get my refuge.
You'll do this for me?
No.
There's going to be no need
to do any such thing.
All our Visas to go to
delhi are ready.
You just get well soon.
Then we'll both go to your Kiritpur
and you can pray there to
your heart's content
Bebe...
Now quickly drink this holy water
She was here in Pakistan
and you in India.
Then how and when did
the two of you meet?
Three... three days later...
and what an unusual meeting it was...
a bus had toppled over
in the mountains.
There were no serious casualties.
All passengers were rescued.
And I was on my way down
to bring the last girl up.
Pull us up.
It wasn't that I'd never seen
a more beautiful girl than her.
But I don't know why
I couldn't take my eyes off her.
Her eyes were lowered
and she was breathing heavily.
She was very scared.
A tendril of hair was bothering
her right eye.
She was trying to move it, but the wind
was strong and the hair stayed there.
As I lifted my hand from
her waist to move the hair...
she looked at me in fear.
We looked at each other
for the first time.
She kept staring at me scared...
then she lowered her gaze, but...
I kept staring at her...
and then my dream was broken...
Stop... stop... stop.
Ranjit. Stop.
What happened?
- My bag has fallen down.
Please take me down.
It's only a bag ma'am let it go.
I can't let it go
that bag is very invaluable to me.
Not more valuable than all our lives?
- Yes it is.
Now will you please
take me down or should I go myself?
My bag.
Stop it.
Ranjit take it down.
- Veer have you gone mad?
Do as I say. Take us down.
Here.
Ranjit, pull us up.
You endangered the lives
of so many people for a little bag.
What kind are you? You know we risk
our lives everyday to save lives...
of people who are complete strangers,
who aren't related to us in any way
But still on our way home our hearts
swell with pride...
that we saved someone's
sister, wife, brother or mother...
gave someone a new life. But today
for the first time in so many years...
I'm doubting my work
For the first time sacrificing my life for
someone else is seeming worthless...
is seeming wrong
I'm sorry ma'am
but it was disgusting
Get out! I don't want to see your face.
Who asked you to give zaara your money?
You know I can't say no to zaara.
Even if I did she would've taken it forcibly
and she's not off to the market
to buy bangles, but to India...
wasn't important enough to tell me?
She made me pledge our friendship
Pledge of friendship!
There's a limit to childishness.
Who got her onto the bus? Call akram.
Call him immediately. How irresponsible.
Zaara... zaara are you all right?
Ma, I'm perfectly all right,
please don't worry
What is this nonsense zaara,
do you know what I'm going through?
Only when I was going to the police
that this godforsaken Shabbo told me
just come back home right away
...come home immediately
Ma, the border closes at four thirty
and I haven't even reached Kiritpur yet
God, for what sin am I being punished
...now it's about to be evening...
Why did you go alone? I promised you
that I would send the ashes to India
I also promised Bebe
that I would take her ashes myself.
Zaara is this a little trip from Lahore to
Pindi that you just took off like that?
Have you gone mad?
I'm really sorry Ma.
But after all my explaining,
you were still unable to understand me
Until now, I've done nothing
really important in my life Ma
Nor will I be doing anything
great in the future
My life, like yours, will be spent
being a good wife and a good mother
But after doing this,
I will always be proud of myself...
That I helped someone attain salvation.
Ma, now that I've come so far, I will
return only after completing my work
But if you stay angry with me,
then my journey will get bad luck...
Stop it. Can a mother ever wish
bad luck on a daughter?
I've been crying since eight hours,
you want me to cry some more?
Relax Ma I'm cool.
Yes, you're the only one who's cool
and we're all fools
If your father returns
before you do then...
don't worry, Ma
Papa's only back next week
and I'm back tomorrow.
Please
Ma I've to hang up now,
there's a long queue
Listen, take care of yourself,
and don't eat any junk
and don't talk to any strangers
and keep calling me... right?
And don't be scared, my blessings
are with you... good bye...
Good bye
Yes how much money?
Why are you worrying?
Our zaara is no less than any boy.
She can get her way anywhere
Thank God that she's safe,
this girl scared the life out of me
Why're you talking to me?
I told you to get out of my sight
You say that all the time.
Now cool it
cool it my foot!
You godforsaken fool
Go do your work... what are you
standing like statues for? Go.
Ranjit, permission for my leave
has come from the base
Mom and dad had asked me
to come home to celebrate Lodi
I'll leave from here in the morning,
that way I'll reach sooner
Negi will accompany you back
Okay, see you on Monday. Enjoy...
- Thank you. Here are the logs...
Mister, are there any buses
to Kiritpur from here?
No Ma'am, no buses leaving right now.
There's one for Kiritpur at seven am
Then is there a hotel
where I can spend the night?
Hotel! Of course... look there's
Kake's dhabha. Our five star hotel
For ten rupees you'll get a blanket
for twenty five rupees you'll get a cot
Ok Ma'am, please excuse me,
I'm getting late. Good night
You risk your life to save
the lives of strangers
There can't be nobler work than that
I would not like you to stop taking
pride in your work because of me
That's why I've come to tell you
the reason for my behaviour
These are the ashes of my Bebe
She was an Indian...
who spent her whole life in Pakistan
serving my family...
and never asked for anything in return.
Just one dying wish...
that her ashes be immersed alongwith
her ancestors in Kiritpur
This is more important
to me than my life
perhaps you were not happy
saving my life
But I am sure you'll be proud that
you saved this urn that was in my bag
please try and forgive me.
I'm sorry.
Sir, here's your buttermilk.
- Thanks.
If only I'd drunk it in the morning,
I wouldn't have lost my temper then
Here's the bus
One by one... who has tickets?
I've got a ticket.
Ladies first. - No pushing.
Easy... easy... no crowding.
That's it. No more.
- But I've got a ticket.
Madam, here everyone has a ticket
but here it's first-come-first-sit
So then where do I go?
- You go up there...
Hey baldie, move on over there.
- Why should I move?
Is my wife your sister that you want to
sit beside her for the entire journey?
Shove, before I break your teeth.
- Sir, I was just moving.
You must be wondering
what am I doing here...?
Can you see that bus over there?
Actually I should've been on that bus
But I noticed you and I saw how
graciously you took this wonderful seat
I thought to myself either you are
extremely brave or extremely foolish...
to do this long journey all by yourself.
Then I realised that...
although I'll reach my village,
I'll be bothered throughout my journey...
and probably my
entire life whether...
that silly pakistani girl reached
her destination safe and sound
So please don't think that
I've come to help you
I'm simply ensuring your thoughts
don't bother me for the rest of my life
Thank you
Would you like to eat some nuts?
By the way I'm Squadron
Leader Veer Pratap Singh
I'm zaara, zaara Hayaat Khan
"Below the blue skies"
"The earth is prospering."
"Every season is joyful"
"O'my beautiful land"
"My land"
"The earth is golden, the skies are blue
and every season is colourful"
"This is my land"
"The sparrow hawk calls
and the nightingale sings"
"and the monsoon clouds arrive
This is my land"
"a crow is calling on my terrace"
"a letter from my beloved will arrive"
"and there'll surely be a mention of me"
"When the wind moves like a comb
Through the fields of wheat"
"It lifts a hundred colourful scarves"
"When the water carriers
come to the well to fill their pots"
"Someone entrances them
with the sweet sound of his flute"
"and so at every step
a new love story is born"
"This is my land"
"Where children, carried on their
father's shoulders..."
"are taken to see the fair.
And treated to comic shows"
"and ice cream and snacks"
"and to candy and savouries"
"These innocent children
as dear as dolls"
"are entertained by their grandmothers
with fairy tales"
"This is my land"
"In my country
a guest is revered as a god"
"and no matter what land he comes from,
He becomes a part of this land"
"I have seen and understood
your country"
"I don't know why
it all seems familiar"
"These evenings are familiar
as are these mornings"
"Such is also my country.
Same as your land?"
"This is my land
What are these people doing?
These are last rites. It is done before
the ashes are immersed in the river
So why aren't we doing it?
- We aren't doing it because...
you are a Muslim.
And this is a temple of the Sikhs
and it's in our interest to quietly
immerse the ashes and leave from here
No, I want to immerse the ashes
with the complete rituals
Hey no, no zaara. It's like this...
some priests are fanatics
So you'll get insulted
and I'll get unnecessarily beaten up
Should I go and ask?
- No, no you don't ask.
You wait here. I'll ask.
- You wait right here... please
dear God, it's all in your blessings
I'd told you about Kiritpur, right?
Just immerse me there. I'll get refuge"
Is your name zaara?
Yes...
You've come from Pakistan?
I've been in this temple
since forty two years
But I have never seen
such devotion
You've done more than
a real daughter would
It would be an honour for me
to do the last rites for your Bebe
come child, come with me. Come...
dear God, it's all in your blessings
come here, please
Now what?
Put your hand out and fulfill
Bebe's last wish with me
But how can I...?
Look here, neither
I nor you are Bebe's children. But...
But... if it weren't for you I wouldn't have
been able to get Bebe here so easily
Like me, now you too have formed
a bond with Bebe
So the right...
to perform this
final rite is just not mine, but yours too
come...
zaara... here's your bus ticket.
You'll reach atari. And from there...
catch a train straight to Lahore.
And here's your change
Have you finished eating?
Anything else...? - No thanks
You've already done a lot for me.
I just don't know how to thank you
I'm very frank about these things.
If you ask me...
I'll tell you what I really want...
- Tell me what I can do for you?
Be careful, I will ask but
you will not be able to give it
You don't know what you've done for me.
Ask for anything you want
It's a promise that I'll fulfill it
You are making a promise without
knowing the price... you might regret it
a Pakistani has made
a promise to an Indian
Now my country's honour is at stake.
Now even if I want to I can't back off
Please tell me what can I do for you?
- Give me this one day from your life...
What?
You drew me close into your life. You created
a bond between me and your Bebe
You're leaving me
with a lifetime of sweet memories
I want to share my world with you.
I too wish to give you memories...
that stay with you
for the rest of your life
I know a day is very precious to you.
But I promise that...
you'll never forget this day
I warned you that
you'd regret making this promise
So you fell in love with her?
What I felt...
I still can't understand...
Why I asked her for a day
I don't know... I just asked her
But yes at that time I did feel
that our acquaintance...
was not destined to end right here.
We hadn't met just to come till here
Our relationship was still incomplete,
there was still something more to happen
With this thought, the words blurted
out of my mouth...
and that poor girl
listened to me silently...
did she come with you?
Saamiya... the honour of
your pakistan was at stake
How could she not come?
Why have you made that strange face?
Your mother scolded you on the phone?
I'm scared of heights...
- Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You said this is a shorter route
The other way would take
half a day more...
so what could I do...?
- Does that mean...
you'll wear this scary expression
for the entire journey?
please smile a little
or I'll get scared too
Okay look, eat some nuts.
It'll take your mind off this
Hold out your hand... - No...
Okay open your mouth
More?
Brother Veer has come.
And there's a girl with him.
And there's a girl with him
Hey pappu's mother see our Veer has come
and has brought his fiancee with him.
Oh a girl won't come
just like that with her fiance.
Veeru must have married her,
she must be his wife.
Maati... Maati...
Oh, what's happened, who died now?
Maati Veeru's here...
Veeru? - Yes.
And he's got his wife
along with him. - What rubbish?
My Veeru will never get married
without telling me.
I'm telling the truth Maati. The whole
village has come out to see them...
What the hell... let him come...
I'm not going to talk to him
Oh chaudhry Sumer Singh where the hell
are you? Where's he gone now?
Bauji... Maati's calling you...
- Yeah right... I heard her...
She always calls me at the wrong time.
Come here son, I'll tell you something
don't ever make the mistake of
getting married. If you do...
you won't be able to score a goal
for the rest of your life
all right Sir.
Oh my dear one, how many times
do I've to tell you.
Not to disturb me during a game.
- And how many times do I tell you...
if you want to die then lie down on
a bed and die... don't play...
with kids old enough to be your
grandchildren and get your bones broken
Let me tell you one thing.
In this entire village...
there's not a single player
who can compete with Sumer Singh
Except your son,
look what he's been up to
Veeru's come? Where...?
- But not alone. He's got married
What are you saying?
- Look there...
How're you Kamli? - Fine...
I'll say hi to Bauji
...your blessings, Bauji...
You son of an ass... without asking
or telling us, you got married?
I'll thrash you!
- Married? Who told you that?
Then who's she, my wife?
- No no...
your wife is right here.
- I'll hit you
Then who's she?
- You're too much Maati
Is there only one kind of relationship
between a man and a woman?
She's our guest Bauji. After saving
her in a rescue operation...
I got her here to show her
our village and to make her meet you
Of course! I understood the moment
I saw her...
such a beautiful girl with
an ass like you... impossible!
What's your name dear?
- Zaara, Sir. Zaara Hayaat Khan
What a lovely name, where are you
from, child?
From Pakistan
Oh wow, that's fantastic
then you're our extra-special guest!
Look...
we've served the people
of our country a lot
But this is our first chance to be
hospitable to our neighbouring country
What would you like to eat?
Should I get some butter milk?
Some milk some...?
- Oh enough now
You come with me. If you get caught up
in his chatter it'll be nightfall soon
Move aside...
- Okay, never mind me.
Make way. - Oh yes.
Oye Veeru, where're you going?
Wait a minute.
All of you get going...
Yes... one minute... - What?
Yes? - Well... have you got my things?
Yes! Here's your bottle of rum.
Don't drink it all alone. - No way.
If Maati catches you this time,
I'm not going to lie to her.
Just once more...
one last time...? - Okay last time.
Now go on... go.
Cheers to the neighbouring country.
Come, I'll do that.
- No, I'll manage.
The way you're making it, it's evident.
Someone else ties your hair at home.
Come, I'll make it for you.
Just feel at home. Come.
This's Veer's room, right? - Yes.
Whenever he'd get a medal or a photo
I'd hang it up here.
And when he's not at home,
then Bauji and I...
warm our eyes looking at them.
- There's a lot of love...
between the three of you. - Because
there's no one else
to share our love. His mother and father
passed away when he was really small
Since then we're the only ones for him.
We're actually his aunt and uncle.
But he calls us his father and mother.
We don't have any children of our own
So it's just the three of us.
Look... your plait is ready
Hey! I look just like all of you.
- This is nothing.
You'll look like a true punjabi girl
tonight... tonight's Lodi
and here we celebrate it
with a lot of pomp.
I'll take out the dress.
I wore for my first Lodi for you.
No Maati, I'll wear my own clothes.
- Hey, you call me mother...
and at the same time argue with me?
Look you've come to our house...
just for a day. For this one day
at least become one of us.
Are you comfortable? - Yes.
Like I was telling you...
when I was young...
I used to take Maati on a cycle
like this right till amritsar.
Now she's so become so fat
that she doesn't fit on a cycle.
No Bauji, she's not fat at all...
- Oh you don't know... I know.
Veer was telling me that Maati and you
have built this village on your own
That's right. At first there were
just fields here.
Then after writing many letters
we arranged for electricity.
Do you see that hospital? - Yes.
That was a cow shed earlier.
...how are you doctor?
Doing fine Sir.
- Very well friend.
And look, the children's school.
Maati and I were the first teachers here.
No one knew how to read or write.
Now the kids study here till eighth grade.
After that the boys are sent off
to Kartarpur, for further studies.
And what about the girls?
- It's not possible for us...
to send the girls so far. And anyway
they have to learn to...
Iook after the household, so what use
is higher education for them?
That's not fair Bauji.
Not fair? What d'you mean by that?
- I hope you don't mind this Bauji...
what you and Maati have done
for this village...
would've have taken people
centuries to achieve
But while you made the men
capable of facing the world...
you disabled the women. That's why a
Veer has become an air Force pilot...
and the girls of the village remain
illiterate and unpolished
Girls today have reached the moon.
They walk shoulder to shoulder with men
With education perhaps a girl from
this village could've outdone Veer
don't you think so Bauji?
Oh chaudhry Sumer Singh...
where are you loitering?
Oh man... whenever I'm doing
something really important...
she comes and bugs me.
Yes Madam, now what?
It's time to light the Lodi.
Come and get ready...
all right, I'm coming
come, dear. Let's light the Lodi
Listen everybody...
come here... come on.
Coming Bauji.
Let's go there... coming
Listen everyone...
to what I have to say
The cricket pitch that was going
to be made here... will not happen now
Why...? - Why Bauji?
Relax, I'm telling you... because now
we're building a Girls High School.
The girls are glad.
I promise you that once
this school is built...
the girls won't have to leave
the village for higher studies.
And one more thing, the first brick
for the school...
isn't going to be laid by Maati or me,
but will be laid by the girl...
because of whom this school
is being built. Miss zaara Hayaat Khan
come dear...
Bauji how can I...? - Why not?
When being so young
you've taught me such a big lesson
Then why can't you do
this little thing for me?
Come dear, come.
Oye Kamli.
I, Ginda Singh... I really like you.
O'Soumitre...
I darshan Singh aulakh.
Will die for you.
Maati is this the custom of Lodi?
- No... this's your Bauji's custom
What d'you mean?
- In our time...
romance was taboo. On top of that
I was from Madras and he from Punjab.
So one night during Lodi he asked
for my hand in front of everybody
My parents didn't know what to say.
And we got married
after that ever since we've come here
and started celebrating Lodi...
he's started this custom that
if a boy is in love with a girl...
he confesses his love in front of everyone.
If the girl wants to refuse...
she quietly throws a fistful of sesame
into the fire
If she wants to accept she calls out
the boy's name and breaks sugar cane
Then after that we get them married
Wow, this's such a
lovely custom... that means...
when the bride and the groom agree,
what's the need of a priest...?
Hey Saraswathi Kaur...
My lady from Madras...
I chaudhry Sumer Singh...
ask for your hand in marriage
for the next seven lifetimes
come on girl
I'll set him right
What... my proposal... rejected?
Maati... what're you doing?
Bauji doesn't stand a chance?
Tell him if he wants to spend
seven lifetimes with me...
he has to fulfill
certain promises. Is he ready?
Promises? What promises Maati?
Sorry Bauji that's it.
Now drop the sugar cane