Frank you betrayer
I'll be back for you, Kishudo
Now, you're the only ones left with me
Frank will soon reveal everything
about you to Kishudo
Through the years I have trained
over 30 assassins
They are experts in martial arts
and Japanese "Ninjutsu"
Excluding those who died & those
who betrayed us
These assassins are scattered
all over the worid
It's crucial that I know their whereabouts
before Kishudo does
or else...
So you want to kill them all?
I'll kill whoever betrays me
We've a secret contact
For all our assassins
He's Snooker
He'd been sent to Northeastern China
Yet we lost him in the past decades
Snooker knows everything
about each of you
Yet, where is he now?
To fetch him, you must find his woman
They fell in love and born him a daughter
Thus he fled, for this is against our rules
Let us go, please
Can not
Then shall never
fall in love with another
but us - The Eight Hundred Dragons
I wonder if all of you think this way
I, Choker
I, Chimer
I, Teddy
I, Huntress
Swear that we'll never betray the group
and you, Master
Or else, May we be slain in the worse
possible way?
How many times have I told you, Pearl?
That you shouldn't be eavesdropping on us
What's the matter? I'll be one of you
eventually
Shut-up
Yes, Master
Master
Don't panic
I indulged in the magic of disguise
when I was young
Now I ended up
with a distorted face
Chimer
Yes, Master
Don't commit the same mistake as I did
Take it easy,
you still have a long way to go
Pearl
I swear I will kill Frank
Frank, your death will come soon
We are closing up, sir
Don't panic, I don't need any help here
any more, go
It's been a long time since we last met
May, where's Snooker?
I've long lost touch with him
Well, how about that letter in your hand?
Red Square, Moscow, USSR
Yes, yes
Photo, 10 Roubles a piece
May I take a photo with him?
Sure, of course
Queenie, somebody wants a photo
Ready?
Look at this! We've made such a fortune
in such a short time
I've told you
Rubles? Change for Rubles?
No, no we can't
Hey you nuts? That's U.S. dollars
Yeah, Yeah
Oh! I see
You sure it's alright?
Of course
What are you two doing?
That's illegal...
My goodness, the police! Run
Uncle, come on, hurry up
Hurry up
Yes, hurry, hurry
Get on the train, go
Go! I'll be alright, go
Hey, here
You two hurry up, I'll take care of uncle
Damn it, you just can't fight with age
You go...
So you take care
Come on, hurry up
Hey, hey...
Yao, here, come on
Come on
Queenie, what takes Yao so long?
Would the snow block the way?
No way, hold this, now wait and see
Yao
It's freezing out there
how about a heart warming hug?
Stop it right there, pal
He's looking at you, kid
Queen, go get your dad's favorite
outfit for Yao
Sure, sure
Yao's gift for me?
Yao
Shhh... Keep this our secret
Put the clothes on
You'll take it, alright?
Wow... Smells Good!
Not bad. Very becoming
I was wearing the same outfit
the first time I met your mother
Let's have some turkey first, shall we?
Let's make a wish before we start
Close your eyes, don't peep
I wish that we'll never be apart
Attack!
Keep the outfit. Take it as a Xmas gift
Thanks, Uncle
Do you blame me for not getting you
any Xmas present?
Haven't you given me your heart already?
You mean it?
What are you doing?
How about me?
So you're in too?
Your so bad...
Bye
Hello...
It's been such a long time
do you still remember me?
The Master of the Dead?
You thought you could escape from me
by hiding in Russia?
Hello, hello
Master?
No
Who are you?
I'm one of the Kishudo's people
Hector?
Record of all the assassins trained
by the Eight Hundred Dragons
What record?
Maybe you'll remember this
How did you get this?
From her dead body
You'll better be cooperative
or I'll send you to meet her
Did I ever say no? Let's go
Hurry, where's the record
Don't you dare to play games with me
No, I'm not.
It's just over there.
Get up, bring me there.
Bastard!
I'll kill you if I don't see it tonight
So you're from the Master of Dead?
I come to send you to hell
Where's the Cello?
May, look at this
It's from Yao
For me
Yao gave this to you?
Come out?
What?
You smart-ass
Snooker
Spare my family please, Master
Take my life, if you want to
Bring Kishudo's Hector up the train to me
Yes
I want you to bring one more person up
the train
Who do you want, Master
A friend of your daughter, Yao
Something wrong?
You're so quiet today
So unlike you
Dad & I are leaving for Japan
We might not return thereafter
You'll be thrilled
Imagine all the shopping you can do
Is that it? That's all
What else do you want?
Japan? You're sure you have to go?
but why?
The pollce is after dad
Quite bad this time
We may never be together again anymore
Can you help me with one thing?
We'll act as of we've leaving for Leningrad
You & Yao will cover us in boarding
The train
We'll jump off the train half way
We'd definitely help you, friends, right
I'll miss you
We should have come together
They might not be able to go pass
the police
Don't worry.
They'll make it here
Let's get in first
* Train from Moscow to Leningrad
is about to leave *
Shall we get the tickets first?
Good idea
Hold me
What?
I've seen that man before in the subway
Who's he?
I saw him kill someone
Wait here for me
I'll fetch them out there
And where's Yao?
I don't know
No time for hide and seek now
board the train first
No, we have to wait for Yao
Don't create trouble
Get on the train
Come on, hurry up
Uncle, Yao may still be waiting
out there
We'll fetch him
Yao, hurry up
Come on, hurry up
This is yours
While here's yours, and this, yours
Why, are we sitting separate seats?
Yao and I each at one end of the train
While you & Queenie stay in the middle
Sitting together will only invite suspicion
Anyway, you can move to his car
after we left the train
So you are the Manchurian?
Yes
Hector, where to go?
Remember I told you this during training
That I'll personally kill
whoever betrays me?
Well, let's see
It's for you
You made this last night?
I promised you this
for your next trip didn't I?
But, I'd stolen the materials from you
and threw them away
May, you don't have to be so nice to me
I don't deserve that
Queenie, you're the only family I have
besides Yao
But... You know the reason
why I wanted you here?
Because someone wants to kill Yao
No, they can't do that
This is the record you want
Yao has already boarded the train
He is in the first car
Both Yao & May are orphans
I brought them up since they were kids
Good job, very clear and to the point
Oh, my pleasure
Actually, when you didn't punish me
despite what I had done
I'll do what you said
By the way
What's the point of bringing Yao to you?
I saw him once in the red square
he's get the right potential
I can train him to be the top assassin
of The Eight Hundred Dragon
But... this is a secret
that's supposed to be kept by me alone
Dad, something I must talk with you
Yao doesn't love me at all
He loves May
I was just a secret admirer...
Dad, Dad!
Daddy!!!
Queenie, Queenie!!!
How are you doing? Queenie!!
Yao! Yao!
Uncle, why are you here?
Uncle, are you ok?
Uncle! Uncle!
I came to pick you up
Why pick me, I don't even know you
Come on, come on...
Go to sleep
Run? How can you run away from me?
Yao! Yao!
Do you know the murdered?
No, I don't know
Can you recognize that murderer?
No
Is your name May Yip?
Yes, May Yip
Do you know a person called Yao?
No
Well, but we are informed that
your friends were being hurt after
as such, you were trying to assist them
to flee the USSR
Is that right?
No that's not true
No! No!
Who are you?
Take all these stupid pins away
I'm your saviour
Poor thing, your are sick
Bull shit!
I've never been sick in my life
Big deal
Who do you think you are?
I'm... Well... I don't recall
Don't play smart ass with me.
Tell me if you know who I am
Of course I do.
You have problem remembering
You've a problem with your past memory
You've lost them
Look at all this clogged blood from you
You mean that's my blood
That's the only way to cure you
You devil!
Stop pinching into my head & my chest
Who the hell are you? Speak!
I'm not telling you
Speak! Who am I?
You're a Vietnamese refugee
illegal immigrant
I'm a refugee?
No, I don't believe you
Tell me the truth, who am I?
Go to sleep, my friend
Eight Hundred Dragon secret base
Good day, my friend
Wow, you always cook desserts
in the morning?
That's ink, pal
That can last my life?
Who's working so hard?
Your another savior
Come help me
Sure
Just the right thing for barbecue
Over my dead body
Take it easy, kid
Don't you have better things to do, Pearl
You still haven't told me about who I am
Your mother is a whore
And your father is just another
Vietnamese soldier
You still have six brothers & sisters
My mom is a whore
And my dad is a nameless soldier
and six brothers & sisters?
If my mom's a whore then isn't my dad
a pervert?
That means I'm the son of a bitch.
Damn it
Hello
What? Watch me well
Starting tomorrow, you'll have to work
like this
Why should I listen to you?
You think you're god
Look at you
You've the most obnoxious face
I've ever seen
You've an obsolete style of clothing
and the height of a dwarf
For a while I thought you're Frankenstein
I'm telling you. I'm leaving-for Vietnam
Be my guest
Sure enough
Watch out, pal
My goodness,
who the hell are these characters
Damn old fool. Why are you locking
one of my feet?
Because my feet is locked to the other end
of the lock
Alright then, but I'd rather be locked
with Pearl
Thanks a lot! But I prefer freedom
to being "imprisoned"
That's right! I'm imprisoned here
You'd be glad, you're in the biggest jail
on Earth
I'm not staying. I'm leaving for Vietnam
Hey, wrong direction, Vietnam should be
over there on the other side
I have to go home
My mom is a whore. Dad's a pervert
I even got six brothers & sisters
what a bastard I am
I gotta go back to Vietnam
My mom is a whore. Dad's a pervert
I even got six brothers & sisters
what a bastard I am
My mom is a whore. Dad's a pervert
I even got six brothers & sisters
what a bastard I am
I gotta go back to Vietnam
Watch out for traps
I have six brothers & sisters
Dad's a bastard and mom's a pervert
I'm going to Vietnam, my dad's a bastard
Mom's a pervert & I've got 6 brothers
and sisters
I gotta go back to Vietnam
Watch out, my friend
My dad's a bitch & I've got 6 brothers
Damn it, this thing is wired
What happen?
The fence is electrified
How big is it?
It covers the whole forest
Has any fool been caught before?
No, you're the first fool
Hey, what's happening to me?
The old fool is pulling you at your back
Watch out for traps
So I'm dead meat
Watch out!
Oh, my goodness, help
What are you searching for?
My mom, damn it
Over there, then go
What do you mean?
Didn't you say you want your mom?
You old bastard, you'd better let me go
right away
You young "bastard"
I guess you'd better stay
He's the boss, pal
Birdie, don't go
Come on, don't play hide & seek with me
Silly girl, playing with a bird all night
See? Where to go, Birdie?
And the old fool's been strolling all night
A funny girl & an old fool...
Everything is so unreal here
Where exactly am I?
Could I be dead already?
What do you want, old fool?
What's going on?
Let me down
Damn you, why are you tying me up here
To sleep
What? This is called "murder"
Don't you understand?
No. This is good for your health
Good for my health,
the biggest bull shit I've ever heard
Where do you folks sleep?
Don't you have proper beds?
No, we don't
How about the one I slept on last night?
Burned to ashes
Idiots
And now what?
See whether you'll respond
Of course I will, I'm still alive
Your're all crazy!!
Just why are you staring at me, kid?
See how long you can withstand, pal
My waist is going to break
Of all my students
You're the one with the worst sleeping manner
Sleeping manner
I salivate, so what!
Smells good
Gee, you use your feet for cooking
I've to, or we'll have nothing for dinner
I wasn't even allowed to think about
dinner when I first arrived
Of course, I can tell from your height
that you were deprived
Your skeleton should be around 5'7"
However, you're now only 4'11. 5'
That old man is bad
If he uses two hands to walk
It means that he moves like crocodiles
If you can't interchange the function
of your limbs
It's better not to use them at all
Bull shit
Come on, eat
Sure
It's delicious
It stinks
Run, pal
Don't you want to unreel it first?
Potatoes only?
Stop complaining! This one is already
hard to get
Don't be mean. I'm sure you can get
something else
Bird's meat would be great
Don't even think about it.
Hey, I just said "bird",
I didn't say "Birdie" did I?
How come you like Birdie more than me
Of course, so stop talking or I'll stop stealing
food for you
I'll fart after I eat potato
May be you won't come, try and see
I'll fell better if both of us fart
You're terrible
Didn't you fart?
No, I didn't
and you didn't either
That means... Who did it?
Who else? I did
Shit!
Let him go, I stole the potatoes
What did I do wrong again?
You eat without being permitted
Let me down. I formally challenge you
for a duel
Shut up
Come on, a duel
Think before you say, you want a duel
You coward!
I know you'll chicken out
Not bad yelling so much,
after all these hours of hanging up side down
Go and fetch the old bastard
Old bastard! I'm going to kill you!
How would you like to fight, old fool?
Take this
With this? You're dead meat
Come on
Watch out, old fool, don't blink!
Are you dancing or exercising?
I'm not eating tonight
If I can't beat you
Pearl
Ok, I'll eat a little
Before we fight
What sort of food is this?
Shut up
Pick a color! Red or white
Red of course, that's my lucky color
Whatever color you pick
You are fated to lose tonight
Come on...
Not bad, at least you look like
a civilized african
What's so funny about that?
Remember you say you'd not eat
if you couldn't beat me
I mean what I said
But my body doesn't agree
Yeah, crocodile walk, yeah
How dare you come in
while I'm bathing
Would you stop staring?
You don't have to check me out
I'm just a normal guy
Don't be hysterical.
I do this to old Master all the time
Big deal. How do I know?
If he's male or female?
Come on, have some, he won't notice
No, I have to keep my word
Tough
If you want to find out about yourself,
If you want to leave
Then you must learn from me
If I learn from you?
Wow... Seen everything!!! Not bad
What are we rushing for?
Food, there'll be nothing left
if we don't rush
What's he doing now?
Frying walnuts
He uses his hands to fry walnuts?
Have one
It's hot
There must be some tricks here
Either in his hands or in the pan
Why don't you find out yourself
Try
Whatever you say
Put some effort into it.
Didn't I tell you? You just didn't listen
The trick must be in his hands
Of course not, I'd have known
if there is any
Don't fool me
So this is our dinner tonight?
That is if you fry them well
Big deal, watch me
Do I look that stupid?
You've to learn to see with your heart
Instead of your eyes
And be able to face any enemy regardless
of where you are
Listen with the heart, see with the heart
Detect the enemy, beat the enemy
Concentrate! Or else how can you
possibly win?
I must win
* My morale is being boosted *
* My blood is burning from within *
* I must break through darkness
and start my eternal fight against tyranny *
* That I will try my best
to uphold the righteousness *
* I'll do whatever I can
to make my dream care true *
* A free man *
* To be a free man *
The pain proves that I'm still human
What are you doing?
Good thing! I'm cooking the bird
I've saved half for you
How dare you! You cook Birdie
Of course I won't
God knows I didn't
Pearl
Birdie!
Pearl, listen, I didn't cook your Birdie
Don't go there, electric fence's over there
Birdie
Watch out,
Silly girl, why are you crying?
Birdie died?
Guess what's this?
Birdie
No, it's not. Birdie is not Indian
What? Wrong color?
Well it's not quite white or gray
Go back down, leave me alone
Look, Birdie knows you miss him too
Hello, Birdie
- Please hold for me.
- Okay.
Why did you let Birdie go?
He's not Birdie, Birdie's here
He's like us too. Searching for freedom
Where are you going?
A Place where both Birdie & I
always wanted to go
I'll release you too once I know how
Dead Master is training somebody
to go against me and kill
Have you heard anything about this iately?
I've long lost touch with him
I don't know
If he really has that man
Then the dead Master will soon be strong
We have to stop this
You mean you want to kill him
If I don't kill him
He will kill me in return
He will never let me go
Don't forget. You've not alone
I betrayed him as well
I've shut off the electric fence
and wear this clothes
I'll cover you.
Old fool won't even notice it
Aren't you two going to sleep?
- Go...
- How about you?
I'll be fine, go
Shut up, go to sleep
- Pearl, hurry up.
- Go. Pal... go!
And remember
When you find your way out,
you have to return to set me free
- I promise I will! - Don't forget!
Off I go! Take care
How could you do this to me?
Don't blame me, clear?
You send for help? I know how to
send for help too!
Master!
Not bad, old fool, you've got quite some help
What happen to you, Pearl?
I purposely come back for you
Pearl, listen to me,
Beside Birdie
You've also got a family here
That's me, your pal
Didn't you always call me pal?
Pearl... Listen to me!!
Beside Birdie, you've still got...
Pearl!, Pearl!
Master are you alright?
I was injured
Listen, you must bring Yao away
I'll catch up with you later
Who are you?
The Dead Master
Who exactly are you?
You don't have to know me
You just come with me
Who are you? Where's Pearl
and the Master?
The organization wants them dead
They won't live long anyway
Eight Hundred Dragon never killed
an innocent
What bull shit organization
How could you be so cruel?
To kill people even if it's an old lady
The enemy is an enemy. It doesn't matter
if it's a he or a she
You have to learn to be more obedient
For the sake of the old Master and
The Eight Hundred Dragon?
You have to obey the organization
I only want to know who I am
You've become a assassin of the Eight
Hundred Dragon
The secret of who you are
will become your best drive
With immediate effect, you are one of us
You're called Freeman
Your first target is to kill
Hong Kong person, Lee Fung