Lornsome night.
Babbits bawlin', wind bitin' the bone.
Wind like this...
full of voices.
Ancestry howlin' at ya,
yibberin' stories.
All voices... tied up in't'one.
One voice different...
One voice,
whisperin' out there,
spyin' from the dark.
That fangy devil,
Ol' Georgie himself.
Now you hear up close,
and I'll yarn you about
the first time we met,
eye to eye.
And thus it was that I made the
acquaintance of Dr. Henry Goose,
the man I hoped might
cure me of my affliction.
Have you lost something?
Question one.
What secret in Sixsmith's report
would be worth killing for?
Question two.
Is it reasonable to believe that they
would kill again to protect that secret?
And if so, question three.
What the fuck am I doing here?
While my extensive
experience as an editor
has lead me to a disdain for flashbacks
and flashforwards, and all
such tricksy gimmicks,
I believe that if you, dear reader,
can extend your patience
for a just a moment,
you will find there is a method
to this tale of madness.
My dearest Sixsmith,
I shot myself through the roof
of my mouth this morning,
with Vyvyan Ayrs' Luger.
A true suicide is a paced,
disciplined certainty.
People pontificate "suicide
is an coward's act".
Couldn't be further from the truth.
Suicide takes tremendous courage.
Any problem, sir,
you just hit this button.
Thank you.
On behalf of my Ministry,
and the future of Unanimity,
I would like to thank you
for this final interview.
– Hello.
– Press pass.
Expecting trouble?
I was Dermot Hoggins' publisher,
not his shrink or his astrologer,
and the ruddy, bloody truth is,
I had no idea what the man
was gonna do that night.
This beach was once
a cannibal's banqueting hall,
where the strong gorged on the weak,
but the teeth, sir, they spat out,
like you or I would
expel a cherry stone.
Do you know the price a quarter
pound of these will earn?
Remember this is not
an interrogation or a trial.
Your version of the truth
is all that matters.
Truth is singular.
Its "versions" are... mistruths.
Don't let them say
I killed myself for love.
Had my infatuations, but we
both know in our hearts
who is the sole love
of my short, bright life.
CLOUD ATLAS
Transcript and sync: jcdr
PACIFIC ISLANDS, 1849
There you are, Mr. Ewing,
as binding a covenant
there can ever be between men...
outside the province of Scripture.
Thank you, Reverend Horrox, I...
know my father-in-law is
profoundly excited about this deal.
Haskell Moore is a great man.
Future generations depend
on men like him,
men capable of speaking the truth.
Quite.
When I first encountered
Haskell Moore's writing,
its perspicuity stroke me as though
delivered through divine revelation.
The learned doctor here and I,
already spent many a night
debating Mr. Moore's tractus.
I'm only willing to conceive
that he makes a compelling case
as to why we are sitting here,
enjoying this divine lamb,
while Kupaka stands
there, contempt to serve.
Indeed, ain'it.
Uh, Kupaka...
you enjoy your life here
with us, do you not?
Oh, yes, Reverend, sir.
Kupaka very happy here.
See, you see, this is Moore's
ladder of civilization.
The reason behind this natural order...
Please, Giles, do shut up.
I've been listening to
this for weeks, I...
would love to know what his own
son-in-law has to say about it.
Let's see...
It is an inquiry concerning
God's will and the nature of men.
And what does he have to say
about the nature of women?
I'm afraid that's a subject
he prefers to pass by in silence.
He wouldn't be the first.
Uh, prey, Mr. Ewing, continue.
Well, uh... the question
he does pose is...
if God created the world, how do
we know what things we can change,
and what things must remain
sacred and inviolable?
Reverend Horrox' real specific
how to run plantation.
Georgian way best way he say.
God, this heat is unbearable.
How do they take it?
Reverend Horrox say
slaves like camel, bred for desert.
He say... they not feel
heat like civilized folk.
Now we should get you out of the sun.
Now what... what is that noise?
– Ah, there you are.
– What happened?
It is as I suspected.
Gusano Coco Cervello,
better known as the Polynesian worm.
Once saw a man's brain after
the worm had finished with him...
maggoty cauliflower. Ooph.
But have no fear, this particular
devil and I... are well acquainted.
Here we go.
Ah, yes, yes, all gone.
I-I don't know what I would have
done had our paths not crossed.
Well for starters, you would have died.
I... I shall find a way to repay you.
Oh, unnecessary, I assure you.
I am a doctor, Adam.
A tiger cannot change its stripes.
CAMBRIDGE, 1936
Sixsmith, I do hope you will be able
to find it in your heart to forgive me.
Mr. Frobisher.
Mr. Robert Frobisher!
The management would like
a word with you, please, sir.
Mr. Frobisher, open this door, please!
I do know you're in there, Mr. Frobisher,
please, comply.
A letter is being drafted
to your father, sir.
Mr. Frobisher!
Hated leaving you like that.
Wasn't the goodbye I had in mind.
By the time you read this,
I will be on my way to Edinburgh,
on my way to fame and fortune.
I know you haven't heard of him,
but trust me,
Vyvyan Ayrs is one of
the musical greats, Sixsmith.
The tragedy is that he hasn't produced
any new work in years due to illness.
My scheme is to persuade him
to hire me as his amanuensis,
and aid him in the creation
of a masterpiece,
before shooting up through
the musical firmament,
eventually obliging
Pater to admit that yes,
the son he disinherited is none
other than Robert Frobisher,
the greatest British composer of his time.
I know, Sixsmith, you groan and
shake your head, but you smile too,
which is why I love you.
P.S.:
Thanks for the waistcoat.
I needed something of yours
to keep me company.
St. George and the Dragon.
Reminds me that composing is a crusade.
Sometimes you slay the dragon,
sometimes the dragon slays you.
Alright, then.
Frobisher, is it?
I trust Mackerras told
you enough to be useful.
I've had this little melody for viola
rattling about my head for months,
let's see if you can get it down.
Subtle grace note before the third.
Soft and simple. Got it?
Now, it gets interesting.
Good.
Play that back.
Would love to, sir.
Um... what key are we in?
What key?
G minor, of course.
And the time signature?
For Christ's sake, did you hear it or not?
– Just... just need a little more time.
– You need?
My dear boy, who is working for whom here?
– I apologize, sir...
– Are you an amanuensis or an apologist?
Now pay attention.
Three-four, changes to
four-four on fourth bar
and back to three-four on bar five,
if you can count that high.
Crotchet G, pause for a quaver, repeat
G quaver, then E-flat on the down beat.
And so on.
Alright, let me hear you.
Stop, please! You're hurting me!
You must have misheard me,
I said I had a melody not a malady!
Vyvyan...
Jocasta, deliver me!
– What's going on in here?
– An exercise in futility.
Should I be introduced?
There's really no point,
the boy is useful as the clap.
Fortunately, he'll be much
easier to get rid of.
Would you be a dear
and get Henry to show the boy out.
Yes, of course, darling.
That's beautiful.
Yes...
That's it.
That's my melody!
SAN FRANCISCO, 1973
Com'on, Luisa, we're made to be together!
Luisa, Luisa, com'on, com'on,
I'm telling you,
I'm telling you baby,
you can't leave me. It's a...
Don't know if it's a past life thing
or a future life thing,
but you know, you and me...
Look. For the last hour, all I could think
about was throwing you off the balcony.
Well then who the hell you think you are?
You write a bullshit
column for a fucking rag.
Elevator!
Thank you.
Nice to know the age
of chivalry isn't dead.
You okay?
No bones broken, I think.
No, no, no, you sit... you sit yourself.
Let me see.
Great. Power outage.
Perfect end to a perfect day.
Still glad the age of chivalry isn't dead?
I'd still rather be right here
than back up there.
Guess Mr. Kipin isn't
everyone's cup of tea.
Guys like that are just
an occupational hazard.
– You were interviewing him?
– Yeah, for Spyglass magazine.
Luisa Rey.
Rufus Sixsmith.
Rey...
You wouldn't happen to be related
to the journalist Lester Rey?
Yeah.
He was my father.
Really? He must have been
enormously proud of you,
– following in his footsteps.
– Hmm.
That's her. My niece, Megan.
She's lovely!
Born physicist, with a better mind
for mathematics than I ever had.
Did her PhD at Cambridge,
a woman at Caius!
Gives you hope for the world.
It's hot.
And we're still here.
That's a very peculiar birthmark.
Yeah.
My little comet.
My mother was sure it was cancer,
she wanted me to get it removed, but...
don't know. I kinda like it.
I knew someone who had
a birthmark that was...
– similar to that.
– Really?
Who was it?
Someone I cared about very much.
A uh... a hypothetical
question for you, Miss Rey.
As a journalist,
what price would you pay
to protect the source?
Any.
Prison?
If it came to that, yes.
Would you be prepared to...
compromise your safety?
My father braved booby-trapped marshes and
the wrath of generals
for his journalistic integrity.
What kind of daughter would I be if I
bailed when things got a little tough?
Saved.
Taxi!
– You sure you don't need a cab?
– No, I've got my car.
Well, you know if... there's ever
something I can do for you,
please give me a call.
Thank you, I will.
Bye.
LONDON, 2012
It was the night of the Lemon Prizes,
and in its two lead forced duality,
I recall a moment of introspection.
Why. Why would anyone in their
right mind choose to be a publisher?
This was the precise moment
that Dermot found me.
– Oy, Timothy.
– Aah, Dermot.
Bad news inexorably does.
Fockin' waste.
Never forget Herman Melville,
writes a ripping yarn about a big white
whale which is summarily dismissed,
and yet today, it is lugged
around in the backpacks
of every serious student
of literature in the world.
I don't give a fock what
happens when I'm dead,
I want people to buy me book now!
Well, as your publisher, obviously
nothing would make me happier.
But sadly, for whatever reason,
"Knuckle Sandwich" has yet
to connect to its audience.
You want a reason? I'll give you a reason.
– Right there!
– Aah. You mean Mr. Finch?
Felix fockin' Finch!
That cunt that shat all over me book
in his poncy fockin' magazine!
– It wasn't that bad!
– No?
"Mr. Hoggins should apologize to
the trees failed for the making of his
bloated autobio novel.
Four hundred vain-glorious pages
expire in an ending that is flat
and inane beyond belief."
Steady now, Dermot. What is a critic
but one who reads quickly,
arrogantly, but never wisely.
Fock it.
Dermot!
Ladies and gentlemen!
We have an additional award tonight,
fellow book faeries.
An award for "most eminent critic".
Mr... oh, beg pardon,
SIR! Felix Finch.
O, B and E!
And what might my prize be, I wonder?
A signed copy of an
unpulped "Knuckle Sandwich"?
Can't be many of those left.
Well...
Just what does that lead-less
pencil you call an imagination
have in mind to end this scene. Hmm?
I think you're gonna love this one.
Now, that's an ending that is
flat n'inane beyond belief.
My thoughts?
If I'm honest, I admit that the
obvious emotions like shock
and horror flew as Finch had,
here and gone.
Tequila, couple of fingers.
While deep down,
I experienced a nascent sense
of a silver lining to
this most tragic turn.
Overnight, Dermot "Dusty" Hoggins
became a cult hero to the common man.
"Knuckle Sandwich" shifted ninety
thousand copies in less than two months.
I was for the briefest
of moments, Cinderella,
and all memory of past misfortune
receded in the rearview mirror
of my dream come true.
– What the fuck...
– Tim-o-tee Cavendish... oy presume.
Caught wi' your cacks down!
Uh, my office hours are eleven to two,
and my secretary
would be more than happy to schedule
an appointment if you so desire.
Friends like us don't
need appointments.
We like it all cozy like this.
– Visited Dermot in the joint.
– Our brother's got a question for you.
Where's our focking money?
Boys. Boys, look here.
Dermot signed what we call
a copyright transfer contract,
which means that legally...
Dermot didn't sign a fockin' contract
for the event of a fockin' season!
Er, Perhap-perhaps... er, we could
moot a provisional sum...
as a basis for on-going negotiation.
Okeydokey.
What sum we gonna moot?
Fifty K will do for starters.
Fifty sounds reasonable.
Tomorrow afternoon.
Tomorrow afternoon?
– Cash.
– No bullocks.
– No checks.
– Old fashioned money.
Gentlemen...
– The law says...
– The law?!
What'd the law do
for Felix fockin' Finch?
NEO SEOUL 2144
Ordinarily, I begin by asking prisoners
to recall their earliest memories...
to provide a context for the
corporatic historians of the future.
Fabricants have no such
memories, Archivist.
One twenty-four hour cycle in Papa
Song's is identical to every other.
May I say you speak
Consumer surprisingly well.
[speaks Korean]
It is unfortunate that the officials of
the Unanimity can only speak one language.
As an officer of Unanimity, I am of
course restricted from using sub speak.
Of course.
Please describe a typical
twenty-four hour Papa Song cycle.
At hour four, each server
is woken by auto-stimulin.
From revival, we proceed to the hygiener.
After dressing, we file into the dinery.
At hour five, we man our stations
to greet the new day's consumers.
Welcome to Papa Song's.
For the next nineteen hours,
we input orders, tray food, vend drinks,
upstock condiments, wipe tables,
and bin garbage,
all done in strict adherence
to First Catechism.
What is the First Catechism?
"Honor Thy Consumer."
After the final cleaning,
we imbibe one soap sack
and return to our sleep box.
That is the blueprint
of every single day.
Did you ever think about the future?
Papa Song servers have
just one possible future.
You mean "Exultation".
Could you describe this
annual Rite of Passage?
On first day, Seer Rhee would
stamp a star on each of our collars.
Twelve stars meant an end to our contract.
How did you feel when you watched
one of your sisters ascend?
Excitement.
I was happy for them,
but envious as well.
Did your sister servers feel as you did?
Most of them.
I would like to ask about
the infamous Yoona-939.
If Yoona-939 woke you,
who woke her?
Seer Rhee.
Why would Seer wake a server?
Perhaps you should ask him, Archivist.
What's wrong with him?
He drinks soap.
It makes him happy.
Then he sleep like us in our box.
Do you ever think about... what it must
be like, up there with the consumers?
Third Catechism forbids such questions.
Yes. It does.
Come. Let me show you a secret.
Platform four, Lost and Found.
Now... Sonmia,
we are inside a secret.
A Kino?
– We are not allowed.
– Sonmia, no one will ever know.
Come.
This is a violation of the
ruddy Incarceration Act!
I will not be subjugated
to criminal abuse.
This is a violation of the
ruddy Incarceration Act!
I will not be subjugated
to criminal abuse.
You could have been excised.
How did you justify
such a risk to yourself?
She was my friend.
Please describe the events of
September 18th from your perspective.
I was stationed at pedestal one.
I will not be subjugated
to criminal abuse!
Step away. Code yellow,
the area is secured.
Hawaiian Islands
106 WINTERS AFTER THE FALL
Nay, this life all rot n' lockin'
no smile a' some yawnee.
In rear's time, I ever fest
the secret of Sloosha's hallow.
Adam, my bro' by law, n' his son n' me
been trekkin' back from Honokaa Market.
It was Adam's custom to cult out
his ancestry with offerin's n' honorin's.
Suddenwise, that fangy
devil's eyes, I felt'em.
Who there?
Ooh, a darky spot you're in, friend.
Ol' Georgie...
Ain't no blade can protect you
from the True-True.
'Pa!
Jonas. Jonas, go.
Go, go!
Zachary!
Zachary?
Zachary!!
Stay here, safe here...
Kona will be feastin' on Adam
n' his boy by sunup.
You say it all the time, ain'ya?
"The Weak are Meat, the Strong do Eat."
The True-truth, what that is.
Whole valley whisperin' about
the blood o' Adam and his son on my hands.
But Rose and Catkin never
believed those rumors, and stood by me.
– Uncle Zach, look!
– Yeah, I see them.
Prescients come batterin' twice a year,
their ships creep-crawlin' on the waves,
just floatin' on the Smart o' the Old Uns.
Barter'll be startin' soon.
Yeah. We must go find ya' Ma.
What are you doin'?
Ma says ya ain't been
right since Sloosha's.
She say we gotta keep out our eyes on ya.
You mindin' me, while I mind the goats?
I see.
Stump is, who's gonna mind
your Ma at the Barter?
She got no tongue for hagglin',
not like you and me.
Sure you alright?
Swear by. Be home for suppin'.
Why words slink n' slide off a tongue,
when we need them most?
If my tongue'd been more bold,
could I have stopped all that
diresome's about to happen?
– Uncle Zach!
– Thi's my big bro I yawned you about.
– What's about, sis?
– Special guest hosting.
Thank you for the kindsome hostin'
in the Valley's day.
I ain't saysoe this, Rose.
– Abbess saysoe a gift of great honor.
– She can be hostin' then?
I brin' you gift, Zachry.
Need no gift from the stranger.
Now kin n' bros n' half-strangers, yay,
even the Abbess, they all come knockin',
they gaped in wonderment like
Sonmi herself was sittin' in our kitchen.
Questions about Prescience n' their
whoahsome Ship poured thick n'fast.
How your ship's slidin',
glides so silent n'...
Fusion engines.
No one queried what fusion engine was,
cos they didn't want to look
stupid in front o' the gatherin'.
Fusion engines...
True really was, Meronym
answered the questions,
but no answer ever quenched your curio.
All o' that answerin' done was
teach everyone to not trust her,
nay, not a flea...
She's lyin'....
Schemin' and wormin' herself in.
Watch her, watch her close.
She's got secrets.
Zachry Bailey?
Sorrysome for wakin'
you up but... a dream.
Some diresome's gonna happen.
Come in, come in.
Ooh, let Sonmi guide your heart.
Ohh, I gonna hear it for us,
I'm prayin' for you.
Ooh, Old Georgie's
hungerin' for your soul.
Ooh, I knew it.
Spit a cuss on your dreams.
"Bridge is broken, hide below"
"Hands are bleedin', can't let go"
"Enemy's sleepin', don't slit that throat"
An augurin'...
Trust Sonmi...
Keep her warnin' with you,
nail it to your memory.
Thank you. Thank you, Abbess.
Thank you.
Wait! Wait.
There's... no reason to hide.
I know you are... Sonmi-451.
My name is... Hae-Ju Zheng.
What has happened to Seer Rhee?
Soap overdose.
It is unfortunate that it had to happen
with everything gone so well.
Cos now it is probable
that the Enforcers
and the DNA sniffers
will find out about you.
And if they do...
if they realize your connection
to Yoona-939, you will be excised.
But you have a choice.
You can remain here
and risk being discovered,
or you can come with me.
– Bear away, boy.
– Aye, aye captain.
Friday the 15th. We made sail
with the morning tide.
Mr. Boerhaave had my cabin changed.
I have been quarantined to a store room
away from the other passengers and crew.
Henry argued in vain that the
Polynesian worm was not contagious.
Not that it matters.
All I want to do now is return home
and unburden myself
from this responsibility.
My dear Sixsmith, I am in
desperate need of your help.
After my last letter, I'm sure
you're rushing to pack your bags,
but you needn't, really.
Unless of course, you wish to witness
the rebirth of Robert Frobisher.
Is it not miraculous how one's fortune
can turn so quickly, so completely.
One moment, leaping from
a hotel window, the next
gainfully employed by one of the
world's greatest living composers.
My only problem is that I
accidentally got hooked on a journal
written in 1849 by a dying
lawyer during the voyage
from the Pacific islands
to San Francisco.
To my great annoyance,
the pages cease mid-sentence.
Half the book is missing.
It's completely killing me.
Could you be a mensch and when
you're next foraging
at Otto's Book's, make an inquiry?
A half finished book is, after all,
a half finished love affair.
America loves oil.
America is addicted to oil.
Some fantasize about
wind turbines or peat gas.
But I'm here today to
tell you that the cure
for oil is right here.
The cure is nuclear power.
The cure is Swannekke.
Hello, Miss Rey. I'm frightfully
sorry for calling you at this hour.
Dr. Sixsmith?
I need help.
I need £ 50,000, not 2,000, 50,000!
I'm going through it again,
Mr. Cavendish, but the total's right.
2,343 pounds and 16 pence.
How is this possible?
The ruddy money was pouring in.
Debts mostly, Mr. Cavendish.
Solvency has its drawbacks.
The situation looked dire,
but I knew that Timothy
Cavendish's capital in this town
could not be defined by
an accountant's balance sheet!
McCluskie!
Look, how are those
delightful kiddies of yours?
Mon cher, tis "Cavendish the Ravenous,"
your favorite Timothy.
Mon cher?
You heard it correctly,
Charles Dickens' own original
authentic writing desk for £ 60,000.
I think that's very fair.
But our records indicate that the
desk is already accounted for
by the Dickens House Museum.
Okay, what about
Sir Arthur Conan Doyle's desk?
In the darkness, I suddenly saw the light.
Blood has always trumped water.
If the Hogginses brutes wanted
to turn this into a family affair,
they'd find the Cavendish Clan
more than ready for the task at hand.
Oh, Satan's gonads, not again.
Look,
just bugger off and leave us in peace.
I'm only gonna asking you nicely once.
Good to see you, Denny.
I'm not lending you a ruddy farthing
until you pay back the last lot.
Why-Why should I be forever
giving you a hand out?
Denny...
I had a minor running with the wrong sort.
If I don't get my hands on £ 60,000,
I got to get an awful beating.
Well, get them to video it for us,
would you? Now fuck off.
– I'm not joking, Denholme.
– Why is this my problem?
Because we're brothers!
Don't you have a conscience?
Couple of my special little pills
and a G&T should just set me right.
Denny. Help.
Please.
Den, who are you talking to?
– Hello, Georgette.
– Hello, Timothy.
Right. Right, right.
What did you-60 grand?
It's gonna take some time, but, uh...
in the interim, I've got
the perfect place for you to hide.
I begun to fear I might never hold
my beloved Tilda in my arms again.
My parasite writhes at night,
igniting spasms of pain,
while visions and voices,
obscene and monstrous, haunt me.
Mister Ewing...
In the name of God!
Mister Ewing, no fear.
No harm, no shout.
Please.
My name Autua.
You know I... see Maori whip I...
You know I.
– What do you want?
– You help, Mr. Ewing.
If you no help, I in trouble dead.
Well, you're already
very much "in trouble dead."
The Prophetess is a mercantile vessel,
not an underground railroad
for escaping slaves.
I be able seaman, I earn passage.
Well, then I suggest you surrender
to the captain's mercies forthwith.
No, no. They no hear I.
They say "swim away home, nigger",
and throw I in drink, but you...
you law man, right? Please.
Captain hear you, Mr. Ewing.
I-I can't help you.
I'm afraid your fate is entirely
your own, and I desire no part in it.
Then kill I.
Don't be absurd...
If you no help, you kill I just the same,
is true. You know it.
I ain't be no fish food, Mr. Ewing.
Die here better.
Do it.
Do it quick.
I found an old transway marker, Captain.
It's got to be the red mountain.
The problem is, the valley
people are afraid of it.
They think the Devil lives up there.
I can't find anybody to guide me
through the Kona territory.
Meronym...
Every day you're out there,
you increase your RAD levels.
This dream of yours is going to kill you.
And for what?
The Off-World colonies
may no longer exist.
I got to go, Captain.
Thank you for coming, I'm in 1404.
I'll be right up.
Dr. Sixsmith?
It's me, Luisa.
Go call the police.
Right now, call the police!
My dear Sixsmith, you alone can
understand how I'm feeling right now.
Today, Ayrs and I presented our first
collaboration to Tadeusz Kesselring,
Ayrs favorite conductor
who arrived from Berlin.
It's called "eternal recurrence".
Wish you could hear it.
It's the most accomplished tone poem
I know of written since the war,
and I tell you, Sixsmith,
that more than of the few
of its best ideas are mine.
At our time of life, Ayrs,
a man has no right to such daring ideas.
I suppose I've won a rearguard action
or two in my war against decrepitude.
Diner of pheasant with
Bordeaux rich as buttercream.
How I love to listen to men
of distinguished lives,
sing of past follies and glories.
The only broken note in the entire
evening was Ayrs wife, Jocasta,
excusing herself early.
Sensed the buried bone.
Later I asked Ayrs about it.
He said Kesselring had
introduced Jocasta to him.
I pried, had Kesselring
been in love with her?
The subject was a prickly one.
Jocasta is a Jew.
Obviously her relationship was impossible.
Why obviously?
Can you really be so ignorant
of what is happening in Germany?
At this point in my life,
all I know, Sixsmith,
is that this world spins
from the same unseen forces
that twist our hearts.
– How is it, Mr. Zachry?
– Thin whiles.
– Minding some company?
– Nay.
But...
Goats, and so do herders,
they're known for housin' temper.
Feelin' that own n' your reveal count out,
for invadin' your house with no saysoe.
True sorrysome.
Well it... Now it's done.
So, you mindin' a stranger
coverin' about your thrivin'?
Swap you. Query for query.
Fair buy.
Cog you and come dow.
Learn stitchin' n' milkin' our heardin'.
Why you here?
I needin' a guide.
Guide? To where?
Mauna Sol.
"Bridge is broken, hide below"
What's wrong?
We cross and recross
our old tracks like figure skaters.
And just as I was reading
a new submission,
a powerful déjà-vu ran through my bones.
I had been here before.
Another lifetime ago.
Ursula.
The love of my life.
I could think of no other
serious applicants.
What had happened to her?
And more importantly,
what had happened to the young man
who had ridden the same train
composing sonnets,
to his so bound a love.
Your augurin' come true, Abbess.
Broke bridge, just like you say.
Meronym were there, yebberin' about
trackin' up Mauna Sol,
why can this Prescient woman
come cursin' n' twistin' on my life?
Mind the words of Sonmi.
"Our lives are not our own.
From womb to tomb, we are bound to others.
Past and present.
And by each crime...
and every kindness...
we birth our future."
Welcome to Neo Seoul.
Come on, out you come.
This... maybe the biggest mistake
of my life, but here.
Thank you, Mr. Ewing.
Now to tell the truth, I was
worried you might try and eat me,
if you didn't get
something in the stomach.
Oh, you safe, Mr. Ewing.
I no like white meat.
Ah. Right.
Before I decide what
I'm going to do with you,
tell me why you were
being whipped so savagely?
My uncle was a sailor.
He took me on a French whaler
when I was ten years old.
Seen too much of the world.
I no good slave.
Why did you look at me?
Pain strong, aye.
Friend's eye more strong.
Look, you are a runaway slave,
and I am a lawyer.
How did you imagine
we could possibly be friends?
All you need.
Ah, Jesus!
Javier Gomez, what did I tell you
about jumping onto my balcony?
Why d'you leave the door open
if you don't want me to come in?
Because, smarty pants,
the only thing worse than having
you jumping onto my balcony,
is the idea of you jumping onto my
balcony, and being stuck out there.
Okay!
What are you reading?
Old letters.
Sixsmith, the plot has
taken a sensual turn.
Last week, Jocasta and I became lovers.
But don't alarm yourself, it is only
a carnal act, performed in service,
not unlike my role as amanuensis.
And I confess women's hearts like
their desire remain a mystery to me.
Afterward, she cried and thanked me
for bringing life back into their home.
I can get clear that Vyvyan
had been there the entire night,
between us like the silence between notes,
that holds the key to warm music.
P.S.: Best news of all,
I've started my own work.
Uh, I... called about an old recording,
written by a man named Robert Frobisher.
Oops. Busted.
I know I shouldn't be playing it, I was...
checking it to make sure
it wasn't scratched,
but... honestly,
I just can't stop listening to it.
This is the Cloud Atlas Sextet?
It's... the symphony.
It's beautiful.
but I think I've heard this before.
I can't imagine how.
I doubt there's no more than a... handful
copies in the whole of North America.
But I know it.
I know I know it.
Before I realized it, my feet had brought
me back to the Temple of Sacrifice,
where I offered up my virginity.
Back to those four-days of Paradise,
when Ursula's Mater and Pater
slift off to Greece,
for a long weekend...
Or so we thought.
Ursula!
Sir! Madam! I assure you
this is completely innocent...
Two sprained ankles, one cracked rib.
Official cause of accident,
listed on hospital form...
pussy.
What were the chances that
she still lived in this house?
And yet, there she was.
Ursula.
Why had I never returned
her calls or letters?
Shame, spinessless,
hallmarks of the Cavendish clan.
I realized I had a choice. I could
slink off and continue as planned,
or I could go boldly to the door,
and discover what hope,
if any, would lay within.
Abbess, come quick,
it's the Bailey girl.
– Catkin?
– Aye, she dyin'.
– What-what...
– Zach.
– Sonmi...
– It's scorpion fish.
Healer said she be gone by sundown.
Ain't right, ain't fair,
but nothing to be done.
Be very still.
Termination charge.
Here!
Just enough to blow your carotid.
How does it feel?
Good.
Catkin's dying!
– What?
– She trod on a scorpion fish.
You can save her.
You got spesh smart in that gearbag,
that'll save her.
That's the True-true!
Prescient Councils swear
by a special order.
Say I can't go play Lady Sonmi
for everythin' twistin' wrong,
and click fingers, make right.
I just a stupid goat herder but
I cog you're killin' Catkin by not actin',
just... by lettin' you up on that bridge,
you Kona meat.
If a Prescient be layin',
with poison meltin' her heart n'lungs?
If it be your kin?
Why the Precient's life worth
more than a Valleysman?!
I'll take you to Mauna Sol.
I know the way!
If you save Catkin,
I will guide you to the Devil's door,
if that's where you wanna go.
While the past may call to us
with the enchantment of a siren,
better, I believed, to stay
the course set by dear brother Den.
Just sign right here.
Tomorrow, life could begin
afresh, afresh, afresh.
This way.
Come.
Designating texture.
That's old Seoul.
If the tides keep rising
at their present rate,
Neo-Seoul will also be under
water in a hundred years.
Your food is in here.
It's not what you're used to,
but I think you will like it.
This is your bed...
These are your clothes.
Mine? But these are...
Pureblood clothes.
No. They are yours.
Did you know he was Union?
No, but it wouldn't have mattered.
Why not?
Because...
It was the first time
a Pureblood had showed me kindness.
I hungry.
Do you like them?
You look lovely.
Here...
Come here.
Now, this used to play Vidis,
but the chip is corrupted.
Stuck in a loop, so I digit it
and found the rest of it.
The rest of it?
...the bloody hell are
you doing in my room?
Keys... go walkies, let's give these
to Miss Judd for safekeeping, shall we?
Leave my things alone,
you pilvering cow.
Cause you're new, I shall not make
you eat soap powder, this time...
You're warned.
I cannot stand for offensive language
in our arrays, not from anyone.
And I never make idle threats,
Mr. Cavendish. Never.
I'll talk to you as I ruddy
will like, you thief!
Make me eat soap powder?
I'd like to see you try.
Ooh, bloody hell!
A disappointing start.
Is this some sort of kinky S&M hotel?
I am nurse Noakes,
you do not wish to cross me.
I am so sorry to keep you waiting.
Uh, I know it's a Miss...
Rey.
– Luisa Rey, Spyglass magazine.
– Right, right.
Luisa, this is Joe Napier,
our security chief.
I was surprised to get your query.
I mean, don't get me wrong,
it-it is a feisty magazine, but...
Anything you need,
sir, just let me know.
We'll do. Guys, I'm good,
thank you very much.
Our editor's trying to
spice things up a little bit,
he says the public wants
more substance, so...
Probably just a fad.
Come on, follow me, let's start
you with the Chicken Ranch.
That is where we keep the Eggheads.
Hello, Mr. Cavendish,
feeling super this morning?
No. I checked in last night,
believing that Aurora House was a hotel.
My brother made the booking you see,
his idea of a practical joke.
But listen, you have a bigger problem
closer to home.
There's some demented bitch
calling herself Noakes,
rampaging about the place,
impersonating a chamber maid.
But the point is this:
she struck me, and she stole my keys.
Right? I'll need those
keys back, straight away.
Aurora House is your home now,
Mr. Cavendish. Your signature
– authorizes us to apply...
– Signature?
The custody document
you signed last night.
Your residency papers.
Oh no, no, no. That was
the hotel register.
Ah, never mind, it's all academic, huh?
This is gonna make a hell
of a diner party story.
Most of our guests get cold feet
on their first mornings.
– My keys, please.
– Residents are not...
– I'm not a ruddy resident!
You'll find temper tantrums
won't help you at Aurora House!
You're breaking the... ruddy...
acting... conservation act,
or some ruddy thing,
and I will not be subjugated
to a criminal abuse.
I will not be subjugated
to criminal abuse.
Outside, fat snow flakes
are forming on slate roofs.
Like Solzhenitsyn laboring in Vermont,
I shall beaver away in exile.
Unlike Solzhenitsyn, I shan't be alone.
Off somewhere?
You bet I am.
To the land of the living.
Soylent Green is people.
Soylent Green is made of people!
Oy! Get back here, you!
You keep away from me, or
I'll be forced to name you,
in the police report, as an accomplice.
I have better things to do than this.
Then go, pit and do them,
you bloody sucker son of...
Right!
God, you take hands off me,
you ruddy bloody...
You can maintain power over people,
as long as you give them something.
Rob a man of everything, and that
man will no longer be in your power.
Alexander Solzhenitsyn,
20th century philosopher complete works,
banned by Unanimity.
How do you know about him?
Hae-Ju.
– Sir Zheng.
– Please, you must call me Hae-Ju.
Hae-Ju...
Fabricants can be excised for this...
Well, survival often demands some courage.
Knowledge is a mirror,
and for the first time in my life,
I was allowed to see who I was,
and who I might become.
Go clean the head.
Good morning, captain.
You can help it remain so,
Quillcock, by buggering off.
I'm afraid I can't do it, sir.
If I was, I would be unable
to inform you of the stow-away
– that I have discovered in my...
– Stow-away?
I assure you that this
Moriori had no choice.
Now he has sworn to me that he is
a first class, able bodied seaman,
capable of earning passage
if only given a chance.
A stow-away is a stow-away,
even if he shits silver nuggets.
Did he ever explain anything to you?
He told me their goal was
the creation of a free willed Fabricant.
Yoona had failed.
I was their last hope.
I have to say if all lady
journalists look like you,
I might start to take this, uh,
women's lib thing more seriously.
Well, I'm sure they can use your support.
Nice.
Okay, uh, you wait here and I will
go find someone smarter who can, uh,
walk you through the details
of some of your questions.
Great.
What would Dad do?
Who the bloody hell is this?
Have you any idea what time it is?
– Denny, it's me, Tim.
- Timothee?
Where are you?
Ah, I think you ruddy know
about where I am.
But residents are
denied access to phones.
Someone smuggled one in?
– You know the rules?
- I helped write them, Timmy.
I have been a principal investor
in Aurora House for twelve years,
it's incredibly lucrative.
You can't believe what people would pay
to lock-out their parents.
Look, Den, you've had your fun,
I think it's high time you put an end
to this little game of yours.
No, no, no, Timmy.
My fun has just begun.
What are you talking about?
I am your brother, why are
you doing this to me?
I think the better question is-would be,
what have you done to deserve this?
I don't know what you mean.
Oh come, naughty old brother,
don't insult me.
You can't think that I didn't know
about you and Georgette!
Georgette?
Look, Den...
I didn't mean to hurt you.
I'm afraid your penance
has come due, Timbo,
it's time to account for your crimes.
Den...
– I'm... I'm so, so sorry.
- No no no, there's
no need to apologize.
Your exile is more than enough reparation.
Oh, I do have my fingers crossed
for a scenario involving you,
nurse Noakes and a broom handle.
Cherry up, Timmy.
Bye bye now.
He sends his love.
I would like to ask about
the night of your arrest.
I remember...
listening to his heart beat.
Your heart beats much slower than ours.
There is a gentleness to the sound.
I find it... comforting.
– Vyvyan, what time is it?
– I don't know. Who cares...
I've heard a melody, boy.
For violin.
Quick...
Find-find a pen.
I heard it in a dream.
I was in a nightmarish café...
Blaring, bright lights,
but underground and no way out.
And the waitresses...
they all had the same face.
There was music playing, not like
any music I've ever heard in my life.
It began...
Wait...
It was so clear a minute ago.
Help me, Robert, help me.
It's slipping away!
I've lost it.
It'll come to you, sir.
The minute you stop trying
to find it, it will find you.
You are naive, Robert.
I am anything but.
There is a gulf between these chairs.
What you want is no different
from what I want.
The gulf is an illusion.
How do I describe that night, Sixsmith...
What had happened between
Vyvyan and I transcended language.
It was music that poured from his eyes,
and breathed from his lips.
Music as beautiful as any
I have ever heard.
What-what are you doing in here?
They found us.
I'll be with you the whole way,
now focus on me.
Stay with me.
Right here.
I won't let you go.
– Mr. Ewing.
– It-It's alright.
I-I talked to the captain,
he'll hear your case.
What's your name, boy?
Autua, sir.
This Christian gentleman,
who knows nothing about ships,
tells me that you're a first-class sailor.
Very well, let's see you'd
lower the main top, son.
Mr. Roderick, my bottle is empty.
Mr. Boerhaave, ready my piece.
What? Sir, you...
gave me your word, Captain.
P-Please, you can't do this.
Nobody tells me what I can
and cannot do on my own ship.
Specially when it concerns
nigger stow-away.
Captain look!
He's got fish-hooks for toes.
Boerhaave, you don't
make a mess of my deck.
Captain, please...
Look, if you can just hear me, I'm...
The darkie's salt as I am.
Mr. Boerhaave!
It appears we have an
addition to our crew.
Make sure he earns his keep.
Mr. Hooks.
I found her. She was in the chem labs,
looking for the bathroom.
Ah? Well, perfect, then, uh, why don't
you take over from here, Sachs,
you know, introduce our
little tribe, and uh...
and guide Ms. Rey through the...
through the tower.
The funny thing is, I am not
even supposed to be here.
I was meant to be in Seoul,
but the air traffic controller strike
put everything up, so now
I'm on the... time jumper tonight.
Did you ever think that
the universe was against you?
All the time.
You mind?
I'm cool.
You seem nervous, Isaac.
– Do I make you nervous?
– No.
Actually, just the opposite.
Will you gonna tell me
why you covered for me?
Freedom. The fatuous jingle
of our civilization.
But only those deprived of it have
the barest inkling of what it really is.
There's much disagreement
on what should be done with you.
The Corprocrats want you
euthanased as a deviant,
the Manufacturer is
demanding a period of study,
the Pyschogenomicists are screaming
for an immediate cerebral vivisection.
However, the problem you
create is a political one.
Which means you are my problem.
I find it intriguing
to imagine that beneath this...
perfectly engineered features, are thoughts
that terrify the whole of Unanimity.
I'm not afraid of such thoughts,
because I do not fear the truth.
There's a natural order
to this world, fabricant.
And the truth is this order
must be protected.
Inform the Archivist,
prepare for excisement.
– Yes sir.
– Sir...
Can you tell me what
happened to Hae-Ju Zheng?
Killed, I was told.
All this feast and excitements,
really Adam, it's...
all too much, you'll need to rest.
I had...
a girlfriend once, she kept trying
to get me to read Carlos Castenada.
– You ever read any o' that shit?
– Oh yeah.
But the relationship was doomed.
Every time she brought up a new...
karma, past-life stuff,
I-I couldn't stop myself from laughing.
And yet...
I can't explain it...
but I knew when I opened that door...
They destroyed most of
the copies of the report.
Most?
There's no good choice here, is there?
If I help you, I can lose my job...
or worse,
If I don't, a lot of people...
Yeah, it will be worse than worse.
You have to do...
whatever you can't not do.
Someone preyin' on you, Zachry?
You really ain't feary about meetin'
Ol' Georgie on the summit?
I'm more scaresome 'bout
the weather than in the Devil.
You cog he's real?
Who tripped the Fall,
if not Old Georgie?
True-true?
The Old Uns.
That's just a rope o'smoke.
Old Uns got the Smart.
They mastered sick and seeds,
they make miracles and fly across the sky.
True. All true.
But they got somethin' else.
A hunger in their hearts, a hunger
that's stronger than all their Smart.
Hunger? For what?
A hunger for more.
Belief like fear or love
is a force to be understood as we
understand the theory of relativity,
and principles of uncertainty.
Phenomena that determine
the course of our lives.
Yesterday, my life was
headed in one direction.
Today, it is headed in another.
Yesterday, I believed I would never
have done what I did today.
These forces that often
remake time and space,
they can shape and alter
who we imagine ourselves to be,
begin long before we are born,
and continue after we perish.
Our lives and our choices
like quantum trajectories are
understood moment to moment
at each point of intersection,
each encounter,
suggest a new potential direction.
Proposition:
I have fallen in love with Luisa Rey.
Is this possible?
I just met her, and yet...
I feel like something important
has happened to me.
That's it.
The music from my dream.
This is from my dream,
that night I came to your room.
This is the music I heard in my head,
somehow I gave it to you.
I've been working on
this piece for weeks now.
I suspect you heard it, and
incorporated it into your dream.
I call it the Cloud Atlas Sextet.
This is obviously the result
of our collaboration.
The Atlas, I believe,
is the only thing I've done
in my life that is of value.
But I know I could not have written it,
if I hadn't met you.
There are whole movements in
the Atlas that I wrote imagining us,
meeting again and again,
in different lives and different ages.
Yes...
Something as important as this
cannot be described as "yours" or "mine",
it is "ours".
That this is exactly how I feel, Vyvyan.
I'm sorry, I...
– I thought...
– You thought? You thought what?
That I might fancy a little buggering
from a fine young dandy like yourself?
I pack my bag, and be gone by morning.
You'll do no such thing, you'll leave
only when I say you can leave.
You will continue working
on Vyvyan Ayrs' Cloud Atlas.
When it is finished, then I will
decide what to do with you.
You can't keep me here!
I'm leaving!
Good luck with your composing.
I'm sure a sterile old fuck like yourself
is still capable of something
completely immemorable.
I suggest you think about this, Robert.
Think about reputation.
Reputation is everything in our society.
Yours, my disinherited reprobate,
has expired.
Did you not think that we would inquire
about someone living under our roof?
Mackerras himself wrote, and I quote:
"He is a prostitute whose liaisons
with perverts and sodomites
were common place in his brief
and forgettable career at Caius.
Lock up the silverware."
Unquote.
Be warned.
Leave here without my consent,
and all the musical society will know
of the degenerate Robert Frobisher.
After that,
even if you compose one of the
greatest symphonies ever written,
no one will hear it,
because no one will want
anything to do with you.
I won't let you go again.
I told you he'd come.
Two things became clear.
Hanging myself from Edinburgh's flagpole
is preferable to letting that parasite
plunder my talent a day longer.
I must complete my sextet.
I can't do it here,
so tonight I plan to make my escape.
Please stand by for vehicle scan.
Clearance granted.
Any jailbreak's a risky proposition.
One little cock-up, and we are
dangling at her majesty's pleasure.
I know, I know.
We could use code names,
but the truth is I'd probably
be the first to forget mine.
So, Mr. Cavendish...
Ernie Blancksmith.
This is Mr. Meeks
and my girl Veronica Costello.
– To trust.
I know, I know.
What about the parrot, then?
If ever that was a likely songbird.
Mr. Meeks is a fine and honorable
gentleman, he would never betray us.
Besides, no one's ever heard
him say anything else.
I know, I know.
Question is, old man,
think you're up to snuff?
Unanimity requires compliance.
We have a security code Red,
prepare to be boarded.
What are you going to do?
Stay calm, stay calm.
" It will end in tears."
You've warned me.
I suppose I'm as hopeless
as Adam Ewing,
oblivious towards the unspeakable
forms lying and waiting,
blind to the fact his friend
is poisoning him.
Wait, please...
The idea of losing this ring
distresses me beyond measure.
Don't be a silly puff here, Adam,
I'm sure your wife will set
your health above a golden loop.
I have seen the onset for dropsy
and it is not a pretty sight!
I know an excellent Spanish goldsmith,
who works with such alacrity,
that your Tilda may not have
to know this was ever removed.
– Give it to me!
– Get your fucking hands off my pudding!
It's not your pudding, you
Alzheimer riddled lout!
You've already eaten...
Better get in here.
Mr. Cavendish!
The room stank of bitter medicine.
Curiously heavy things, guns.
Why did I take it, exactly?
Can't say.
An intuition.
A sense of significance.
That from this point on...
there was no going back.
Just seein' them clouds,
we run out o' time.
– Don't need no smart rope.
– Yeah, see you fall,
I'll catch you.
Hands in the air. Now!
Move it, step off of the vehicle!
Get down.
Down, now!
Fuckin' migrant monkey-talk.
Why do they hire these greasy stubs?
Negative, sir.
Definite illegal.
You turn him from now.
I'm reading a second life form!
– Where?
– In the truck.
– Check it out.
– Yes, sir.
You troddin' on the Devil's ground now,
Valleysman.
I'm sayin' just once.
That off-lander ain't gettin' to the top.
Time for you to let go that rope.
You trespass...
You pay the price.
Now drop that rope.
Drop that rope.
– Forcecom 1, entering the truck.
– Roger that.
I turn in visual.
– It's her!
– It'll be okay, uh?
Fire at me.
Fire at me!
Who are you?
Commander Hae-Ju Zheng.
First science officer
of the Union rebellion.
Why are you doing this?
Because I believe you have
the power to change this world.
Drop that rope...
Let go that rope.
"Hands are bleedin', can't let go"
Hands are bleedin'.
Can't let go.
Thank you Zachry.
You savin' me twice, ain't ya?
You fall, I catch you.
Excessive force confirmed.
Stop them.
Stop them now.
What are you doing, boy?
I thought I made myself clear.
– Do what you want. I'm leaving!
– Fine, Frobisher...
Go, but I take this.
– Give that to me.
– It's mine!
I'm warning you!
Under the conditions of this relationship,
I'm certain that I'm in my legal rights.
Give it to me. Give it to me, or I swear
to God I will kill you as you stand!
Please... you're a coward.
– I'll do it.
– You won't pull that trigger.
Your kind never does.
PACIFIC JOURNAL OF ADAM EWING
Yes. Yes, well...
How-how fares our worm today, Adam?
I- I'm afraid it has taken the best of me.
Oh no no no. Nonsense.
Nonsense.
You mustn't give up.
You must think of your beautiful wife.
You must think of Tilda.
They're trapped in the downway.
We've got them.
What are you doing?
Nay, the dead never stay dead.
Open your ears, and
they'll never stop a yibberin'.
What is this place?
Before the Fall,
Old Uns built dwellings,
beyond the sky, among the stars,
this place joined here with there.
Sonmi.
It is she.
The Old Uns pray to Sonmi
same as Valleysmen?
Nay... not 'zactly same.
Stay close.
Fabricants get snatched here.
– All clear.
– Thank you.
No sweat, we're partners.
But you got to tell me what's happening.
Okay, let me take off these clothes,
call the cops,
and I promise I tell you everything
that happen in the morning.
Okay. But I hope you
realize you just said exactly
what every character in
any decent mystery says
right before they get killed.
Good night, Javier.
What'd you mean down there?
'bout...
The Old Uns and Valleymen prayin'
to Sonmi not 'zactly the same?
Old men... they were different.
Different?
How?
You want the True-true?
This is where you live?
This... is where Union was born.
Sonmi were no God.
She died hundreds of years ago
on a faraway peninsula, deadlanded now.
What?
I cog Valleysmens beliefs,
I know Abbess teach you
Sonmi was a miracle,
birthed o' Darwin god o' Smart,
but ain't the True-true.
Her life was sad n' judased, she died
tryin' to change the Old-Uns thinkin'.
Liiiies... nothing but lying.
Nay, nay you-you're lying.
The nature of our immortal
lives is in the...
Sonmi?
Before she died, she spoke
of her acts n' deedins'.
Her words are heart savin' blessin',
remindin' me what's the True-true.
How long you lissin' to this?!
How long you jus' stand there,
n' let a stranger keep fuggin'
your beliefs up n' down, in n' out!
Our lives are not our own,
from womb to tomb,
we're bound to others.
Zachry.
You alright?
Finish your saysoe...
If I wanted to kill you, you'd be dead.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I just want to talk.
Be cool.
Alright.
And if I wanted to kill you,
you'd be dead already.
How's it feel, uh?
Good conversation start, isn't it?
You are Lester Rey's daughter,
that's for goddamn sure.
– You knew my father?
– Korean War.
I was in the two-one.
That's me on the end, next to your dad.
Mortar landed so close
it could have dropped out of my ass.
If your father hadn't done what he did,
I wouldn't be here.
Guess that makes two of us.
You ain't let go that rope cause you' a
lustin' for that darkly, sweet'meat.
I cog it all, now.
This whore, with her cokeynut
skin, and her slywise mask,
smilin' n' wormin' her way into
your trust so you brin' her here,
scavin' n' sivvin' for what?
For what, fool?
They want the island.
The Prescients want it all.
You judasin' your kin for a piece of ass.
She ain't your tribe, she
ain't even your color,
she just 'bout ignorin'
all your yarns n' ways,
spinnin' n' spoutin' her whoahsomse lies,
and you lap it up, like a dog in heat!
– That ain't truth.
– Ain't it? Then do sumthin', stop her!
Take your spiker an' slit her throat!
Protect your tribe,
protect your sister, little Caktin,
kill her now, before it's too late!
They will kill you.
– You don't know these people like I do.
– Yeah?
Well if that's all you came to tell me,
you're a little bit late.
Somebody just forced me off
the Swannekke bridge.
This is out of control.
Do you know who did it?
The contractor calls himself Bill Smoke.
– And...
– What?
He got Sachs.
Isaac?
A bomb on his plane.
The press is blaming the PLO.
He was a treat.
Like Sixsmith, like... you.
Bring them thru.
Sonmi 451,
I'm most honored to meet you.
I am General An-Cor Apis,
leader of Union.
Who is paying them?
The same guy that pays me.
Lloyd Hooks?
Hughes & Pikes Consulting.
I've heard of them.
They're, uh... lobbiers for oil companies.
Why would big oil... hire
Lloyd Hooks to run a nuclear reactor?
You get that same look your father
used to get. You see I told you.
Hooks doesn't want the report discovered,
because he doesn't want the reactor fixed.
He wants it to fail.
This is about the future
of energy in this country.
They want the explosion.
The chaos and carnage.
The more deaths, the better.
Can't cog o' thing,
words n'worrins' like a wasp's nest,
proke'd n'prod'd by you.
You come elbowin' in' our life,
yibberin' about the True-true,
and never tellin' the whole true.
I need to cog what you doin'!
I told you.
I come to send a plea o' help.
Help, why?
To steal our land?
To kill n' slave us all?!
What d'you want?!
Prescients' dyin', Zach.
Just like Catkin.
This world poison me n' all my kin'.
We get no help,
ain't no home if I don' find a way.
I say the truesome.
We not survive.
We not survive...
Ayrs has the dogs after me.
The bullet passed through,
killing little more than his appetite,
and he's out for blood.
I'll have to pay the piper.
– I should call the cops.
– It won't help.
How do I know you're not lying to me?
Smoke will be coming for me,
as soon as he figures out I'm with you.
We need that report.
I can't protect you for long without it.
– General Apis...
– You, my dear...
are proof... our efforts were not in vain.
But... I'm just a dinery server.
I was not genomed to alter reality.
No revolutionary ever was.
I'm sorry.
I cannot do what you're asking.
It would be a difficult choice for anyone.
But, before you call your decision final,
there is one last thing
I would like you to see,
in order to fully understand
what we are fighting for.
Cross your fingers n' toes.
If your pray' be answered,
nay Prescients never
return to the Valley again?
Those wishin' to come with us,
they're welcome.
The Valley is my home.
Are you alright?
I know... it is forbidden.
Sixsmith. I climb the steps of
the Scot monument every morning.
And all becomes clear.
Wish I could make you
see this brigthness.
Don't worry, all is well.
All is so perfectly, damnably well.
I understand now, that boundaries
between noise and sound are conventions.
All boundaries are conventions,
waiting to be transcended.
One may trandcend any convention,
if only one can first
conceive of doing so.
Moments like this, I can feel your heart
beating as clearly as I feel my own,
and I know that separation is an illusion.
My life extends far beyond
the limitations of me.
Storm is coming, Mr. Ewing.
Gonna get you down below.
I'm not running a fuckin' charity,
out with you! Off you go!!
Aah, Mr. Ewing!
A-a-a word if you may.
Dangerous times we have here.
About that scandal. They say that
ruffian Robert Frobisher is a composer.
You're a composer too,
aren't you Mr. Ewing?
– What d'you want?
– The constable asked to search my rooms.
I know how hard... you're working,
so I told him there's
no one on the third floor.
It costs quite a bit of money
to keep an entire floor empty.
– That's all I have.
– Hmm...
What a beautiful... waistcoat.
If these letters are important,
– why d'you keep reading them?
– I don't know.
Maybe I'm... just trying
to understand something.
What?
Why we keep making the
same mistakes, over and over.
Maybe you should ask... Megan.
– What?
– Do you know a Megan?
That's his niece.
How do you know that?
Looks like he mailed something to her.
Probably used the envelope
he was keeping letters in.
Come on, Luisa.
First rule of mystery writing:
a good clue always leads to another clue.
When the ghostly ordeal of Timothy
Cavendish is turned into a film,
I'm thinking for the role of the hero,
one patch of Laurence Olivier
with a dash of Michael Caine.
Who the hell is this?
The Doctor Conway of Aurora House,
I'm covering for Dr. Upward.
– Ooh, is this about mother?
– Yes, it is, Mr. Hotchkiss,
I-I'm afraid you must deal yourself,
I don't think that she's
gonna last the night.
Unfortunately, it is an
unconvenient time for us,
do we really need to come right now?
No no, of course not, but she
did ask for you specifically,
and she seems quite upset
about her last will.
I'll be right there.
The plan was a series of topling dominoes,
that had commenced with Ernie
announcing my death to nurse Noakes.
– I know, I know.
– Shhh!
The entire ambush hinged upon
the silence of Mr. Meeks.
– I know, I know.
– Shh!
Mr. Cavendish?
Everything alright?
– Don't leave me here.
– Shh.
Mr. Cavendish?
– I knew it was too good to be true!
– You temp-temperous witch!
Mr. Hotchkiss, your mother is my
dearest friend here. Do please hurry.
And so... adieu!
Which, translated literally from the
French, means: "To command before...
God"!
I have Joe Napier on Line 1,
Mr. Hooks. He said it can't wait.
For God sake, Joe,
I am late already. What's up?
I got a call from that reporter. Rey...
She was asking about Sixsmith.
I see.
You said she wasn't gonna be a problem.
Well, some problems are
more resilient than others, Joe.
– Where's the ruddy key?
– He didn't leave it in the ignition!
His wife was driving, she took it,
the ruddy female took
the key in with her!
Oh Sweet Saint Ruddy Jude,
what do we do now?
Look under the sunpad.
What is it?
It's not a key, what'd you do with it?
– What else could it be?
– Well, how does it work?
– Shite!
– Oh no!
Well, think of something,
you're the genius,
you're the bloody ruddy genius!
We're done for.
Oh right... I can't even believe
I'm going to do this.
Is this thing working?
I mean is it still on, can you hear me?
Just keep walking.
I think he's behind me.
Whatever you do, don't look back.
Get out of my car!
Press that button thru!
Oh no, it's Mr. Meeks,
he doesn't want to come.
Ruddy bloody hell!
All for one and one for all?
The gate!
Veronica, would you unlock
the door for Mr. Meeks.
Hello Mr. Meeks,
we're off for a lifetime trife.
I know, I know.
– Rev in speed!
– Ho, how fondling!
Oh, no!
Go for it, cavendish!
– Here we go!
Here we go.
Come on, Adam, we haven't all day.
You really need to drink this.
The worm fights back,
it is always darkest before the dawn.
Mr. Ewing?
Mr. Ewing is at a critical
juncture in his treatment.
The next few hours will
determine if he lives or die.
Then I stay here.
– No, no, no you can't.
– I must. Mr. Ewing saved my life.
It my duty.
Listen to me, you ignorant ape,
Mr. Ewing doesn't want you around him,
you probably infected him to begin with.
He begged me, and I quote:
"Keep that dirty nigger away from me!"
So please kindly respect his wishes!
– Where'd he go?
– I don't know.
Shit!
To freedom.
You are going to be sorry
in ways you cannot even imagine.
– No immigrants here, no immigrants here.
– Look,
I'm not an inspector.
We need your help...
I don't understand.
[IN PERFECT SPANISH]
We don't want the police to get involved,
but there is a man trying to kill me
and we really need your help.
Are there no true Scotsmen in the house?
Those there English gerrrrunts
are trampling all over
my God-given rrights!
These people are mine.
They've used me an' my pals most direly,
and we're in need
of a wee pit of assistance!
Right, pal...
We'll not gonna let ye down.
Now you just look here, you grebo,
you can go shag your bloody sporran...
They two people came in here,
which way did they go?
Which way they go?!
Shut up!
Shut the fuck up!
Stupid fucking wetback.
What-what's that, Ewing?
How shall I comprehend
when you drool and dribble so?
Oh, let me hazard a guess,
something in the key of
"Oh Henry, how could you do this to me?
I thought we were friends?"
Oh, unfortunately, you're wrong.
Wrong like Horrox and
your silly father-in-law.
There is only one rule that binds
all people, one governing principle
that defines every relationship
on God's green earth.
"The Weak are Meat
and the Strong Do Eat."
That way.
I told Hooks you couldn't be trusted, Joe.
You'll be next, you silver bitch.
Part of the business.
Enjoy your retirement.
Amaba... a este... perro!
And don't call me a fucking wetback.
"Why?" you ask.
It's absurdly simple,
there is gold in your trunk, I want it.
so I've killed you for it.
Get off Mr. Ewing or you know I kill you!
Mr. Ewing, Mr. Ewing!
Gotta flush you out.
Com'on, Mr. Ewing.
What was that?
Kona war-cry.
Zachry!
Oh no no, Sonmi, no.
This is what the general wanted me to see?
The end rushes towards me.
Unable to eat or sleep.
Like Ewing, the "mortal coil"
has become a noose.
I'd rather become music.
They believe they're going to Exultation.
But they are not, are they?
Welcome to Exultation.
Take a seat.
Just relax.
This is to remove your collar.
"Enemy's sleepin', don't slit that throat"
The genomics industry demands a huge
quantity of biomatter for wombtanks.
and more importantly to sustain
their engineered labor force.
Recycled Fabricants are
a cheap source of protein.
Soap.
They feed us to ourselves.
That ship...
The ship must be destroyed.
Yes.
The systems that built them
must be turned down.
Yes.
No matter if we're born in a tank
or a womb, we are all Pureblood.
Yes.
We must all fight...
and if necessary, die
to teach people the truth.
This is what we have been waiting for.
It's done.
You were then taken to
a Union control satellite link.
I broadcast my Revelation to the
twelve States and four Off-World colonies.
18 minutes later,
the Enforcers attacked.
To be is to be perceived.
And so to know thyself is only possible
through the eyes of the other.
The nature of our immortal lives
is in the consequences
of our words and deeds,
that go on and are pushing
themseves throughout all time.
Hide.
From good chief, now you're meat.
– Catkin...
– Uncle Zach.
Thanks, Zachry.
No, thank you.
Com'on, Mr. Ewing.
One more.
Salt clean out your stomach.
Close.
Com'on Mr. Ewing, com'on!
Do you see where we are, Mr. Ewing?
Home.
Megan Sixsmith?
Make them pay.
You can count on it.
Thank you.
My uncle was a scientist,
but... he believed that love was real.
A kind of... natural phenomenon.
He believed that love could outlive death.
I finished it in a frenzy that reminded me
of our last night in Cambridge.
Watched my final sunrise,
enjoyed the last cigarette.
Didn't think the view
could be anymore perfect,
until I saw that beat-up trilby.
Honestly, Sixsmith, as
ridiculous as that thing makes you look,
I don't believe I've ever seen
anything more beautiful.
Watched you for as long as I dared.
I don't believe it was a fluke
that I saw you first.
– Okay.
– Thank you.
Captain saysoed he take you with us.
– I wanna go with Meronym.
– Go... Go where?
Prescients in the same boat as all us.
Got no home neitherwise.
Nay, not yet.
You think someone will gonna hear
your prayer, come down from the sky?
Perhaps...
Perhaps one day.
One day ain't but a flea o' hope.
Yay, and fleas ain't so easy to rid.
I believe there is another
world waiting for us, Sixsmith.
A better world.
And I'll be waiting for you there.
May I help you, sir?
Yes, thank you. I-I'm looking for
a friend who came to Edinburg...
I believe we do not stay dead long.
Find me beneath the Corsican
stars where we first kissed.
Yours eternally.
R.F.
The report said commander Zheng
was killed in the assault.
That is correct.
But you say that you loved him?
Yes I do.
You mean you are still in love with him?
I mean that I will always be.
Our lives are not our own.
From womb to tomb,
we're bound to others.
Past and present.
And by each crime and every kindness,
we birth our future.
In your Revelation, you spoke of
the consequences of an undividual's life
replicated throughout eternity.
Does this mean that
you believe in an afterlife?
No heaven or hell?
I believe death is only a door.
When its closes, another opens.
If I'd care to imagine heaven,
I would imagine a door open.
And behind it,
I will find him there, waiting for me.
My love.
Oh God, I missed you so much.
Thank you, sir.
If I may ask one last question...
You had to know this Union
scheme was doomed to fail.
Yes.
And why did you agree to it?
This is what general Apis asked of me.
What, to be executed?
If I had remained invisible,
the truth would stay hidden.
I couldn't allow that.
And what if no one believes this truth?
Someone already does.
Adam, good God...
I have just been recounting
your astonishing adventure.
Please, join us.
Give him a chair.
No no, thank you.
I cannot stay.
What are you doing here? Has not the
doctor said at least three weeks in bed?
He did, but this couldn't wait.
I need to speak with you, sir.
Privately.
Of course.
Is that the contract
from Reverend Horrox?
– It is indeed.
– Well, you know I could have sent a boy.
Are you insane?!
I owe my life to a self-freed slave.
And I cannot in good conscience participate
in this kind of business any longer.
This would make such a good book.
I'll drink to that.
Outside, fat snow flakes are falling
on slate roofs and granite walls.
Like Solzhenitsyn laboring in Vermont,
I shall beaver away in exile.
Unlike Solzhenitsyn, I shan't be alone.
Goddamn you, sir, if you were
not my daughter's husband...
Hello, Father.
Tilda?
What's going on?
I've come to say goodbye.
Goodbye?
Where are you going?
We're moving back East,
to work with the abolitionists.
What?
That poison has rotted your brain.
Oh if it has, I highly recommend it.
I've not felt this good in years.
Tilda, I forbid you from going
anywhere with this mad man.
I've been afraid of you
my whole life, Father.
I'm going with my husband.
Adam.
Listen to me...
For the sake of my grandson,
if not your own...
there is a natural order to this world,
and those who try to upend it
do not fare well.
This movement will never survive.
If you join them, you and
your entire family will be shunned.
At best, you exist as pariah,
to be spat on and beaten.
At worst, lynched or crucified.
And for what?
For what?
No matter what you do, it will
never amount to anything more
than a single drop in a limitless ocean.
What is an ocean but a multitude of drops?
Fire is dyin'.
Just as well, my yawnin' is done.
No, please Gran'Pi, Please!
Come on, come here, you little buggars!
Com'on, it's getting cold!
No, you heard your Gran'mi,
com'on, get on with you.
You like it down here, don't you Gran'pi?
Supposin'... reminds me of my Valley.
Which is Earth?
That in there, that blue shimmerin'.
Now, help your Gran'pi up.
You gonna tell us about the
roguesome ship, and the big split,
and all the next-next?
Oh, your Gran'mi tells the next-next
way better than me.
D'you still love Gran'mi?
Your Gran'mi is the best thin'
that ever happened to me.
Come on, you Gran'pi.
Let me warm that li'le ol' bone.
Transcript and sync: jcdr
v1.1 - 05.01.2013