Pals, I'm Siu Chiu
the maid of King of White Eagle
This is the grandson of White Eagle
Mr. Chang Mo-kei
You're Chang Mo-kei?
Yes, I am
The order of King of White Eagle
who claims to be Chang Mo-kei
whoever should be killed. Kill him
Go
Rush over there
I'm really Chang Mo-kei
Kill
Don't even know who's enemy
you deserve to be beaten
Great Solar Stance
Bravo
Hero, which school do you come from?
Master, he's Chang Mo-kei
He's the son of Chang Tsui-san?
Why is he so powerful?
Where are you taking me to?
This is the forbidden zone of Ming Sect
What? Forbidden?
Shall we go in?
Other than the master of our Sect
can enter before his death
If he dies outside
the ones who carry his corpse
should commit suicide in here
How about you?
I'm a maid, King of White Eagle
doesn't let mejoin the sect
Don't go
Go
Damn it, if you move one more step
I want you to die terribly
lfl stay here, I would die terribly
You fool! Mister, let's go
Commander, what'II we do?
This is the grave of our ex—masters
There are many traps inside
If they go in, they'll surly be killed
Let's go back to help
What's the matter?
I'm scared
Don't be afraid. Look
They're all skulls
I think they're the ones
who carried the corpse
Why don't we go out?
We're surrounded by the Flag Soldiers
So many men outside
I don't want to hurt
my grandfather's men with my kung-fu
I think, we have no choice
but to go forward
I know there is a road
to get to the Bright Summit
You're only a maid of King of Eagle
why do you know that much?
I heard it, thus I know it
My grandfather locked you
with such heavy chain
There must be some reasons
Who are you? Don't cheat me
Don't you trust me?
I just want to know the truth
Mister, l have made an oath
I can't tell anybody
But I promise, I didn't mean
to hurt your grandfather
and I'll never hurt you
Please let me keep some secret
will you?
I promise, when it's time, I'll tell you
OK. Let's talk later
There're foot marks on the floor
Yeung Ting Tin, you're the master
of the Evil Sect, but so what?
Even you took away my lover, so what?
Can't imagine you would die here
l, Shing Kwun, am now using the schools
to destroy your Evil Sect
I want to take your Magic Stance too
Then I'll be invincible
and to be the Pope of Yuen Dynasty
Even I don't have the To Lung Sword
I can be the supreme
of the world of martial arts
The ex-master of Ming Sect
disappeared for over 20 years
In fact, he died right here
This may be Shing Kwun
the foe of my God-father
I see, he became
the dog of Yuen Government
He set a variance
between the schools and Ming Sect
That's why he dragged
my God-father's family to death
Who?
Chang Mo-kei
Didn't you die?
What's the enmity
between you and Ming Sect?
between you and my dad?
Why did you drag them like this?
Yeung Ting Tin took my lover from me
I had adultery with his wife for 3 years
At last he discovered that
That's why he got mad
But he still wanted to kill me
My lover wanted to cover me
she committed suicide
I stayed 20 years
in the Shaolin as undercover
I just wait for this chance
to destroy Ming Sect
You seduced his wife
and ruined his Evil Sect
and you claimed yourself reasonable
What a shame!
No matter it's right and wrong
It's not your turn to criticize me
Chang Mo-kei, I'm sending you
to see your parents
Get lost
What kind of kung-fu is it?
Great Solar Stance
I can't imagine
I'd be defeated by you
In fact, Chang Tsui-san had a secret
What is it?
Shit
Get lost, I try to break it
with my Great Solar Stance
Mister
Don't use Great Solar Stance
I'm afraid it would collapse
Are we waiting for death then?
We've to find other exit
There're some words
Those who come into this cell
Should bow to the skeleton
or the soul will give you trouble
We're going to die
we'll be souls too
We don't need to be scared
Maybe we'll be saved
We should respect the dead
Come and bow
Master Yeung
we're forced to disturb you
If we have a chance to get out
we'll take revenge for you
to kill Shing Kwun
Please bless us
What are these word?
It's the Persia language
Can you read it?
Sure
After bowing to me
You'll have my Magic Stance
After you learnt it
you can push the stone open
and reach Bright Summit
Mister
the Magic Stance is written on the rocks
He was really wise
he knew Shing Kwun wouldn't bow to him
So he designed such trap
Practise now, then we may get out
But it's not right
to steal Ming Sect's kung-fu
It's written that
after you've learnt it
You should pass a message
on behalf of Master Yeung
ask King of Gold Lion
to be his successor
the Magic Stance
should be kept by him too
and get the Holy Fire Tablet
from Persia's Ming Sect
He wanted your God father
to be his successor
Since you're his God-son
it doesn't matter to learn his kung-fu
But, how long should it take?
It's written that
for ordinary people, it takes 30 years
For those great kung-fu masters
ltjust takes 3 hours
l have the base of Great Solar Stance
ljust need 3 hours
Go ahead then
King of Green Bat, you're hurt
Don't waste it...
Where are the women?...
Over there
Do you want me to eat your blood?
We're the red cross
We come to save
He's bleeding
Beat him
You come to save, don't you?
We save those from strong sex desire
and to save those
who reincarnated wrongly
How?
Kill you and let you reincarnate again
Kill him
You bastard, if I were not
hurt seriously I would kill you
Old bluffer
I've stopped the bleeding for you
King of White Eagle
you're really something
We break even
Dad, he's hurt
Why don't you kill him?
He fought against five, instead, he won
If we take such chance
how can we claim ourselves heroes?
Stop
What's the matter?
You don't attack
We, Wah-shan School will attack now
Men, remove your rings and chains
Women, undress
Or, you'll be killed
I can't imagine I'd be bullied
by such jerks
Old bluffer, let's fight together
for our beloved sect
The Evil Sect is going to be terminated
Chi-yu, go with your sisters
to kill all the people from Evil Sect
and extinguish their holy fire
Yes, Master
King of White Eagle
you're a great kung-fu master
Your Eagle's Claws Stance
in the world of martial arts
is as great as
the Dragons Claws Stance of Shaolin
You'd better commit suicide
Old Bluffer, don't be so impulsive
Listen
I, Chang Mo-kei request you
to stop for a while
Mo-kei, aren't you dead?
Is he the son of So-so?
That's your grandson?!
Thank you for your concern
Today, the fight between Ming Sect
and the schools
is all a trap set by Shing Kwun
the master of Tse Shun
Please keep calm
and not fall into his trap
Bullshit, the Evil Sect
is so brutal
Wai Yat-siu needs blood for practicing
Tse Shun killed many innocent people
they should be killed
Yes, I need blood for practicing
but I need chick's blood
pig's blood and my blood only
On that night
Mrs. Ho of Kwun-lun school
was killed by you
I didn't bite her
About manslaughter?!
Old nun, you killed more than me
You
Shing Kwun serves Yuen
he wants us to kill among ourselves
Master, I hope you'll understand
As you said
Where is Shing Kwun now?
He went undercover in Shaolin
for over 20 years
He's masked
How dare you frame my Uncle Yuen Chun?
Where's Yuen Chun?
He sneaked into the graveyard
and wanted to steal the Magic Stance
Master Yeung was dragged to death by him
Siu Chiu, make it clear
Grandfather
I won't let anybody hurt you
Kid, you insulted Shaolin
what a big mouth you're having
Try my Dragon's Claws Stance
Master, would you let us go
if I can defeat you?
Deal
So go ahead
The Dragon's Claws Stance of Shaolin
is powerful than our kung-fu
This guy is really powerful
If I have 6,000 points
He has at least 10,000 points
Dragon's Claws Stance
OK. Terminate my kung-fu now
I just come to stop your fight
Not to create any more troubles
By the way
I used the kung-fu of Shaolin
It's not an insult at all
Please forgive me
OK. Let's go
Chang Mo-kei, let me challenge you
They pushed my dad to death
Now, they come
to slaughter without reasons
I have to take revenge for dad
No way, if I duel with them
it's being trapped by Shing Kwun
Want to hold my temper
to be supreme
I can fight against the Government
Watch out
you should take care of her sword
Right, don't fight with her
Master, please go ahead
Magic Stance
Damn you nun
Siu Chiu
Yes
Thank you, mister
Brother Mo-kei
in fact I was forced to trap you
Please forgive me
I've never minded that
Please bring this sword to your master
Anybody wants to challenge me again?
Chi-yu
Brother
Mister
Mister, don't die...
Mo-kei
Let's attack them together
I'm sure we can kill him
His girl is so pretty
Rape her
Who dares to take their advantage
Who is going to be Wu-tong's enemy
Just a misunderstanding
Let's call for hookers
Don't rape
You're the bastard, let's go
Mister, you can't die. Don't leave me
I'm protected by Great Solar Stance
I won't die
But I can't use my kung-fu in this week
Mo-kei, take a good rest
If you have time
come back to visit Master Chang
Since we protected you
we've gone against the other schools
We should leave as early as possible
or we'll be blamed
of being allied with Evil Sect
So what? Who do you think you are?
Maybe, we'll save your Wu-tong one day
What are you bull-shitting?
Ching-su Uncle
please bring the Yee Tin Sword
to Master Chang
don't let No-mercy get it anymore
Alright
Mister Mo-kei
Go
Take care
Mister
Yau Tin Tsing, Wai Yat-siu
and Elements Flags, greet Master Chang
I'm not your master
It's a tradition that
whoever uses Magic Stance is our master
Our Sect has been split
in all these years
Two Fairies
King of Gold Lion
and Queen of Purple Dragon
they left after fighting
for the leadership
You saved us today
Other than you
who is qualified to be the Master then?
But Master Yeung's will
was my God-father to be his successor
Either you or your God-father
is the same
You Highness
Wah-shan School
is coming back with a troop
they want an attack
Damn it, what a bastard
I'm Chu Yeun-chang
now it's an emergency that
please instruct us what to do
Since many of you are hurt
we'd better hide up in the graveyard
What do you think?
If you're willing to be our master
We will do whatever you instruct
Listen, my followers
Get to the graveyard and hide up first
After we've recovered
we'll take our revenge
Bravo, Holy Master...
Wonderful
It's really a blessing
to have you be our leader
Chu Yuen Chang, ljust take the post
temporarily for my God-father
May I be frank
although you kept on refusing
to be the Master
I could tell from your eyes
you're willing to be the Master
We have so many followers
and we fight with the gov't continuously
we have strong power
Since you want to take revenge
after being the master
you'll have greater chance to take revenge
and you may turnover Yuen's Dynasty
and to be the King
It's not impossible
Cut the crap
King of White Eagle is old
King of Green Bat is so care free
They can't assist you much
No matter what
Just instruct me, I'm willing to help
From your eyes
I can see you're ambitious
If I make you my right hand
you'll have better success
You're really wise
I do want to be the Master
But the wise people
is usually disgusting
I understand
Get out of here
Master, please let us go
Wah Shan is a decent school
but with you jerks
Master, don't kill us
I'll tell you some secret
Go ahead
We've got some information
the days before
Wu Tong's students were attacked
by some monks
They seem to be from Shaolin
All the students from Wu-tong
were caught
Don't be afraid
they'rejust being kidnapped
not being raped
Master
we've discovered that
Mr. Yan of Wu-tong is hurt
He is ahead
Uncle Yan Master
Uncle Yan
Mo-kei
How are you?
We met some Shaolin monks
on our way back to Wu-tong
They poisoned us with Scent
which is the most poisonous thing
in this world of martial arts
those who smell or are it'll lose
his kung-fu and energy
Only the special antidote can solve it
I held my breathe, so I could escape
My brothers were all arrested
But later, I met two monks
They were so powerful
l was seriously hurt
They broke all myjoints
They're so cruel
Let's go to Shaolin
and get my uncles back
All hired? Right
Yes, you may ask them Over there?
Master, all the doctors around are hired
and all the herbs are all bought
by one person
It's strange
It may be done by the Shaolin monks
No, he's living nearby
a place called Green Willow Villa
Master
I think, they're sure that we need herbs
to cure Yan
So they set this trap for us
Green Willow Villa?
Welcome
My master is long waiting for you
May I know his name?
You'll know it later
Damn it, do you want to trap us?
Speak up, or I'll suck your blood
My men's blood is stink
If you want it
I've prepared some fresh blood for you
What's so mysterious
Why don't you tell us your name?
I'm Chao Min
a nobody in the world of martial arts
It's meaningless to you
If you're scared, please leave
Watch out
Mister, she's the one
we met in the restaurant
Grandfather, King of Bat
she's the master of Jinxes
There may be a severe fight later
You're really something
Couldn't think you're so powerful
when I saw you last time
I can't imagine
you could defeat the schools
and be the master of the Ming Sect
What a young hero
May I know why did you buy all the herbs
and hire all the doctors?
I've heard that
Mr. Yan is hurt by Shaolin
I'm afraid he'd be mistreated
by poor doctors
so, I caught all the poor doctors here
But instead
I've prepared
the Black Jade Paste for him
Mister
We're not friends, why do you help us?
Making friends with heroes
is always the practice
of our Yuen Government
You're the No.1 kung-fu master
in the world
this doesn't mean anything
The Black Jade Paste is
the most wonderful medicine in the world
How can she give us that easily?
You're Manchurian
My dad is Emperor Yu Yang
Shaolin is so foolish to challenge you
We'll help you to terminate them
Master, is it Yee Tin Sword?
Right
We'll settle our own matters
We don't want the interference
from the government
Thank you very much
Master Chang, please stay
I've prepared some food for you
I'll get changed first, may I be excused
We're leaving
Are you sure there is Black Jade Paste?
Damn it, how cocky she is!
Isn't it true or not?
It smells nice
It's nice
This may be a trap, we'd better go
You...
Master, we're so tired
We lost our energy
They're poisoned
My brothers were all poisoned by this
I'm the only one who held the breath
What we can do?
I'll get the antidote from her
Siu Chiu, take care of here
You do keep your promise
You come to drink with me
Why do you trap us?
Master Chang, no one asked you
to touch the wooden sword
It's because one of you is greedy
That's why they're poisoned
Bring me the antidote
Master Chang, are you begging me?
Or forcing me?
Where are the Jinxes?
Ask them out
Are you scared of them?
I won't tell where they are
So you'll be scared
Don't think that I won't beat you
because you're woman
I know, so, I decided to...
attack first
Yuen is such powerful that
it has the greatest territory
You'rejust a man
How can you beat our government?
The totalitarianism of Yuen
is hated by the people
I just work for the will of people
We have voluntary armies
to fight against Yuen
It's the will of the people
Can you beat the will of the people?
Master Chang
why not play a song with me?
Stop playing
I love it
Master Chang, do you want to see my leg?
Just tell me
Why do you take my shoe?
You're so cunning
how can you claim yourself heroic?
I'm not hero
I'm a cunning woman
Have you heard that? Woman is cunning!
I won't argue with you
If you don't give me antidote
I'll burn your Green Willow Villa
I won't give in a damn
but your fellows are seriously poisoned
If they can't get the antidote
within 2 hours
they can never regain their kung-fu
Time is running short
Jinx's Palm
This isn't Jinx's Palm
Yes, I don't know it
I just want to scare you
If I didn't take back half energy
you'd have been killed
You don't wish to kill me
You like me
Bullshit
You love your maid more?
or love me more?
If you still don't give me the antidote
I'll kill yOu
Go ahead
Answer me, or I won't give you antidote
You
I know you love that maid most
But I have made No-mercy go there
How cunning are you!
Go, if you go like this
your fellows' kung-fu
can never be regained
I have no choice
Give me or not?
No
Once more, are you giving me?
No matter how, I won't give it to you
Aren't you scared of me?
I'll be your woman sooner or later
I don't need to resist
Anyway, no one will help me
You can do whatever you want
Shameless
Chang Mo-kei, I can give you antidote
and the Black Jade Paste
But
you've to promise me three things
Master
where are those people of Ming Sect?
They seem to be disappeared
Master, look
No-mercy again
Siu Chiu, leave us alone
No, Mister asked me to stay here
No matter how, I have to delay
You bastards
what evil deeds are you planning?
Master, they seem to be poisoned
Damn you, if you dare to come over
I'll drink all your blood
What are you looking?
I have too much blood
it's alright to spit some out
I have let you go once
Now, I have a chance
to kill the evils
for the world of martial arts
Master
it's not heroic to take such advantage
Bitch, get lost
Bitch, if you can resist stances from me
I'll let you kill
How dare you
Or, I'll take three stances from you
I'll let you do whatever you want
if you defeat me
What a sharp tongue
If you can resist three of my stances
I'll let you go
Come on
Siu Chiu...
How are you?...
Are you alright?
I can stand it
Two more
Master, she's seriously injured
Why not let me kill her?
I should not take my words back
I dare not
Siu Chiu, leave us alone
One more
You're looking for death
I can't help you
Siu Chiu
Mister
Go
King of Bat, take the antidote to them
Mo-kei why did Chao Min
give you antidote?
Be careful of tricks
I wanted her to take 3 in front of me
It should be real
Siu Chiu
Mister
What a couple
Bitch, how dare you come?
Why not?
Your Master promised
to do 3 things for me
That's why I give him the antidote
to save your lives
Mister
I just promised to do 3 things
which aren't against conscience
Not against heroism
I won't let you marry such pretty girl
Siu Chiu
Isn't it against conscience?
Master Chang, not that easy
When I have something in mind
I'll look for you
I've never met such cunning woman!
This woman must be a great foe
of our Ming Sect
There must be some stories
behind the raid against Wu-tong by Shaolin
We have to go to Shaolin Temple now
to get the truth
Master, are you alright?
Master No-mercy
Emperor Yu-yang wants you to be his guest
After you
Why is it so quiet?
Master Chang Mo-kei
together with King of White Eagle
and King of Green Bat
want to meet your master
Our Master has his order
he doesn't want to see anyone
We come a long way to here
We want to see him now. It's urgent
Please tell your master
He doesn't want to see you
Go back
Wait, from your movement
it doesn't seem
to be the kung-fu of Shaolin
You have your head newly shaved
You aren't a real monk
I said he's fake
Master, let's go in and check it out
OK
Mister, look
Kill Shaolin first, then Wu-tong
We, Ming Sect is the supreme
of the world of martial arts
It's a trap
Are all the kung-fu masters
of Shaolin killed?
They may be poisoned by Scent
I think most of them may be nabbed
Shit
What is the matter?
Kill Shaolin then Wu-tong
They must have gone to Wu-tong
Let's hurry there
Do you want to leave? Not that easy
Master, you'd better leave first
Master, what's the matter?
Hung Shang from Shaolin
wants to meet Master Chang
Follow me
Master
Shaolin has had the greatest disaster
We were raided by the Evil Sect
Other than me
no one is alive
Really?
The kung-fu Masters who launched a raid
to the Bright Summit
were all arrested by the Evil Sect
Master Chang, if you don't do something
the whole world of martial arts
will be under the control of Evil Sect
Get up first
Watch out, Master
The monk is fake
He's from the Evil Sect
Where is your dad and your uncles?
Master
Mo-kei didn't die
Hejoined the Evil Sect
and learnt lots of Evil Magic
My dad and 4 uncles were not prepared
they're assassinated by him
Five of them... Master!
Ching su, what happened?
Master
Ching su, how dare you assassinate me?
Even a scapegoat couldn't cheat you
Master
you should be the man of the world
You're a great in kung-fu
It's not wise to be a Taoist here
Why not follow me
to work for the government
to enjoy prosperous life together
You?!
Chang San Fung, do you remember us?
I see, the troubles in all these years
were designed by the government
Right, you're right
Our Majesty wants to make you
the Pope of our government
If you're willing to work for us
your school
will enjoy prosperity together
and your students will be the generals
to settle the riots for my government
I, Chang San Fung, dare do everything
but not to be a tribal betrayer
Chang, you don't work for us
all you have to do is to only go to hell
Don't panic
I just want to scratch my back
Chang, how much blood do you have?
Protect Master
Don't. Let me handle it
Magic Stance
Master
Master, are you alright?
Mo-kei
How are you?
Ching-su, that bastard assassinated me
Why are you so powerful?
You asked me to keep my virtue
I haven't used that
Every morning
it's erected
No woman likes me
That's why I'm still a virgin
You have chance, use it
Cut the crap
Your Highness
How can you be that impolite
to Master Chang?
How are you, Master Chang? I'm Chao Min
Your Highness
Master Chang, don't be tough
Do you want your students to be killed?
Men should die once
but we should die meaningfully
Master, don't panic. I'm here
Master Chang, do you remember?
You're promised
to do 3 things for me
Will you keep your promise?
If only they aren't against conscience
and not heroic
I'll help
First
you can't use the Great Solar Stance
Just tie himself up, alright?
What a sharp tongue
I'll seal your mouth sooner or later
Second, don't use your Magic Stance
Alright, I promise
Mo-kei
what kind of kung-fu will you use?
Whatever, Master
Teach me any kung-fu of Wu-tong?
Isn't it alright?
It's alright
Master, come on
Tai Chi, grows from nothing
Master, you start that so late
I couldn't stand. Quick
Mo-kei, now I teach you
my self-developed tactics
since 100-year-old
Tai-chi Fist
It's the origin of motion
The origin of everything
Positive and negative is connected
Can't be separated
Elements help each other
They are against each other
Keep calm
Mind your respiration
Concentrate your mind
Pay full attention
Turn soft to hard
Use both soft and hard
In Tai-chi
There is soft and hard
Use both soft and hard
Generate the force as you wish
Mo-kei, you're protected
by the Great Solar Stance
You can learn
all kinds of kung-fu quickly
Tai-chi, just remember it's meaning
not the stance
Forget all your stances
Thus you can make it
Can your remember?
I've forgotten
What is the name of these stances?
Forgot
What's the surname of your dad?
OK, just remember
to beat them with no mercy
Congratulations
you have such a good student
You have a good grandson too
I'll let you go now
This should be the third thing
Chang Mo-kei
I won't let you repay me that easily
The lives of the schools
are controlled by me
If I don't go back within three days
they'll all be killed
What do you want?
Today, you're lucky, let's go
Not that easy
Don't go
OK, I won't go
I'll stay here or more days
You'd better prepare the funerals
for your friends
You may go
but Ching-su can't
Your Highness, don't leave me
Such heartless dog
It's useless for me to keep it
Take it if you like
Master, I deserve to be killed
I'm useless
Master, just let me go
How can you face your dad?
Mo-kei...
Since we grow up together
Please beg Master to let me go, please
Mo-kei
Uncle Sung has a son only
If I kill you
he'll have no descendant
Alright
Master, I've terminated all his kung-fu
Please let him stay alive
Alright
Master, thank you
Thank you...
Chang Mo-kei
you still have to do one thing for me
Remember
if you want to save the schools
come to the capital to look for me