"My hands do not
have strength and power."
"My heart embraces peace and calm."
"Resigning myself to adversity.
Seeing richness out of void."
"Violence be turned to peace.
There are always guiding fate."
"Dynamic or still. Divide or multiple."
"Follow fate to go in and out of
mortal world. Merciless is mercy."
"Follow heart and not be aggressive.
Merciless is mercy."
"Dynamic or Still. Divide or multiple."
"Follow fate to go in and out of
mortal world. Merciless is mercy."
"Follow heart and not be aggressive.
Merciless is mercy."
Tianbao, now that you're a monk...
you've to obey the regulations.
You mustn't kill or eat meat.
Master, I have never eaten any meat.
You're born to be a monk.
It's just that we were too poor
to afford any meat.
I wanna try its taste, too.
Master.
This is Tianbao.
He's your senior, Junbao.
Shaolin Temple has very strict rules.
He'll teach you everything.
You must obey your senior.
Junbao, teach him to recite
the Book of Buddha.
Which part?
I thought you knew only one part.
Tianbao, my junior.
I'm taller and older than you.
Why do l have to call you "senior"?
I dunno. Master says this is a rule.
l'll call you senior
only in front of others.
They didn't hear us.
It's like there's no one around.
Do you want to be a senior or not?
Of course!
There's no one now. Call me senior.
- Senior!
- Good boy!
- Let's do our homework.
- Let's play first.
The Hands!
"Dance of the Phoenix!"
"Behold, the Golden Rooster!"
Tianbao my junior, come here!
Why do you call me junior
in front of them?
They won't hear!
It's just the two of us here.
You're right.
"The Wild Goose Glides along the Beach!"
"The Leopard Leaps over the Cliff!"
If I'm given a chance
to practice kung-fu...
I'll be better than them.
Well, this I'll have to
consult the Master.
"The Octagon Transforms Itself!"
Why do you hit me?
Why are you messing around here
instead of doing your homework?
I am your senior.
I can hit you anytime I like.
Why hit me?
Are you okay, Tianbao?
You mustn't try learn kung-fu secretly!
Let's go! The Master is angry!
We'll tell our Master. Let's go.
No big deal!
My Master is the senior of yours.
Master, this will keep you
from the sunshine.
Everything has a life,
including the plants.
We mustn't hurt the life of nature
for our own profits.
This'd be too selfish.
Understand?
Yes, Master!
We won't care if you would be
burnt by the sun.
Master, l want to practice kung-fu.
What for?
- To have a healthy body.
- To avoid being bullied.
Think twice.
I'm serious.
You should use your kung-fu
to help others.
Remember that.
Yes, Master!
Try this!
Who's that? I'll teach you a good lesson.
Come, join my hands.
Let me cover him up!
- Go to hell!
- Stop!
I know who you are.
How do you know that I'm Junbao?
You've just told me!
It's all your fault!
You idiot!
He said he knew!
How did l know that he's lying?
You believed him?
See what you've dragged me into.
I'm starving!
Me, too!
- This is really too much!?
- Master!
I told you to practice kung-fu
to help others. You used it to fight!
You've shamed me!
Beating my senior's student!
- Master...
- Shut up!
I'll teach you a good lesson!
Master is too lenient with you
by making you kneel for just 3 hours.
Go confess yourself.
Master, have you any red-bean bun?
Plain bun will be good enough.
After this, we'll still
have to clean up Luo Han Hall.
It's all your fault!
I told you to be on guard,
yet you went to eat.
Now we're being penalized
by having to clean up Luo Han Hall.
You'll be punished one day
for burning the rat.
"The Fairy Sign!"
"The Dragon Shows its Might!"
How did you attack with a pole?
How did you play your move?
It's very simple!
"The Fairy Sign!"
"The Dragon Shows its Might!"
"The lnvincible Move!"
This is called...
"Knocking on your Head!"
Tianbao, you're playing tricks
with me again!
You're too slow!
Watch out for your head!
Junbao, wake up!
Tianbao, you gave in to me.
Master always says
to help others with kung-fu.
Everybody practices kung-fu here.
Who should we help?
We help ourselves. I want to be
Number One of Shaolin Temple.
You're too naive.
When can I achieve this status?
Beat the 18 Bronze Men
and the Wooden Warriors.
Get off! You mustn't let others see this!
No one will see me!
I don't care.
Get off and sit on the ground.
You're bullying me again!
I told you. You're too slow.
I'll go inform on you.
What? You think you can
get away with this?
Each punch of Shaolin Fists
must be forceful!
Each move is a surprise for the enemy.
It has to be swift as a wind.
These are the basics of the Fists.
You must be every steadfast.
What happened?
Easy! The door collapsed
just like that a few days ago!
I've told you that it's the termites.
Be careful! Don't eat them!
To achieve the highest level,
your body must be hard as steel.
- The bed's collapsed, too.
- Easy...
Go to sleep.
We've to practice Iron Palms tomorrow.
Junbao, watch my sword.
You're short of practice.
Your arm isn't strong enough.
Strike first to forestall the opponent.
Let's practice!
What's this? Everything is broken!
Now the cloths are like that, too.
The monks at Luo Han Hall
will laugh at us.
We'll tell them that
we've over-washed them.
Senior, ours are okay.
Of course! I've saved
the best for ourselves.
Master, we're off to do
our morning homework.
What happened to them?
I dunno. Maybe it's the rats.
How rampant are the rats
and termites these days!
Go do something about them.
Where do we find termites and rats?
We can tell him that
the sparrows have eaten them up!
Wow! What kung-fu is that?
Thank you... It's nothing!
Senior, you're the best among all of us!
I'm sure that you'll win
the martial arts contest.
Thanks. I think the same of you.
Rice is coming.
Watch my stance.
- Boy!
- You eat first.
Why did you throw the rice at me?
You saw how I slipped.
I did that, so what? Go tell your Master.
My Master is the jury of the contest.
I'll make sure that you won't
be promoted into the Da Mor Hall.
Let me go!
I swear that I'll beat that son of a gun.
Twelve, thirteen...
I've just smashed that.
Junbao, the examination for promotion
into the Da Mor Hall will be held soon.
Do you think you'll make it?
Relax. It's all up to chance.
No way! I will be Number One.
That's why I practiced so hard...
How many bricks have you smashed?
Seventeen.
Eighteen.
How could you do this?
I couldn't!
Your moves are different.
"The Buddhist Palms!"
The key lies in the way you breathe.
Today, we're going to choose from
among you the best four students,
to be promoted into Da Mor Hall...
to further study
the best martial arts technique.
Remember, the purpose of
kung-fu practice is to help people.
The contestants must restrain themselves.
The first round: Tianbao vs. Xinbao.
That son of a gun
is going to meet his fate.
Please!
Start!
Try my stance.
Xinbao, you'll lose.
Surrender!
You cheated!
Stop...
How dare you hit me!
Please forgive me!
You're simply not fit to practice kung-fu
because of your ferocious intent.
You're expelled.
Please, don't.
It's Xinbao who played tricks first.
Are you implying that I'm being unfair?
I dare not say so.
Are you blind? Didn't you see that?
This is an insult to your masters.
- He didn't mean it!
- Go away!
I'm going to destroy
your martial arts skill.
Please, don't!
Stay away from this!
"The Buddhist Palms!"
How come you know "The Buddhist Palms!"?
I told you that you're blind!
I learned it from you.
Tianbao!
He didn't mean to peep.
Catch them!
- Deploy the Luo Han Pole Formation.
- Yes!
We're all brothers. Let's talk.
Say something.
"Buddha has Sign! Surrender,
all ye Devils!"
Tianbao, break the formation
by using the pole, too.
I'll break them up!
You'll never escape this.
- lt's slippery!
- Yeah!
Got it!
Junbao, move!
- Watch out!
- Deploy the formation!
It's very slippery!
We can't form our line.
"The lnvincible Move!"
We're all brothers!
Stop trampling on each other! Stop!
Don't run!
Don't let them run away!
- Master!
- Run, quick!
Jueyuan!
You're defended for your students!
What are you going to tell
the Chief Reverend?
You're spoilt them so much!
Everyone can see that the son of a gun
tried trick me first.
Yet I was the villain!
What did I do?
- They even tried to kill us!
- Wonder how's Master doing.
You use Luo Han Pole Formation?
There's no justice in the world.
Master, we were wrong.
Fate has it that we have to part.
I can't be your Master anymore.
Join the outside world and learn from it.
The roots of trouble
are also the roots of Buddhism.
Junbao, you're a kind man.
I don't worry for you!
Tianbao, you have a
competitive personality.
This book is for
the practice of your "Qi".
It doesn't concern with
any martial arts skill.
When you're restless and emotional...
it'll bring you peace.
Practice it often.
Remember, try keep a peaceful mind.
You don't have to study Buddhism
only in Shaolin Temple Go!
Yes, Master!
Ladies and gentleman,
hope you enjoy the show!
Which school do you think is that?
They're just street entertainers!
Why do they shave
only half of their hair?
They stink! They must have
come from Cedan!
I'm starving.
Me, too. Let's go beg for alms.
No one pays attention to us!
Are they all that poor?
No. We're just being useless!
I bet that girl over there
won't turn us down!
If she has money, she won't have
to perform on the street.
You son of a...
May all of you benefactors
have a long and prosperous life!
No wonder we had bad luck today!
lt's all you stinking monks!
Happy birthday, benefactors!
Wish us good luck in gambling!
Cut the crap!
There's no need to be rude!
- Excuse me!
- It's alright!
Reverend, do you know
someone called Murong Bei?
Sorry to bother you!
She's looking for someone;
we're looking for food!
We need a job, too.
To earn money.
I've realized that
Shaolin Temple is the best.
Pay your protection money!
I've paid my due!
Not to me!
Pay or die, you can choose
for yourself! Beat him!
I really have no money!
Please, stop! Help!
I have to eat, too!
I'll report to the officer!
Really? The Governor is my cousin. Go!
Lady!
Fuck off!
Wanna have a drink with me?
Wanna go?
Are you too shy to say yes?
Take this money, quick!
It's the villain's!
Thank you, Miss!
Where's my money?
- It's must be her!
- You may leave first!
Beat her!
Shit!
Bingo!
- Is this a street performance?
- No! They're fighting!
Don't you think you can get away.
They've out-numbered her. lt's unfair.
- Shall we help her?
- Of course!
Don't hit her! Hit me!
My pleasure!
You hit me first!
Miss, are you alright?
Are you alright?
I'm okay!
The 15th move.
The 16th move.
17th.
18th.
20th...
The 35th move...
The 36th move...
The 36th move... Have you finished?
One last move! I created it myself!
Could you...
You can never learn
that skill I taught you.
Master Liu, who has done this to you?
Run, quick! The troops are coming.
Arrest those two monks!
- After them!
- Yes!
It stinks!
They're over there! After them!
Guess who I am!
Where are those two damned monks?
I look like a Cedan native.
So do you.
What are you playing?
It's a game devised by us.
Teach me!
If you win, you'll be senior.
If you lose, you'll be junior.
But he's senior every time.
You're just being slow.
You must be cheating!
If you play with me,
I'll be your godmother!
Godmother?
Get away!
Master Liu will offer
his respect to Buddha! Move!
How prevailing!
If he's a Buddhist, why is he so cruel?
He's like a snake inside.
He's Liu Jin, the Royal Eunuch!
He's killed less people than usual today!
I wish I could be as prevailed as he.
Go be a eunuch then.
Why not?
"Fu Shao Restaurant"
Eighth Master, you're being early today.
I'll prepare some nice dishes for you.
You may order for me.
Thank you.
Mister, there's a dark mist
on your forehead...
Piss off! Keep on eating...
Lady, there's a dark mist
on your forehead...
Are you looking for someone? May not be
a good thing even if you can find him.
- Would you like to buy a charm?
- Con man!
No big deal for not buying!
The most famous dish here
is roast pigeon!
Miss, do they have vegetarian food?
Plain rice is fine.
Junbao, one has to adapt himself
to strange environments.
Remember what Master told you?
Discover the spirit of Buddhism
in the secular world.
Let's try it with this bean curd.
"Love starts from the gaze."
Have more bean curd, or you'll have none.
Thank you.
Here's your meat.
Miss Liu, welcome.
- We have reserved this table for you.
- My dear.
What wish did Master make?
- Mind your own business.
- Yes!
- My dear, please.
- You first!
What do you want to eat, dear?
- Anything!
- Whatever you say.
Murong Bei! So it's really you.
Qiushue? What are you here for?
Shut up!
All this way for your husband!
How touching!
Regrettably, his name is no longer
Murong, but Liu, after my family.
He would have starved to death
if I had not saved him.
Men have no shame!
They'll stay beside you
if you keep them warm and happy.
Don't you see that?
Qiushue! Go home!
This guy has no heart!
For me, Murong Bei is
no longer a man, but a dog.
I used to play this guitar every night.
I would never agree to sell it
for the money I needed.
Now everything has changed. Take it back.
Trash!
I think you need it move.
Do you know who I am?
She's Liu Jin's sister.
Restrain yourself.
That's enough. I won't stand it anymore.
Dear, are you alright?
Dog!
Have you had enough?
I'm finished with you. Go away!
What are you staring at? Piss off!
Let me help you.
Miss, you're bleeding.
Excuse me...
Let's change the position.
Make way!
Stand still!
Shit!
Shameless!
Don't be afraid! I'm here...
Who are fighting inside?
Don't move, everybody!
The troops are here! Stop fighting!
Why are the troops always after us?
Don't let those two Cedanians get away.
Yes!
Follow me.
What's wrong? The troops are coming.
There! After them!
Go to hell!
It's heavy!
It's a woman. Of course it's heavy!
Buddha, forgive me for being lustful.
Lower your voice!
Over here, quick!
Where are those two guys?
Back to the restaurant?
Why are we back again?
This is a branch.
Really! This restaurant
is known across the country.
You two sleep on the floor.
I'll look after her.
I feel more at ease with being a monk.
Junbao, we mustn't rely on others
Iike that guy Murong Bei.
Sure. We'll work for the restaurant.
They'll let us stay here
just for the night.
They can't let us stay forever.
I promise I'll become
an official one day.
Well, it doesn't matter to me
what you are as long as you're honest.
Go along with your late!
Let's go to sleep.
My fate?
I promise I'll be rich one day!
Liu Jin would never have imagined
that his bribe money...
would be stolen from him.
What shall we do with the money?
We should give it back
to those who owned it.
Give it to the poor.
Right... He collected
this tax money from the people.
So long as he lives,
we'll keep stealing from him.
These people are rebels!
Let's not get into trouble and leave.
I can't pretend I didn't see what I saw.
Alright... go to sleep.
Another masked-thief!
How dare you steal from Master Liu!
So what!
They threw a piece of gold
into my room last night.
They're worth 300 teals of gold each...
Mind your own business.
- Delicious!
- Yeah!
- Roasted human flesh bun!
Gentleman,
I am a newcomer to this place...
What're you performing?
Hitting your chest with an iron hammer?
No. It's human sandbag.
What's that?
One cent for a punch.
- What do I gain from that?
- Right!
If I yell in pain,
I'll pay you three cents.
What if you throw up blood?
I'll pay you six cents.
What if I kill you?
If I'm dead...
you have had my life!
lt's worth at least fifty cents.
Right! Worth fifty punches.
You'll die from that!
Die...
Enough, boss?
- More.
- Go on.
I'll kill you.
46, 47, 48...
Does it hurt?
I was just pretending
in order to hook him.
Boss, he's falling apart!
Quick, get up.
Get up and beat him.
Where're my servants?
I'll pay you to beat them to death.
How effortless it is to earn these!
It's not good enough.
I wanna make big money.
I just wanna have a good meal.
I wanna buy a house and be the boss.
How many more punches
do you have to take?
Give me the money.
Why?
For tax! Fifty cents
for your personal profit tax.
Another fifty
for using the government land.
Another fifty for entertainment tax.
Total a hundred and fifty.
- I am not going to pay.
- This is tax evasion.
Arrest them.
Sir, we are just common people...
we'll never dare argue with you.
Please accept these money. Sir.
You're smart.
Sir, we are new here.
We don't know nothing but fight.
We want to work for you, Sir.
You surely know how to please me.
Beat him!
Thank you, Sir.
He deserves it.
My pleasure, Sir.
Well, you're real smart.
The Royal Eunuch, Master Liu,
is recruiting newcomers...
Alright, follow me.
Thank you, Sir. Junbao, let's go.
You're really going?
I'm not coming.
I'll come look for you
when I become a high official.
Tianbao. Take care!
I wish you every good.
This is bad for your health.
Little Melon, there's something
which you simply can't forget.
You wouldn't understand.
Where's Tianbao?
Look at me! You still
want the company of men?
I didn't say I like him.
Very telling! Drink up!
This is wine, not tea.
No one drinks like this.
Don't drink anymore.
Give it back to me!
It's broken. No more wine.
Kid, one should enjoy one's life.
You're okay.
Mind your own business.
Stop drinking,
- will you?
- None of your business.
Again?
He'll stop when he's tired.
I can't stand it anymore.
I have wine here.
I don't know which side I'd be on.
- What do you want?
- lt's my own life!
I'll do what I like.
Go on...
Break them all so that there won't be
any wine left. Let me help you.
Will you calm down?
Zhang Junbao, will you let go of me?
Stop!
You...
Calm down!
The past only makes up one's experience.
It mustn't become one's burden.
If you go on like this,
you'll only have yourself to hurt.
Why are you always
playing with that ball?
I'm trying to understand the "Tao".
Everything is round in Taoism.
The sun is round, so is the moon.
One has to be a little smooth
and round, too.
Who's the boss here?
Show his face!
Sirs, you're early.
We haven't started business yet.
Do they come for tax again?
Come in and have some dim-sum.
Cut the crap. Pay your tax.
We did a few days ago.
You ate a few days ago, didn't you?
Master Liu is expanding his armament.
You've to pay a military uniform tax
and entry tax, a good-living tax...
This restaurant has to pay taxes
worth 500 taels of gold.
It's worse than robbery?
You aren't involved in
anti-government activities, are you?
Even the government has to be reasonable.
Bullshit.
Be patient!
Whoever has a sword in his hand
can raise his voice.
Eat this!
Persevere!
If you don't eat this,
I'll arrest everyone here!
Does he look stupid?
No! We mustn't bring troubles
to our brothers.
It's alright if you don't have any money.
But you must koutow to me for 30 times,
I'll consider granting you an exemption.
Koutow, quick!
Kneel!
You're tough!
If you don't kneels, it'll mean that
you're an anti-government rebel.
I'll execute you.
This is too much. Go to hell!
Koutow!
You rebels! I'll kill all of you.
You go to hell!
Shut the door. Don't let anyone go!
What sins we've committed!
You go get rid of these corpses.
Get him! We'll be dead
if we let go of him.
It's not right! How come you're
running backwards?
We're both vegetarians
and therefore of the same species.
Do me a favor.
Shit! It's almost the barracks!
Please, run!
If we don't get him, it'll mean disaster.
What happened, Sir?
The gang at the restaurant are rebels.
I'll report to Master Liu.
- Stop him!
- Yes!
I've killed him for you.
Junbao, the ones at the restaurant
aren't good people.
You mustn't go around with them.
I think they're pretty nice people.
Now I'm a soldier and you're a criminal.
We'll become enemies.
No!
How is your life in the barracks?
I have always been the bully.
How are you?
Me? I think I like my old days better.
We were so carefree.
I'd be extremely happy
if I had a sweet bun.
Junbao, don't think of the past anymore.
Look at what's lying in front of you.
It's reality.
I'll fulfill my wish one day.
How do I ride this horse?
It's simple.
It's too fast.
I am the Lord of my own destiny!
The purpose of today's contest
is to choose...
the person with the best
martial arts skill to be the general.
Let's start.
Master, it's too easy for me.
So, whoever isn't convinced
can come up and challenge me.
Master, my name is Dong Tianbao.
May I learn from you?
My pleasure.
Yes!
Very vicious!
I'll warn him.
Master!
Disband!
You're trespassed your rank.
You're not worth being a soldier.
You've shamed me.
Don't you know that in the army,
you mustn't offend the majority?
Luckily the Master is being very kind...
Master...
I was being too impatient.
I don't want to be just a soldier.
Give me one more chance
and I'll perform for you.
Then I'll wait to see your performance.
Qiushue, you can be a bar-tender here...
Good idea! As long as
there's wine for me, I'll be happy.
Junbao can be a waiter.
Yeah!
Will you wash the toilet?
No problem.
Will you wash my underclothes?
Okay...
Stinking monk! You're so lazy!
You don't wash your underpants?
What are you laughing at?
Tianbao.
What bring you back, Tianbao?
Quick, let's go.
They've found out everything...
the money you stole
from the Master and the killings.
Master Liu is leading
the troops to arrest you.
Let's go, then.
You go first. I'll destroy the evidence.
- Be careful!
- Quick!
- Go inside and arrest them!
- Yes!
Boss!
Did you kill my tax officer?
You impotent oppressor! I'll kill you.
Boss, rest in peace!
Bless us in heaven!
We must revenge for Boss.
I'll go to the barracks single-handedly
and kill the Master!
Do you have a plan?
How can you be so impatient?
Last time he didn't plan,
yet he killed them all.
We can't fight the whole army!
You must know the other
anti-government gangs.
Why didn't you contact
and join forces with them?
I'll head the attack.
Good! I'll be the internal connection.
Most of the army will cross the river
for a practice 2 days later.
This is the best chance
to assassinate Master Liu.
You should try contact
the other comrades...
All right!
We'll co-ordinate with each other
and destroy them.
- Great!
- Let's prepare for the strike.
- Yes!
- Tianbao! Take care!
That way!
Who is it?
It's me. Just bad a leak.
- I wanna pee. Together?
- Okay?
I'm nervous. Makes me wanna pee, too.
Be serious.
- Where's the Master?
- Resting inside.
There are only a few guards.
We must not waste the chance.
Right!
- Why is it like this?
- Where's Tianbao?
Kill them!
Attack!
Strike! Come on, kill them!
Strike!
I've killed five of them, Blacksmith.
What a tragic fate I have!
Keep your life.
To live is to die, to die is to live.
Tianbao, did you betray us?
I wanna earn more than my life's worth.
Brother blacksmith...
Who'd betrayed us?
Brother blacksmith, hang on...
Tianbao?
Let's go.
Qiushue!
Junbao, run!
I've overestimated their strength!
But your clever set-up...
did save me a lot of troubles.
I'm remain loyal to you, Master.
If you can betray your best friends...
you can also betray me in the future.
Master, my career depends on you.
Will I destroy my own career?
Tianbao, I should have promoted you
to General last time.
But you were only a soldier.
Your promotion would cause jealousy
among your fellow soldiers.
But from now on,
you'll be the Royal Lieutenant.
Thank you, Master.
The one who escaped
has great martial arts skill.
I'll need the best persons.
Recruit him if you can.
Let's all work for his Majesty.
Destroy him if you can't.
- Get up. Let me carry you.
- Stop pretending.
You traitor!
You dragged them to death.
Go to your good brother
for wealth and poor!
My poor brothers, how you have died!
I'll kill you.
Don't...
He doesn't feel any better than you.
He was betrayed by the one
he trusted most.
We mustn't blame him.
It's all your fault!
Let's go back!
Junbao!
I'll go save them by myself.
I know you'll be mad at me.
But I just wanted to save you.
Those rebels would have met
their fate sooner or later.
The most important thing is,
we'll be together ever after.
I thought you're a ruthless person.
I've never realized that
you can't even give up a woman.
Master... I was being too impulsive.
I beg your forgiveness.
I'll kill you.
You're betrayed us. You should die, too.
How can you keep a rebel in you barrack?
Are you a lieutenant?
I'm successful because
I don't need a woman.
Master doesn't like woman.
I mustn't destroy my career
for a woman either.
But I didn't ask you to kill her.
Thank you, Master.
Junbao, the door of great wealth
has been opened for you.
It's awaiting your entry.
I don't want it. Release her.
Have you forgotten that
we've been together for twenty years?
We shared everything among ourselves.
Master Liu has agreed to promote us.
We've got lots of opportunities.
Let's build our career on these
and be a great man.
I don't know you anymore.
I don't know anyone
who betrays his friends for wealth.
Just look at the fate of those rebels!
They died because I trusted you.
I'm responsible for their lives.
Release her.
Whoever stops me must die!
- Strike!
- Yes.
I'll ask you one more.
Will you join me?
I'm all by myself. I'm useless to you.
Junbao, don't press me.
You pressed me into this.
Junbao, your kung-fu is inferior to mine.
For all of them innocent victims.
I'll have to fight you.
I've killed Little Melon, too.
I am not surprised to hear that.
Junbao, I'll strike.
I wanna teach you. One more stance.
Strike fist to forestall the enemy.
"One-Thousand-Catties Pendant"!
Junbao!
Put it on his wound.
This is very effective.
Persevere. It won't hurt.
Why doesn't he feel anything?
How come?
He's no feeling at all.
Is it painful?
Very painful.
Hang on!
What do you think?
He's had the hardest blow of his life.
He was betrayed by someone
he most trusted...
and so many people were killed
because of that.
This accounts for his abnormal behavior.
Will he be able to recover?
Maybe in a couple of days.
You knew that I'd mistrusted Tianbao!
You're a Sacred Man.
You shake your head and sign.
Admirable...
I don't think he can recover
in two or three year's time.
Admirable!
- I didn't betray you.
- Junbao...
I didn't betray you. I didn't.
It's alright! It's just a dream.
No, it's true. It's all true.
They were all sitting here.
The Boss, the blacksmith...
Drink some wine to calm down yourself.
Come on.
To calm myself?
I know I killed you.
But I can't control myself.
Sorry...
Will this work?
No harm in trying.
Make him talk.
Junbao.
- Sacred Man.
- Sacred Man?
The Sacred Man is dead.
- This will do you good.
- Yeah, it is.
I don't want any good, you take it.
Hey, don't go...
There's no need to cry like this.
No, he punctured my crying nerve point.
You've been punctured too.
It's your laughing nerve point.
You're a pile of shit.
He Kun, how did you train your troops?
Shitty coach, shitty soldiers!
You don't have to insult me.
The way you coach them...
they'll rebel against you someday.
Only the best will survive.
Including yourself.
Dong Tianbao,
although you control the military...
you mustn't forget,
I'm the one who gave you your break.
The military law has no room
for gratefulness.
He Kun, we have no friendship.
I think we should stop.
I'll go see Master Liu.
Those who disobey must die.
Go on practice.
Junbao.
Where's he?
Strange.
Junbao.
Stay cool.
Why? You look awful.
Watch out for your wounds!
I'm okay!
You should all stay cool.
Come out.
It hurts...
This is a good sign of recovery.
Master!
Master, I'm afraid...
I don't want to practice kung-fu,
I don't want to fight.
I am just a little hungry.
Master, you've lost weight
and grown taller!
More wrinkles,
but still smart and handsome.
Junbao...
That's only a log, not your Master.
Don't hit me...
Don't kick me.
- Don't kick me.
- Please.
Are you alright?
Yes!
- Does this look okay?
- Alright.
It's alright,
he simply needs a good rest.
Go to sleep...
This sheet is too small.
Is this okay?
If I don't make it this time.
I'll slap myself ten times.
Rest well and you'll recover.
Gosh! I deserve it...
12345678...
You helped me build my confidence once!
I'll help you do the same.
Ten times more.
We mustn't let down the Lieutenant.
- He has high hopes on us.
- Yes.
Whoever doesn't practice hard enough...
will be persecuted by military law.
- Listen, soldiers.
- Yes.
To practice kung-fu,
you must have a body hard as steel.
Keep on practicing, don't ever stop.
Zhang Junbao, you've caused
the deaths of so many people...
you deserve to die, too.
I'll take your life.
- Take my life.
- He does this almost every morning.
Don't you understand?
You do? I don't understand what you said.
I do.
He's like this at noon, too.
The third time happens in the evening.
Three time a day.
Let's call him
"Sanfeng" (Thrice crazy) instead.
Junbao, time to eat.
You haven't eaten for three days now.
You eat your rice,
you don't smell them, Sanfeng.
Eat!
Punctual as a clock, Sanfeng!
Master, these are the rebels I arrested.
And the tax I collected.
You've done my job.
I'm just learning from you, Master.
I simply want you to enjoy your office.
There're rebellions
all across the country...
Except my province.
Tax returns are high, too.
His Highness has asked me
to report to the Royal Court.
We'll be loyal to you, Master...
to return the kindness
you bestowed on us.
The other officials
should learn from you.
Why don't you join me to the Capital?
Thank you, Master.
But before that I don't want
to hear anymore rebellions...
nor any discontents of the Court.
Yes, Master.
We wish you the best of luck, Lieutenant.
Junbao, the water is dirty.
Drink this.
Thank you.
Your hands are dirty, wash them.
They're clean now.
Junbao, I've told you that they're dirty.
Me dirty? Okay, I'll wash myself.
No, Junbao...
Let me wash.
The sun and the air will help you.
I'll stand over here.
The sun will burn me.
No.
Nature has its own life.
This tree has withered,
but a new life has just begun.
You can be that.
Brother...
What's the matter?
Sister-in-law has just given birth.
- Go home now.
- Really?
Quick...
What shall we call the baby?
The firewood are surely heavy.
Your child's waiting for you.
Put down the firewood, you're greedy.
Right... Quick!
Wait!
Lower your burden,
run towards the new life.
I wish he could be home quickly.
Lower your burden,
run towards the new life.
This is the book of the "Qi",
not a bible of martial arts.
When you're confused,
it can bring you peace.
This book of the "Qi" is so mild,
it doesn't want to kill the enemy,
but teach you how to make
the best use of the chance.
Stick together.
Don't use force. The force will break it.
But if I don't use force,
how to break it?
Not to use trick.
Trick will end it.
Keep the air to match the universe.
No desire, no lust.
What other moves have you devised?
No root, no dust, all natural.
That's called Tai Chi.
Tai Chi?
I am alright.
It's just that I still feel
a certain responsibility.
The past forms parts of your experience.
It shouldn't become your burden.
Junbao, eat.
You've just recovered. You must eat more.
Sanfeng.
Sanfeng (Triple richness)?
Zhang Sanfeng? Sounds good.
Yes...
Forget the past, Junbao!
Why doesn't he sleep in a lying position?
He can't sleep.
That's why he doesn't lie down.
Cut the crap.
He's put a piece of iron down under.
Let your breath precipitate.
Keep your centre of gravity and
use other's force to strike your force.
A swirling ball can spin away
other objects that hit on it.
But the ball stands on itself
steady and firm.
I didn't eat because of you.
Shit.
There are always movements
even in stillness.
He seems to have understood something.
No matter how hard I strike the ball,
it'll spring back by the water.
The stronger you are,
the stronger the opponent.
I can't even defeat water!
How are you, Junbao?
Have you gone crazy again?
I know what is natural now.
Everything is found in the nature.
Who is he?
"My hands do not have
strength and power."
"My heart embraces peace and calm."
"Resigning myself to adversity.
Seeing richness out of void."
"Violence be turned to peace.
There are always guiding fate."
"Dynamic or still. Divide or multiple."
"Follow fate to go in and out
of mortal world. Merciless is mercy."
"Dynamic or still. Divide or multiple."
"Follow heart and not be aggressive.
Merciless is mercy."
"Follow fate to go in and out
of mortal world. Merciless is mercy"
"Follow heart and not be aggressive.
Merciless is mercy."
What is the matter?
My dear.
Kneel!
Where's Zhang Junbao? Any accomplice?
Who? Which Zhang Junbao?
Kill his wife!
- Mom...
- If kill her, he doesn't confess.
- Dad...
- No...
Don't kill my daughter.
- Kill!
- Sweetheart!
You killer! Damn you.
- You killer!
- You are cheap!
Whoever defends for Zhang Junbao
is an enemy of mine.
The end will be like this.
Reverend Ling!
What happened?
Dong Tianbao is getting
more and more powerful.
He's even more ruthless than Master Liu.
He's killed the whole family
of the food-store owner.
He said he's going to kill more people...
if we didn't inform on your whereabout.
Take care of yourself. We'll go first.
You, too.
Taoism teaches us to avoid disaster
and behave ourselves. Let's go.
Taoism also teaches us to forget oneself
and save other people's lives.
You should know
the importance of nothingness.
If you've a heart, it doesn't matter
if you must practice none thingess.
To avoid more deaths...
I must stop him.
If ever something happens to you.
It's all predestined!
I will go with you.
Reverend, you'd better stay.
I know I'll only bring you trouble.
These charms usually don't work.
I hope they'll work this time.
I've studied Taoism all my life.
But you realize its truth all in a blink.
You'll be the Master of Masters.
I'd better retire.
Congratulations. Please.
You'll have a long life
and enjoy great wealth.
May God bless you!
You rebels, how dare you come here?
To meet your fate?
This is the end of your life.
You can't escape anymore.
Kill him.
God is benevolent!
Why fight with swords and weapon?
Don't kill me.
I just want a favor.
Get up.
- Don't get mad.
- Be careful of Master Liu.
Step back.
Junbao, you've become smarter
by taking Master Liu as a hostage.
I've been a smart man all my life.
I'll never employ such tricks.
What do you want?
I wanna tell you.
You've chosen a way of no return.
You've always been inferior to me,
in terms of conspiracies
and martial arts.
I've even exploited you once.
You're no equivalent to me.
Tell him to kneel.
Kneel...
Kneel!
You're kneeling to me now...
How will you defeat me?
Junbao, didn't you like to help people?
I earned my power
by paying a lot of efforts.
I won't give it up.
Do me a favor.
Release Master Liu.
Fame and wealth are only temporary.
I'm acting for Heaven.
I'm my own God.
What school of boxing is this?
Nature is the origin of everything.
Tai Chi!
Junbao, I'll never allow myself
to be defeated by you.
You're obsessed with lust and desires.
How can you win?
"One-Thousand-Catties Pendant!"
You can't balance yourself,
how can you attack?
Go down!
Use other's force to strike one's force.
Kill him!
No one move!
I'll kill whoever moves.
Attack! Why don't you attack him?
- Don't you move, too!
- I don't move...
You!
Master Liu ordered me not to move,
it's not my wish.
Dong Tianbao,
if only I lose a single hair...
I'll chop your head.
- Master Liu...
- He killed the Master.
- What should we do...
- Master Liu...
Master Liu has died. Now I'm the leader.
- Attack!
- Go...
He's killed Master Liu.
He'll kill you all sooner or later.
Will you still help him?
Don't move!
Step back.
Everyone has deserted you now.
No one's going to help you.
Help me, are you going to against me?
You deserve it.
You don't ever treat us as human beings.
You took us as buddies
when you were a soldier.
But you put on air
once you were promoted.
Kill him...
Please forgive me before l die.
I've wronged you!
Junbao, think of the times
we spent together...
Will you forgive me?
You always defended me
when we were small.
Don't trust him.
Go to hell.
Okay...
If he dies, what about me?
Let's part here.
Where're you going?
I'm bringing Tianbao's ashes
to the Master.
Shall we see each other again?
Our fate will tell.
Farewell, Zhang Sanfeng.