Fu-seng, finish him off
Give it to me
Where is my sister?
Shoot if you dare
Hold me up
Take your hands off me
Watch that side for me
And what will you do?
You're removing your vest?
Hold it
It's full of dynamite
Dynamite? The evil bastard
I cannot get shot
Neither can I
Hurry
Get in
I told you I shouldn't have brought you
So clumsy
You're clumsy
See what we can use
The gun is empty
Catch
Freeze, or I'll shoot
What did he say?
I don't know
I don't think they will dare to shoot
I'll count to three
Pretend to throw a hand grenade
One, two, three
What?
Didn't you hear me say "pretend"?
Speak clearly next time
Come out, Chaibat
What's the occasion, General?
Chaibat, you dare come to my place
and wreak havoc!
You make me lose face
And vice versa
What happened just now
You never even tried to help me
How can you blame me? How can I
explain to them?
You don't have to explain to anyone
I'll take over your goods from now on
I'll repay your losses this time
You think a repayment will be enough?
I can't help it if you refuse
But I know you are clever
And of course I came prepared
If your eyes are still good
look around you
God, I also don't want to go too far
But as for taking all my goods
That is not my decision
Do you want to see Mr. Ginsha?
If you will make the introduction
I wouldn't mind the trip
Good; get the helicopter ready
Yes, sir
Are you all right?
Chaibat
You had my sister wear a dynamite-
stuffed vest so she can be your shield?
What if she got shot?
Don't move
No one dares speak to me
in that tone
Hua-nui
You bastard
See? This is bullet-proof
I would not treat my team like that
These two are cute
Chaibat, you are great; this way
Take them to Malaysia to wait for me
Have fun!
The scum; we'll get him sooner or later
Miss Ching, Mr. Chaibat says hello
You came to tell me this?
No matter what the verdict is
w can still appeal
I know local law well
There must be a reason for his confidence
Talk is cheap
Yes, he wants to ask you...
where the Swiss bank code is
I'll tell him when I see him
Get your bearings
Let me take a picture of you two
How about right here?
Smile
Let's look over there
Fu-seng, this side is important
Gather around
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to Merdeka
Square; and now behind us we have...
Familiarize yourself with this street
Let's go over there
Serious offenders go through here
Take a good look
Pao, can you tell us what
we will be doing?
I'll tell you when the time comes
Let's look at the intersection
Do you want to go for a swim?
Do you think Chaibat wants a jailbreak?
It's possible
I wonder when
You heard him, he'll tell us...
when the time comes
Let's go swimming together
Let's take a picture together
Come, let's take another one
Stand still
Sorry
The pictures are ready
We don't know anything
and we've lost contact with Hong Kong
What are we doing here?
Look
At what?
My brain, it's thinking the same thing
Look, she's cute
Very exciting
Let's go over to see
What's happening?
May, what's wrong?
Nothing
Would you like a drink?
What's going on?
My girlfriend is here
Where is she now?
She's coming over
Give me a massage
Ka-kui, Chan Ka-kui
Chan Ka-kui
Yes, Miss?
I'm just picking up my pictures
Fu-seng
What are you doing?
Headache
Your brother must be pent up
After we finish this job...
I'll take him to enjoy himself
Great!
Excellent
I feel much better now
Have you ordered yet?
We don't know what to order
Because we don't know English
I'll order; what do you want?
Paris Water
What?
Do you want one?
I'll have Paris Water as well
I'll teach you later
Hua-nui, I'll teach you, come
Be brave, tell the waiter:
"Two Perriers", okay?
It's all right, go ahead
Chan Ka-kui
Chan ka-kui
Miss, are you talking to me?
May, listen to me
No; don't explain anything
Do you have the number for the
chemical materials truck?
What's Fu-seng doing? Flirting?
I left it in the room
I'll get it later
I'll go see what's going on
Hurry, I'll wait in the lobby
I'm really working on a case
If people know my identity
I will die
If I were here on vacation
I'd be swimming now
Thank you
I can't talk too much
Where is your room?
I'll call you later
Why are you still here?
What's going on?
Brother said he's not interested
She wants my business
I said "no", get away
Don't touch me
Go!
Get away!
Don't make faces at me!
I'm just talking to my boyfriend,
stay out!
Not bad
But my sister doesn't like it
How much?
I guess not too expensive
Who is your boyfriend?
Leave her, let's find a better one
She's fine, a shame to waste
What the hell are you doing to May?
Miss, if he won't have you, I will
How much do you charge?
Only your mother would charge
Drink water
What are you doing? May!
Let's go
Are you okay?
Yes
Let's go
Give me your key
Why?
I left mine by the pool
Go get it for me
Hurry back, don't run off
What's happening. Miss?
I want to cry
Miss, you cannot solicit
customers here
Your mother solicits
We are staying here
How can I help you?
Kill the people who pushed me
into the pool
What did he say?
He said we're so beautiful
She is a hooker
May, please let me explain
I can't talk about it
Fine
May
Let go of my hand
I know you've been offended
You do?
The whole hotel...
thinks I'm a prostitute
What do you want me to do?
Come here
You should know now what I'm doing
Please smile
Call Uncle Bill when you get back...
Go to hell, you bastard!
May
Let go, I said I don't want your business
I'd rather have the gentleman behind you
than do business with you
Look in the mirror
I'm not having anyone as ugly as you
A pretty hooker is a sign of trouble
Let's go
What's going on?
Nothing, I'll tell you later
Let's go, hurry up
What is it?
Same thing
First things first; can you drive a truck?
Yes
Excellent
Why don't you call from the room?
A public phone is better
I told you to get my key
I forgot; I'll go get it now
See you in the room
What's going on?
I'm not too sure
That was my boyfriend
Really?
He's an undercover police; I think he's...
on a case, but I'm not sure
He didn't tell you?
No, because it's too dangerous
But I just did something which he would...
never dream I would be so clever
Like what?
I don't want to talk about it
Get some good rest
Bye, May, I'll see you tomorrow
Okay; oh, don't be late
Okay
Hua-nui, where is Pao?
Telephone, Pao
No matter what you hear, act as though
nothing is happening
Our two assistant now
He is Chan Ka-kui of the
Royal Hong Kong Police
I have his girlfriend
You decide what we should do
All right, we'll push it back one day
Don't worry, we're delaying by one day
Give me your guns
Case 2370192 Ching Wing-xi
with regard to the charge, I am satisfied...
that the evidence produced
by the prosecution...
has not be rebutted by the defence
The accused does not cast any unreasonable
doubt on the prosecution's case
Under the circumstances,
I find the accused...
guilty as charged...
and convict her on the charge
and sentence her to death
All rise
Chan Ka-kui
Over
They are walking towards you
If you don't want your girlfriend harmed...
you better pay attention
Copy
Out of the way! I don't have brakes
Stop
No brakes
Back up, everyone
Where did you learn how to drive?
Poison gas inside the car! Go away!
What did he say? I don't know
Let me go
The chemicals are toxic;
you'll die if you inhale them
Get out of here now!
Hurry, disperse the crowd
Let me go
Hurry up
Go
What are you doing?
Get in, hurry
I won't let her go until I see May
Get in first
No deal
Ka-kui, save me
Let my wife go now
Ka-kui
Let May go, or I'll shoot her
I'm scared
Let her go or none of us can go
Ka-kui
May
In the car, hurry
May, are you all right?
Boss, the police are here
Let's go, hurry
Get her an ambulance
Stop, give me back my car
Come down, hurry
Pao, crash into him
Hua-nui, get down
Over there
Someone's on the roof
She's up there, coming over here
Up there
Are you all right?
Chase him, hurry
Out of the way!
This way
We'll go that way
Back off, remove her handcuffs
Well?
Give me the gun
Boss is coming, hurry
They're over there
Over there
Wait there, Boss is coming
They're over there
Hurry, fly over
What are you doing?
I dropped my gun
Pretend you have one
Pretend?
They don't have guns
Run!
Don't move
Back off, or I'll shoot
Beat him up
You'll die for sure
Great timing!
Come down, save me
Okay
Climb up
Are you all right?
Leave me; chase them
Let's go
Kill him
Fly over there
Land on the train
Got it
Save him
Hurry, save me
Fly lower to get Boss
Kwong, get down here
Boss, are you all right?
I'm fine, kill him
Hang on
Take off
How are you?
Get him!
Help
Get in
Come up
3386776, code 1270WKU
That is my Swiss bank account code
Anyone can get the money
I'd love to get the money...
but it belongs to the
Hong Kong government
No, it belongs to all China's people
Let our Hong Kong Government hold it
After 1997, we will also be China's
people, and it will be yours, too
No way