(CAMERA CLICKING)
Am I staring?
A little.
RUBY: Sorry.
You just have such beautiful skin.
I'm Ruby, by the way.
Do you have a name,
or you want me to guess?
- Jesse.
And you just got to LA, Jesse?
How did you know?
You've got that look.
Oh, don't worry, honey.
That whole deer-in-the-headlights thing
is exactly what they want.
Here. Let me help you with that.
Are you a model?
No, I do makeup.
So, where are you staying?
At a motel in Pasadena.
By yourself?
Mmm-hmm.
What do your parents think about that?
They don't really.
Don't think, or just don't care?
They're not around anymore.
I'm sorry.
Hey, You wanna go somewhere?
Where?
A party.
What kind of party?
The fun kind.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(INAUDIBLE)
God, I love this color on me.
RUBY: Red Rum.
What?
That's what it's called.
They say women are
more likely to buy a lipstick
if it's named after food or sex.
(TOILET FLUSHING)
Just think about it.
Black Honey.
Plum Passion.
Peachy Keen.
Pink Pussy.
(RUBY LAUGHS)
What about you, Sarah,
what would your lipstick be called?
Fuck off.
RUBY: Apt.
What about you?
What about me?
Are you food
or are you sex?
She's dessert because she's so sweet.
Hmm.
Shouldn't we get back to the party?
Don't talk.
Still.
(RUBY LAUGHS)
So what do we think?
I think that I wish I had your hair.
Is this your natural color?
You are just so beautiful.
Don't you think that she's just perfect?
Is that your real nose?
JESSE: Yeah.
God, life is so unfair.
Gigi just got out of the body shop.
She's still a little sensitive.
You had work done?
You say that like it's a bad thing.
Sweet, plastics is just good grooming.
Imagine going a year
without brushing your teeth.
I go to this guy in Beverly Hills.
- RUBY: Andrew.
- GIGI: Dr. Andrew.
- She is in love with him.
- GIGI: (CHUCKLES) Of course I love him.
Look at me.
He calls me The Bionic Woman.
Is that a compliment?
(SARAH SNICKERS)
I hear your parents are dead.
That must be really hard for you.
Do you have other family?
No.
GIGI: No one at all?
You must have a boyfriend.
(JESSE STAMMERS)
All she really wants to know is,
who are you fucking?
Sorry?
What?
Isn't that what everyone wants to know?
A pretty new girl walks into a room,
everyone's head turns,
looks her up and down, wondering,
"Who is she fucking?
"Who could she fuck?
"And how high can she climb,
and is it higher than me?"
I don't... I don't know.
I just got to town,
so I don't know anybody here.
Right. But you've slept with men before.
You do sleep with men, don't you?
All the time.
I think I will get back to the party.
Someone said there was gonna be a show.
RUBY: Jesse, are you coming?
(DOOR CLOSING)
(ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING)
ROBERTA: Who did you say shot these?
A boyfriend?
Not really.
Not really or no?
No.
It was just some guy, he found me online.
Be careful with that.
You're very fit.
Thank you.
You're also very young.
I think you're perfect.
I would never say you're fat.
But that doesn't mean
that someone else won't.
Understand?
I see 20 or 30 girls
come in here every day.
Mostly from small towns with big dreams
because some guy named Chad
in the food court told them
they were beautiful enough to be a model.
And they're all good.
You...
You're going to be great.
Some girls crack under the pressure,
but if you do okay,
then we are off to New York.
You'll work with all the top designers.
International success.
So the first thing we need to do
is get you some pictures
that are a little less amateur hour,
no offense.
Jack MacArthur is in town. Do you know him?
No.
Get to know him.
I had to pull some strings,
but I sent him your Polaroids,
and he has agreed to do a test with you.
How does that sound?
It sounds great.
It sounds...
Sounds good.
Well, there's just a teensy bit
of paperwork.
I'll need a copy of your drivers license
and a voided check,
and I can take those right now.
When did you graduate from high school?
I'm actually still kind of working on it.
I need a parental consent form.
You can go.
Parental consent form.
Just one signature there
for parental consent.
One little signature and we're off.
When someone asks,
I want you to say you are 19.
Always 19.
Eighteen is too on the nose.
No one's going to believe that.
Honey.
People believe what they are told.
- Hi.
- I have...
- I bought you flowers, but...
- (CHUCKLES) Oh. Sorry. You go.
- No, you first.
I was just gonna say
I signed with that agency.
That's great news. Congratulations.
Thanks.
Hey, did they say anything
about my pictures?
Didn't come up.
Cool, that's cool.
Come on.
Don't forget me when you're all famous now.
(JESSE CHUCKLES)
In Georgia, the sky is also this big.
Makes being a person down on Earth
feel really small.
You could feel small here, too.
Do you?
Sometimes.
When I was a kid,
I would sneak out onto the roof at night.
I thought the moon
looked like a big round eye.
And I would look up and I'd say,
"Do you see me?"
I would stay out there for hours.
Sometimes I'd fall asleep just dreaming.
About what?
What I would be.
What was that?
I could never figure it out.
I can't sing. I can't dance.
I can't write. (CHUCKLES)
No real talent.
But I'm pretty,
and I can make money off pretty.
So...
I think you're probably good
at a lot of things.
You can't tell.
We just met.
We didn't just meet.
We met the other day.
Trust me.
I can tell.
They want me to lie.
Who wants you to lie?
The agency.
They want me to say I'm 19.
How old are you?
Sixteen last month.
You know, I think
I left the stove on at home.
Stop.
(DEAN SIGHS)
DEAN: Listen. I think
you ought to do what you think is right.
I should go.
- Bye.
Thank you.
(SIGHS)
DEAN: Jesse.
Do you wanna go out again?
Yeah. That...
That'd be cool.
(SWITCHES CLICKING)
(GASPING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (LOUD THUD)
- (SCREAMS)
(SIREN WAILING)
(BANGING)
- HANK: Yeah?
- Something's in my room.
What do you mean,
something's in your room?
I saw something in my room.
HANK: Are you high?
What are you doing?
Calling the police.
Whoa, whoa, whoa...
Relax, okay?
Mikey.
MIKEY: Yeah?
This lady has an unwanted guest.
212.
All right, asshole. Party's over.
Open up.
Give me the key.
(LOCK RATTLING)
(GRUNTS)
Mikey, open the door.
(SWITCH CLICKING)
Mikey.
The fuck?
You're paying for this.
I didn't do it.
- You fucking kids are all the fucking same.
- (GASPS)
I will find you.
Got it?
There's your visitor.
(SNARLING)
(CAMERA CLICKING)
(INAUDIBLE)
You're done.
Let's go show him.
Jack?
Ready, ready.
Take off your shoes.
All right, everybody.
Thank you for your work.
It's gonna be a closed set.
I don't mind staying. It's not a problem.
We're good.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Take off your clothes.
Is there a problem?
All of it.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Turn around.
(OPENS CASE)
(INAUDIBLE)
Jesse.
You're still here?
How did it go?
It went good.
It was great actually.
Did he say anything?
My agency said
if the pictures turned out good,
he might consider them for an editorial.
Do you think he would?
I think he makes
a lot of promises to young girls.
I should go, before my meter runs out.
I don't think you should be alone with him.
He seemed fine to me.
That's not what I'm saying, Jesse.
I'm not as helpless as I look.
(LAUGHING)
Will you promise me something?
Will you call me if you need anything?
Night or day. Doesn't matter.
Give me your phone.
It's good to have good girls around.
- (CAMERA CLICKS)
- (CHUCKLES)
You promise you'll call?
I promise.
Thank you for the makeup today.
RUBY: Sorry I'm late.
WAITRESS: Would you
like to hear the specials?
- Sure.
- (SCOFFS) You're not gonna eat it.
But they work so hard to memorize them.
WAITRESS: Today we have a loaded
baked potato with a side of broccoli,
a pan-seared halibut
served with rice and a fruit cup,
and a steak sandwich that comes with fries.
If I don't want fries,
could I substitute the fruit cup?
WAITRESS: If you just want the fruit,
you'll have to order the fruit bowl.
How about we just have three coffees
and a fruit cup?
How was the shoot?
Jesse was there.
Who?
Oh, yeah, her.
Why?
RUBY: Jack was shooting her.
What?
She's been in town for, like, a minute.
They brought her in for a test.
Jack doesn't test new models.
RUBY: Well, he does now.
Apparently, they think
she is gonna be this giant star.
Jack shoots me all the time.
That's not gonna last.
GIGI: What's that supposed to mean?
SARAH: It means
your expiration date is almost due.
Who wants sour milk
when you can get fresh meat?
Right.
Sarah, these girls
come and go all the time.
She's not special yet.
Mmm...
But you have to admit,
there is something about her.
Like what?
She's young, and she's thin.
RUBY: No, it's more than that.
She has that
thing.
(CHUCKLES)
(WOMAN CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
(MODEL WALKING)
ASSISTANT 1: Thank you.
CASTER: Erin.
So the same. Straight back.
ASSISTANT 1: This way, ladies.
CASTER: So do straight back between
the pillars, and then right back here.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Next.
Robert, you remember Sarah?
(ASSISTANT 1 WHISPERING)
Oh.
CASTER: Let's just see the walk.
Should I go again?
CASTER: No, thank you, that will be all.
Could you come forward, please?
This is Jesse.
Where's your card?
I don't have one yet.
CASTER: Jesse's new in town,
but she's just been signed
by Roberta Hoffmann.
How old are you?
Nineteen.
ROBERT: Any runway experience?
Not really.
CASTER: Okay, let's see the walk, dear.
ASSISTANT 1: Thank you.
We'll take her to measurements.
Thank you.
ASSISTANT 2: Lift up.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(GASPS)
(DOOR CLOSES IN THE DISTANCE)
(GLASS CRUNCHING)
- You should really fix this.
- SARAH: I don't wanna fix it.
I thought you did great.
Honest.
Don't do that.
Pretend that you don't know.
People see you.
They notice.
Do you know how lucky you are?
I'm a ghost.
What's it feel like?
What do you mean?
SARAH: To walk into a room,
and it's like in the middle of winter,
you're the sun.
It's everything.
Ow!
(JESSE BREATHING HEAVILY)
- Oh, shit.
- SARAH: Let me see.
(GRUNTS)
Stop! Stop!
(JESSE CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
(WHIRRING STOPS)
Sorry, I'm late.
MORTICIAN: Hey. No problem.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(PANTING)
(SCREAMING)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
DEAN: Are you the manager?
Depends who's asking.
DEAN: My friend says
she owes you some money.
Room 212.
Oh, the wildcat.
That's some real hard candy.
You know what I mean?
I beg your pardon?
- What, are you a Mormon?
- DEAN: No, sir.
- Are you with the DPH?
- No.
'Cause we passed our last inspection.
I can show you the paperwork if you want.
She said she owes you for the damages.
HANK: I should charge her
for emotional distress.
You know how long it took
to get that thing out of here?
Well, I don't think she should have to pay.
- That so?
- Yeah. I mean, technically it wasn't her fault.
Not her fault?
Who do you think
left the sliding door open?
- Yeah, but I don't see how that makes...
- Was it you?
- No.
- Sure as hell wasn't me.
How much?
HANK: New door plus labor.
At least 100.
Or was it two?
- I have 140 in cash.
- Sold.
(DOOR SLAMS)
- Is there a pharmacy around here?
- HANK: Why?
She send you out for tampons, too?
You know, you've got
a real attitude problem, you know that?
I'm just being friendly.
I just wanna make sure
you're getting something out of this deal.
'Cause if you're not,
got plenty of other girls here.
Take a peek in Room 214
if you get a chance.
Rented it this week to a girl
from Sandusky, Ohio.
Runaway.
Thirteen years old.
Real Lolita shit.
Room 214.
Gotta be seen.
(JESSE GROANING)
Jesse?
What are you doing here?
They told me to wait.
For what?
For makeup.
You're in the show?
Yeah.
This show?
Yes.
That's my chair.
Well.
You certainly move fast.
What do you mean?
You must be fucking him.
Sarno doesn't let just anyone
walk his collection.
I don't think I'm his type.
GIGI: Why not?
You're very masculine.
I bet they made you do the casting.
I didn't have to.
I just come in, choose what I wanna wear.
But I'm not sure
about the makeup this year.
I think you look perfect.
Yeah.
Well, flattery will get you everywhere.
You wanna know what I had done, don't you?
Well, I thought I'd get more work
if I went down a cup size.
So I look like a hanger. You know?
But then my surgeon, Dr. Andrew,
he pointed out a lot
of other problems with my body.
So I had them shave my jaw,
I had a slight eyebrow lift,
new nose, cheeks, inner and outer lipo,
oh, and they pinned my ears.
Why?
So I could wear a ponytail.
Didn't it hurt?
Anything worth having hurts a little.
Besides, nobody likes the way they look.
I do.
(GIGI SCOFFS)
ASSISTANT: Are you Jesse?
Mmm-hmm.
They wanna see you.
I already had my fitting.
I'm just the messenger.
You.
I've decided you're gonna close the show.
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
ROBERT: "...pry through
the portage of the head..."
- Hi.
- ...like a brass cannon."
I want you to meet my friend.
This is Dean.
Hi.
- Your name's Bean?
- No, Dean.
- Dean?
- Dean, yeah.
- ROBERT: Dean, nice to meet you.
- DEAN: Nice to meet you, too.
Well, come, join us. Have a drink.
Sit down.
I don't think there's room for two.
That's all right,
we can just sit over there.
"Now set the teeth
"and stretch the nostril wide,
"hold hard the breath
"and bend up every spirit
to his full height.
"Oh, oh!"
And so on and so forth.
Wow!
Did you always wanna be an actor?
Well, performing always
came naturally to me
because I'm a creator.
All right? I build, I make.
It's in my blood.
So whether I'm designing a collection
or creating a character,
it's all the same, right?
- I went out for a film last week.
- Oh, yeah, how did it go?
They said my face didn't match my voice.
- Well, you can fix your face.
- No, don't do that.
Why not?
Because you can always tell
when beauty is manufactured.
And if you aren't born beautiful,
you never will be.
- That's terrible.
- No, it's true.
I don't think you can always tell.
Dean,
we're having a little debate over here,
and we need your expertise.
Okay.
You know Gigi, right?
Well, I mean, we just met.
Will you stand up so that
he can take a look at you?
Go on, stand up.
Well?
Well, what?
What do you think?
Do you think she is beautiful?
I don't know, I mean...
Yeah, I guess she's fine.
Yes, yes. That's exactly the word
that I was looking for.
She's fine, right?
You can sit down now, thanks.
Thank you, Dean.
Now look at Jesse.
Nothing fake, nothing false.
A diamond in a sea of glass.
True beauty is the highest
currency we have.
Now, without it, she would be nothing.
DEAN: I think you're wrong.
Excuse me.
I said, I think you're wrong.
So are you gonna tell me that
it's what's inside that counts?
Yeah, that's exactly what I think.
Well, I think
that if she wasn't beautiful,
you wouldn't have even stopped to look.
Beauty isn't everything.
It's the only thing.
Hey, let's get out of here.
I wanna go.
So go.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
What are you doing here?
What are you?
Is that what you want?
You wanna be like them?
I don't wanna be them.
They wanna be me.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(KNIFE CLICKS)
(GASPS)
(HANK CHUCKLES)
Wider.
(GROANS)
(GAGGING)
Wider.
(GASPS)
(DOORKNOB CLICKING)
(DOORKNOB RATTLING)
(BANGING)
(BANGING STOPS)
(DOORKNOB RATTLING IN THE DISTANCE)
(DOOR OPENING IN THE DISTANCE)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(WOMAN WHIMPERING)
(WOMAN SOBBING)
(WOMAN PLEADING INDISTINCTLY)
(WOMAN GRUNTING)
- (LOUD THUD)
- (WOMAN SCREAMS)
(WOMAN SOBBING)
(PHONE RINGING)
RUBY ON PHONE: Hello?
JESSE: (WHISPERS) Ruby.
- Thank God you're awake.
- RUBY: Jesse?
JESSE: I didn't know who to call.
RUBY: Are you okay?
JESSE: Lt sounds like he's killing her.
RUBY: What? Who is?
JESSE: What do I do?
He already tried to get in.
RUBY: Can you get out?
JESSE: I think so.
RUBY: Come here.
You're gonna be safe.
(DOOR SLAMS)
I brought you some things.
Thanks.
You can wear this if you want.
Unless you prefer to sleep naked.
Are you going out?
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm going to stay here with you.
JESSE: This house is amazing.
How long have you lived here?
I don't live here.
JESSE: But I thought
you said this was your house.
No, I said I'm house-sitting.
Watering the plants.
Checking the mail.
JESSE: Oh, well...
Do you think they'll mind
that I'm crashing?
RUBY: You can stay here
for as long as you like.
Sit.
My mom used to brush my hair
after a bad day.
It's very soothing.
Ruby?
Just relax.
Mmm?
Thank you.
For what?
For being so good to me.
It's what friends are for.
No, I mean...
I think you're really wonderful.
I think you're just...
I think you are, too.
I think you're so beautiful.
And you have such beautiful skin.
What are you doing?
(SHUSHING)
I thought that's what you wanted.
No.
Oh.
It's not what you think.
Then what is it?
I lied before.
I've never been with anyone like that.
I don't care.
Ruby.
- Stop.
- (SHUSHING)
- I want to.
- I wanna be your first.
- Stop.
- (RUBY SHUSHING)
- (JESSE STRUGGLING)
I said stop!
(BOTH PANTING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(DOOR LOCKING)
(SPITS)
(MOANING)
(RUBY MOANING INTENSELY)
Jesse.
What are you doing?
JESSE: You know what my mother
used to call me?
Dangerous.
"You're a dangerous girl."
She was right.
I am dangerous.
I know what I look like.
And what's wrong with that anyway?
Women would kill to look like this.
They carve and stuff
and inject themselves.
They starve to death,
hoping,
praying that one day they'll look
like a second-rate version of me.
Are we having a party or something?
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
(JESSE GASPS)
(GASPS)
(GROANING SOFTLY)
(SHOWER RUNNING)
ANNIE: My girlfriend,
she hasn't worked in months.
I mean, I keep telling her,
"Girl, you need to retire."
MAKEUP ARTIST: Right.
ANNIE: Once you hit 21 in this industry,
you're so irrelevant.
MAKEUP ARTIST: (SCOFFS) Try 20.
ANNIE: (CHUCKLES) True. She won't listen.
MAKEUP ARTIST: Of course she won't.
ANNIE: No.
I mean, she's so desperate,
the other day she went uptown,
she was trying to buy this baby seal fat
from this random woman.
(SCOFFS)
What, you think that's funny?
No, I don't.
(CHUCKLES)
You ever had a girl screw you out of a job?
Yes.
So what did you do about it?
I ate her.
ANNIE: Ew! (LAUGHS)
Gross.
Do I know you?
What are you doing here?
I'm waiting for my friend.
I'd like to use you for this.
Would you be okay with that?
Annie, you're fired!
Thank you.
ANNIE: Are you serious?
It's not fair.
You... You can't fire me.
(GIGI RETCHING)
Gigi.
Can you tell us what's so interesting?
You're staring in the pool.
Look in the camera.
(CONTINUES RETCHING)
(COUGHS)
(RETCHING)
(GROANING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(RETCHING)
(GIGI BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GIGI CONTINUES RETCHING)
(GIGI CRYING)
I need to get her out of me.
(GIGI RETCHING)
(STABS)