We live on Fortune Shell Island
in Taiwan.
A hundred years ago there was
no TV here, no bars, no karaoke.
Just a small fishing village
in which a young couple lived.
They were in love. The kind of
love that feels like it's supposed to.
One day when the man was fishing
in the ocean, a storm sank his boat.
The woman saw it and shouted: "Bu!",
which is Mandarin for "No".
She dove into the ocean to rescue him,
and they were never heard from again.
Some say they found each other
in the afterlife.
Some say they turned into dolphins -
- because once they find a mate,
they never part.
Of all the dolphins on Earth, -
- only the ones on Fortune Shell Island
make the sound: "Bu!".
The man was swept out to sea. Some say
they're still searching for each other.
When you love someone and lose them,
you just keep searching.
How about that?
What do you guys know?
That story is so depressing.
- Mind your eavesdropping.
- Gee, sorry.
- Are you hungry, honey?
- No.
When I ask a question,
you might not always say "No".
You were the one who called me Bu, Ma.
I need a little help here.
Don't talk to our daughter
in so many different languages!
Look at her. Half the time she speaks
Taiwanese, half the time Mandarin, -
- the other half, she speaks English.
If you think it's so easy,
you raise her.
- Or keep it to yourself, Tubby.
- What did you just call me?
What did she just call me?
I want to know.
What did you just say?
Well, I'm on a diet.
Okay, you're done.
I learned it from a fashion magazine.
It's very stylish. Do you like it?
Have you got a second?
Wait until you see what I bought you.
In my whole life,
I've never seen an oyster like this one.
- Any pearls?
- No.
- Looks like it's expensive.
- A hundred dollars.
- Thank you.
- I also have this.
My friend owns a wedding chapel.
He'll give us a discount. So I...
- Are you asking?
- No, just wondering if... I'm asking.
You got this gigantic oyster
because you want us to...
I bought this because the jewellery shop
was closed. Will you marry me?
Yes...
I'll consider it.
Why did you come
all the way from Hong Kong to marry Pop?
Your old pop was quite a hunk.
And a good cook, too.
- Did you like Hong Kong?
- I loved it. Especially the pot rice.
You don't really love Louis, do you?
May I give you a little advice
before it's too late?
You have to trust your heart.
Hi there, Buddy.
I've got some news for you.
Louis says he wants to marry me.
Cut it out!
I heard a story once.
Souls start out together,
but when they enter into the world, -
- they somehow get separated.
They continue to search on,
until they can find -
- who it is that they were
destined to go through life with.
What?
Bu! Where are you going?
"I'm waiting for you in Hong Kong.
Albert."
How romantic.
Excuse me,
I'm looking for a place to eat.
Can you write down the names of
some restaurants? Thank you.
- Taiwanese white trash.
- Don't be like that.
- You speak English?
- Yes. Surprised?
- Is this your first flight?
- You can tell?
Of course, I can tell.
Hong Kong is enormous, you can get lost.
I could show you around.
Manhattan Robert here. I know everyone.
Just ask around.
You could say I'm famous.
What do you say?
- What are you doing?
- Do you have a twin?
Excuse me a second.
"Gangster's girlfriend disappears."
- Good morning, Mr Chan.
- Good day. Wall Street moving today?
Yes, the Lion Fund borrowed heavily
from the interbank market.
They get a 20 per cent interest rate.
That could climb even higher
by morning.
Poke around a little. See if Lion Fund
has sold any Nikkei futures.
Then see if the yen is rising.
Check if Japan's naval base contract
with the U.S. Expires soon.
If all answers are positive,
I'll buy up every possible share.
Are you aware that Lion Fund
is run by two Nobel Prize winners?
It's a great formula, why doubt them?
I have my reasons.
They're greedy.
It's all on paper, their cash is poor.
It's time to make our move.
Go ahead and do it.
Order 100 roses and have them
delivered to Carmen. Attach this card.
- Didn't you two break up?
- We're still friends.
You're a big boy. You should settle down
with someone soon.
- Impossible.
- With all those women?
- They're so beautiful and elegant, too.
- Too elegant for me.
Make sure you know the right girl
when you see her.
I'll know her.
Don't wait for me. Help yourself.
That bottle
floated all the way to Taiwan?
And you came here.
Hopped a ride to Hong Kong.
Romantic and endearing.
- There's news I need to break to you.
- Yes?
- One little detail you should know.
- What?
Listen.
- No way!
- Oh yes, it's true.
- Come on, honestly?
- Yes, I swear.
- The note was to your boyfriend?
- Ex-boyfriend.
- But why?
- Because he broke it off.
- I mean, why are you gay?
- As if it's a choice.
- Well, you're a handsome guy.
- True. None the less.
All right!
"I'm waiting for you here."
That's how you got the idea.
I chose this apartment
because of the billboard.
I'm sorry. I'll make it up to you.
You don't get seasick, do you?
Beautiful!
It's a good job.
You sounded nervous on the phone.
What's the emergency?
There's no emergency.
I just missed you. You don't miss me?
Sit down, I'll get you a drink.
Tell me what's going on.
Maybe you better go.
Such a shame.
You're boating and you didn't call me?
- Yet you're here.
- The papers say you're dating my girl.
You believe everything you read?
That's childish.
- Well, tell me: Are you?
- Yes.
You've been competing with me
for everything since we were kids.
Chan, come here.
I heard you're interested in my stocks.
I'm interested in many stocks,
not just yours.
My associates and I
hold all the controlling stock.
- No way you're taking over my company.
- Why not?
You're standing on my boat,
with my girlfriend.
You must have a death-wish!
Maybe you can try to get to the point.
I think I deserve an apology.
You don't have to do it in front of them.
Call me five minutes after I've gone.
Five minutes.
You've got the time?
The little hand is on the six.
If your watch doesn't work, why wear it?
I like the diamonds. Genuine.
Guys, keep an eye on him.
If he doesn't call me in five minutes,
throw him right into the ocean.
Give him a life preserver.
Don't let him drown.
So long, Boss. See you.
Do yourself a favour.
Call him and tell him you're sorry.
- Hurry up. I've got a really hot date.
- You must want to go in the water.
Get the life preserver...
Let's go.
- I'm not interested.
- Don't fight it.
- Here's the life preserver.
- Hurry, he's drowning!
He's over there!
Don't move.
Help him. Chan went that way.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
I'll call you.
Where is he?
I don't see him. Can you see him?
Are you okay? I'll go help the others.
Hey, I know you... He's over here!
He's in the back!
Help me, I'm drowning.
- Here, have a life preserver.
- Thank you.
- Does anybody see him?
- No.
Catch!
Wait, there he goes!
- He got away!
- The Boss gave us instructions.
Throw him into the ocean with
a life preserver and that's what we did.
Job done, let's go eat.
Thank you.
- Are you all right?
- You are...
I'm Bu.
- Are you escaping?
- Sure, why not?
- From Vietnam?
- Yes, that's right.
- How many are you?
- Just one.
Well, then who's driving?
- You want to give me a hand?
- I'm starving. I'm hungry.
- How about you?
- I'm not starving yet, but I am hungry.
Let's talk a little.
It'll help us forget that we're hungry.
What about?
About all the things you really enjoy.
Music, bowling, cars, women.
Nothing?
What are you smiling about?
It's so boring.
Let's talk about things you don't like.
I don't like nosey people.
Tell me what you don't like.
I don't like growing up.
Because you can't act spoiled.
- Did you say "soiled"?
- I said, "spoiled".
The more you're grown up,
the less people like you.
What do you like best?
Taking a shower when I'm really hot.
When I wake up to a fresh cup of coffee.
That sounds good.
- The stars in Hong Kong are gorgeous.
- The stars in Hong Kong?
Stars everywhere are just as beautiful.
You just have to look up and see them.
What?
A shooting star! My Mum says you
should put your hands in your pocket, -
- make a wish, and it will come true.
Too bad I don't have any pockets.
There's another one.
- What did you wish for?
- I'm not telling. It'll be bad luck.
You're a nosey body, aren't you?
I'm so sleepy.
- Look, out there!
- What is it?
A boat! A boat!
Over here.
Busses don't go here and the authorities
check out ID. You want a lift?
That's okay. Just tell me where I am,
and I'll walk back myself.
No one lives around here.
We're in the middle of nowhere, Miss...
- My name is Bu.
- Boob?
- All right, just get in.
- Okay.
Wait, not you.
I was talking to her.
- I've noticed there's only two seats.
- Yes, here's 20 bucks.
Walk straight ahead till you see a taxi,
or bum a ride on a boat, like I did.
Come in.
- You live here all alone?
- There's a butler.
- You're kidding. Must get real crowded.
- Have a seat.
- Can I look around?
- Yes, sure.
I'm hungry.
Oh, I'm so hungry.
- You need something?
- The fish food.
They don't need it,
they're virtual fish.
- Come here. Over here.
- Why do you have electronic fish?
I never have to change the water.
- What if the power goes out?
- I don't know.
With this big house
you must have parties all the time.
- I don't have any friends.
- You must be lonely.
Now what?
You like to fight, huh?
Some like to play golf,
some like horse-racing.
I like boxing and fitness training.
- What's this octopus thing?
- Come on, let's go.
This should fit you.
You can change in there.
Behind there.
Hi, Betty.
I need a taxi.
Half an hour? Great.
I didn't mean in there.
There's a room behind the mirror.
I was afraid I'd get lost in there
and never find my way out.
- Are you hungry?
- Absolutely starving.
- Then let's eat.
- Do you have any Chinese pot rice?
What?
- This is the best take-out food.
- I use this restaurant a lot.
- Such a nice kitchen and you don't cook?
- I don't like all the grease.
- Stop staring at me. Eat your lunch.
- Okay.
- Why are you smiling?
- I enjoy watching you eat.
- Are you rich?
- I guess so.
- How did you make it?
- Garbage.
- No, really.
- Buying and selling it.
Don't be that way.
- Do you happen to have a soda pop?
- How about juice? It's healthier.
Looking for Bu?
She just went down the elevator.
Your boyfriend is in these every week.
Each time pictured with a new girlfriend.
I'd call him promiscuous
and not cute.
Look at this. Let's hear it
from one of his ex-girlfriends.
"He doesn't know how to please me.
He doesn't say sweet things.
And yet,
I'd say he's very romantic.
He gets right to the point.
Always doing business deals.
And yet, he's just a kid.
He's very competitive.
He enjoys new things.
He never changes,
once he's made up his mind.
With him... I feel very insecure."
- So. That means what?
- He likes new things, as in new girls.
Soon we'll be reading about you.
All those girls are just mean.
They were insecure to start with.
- I, on the other hand, am secure.
- Forget it.
Hong Kong is such a boring place anyway.
- Going home?
- No. C.N. is fun.
You don't even have him yet. You can't
just go up and take off your clothes.
- Do you think I'm like that?
- Do you think he isn't like that?
He likes girls, he's successful.
I have an idea, and it involves you.
Count me out.
- Please?
- Fat chance.
Tell me where your daughter went.
Bu found a bottle
and went to Hong Kong.
If Bu's here in Hong Kong,
I'll find her.
We checked out
Lo's Chemicals Manufacturing.
Last year they had a 13 per cent growth.
The net profit was 130 million dollars.
The stock prices are 30 per cent higher.
Shall we keep going?
We've bought 16 per cent of the company.
Mr Lo and partners have a death-grip
on their 65 per cent and refuse to sell.
If we continue to raise the price,
the stock will become too high.
Sell all my shares.
If you sell all your shares at once,
the price will plunge.
If we sell low,
our company will suffer a loss.
Just do exactly as I told you.
- I need to see K.K.
- Yes, sir.
- Who's K.K.?
- The head of Environmental Protection.
"You're a dead man."
Going down?
Sorry, I'm going up.
- I'm meeting a friend on the top floor.
- This is the top.
- Really? Oh yeah, she lives downstairs.
- Her name is?
Actually, it's a blind date...
This floor is nice.
I bet the rent is high.
- Who made you write on my door?
- What do you mean?
Hey, look over there!
Don't move, or I'll break it.
Let go, let go!
- Why did you do it?
- Let go first.
Some handwriting, huh?
Cut it out!
I'm bad at kung fu, I'm just delivering.
- To me?
- Check the rear pocket.
You big bully, now it's broken.
You'll hear from my lawyer.
Now read it.
"Gangster's Girl Missing."
- What happened?
- Don't worry about me, I'll be fine.
No, with C.N. Did he buy the story?
Does he believe I'm the gangster's girl?
Who knows?
Do you think it'll work?
Of course it will.
- What do we do next?
- Get help from your buddies...
I mean, your boyfriends.
You're in big trouble, lady.
We'll chop you to pieces.
Make it good...
You're going the wrong way.
Your boyfriend is the mob boss of Taiwan.
Our boss hates your boyfriend.
So he told us to cut up your face...
Your turn.
If you don't believe us,
just read the newspapers.
Now everybody's looking for you.
It worked. He's riding over.
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine. And you?
- It's you!
- Are you okay?
I'm not sure who those guys are...
Never mind.
What's the matter with you?
Don't let him see your face.
These guys are really good for actors.
Stay away. I'll stab you.
Let her go, or I'll stab myself.
You just cut yourself.
- We'll let you live.
- Let's get out of here.
Don't chase them.
Let's go, before the cops get here.
- Whose factory is this?
- We're okay here. I own it.
- Why is it loaded with garbage?
- I told you, I buy trash.
- It's worth a lot of money.
- I should tell my boyfriend about this.
First you told me you were a refugee.
Now you're
a Taiwanese mob boss's girlfriend.
- Are you really?
- Yes. A dangerous woman to be with.
- Are you afraid?
- I'm never scared.
You're not afraid
my boyfriend will kill you?
How did you become
a gangster's girlfriend?
There's a police station near my home.
One day I saw these "wanted" posters.
One of them had these beautiful eyebrows
to go with these beautiful eyes.
I went in every day and saw those eyes.
It was love at first sight.
- Then what happened?
- I got his address. Now we're together.
What was it you liked about him?
He had a lot of style
and was a great dancer.
Very romantic.
- Dancing means romance?
- Like you're romantic.
I can dance.
- Like this?
- Yes.
How about tango?
Yes.
You're dull!
Don't you know any exciting dances?
- I know one.
- You mean it? Let's see.
- Don't be scared.
- No way.
Hands here... Jump up here.
Here we go.
- Pretty good.
- More.
- Not bored yet?
- No, you're lots of fun.
Just make sure you hold on tight.
Don't let go.
- We'll be going pretty fast. Ready?
- Yes.
Put your hands here and jump.
1, 2, 3
Howie, the Exchange closed.
It dropped a lot. Our stock took
a 20 per cent hit. Closed at 6.50.
- What's the loss in assets?
- Ten million. Give or take a little.
It's because Chan
is dumping off our shares.
What about our investigation?
If Chan's goal is to control the company,
he can't get rid of us.
Then why dump his shares
after buying so high?
It doesn't make sense anymore.
What's going on?
It's a scheme. What's he up to?
- What happened?
- We ambushed Chan.
- Is he hurt?
- No. Not a scratch on him.
That makes me feel better.
If something happened, I'd blame myself.
And if any of you men got hurt,
I'd be devastated.
- I'm feeling guilty already.
- It was your dad's idea.
My dad's? What was he thinking?
Ambushing my best friend.
Why don't we shoot him in the back?
- Pull the trigger, it'd be much faster.
- Ah, a sniper.
I'm kidding. It's too cowardly.
You guys have to call him out.
Smart, Boss.
I've got it.
What we're gonna do is hire a fighter.
Stronger than Chan.
Also, he's smaller.
Someone from overseas.
Someone he doesn't know.
He'll be disgraced.
Come on, don't you know this signal?
It means: Take a hike, go away!
Confusing.
- Have you seen this girl?
- Yes.
- That's Mary.
- Mary?
- That's not Mary, that's Bunny.
- That's not Bunny...
I'll show you where she is.
- Put your glasses on.
- She's got short hair.
- What did you say to me?
- I told you to put your glasses on.
I have to go now.
Oh, my gosh! What is he doing?
This hadn't happened
if I'd shown him where Bunny lived.
Albert?
I'm such an angel.
Yes? What do you want?
- What the... Stop it!
- Where is she?
- Let go of me!
- You better tell me.
Where's my Bu?
What did you do with her?
Where did you take her?
Bu and I are engaged.
- What's this?
- Excuse me.
This lady is so beautiful
she deserved some wind effect.
- You're gorgeous.
- I know.
Do we drink it?
Yes. It's a 1982.
That's not all.
I can tell something else by tasting it.
The grape picker was born in 1960.
Let's order.
I'll do it.
Do you make Chinese pot rice?
- Just kidding.
- You had me worried.
Do you always eat
with so many people watching you?
Tell those guys they can leave now.
Excuse me.
- How come there's no one else eating?
- I bought the restaurant.
Then I can't see any stars!
Without celebrities it's a bore.
Why do you hate crowds? They're just
people. You really don't have friends?
But I have enemies.
Why did you dump my company's stock
and drive the price so low?
I'm in the middle of dinner.
I'll call you later.
Tell me why? I'm losing money,
and you're not doing too well, either.
Please leave. The restaurant is closed.
- Sir, you appear to be a smart guy.
- You might say that.
You must have a lot of time.
Why not use it to save your company?
- And leave now, okay?
- Tell me who you are.
I'm a guest,
and I'm appalled at your behaviour.
We're trying to enjoy a dinner for two,
and you're disturbing our meal.
- Let's talk.
- We talked already.
Outside.
When will you get it?
That sign means, "follow me"!
Confusing.
I like your attitude.
It's nothing.
Being around gangsters and all...
You have to go?
Yes. I'll be right back. Excuse me.
Be careful.
Watch your back.
I cleared it with your boss.
You can close up the parking lot, too.
Then you guys can just take off.
We'll have a little fun.
Don't worry, I'm footing the bill.
You heard Mr Lo. Move out.
Mr Chan, have fun.
Howie, what's going on here?
I want you to meet someone.
I invited him from overseas.
Ladies and gentlemen: Alan!
Alan here is undefeated
in a very tough weight class.
Alan will fight you, one on one,
on behalf of me.
Why don't I fight you?
We're not the same weight class.
- I'd have to much of an edge.
- That's the point.
If you lose to a short guy,
it would be humiliating.
Act like an adult.
You have no choice.
- You're going to use gloves?
- Do you think he's a street fighter?
- I don't want him dead.
- If he hits with a glove, it won't hurt.
No? Have him hit you with a glove.
Tell me if it hurts.
Try to knock me down any way you can.
But no dirty tricks.
They say you're a great fighter...
Come on.
Look! They will not let you leave
without a fight.
You asked for it.
- Ready?
- Of course.
- Alan is losing to him.
- No, he's just testing him.
He wants to see how hard he can punch.
- Why is he changing gloves?
- He's giving C.N. a little advantage.
He knows his punches are too soft.
I've come a long way.
I don't want a short game.
Every boxer fights to their own music.
Provides the rhythm for their footwork.
C.N. Has no rhythm.
His footwork is a mess.
- Look at Alan's controlled rhythm.
- You sound like an expert.
Why don't you box?
C.N. and I used to box,
but I always lost.
I thought, I'd go into announcing.
- You like that better than boxing?
- Yes. Talking, I sound invincible.
In the ring, I'm like you...
Mostly useless.
C.N. used to have brilliant moves.
What happened?
He's concerned with other things,
like buying stocks. He'll lose.
C.N. seems like he's distracted.
That's why he's going down.
Good hit... But not enough power.
Are you okay?
You win.
- You deserve it. We win!
- While he's down, let's kick him.
What do you say, Boss?
How many times have I told you?
Real men fight fair, not like cowards.
Do you think there's honour
in kicking a man when he's down?
You're good.
Let's go.
My job is done. He's good.
Are you okay?
He didn't hurt you too bad, did he?
You must be delighted that I lost.
It might look like that, but I'm not.
Do you need to call anyone?
Forget it.
Call me. Take care.
- You didn't leave?
- You said that I should wait.
I came down to look for you.
- They used tricks and outnumbered you.
- No, it was one on one. I really lost.
All right, so you lost.
You'll get used to it.
Just kidding. Train hard, then, when
you're ready, go back and beat them.
I do have to train.
But not to beat up people.
- Why else would you train?
- For a strong body and a sharp mind.
- I haven't trained in a long time.
- But your gym is huge! What a waste.
- Is it just for show?
- I just hate to train alone.
Okay, I'll train with you then.
- Why are you being so nice?
- Because you're rich.
See how nice you look when you laugh.
Out there you looked so grumpy and sad.
That's probably the reason you lost.
See? Nice laugh.
You know, you don't need
make-up and fancy clothes.
Can you take tomorrow off?
Just say yes.
- First tell me what we'll do.
- Just say yes.
- Okay. What'll we do?
- Have fun.
- Are we in love?
- Huh?
- I think you're really nice.
- I'm in love, it's your turn to say it.
I'm waiting for an answer.
Here's how it works.
You can just tell me -
- in four words... or less:
I love you... I don't love you.
When did you get back? What is it now?
I'm confused. I think I'm in love.
Love is just a state of mind.
More fantasy than truth.
Love is like a radiant dream
that quickly turns into a nightmare.
Albert, you're such an inspiration.
- I have news for you.
- What?
- Your boyfriend Louis is here.
He tried to strangle me. Fortunately,
I'm strong enough to fight him off.
He's been drunk ever since.
- I think I really let him down.
- We're talking about love, not pity.
The worse you are to him,
the better off he is.
Until you figure out your feelings
for Chan, don't let him see you.
Good morning, how about a Bloody Mary?
- Let go of me.
- Where are you going?
- To the kitchen.
- No! Wait.
- I need, I need...
- What are you looking for?
- A bottle-opener.
- I'll get you a glass.
- Here, take two.
- How am I going to open it?
- Bu, this is crazy.
- Okay, I'll tell C.N. the truth.
If you tell him now, you'll ruin it.
He'll move on to the next girl.
You're wrong.
C.N. is not that kind of guy.
He took a day off to be with me.
It was a perfect day.
When he's not around I miss him
day and night. I'm the only girl for him.
I love C.N. and I know he's in love, too.
Sure sounds like love to me.
- What is it?
- I want sake.
- You haven't even finished your wine.
- No! I want sake, I want sake!
Don't go away.
Oh, excuse me. Thank you.
Here it is.
- Do you want to sing with me?
- What do you think this is? Karaoke?
Let's drink our sake. Here's to Bu.
- It's too much.
- You want more? Allow me.
- Here's to my health.
- Be careful, you'll get drunk.
Well, bottoms up.
You need some sleep.
I've got her with me here.
She's all right.
Sure, you can talk to her.
- Gloria, this is Bu. Gloria's a friend.
- Oh, you're my new look-alike.
I can see it.
You knew it all along, didn't you?
- You lied.
- You started it.
You loved me, so I loved you back.
Was that a lie, too? Or was that real?
Our happiness was real.
If you like Hong Kong, why not stay?
So, why am I here?
So I can just be one of your girls?
The note in the bottle said
to go to Hong Kong right away.
I thought this fairy tale was real.
You changed the ending.
C.N., you've got
some important information.
The government passed a law
prohibiting the use of styrofoam.
Howie Lo's stock
dropped dramatically. It's worthless.
All stockholders sell off their shares.
You knew the law would be passed.
Why didn't you inform us?
- It was just a matter of time.
- The project waits for your decision.
That'll be all.
- What's wrong?
- I'm okay.
What?
It's for you.
"Nothing can change a man like love.
For he's going nowhere.
And yet, so far."
- Meaning what?
- Going nowhere, and yet, so far.
- Yes, I heard you. It means?
- I don't know.
I've been with you so long,
and I never saw you like this.
Garbage tossed about.
Try moving forward.
- Leave me alone.
- Move on.
- Beat it.
- Be strong.
I don't want to listen to you anymore.
Fine, I can take a hint.
You don't have to tell me twice.
- How did you get in here?
- We broke in.
Call the police.
- I don't think they'll let me call.
- I bet they will.
- I told you so.
- You guys beat it.
You ruined our boss's life.
We lost our jobs.
You're the reason why!
Mister Chan...
I heard you're back in training.
- Yes I am, but not because of you.
- Rematch?
- Mr Lo sent you here?
- Mr Lo's broke. It's not about the money.
- Not now.
- You've got no choice.
- You really enjoy fighting, don't you?
- Only with the best.
- Here we go again. I hate this part.
- You don't know much about boxing, huh?
Do you know why they do this?
Okay.
- Rules?
- No rules.
Anything goes. But no dirty tricks.
You like white.
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
Good training.
Wait, wait...
What is it?
- Can I ask him if he's okay?
- If you insist.
Are you okay?
Okay. He's okay.
Pretty good.
I'm coming.
Ready?
C'mon!
"Just smile."
See how nice you look when you laugh.
You looked so grumpy and sad.
That's probably the reason you lost.
See? Nice laugh.
Are you ready?
Don't worry, be happy.
Let's dance.
Hey, let's finish...
Hey, come on! Get up!
Sir, are you all right? Up, up, up!
Sir, are you hurt bad?
- I'm okay.
- You did it. You won!
- I lost.
- Why?
If we were in the same weight class,
he would have won easily.
See if he's all right.
- Why do you smell like gas?
- Boss is setting fire to the factory.
That's excellent.
We'll be arrested for arson,
if we're here.
- This is dangerous. Be careful, Boss.
- It's okay.
If I get caught,
I'm going to jail for sure.
- You made sure everyone's out?
- They're all gone.
Deliver this to my father.
Tell him I love him a whole lot.
Give this one to C.N.
Tell him I hate him a whole lot.
Give this one to the authorities.
It blames the fire on me.
Really? You're going to jail, not me?
I'm not going to jail, either.
Stand aside.
- I'll burn your factory to the ground!
- Don't do it, Boss!
I burned my eyes.
I'll die anyway.
So what if I can't see?
I love you, Mary!!
- Howie, what are you doing here?
- C.N. It's all your fault.
You took it too far. My father
kicked me off the board of directors.
I have nothing now. Nothing!
- What about us?
- What'll we do without you?
Shut up!
- Warmer?
- Yes.
- Okay?
- That's good.
Are you still blind?
You're a good man.
Better than I was.
Styrofoam is bad for the environment.
That's why I wanted to shut you down.
But we can still be partners.
We can team up together.
We can open up a recycling centre.
How come you're doing this?
When we were in school together,
you had to get higher grades.
You were always more athletic.
You had to have every girl I liked.
As soon as you saw them once,
you never saw them again. I hated you.
- I hated you.
- What for?
For laughing.
For being born so wealthy.
It was all given to you.
I had to work for everything I ever had.
What I really hated was that
you stole the love of my life, Carol.
That was in second grade! Carol?!
I heard she married a guy,
what was his name...
- Oh, Bob. No... Fred.
- Fred!
A major moron. He was so dumb.
After so many years,
neither one of us has found a girl -
- we really truly loved.
- You said before: "I love Mary."
- You're crazy.
Hold on a minute. You were engaged.
What happened to her?
Don't bring it up. I got cold feet.
But Mary was a great girl.
We laughed a lot.
All day long.
You should hear her laugh.
It was great.
I wish I could turn back the clock.
She moved away
when I broke off the engagement.
I don't know where she went.
I never found her.
What's wrong with you?
- I'm gonna find her.
- Who? Mary? You never even met her!
Hey, Bu, I missed you.
How are you doing?
What? Come back! Bu!
"I miss you. C.N."
What do you want?
Go, you're not wanted here.
- You hurt Bu.
- No, I didn't.
She used to laugh. Now she's always sad
because of you. You took her grin away.
Now I'm sad, too.
That's not good. You've got trouble.
- What did you do to her?
- I didn't do anything to her.
Then why is she like this now?
Leave her alone.
- Go home or I'll beat your brains out!
- Take it easy, please.
You heard him. Get out of here!
I warned you. Watch it!
It'll be okay.
I'll sit right here.
Just try to get past, jerk.
Check out your dad. He's The King.
Are you okay, sir? Let me help you up.
- Is your back hurt badly?
- She doesn't want to talk to you.
- Let me talk to her, please.
- What would you say?
- Bu, listen, I...
- Stop it!
- Bu.
- Shut up!
- I said: "Shut up!"
Bu.
- I guess you just don't listen.
- You can kill me or let me talk to her.
All right. You want to talk?
Come with me.
It's now or never.
Well... Talk!
- Let's go. Don't bother them.
- I want to hear what he says to her.
Why come here?
- You left your clothes at my house.
- I have a lot more.
I know you like Chinese pot rice.
It got cold. You can just nuke it.
You think old clothes and pot rice
will fix things?
That's not all.
- I've written a note in each bottle.
- Really? What did you write?
I love you. I miss you.
All in four words or less.
And I got writer's cramp.
Why all the fuss?
If you just stick a thousand dollars
in each one, you'd get my attention.
Say out loud that you love me.
- Okay. I love you.
- When did you start?
When you went through my wallet.
That night on the boat when we saw
the star. What did you wish for?
It just came true.
What are you crying about?
- Leave them be.
- Hey, Don Juan! Kiss her!
Don't just stand there wearing white.
Kiss her!
It's okay.
Look over there.
Are all the girls here so beautiful?
Don't say it! I'll introduce you
to a friend. He lives over here.
Where?
Subtitles by Sharon Taylor
Scandinavian Text Service