That was a bit bluff...
If she'd believed you,
I'd be dead
But if we didn't hate each other...
you wouldn't have had to hide
So you change your story
as it pleases you?
Fong!
I can't take you further.
I must save Master...
You be on your way
Fong
What?
I was called Lotus when I was alive
Why're you telling me?
I won't be visiting you...
and you won't be visiting me...
Man and ghost can't be together...
and even if you were human,
it'd be hopeless...
because monks and women
can't be together...
Remember,
be more careful in future...
If you meet any other monks...
they won't give you a chance
Take care of yourself!
Damn monk,
think you're the most powerful?!
Tree Devil, you kill innocents,
and insult God...
I'm going to capture you...
That will your punishment
Punishment?
You mean I will reap what I sow?
Exactly!
Those are the karmic rules
Don't you know wicked people
are buried with honour...
Their deeds enshrined in books and songs!
But when dead,
they suffer in hell...
Hell is only as dark as the human world...
Only the powerful and ruthless thrive...
There's still time
to change your ways, bald monk!
I've been to hell,
so I know...
Maybe you should go
and see for yourself!
Master! Your staff!
But I used it to pin down the other ghost!
The dark deep underworld arise!
There is no justice!
Master!
Evil will win, and never fatter!
Fong, give me the Gold Buddha!
Right!
I forgot to tell you it's broken!
Now you tell me!
Master!
Fong,
ride my staff with the Buddha...
Get it fixed,
then come and save me
Master!
Fong!
Who is it?
Show yourself!
Leave quickly!
The Priestess will be back soon!
Follow my cloak!
You can't fight the Priestess...
Don't look back,
just move forward...
Remember not to look back...
Never come back!
It's getting light
Come and look, brand new weapons
Come and look
You're from Shaolin Temple?
Special price!
I have no money
Who shall I ask?
We use real iron
I'll think about it
For every $10 spent,
a free horseshoe!
I'll give you two
I'm only here to beg for food
Beg for food? Get lost!
The world's corrupt,
it's hard to find honesty
Let me help you!
Little monk, this place is bad,
go elsewhere
Brother,
you're a blacksmith aren't you?
Not much longer,
a decent man can't survive here
Will you do business with me?
I don't sell weapons
I don't want weapons,
I need repairs...
Have a look
You crazy?
If it's seen, you'll be dead...
Put it away!
Please help me, it's an emergency!
Is this Buddha yours,
or did you steal it?
Do I look like a thief?
Alright then, I'll do a good deed
You are so kind
Thank you
I thought,
you were going to fix the Gold Buddha?
What Gold Buddha?
I didn't see any...
You just threw it in there!
Leave me alone,
I don't want your business, scram!
Give it back...
I need it to save someone...
Give my Gold Buddha back!
Help!
Give it back, or I'll kill you!
I'm being beaten up by a monk!
I don't want trouble,
but he stole my Gold Buddha
Gold?
Not gold, just my Buddha
Search him,
maybe he's carrying more gold
I'm not, I'm not...
Get him!
What the hell?
It's the little monk!
It's you?
They stole something from me
Let's go!
Do you want me to help you?
Yes
Your Master owes me $10...
With this, it's a total of $15
They... they stole my Gold Buddha
Gold? Hang on...
Makes it more pricey,
an extra 300...
Plus a bowl of noodles, that's $320
But I have no money!
Goodbye!
But my Master has some
That makes it okay!
I won't cheat you, let's go
Quickly!
Calm down!
It's them!
- Brothers...
- They're here ...that Gold Buddha is mine...
It should be returned
to it's rightful owner
Who says? Finders keepers,
just because you've got a big sword
There are more of us!
Attack!
Let's melt it, goodbye Gold Buddha!
The Gold Buddha!
Oh no, it's melted!
You're amazing?
What's amazing?
Isn't it hot?
I wonder if it still has any powers?
Master is in real trouble now...
Don't be negative,
there's always a way...
Little monk...
Let's go and get money from your Master
But I haven't worked out how to save him
That's easy, hire me to help you save him...
I'll give you a special discount,
2 times $300...
What do you think?
Forget it, no deal
Get out of my way!
I'll kill you!
Don't you want to save your Master?
Of course I do
Then you have to pay me
But I have no money
Will you do it on credit?
Sure! It's a big deal
Wonton noodles!
Hey,
you look like you're starving...
Have some noodles!
I told you I have no money
It's okay, I'll keep a tab...
You'll have to pay up
when it reaches $1,000
Don't worry,
as long as I'm around it'll be fine
Hey, I don't even know your name
My name's Yin (red dawn)
That's quite a name
It was someone else's name,
a high Priest...
I begged him
to take me in as his student...
But he said he didn't like people...
and refused to teach me!
You see, he's really stubborn!
Maybe if you ask again,
he'll change his mind
He's dead now!
He was antisocial
so had no friends...
Not even money to buy a coffin!
I've learnt my lesson,
money before everything!
Why's that?
With money you can be whatever you want!
What do you want to be?
A rich Yin!
And what do you want to be?
A good man!
A good man? Like my namesake?
Living a lonely life.
You think good reaps good?
All good men end like that!
Help! A ghost!
Someone's in trouble!
Don't worry, it's her!
Help, help! Open the door!
There's a ghost after me!
Hey, it's me, hey...
Ghost... help me
Hey, she's on our side...
it's me...
I've been waiting for you,
it's Fong...
You can stop all
the dancing around...
Hey, stop it, stop it
Stop it?!
Who are you?
I'm so scared!
Come over here
I don't get it.
Explain what you're doing
I can't, it's all a mistake
Something over there's moving!
Yes...
I know a ghost's after you...
Then you must protect me!
I know you need protection
But we're not suited to each other
Why?
I mean...
I don't mean you're not pretty...
To be honest...
Please don't get angry, but I...
I don't go for your type,
that's all...
I prefer a longer face,
slight buck teeth
Maybe that much taller than me
Ow!
If you know her,
go and ask her to come here
Be careful not to burn your clothes
You're so bad,
you want a manage a trios?
What's that?
You studious types are so naughty
Ow!
Hey, come over here!
Lady, just hang on a moment
Wait here,
I'm just going over for a chat
What's the matter?
She's not right for you,
but she is for me...
I don't want your money,
I'll have her instead
No way!
What, you've undressed her?
No need to undress,
let's do it like this!
Give that to me!
No,
the clothes are stuck to my hands!
I said no, I don't know her!
Come on!
Another piece of clothing?
You don't know her,
but you remove her underwear?!
Put it on, put it on!
I don't care, I want her!
I'm paying you instead
I don't want money!
I don't want money, I want her!
No!
Hey, what're you doing?
Hey, now about if I pay you?
Look,
I'm giving you a good deal!
Just stop it, it's been decided
I'm sorry Miss!
It's the first time I've played this game!
I'm sorry to bother you...
Remember, long face,
slight buck teeth when she smiles...
About 6 inches taller than me, thanks!
What a waste,
you didn't even ask her name...
How can we find her again?
We're here to save my Master...
Not do that sort of thing...
If you want it so much,
come back another time
Don't worry, I will!
Help! Help!
I'll go!
I'm going!
Help!
It's you!
Why are you back here?
I'm so glad,
it's finally your turn!
These ghosts are beauties...
...she's even better
I almost mistook the last girl for you!
Who was here?
Your sister!
Anymore sisters?
We'll be discovered here,
let's go upstairs
Right
There's no one else!
Going to keep here for yourself?
Hey. What are you doing?
What?
What are you doing?
Pretending to be intimate!
Pretending to be intimate?
He's Yin,
I've employed him to help save Master...
She's Lotus
Hey, what are you doing?
Pretending to be intimate
You don't have to as well
stand aside and watch!
I don't trust you
Damn monk, if you can why can't I?
Don't use business as an excuse for pleasure
Do you think I want this?
I'm a reluctant victim too
We're not looking very convincing...
Let's get into bed!
Into bed?
If you won't do it, I will!
You won't go to be! I will!
How come I can't?
Come on
It's better if you're on top
Let's make it clear,
no more praying!
I'll try my best, what next?
Next we kiss!
Undaunted by the misty fog
Behind the mystery is a sweet surprise
Dashing through the sun and moon
Dancing to the beat of the gong
Nothing can dempen my chivalry
Stop the noise, this a serious business!
Nothing can stop my will to strike again
Do you know where Master is?
The priestess's got him,
but I don't know where
How can we get her to come here?
There's a bell on my ankle...
She'll answer it if she hears it ring
A bell?
So why don't you ring it?
Don't stop,
or they might suspect us, carry on!
Don't stick your tongue into my stomach!
I won't, we'll just kiss!
That's okay!
I can't bear it,
I'm going for a walk!
Hey, don't go!
I can't be bothered to watch
Yin, where are you going?
For a walk!
You can't go, stay here
Go away
What will I do if you go?
I can't bear watching you two
Young student!
Open the door,
I'm so scared outside
Let me come in
She's so scared!
What's that got to do with you?
It's Butterfly!
You wait here, I'll handle her
Don't go, the two of us are rivals
Even better,
then there won't be any bickering
You're really a pain in the neck...
Carry on like this and I won't pay you
Don't mention money,
I haven't seen a cent yet...
Where's the money? Huh?
Hush!
Lotus,
lend me some money so I can pay him...
Just so I can shut him up!
I don't want money,
he wants me to take it...
I'm happy with alternatives
You can talk, but touch her
See, if you don't help me,
he won't help me...
So you've got to help me
You two are trouble, I'm going
Let me protect you
Forget it!
So you got thrown out too?
No such luck...
Those two fought over me...
If not for the fact
they've got more friends coming...
I would have left ages ago
Don't stand here, go in and help
Lady,
we students love playing games...
Let's have some fun!
Okay!
I said you weren't my type,
don't hang around
Open up, open the door
I have no time for you
I don't believe I'm less attractive than Lotus!
You can't force your way in!
I want you to fancy me
Seduce me, I'm easy to seduce!
Can't we talk a bit first?
I can't wait
You have no hair! You're a monk!
You're that old monk's student?
Fong, come up!
Demon, take my spell!
Soldiers of wind and fire heed,
the spell is cast!
Heaven and earth move,
lend me your powers!
Wow!
Follow her!
Damn, she's got my sword
You like playing games?
I'll kill you
Belittling me?
Let's see who wins!
Little monk, I've been waiting for you
to save your Master...
I was wondering who
you'd find to help you...
and you get a midget with a giant's sword...
You want to amuse me,
so I die happy?
Old witch, careful you'll die laughing
Do something quickly!
I haven't begun my chanting yet
- Don't scare me, it's too late too look for a spell now!
- Shut up!
Let's bet
Yin, chop this side first
Chop...
They keep multiplying,
cast any old spell
What spell?
I can't even open my manuscript
I'm going!
Trying to escape?
You coward!
Lotus!
I'll help you get away
Come on!
I almost missed you two
Bastard, you ran away,
you've no loyalty
I was sacrificing myself
to distract her...
But she didn't fall for it,
what can I do?
So that means I get
sacrificed instead?
Stop arguing.
Let's get out of Orchid Temple
Let's hide
I can't let the Priestess see me here
We'll work together, and distract him!
Hey, catch!
Going to fight me with your little games?
My little games will kill you
Is that all you're capable of?
That wasn't for real,
but my next move is!
Miraculous armour, go!
You decide to change your clothes now?
I'm off
Trying to trick her again?
Let's go!
Priestess, you've been wounded!
How could we let him get away!
Did he think he could hurt me?
You won't get me!
Keep running away like that,
and even if you save me...
I'll die of fright!
This is strategy, do you understand?
At least you could have warned me
I'm saving you and all you do is complain...
You still owe me money,
where's the money?
Lotus
I mentioned borrowing some money, I...
Not now,
I've got to be careful when I get back
Why don't you leave Orchid Temple with us?
Your situation's dangerous;
don't go back...
Why not leave with us?
You can be a ghost anywhere
No, I'm used to this...
I suffered before,
I prefer living day by day...
Not like you,
not knowing what tomorrow will bring
It doesn't matter not knowing
Don't try and change my mind!
Here I live well and dress well
I'm not related to you...
What place do I have following you around?
I can't talk anyone,
I have to go...
Forget about me
She said we don't know where we're going
She's right...
Let's take care of ourselves first
That means we forget about her...
You said it
Jade, is the Priestess back yet?
The Priestess?
No
Then start combing my hair...
If she comes back,
say I never went out
What's wrong?
Nothing...
I'll miss you...
In two days I'll marry the Mountain Devil...
Whatever happens,
you're always my sister
I'll talk to the Priestess,
someone else can marry him...
Then we can stay together
Lotus, I really love you
I believed, that when you went out,
you were a good girl...
Tell me where they are hiding?
Priestess, forgive me,
I was wrong
Forgive you?
Tell me, how should I punish her?
Jade, you tell me
Why don't we, don't we...
marry her to the Mountain Devil
Jade, you?
Sold when you're alive,
and sold when you're dead...
That Demon has many concubines,
you'll suffer!
You betrayed me!
Cut off her hair
What a waste of beautiful hair
I've spent so much time combing it...
What a waste!
Scissors!
Jade, didn't you just call me your sister?
You knew the Priestess was hiding here...
Why did you betray me?
For her own good...
I'm going to scratch your face!
Priestess, please forgive me!
Go to hell!
Please forgive Lotus!
Jade...
Sister...
Don't worry, I'll marry in your place
Crocodile tears
But I won't let you get away
Let who get away?
Come here!
You're sisters!
You'll both marry the Mountain Devil
Scratch her face!
Priestess, don't...
Won't you forgive me?
You want me to really damage your face?
I want her face scratched to hell
Is this it?
Yes!
Come on!
I'm one of you!
Who are you?
Lotus?
Run away!
Don't be afraid,
Buddha'll protect us, good will win...
You better let her go!
Hands off!
or I'll blow you up...
I'll come back and fight later
Come back!
I'm going to eat him first
You can lick me, but no kissing!
Did I save the wrong girl?
You'd better turn over a new leaf
I will!
I better take you back,
you can't be tamed!
I'm back!
I'm off!
Sister, run!
Jade!
You witch - still dare
to call my fighting 'games'?
Next time I'll blow up your nest!
Jade!
We're far away from it now
It doesn't matter how far we go
Why?
What are you two up to back there?
My urn of ashes
is in the hands of the Priestess...
Under the 1,000 year old tree,
at daybreak...
My soul will have to return there
I promise you I'll find your urn of ashes
Don't depend on me to help
Concentrate on flying!
Be careful!
What did you just say?
You're going to back out now?
I do one thing, something else happens,
it never ends
So what?
I'll never be able to work out my payment!
Add you stupidity,
plus my naivete and intelligence...
You should also add
your greediness and heartlessness...
In the end you're just jealous of me!
Jealous of you?
You two are always in an hot embrace...
I never get a chance!
I don't know what type of monk you are,
but I'm also human
I need love too!
I'm only doing this to save someone
Stop fighting!
The Priestess isn't easy to handle...
I don't think I'll ever get away...
Fong,
just pretend this never happened
I'll go by myself!
Stop putting it on I won't help you
If you're going to help him, move!
Even if he begs me,
I won't go...
But if you beg me,
I may consider it
Well, take your time then
Hey!
Fong, what're you going to do?
Get your urn of ashes,
then save Master
That would be suicide!
Give yourself a break...
It's none of your business!
Look what you've done to me...
If not for you, I wouldn't be in this mess
I saved you, and you're blaming me?
You can't fight me,
how can you help me?
I'm not afraid,
I'm not afraid
It's getting light,
I can't stop you
No one'll help me,
I'll have to help myself
Take care
I knew I'd find you!
So many urns!
How to find hers?
Let's look together
I don't need your help,
I can't afford you
The likely ones go on this side
I wonder which one contains Lotus's ashes?
None of your business!
Smart ass!
This might be
Or, this could be too
It's so big!
Lotus wasn't so fat...
It goes on that side...
How am I going to carry all of these?
Want me to get a horse and cart?
Forget it, I can't afford it
Just for you, I won't charge
Abracadabra - show the way!
Look and see if it's in that urn
It really is Lotus!
We found it!
Put it away then!
Tree Devil,
how dare you belittle me!
I'm going to burn you up...
Then let's see what you can do?
The old monk!
I've found your Master
Bring him down please!
Okay!
How is he?
I can't tell!
His eyes are swollen
Master!
Move your Master,
I'm going to burn the tree
It's raining,
let's get out of the rain...
If it doesn't stop raining, we'll run
I'm angry we didn't burn that old witch!
Master!
Are your alright, Master!
Master, your eyes!
Fong!
You finally made it...
Fong, someone else is here,
who is it?
It's me sir... The nice young man
you met at the market
Good, you decided to change
your ways, and join us
Yes, I'm not as greedy as you think
We should be safe here
There's an inn over there,
we can rest awhile
Okay!
Wait!
Why?
What's the matter, Master?
They're here!
Who is?
Those filthy ones!
What filthy ones?
Fong!
Lotus, it's Lotus!
Lotus!
I'll take care of her
Don't Master, she helped us...
She's on our side!
Really?
Lotus, I found your urn of ashes
Hold on, there's another one
Fong...
Don't believe her,
she's a fake!
Fong, don't believe her,
I'm the real one
Which one's real?
How do I know?
Which is the real one, Master?
How should I know?
Fong, don't believe her, Fong...
Reveal yourself!
It's the Tree Devil!
Lotus
Hey!
Fong!
How come we're still in Orchid Temple?
We never managed
to escape the Tree Devil's grasp!
I know where Fong is.
You must go quickly
Of course you know where he is!
You lied to us from the beginning...
Now you're trying to trap us
My soul's always been with my urn of ashes...
Like you,
I was set up by the Priestess
Rubbish,
you expect me to believe you?
I'm going to break your urn...
and disperse your spirit,
so you won't do more harm
I never lied to you...
You think
I let the Tree Devil take Fong on purpose?
Yin, don't you believe me?
Demon, I'm going to destroy you
Master, let's get the old one,
and let this one go
Go!
Go on!
Fong is in Orchid Temple,
go and save him
Let's go
You dropped your abacus
Forget it,
I'll never make money on this job
Let's go and save Fong
Right
Master, the devil hurt by you...
...is now recovering.
Fong!
Fong, where is he?
Over there!
Can't you see,
he's hanging up there
Little monk,
I'm going to suck your energy...
Then I'll sell you to the Mountain Devil...
You'll never be able to reincarnate...
and you'll rot in hell!
Butterfly...
You can't even handle this monk,
you're useless
Priestess, I can do it!
I'll seduce him, just you watch!
Lotus!
How dare you come back!
Priestess, I'll finish her off
No, I came for forgiveness...
I brought the other two back with me...
They're hiding behind the grass
Damn her, she's sold us out
You witch, how dare you betray us...
I should've destroyed your urn!
The underworld is invincible!
Abandon law and order!
Heaven and earth move, lend your powers!
- Stars scatter - ...sword fly!
Cover the skies!
Oh my gold!
I'll hold them back!
The light of Buddha shines!
Butterfly!
Priestess, help me!
You're wounded, you're useless now,
I need your energy
You old Tree Devil,
you devour your own people!
No matter how powerful you are...
or that you're in human form,
you're still a demon
Go to hell, take my spell...
Soldiers of wind and fire,
show your power
Why did you betray
my Master and Yin?
How else could I distract the Priestess
and save you?
My manuscript!
Stars scatter!
Heaven and earth move,
lend your power
The Mountain Devil...
The Mountain Devil will come, run quickly...
You go first!
Butterfly!
Fong!
Come on, Lotus
Butterfly!
You were right,
leave with the monk...
At least you won't end up like this
I was wrong, too!
I shouldn't trust them!
Otherwise,
I won't be a wandering ghost!
Quick, help me!
Butterfly!
Help me!
Let's go Lotus! Come on!
Come with your Master!
We can't get away like this,
step on my cloak!
Onto my cloak
Master, wait for Lotus
She's a demon,
don't be seduced by her
Fong!
Lotus, quickly, Lotus!
Lotus!
Fong!
Lotus?
Lotus
Fong, I'm over here!
Lotus, your urn of ashes!
Old monk, your student is down here...
Don't you go back to save him?
Soldiers of fire and wind,
come, come, come
Buddha be merciful
Master!
Come on up
You kill the tree devil
and I bring you all to hell
Mountain devil is coming!
Thank you for saving me sir...
I was only trying to save my student
Master, Lotus is really...
Forget it,
there's one hour before daybreak...
Once it's light we'll be fine
Come to hell with me, you can't escape!
Master, we won't make it!
Yin,
let's break a path through it
Right! Heaven and earth move...
- Lend your powers
- The light of Buddha!
We won't make it
I'll use all my life force to fight it
Come on!
Fong, is it light yet?
Not yet, Master
He's made the skies dark,
we're in his clutches...
You take care of the monk,
I'll distract him
You're no match for them
I'll find a way
Yin!
Mountain Devil,
I've destroyed your bastard sister
Are you afraid to show yourself?
I'll destroy you!
The spell exerts itself!
Here I come!
He's gone!
What can you do?
- Master
- Fong.
Your body'll hold the Gold Buddha's energy
I'll send you above the clouds
to absorb the sun's rays
Master, you'll bleed to death!
Concentrate!
Master, Master
Are you alright, Master!
Let me go!
You'll die if you go up there!
If I don't, you'll all die
Monk, if I don't come back
Please bury my urn of ashes properly for me
Lotus, we're all depending on you
Lotus!
Lotus
We keep trying to be apart...
Yet we end up together!
But where we're going is not for you
I know why I've to go, don't worry!
What're you doing?
I'm afraid I might let go of you
Untie yourself!
If I let go, you'll fall down!
Take care of yourself first!
My eyes!
The sun!
I'm out of breath!
Wow!
I fell so far, and I'm not hurt!
Lotus
Hey, help me out!
This is what I get for being kind!
Lotus... Lotus!
Lotus!
It's a shame your spirit is dispersed...
Is this what one gets for being kind...
I hope good will come to you in the end
Fong
Lotus, Lotus
I thought I'd never see you again!
Take my urn of ashes with you,
and I'll leave here, too.
Who are you talking to?
All that is left is this red ribbon!
You mean her spirit dispersed?
Yes!
I must go now, hope we meet again
We'll leave that to fate.
We've got to go too, bye for now
Goodbye
Let's go, Master
Fong, why're you walking so fast?
I can't find Lotus's urn of ashes!
Really?
Lotus,
let's get to know each other better
You reap what you sow,
stealing is wrong
I put the ashes inside my gourd
Fong!
I'll find you wherever you're gone!
Fong, where are you taking me?
The demon said there's no heaven...
Is that true?
Stop talking and do something...
Help me up!
Sure!