Bring back my clothes and handbag.
Why?
Clothes.
Clothes? Yes, yes, ok.
Come here.
Aaah! Look over there!
- Whoa!
- What the hell do you want?
I am gonna tell
you right now! Yeah?
First! Put on some clothes!
Hey, fucker. What are you
looking at me for? Come on up here!
Nothing's happening here.
Just go. Just leave. Please!
If you don't back away in 1 minute!
I'm gonna push him off!
Push? Push?
- This is hilarious!
- Which broadcasting company did you come from, you fuckers?
Just take it easy.
That's why I said to leave here.
We'll be down soon.
- Hey, bastard! You still don't have your pants on?
- I'm wearing them.
What are you bastards doing?
- Don't move fuckers!
- Everybody's going to die, fuckers!
Help me!
This bastard is the one with
the bull's testicles?
Yes.
What kind of fool is
this character?
It says in his chart that
he's a student but!
38 hours ago he came in with
an erection and he's still got it!
isn’t that dangerous?
If it doesn't go down by tomorrow
we'll have to cut it out.
I'm sorry.
It’s ok.
You hurt there twice now.
I've got to go now. Take care.
Yes.
When did you meet him?
Not too long ago.
Tell me about him.
He's the best looking hottie on campus.
What's a hottie?
Oh, you know it's all right.
He's very kind to me.
Strange guy.
What?
Why would such a handsome guy
be interested in a girl like you?
What's so special about you.
I'm very popular in school.
That's crap!
Can't you see that I'm a hottie too?
B.S. Does a hottie have
tiny breasts like you?
I can't even recognize where they are!
- Let's see!
- No.
Let's see.
Mom, show me yours first!
No! Let me see if you're
a hottie or not-let's see yours.
No! Look at that! Look at that bitch!
That bitch has a hickie. She always
has a souvenir from her nights out.
She really embarrasses me.
What is a hickie?
It’s a love bite.
A bruise on your neck you bitch!
How do you get that?
A mosquito bite?
Hello? If a mosquito bites you
do you put on a bandage?
This bitch is so stupid.
Aah! Next week is your birthday!
Right!
Do you want anything?
Why?
You gonna buy me something?
Well~ We'll see how you
act in the next few days.
Let's eat some Ramen.
- Did you check out that ring?
How much is it?
- How much do you think it is?
How much?
More than a 1000 bucks.
Hey, fucker! What kind of
a ring costs more than a grand.
Not even a championship belt
would cost that much! Fuck!
How can I get a 1000 bucks
in one week.
Older hey, take off your pants!
Take your shirt off!
5, 6, 7, 8. Look ahead!
Look at your hands! Hands!
Don't move your legs!
Back straight!
Keep your backs straight!
Stand up bitch, or I'm gonna
whack you on your head!
How can we win
a championship like this?
The competition is
in less than a week.
Don't you guys think!
Don't you have brains?
Are you sure?
What?
Don't you use birth control pill?
See! Those bitches are all alike!
How can you tell if the baby is yours?
Did you check?
Just give her a couple of hundred bucks
and tell her to get rid of it. Okay?
Can't you just do it?
No. You'll have to come back
tomorrow with your guardian.
- What's up?
- Do you have time tomorrow?
Why?
I've made an appointment.
Appointment?
Why?
What is this?
You need money to do that, uh?
Why? You want me to go with you?
Today is my birthday.
You and me have birthdays.
But this baby will never have one.
It’s just waiting to die.
When did I ask for money from you?
Why do you have to
make me so pathetic?
What's this?
Change it.
Look at this one more time.
Look at the finish on this.
No, no, Miss!
Happy birthday to you.
Dear Eunhyo
Surprise!
Yeah, I bought an expensive stuff for her.
But next thing I know she popped me and then
she's giving me a nasty look.
Where the hell is it?
jeez...
Yeah, so I pulled it out.
I gave it to her and thought
she would be happy! Fuck!
But she slapped me and
fuck I fell down so hard. Fuck!
Excuse me...
Is that possible?
Listen Eunsik.
What do you mean she popped you?
Is that some new language?
Do you know what
you're talking about?
I don't know.
You don't know
then it's not important.
- Hello.
- Eunsik.
Eunhyo?
What are you doing today?
A date?
Are you her guardian?
Yes.
You're not kids!
Why aren't you more responsible.
Sex is not a game to play with.
You should think about the consequences!
Your enjoyment can ruin a woman's life!
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Yes...
Lee Eunhyo.
Yes.
- I'll be right here.
- Okay.
Lie down.
What are you doing?
Hurry up and lie down.
- Are you ok?
- Move aside.
What are you doing?
We're almost there, easy, easy!
Do you want something to drink?
Relax. I'll be back soon.
Where are you going?
I'll be right back.
Eunsik.
Don't tell Sangok.
Please, I really need to
refund this ring.
Sorry, I can't help.
I paid you $1000,
just give me back $950.
Sorry, sir. We can't do that.
I will give up $50.
Please I just need to get the money back.
Are you awake?
Just a minute.
Here you are.
- It’s painful!
- Ok. I know.
Don't move!
Just stay still.
My mother said abortions are
just as difficult as giving births.
You have to keep your body warm
for at least 15 days
afterwards otherwise it hurts
even more when you're old.
This hand.
What are you crying for?
Do you want me to show
you my exercise routine?
Hup! The basis of these
exercises is patience and gut.
Say it! Gut!
Are you kidding?
Say it! Louder! Gut!
Gut!
One! Two! Longer One, two,
three, four! One, two, three, four!
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two... Three, four, five,
six, seven, eight!
Yahoo!
What's that? Keep your legs straight!
Look at your feet!
Hey!
You little shit, what time is it now?
What are you thinking?
You don't remember that
tomorrow is the big competition?
Have you finished goofing around?
I'm sorry. Don't worry about me.
Let's practice!
One, two, one, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
- Oh! I'm sorry.
- Aaugh, What's the matter?
We are invited to the national
championships to perform tomorrow.
- It’s going to be broadcast on TV.
- Really?
Hello, where were you?
- He said internet!
- Really!?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8
1, 2, 3...
Oh, no, no!
Not this bastard again!
What's up with him?
What's all this about?
What are you doing here?
What did you hit me for?
Didn't you say Taehak had no stamina?
Stop talking shit, you bitch.
What the fuck! It’s annoying.
I can't keep doing this!
Fuck!? How dare you could
say such a word to me?
What are you hitting me for?
Enjoy a great performance of the
National University Aerobic athletes!
- Hold on.
- Why are you so late?
Songguk is really pissed!
You're dead!
Hurry up and get changed.
We're in trouble.
- Hold on.
- You have to hit in the center.
Hold here! It’s ok.
Hey~
How are you?
We're gonna lose
because of you!
Waaaa! Ok!
We'll now take
a ten minute intermission!
Until then the Sunjong University
Concentration Power Team will entertain us!
Our team's first performance!
Yippie! Yea!
Hup!
- Hup!
Oh! Look at that!
Oh, damn!
Wha!
Great! Fantastic!
Excellent! Fantastic!
Thank you, thank you!
That's great! Terrific!
I knew you guys could do it!
It’s ok it won't make any damage.
What's going on!
After eating it'll be ok.
- Songguk, Songguk.
- Yoomi, Yoomi.
- Yoomi my Yoomi! How were we?
Perfect! Everything was perfect!
- Songguk, Yoomi
- The next competition is for Solo Female Routines.
Competitors be prepared.
Lee Eunhyo! Eunhyo!
Lee Eunhyo Where is Eunhyo!
Where is that bitch?
Where is she?
That brainless bitch!
Lee Eunhyo. Lee Eunhyo.
What time is it!
Next is Lee Eunhyo,
a junior from Sunjong University.
Go for it, Eunhyo!
I'm losing my voice.
Where's Eunhyo?
Eunhyo? In the restroom.
- Restroom?
- Yes.
Why is he panting for?
Eunhyo, where are you?
Eunhyo, what's wrong?
I'm bleeding.
Eunhyo.
Eunhyo! Eunhyo! Eunhyo!
Eunhyo wake up! Wake up!
Where should we go?
Where! Where! Where?
Eunhyo! Hang on.
We are almost there!
You can't come in here.
You must wait.
Mother!
Bitch, you can't do this!
How can you do this to me you bitch?
Why don't you die you bitch!
How could you do this to me?
How can you do this to me
after how I raised you?
Bitch! I didn't raise you like this!
Is that all you are? Huh?
Why?
What are you doing?
How could you after I raised you so well!
Please calm down!
What! Did you do this?
Did you to this to my daughter?
My Eunhyo! What are you
going to do? My Eunhyo!
You bastard! You did this to my Eunhyo!
You bastard!
No! Stop it!
Mother! Mother! Mother...
- Congratulations! Yea!
- Thank you.
Eunsik!
Why are you still wearing you uniform?
- Our performance finished long ago.
- Sit down.
It’s just a joke!
No! Don't!
Stop him! Stop!
Leave me! Leave me alone!
You motherfucker!
What's with all the language?
Sit down and chill out.
Fuck you!
Have you been drinking?
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Love is not a fucking joke!
Your one time enjoyment!
Fuck!
It hurts the woman and now that woman'll have
to spend the rest of her life with that pain.
Fuck you!
You've learned only shit!
You don't know what love is!
Fuck you!
What can of crap is going on here!
Take out your hand and go in.
Hit me anywhere you want.
Hup!
One, two.
Hit me on three!
Wha!
One, two, three!
Now this is how it should be!
Come on, Eunsik.
Hit me anywhere!
Anywhere.
Really? I can hit anywhere?
My body is like a stone!
A stone!
Who put a real balk in here?
I'm so fucking embarrassed!
Shit!
Hey...
Maybe the exterminator is spraying again.
Exterminator?
Yeah, it's a monthly thing.
I see.
Eunsik!
Yes?
Have you changed your mind?
Changed what?
You said you love me?
When did I say that?
If not! Never mind.
What shit's going on!
Fire!