Conquer! Come out, you old bastard!
I seek revenge on behalf of
the Unchallenged City!
Ming! You think
you can upturn Conquer's Clan?
You are too naive
Conquer's Clan destroyed my family
My father was murdered
Unchallenged Sword was stolen
Even if I, Ming, cannot get revenge
I must have Conquer explain
his evil deeds
Give me Unchallenged City,
give me my Unchallenged Sword!
What's your business with them?
Monks should be charitable and kind
So I promised Young Master...
to help investigate
the murder of his family
I hope you will help,
in the name of Buddha
How dare you!
Today is my daughter's wedding
I won't
let any conflict interrupt
tonight's celebration
Conquer's Clan may not be
as influential as Shaolin
But we are the leaders of all
the other clans
Excuse my directness
Support me and prosper
Or oppose me and die!
Buddha have pity
You have explained your position clearly
Young Master, what do you think?
My skills are not strong enough,
I cannot even defeat Wind
I am certainly no match for Conquer,
I came to deliver this for my uncle,
Sword Saint
"Our battle should take place
on the autumn solstice
This will settle
our ten-years-old appointment"
I've waited for this for a long time
Everything's fine now!
A toast, everyone! Music!
I wish I were the bride
You're such a tomboy
Who will ever marry you?
Wind is one of the favorite disciples
of my Lord
and he will be his son-in-law
So after the ceremony,
he will be twice as close!
Wind, promise me,
you must treat Charity well
Understand?
I will obey your wishes
Let's bow to the ancestors. Kneel...
Hold it!
Cloud
Come with me
Striding Cloud, how dare you!
I thought you would never come!
Why did you agree to marry Wind?
You never asked why
I cannot let another man touch you!
I can marry him
and still keep seeing you
Charity
Come back!
I have obeyed you for 10 years
I'm leaving Conquer's Clan
and taking Charity with me
If you're a man,
go and fight for your wife
Don't let the world laugh at you
Fight for your reputation!
Cloud
Master! Shut up!
Father!
Look out!
Charity!
She is already my woman. Go away!
Charity, is it true?
I'm sorry, Wind
Why did you agree to marry me then?
Have you ever loved me?
Yes
It's all right if you don't love me
Love doesn't call for an explanation
You'll always be mine
Charity, I love you
I'll always be with you
Charity...
Master!
I killed my own daughter...
Thanks to the ancestors
Phoenix is finally pregnant
The Lui family line will
have continuation,
and the Xia's family will continue
for generations and prosper!
Father-in-law, bless us
I will take good care of
your descendants
Lai
You guard this shrine well
Even though he is preserved by lce Vigor
You must still protect
my late father's body
Yes, sir
Sit down, Phoenix
Who is it?
Striding Cloud wishes to borrow
your lce Vigor
What?
It is
the heirloom treasure of our family,
how dare you take it?
I will accert any condition
only if you agree to lend it to me
Cloud, lce Vigor is buried with
my late father to preserve his body
I am very moved that you would risk
so much for a loved one
But have you thought about
my position
if you took it away?
That is your problem, not mine
Sorry, I cannot oblige
See our guest out!
Phoenix!
Dragon!
Phoenix, are you okay?
I came for the lce Vigor
I do not wish to hurt you
Halt!
You may not enter!
Leave if you wish to live!
Striding Cloud,
return Charity's body to me
No one can take her away
With your powers?
I did not teach you
the last move of Cloud Palms
I will show you today
so you will die in peace
Cloud Palms will only work with liquid,
and here we are in the desert now
I followed you here
before I confronted you
Let's see how much blood you have
I will use it to enrich
my Trinity Strength
Charity, wait for me!
Father, look! Someone has fainted!
It's Striding Cloud who stole the bride!
Hurry! Let's bring him inside!
Striding Cloud...
Give me back my daughter!
I must avenge for Father?
You must love that girl alot
You're so romantic
You can even love in your dreams
Charity...
Muse, what are you doing?
Nothing. He is still sweating
I'll get some medicine
I've been asking around
After Conquer killed his own daughter
Striding Cloud took the body
and got into a lot of trouble
Conquer did all this to him
at the royal mausoleum
There is so much hatred
between Master and pupil
How sad!
He lost his lover
and his arm all in one day
Father, will he die?
So you must be very careful
when picking a husband
Who says I want to get married?
You do. Its written all over your face
You taught me yourself
As herbal doctors,
it is our mission to save
and help those who need us
No matter good or bad,
a life is a life, right?
Father! What's wrong with you?
Father...
Are you all right?
I won't think of marriage any more...
This arm
Ever since I succeeded training
this Fire Beast Arm,
it has been rejecting my body,
as though it doesn't belong to me
I can't control it
Muse, tell my assistants to get ready
for an operation
Hurry!
Since Striding Cloud's arrival,
I've had a feeling that
this arm has found its real master
I am going to give him my Fire Beast Arm
Striding Cloud, think of it this way
We are repaying a debt
from a previous life
Good medicine always tastes bitter
lts good for you
You are...
I am Muse
You have fainted for four days
If my father had not rescued you,
you would have died
My arm... Why?
Like it? I put it on for you
You've wakened
It was my arm
Take it as a present from me
We've met before, during the wedding...
Muse
Fire Beast Arm finally found
its rightful owner
Thank you
Don't mention it
Striding Cloud,
your arm is still in recovery
It needs plenty of rest
Muse, let's go... give him some peace
I'm feeding him his medicine
He has his arms now
He can do it himself
Wind
For two months
you've done nothing but drink and sleep
If you go on like this,
you will be wasted!
I'm wasted anyway
Go with Hawk and Bat
Bring me the Blood Bodhi fruit
It is in Cirrus Cave
where your father was killed
Behave if you know what's good for you
This is an order
Cloud...
Cloud
Cloud, meal time
You still miss her?
Let me tell you
When I saw your lover at Conquer's Clan
wearing that beautiful bridal gown,
I was so envious
They call you Muse
because you are easily amused?
Certainly not!
I was blessed
by a Muse at birth
Simple as that
Thank you both
for rescuing me
Don't mention it
Will you be returning to Conquer's Clan?
I must
To seek revenge
Revenge back and forth with no end
When will all this vengeance end?
In this world some people...
have no friends and no love
I am such a person
Father, I like
the feeling of being carried by you
Mother!
Master Wind
Have some water
Come
What is that on the cliff?
Blood Bodhi fruit!
They must be Blood Bodhi fruit!
His Lordship once said
just one will increase your powers
Go away!
Come out! Beast! Come out...
Stop shouting
If you keep shouting
the beast may come out
Master Wind, please don't blame us
That day,
all 296 people at Unchallenged City
took this poison
It's colourless, scentless,
flesh-rotting and bone-eating
They died in the hands of Master Cloud
Why are you doing this?
Lord Conquer ordered it, so we must obey
Senseless, it's senseless...
It will be
a great achievement for us
If we bring back your head
and the fruits, we'll be rewarded
I'll give you back the fruits
Then we'll call it even. Deal?
"With a heart as clear as ice,
the sky may fall and I will not fear"
Who is it?
It's me, Jester
Congratulations my Lord,
you have achieved amazing powers!
World-dominating powers!
What are you saying?
This Sword Saint, such arrogance
To challenge my Lord
He doesn't know you have achieved
this amazing power
Really, you're fulfilling destiny
Fulfilling destiny?
Yes, fulfilling destiny. Oops
Jester
You sweet-talker, that is nonsense!
No, I dare not
Every word I say comes from my heart
Go out
Yes
Yes, Master
You are the only one
I don't have to worry about
Now that Wind and Cloud have
both disappeared and
I must go to battle tomorrow,
I command you to take leadership of the
three halls, and help me rule the world
I only worry about by inability
I have full confidence in you
Frost, it is my life's ambition to
beat Sword Saint
Soon,
the leadership of Conquer's Clan...
will be yours
Thank you, Master
In the face of battle,
to preserve our interests...
Conquer's Clan cannot afford
any mistakes
Whoever is disloyal to me must die
Terminate Jester! He's a nuisance!
Have you seen Jester?
No, no
Stop!
Please don't kill me...
Lord Conquer is a true villain
He is playing tricks on us all
Rubbish!
You betrayed Master. You must die!
He tricked Wind and Cloud
and killed their parents
I'll bring you to a person,
then you'll understand
It is Mud Buddha,
Lord Conquer has imprisoned him
Jester, you look ridiculous...
in those clothes
Let me get change first,
and I'll take you to Mud Buddha
Master Frost...
So the man who kidnapped him
the other day was Master
I must fight. I must persist...
I must not die now
Conquer killed your parents
I purposely gave him
yours and Cloud's birth chart
so he would let you live
Destiny...
All things go in cycles
Cause, consequences...
Everything will have its final judgement
What shall I do?
"The Dragon is powerful,
but will be stranded
when wind and cloud become a storm"
Sword Saint has come for the duel
A long-awaited occassion!
Although I now rule
the martial arts world,
not being able to fight you is
like having a bone stuck in my throat
I must get it out to ease my discomfort
I am glad you have preserved
your strength. You still look strong
If I can defeat you today
I will have no regrets
I accept your challenge with
my Unchallenged Sword
And I will have...
Defeated your entire family
Wait here
Is he human? Why is he not moving?
Don't
Stay here. I'm going in
Uncle!
Conquer, I'll die with you!
I am so useless...
Help me seek revenge
Mud Buddha said,
Wind and Cloud must be together
Or it won't be a storm
Cloud!
Blood Bodhi fruit can increase
your powers
Frost, announce to the world,
I have defeated Sword Saint,
my ultimate opponent
I am now truly invincible
You killed the parents of Wind and Cloud
You ordered Hawk and Bat to kill Wind,
right?
So you didn't kill Jester?
Conquer, you cold-blooded murderer!
I was right
Of the three, you are most naive
I refuse to be your successor
You're only using me!
Correct. Let it be known to all
Better that they owe me, than I owe them,
including you
Frost, where are you going?
I'm leaving Conquer's Clan
You think you can come
and go as you please?
Frost
So you two are still alive
Conquer
Sword Saint's martial arts is
truly powerful
But nothing
compared to my Trinity Strength
Ten years ago, I asked you
Aren't you afraid I'll avenge my father?
If I can take you in,
I have planned for such a day
Master Wind
Do not use all your force,
do not say all you think
If you go too far,
destiny will prematurely end
I taught you
all the martial arts you ever knew
Remember, I am your Master
Cloud is unpredictable, Wind is formless
You think you two can defeat me?
Let me tell you
This is Sword Grave,
besides swords
it will also be your burial ground
Prepare to die!
I taught you Fists, Palms and Kicks,
but I ultimate weapon is the sword!
"The Dragon is powerful,
but will be stranded
when wind and cloud become a storm"
Mud Buddha,
I don't believe in your predictions
I only believe in myself
I have hidden the sword
Even if you find it,
you cannot use it without my blood
or that of my son's
Charity...
Charity
Father...
don't leave me alone
Father, help me...
I'm suffering!
Give me back the lives of my family...
Give me back my reputation...
Give me back the lives of my family!
Give me back my reputation!
Cloud!
What are you doing?
Get out of my way
After all, he raised us
Sword Saint, Whispering Prince
Where are you? Help me
I am Conqueror of the World!
It is said "If you go too far...
Destiny will prematurely end"
I am Conqueror of the World
I am Conqueror of the World...