TUBE Entertainment presents
A Dreamax production
Executive Producers KIM, Seung-Bum
MOON Sung-Joon
Produced by WHANG, Phil-Sun
LIM, Soo-Jung
KIM, Rae-Won
LEE, Mi-Sook
Screenplay by KIM, Jin
a film by LEE, Eon-Hee
Why do you get so excited
every time you see the ballet?
Isn't it awesome?
I wish I could see one live
just once
I wonder if this troupe will
come to Korea?
How would you like to go see it
over there?
- Really?
- Really!
- We're going to Europe, then?
- Yes
And we're really seeing
the ballet, too?
Let's watch it
until we're sick of it
- Then how about your restaurant?
- I sold it
- What?
- To go to Europe
Really?
No! Lies, lies!
All are lies!
What a liar!
Want me to prepare
a bath for you?
Sounds good
- Did you bring your medicine?
- Yes, here
Did someone move in?
Get in the house
I'm going
Didn't you forget something?
- You're insatiable
- That's an expression of affection
Why don't you
get a boyfriend?
What a hopeless class this is!
Teacher, please help
us wake up
You come on up here
I'll wake you up with
a slap to the head
Teacher, please tell us about
your first love!
Haven't you loved someone
like the crossing guard did?
Oh, you poor girls, do you
really believe that story?
Stop talking and
write this down
A 100-day anniversary ring
How are you doing in class?
It's okay
Because as you came in the
middle of the semester
it won't be easy to get along
But they'll be friendly soon
Don't worry too much
I guess she's Mina?
Don't hesitate to tell me
if you feel uncomfortable
And ask me anything
if you want
Now, go!
Well...
I have one question
You mean about Kisu
the crossing guard?
Oh, Ki-Su?
The man with the flags
in front of the school?
When he was in high school
he liked a girl in our school
And one rainy day
when Ki-su
was waiting for her
she was run over while crossing
the street and killed
Since then, he has stood in front
of our school, directing traffic
Crying when it's raining
Isn't that just a made-up story
that students tell?
Yes, I guess so
- Excuse me, White wine, please
- Yes, just a moment
Juk-ja asked a fortuneteller
if she would find a boyfriend
before she died
The oracle said
she would find
a boyfriend that winter
So Jin-ju asked
the same question,
and the fortuneteller said
Why don't you just
watch TV drama instead?
Being in love
is a nice thing, isn't it?
You don't get hungry nor cold
even when you don't eat in winter
You are right, We had
those days too, didn't we?
- Misuk
- What?
You know about Mina
Don't say anything
if it's about Mina
I've thought about it enough
But still, why isn't she
in the hospital?
There's no cure for her
So, why stay
in the hospital?
But there could be
a miracle
Miracle? Yes, there could be...
But I think it already was a miracle
that Mina has lived until now
Mina has been in and out of the
hospital since she was born
with operations and injections
all over her body
Now they say
there's no more hope
I can't make her
suffer more
for her few last months
You sure you won't regret it
after Mina's gone?
Then, I will drink cry
and I'll call you
Oh gees, you!
Are you watching that again?
It's so embarrassing
What?
Naked guys dancing like that...
I don't know where to look
Just don't look down there
How? I just keep looking there
Protruding... and so noticeable
I think I'm still a woman, too
I'm leaving
Lock your door
I'm sorry, did it hurt?
I'll get you some medicine
Hello?
Look down here!
Hey! Look! Look!
Look right here!
Can't you see me?
Can I get a cigarette?
Cigarette!
Take off your headphones
and look at me!
Will you give me a cigarette?
I'll pay you double
I just moved in downstairs
Shouldn't you say, "Nice to meet
you", or something like that?
Give me a light, too!
No lighter?
I'll return it as soon as I use it
This is interesting
Isn't it a navy insignia?
- Throw it to me
- Next time
Hello
I just moved
into downstairs
Nice to meet you
Oh, I see
Thank you about yesterday
I'll give it back to you soon
- Did you lend him something?
- Er... yes
Isn't he handsome?
You weren't looking
at his face, I guess
Come on, he's
exactly your type
You can have him if you
like him that much
Don't bs me
Oh, I got a present for you
in the back seat
A present?
- A cellular phone?
- Why, you don't like it?
Hello...
What?
Since this is your first time
I'll give you a break
If you call me for no reason
I'll stop carrying this phone
The total is 29,000 won
Isn't it too warm to
wear a mitten?
Don't you have
any bag with straps?
Hey, trouble-making girl!
You look like an
exemplary student, though
Sneaking a smoke without your
mother knowing?
Give me my lighter back
Why, so you can smoke
secretly some more?
Why are you picking on me?
That's what guys do when they
find a girl they like
You know what, I studied
psychology a little
Human beings have a tendency
to solve problems unconsciously
So if someone makes you feel bad
you keep thinking about him
Like how school boys pull on
the skirts of girls they like
Those little kids
know that instinctively
It's all in psychology books
Wasn't that on TV?
I saw that program, too
Huh? It was on TV, too?
Oh, I forgot your
lighter again
Take this, instead of the cigarette
that I borrowed yesterday
No I want my lighter back
Hey, don't be such a grouch
This isn't just a candy, it's my heart
Hello my princess
Did you have fun today?
Icky... Am I a baby?
Of course, spilling things all over
Didn't you forget something?
Someone found it
and gave it to the janitor
Keep it safe
It's expensive
Save my number and my restaurant
number in your phone
You can save up to
1,000 numbers on it
I don't even know 10 numbers
Aren't you going to answer it?
- Hello
- Hi, trouble-maker!
Wrong number
Hey, don't hang up!
I'm really sorry about today
Give me a chance to apologize
What number did you dial?
Oh, is your mother there?
- You got the wrong number
- Wait, hold on!
Open the window in an hour
It's important, please!
Wow, this phone is so cool
I can take pictures, too
Mina... don't you want to
fall in love?
Misuk, wake up
Okay, here is a picture of
a crazy woman
When I was your age, that's
what I always thought about
Where I could find a hot boy?
Where I could find my love?
So was it successful?
Of course, My romantic life
was really prospering back then
My dating life was always
packed and croweded
It was awesome
That's your problem, Misuk
confusing love and business
And you want to get
as much as you give
Real love isn't like that
It's just being happy without
getting anything... only giving
You must have read too many
romance comic books
In my opinion
Love is like this...
Someone you love gets hit by a
car and killed one rainy day
After that, you can't leave
the accident site
You go there to direct traffic
thinking about your love
Never missing a single day
Crying when it's raining...
What an ominous
comic book you read
Anyway, I will definitely find
the man of my destiny
and fall madly in love
with him
When I finally introduce him to
you, please be opposed to him
- even if you like him
- Why?
Because it would be cool
I will have an immortal love
that overcomes all obstacles
A love that can't be defeated
by parents, nations
or even death
How about you? Have you had
a passionate love?
Sure
- My dad?
- Yes
Do you still love him?
I don't know
I forgot everything
- Lies!
- It's true
- You still think about me, don't you?
- Once in a while
- What kind of thoughts?
- Thoughts of how much I owe you
Do you think Mina is a debt?
Mina is a present
The biggest present you gave to me
Then what do you think
you owed me?
Happiness
I owe you my happiness
And I owe Mina
There's no way
I can repay you
but I can reward Mina, so I'll do
as much as I can for her
So you must help me
Help our Mina only to
have happy times
until she goes to you
Hurry and open your window
or you'll regret it!
Tonight, I'll wait for you
Same time, same place
Hey, hey there!
Room No 306!
Hey! Hey you
What are you doing there?
Oh, well there...
There's a mouse
on the window ledge
A mouse at night...
What a strange boy...
You know
You knew my hand was like this
before you gave birth, right?
I read that people
get abortions
for much smaller problems
Why didn't you do that?
Mina, you're all
grown up now, right?
There is one secret that
I never told anyone
I didn't want to tell you in a
place like this, in this way
What is it? Tell me
The truth is, your father...
isn't your real father
You just resembled so much
your father's hand
Your father was an alien
- Get out!
- You really believed me, right?
- No way! I didn't
- You were definitely taken in
You totally believed me
for about 30 seconds
Knock it off!
Maybe for 3 seconds
Someone left this at the door
Isn't it yours, Mina?
Oh, my!
This turtle cannot live
without its mate
And I've taken the
other one hostage
If you don't want
the turtles to die
surrender now
Aw... it's so sweet
Come on in
Why are you standing there?
You think I set a trap?
What kind of house is this?
This apartment was
just a studio originally
The owner let me rent it cheap
providing he could leave his stuff here
Say, why are you empty-handed?
Where's my turtle?
Wasn't it a present for me?
A present? That was just bait
Then I spit the bait out
so give me my lighter back
What a heartless neighbor
Okay, wait a second
Where did I put that lighter?
I can't find it right now
Use this one instead
Call, when you are lonely
Oh, hey, that's not mine
This must be my friend's
What a clumsy guy he is...
Here it is
Heran Erotic Massage...
Wait a sec!
Where did I...
I don't care
Just give me mine
I'm sure I put it
somewhere safe
It's really important to me
Find it right now
Don't worry I'll find it
I don't believe what you
say mister, just find it
Mister? I'm just a few years
older than you
Call me "big brother"
Say it, "bro-ther..."
Hmm, you don't seem to trust me at all
Wait...
Here!
Take this as a hostage, to go
with the one in your house
I wanted to use them as bait
but now they are real hostages
Wait a little, I will come
to save you soon
Don't make any trouble
Oh well, at least she won't
eat you or anything
By the way, what was your
phone number again?
I memorized it from your phone
the other day
but I forgot it
What for?
You don't want to get
your lighter back?
- 011-9262-8979
- Hold on! Wait!
What was it?
011-9262-8979
What on earth are you doing now?
It's okay Don't you watch TV at all?
Like the TV ad, you can remove
stains like this easily
Huh? Isn't this supposed to work?
Erased! I think it's working now!
It should be... What do you think
we're doing this for?
Oh crud! Crud!
Why the hell did you do this?
He's crazy
I saw them just wipe it off on TV
This must be a different
kind of floor
Sure, you silly!
Only new floors have that feature
It's not him being crazy
He's just dumb
How stupid!
Wait a minute...
Isn't this Mina's
phone number?
Why did you write this?
What?
Right!
How come Mina's
number is here?
What the...
Oh, that's...
I take photographs
She's so pretty
I was going
to ask her to be my model
- Oh, It's nothing...
- Hey, hey
Well, isn't that a typical way
to seduce a girl?
- No! It really isn't
- That's right
He's trying to seduce me
The photo thing is just an excuse
I knew it
It's so obvious
Once you start taking photos
he'll ask you to take it... uh...
That... what do you call it,
a "noodle" model?
You know... A model
taking photos naked?
A nude model?
Yes, a nude model
Well, on the other hand...
having a picture of you all young
and pretty wouldn't be that bad
Really? Then I should do it?
Um, nice model...
nice expression...
Give it to me
- No?
- I don't smoke in the daytime
What a cowardly, delinquent girl...
Give it to me
I'll show you
Let me show you
the easiest way
Set this on P
Then it's automatic
Hold it on an angle, like this
And then press this button
to get a focus
And after the "click" sound
just press the shutter
Try it
Why are you taking my lighter
when you've got so many already?
Didn't you smoke yesterday?
That's not your business
Did or didn't you think of me
when you were smoking?
You did!
You've started thinking
about me every time you smoke
It's because I have your lighter
What do you think of my
tension-creates-attraction theory?
No wonder you've got so many
lighters in your house
Okay, you deserve to meet me
I agree!
Who deserves whom?
You and me
How dare an old guy like you say
such a thing to a young girl?
I'm only a little older than you
Besides, I treat people 10 years
older or younger like my age
Than I should treat you
like my age too?
I think I had crush on you
from the first time I saw you
I'm going home now
I heard that the downstairs boy
came by today?
Boy?
How would I call him then?
Downstairs fellow? Downstairs dude?
I like That
I heard he gave you turtles?
What's the name?
Neil and Armstrong
What?
I mean the downstairs dude
Lee Young-jae
- What does he do?
- Takes photographs
What a handsome guy
doing such a cool thing
Which means he's just
fooling around
Well, he seems like a nice guy
You know I have an eye for men
I can introduce you if you want
Never mind
You keep him!
I'd rather buy an egg and wait
for it to become a chicken to eat
than wait for that dude to grow up
Kang Mina!
It's going to rain today
Hi my Mina!
What's up with you
visiting me here?
To maintain my popularity
Then why didn't you come to
the hospital to see me?
Did you have to
bring me out here?
You don't even want to
set one foot in the hospital?
I even wish I could rip off your
nurse's uniform
No, not today
I'm wearing a cheap bra today
It's raining
I don't have an umbrella
I have one I'll walk with you
to the hospital
Okay
Hey, you still don't
have a boyfriend?
Except for eating meat
I'm practically a monk, you know
Then you've never had a boyfriend?
Well, can I call them boyfriends?
Why do you ask
by the way?
Have you got a boyfriend?
Huh?
No, I was just...
You really don't
need to feel insecure
Don't worry and do
what you want to do
There are no right answers
Follow your feelings...
- That's the right answer
- Okay
Okay
I'm sorry but some customers just
showed up without reservations
Let's go some other time
How about this flower? sir
- Over there!
- Okay
Gosh, I am late I've got to go
Talk to you later Bye!
Hello?
- What are you doing now?
- Going home
What will you do at home?
I've got lots of time, Is there
anything you want to do with me?
I want sacks
What? Sex! Hello? Hello?
Mina?
Well... that is...
After we've been
dating for a while
After we're really close...
I mean, when two people
really want each other
This is so embarrassing
but I should be considerate
Oh god... Uh, but if you want to
do it, I'm sure I'd be good...
Tramp
No, I'm not
It really sounded like that
And who call them
sacks these days?
The way you talk to me has been
disrespectful recently
Didn't you say you treat most people
like they're your age? Oh! My bus!
Oh my! What's this?
What am I going to do?
I'm so sorry
I'm sorry
It's okay
Can't help it...
I apologize
Take off your glove
- It's okay
- It's all sticky
Is it ticklish?
It may look strange
but it works fine
Blast all the humans with your death ray!
Hey, don't step on my head!
- What are you doing under my legs?
- Enjoying the view
Hey, are you hungry now?
Here's a donut for you!
Can't you do it better?
It can't make up here
Hey! What are you
doing up there?
Hey Mina!
You really disappeared quickly
Why did you leave me alone?
The guard saw your
empty window
and treated me like a thief
You should thank me for
not shouting "Stop thief!"
Hello, ma'am How are you?
This is for you
Oh, I am sorry to
trouble you so often
You must be very tired?
Yes, I'm a little worried about
the young man downstairs
Single guys living along can be
crazy with girls and drinking...
It gets on my nerves
- I don't...
- Take care!
Oh, you leaving?
Take care!
You shouldn't
look down on them
I couldn't help you even if
they ran away
Don't you think they feel all
cooped up in a goldfish bowl?
They should get some
fresh air sometimes
Am I that pretty?
Well you have a disease too
A princess disease
Wow It's been a long time
since I saw this
What is it?
You don't know this?
It's the right-left-net game
By the way, Misuk and I
are going to Europe
Only two young girls together?
Oh, Misuk is my mother
You're so sassy
How can you call your
mother by her name?
Is she your stepmother?
I never heard this story
What are you some kind
of private investigator?
Oh no, You know how
the maid talks sometimes
Since I was sick and
in the hospital
instead of going to school
What's that got to do with
using your mom's name?
So I had no friends
The kids in my ward
were scared of my hand
By the time we got used
to each other
and became friends...
they'd have gotten well and
left hospital or they died
How about you?
I was in and out of the hospital
Once, after a big operation
I was in a coma for months
Even if I woke up
I just caught
some other disease
Do you know what my nickname
was among nurses?
The 13th-floor fixture
How about now?
Are you okay now?
- Yes, clearly
- You, you're dead!
What?
You're dead if you
step on the crack
So?
I was always complaining about
having no friends
So one day
Misuk entered my room
wearing pigtails, holding a doll
And she said "Hi, my name is Misuk
Can we be friends?"
- What a nice mother
- I like her too
Good night
Why such a dutiful kiss?
Why are you complaining
when I'm so nice to you?
Wait a minute You look different
Not natural
Do you have a boyfriend?
You've been practicing your
kissing, haven't you?
What? Knock it off!