Catch!
Take it back
Ah, it's just wires
Ok, let me come up and play with you
Right ladies, let's test your balancing skills
Now, only the Holy Mother is left
You will be my student!
Double Dragon's stance
Master's feet are tied
Go down
Not that easy
Come here
All right!
Cut!
Take it back
Come up
Cross the bridge
Your bridge is ruined,
why don't you release us now?
Retreat!
Master, my money was on you!
No... I mean.
I was sure you'd defeat them
Burn the bridge
Fei Hung
How are you?
I am fine
Fei Hung,
I was worried about you
It's a mess, a mess
If Aunt Yee sees Master holding Aunt May,
there'll be trouble
Fei Hung, it's fine, let's write to Aunt Yee
to tell her we're safe
Aunt Yee is enough,
how can he court Aunt May?
Aunt Ching will come
next month... Oh my God!
What is it?
Who's there?
I want to comfort that lady
But you don't know her
So how can you comfort her?
If I don't comfort her,
how can I get to know her?
They are back! Come out!
Master, master
Are you all right?
I am fine
Of course, they can't
compete with master at all
How are you, sir!
I'm glad you're back
Old Master Wong, Master Wong
We were thinking of ways to save you all night
Then we discovered
the Red Lantern Sect had visited
We've just sent someone to rescue you,
but you are back now
Sorry for worrying you
Time
Shit, it's started
Master Wong
Your Excellency
General Guan has instructed us
that if we see you
we should ask you to go
to Tun Chau Square at once
The Dragons and the Lions are fighting now
What?
The Lion King Competition is being held today?
Right, The Lion King Competition organized by
the 8 countries is being held today
Right, Master, it's today
Why are you so excited?
I thought you'd forgot
Think again!
Your Excellency,
please show me they way
Fine
Fei Hung
Aunt May
Brother-in-law,
let me go with you
If anything happened,
how could I explain it to your sister?
Club Foot, follow me
Yes Master!
Ah Fu
Why are you standing there?
Come on now!
So childish
Childish
Bastard! What a copy cat
Our nine golden dragons
must stay alert
Under the bait,
there are machine guns
Nine Dragons set out
They are blocking our way,
we've to find a way out
Dragons in the sky
Dragons in the sky...
The Yellow and the
Red Dragon are destroyed
There are many enemies,
you'd better be more careful
Got you!
Halt!
We are the competitors
The competition had started,
leave now
What did he say?
He said the competition has started
We are not allowed to go in
How come!
Master, let me talk to him
Consider it carefully Fei Hung
Fu, Club Foot, let's go
Forget about them,
let's rush in
Fine
Don't let them leave
They have gone that way
Don't let them get away
Ride on it's back
Be careful of it changing position
Catch the dragon head
Let me ride that horse
The dragon of the Blue Clan is in trouble
Take the wounded away
Yes Sir!
The great eagle is coming
White dragon, watch out!
Yellow dragon, be careful!
Sir, the red dragon is trapped
Close the gate, hurry up
Prepare to fire weapons,
close the gate now
Close the gate
Fei Hung, they are trying to close the gate
They won't!
Hurry up, they are chasing us
Don't be afraid, I am here
Club Foot, you have no horse,
you can't catch up with us
Open it, quick
Yes!
Let's see who's faster
Damn you Clubfoot, how dare you
step on my shoulders?
They are shooting...
Get down!
Fei Hung, we've made it
Watch out, it's coming
Just our dragon is left
His Excellency is in the middle
It's oil, let's escape
Hurry up
Sir
- Fei Hung
- Sir
Wong Fei Hung
You must take revenge... for me
Your Excellency...
We were too late
What a pity
Your Excellency...
Your Excellency!
The officers from Tai Lei Temple
send their condolences
The Officers from Shun Tin Office
Sirs, thank you for your condolences
His Excellency Li Hung Chang
sends his condolences
His Excellency send his condolences
Wong Fei Hung sends his condolences
A blood letter from Wong Fei Hung
I am the Lion King of Ching Dynasty
I was too late to participate
in the competition last time
Now I am challenging
the lion kings of the 8 countries
If you accept the challenge,
I'll meet you in two days time
in the same square
Let destiny determine who will win or lose
Wong Fei Hung
Does Wong Fei Hung want to take
revenge for Guan Shing-tao?
Fine, tell him that I will give him a chance...
To meet an even worse fate!
Brother Fu, how do I look?
Fine, just look at Clubfoot
so lady like
To be honest, I don't think so
But I am afraid we'll be discovered by others
Don't worry!
If we are discovered,
I'll handle it. Let's go
Sister Fu, what does your lady look like?
She is like me, so lovely
We're so well matched!
Sister Yan, don't run off
It doesn't matter,
we will go for our own targets later
What for?
To look for our own ladies
That's big trouble
This seems to be the road
leading to the rented territory
Who cares if it is or not?
Let's concentrate on the ladies!
Let's go
Master Chiu, why are you looking for me?
I have heard that you are going to challenge
the lions of the 8 countries
Our ancestors have left us something
to combat the "Powerful Fists"
I asked the smith to repair it overnight
I don't know whether it's useful to you or not
The copper lion
Yes
It's made from 90 catties of copper
Look at the craftsmanship in this lion head
It is a work of art
But our students can hardly handle it
If it is useful to you in the competition,
Please take this as a present from our school
Master Chiu
Please rise
Fei Hung, this lion head is much heavier
than normal lion heads
It's not easy to handle
Yes, but there are merits too
The lions of the 8 countries
are strong and powerful
It's useless to rely on our Kung fu against them
We should destroy them by tactics
I agree with you
I would like to accompany you Master Wong
Master Chiu
Father...
Father
The Red Lanterns are here
Red Lanterns?
Listen, keep calm, keep calm
It is not safe here, we'd better leave
Where are you going?
You devils!
Sister, let's chase the devils separately
The rest of you...
Burn the church. Go
Go, chase after the devils
Yes!
It's on fire
What? On fire?
Where is on fire?
It should be the East Alley
The church of Father Thomas is over there
I have to take a look
Fu
What's the matter?
The Red Lantern ladies are burning and killing,
what'll we do?
Don't disclose our identities
Leave at once
Freeze
I know you are men posing as women
So, you've seen through our disguise
Ladies, castrate them
We are in danger!
Let's run for our lives!
Where are you going?
Club Foot, let's go separately
So, whom should I go with?
Kill them right here
Wong Fei Hung?!
Go
Why don't you go now?
Go now
Oh... He asked us to go
This way is safe
This way
May, you'd better stop searching
for Fei Hung with us
Well, I will wait for you right here
Master Chiu, let's search for
Fei Hung separately
Fine
Go over there
Sister, the foreigners are over there
Let's attack them from both sides
OK, follow me
Yes!
Father Thomas, are you all right?
Heaven have mercy
My child, the Red Lanterns are after us,
run for your life!
Go that way
It's you?!
Yes, it's me
What bad luck!
Father, you are here!
It's you
Go over there.
Let me fight with them
Go!
Yes, Senior
Ladies, no massacre please,
they're innocent!
If you want to kill, kill me first
Get lost,
you have no say here
Catch them and kill them right here
Yes
Let's run for our lives
I'll kill the woman,
you take the foreigners!
Sister, stop!
Father
You!
Kill the devils!
Sister
He saved me once
You liar!
You are the betrayer!
When Wong Fei Hung came to our hall,
I started to suspect you
Now, I'm proved right!
You are not qualified to hold
this Anti-foreigner's Flag
Shoot!
Senior!
She deserved it,
God will punish her
Miss
Let's go
Get lost, forget about me
Don't leave me alone!
I didn't betray you
Die bitch!
Let's see your magic now!
Miss
Stop!
Help!
Fei Hung?!
Take her away
Prepare to fire!
You are hurt, why do you still want to fight?
Don't go!
Move her over there
She's been hurt.
She must be cold
Use this to cover her
It's dark! I can't see anything
What a fate!
Where is Wong Fei Hung?
Fei Hung...
Where is he?
He is here
You're not him!
I'd never have believed
I'd die saving the devils!
It's my punishment!
I may die in peace now
Wong Fei Hung, at last, you've come
Brother Fu, let's go
Brother Fu, the Holy Mother is coming
Brother Club Foot,
come and save us!
Go to hell
Stay where you are!
I want to punish you
Club Foot, are you all right?
I'm fine
Take aim!
The symbol of heresy!
Should we save her?
How?
We are wearing the uniforms
If we go out like this,
we will be shot at
I'm Goddess Lotus,
the spirit resides in me
I'm invincible!
How dare you offend me!
I've to punish you on behalf of God
I'll send you to hell!
To tear your skin off!
To break your bones!
You bastards!
Let's go
Master
The three of you, stay where you are
Club Foot? Ah Fu? Ah Yan?
Why are you dressed like this?
Are you going to be opera actors?
You had it coming!
Holy Mother...
Don't cry, tears can't help
Right, Holy Mother hasn't passed away,
she is living in our hearts
Let's take an oath, we should
carry on the mission
of killing the foreigners!
Kill the foreigners,
save our beloved country!
This bait could hurt us anytime
If the opposite side use fire.
Getting the bait is less important
than beating their lions
Let's attack them remember
Yes, Master
Music!
The lions roar!
Each lion attack a monster
Yes!
"One step to the sky"!
Stop turning!
We can't turn
"Magic Turn"!
I want you to "turn round and round"
Old Master Wong,
I can't identify the flag in the front
It's so messy,
I can't identify either
Forget the flags,
let's recognise their face
Should we beat this one?
No, not this...
Club Foot, hold this for me
I feel better having no lion head
But, how am I going to handle
two lion heads?
You are abnormal anyway
They may be scared of you
holding two lion heads!
That's it
It's our turn!
All right!
"Swinging lion tail"!
Come on...
Fu, what are you doing?
You should be careful!
"Tiger jump"!
Come on...
Why has it gone dark?
Where am I?
Who are you?
Big head Buddha,
don't you recognise me?
Let me show you
Some more!
You want to fire?
Not that easy!
Here comes a cookie!
This one is even better,
I'll leave it with you
Let's help old Master
Attack!
Master Chiu, watch out!
Catch the lion tail
So you are scared away?
Brother Fu, look out behind!
How dare you scare me?!
The sun will soon go down
behind The Forbidden City
History will be re-written
We'll see who is going to be the winner
Throw the burning lion heads up here
Yes!
The bait?!
Ah Yan
Ah Yan!
Take cover!
My ass is shot! Take me out!
Go!
Club Foot, come over here, be quick!
Master, let me send you up there
General, leave here quickly
We won
General Henlintak
Good news
Long live Germany!
Long live America!
What has happened?
Why are they so cheerful?
Bull shit, they are celebrating for us
It's bull shit indeed!
Let's go and take a look
I can't see them, move forward
Move forward
Yes
Fei Hung
Sir, why are you dressed like that?
The allied troops of the 8 foreign countries have
marched into the Forbidden City
The Empress Dowager has surrendered
Master Wong, let's go
Let's go!
Although we won this competition,
we lost our country!
Henlintak
General, go to the celebration now,
let us handle Wong Fei Hung
Wait for me
Fei Hong
Henlintak!
Get lost, don't block my way
Wong Fei Hung
I am here
Hurry up
Don't go. Protect the General
What's happening?
Henlintak, get down!
Lui, protect the general
Henlintak!
Wong Fei Hung!
Master!
Let me handle this
Go down
Club Foot!
Try my kick!
Watch out!
General
Do you wanna escape
Do you want to cuff me?
Watch my kick
Club Foot,
I'm going to kill you
Not that easy
Try my "Scissors kick"!
Henlintak!
Strike!
You had it coming!
Lui
Master
Club Foot, let me handle it!
Master, let me handle it!
Strike!
Eat dirt!
I wanna break your leg!
Go and protect the general
Go
Wanna escape?
Club Foot they have guns!
Fire
Let's go!
Master,
shall we let them escape?
We can't change anything
by killing him
Let's go
Master!
Master
Are you seriously hurt?
No!
Fei Hung
Brother
It's dangerous here, we'd better leave
Dad, let's go back to the South
Yes. Our capital is occupied.
We should go back and prepare to retaliate
OK, let's go back to the South, now
Get in
I can't sit down!
My ass hurts!
Lie down then
Subtitles adapted by Peacht
acfmovies.com