Order them to approach the plane
with caution.
Yes, sir.
Approach the plane with caution.
We´re ready, sir.
Move in.
Everybody get down, now!
This is Commander Chan speaking.
Report status immediately.
They´ll never... give in...
Commander Chan, you betrayed
my trust. You attacked us.
Listen Kiang. We shall never give in
to hijackers or terrorists´ demands.
I´ve also alerted Taiwan about the
situation, so you can´t land there.
In that case, Commander,
watch your sergeant die.
All right, Commander, send
the tanker to fuel the plane now.
Don´t you understand?
There´s nowhere else to go,
so what´s the point?
And that´s all your doing.
This is hopeless!
Give yourselves up!
It´s too late for that. So you´d
better give in to our demands.
If you don´t have the fuel ready
in five minutes,
we´ll start shooting hostages.
You heard him, Officer.
Send the tanker now.
Prepare for takeoff.
Commander, order your men to back
off, except for the fuel attendant.
I´ve just connected the fuel line.
Nobody seems to be watching.
Proceed with caution.
Red One, what was that noise?
I´m unloading the fuel.
I´m moving toward the rear entrance.
Hey! Get back!
All right, start the plane!
Go on, damn it!
Arthur!
Joe! Are you all right?
Talk to me, man! Joe!
Joe.
Retreat, Red One! Get out of there!
Red One, retreat! Do you hear me?
Damn it!
It´s the control system.
- Where is it?
- At the back.
According to the report,
you went after the hijacker against
Commander Chan´s direct order.
Why, Officer?
General, those hijackers
are a bunch of terrorists.
It is my duty
to combat terrorism.
And to follow orders.
Yes, sir.
Although you saved those hostages,
you have violated
the army´s code of discipline.
You put the whole team at risk.
Therefore, I´ve decided
to have you transferred
to the Chinese Embassy
in Lavernia... immediately.
Wish I was that baby´s dad. Yeah.
- Well, well, Andrew Kwok.
- Long time no see, Arthur Dong.
You´re late again, as usual.
I couldn´t disappoint you.
You´re hopeless, you know that?
I´m glad you´re here,
in spite of the circumstances.
This dump might be
bearable with you here.
What are you talking about?
Lavernia´s a great place!
Is that your luggage?
Interpol agents?
Come on!
Hey, you!
Hey, why are these cops
making us wait for so long?
That´s typical of the Lavernians.
Don´t be surprised
if they´re not very accommodating,
especially to us Asians.
Well, since this is their country,
we´ve got to stay out of trouble,
otherwise there´ll be problems.
If you do get in a fix,
say something like...
I couldn´t help it
or it was unavoidable. That´ll help.
Well? Say something.
Listen.
Mishima...
- Ever seen him?
- Look, it´s your guy.
Great, he´s all over the news,
the Ambassador will be furious.
Now we´re in deep trouble.
Uh-oh, they´re here.
- Mr Ambassador, Mr Secretary.
- Are you Officer Dong?
- I´m to blame, sir.
- Blame?
Yes, sir. I should be held
responsible, since he´s new here.
The fault is mine.
Listen, no-one is blaming you
for anything.
In fact, you´ve both been invited
to the President´s banquet tomorrow.
- Hear that? We´ll probably get...
- Remember...
look smart and be on your best
behaviour. Is that clear?
Yes, sir!
Officer Dong, welcome to Lavernia.
I would like to thank...
the Lavernian government,
my mother and father...
Andrew, are you all right?
What´s the matter?
We caught the guy,
but nobody gave us credit for it.
It´s not the medal, but...
Does this go on all night?
- I propose a toast.
- Cheers!
Wait! A toast to what?
To our protest.
Let them look down on us, that´s
their loss. We´re still the best!
You know something else?
I even told my girlfriend
I´d be getting a medal tonight!
So get yourself a fake medal!
Looks like you need some company.
I´m Lone Sung. I own this bar,
and I know that look when I see it.
You´re homesick, right?
It isn´t easy for us Chinese
to build a life in a new country.
So I opened this bar, where
we can all drink our sadness away.
Yes, sir...
Nobody here calls me sir,
it´s just Uncle Lone, OK?
You know, young man...
I´m Arthur Dong, call me Arthur.
- Dong, let´s do it!
- Sure!
Come on guys, watch the show.
That was great!
I never thought
you danced that well, Andrew!
- You guys are fantastic!
- Not bad at all!
Tammy?
Let´s get out of here!
- But my wife´s badly hurt!
- I´m going alone, then!
- Tammy!
- Arthur!
Let´s get out of here.
- And go where?
- Anywhere!
You can´t desert your country!
Oh, my God, she´s dead!
How could you let this happen?
- Arthur...
- Tammy, the boat´s leaving!
- Come with us.
- I´m sorry, I just can´t.
It´s strange
that after all these years,
we´d end up feeling
like we were total strangers.
I guess I´m just a little nervous
about seeing you again.
I didn´t know what to say... although
it´s really good to see you again.
I like being near you,
so I was glad to hear
you were transferred here.
Who told you?
Andrew told you, didn´t he?
One second...
You never wrote to me.
Would you have replied?
Is that why
you´re still angry with me?
It´s a lot deeper than that.
You left me just when I...
There was a revolt, remember?
I had no choice but to run away.
So you think running away
solves everything?
I was afraid I might die there.
I would´ve protected you!
I got scared.
I was really scared then, OK?
You didn´t trust me then,
that´s why you left.
You didn´t care about me.
And now suddenly you show up
and think everything´s the same.
So, you don´t trust me any more?
Trust? You want to talk about trust?
Not only did you leave me,
but our country, too.
The country
where you were born and raised.
You left without a word, and now
you´re asking me if I trust you?
Now you´re living somewhere
much colder than Beijing.
It won´t be so cold
now that you´re here.
I don´t know.
It´s not the same any more.
You kids just love your heroes.
That´s from watching so many movies.
You´ve always been my hero, Uncle
Lone, we can always rely on you.
Tammy needs a room.
We´ve been friends since we were
kids and I was wondering...
could you let her stay here?
That´s if it wouldn´t be a problem.
Sure, why not?
Have this liver. You look pale.
Thank you, Uncle.
- What about me?
- Forget it!
You´re strong as an ox -
you could take on all the blondes
in Lavernia.
I´m such a hunk!
There you go again!
Stop bragging about yourself.
How do you put up with this airhead?
- So where have you been?
- Croatia.
She left Beijing in 1989,
during the revolution.
And went
to an even messier war there.
At least now she´s all right.
It´s never easy to grow up alone.
What matters is that we stay whole.
I´ve something you might like.
I´ll show you.
- Recognise it?
- Duckweed.
Although they have no roots,
they still manage to survive.
- They´re lovely.
- Great.
I have an extra room upstairs,
and I´m going to let you stay,
if you take care of these.
I will, Uncle.
Look out! Get down!
No!
Ambassador.
Officer, the Defence Minister called
earlier. Mishima wants to see you.
For what?
I´ve no idea, but he said
it´s important you see him.
- Should I go, sir?
- That´s your decision.
In that case, since I´ve nothing
to be afraid of, I´ll go see him.
- Yes, miss?
- I´m looking for Officer Dong.
- Your name?
- Tammy Chan.
Please wait here.
Sorry, miss, but he isn´t here yet.
I´ll just wait here.
Sorry miss,
but this is an embassy compound.
You´ll have to wait outside.
OK, thanks.
Hey, there´s a lady
waiting outside for you.
Come on Arthur, let´s play again.
Ready? One, two, three!
Gosh, you won again!
That´s because
you let me win on purpose!
Will you always
be this nice to me?
My daddy is always nice to my mummy.
I never saw my parents.
That´s all right, you have lots
of friends at the training centre.
As soldiers,
we´ll protect our country.
Are you going to protect me too,
Arthur?
Of course I will.
Chong said something about swords:
"There are three kinds of swords -
for commoners, nobles and kings."
You think I´m nothing
but a heartless killer.
Well, you´re wrong,
for I bear the King´s sword,
and I was sent by God to cleanse
this world of sin and corruption.
A true king´s sword
is never used to hurt or kill,
and a true king should rule
with kindness and love.
Confucius´ teachings
have made you softhearted, Officer.
Let´s just say
my conscience doesn´t bother me.
You think I enjoy what I do?
That I don´t suffer
every time someone dies?
Well, you´re wrong.
You can´t imagine the pain I feel
whenever I kill others.
But I was chosen to bear the cross
of the sins of the world.
That is my destiny.
Take Hitler. He was also
lonely and misunderstood.
Every great hero goes through this.
I suggest you see a psychiatrist.
You´re no hero.
You´re just an insane egomaniac.
I can sense your disillusionment.
Join me and we can serve
our divine purpose together.
Is that why you wanted to see me?
I´m sorry, you got it wrong,
I´m not interested.
Officer Dong.
What I´m offering may be your last
chance of walking into the light.
I´ve always been living
in the light.
Good morning, Arthur.
Here, I made you a coffee.
- You´re nice today.
- I´m always nice.
- How is it?
- Tastes great.
Yeah, it´s from Croatia.
- Tammy bought it.
- Meaning?
Are you still angry with her?
The Ambassador
will be late for his meeting.
Wait! What about your coffee?
What? Arthur, wait!
Hey, Arthur, I hear
your girlfriend was here yesterday.
Tammy Chan, right?
Andrew told us everything.
Right, Andrew?
Arthur, listen.
Our country´s revolution started
because of a misunderstanding
between our government
and our own people.
Yet you stayed in China
and gave her a chance.
Why don´t you give
the same chance to Miss Chan?
Thank you, Secretary Wong.
- Good morning, Ambassador.
- Good morning. Let´s go.
Cover the Ambassador!
Secretary Wong!
I´ll take care of him!
Over here, hurry!
The Holy War has just begun!
Hail to the new Messiah!
And that one.
You´d better go inside.
Wait! Tammy, where are you going?
I need to see Arthur.
What? You´re staying right here.
But I...
Come here. You´ll be attacked
by the Lavernians!
They can´t tell Chinese and Japanese
apart. That´s why I´ve closed up.
Don´t worry, I´ve seen
worse things, I´ll be fine.
I´ll be back later! Bye!
Don´t hurt me, please!
I´m not Japanese, I´m Chinese!
Listen to me, I´m Chinese!
I´m innocent! Please don´t hurt me!
Don´t! Please, don´t!
Let me go! Please, I´m innocent!
I´ve been looking for you all day.
It´s all right, I´m here now.
Sir?
Do it for the boat people.
I don´t feel good about this.
What if something goes wrong?
Well, we have to do the right thing.
Gentlemen, the Holy War to save
our master is about to begin.
Hey, has it occurred to you
that they might just have
surrendered Mishima´s double to us?
Can someone say something?
The silence is driving me nuts.
I wasn´t talking to you, so shut up!
You crazy bastard!
Cool it, OK?
Well, it´s the truth, he is crazy.
If you´re getting nervous,
spit it out.
Sure!
Andrew, cut it out!
Go ahead - feel sorry
for a guy who kills for fun!
Oh, shit!
I don´t feel good about this, guys.
Stay calm.
It´s all right. Just drive slowly.
Everything´s going to be all right.
- My God!
- Reverse!
Are they rescuing
or killing the bastard?!
Move it!
- We´re dead!
- No!
Straight ahead! Gimme that!
Chaaaarge!
I haven´t had
so much fun in ages!
- Enough! We have to get going!
- Yes, sir!
- It´s an ambush!
- Get him.
Take cover!
Move!
Enemy at 12 o´clock!
Forward!
There´s too many of them!
Get back!
Listen to me! I am your messiah,
I´ve come to usher in a new era.
Hail to Mishima! Hail to
the Messiah, master of the new era!
- Hail to the new era!
- Hail, hail!
Hang on, my children!
For I will take away
the sins of the world.
Move it!
Come with me!
We can still save this world!
Let us die together! Father,
we are coming! Our time is coming!
Tony!
Arthur!
Andrew!
- Andrew, no!
- He´s already dead!
Andrew!
Sato, come in, please.
Sato, are you there?
Please, respond!
He´s dead, you motherfucker!
And so are all your men!
Recognise my voice, Arthur?
This is Uncle Lone speaking.
I´m the commander
of Red Sun in Europe.
Right now, we´re inside
the Chinese Embassy.
We´ve taken your ambassador hostage.
Bring our master here
within two hours
or we´ll start executing
every hostage here!
Talk to him, Tammy!
Arthur, don´t listen to him,
it´s a trap!
Goddamit!
Thank you, dear. You just gave him
another reason to come over here.
You poor girl. You always get
yourself into the wrong places.
And now you must pay
for my kindness.
Master.
Let him go, Arthur.
Release all the hostages first.
You´re in no position to bargain.
I´m ready for the worst.
We´re ready to die for our master.
Long live the Messiah!
You are brave. Tammy looks at you
as some kind of hero.
You´re tough enough to come here
alone to save all these hostages.
You know that their lives
depend entirely on you.
Tammy, you were right about him.
Arthur!
Why don´t you join us?
It´s pointless to serve
their worthless cause.
We can turn this into a new world -
a better world.
I´ve no interest in serving your
cause. You´re a bunch of madmen.
Be careful of what you say.
Arthur!
Let him go or I´ll shoot!
- Shoot me instead.
- Sit down.
I represent the Chinese people,
and she´s Chinese.
If you intend to shoot her,
you must shoot me first.
This for someone
who deserted China!
Did you know that?
She´s still Chinese.
Tasta! Just get it over with!
Uncle Lone, don´t listen to him.
I still believe you´re on our side.
I´ll count to three,
and you´ll let him go.
One... two... three!
Let him go, Arthur.
Go on, shoot.
He´s not afraid to die.
Arthur. Arthur!
One...
- Arthur!
- Two...
All right!
I´m free!
Long live the new Messiah! Hail!
Hail! Hail! Hail!
- Tasta.
- Yes, sir.
Well done.
Since I am the new Messiah,
it´s my duty to send the unworthy
to their deaths.
I already gave you a chance,
but you refused to be saved.
Now it´s time to say goodbye to this
world and those you tried to save.
Arthur!
Hang in there, buddy!
Someone get me out of this thing.
Let him go,
I said let him go, you bastard!
Let him go!
Tammy, it´s all right!
Look, it´s me!
I´m here! It´s all right!
- Let´s get out of here.
- I have to stay. Join the others.
It´s the police.
Please don´t. Don´t shoot us!
Don´t... don´t...
Great, help´s here!
Hey, over here, guys!
We got rid of the terrorists!
Come on!
Come on down, it´s all right!
Get down!
What´s going on?
They won´t let us
leave the compound.
- Where´s Arthur?
- He´s still inside.
No, Miss Chan, come back here!
Tammy! Tammy!
Arthur?
Arthur!
Tammy!
Arthur... Tammy.
Look, Tammy,
I've got your hero's trousers again!
Come on, Arthur!
Catch me if you can.
- You can´t catch me!
- Give it back, Andrew.
Hey, wait for me.
Arthur, don't leave me!