- Be careful, brother.
- I will.
It's here so much of the time,
it'll come back by itself.
It's only on loan -
we will win it back.
Why aren't you working?
- I am working!
- Get to it!
(Referring to the custom of lion
blessing audience with the greens.)
Not great, won't eat.
Great, great, will eat!
- Is it prepared?
- Yes.
- Have the costumes arrived?
- They're coming later.
Master, Mrs. Hoi has arrived!
Of course I'm here on time!
Mrs. Hoi!
Thank you very much!
These are the costumes -
hurry up if you want to look good.
Don't get them mixed up.
Each is responsible for his own.
You as well.
- Brother!
- I'm coming!
Yours is here, Keung!
Brother!
- Are you all right?
- My leg hurts.
Who put the bucket here?
- It was Orphan Boy!
- Me?
- Help me up!
- Get him up.
You sit down!
If it's not this, it's that.
You were to be the lion's head.
Without Keung as the lion's head,
we'll lose.
Can't anyone else do it? I can.
- I'm better than you.
- Shut up.
Someone else will have to be
the lion's head.
- Brother...
- I'm not up to it.
Of course you're not.
Lung, you'll do it.
- Orphan Boy is no good.
- If he can't, I will.
- I'd do it!
- You?
Quiet!
Ready the lion!
Fellow villagers, last year was
peaceful and the weather was good.
And not breaking with tradition,
this year we will again have
the Greens of Peace.
Ching-fung and Wai-yee
martial arts schools will compete,
to see which of them will bring us
another year of peace.
- Wow, it's big!
- What kind of greens are they?
- A green face.
- What?
My face will turn green
if I have to do it.
This isn't a joke.
Wow. That's good.
This is great.
He's good.
The lion has great energy.
That's not Wai-yee style.
Lung, you're the head,
Chan, you take the tail.
Everyone get ready.
Get in your positions.
Official Bookmaker
- Which one?
- Black.
- Are you sure?
- Of course.
- What are the odds?
- Black is 20-1,
- For gold, $1 pays 5 cents.
- Just 5 cents?
The golden lion is going to win and
if everyone backs it, I'll be broke.
- Betting slips costs money.
- I'm backing the black lion.
Queue up there.
What, black?
No need to queue then.
It's brilliant!
Come on! Jump across.
- Brave enough to jump?
- Yes.
Let's see how they do it.
Go up!
Don't let them get up!
Good. Well done!
Push!
The belt, Chan.
- Is it on, Chan?
- It's on.
I'm going down.
- Big Brother!
- Don't talk. Take it if you can.
Big Brother, you...
Bring me up.
Don't let go!
Why are you doing this, Big Brother?
Right now, I'm not your brother!
Get it if you can.
You're making it hard for me.
Hang on. Don't fall off!
- Hold him!
- Quiet. Get the greens.
Go on!
Useless! He's rubbish.
Bravo, well done!
We won! We won!
Brother Bill danced our lion
magnificently.
Stop talking and get the prize.
Clear up and go.
Aren't you down yet?
I've won my bet.
You're useless.
You lost me my money.
I'm the black lion,
you be the golden one.
Come on.
You count it. It's all there.
It gets easier after the first time.
- You'll have to help us out again.
- But they'll find out.
So what? Join us
and we'll make you an instructor.
Think about it.
I'll think about it.
Who won, Master?
M-M-Mas..
So we lost. Why the long faces?
Go and practise!
Ah-Lung!
You couldn't hold onto
the lion's head.
Lift the table one hundred times
to strengthen your arms.
Watch the water,
you're getting it everywhere.
- Over here.
- Wipe mine down, would you?
Wipe yours?
Who's going to wipe mine?
Don't be so lazy.
- Wipe it yourself!
- Be quick.
Watch out - you're splashing me.
What! That again?
Do as you are told to.
- Hey.
- Over there.
I know, into that room.
It's not my first time.
Not so loud.
Master has just fallen asleep.
If you don't want people to know,
you shouldn't go looking for whores.
Here I am, naughty one.
- Big Brother
- What?
- Her again?
- Get out.
- Don't be long.
- I know. Go away.
Come and play with me.
Get up, fat pig.
The Master's coming.
Master.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing. It's cooler in here.
- Cooler in here?
- Yes.
- Do you want to suffocate me?
- Of course not.
You're copping a feel!
Master, I won't do it again.
This is again!
- Get off me!
- Get out!
This is a martial arts school,
not a brothel. Get out!
I'm going. There's nothing
to stay here for anyway.
Haven't you ever seen a woman before?
Give me your belt.
Wai-yee School?
Why are they giving you money?
- Explain.
- I...
Tell me! What have you done?
Tell me!
Give it to me! Give it to me!
Keung?
Keung!
Why is Wai-yee School giving you
money? What have you done?
Didn't he tell you that
I did their lion dance?
I've said nothing! Big Brother, he..
You get out!
- Big Brother!
- Get out!
Get out!
Master!
You still call me Master?
You'd bite the hand that feeds you?
You betrayed us.
Do you remember when you and Lung
were children and parentless?
Fighting stray dogs for food.
Dirty and muddy all over.
Who brought you back here?
For the last ten years, I have raised
both of you like my own sons,
giving you a good education,
and have I asked for a penny?
You lion-danced
for someone else for money!
Why did you do that?
Ah-lung isn't good enough.
This school was counting on you.
Did you want
to give me a heart attack?
- I knew he'd betray us.
- He'll be the death of the Master.
Tell me!
Leave!
Don't say any more. You treat me well
and I've wronged you.
I am leaving!
- Big Brother...
- Don't obstruct me!
Master.
Big Brother! Don't!
If you leave now,
don't ever come back!
Big Brother!
I heard the boss will be up
for sentencing in two days.
If we don't do it now,
we may not get another chance.
It isn't that easy!
Just the two of you. It'll be risky.
Two of us is enough.
The police only care about their pay.
They can't be bothered to train.
They can't beat us.
But Master Kim is in their hands?
He was drunk when he was caught.
Otherwise, even with ten more,
they couldn't take him!
Even so, we should plan
before we act.
You're up early, Uncle.
Have you had breakfast?
Breakfast? Not yet.
- Shall we go together?
- OK.
You? Come to learn Kung fu?
I'm here to see Uncle.
You want to see him?
He wants to see you, Uncle.
Why are you here?
I've paid you for the lion dance.
You want payment for next year too?
No. You said I could be
an instructor here.
That was yesterday.
Now, I've got two more brothers.
If your school lacks teachers,
please hire my brother.
- You tricked me!
- Good morning, Uncle.
Look at you. You haven't
done your button yet.
Why is he here, Uncle?
He wants us to take him in.
But we can't feed him!
I really didn't know that it was you
who lion-danced for us.
I do feel a bit guilty
but if we take you in,
your Master may get the wrong idea.
He's kicked you out because of this.
What if I tried to talk to him
and asked him to take you back?
No need. I'm sure I'll find someone
who will take me.
Stop right there.
What do you want?
I've got a way for you
to make some money.
You just have to be brave enough.
What choice do I have now?
Tell me.
There's no seats inside, Master.
Please wait here.
- Make way!
- Hi, Chung.
You're early, Master Kim!
Waiting for a place?
Your place is reserved,
Brother Bill.
Wait patiently then!
Morning, Uncle.
There's a place over there, Sam.
Good morning, Master Kim.
Having breakfast with your students?
Sorry.
- The bill, waiter.
- Coming.
- A place.
- Are you going? Three and six.
Thank you.
Yesterday your lion dance
was excellent, Brother Bill!
I am Big Cannon Bill. Watching
my lion dance is always a thrill.
Only because my Big Brother
helped you.
You can't even feed your students.
Anyone with sense would leave.
Look at us. We always have so much
to eat. Nobody will ever leave.
Let Big Cannon Bill give you
a roast pork bun.
Look at him!
He must have been starved!
- That took guts.
- Hit him.
Stab. Stab. Stab.
Stab this.
How do you like my punches?
Don't mess around any more, Brother
Bill. Look! The Master is angry.
He's still a Master.
We're going!
You haven't settled
your bill yet, Master.
- We haven't even ordered.
- Service is double with no order.
Thank you so much, Master!
Master!
You finished breakfast so quickly?
- What happened?
- It's all his fault!
I got beaten up because
he lost the lion dance to them.
Who's that?
Your useless Kung fu is
no good to anyone!
Your useless Kung fu
is no good to anyone!
We'll show him our Kung fu!
Leave me out of it.
- Why don't you do it now?
- We'll show him!
Come back!
Haven't we been shamed enough?
Home now!
Didn't you hear
what the Master said? Move!
Let's go, brothers.
Your Kung fu training isn't complete
and you want to cause trouble?
You've ruined my reputation.
They started it!
- If our Big Brother was here then...
- Silence!
All I hear is Big Brother,
Big Brother!
Was it just him I taught Kung fu
and not the rest of you?
What was that rubbish you were doing?
Show it to me again!
Go on!
Now!
Punch... Leopard...
Leopard? What else?
- Hang...
- Hang? Hang?
Is that what I taught you?
What else!
Continue!
Stab... stab... stab.
Stab? When did I teach you
to stab like that? What else?
- Horse...
- Horse? Haven't you learnt anything?
Everything you have learnt is
useless. It's all useless.
Get up. Get up now.
What did I do in a previous life
to deserve being your Master now?
Not one of you is good!
If you're not wasters,
you're traitors!
He lion-danced for someone else
for money,
using the Kung fu that I taught him
and bringing me shame,
completely ruining the reputation
of our Ching-fung School.
Even at breakfast, we were insulted.
What else have you done
to shame me?
Stop crying!
You!
Have you practised your Kung fu?
Fat as a pig!
And you! You're the youngest
and the naughtiest!
I haven't hit you and you're crying!
- Master.
- Is this how you do up a belt?
Did I teach you
to tie it up like this? Tell me!
You make me so angry!
Why are you still crying? Shut up!
Master! You can't blame us, Master!
It's the fault of those orphans.
They betrayed us! It's not our fault!
Silence!
Talk back at me?
How dare you talk back at me!
I haven't even punished you.
That's enough!
Because of that prize
you banished our Big Brother.
Now, you take your anger out on us.
What are we to you?
It's true that Big Brother and I
are orphans.
We've lived off you
and not paid you a penny.
And so useless!
If you need to hit someone, hit me!
I've got thicker skin!
I know you hate me the most, Master.
You're not even bothering to beat me!
If you don't punish me now,
you will not get the chance again.
I know that if you didn't take us in,
Big Brother and I would have starved
to death a long time ago.
I wouldn't be alive to shame you,
Big Brother wouldn't have lion-danced
for someone else!
And no one would have looked down
on us and called us orphans.
Now I understand
why Big Brother had to leave.
How can a man live in a place
where he is not respected?
Master, Big Brother left
in too much haste.
He didn't have time to tell you,
so I'll speak for him.
Thank you for teaching and caring
for us for all these years.
- I am leaving now.
- Where are you going?
If Big Brother hasn't starved
to death, I will go to him.
Stand there!
Then go and find him.
Bring Big Brother back home.
When did our Wai-yee School
turn into a refugee shelter?
So many refugees have come here!
Don't be like that! We're all human -
we all eat the same food.
Wai-yee School eats well. You lot
are just on three meals a day.
How can we eat the same food?
You are just a mouse.
- Brother Bill...
- Don't bother!
- I only want..
- Save your breath!
I've waited too long
for those bastards to go.
It's my time for glory. Don't stand
in the way of me getting rich.
- But...
- Leave.
Leave Orphan Boy.
You don't have to wound me
with words.
Wound you with words?
If you don't go
I'll wound you with my fists.
- Brother Bill! Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
For a big guy,
you don't stand firm.
Where were you when your teacher
told you to practise?
Call the proprietor.
- You sure you aren't hurt?
- I'm fine.
Say someone is causing trouble.
Why don't you have a lie-down?
You're so fat you can't spring up.
Stop fighting. Don't hit him.
You were lucky.
Enough, brother, no more fighting!
It's him who was hitting me
from the start. You tell him.
- Why did you come here?
- I came to see if my brother's here.
He came and he even asked me
to take him in, but I didn't.
And I thought
you came to steal my job.
Everyone, I'm sorry for the trouble.
I'm sorry Brother Bill.
It's over now, we can go back in.
They're coming.
Halt!
Get ready!
I want him.
Attack!
Boss.
How are you, Boss?
- Who is he?
- He's one of us.
- Boss?
- Let's go.
Quick - report that
we have been attacked.
- What if they ask who by?
- Tell them it was White Fan.
Thank you.
Have a look.
Have you seen a man
carrying a fan like this?
If he had any money,
I might have noticed him.
You're just a nuisance, so piss off.
Go!
Take a look.
Get out of here!
Please take a look.
Isn't that the White Fan?
- It doesn't look like him.
- Look closely.
- He looks similar.
- No, he doesn't.
The police sketch artists never
get it right. We could get a reward.
Go and get some back up
and I'll follow him. Hurry.
He's inside. Follow me.
- He's not here!
- Yeah!
He was here praying -
where has he gone?
Holy Bhudda...
Are you looking for me?
Five police officers.
What seems to be the problem?
White Fan, you've been caught
and you're still lippy.
You're coming with me.
Hang on, Officer, are you sure
you've got the right guy?
My eyes are never wrong.
I suppose the transport was attacked
by your Big Brother!
Arrest him.
Attack! Give me your sword.
- Are you hurt?
- No. Give me a sword.
Thank you.
How dare you slash at the God of War!
- We apologise.
- We don't believe in the spirits.
Get him.
You don't believe in the spirits?
I'll send you to meet them.
Are you frightened?
It's just cut your belt.
Oh, yes. I didn't believe before,
but now I do.
If you believe, go and pray.
- Give me the sword.
- You're still attacking?
Are you scared of the cross?
Are you OK, Sergeant?
The Sergeant is fine. Attack!
Are you going, Sergeant?
- Give me a sword.
- You've had all of them.
It's not going well.
You stay here and I'll get Sam Kung.
You go to the station
and I'll go to his house.
Sam Kung, open up!
Fourth Brother, is Sam Kung here?
Hey, Fourth Brother!
Answer him, will you?
You're not deaf.
What is the matter?
Me and my colleagues have arrested
the White Fan.
The White Fan?
Yes. So I've come for Sam Kung
so he can get a statement from him.
My father is already at
the police station.
What? Sam Kung is not here!
Oh, no.
Who's going to take the statement?
It's only a statement,
as you've arrested him,
take him back to the police station.
But he won't come with us.
- Let me help you out.
- How? The fight's over.
They don't need you to fight.
There'll be a sequel when I arrive.
Let's get going.
Wait until Dad finds out.
If you don't tell him,
he won't find out.
- He's over there, Fourth Brother.
- Get over there.
He doesn't like me.
You go over there.
Sorry.
What's the problem?
You go first then.
What are you trying to do?
Why are you picking on me?
I don't know even know who you are.
Give me back my bag.
Trying to rob me?
You can't rob me that easily.
Who are you?
I can't be bothered with this.
I didn't realise you stance was
so solid, Fourth Brother.
With your good stance
and my good eyes,
the 200 big ones will be ours.
- Where is he?
- I saw him go that way.
Why didn't you say?
Can I get a cup of tea, Uncle?
- Please, don't hesitate.
- Thank you.
- Sit.
You're drenched in sweat.
I've had a very bad day.
Some bloke just crept up and
attacked me without saying a word!
And there's a corrupt policeman
who's trying to stitch me up.
Luckily, I got away
or I wouldn't be sitting here.
Your pipe is so unusual.
Can I have a look at it?
By all means - take a look.
Look at it closely, otherwise
you won't get the chance again.
- From the Emperor!
- It's not any old tat!
It's an antique.
That is such a big fan.
Can I have a look?
You definitely know your stuff.
- It has Ming inscriptions on it.
- Gold lettering on a white fan.
- It's beautiful.
- No mistake.
There are so many glorious
stories about this fan.
- But you wouldn't want to know.
- Have a drink of tea first.
Uncle, you are a good man.
Do you live here?
No. I'm just waiting for someone.
- This person is notorious.
- How so?
He attacked a transport
and took away what it was carrying.
He doesn't care
that the police are looking for him.
He doesn't even acknowledge the
District Marshal when he meets him.
This person must be infamous.
Yes, but he is short-sighted.
Short-sighted?
Like he can't even see you?
It's like he's blind. He's here.
Here?
Where?
Can't you see him?
Is it him?
It was him I was talking about,
the dog! Has he bitten you too?
Not only bitten me, he feeds off
of me, pesters me and stalks me.
- What for?
- He's stalking an inheritance.
You are so cruel.
Bullying old people are you?
When I first saw you,
I knew you weren't a good person.
Now the police know about you.
Since you are so infamous,
what's your name?
Can't you talk?
Not a care in the world.
Some people are born arseholes
but his father must be
the biggest arsehole of all.
What are you laughing at?
Don't get angry.
Let me teach him a lesson.
You with the bench,
you're nothing but a mute dog.
I'm not going to let you off
this time.
That worthless boy is
quite good with that bench.
Watch it, boy!
To teach this boy a lesson...
you have to use this.
Thank you, Uncle.
Give up.
See, Uncle? He might be good with
the bench but this is my speciality.
Of course, without this
you couldn't control him.
You can't move now, can you?
Uncle, this slap is from you.
And this slap is from me.
And this slap is from
your dead father.
And this...
Uncle, he's staring at you.
- You stand there a moment.
- OK. You hit him.
You were told to behave
but you thought it was a joke.
Sister Sue was looking after you
but you didn't practise your Kung fu.
You just wanted to show off
with your bench work.
And now you've been beaten
to the bone.
You know all about his faults.
- He is my little runt.
- Little runt?
- Little Brat.
- Little Brat?
He is my son.
So you must be his father.
Damn you!
I still won.
Get up!
So it's father and son together then.
You're quite talkative
for an old git.
You deserve what's coming to you.
I missed my lunch waiting for you.
Hold on!
Lunch! Why didn't you say?
It's simple. I haven't got much.
But here is a few coins, which should
be enough to buy you two a meal.
I'm buying your lunch and you hit me!
Kneel down.
We don't need your charity,
my father eats at the police station.
- So he's the Top Dog.
- Who else?
Why did you come out?
- Sister Sue asked me to buy food.
- Why haven't you gone then?
You have the right to remain silent.
But what ever you say
may be taken down as evidence.
You must have heard that a lot.
You have the fan.
So do old women
but you don't arrest them.
And your son
goes around with a bench.
- Don't mention him.
- If he was yours he'd listen to you.
He makes me so angry.
Not a sound. Not even a fart.
- You'd think he was a mute.
- So you two don't talk.
That's true.
It's not like the way we can chat.
Of course.
- Get moving!
- Can't I take a leak?
A leak? Over there.
How can I go with handcuffs on?
Drop your stuff and I'll uncuff you.
You are a good man, Uncle.
How can I go with you watching me?
If I don't watch you,
you'll run away.
Even if you do watch me,
I'll still run away.
I'm running away.
Why isn't he after me?
I'm really running away.
Run away to start a new day.
Run, run, run.
He's running
just where I want him to!
He's not following. What a relief.
What's going on? It's all sloppy!
That's what you call dropping
a criminal in the shit.
- Get me out!
- Don't breathe or you'll sink.
Get me out.
Every criminal who comes here
will fall in.
- Please, get me out.
- It's not even over your head.
I could help you out
but first you have to sing me a song.
If I like it,
I'll consider your plea.
OK, I'll sing.
A little birdy falls into the water,
into the water, into the water...
Why have you stopped?
If you don't grab the branch,
how can I rescue you?
Hold on tight.
Come on.
Steady.
- Climb up.
- I nearly drowned.
Over there!
Don't get the things dirty.
Get me out!
Quick, get me out!
You're a good man.
You could have run away.
Oh, yeah!
Thanks for reminding me. I'm off!
What if I sing you a song?
- Help me out!
- Sing then.
A little birdy
has fallen into water...
Stop, it's awful! I'll get you out.
Hurry up. Quick!
Hold on. Too bad if it breaks!
Anybody in? Anybody in?
Am I in luck?
Hey, young lady! Young lady.
Who are you?
I am me. Please open the door.
Success.
I smile and answer 'I am me'.
Hello, young lady.
- I'll wipe it off. I'm sorry.
- It's OK.
Not from round here?
No, this is from this round here.
No, you must not be from round here,
since you fell into the quicksand.
Yes. Look how dirty I am.
I just need a bucket of water.
I won't make a mess.
Can I borrow that, please?
- Here.
- Thanks.
Clever, eh?
Wait! Am I leading you to
the washroom or are you leading me?
That's better.
Not a single footprint.
It's all right for you!
You can walk from here.
- Thanks.
- There's the washroom.
Thanks. Thanks a lot.
It's unisex, is it?
You can't wear those dirty clothes.
I'll get you my little brother's.
Damn! I forgot to buy the groceries.
I'm going to the market,
will you be all right by yourself?
Off you go. I'll be fine.
I'll be fine. I'll be fine.
Only dirt and grime.
The District Marshal is a swine.
When I find that bastard,
I'll cut him to pieces!
No more talking.
Good job the kids aren't home.
That little brat is back so soon?
Little brother?
What a mess!
Are you OK?
I was only playing with you.
- It's not breathing.
- You've killed the fish, you brat!
- It's you.
- How come?
You won't escape this time.
You are something. You and I are only
borrowing someone's place to use.
You made all this mess
and I even swept up after you.
So what?
I told myself that if! met you
again, I wouldn't speak to you.
Suits me. The less said the better.
It's not your fault.
It's come back to life.
I'll cut you to pieces!
Hey! Stop being so unreasonable.
I'll kill you
and then report you missing.
You think I'm your son.
So it's the Emperor's.
Chop it.
It may be the Emperor's,
but why is it sword-resistant?
The Emperor fights the Hun,
the Emperor will make you run!
His head didn't break it.
How about this pole?
It still hasn't broken.
Still not broken.
- Put down the pipe.
- Put down the sword.
You first.
OK. I'll put down the sword.
That's more like it.
I'm just putting it away.
Die!
It wasn't me. He broke the furniture!
It's him. It's him.
Hit him.
Father.
He's your father?
You old stud!
You've got children everywhere!
That's enough.
Damn it! This can't be happening!
I'm just letting you win.
Game over.
OK. Rest here.
It's a dead end and there's no cover.
What's so good about it?
- Precisely, it's a dead end.
- I'm desperate, Sam Kung.
Typical. He needs a piss again.
Really? You're just looking for
a chance to escape again.
No, I really want to have a piss
this time.
Uncuff him.
Thank you.
Thank you, brother.
I can't go with you watching me.
Hey! What are you doing?
I always piss like this.
Good arm strength.
Practising your Kung fu?
I'm finding out
how wide the alley is.
Well, now you know, so get down.
Eat.
Your dad talks about you as if you
were worthless. I feel sorry for you.
The way you cuff me, you must be
expecting me to run away at any time.
When you do run away, ring the bell -
make my job easier.
The sun climbs to the mountain top,
the river runs to the sea.
If you want to see a long way,
climb higher still.
There's nothing to see up here,
go back down.
He's like a ghost. He's so annoying.
District Marshall, I've been
looking for you everywhere.
Oh, it's you. What's the matter?
I've heard some rumours,
somebody is going to rob some...
the bank!
Pak and his gang are going
to rob the bank at about 11 o'clock!
- Pak Zi-sin?
- Yes.
11 o'clock?
- Don't mess me around!
- I've never messed you around!
- Sin says Pak's going to rob a bank.
- We've got the wrong man, then.
I told you! You made a mistake!
You're the suspect
until I get the criminal.
If you don't release me
I'll sue you both.
All right, just the old man.
I can detain you
for obstructing justice.
You're not being reasonable!
If you won't run, I won't cuff you.
- Give me the key.
- Just till I get back.
I'll wait for you.
Hold on. Why don't I run now?
Why isn't Pak here?
- Those two have gone. How about you?
- You want to quit?
I fear nothing.
So why don't you go now?
Shall we say 1 o'clock?
The earlier the better.
All right, I'll go.
With him out of the way,
we'll get a larger share.
We'll use the others
to get rid of him,
then get the stash
at Fok Fu-ling tomorrow.
Man Loong Bank
Let me out!
It's no use shouting.
- Let me split this up.
- He'll die.
Someone will take the blame.
Your fan is in there,
go and fetch it.
- What was that for?
- I am representing Master Kim.
You're too young
to be part of our gang.
You're a scapegoat.
That's right.
Take your fan, it's hot in prison.
- What are you looking at?
- What's so funny?
There's nothing to see.
I told you there'd be money.
You've tricked me!
Have it back!
Hit here!
I thought I was smart.
Oh, you've killed me, I'm dead.
He'll kill him at this rate.
Please don't, you'll kill me.
You old git!
Please don't, you'll crush me.
Do you want to kill a poor old man?
I'm finished.
Oh, I'm dying.
Please don't.
If your stall is destroyed,
I'll get all your business!
Still pretending?
Stop fighting.
I'll die.
Here's your whiskers.
I won't fall.
Thank you, thanks for watching.
I'm finished.
My fabrics!
You want more?
Take them, they're not mine.
How can you do this?
Let me hide here.
You bastard!
Serves you right!
So precise.
My skirt, you pervert!
Skirt?
I won't fall.
I'll bounce.
You want a fight?
Fight me properly then.
Let me down!
- We should've brought more help.
- Too right.
Where are they?
They're behind me.
I'll break your legs.
They're his.
Fooled again.
I've warned you, and you still come.
Don't go.
- My fabric.
- I'll give it back.
Run! The police are coming.
Guard the bank!
Those inside, pay attention.
You are surrounded by the police.
Put down you weapons and surrender
before I count to three.
One, two, three!
I'm tied up, I can't move.
Calm down, Big Brother.
I know it's tough to walk like this,
I'll do the same.
I promised to take you back,
but how can I if you're on the run?
So you locked me up!
I'll take you to the police
and tell them not to come after you.
Rubbish! You're not haggling
at the market now.
What happened to sympathy?
Laws are laws. No deal.
What about plea bargaining?
He attacked a transport and did
unspeakable things. No sympathy.
What about when the police do
unspeakable things?
- Rubbish! It's a serious offence.
- But I brought him back.
- Rubbish!
- Rubbish? You can't see sense!
You cut someone and he heals,
does that mean you didn't cut him?
Fine. I have your pipe.
Put down my pipe!
I put it down,
it's like I never picked it up.
Dad, he did help you catch him.
What's wrong with that?
I could have caught him myself.
You didn't know where he was.
But I did.
- He's back now and we're off.
- Stop right there!
You're collaborating with a felon,
so you're under arrest.
Don't be unreasonable, Marshall.
I've said my bit, you figure it out.
I'll tap three times for a decision
so it's up to you.
One, two three.
OK. Fine.
Bring back Kim,
or visit Keung in prison.
Forty-sixty, fifty-fifty,
thirty-seventy!
Seventy for you and thirty for me.
Nothing for you.
Just a token amount
for all these years together?
Go on.
You really want a token?
All right. Have this.
I'm dead!
I've caught it.
You?
For what you two did to me
and my brother, you deserve to die.
So why did you catch it?
I didn't want to see anyone else
get hurt.
You're getting in the way, lad.
What are you doing here?
I've come to take you back
to the District Marshall.
The snake catcher's here, Kim.
Catch me?
What, you?
- What's so funny?
- It's funny if you think about it.
You can laugh.
Be careful, Kim is very dangerous.
Watch out for his Tiger Tail kick.
Trying that Kung fu on me, boy?
Not unless you want to die.
Oh, damn!
Although I don't know him,
I have to help this lad get that Kim.
Watch out.
Attack.
Get ready... Attack.
Don't rush in,
I haven't spoken to you yet.
His lower body Kung fu
is incredible.
Go for his upper body.
- Upper body?
- Go on.
Brilliant.
You're brilliant. In a few moves,
you've found his upper body
is just as good.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- You rushed off.
You're not the one who's fighting.
Can't you see his weakness?
He only uses his left leg.
You fight him, since you noticed it.
If I fight, how can I
be your fight co-ordinator?
Go on.
There's two of us fighting him.
Don't be afraid.
Come on, get up. Get up.
- Why aren't you hitting back?
- How can I?
Stop messing about.
Don't let go.
No matter what, don't let go.
I got him!
Well, carry on.
Watch out!
Win one, lose one.
That was a strong kick.
He's coming again. Get up. Get up.
Get up. Get up!
Get up... Hit him again!
I can't bear to watch.
Compose yourself. Concentrate.
Soon he'll be worn out.
Then it'll be your time for glory.
I'm exhausted.
Fresh air.
- Fresh air.
- Water, water.
Here's holy water. Drink up.
That's the end of round one.
What! That was just the first round?
Three more rounds and
the old bastard will be exhausted.
Oh shit, he's coming.
Get up. Get up.
Show him no mercy.
Hey, don't come over here.
You can't hit the referee,
it's against the rules.
Protect me.
Don't show that bastard any mercy.
No need to respect him. Go on. Go on.
Go on.
Fresh air. Fresh air.
- Fresh air.
- Water, water, water!
- You won this round.
- How?
I'm the referee.
He's coming. Attack!
Try and hit him again.
Lock his legs!
Don't let him rest.
- Drink some water.
- Water.
Here he comes.
He'll soften the blow.
I didn't know I was so light.
I admire you. I now appreciate what
youth really is.
You are indestructible.
Don't comfort me. I need water.
Water. I'll get it.
Here's some water.
I won't let you go thirsty.
Drink as much as you can.
Be a real man.
Drink up, it'll kill the germs.
Pipe water is still water.
Only bitter.
Fresh air.
You rotten bastard,
you kicked me up the arse!
Taking the gold and not the silver.
The gold price is going up.
What goes up quickly
comes down quickly.
Fantastic!
Stay right there.
You're brilliant, boy.
You're brilliant. You won!
We'll spilt the prize in half.
What are you doing?
You want the belt. Take it.
Master, Big Brother is home.
Come.
- Big Brother's home.
- Big Brother.
- Master.
- Get up. Get up.
- Where's Lung?
- There.
Come on!
Come on. Hurry up.
Give way. Peace.
End to violence. Tranquillity.
Hurry up, he's over there.
Master, I'm home.
How did this happen? Carry him back.
Kaifeng County once had
a governor called Bao
He was upright,
could tell good from evil
The heroes were all
willing to help him
He had Wangchao on his left,
and Mahan on his right