Come in, Weather Channel.
What‘s the forecast?
Fair skies, not a cloud in sight.
- Poolside?
- The same. Under control.
- How‘s the perimeter?
- All secure.
I like to come out
and do a few laps every day.
Keeps the health in good shape.
- It‘s very refreshing. Private, too.
- Yes, indeed.
Cumulus! 0n the double!
Maximum cloud cover!
Go!
Go! Go! Move!
Cover ‘em! Get ‘em out of here!
Get ‘em out! Let‘s go!
Open the door!
Let‘s go! Go, go!
Watch yourself!
- Move ‘em out!
- Come on! Move!
- Watch his back!
- Let‘s go!
- Here they are!
- Can we get a statement?
Move! Outta the way! Get down!
What‘s going on?
- Come on!
- Watch it!
- Friends of yours?
- No, not at all.
Sorry. Do I know you?
We‘re having a private conversation,
so if you don‘t mind.
Why are you just sitting there?
Quick! Get him into the car!
- No!
- Just do it.
- I‘m in charge.
- I don‘t think so.
Forget it!
Can anyone in this classroom
distinguish between
protectors and assassins?
Because I‘m having a hard time.
If this wasn‘t a simulation,
I‘d be handing in
my resignation about now.
to hold a gun to the head of the man
you are supposed to be protecting?
Are you bodyguards
or are you kidnappers?
You‘re supposed to be
using your heads.
Chang, how about letting the rest
of us in on what you were thinking?
Sir, one of the lessons
that you taught us was to,
under certain circumstances,
you must be prepared to die
to protect the life of the subject.
I realised I was prepared to die.
There‘s more to being a bodyguard
than being fast or prepared to die.
In the end, your decisiveness
saved your man‘s life.
But you didn‘t earn his trust
and that‘s something
you are going to have to learn.
Thank you, sir.
What about the objective?
Will I be going with the others?
I think we‘ll be able
to find a place for you.
But I have another assignment
for you, a short one, in Hong Kong.
Hong Kong? Doing what?
That is James Shong,
chairman of the Tai Fung group,
a corporation that brings in
millions in foreign money.
You are going to be protecting
that man‘s girlfriend.
0n the evening of May 27,
a man was strangled to death
at the Clear Water Bay Yacht Club.
The victim was Lu Kin-chue,
an elderly accountant.
The suspect is Chu Kwok-man,
the reputed boss of the Liang mob.
The police believe it is related to
a case which the CAC is working on
involving $100 million
in drugs and money laundering.
Michelle Yeung, a 24-year-old,
witnessed the murder while driving.
There were two additional witnesses:
a sailor, Chan Tai-keung, 28,
and a security guard,
Chu Tung-ming, age 51.
Two days later, Chan Tai-keung died
in an unexplained elevator accident.
0n the same evening, Chu Tung-ming
was blown up by an unknown bomber.
On June 1,
as Michelle Yeung prepared her bath,
she discovered it had been
rigged to electrocute her.
She escaped injury,
and is now the sole surviving
witness to the accountant‘s murder.
Please, be seated.
Miss Yeung, this is Sergeant Lau.
He‘s in charge of the investigation.
Not bad.
Ken, come over here.
- What?
- I‘ve gotta get a bet down.
Wait a minute. Trust me.
He‘s number two to win.
- No way. Four‘s the favourite.
- Forget about it. Trust me.
Why the hell should I?
Miss Yeung, here‘s your tea.
- I made it myself.
- I appreciate it.
Most women as attractive as you
are afraid to testify.
What does that have to do with it?
I was a witness.
All righty then.
Miss Yeung, do you recognise
any of these men?
Are you aware of all of the dangers
that are involved in
identifying an accused murderer?
Mr. Shong says pick number one.
I see. Tell James I‘m a big girl
with my own mind.
- Understand?
- If you‘re scared, you should go.
- It‘s not me that I‘m worried about.
- They can‘t see you.
That guy. Number two.
James had no right to send you.
Miss Yeung, do you think the other
two witnesses died accidentally?
They were eliminated by Gregory Chui.
I wish you would
reconsider testifying.
Hello, Miss Yeung.
I heard you had
an electrical problem.
Perhaps you should take care.
I see. Thanks so much.
Bye now.
I could arrest you
right here on the street!
- On what charge?
- I haven‘t made up my mind.
- Then...
- Bye. Goodbye.
- Who won?
- The favourite.
- We won some money then. How much?
- I bet on your horse!
Why do you listen to me?
His name is John Chang.
He‘s been trained in Beijing
to be a member of an elite corps
of bodyguards called the Defenders.
They‘re the finest in the world.
I want nothing but the best for you.
I don‘t need a bodyguard.
Why can‘t you come be here with me?
You‘re all I need.
Come on, Michelle. If I could change
things, I‘d be there already.
Only it‘s impossible this time.
We‘ve been through this
so many times.
You‘ve made it very clear.
See you later.
Wait! Wait! Wait a minute!
That was so stupid of me. God.
What a place.
This guy Shong‘s got it made.
You know, he brought in one of those
big-time, Red Army bodyguards.
Supposed to show us
how to do ourjobs apparently.
So what? Maybe you and me,
we‘ll have to show him
how to have a good time.
Capitalists and communists.
Hand in hand.
What‘s this, a parade?
Sergeant, this man says not to worry.
He‘s taking over.
Hello.
- Charlie Lau.
- Lieutenant Chang, John.
- One of the Defenders.
- Listen, John.
That army uniform you‘re wearing
makes me kind ofjumpy.
- I‘m in the army.
- And I‘m in the Hong Kong police.
- ID.
- What? Did I hear you right?
- Right.
- Let me see yours then.
- Let me show you mine also.
- No one asked. Put it away now.
I got one.
You‘re John Chang?
Pleased to meet you.
David Lai. Shall we?
Mr. Shong left $200,000.
You may use as much as you need
to protect her.
Thank you.
Please sign.
That‘s an awful lot of money.
He must be pretty good.
He looks out
for half the world‘s population,
while we only have a few hundred
crooks in Hong Kong to worry about.
- Mr. Shong say anything about me?
- Yeah.
- What‘d he say?
- Don‘t touch the money.
You tell him not to worry!
I didn‘t hear you ask permission
to go through my personal things.
I‘m sorry.
- It‘s my job.
- What job?
- I don‘t even know who you are.
- But I know who you are.
Michelle Yeung,
youngest daughter of a magistrate.
You had a private school education.
Harvard. Sorbonne.
- You enjoy going out shopping.
- Yes.
Tell me.
Am I supposed to be impressed?
My responsibility is to protect you.
Let me be honest.
You seem too young, too eager.
Must be yourfirst time.
- What the...
- He‘s a fake!
Freeze!
Hold it. Try something funny
and I‘ll put a slug in your brain.
I didn‘t mean that.
I was only fooling.
Yeah, boy.
You can‘t keep putting
metal cans into the microwave.
It exploded.
Michelle, sis, are you all right?
- You OK, Miss Yeung?
- What? Leave him alone!
- It was empty.
- What?
There‘s no way.
Like the man said, it was empty.
Billy, did you take
Charlie‘s bullets?
I only took them so I could see
how a gun‘s supposed to work.
- You shouldn‘t play with weapons.
- Sorry.
- Would you like some water?
- Thanks.
Don‘t drink it. No water or anything
else until I tell you it‘s safe.
- Only when you tell me?
- Yes.
That‘s... crazy.
I‘m calling James.
How many people have access
to this house other than family?
Let‘s count ‘em. One, two, three.
- Wait a minute.
- Take your time.
One, two, three, four...
..five, six,
seven, eight, nine.
That‘s your severance pay.
He won‘t be needing you.
It‘s OK. Thanks, Sergeant.
- You better thank the man in charge.
- Tell ya what. Call me any time.
I‘m sure you‘ll
be hearing from me. Go on!
Comrade Chang,
would you explain to me why we‘ve
just freed our entire security force?
The fewer people allowed around
Miss Yeung, the better I like it.
According to Chairman Mao,
the masses have boundless power.
You paid off the masses.
Now, I‘m not asking you for money.
Protecting Miss Yeung is my job.
Don‘t try to buy me out!
I have as much integrity as you do.
I was just kidding. Come on.
Please, don‘t get
too close to her, Sergeant.
That guy,
he‘s a real professional, right?
That‘s one hell of a professional,
that guy.
But I‘m one hell
of a professional too. Watch me!
I just shot you full of holes.
Why don‘t you fall down?
There are no bullets in your gun.
- Miss Yeung?
- My bedroom is off limits, soldier.
I need to make a security check
right now.
I‘m not opening the door.
- What?
- We‘ll change it.
Get out of this room
or I‘ll call the police.
- I‘ve already given them a call.
- You what?
Miss Yeung, you must always keep
your blinds closed.
Why? You can‘t do this to me.
That window needs bars on it.
And keep this light off. There.
Hold on. This is my room
and I want you out.
- Now!
- Just wait.
No, I won‘t wait.
I want some privacy.
This water valve should be replaced.
When are you gonna get out of here?
I wanna change.
You can‘t take those things.
They‘re mine.
Bring them back. Do you hear me?
Damn it!
Use this.
I don‘t want this junk.
I want you out of here.
Well? Let me have some privacy.
Your privacy
is not really my concern.
I‘m here for your safety.
In Beijing, do you put
cameras in women‘s bedrooms?
Only the ones I‘m asked to protect.
All done.
I‘m giving you an electronic amulet.
You must always wear it.
Press the stone to signal me.
There. Not bad.
- Impressive.
- That‘s what I keep telling you.
I‘m the one with all the talent,
the real bodyguard.
Let‘s see him try to do that.
That was just incredible.
Impossible.
You just throw the dart
and the board catches itself.
Mr. Chang,
I‘m Michelle‘s brother. What‘s up?
I‘ll give you 50 dollars
for a kung fu lesson.
I‘ve got something.
First edition Dragonball cards.
It‘s worth at least a hundred.
Mr. Shong gave it to me
for my birthday.
He‘s such an awesome guy.
Why are you sitting in my car?
I was told to by
your hotshot professional bodyguard.
Who the hell does he think he is?
I don‘t believe this.
This is a nice ride.
Ready? Let‘s have some fun,
Mr. Bodyguard.
Come in, Charlie. Do you read me?
- Take the old tunnel. It‘s safer.
- Yeah.
It‘s all right. I‘ll stay close.
- The old tunnel?
- Slick move.
Give me a little warning next time.
OK?
Trouble behind you. You read me?
He thinks it‘s Michelle.
He‘s after your car.
Take care of my back. I‘m on it.
This guy isn‘t that bright.
You don‘t look like my sister.
- You scared?
- Are you kidding me?
Come on. Watch me now.
- Hold it. You ready to die?
- It was an accident.
Yeah? How about if I accidentally
shoot you right here?
No.
Nice and easy.
Just some simple exercises.
One, two, three and down.
You left there in a pretty big hurry.
I thought you could handle it.
My only job here
is taking care of the girl.
Well, you take yourjob
too seriously.
You should learn
how to relax a little bit.
A cop can screw up
and still keep his job.
A bodyguard always has his mission.
If he fails,
he‘s not really a bodyguard, is he?
I‘ve sent for the headmaster.
Now, ready...
- It‘s only for two weeks?
- Yes, it‘s just a leave of absence.
He‘s made me a prisoner
in this place.
They gave me two weeks‘ leave
from the school because of him.
He sent my hairstylist home.
I wanted to work out,
so he bought all this stuff for me.
James, I can‘t stand him any more.
I want him to give me some peace.
Keep calm, Michelle. Put Chang on.
Bodyguard!
- Sir?
- John, can you ease up on Michelle?
Why would lease up?
If I‘m going to successfully
protect Miss Yeung,
I want to restrict
the scope of her activities.
It‘s not much longer. I just want
to be absolutely sure she‘s safe.
But if you‘re not happy with
what I‘m doing, I‘ll just walk away.
- Forget the contract.
- No. I‘m happy, John.
I want you to stay. Michelle
is impossible sometimes, isn‘t she?
It isn‘t easy being protected.
- It often is very stressful.
- I‘m sure she‘ll be all right.
- Let me have Michelle.
- He wants to talk to you.
So, is he leaving?
No, actually, I, well, I warned him.
Now, Michelle, how‘s this sound?
If John doesn‘t ease up by tomorrow,
you tell me. I‘ll get someone else.
Yes, all right. Wait.
What time will I see you tomorrow?
- Tomorrow?
- We talked about it.
Tomorrow I‘m going to be shopping
for your present. Something nice.
What?
You spend all of your time away.
I have a house full of presents.
I want you here with me.
But you have a birthday coming up.
So you think about it.
You listen. Do you think
you can just buy me, James?
It‘s OK.
Too much.
- Come on, five!
- Go, number six!
No, no, no, no, no!
- Yeah!
- You rotten nag.
Let‘s see what we got.
What? Seven to one. Oh, my God!
If you‘d listened to me,
you would have made some money.
You bet my money
on your horse, right?
I can‘t believe it!
You fat fool, I want my money!
How am I supposed to get your money?
I bet it with mine.
You bet all my money on your horses?
- Pay it back!
- You know I can‘t do that.
All my money goes to my son‘s
education. Every last cent of it.
Why did you do this to me?
Let me look at my bank account.
I never should‘ve bet so much money
on a horse like that.
Yeah, what?
I know it‘s late.
You‘ll have your money before
the semester‘s over. More than half.
Yes, I have it,
but it‘s in my wife‘s name.
And it‘s being invested.
And wisely, I might add.
Who is it? Who‘s there?
What do you want? What? Get out!
How dare you!
Sorry.
Sorry, I touched it by mistake.
But Michelle! OK, I‘ll get out.
She‘s got a bodyguard from Beijing.
We can‘t get near her.
Too many excuses.
I want to hear some options.
We‘re working on it.
Thursday is my court date.
I want you to close this up.
Billy, you ready?
I got you something. Look at that.
- It‘s a model of my gun. Like mine.
- Gosh.
Who needs a ball?
- Where are you going, Miss Yeung?
- I have to go somewhere.
- I‘ll come with you.
- All right.
Just what do you think you‘re doing?
Do you really think that
Ken will protect you?
It‘s my mother. Since my father died,
she‘s all alone.
She just wants to see me. It‘s not
a crime for me to see my mom. Is it?
You‘re too dressed up for that.
Your friends invited you to
a birthday party, 1 Maryville Road.
You monitor my calls. You‘re always
listening to every word I say.
I have to have my privacy.
Nobody, not even you, can take away
my freedom. Not even my boyfriend.
You‘re lucky to have him around.
You know why?
Otherwise you‘d be dead.
And you should know it.
You bastard! Let me tell you
something. That hurt.
All of you are just leeches.
If it wasn‘t for Mr. Shong‘s fortune,
would you be protected?
Maybe... Not by you.
That‘s right.
Anybody as pretty as you
is bound to have a rich boyfriend.
Shut up! You shut up!
If I‘m pretty, is that my fault?
I can‘t help it
if this is what I was born with.
I love being attractive. I do.
And I love having
all of these things. Is that wrong?
I‘m tired of everyone
passing judgement on me.
Sorry, Miss Yeung.
Here. Take this.
You made me cry.
It won‘t happen again.
Miss Yeung,
after you testify in court,
my work here with you will be done.
Maybe I‘ll see you again
another time.
- I seriously doubt it.
- All right, let‘s get things moving.
All right.
Come on, Billy. Let‘s go.
Why is it
you‘re always creeping around?
The case will have to be delayed.
Gregory Chui has gastroenteritis.
He checked into a hospital.
My God.
- James!
- It‘s been delayed.
- Indefinitely.
- I‘m dying!
- Maybe a month.
- It‘s his fault.
- For all of this.
- That means I‘ll miss the mission.
I‘m hoping he‘s going to let us
get out of here!
I really need to go shopping,
without John Chang.
OK. If that‘s what you want.
I feel like I‘ve been locked up
forever. Ijust wanna shop all day.
Me too. And play video games.
Wait. I bought extra.
So how about eating some?
Here, Michelle.
Safe.
Come on, Billy. Over here.
So you‘re the bodyguard now.
- Do you think this one is pretty?
- You shouldn‘t be here.
This place is too crowded.
- I thought you were protecting me.
- We are.
It‘s just that this place
is kind of crowded.
Don‘t worry,
we‘ve got it under control.
What‘s that?
It‘s possible it came from upstairs.
- Billy, don‘t you think I know that?
- Just checking.
Michelle,
I‘m going to the video arcade, OK?
All right. Win some prizes.
- You take her, I‘ll take him.
- For sure. I‘ll take her.
- Excuse me.
- Full house.
Don‘t move, Billy.
- What‘s going on?
- Just this.
Billy thinks he‘s so tough.
I can show you a real police pistol.
- Stop lying.
- No way.
Miss Yeung, now it‘s empty.
Sorry. I never know
what to say on an elevator.
Race one, number seven.
Race seven, number one.
No, not race one, number one.
Race seven, number one,
and race one, number seven.
God, what could be simpler? Do I
have to repeat it all again? Billy!
You dropped your gun.
It was on the ground, see?
Put this right back where it belongs.
Thanks a lot.
The first race started?
Let‘s go back then.
See this? It‘s a .38 police revolver.
Who can we bump off?
Tell me about it.
It‘s not a real police pistol.
- Let‘s try it out.
- Don‘t move!
Wait! Don‘t do that!
It‘s a loaded gun!
- Come on! You know it‘s a toy.
- No, Paul. Paul!
Shoot me. Come on.
Paulie, don‘t do it!
- I‘m not scared.
- It‘s my gun. Now, hold still.
Paulie, please stop.
- What are you doing with that?
- What‘d you say?
- Give me that!
- It‘s a real gun!
I can try and special-order it.
But if we do that,
is the return policy still in effect?
I would need a deposit.
- They don‘t have my size.
- Try this one.
- Please, try this one on.
- I don‘t like the colour.
Go! Get out!
Quiet.
Ken, take care
of getting rid of the body.
Let‘s go.
I knew this wasn‘t a good idea.
Come on. Let‘s go.
No. Paulie, don‘t do it.
It‘s loaded. Listen.
Someone‘s gonna get it now.
Charlie, your gun!
We‘re the police.
I want everybody on the floor.
Wait!
- Are you all right?
- No, no, no, no.
- You.
- All right, show me your hands.
Here‘s your pistol.
That‘s the fake one.
- Charlie, talk to me.
- Get away. Go.
- Don‘t die. It‘s my fault.
- Stop it.
I‘m not dying, Billy.
I‘ve got my bulletproof vest on.
Then you won‘t die?
That‘s right.
I‘m sorry.
Thanks.
You‘re welcome.
Why are you crying?
I‘m sorry.
What for? For taking the gun?
Or for something else?
I once knew a boy named Ye Tung
who studied at the Shaolin temple.
He was given a new master
when he was nine.
The master would forgive whatever
he did, no matter how severe,
as long as Ye Tung
would say, “I‘m sorry.“
Instead of any kind of punishment,
the master would just ask Ye Tung
to say he was sorry.
It didn‘t matter what he‘d done.
Ye Tung got very good
at saying he was sorry.
One day he was playing
with some lighted candles
in the temple
of the Shining Waters.
He dropped a candle,
and the next thing he knew,
there was a fire
burning out of control.
He ran just as far
as he possibly could...
until something made him stop.
He returned,
hoping he would have a chance...
to apologise to the teacher.
He was sure that saying those words
would redeem him.
There was no opportunity
to say those words.
The fire made sure of that.
The master died
in the flaming temple.
The boy stopped saying “I‘m sorry.“
Hold on, John Chang.
Or should I say Ye Tung?
Just as the boy learned
how to stop saying those words,
some of us need to learn
how to say...
I‘m sorry.
Let go! That hurts!
- What are you trying to do?
- Where‘s the body?
He‘s right in there, in that drawer.
You‘re not supposed to remove
the bodies. It‘s against the law.
No. No. No, no. No, no, wait.
Take this to buy your silence.
Brother!
- Brother, are you all right?
- I think so.
Brother, you took my bullet,
the one that was meant for me.
As long as I live on this earth...
nothing will ever harm you.
I will protect you.
Mr. Chui isn‘t paying you
to burn ceremonial fires.
He‘s paying you to kill that woman,
and you haven‘t succeeded.
- This is your last...
- My brother‘s dead.
- No, please.
- Don‘t talk to me about fires
or Chui‘s money.
Now, you listen.
Before this is over, she‘ll be dead.
And you - you could be dead also,
as well as your boss.
The wounds are very strange.
The victims all died
from a loss of blood.
I don‘t know what kind
of weapon caused this.
It‘s a Red Army bayonet.
The three edges
cause rapid blood loss.
- Thank you, Doctor.
- Don‘t mention it.
They killed these guys
to get to the corpse, but why?
I really don‘t know.
Anyway, thanks for takin‘ him out.
He would have killed me.
Is your arm all right?
Yeah, it hurts a little bit,
but not as much as dying would have.
Yeah. Come on.
I‘m gonna have to ask you again.
Do you know this man?
I‘m warning you, Mr. Chui!
You better answer.
Don‘t threaten my client.
He has the right not to answer,
and you know it!
All right then. You‘ll be sorry.
I think he‘s retired Red Army.
The Assassin Squad, right.
Let me know when you
find anything out.
His name is Kar Kwok.
His brother‘s body was
stolen from the morgue.
He‘s the one that
almost killed Charlie.
Here‘s something to keep us going.
Do you think you‘ll catch him?
- Yeah.
- We‘ll catch him, no matter what!
I‘ll be around back.
- Clear!
- Look in here!
Clear!
What‘s that over there?
- Clear!
- Clear up here.
- Thanks.
- You‘re soaking wet.
You really shouldn‘t be up here.
I just want to thank you
for protecting me.
- I was assigned to you.
- I‘ve given you a lot of trouble.
But do you think we could start over?
I mean, what else do bodyguards do?
Tell me about your girlfriend.
There‘s nobody to tell you about.
That can‘t be.
Tell me about your family.
Do you have any brothers or sisters?
Did you get straight A‘s?
Don‘t ask me.
That‘s privileged information,
top secret.
- Pretty good hands.
- For some things.
Keep holding on to me.
You wouldn‘t want me to fall,
would you?
I might get wet.
I like walking in the rain,
don‘t you?
- It‘s him!
- What‘s wrong?
What is he doing?
Follow me!
“I am everywhere.
It‘s just a matter of time.“
Bulletproof windows
throughout the house.
I‘m tellin‘ ya. This has got me
jumpy. Is it that important?
Yeah, it is important. The assassin
knows this house, and he knows us.
I told Ken to stay alert.
You know,
tomorrow is Michelle‘s birthday.
- How about if we surprise her?
- We should have a party.
Thank you. It‘s safe, right?
I got you something.
- Here. Look. What do you think?
- I like it.
- Hello?
- It‘s me. I found a new bodyguard.
Wait a second.
It‘s James. He asked me
if I want a new bodyguard.
Look, let‘s just keep this one. Bye.
Wait.
- Good night.
Happy birthday!
Thank you!
Everything is just perfect.
You know what would make it perfect.
She loves flowers on her birthday.
But once you cut a flower, what
happens to it? It loses its life.
It‘s her birthday.
- Make a wish.
- All right.
- Happy birthday! Go ahead.
- Thanks.
- I love roses.
- I hope you like the colour.
They‘re a bunch of lifeless bodies
now, at least John says so.
I‘ll put them in water, OK?
Freeze!
- What?
- They‘re only flowers.
Right. From Mr. Shong, right?
All right. Sorry. Get outta here.
OK, I‘m clean already. Geez!
- Flowers from Mr. Shong.
- Here. Give them to me.
Makes your flowers look kinda puny.
Who asked you?
- Hello?
- Happy birthday.
- Thanks forthe flowers.
- Dinner at the Fond du Lac?
- The Fond du Lac? When?
- Tonight.
- Won‘t that be difficult?
- Not for me.
I came in from Beijing
to take you out. I‘m in the driveway.
You‘re where? Out front?
- You better not be teasing me.
- Look out the window.
- Hi, James!
- Why don‘t you wear something nice?
All right, I will.
I‘ll meet you in 20 minutes. Bye.
Mr. Shong,
when did you make the reservation?
Yesterday.
Does anyone know you‘re having
dinner here with Miss Yeung?
- You don‘t trust me?
- That‘s not what he meant.
John‘s just making sure
I‘m not in any danger.
And you seem to understand each other
pretty well. Cheers.
Wait. Please, drink some first.
Sure.
Thank you.
It‘s safe. Excuse me.
- You take no chances.
- No. He‘s very, very good.
- He doesn‘t make mistakes?
- No. Never.
If he did, then
he couldn‘t be a bodyguard any more.
So now you‘re an expert.
- Mademoiselle.
- Thank you.
The chef does
a wonderful Chilean sea bass.
What do you think?
I don‘t know.
How about the salmon?
I‘ll... I‘ll take another look.
It‘s too much for me. You decide.
- So how was your dinner?
- It was nice. Thank you very much.
- Champagne?
- No. I need to use the ladies‘ room.
- Miss Yeung?
- Thank you.
Let me help you...
John, she just fell.
Help us.
- Your boyfriend‘s a real gentleman.
- Yes, he is.
Thank you.
I‘m finished. Can we go home?
Please, Billy.
Don‘t be rude to James.
Maybe it‘s not Billy‘s
kind of restaurant.
Michelle,
I have to go back to Beijing tonight.
- I can‘t drive you.
- That‘s fine.
I‘m coming home on Friday.
John, you‘re just about to come
to the end of your mission.
- Thank you for guarding Michelle.
- My pleasure.
Good night!
Where are you going?
Making the rounds.
What are you doing?
Surprise.
Really? For me?
Let me help you.
It‘s automatic,
totally reliable, like you.
It‘s perfect.
Perfect.
- Good night.
- Yes, good night.
I won‘t see you once this is over.
You probably won‘t.
You never know. Good night.
Good night.
Michelle, what happened?
I touched the button by mistake.
It‘s all right.
I have something to tell you.
I know it‘s wrong,
but I love you.
Does that mean you
don‘t want to kiss me?
Me?
I don‘t know what I want.
I do.
What‘s the matter?
- Nothing. Why?
- Sure, you‘ve been eating all night.
When something‘s bothering me,
I smoke like a fiend.
What‘s bothering you?
It‘s just money problems.
My son has a chance
to study medicine in the US,
but I can‘t afford to send him there.
I even gambled some of Ken‘s money
away trying to raise the cash.
Can you make any dough workin‘
as a bodyguard? Looks like it.
I thought you were happy being a cop.
With more money, I would be.
So why‘d you join?
I wanted to be a big hero,
so Ijoined the force.
During my first year, I interrupted
a bank robbery in progress,
rescued four hostages
and shot the robber.
- So you did become a hero, right?
- Yeah!
Damn right.
They even gave me a medal.
It was when I first met my wife.
Look at this.
That was when we were still together,
before I screwed things up.
Oh, boy!
I spent so much time
trying to live up to my reputation
that I didn‘t have time for her.
And she found someone who did?
Yeah, she sure did.
Some guy with a corner office started
buyin‘ her things, you know?
How am I supposed to compete
with that on my salary?
I thought maybe she was just
looking for a little attention.
So I said to her, “It‘s him or me.“
She chose the corner office.
Why couldn‘t you talk to her?
That‘s my point:
that women like to be talked to.
I was too busy being the quiet hero.
Which reminds me,
you‘re up the same tree.
You know opportunity - it disappears
before you can ever stop it.
How many chances do you suppose men
like us are gonna get to be happy?
All the kung fu in the world isn‘t
gonna help when it comes to women.
All I can say is...
you gotta take your shot.
Otherwise, you‘ll regret it.
What about my responsibilities?
Sure, it would be nice.
I bet it would be
much better than that.
But don‘t try and you‘ll never know.
It‘s her.
- She‘s calling you.
- No, the pager gets stuck.
You‘re the one who‘s stuck,
and you know it.
Come on!
Come on! Hang on, Ken!
That‘s just how you looked
when you shot my brother.
Only this time, you‘re the one
that‘s gonna die, so get ready!
Charlie, take this money.
Go on. Bet it all.
Number three in the sixth.
Forget it, Ken.
You know I can‘t do that.
Come on. It‘s for your son.
If I could, I‘d bet it myself.
That‘s very good of you, Ken.
I stole a picture
of you the other day.
Could you sign it for me?
How about...
How about signing it with a kiss?
No! Ken!
Come on out, you cowards!
My foot.
Hurry. Hurry.
That was close.
Watch it!
Wait! The room is filling with gas,
the windows are bulletproof
and the doors are locked.
One shot and we‘re all dead.
That doesn‘t scare me.
Ready, bodyguard?
For me, the battle is always on.
The battle?
This is your execution.
And yours as well.
You killed my best friend.
Your best friend?
What are you talking about?
He killed my brother!
Forthat,
you‘re going to suffer, long...
and then you‘re going to die.
- No!
- Say goodbye..
Come on, pal! Let‘s do it!
Only one of us will stand
when this is over.
I am trained to attack.
lam an assassin.
But you‘re just a defender.
Honey, I‘m home!
Wait!
Please let her go! Whatever
Chui‘s paying you, I‘ll triple it!
You get away from her. Over there.
Get going!
He shot my brother seven times.
Oh, yeah!
Now it‘s gonna be my turn to shoot...
seven times!
I have millions.
How much will it take?
I‘m afraid your offer‘s no good.
It‘s meaningless...
unless you want to pay someone
to take the first bullet for her.
Come on. Take the bullet.
Save the girl yourself.
- Then she‘ll love you forever.
- Wait.
What do you think about that?
There you go. I knew you‘d do it.
It‘s almost over.
Aren‘t you prepared to die?
Oh, no, John. No!
Please. My God.
So... one more bullet then.
John! No!
Please!
- No! Uncle Charlie! Come on!
- I‘m OK.
Please!
Faster.
Mr. Shong, John Chang
was trained to take a bullet.
You ducked because
that‘s the natural instinct.
There‘s no reason
for you to feel guilty.
This is from comrade Chang
to Sergeant Lau.
Step on it, OK?
We‘re going to be late.
You could get authorisation
for Chang to stay in Hong Kong.
With all your money,
you could pull the strings.
Charlie,
this is just between you and me.
It‘s for your son‘s education.
No more gambling, OK?
No more gambling. Yeah.
- John, wait! Wait!
- Stop right there.
- I have a permit.
- Talk to the bodyguard.
I have written authorisation
for Mr. Chang to remain in Hong Kong.
Mr. Chang wishes to return to Beijing.
He left you this.
He‘s not coming back.