I stole it for you.
It talks too much,
so I don't want it.
Hey!
What should we do?
It looks good to me.
Leave it there so it
can ramble on by itself.
Think we should?
Prices are too high I tell you.
So you mean that taxi fares
are too high as well, right?
No way,
taxi fares need to go up.
I was valedictorian,
and I didn't get in.
But tall and pretty Ji-hyun
who doesn't study gets in.
Mister,
does this make sense?
Does this make sense?
I said does this make sense?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No, that's okay.
Do I look strange?
No, you look good in jeans.
Please come this way.
Yes, sir.
So where shall we go?
I have an idea.
Young-hee really smiled?
Yes, sir.
It would've been nice if you
had saw it, Mr. President.
Please don't call me
Mr. President.
Just call me Mr. Han.
Or Min-wook perhaps.
Yes, Min-wook.
Why are you so late?
Man, it was damn hard.
That's why I told you
to go on time.
How'd you get
so much dirt on you?
She and I live together.
She?
In high school, we were
in the same movie club.
He was so handsome
all the girls liked him.
But after serving in the army,
he came back as a girl.
I see.
Hey Eun-soo.
Why'd your reserve training
end so late?
I had to make up for missing
out on the last session.
It's you, right?
Right?
Pleased to meet you.
It's a tremendous honor, sir.
You look a lot handsomer
in person than on TV.
Am I dreaming or what?
This isn't a dream, right?
Ha-rin, aren't you going to
change into something prettier?
Oh my, where's my head?
I'm going to
change very quickly,
so please wait a moment, sir.
I'll be right back.
- Let's drink.
- Sure.
Mr. President,
I mean Min-wook.
Have you ever been
without your bodyguards?
No, I've never had the chance.
Don't you want to try once?
Well...
It won't be that easy.
The bathroom has a back door.
See you soon.
Hurry.
Out of shape?
It's locked.
Let's jump over.
Are you okay?
Where did he go?
Let's look for him again.
Noodles and a soju bottle
for table three.
What's this?
This is a tavern, right?
Actually, these huge guys
dressed in black suits outside.
I know, I know.
You're fugitives, right?
Yes.
Trying to hide, right?
Follow me.
- Thank you.
- Hurry and go upstairs.
Don't worry about big men.
I used to be a Marine.
Oh my, isn't that him?
Just finish your food.
They're coming.
What do you want?
Was the President here
by any chance?
The President?
Of course.
Really?
Yeah, 30 years ago.
President Park
came to my Marine unit.
Pardon?
Bastard didn't know
what a real Marine can do.
I knocked him out,
so you can relax and drink.
Follow me.
Sit, sit.
Sit over here.
It's nice sitting together, huh?
So what drink
can I get for you?
Since we were drinking
Something newer?
I told you there's
no one like that here.
No, a customer that just left
said there's someone who
looks just like the President.
I'm sorry,
but I'll have to look upstairs.
You can't.
Ma'am, you can't do this.
If you keep this up,
I'll call the police.
Big trouble.
They have guns.
Hurry and hide.
Hurry and go.
Go inside.
Hurry.
Go in.
Wait...
Do you want to get shot?
I was only a security guard.
Sorry to interrupt.
Salute!
Everything's clear,
Mr. President.
I think we've put them
through too much,
so how about we quit?
What a beautiful morning!
Oh my,
Young-hee's here early today.
What a great day it is.
Life is happy and beautiful.
We're going to study
hard today, okay?
Just do it!
Teacher, please have some.
It'll help start your great day.
Thank you!
Well, see you in Korean class!
Just do it!
Teacher!
Teacher, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Vinegar is a good
beauty treatment.
Just do it!
Sorry, teacher.
It's okay.
Hey, it tasted better
than soy sauce.
We mixed it with
soap water, too.
It's okay.
We spit in it, too.
The files on the eastern front
you'll be visiting today, sir.
Yes, good work.
There are so many.
Here you go.
Mr. Chang.
It concerns
Young-hee's teacher.
Well, some place
people can't notice...
That is, a quiet place...
Well, for the two of us...
I understand very well.
I'll set the time
and place for you.
Thank you.
- Good afternoon.
- Hi.
Hello?
Is this Miss Choi Eun-soo?
Yes, it's me.
This is Mr. Chang
from the President's office.
Yes, we've met before.
The President wants to meet
you at a quiet place tonight.
Yes.
The place is suite 2301
at the Hyatt Hotel.
The President
will arrive at 10 p.m.
It's suite 2301,
and please don't be late.
Hotel suite?
Our policy shouldn't
be superficial or formal,
but being full of hope for
the future is most important.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, sir.
Oh yeah, what happened
to that favor I asked of you?
Right, sir.
The room has been reserved,
and security has been sent.
What? Reserve a room?
Yes, if you go to suite 2301
at the Hyatt Hotel at 10 p.m.,
Miss Choi will be
waiting for you.
It's the room President Clinton
slept in during his visit.
It's the best place for secrecy.
Look here, Mr. Chang.
I'm sorry, sir.
I should've mentioned it
when no one's around.
Look here, Mr. Chang.
Are you out of your mind?
Sir?
This is not what I wanted.
Cancel it right now.
Now!
What's wrong?
Something happened?
I want to get drunk.
Why?
What happened?
Which bastard did this to you?
The President bastard.
Hello?
Oh, right.
Hold on please.
Answer it.
Who is it?
The President bastard.
I don't want to.
Answer it,
he wants to talk to you.
Just tell him
what's on your mind.
Hurry.
Hello?
Eun-soo, it's me.
I'm sorry that
I'm not that kind of girl.
I'm not like that
so I'm very sorry.
Good-bye.
Yes, Mr. President.
Get the car ready.
I think I've fallen in love.
Okay.
Good luck with him.
Good luck with
that president guy.
It's all over now.
Don't ever talk about him
in front of me, okay?
Hey, Han Min-wook!
It's all over!
The end!
End!
But it's not about
my sweety Min-wook.
Hello.
She just left.
Where did she go?
Eun-soo!
Eun-soo,
I know you're very upset.
It's all my fault.
But I wish
you'd let me explain.
I'm sorry.
This may be rude of me,
but one thing is for sure.
I'm not that kind of girl.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
It's the President!
It's an honor to meet you.
What a handsome fellow.
Hello.
You're so cute.
This guy who likes this girl
made a mistake.
It wasn't directly his fault,
but if he nonetheless
hurt her in the end,
I think he should apologize
and make up to her.
If you were her,
what would you do?
That girl was riding
in the subway.
She waited for him to come
closer and missed her stop.
So what would you do?
I'd have to take her
all the way home.
Let's get off at the next stop.
Seoul Night Club,
Waiter Han Min-wook
It's here.
I see.
It's a nice place.
I'm sorry and grateful
for today.
I had a good time.
I had a good time as well.
I wonder why people
find courage in the dark.
Feeling the hiccups
coming again?
President Han Gets Caught
On A Secret Date
In a recent newspaper,
President Han was found
embracing a woman.
Her name is Choi Eun-soo.
She's the President's
daughter's teacher.
But the thornier issue
is Choi Eun-soo's past.
In college,
she was suspected of
kidnapping the Unification
Minister's granddaughter,
and was being investigated.
My granddaughter
was taken hostage.
Is that a humane thing to do?
Hello.
Hey, did you guys hear?
Ms. Choi came to our school
to become the President's wife.
That sucks.
For that kidnapping,
she seduced these guys
and then betrayed them...
No wonder she tried
to manipulate Young-hee.
I heard she stole something
to get close to Young-hee.
Repeat what you all just said.
What?
What did you just say?
Say it, you bitches!
Say it!
To be the President's wife,
become a teacher and
transfer to different schools.
Then go to the President's
daughter's school.
Afterwards,
be her homeroom teacher.
Since there needs
to be an opening,
use any means
to kick out her old teacher.
I'd like to
point something out.
There's something very
important to be his wife.
What's that?
You must kidnap
a little child ten years ago.
Our country has
gotten a lot better.
In the old days,
he'd go to jail for saying that.
Who is he talking about?
Just keep eating!
A woman who dates the
President can become his wife.
Who is she?
The mother of our country.
But at the same time,
she lives with another man.
Does this make sense
in a civilized country?
Look at this.
Shin Kwang-bae's ID
is 730728- 1052511.
Have you ever heard of a
woman called Kwang-bae?
And ever seen a woman's ID
start with a male's number?
Ha-Rin.
Our party's approval rate
has fallen by 35% this month.
This will negatively affect
the local elections next month.
Sir, shall I catch you
on a better time?
Are you really dating
the President?
- When did you two meet?
- Is it true?
How do you feel now?
Please say something.
Mr. President, please allow me
to begin by addressing your
alleged relationship with Miss Choi.
Is there any truth to this rumor?
She would like to first
ask you about the rumors
that is troubling you at the moment.
To protest his objection to the
North-South student summit,
we stopped the Minister's car.
But he had mistakenly left his
granddaughter and drove off.
So we're not kidnappers.
Choi Eun-soo is simply
my daughter's teacher.
We had no time to develop
feelings for each other.
All I did was hear her advice
on Young-hee's education.
And I'd really like
to point out something here.
Shin Kwang-bae
had a sex change,
but she's not treated
legally as a woman.
She's my best friend
and is like a sister to me.
I'd like for you all
not to hurt her any longer.
As our country's President,
I deeply regret that
I've confused the people.
From now on,
I'll restrain from these acts.
Is your relationship
with the President true?
Please tell the truth.
Yes, it's true.
I had feelings
for the President.
So I did what I could
to get close to him.
By doing this wrongful act,
I've brought trouble
to the honorable President,
so I'm deeply sorry.
Didn't the President realize
you intentions?
Will you keep teaching
at his daughter's school?
Miss Choi.
Don't be too upset.
The President has no choice
but to be a politician.
Why are you up there?
Just because.
I'm really sorry.
For what?
Just because.
I bet it's nice to
quit this dumb school.
Envious, huh?
I'm going very far away
to the countryside.
Did you really like my dad?
Yep!
But you're giving up?
Why?
Just because!
When are you coming down?
After you leave.
Okay!
I'm done having fun,
so I'm going home.
You're the first person
to hit me.
And the last, of course.
You need to be hit more.
Teacher!
Excellent work
Mr. President.
You're 35 minutes
behind schedule, sir.
This year,
there are many paintings
that entail fantasies
of a cyber-future.
When I was young,
I'd paint landscapes
of my dreams.
Kids today
are surely different.
Who's the person
standing there?
It's me, sir.
Your dream must be
to become president.
Yes, sir.
When I grow up,
I want to be a great
president for the people.
An honest and great
president like President Han.
At a countryside school
in Youngwol Town,
a elementary school student dreamed
of becoming president.
This boy painted a picture
of his dreams and ambitions.
It was rough
yet sincerely made.
And into the far future,
this boy became president.
But this president lied to
the people who elected him.
And terribly broke
this woman's heart.
My beloved citizens.
Today,
in front of all of you,
I'd like to confess
something to you.
Frankly,
I don't play the piano well.
For the last election,
I practiced to artificially create
this image of a
piano-playing president.
You voted for
a person like this.
And I was elected president
thanks to you.
But I can't lie
to myself any longer.
I'm very embarrassed
for lying to you all until now.
My beloved citizens,
I'm very sorry.
But I'm not going to
disappoint you any longer.
I...
I love Miss Choi Eun-soo.
She helped me
find myself again.
Ladies and gentlemen.
If I don't hold on to her,
I'll never get married.
Teacher!
Hi.
Which one is prettier?
This one is, right?
No, this one's prettier.
Mine's prettier.
No, both of them are.
Teacher, you take them.
Thank you.
A man who loves this woman
made an unforgivable mistake.
But this man desperately
wants her to forgive him.
If you were her,
what would you do?
Can I answer in a poem?
A poem?
Can you say Han Min-wook
by character?
Han...
Han is the first character
for big mistake.
Min...
Min is for broken-heart.
Are you prepared to pay for it?
Wook...