You're going to see the boat people
trying to sell...
It's so hot.
Let me tell you something nice.
Watching them makes me very happy.
They want us...
Right. Tell Tong
to drive us around tomorrow.
You tell him.
He's your man. You tell him.
Have you finished?
He hopes we'll go easy on him.
But we've never been hard on him.
Hey, Tong,
take Mr Wong sightseeing tomorrow.
What about a boat trip?
Whatever! Just don't be seen.
Have you finished?
We've got business to discuss.
- Call Inspector Ho for me, please.
- Yes, sir.
Tomorrow we'll take a drive
to the Peak, and then the Gardens.
Don't forget the camera.
We'll have...
Don't walk about like that,
you're making me ill.
I want to.
Now don't forget.
The boat people who we left
asked us to entertain...
Mr Kuo, please.
Boss, the telephone.
You're using my shoe as an ashtray?
Mr Wong wants me to get
Chief Inspector Ho.
Where can I find
an Inspector Ho for him?
- What's wrong?
- I thought you'd fixed everything.
- Is that my call?
- Yes.
Fixed.
I'll go clean the car.
- Are Filipino maids popular here?
- It's becoming fashionable.
They're hard to come by.
There is so little money.
Why should they have first choice?
Fei, you can take it, but we can't.
You've helped us for so many years.
We won't forget it, will we?
You can have anything you want.
Just say the word.
I thank you for your goodwill.
Have faith in me.
Better days are ahead. Let's go.
Let's go.
Where's Snake Ming?
He left without saying
where he was going.
- Have they found Wong?
- Not yet.
Who did you call?
My cousin,
he works for the shipping company.
He's checking the passenger list.
- Inspector.
- Where did you go?
The Five Continents Hotel,
Luk Kwok Hotel...
Is our Mr Wong at the Five Continents
or Luk Kwok?
- Neither.
- Then why did you go there?
Then later I found out
he was at King's.
Then why did you go
to the other places?
- I've got it.
- Got what?
Wong's already here,
so I'll check the hotel.
Who told you to check on Wong?
Find the reporters for me.
Why do I have to do everything?
I've never lied in my life.
I'm really scared.
We mustn't disappoint them.
Uncle, you're more than an hour late.
Tiger means business.
Do you think Tiger will trick us?
- Our boys will be watching.
- I have to get my lucky rose.
- Tiger's been waiting all morning.
- We'll invite him for lunch.
He wants to see you now.
I must get my rose first.
Boss.
A couple of Tiger's stooges.
They've got some nerve,
walking in here.
What's up?
- Our boss doesn't like waiting.
- So I'll invite him for dinner.
Freeze!
- Stay there!
- Come with us, Tiger's orders.
Look, guys... this is our turf.
I'll go with them.
You and the boys...
You dare make trouble here?
Tie them up!
I'll buy my rose,
then I'll see your boss.
Let's go.
Tiger will get you for this.
So you're planning
to issue stocks here?
That's the idea.
The door! When?
Very soon, I hope.
Gentlemen.
We're associates of Mr Wong's.
Is he in?
- Mr Wong is not here right now.
- We were told he was in his suite.
He's breakfasting right now.
- We're good friends of his.
- Long time associates.
Just the man. These are
Mr Wong's business associates.
- What now?
- I don't do anything illegal.
That's kidnapping.
- Close the door.
- How many have you tied up now?
You own a steel foundry as well?
Good morning, good morning.
You're very early today.
Mr Wong,
is everything to your liking?
Fine, very comfortable.
Mr Wong likes it here.
- Is everything OK, cousins?
- Of course.
Fresh roses. They're lovely.
A rose to bring you luck.
Why do you give him a rose?
Tradition, it's a family custom.
- A tradition.
- A family tradition.
- Wait! Come back down!
- Not so loud.
Inspector Ho is coming up
with two others.
Mr Kuo, an urgent call for you.
I'll take it there.
Inspector Ho is on his way up.
He's already in the lift.
What do we do now?
Cousin. Cousin.
He's calling you.
- You forgot our business deal.
- Today?
They're on the phone.
I'd completely forgotten about it.
He's so busy.
Give me some clothes.
Inspector Ho's on his way up.
This way. Take this.
And this.
Go on, follow him. Inside.
Mr Wong, sir.
Tell them I'll be home by noon.
Mr Wong, I'd recognise you anywhere.
You are sharp.
You must be the famous Inspector Ho.
At your service, sir.
Have you been that busy
you couldn't come to the dock?
Oh, but I was. Let me explain.
Come with me. I'm on my way out.
- Butler, that's all.
- Yes, sir.
- Who are they?
- My assistants.
They've gone.
That's that taken care of!
Tiger is on our backs
and you're still prancing about!
It may not bother you,
but it bothers me.
You taught me to how to dress,
how to walk, how to talk,
how to negotiate, how to fight.
You treat me like a puppet.
Aren't you bothered about that?
He's right. The car.
- That's what you should be doing.
- That's what you think.
- What do you think you should do?
- What I'm doing right now.
- This makes you happy?
- Do I look happy?
- Continue with what you're doing.
- I will.
- Go on, then.
- I would if I knew what I was doing.
Imported goods are excellent here.
- Have you got any currency?
- Not yet.
- I'll lend you some.
- How kind.
- When are you floating your company?
- Soon.
He's worth a fortune.
He even owns a goldmine.
And the shipyard and the steelworks.
Go and find the reporters.
I'll handle this.
Mr Wong,
how much are the shares worth?
One dollar.
$2.80 once they're floated.
Double your selling price?
- There are no outside buyers.
- Can I buy some?
You're not an outsider, nephew.
Nephew, I'm one of them.
Inspector Ho, Chairman of
the planning committee, police club.
That's the police club.
I'm in charge of fundraising.
Nephew, your charitable deeds
are praiseworthy indeed.
- Very good, very good.
- Thank you.
Are you all right?
I'm just sighing.
It's no use sighing.
You must enjoy life.
I'm sighing
because the club needs $80,000,
but we've only raised $15,000
in 3 years.
That's only about $60,000
short of the target.
After the stocks are issued,
I'll see what I can do to help.
Mr Wong... I'm sorry.
I know all it takes
is one word from you.
You're so clumsy.
My son will treat Belle well.
How can I say no to you?
Thank you for being my guide
for the day.
It's nothing.
Make a note of what I bought.
I'll pay you back soon.
Consider it a deposit.
Deposit?
You promised to sell me some shares.
- Of course! Take these to my room.
- Yes, sir.
Shall we sign the papers upstairs?
No, let's say your office tomorrow.
The shares will be ready then.
Fine.
Mr Wong,
I'll accompany you to your room.
- There's no need.
- I insist.
I'd really like a cup of coffee right now.
- Let's have a coffee, then.
- Fine.
- No coffee?
- I'd better go back to my room.
Back to your room.
Why don't you call the station?
- Call the station?
- In case they're looking for you.
- It's all right.
- Call to please me, then.
- I will.
- I'll wait here.
- I'll go to the ladies.
- I'll come.
- No, you go to your mother.
- OK.
- Why is he tagging along?
- He wants to.
- Don't let him.
- I'm doing my best.
Luming, let's go.
- What's up?
- Inspector Ho. Sort him out.
I'll be back soon.
Kwong-On Bank, please.
Uncle, why are you here?
Admiring the lights.
Inspector Ho, Inspector Ho.
- You?
- There's a fight outside.
Can't you see I'm busy?
But you are the inspector.
Don't you lecture me. Yes?
Kwong-On Bank? Go away!
Sorry, not you.
- They're still here. Are you busy?
- No.
Then join me.
Why is he here?
Think of something.
I couldn't find you earlier.
I have something to say.
Where's Chen Wah?
He's just gone to the restroom.
We can't leave yet. Come, come.
Sit down and speak slowly.
I've no time.
Floating in three months!
They didn't sell as well
as they thought? Thank you.
- Excuse me.
- One moment. Yes, sir?
- Is Mr Wong living here?
- Yes.
Is that...?
He's over there.
- A friend of yours?
- A small business matter.
Hey!
Nothing. I'm rich!
Finished work already?
Mr Kao has an easy life.
- Sit down for a chat.
- I'm still busy.
Inspector Ho? Is your eye better?
- Who are you?
- I hit you in the eye.
- You're confessing?
- Not exactly, I want your other eye.
Go, I'll chase you
to the ends of the Earth.
Stop, I'll get you!
What's the matter?
I think the gangsters are fighting.
I'll take my leave of you.
Have dinner with us tonight.
We'll be there.
I'm not going to talk business
any more. I'll stay and have tea.
- Don't bring them here for tea.
- It's difficult to control them.
- You'd better stay here.
- Sit down again?
Take them to the room.
I'd prefer to stay
and have tea and stay for dinner too.
All right.
Mr Kuo, the press.
- How did they get in?
- Bribery, I suppose.
And that's why I came to Hong Kong.
Is that so?
A photo, if you don't mind?
Fine, fine.
- Mr Wong.
- Chen Wah, I'm glad you're here.
Come, let's have a group photo.
Everybody join in.
- A photo, Dad?
- This way.
Good. Altogether. Altogether.
Ready, set...
Thank you.
Auntie, come and sit down.
- A moment. What paper are you with?
- The Sun.
- When will it be published?
- Tomorrow.
Get the flower, then we can go.
- Good luck.
- You're very busy.
- Do you really believe that?
- It's not a matter of belief.
Why haven't you introduced
your friend?
Why does he hide behind you?
He's shy. You must excuse me now.
- Chen Wah, I want to say something.
- What is it?
Madam Kao has consented
to a Shanghai wedding.
In Shanghai! Congratulations!
Madam Kao, thank you
for your hospitality
and consent to this marriage.
You're very kind.
My trip is so brief
and I've missed so many people.
I suggest an engagement party
with all the Hong Kong dignitaries
and your friends.
What do you think?
- Chen Wah, what do you think?
- Me? I've no objection.
Then it's settled.
Good idea.
Kill two birds with one stone.
Mr Wong, please, excuse me.
Chen Wah, for an engagement in Hong Kong,
all the VIPs must be invited.
All right. You take care of it.
Did you get that?
Western style is more grand.
Eastern style is more relaxed.
Do your Chinese friends
outnumber foreign friends?
We have more Chinese
than foreign friends.
Cousin, cousin.
He's calling you.
Sorry,
shall we discuss the guest list?
Luming, come here.
We need to talk about it.
- Sorry.
- No, no, go.
Sit for a while.
Madam Kao, any other ideas?
Lots of foreign friends?
How are we to get VIPs to attend?
Nothing is impossible to you.
Thanks for the confidence.
Mr Wong is making such a big fuss
about everything.
It's all your fault.
Simple, you said.
Just get a suite, buy some
new clothes, a little make-up.
It's one thing after another.
Kidnapping reporters and businessmen.
Beating up police. This is a mess.
But you just said you were happy.
Shut up!
You started all this. Fix it!
It's a bit late to start blaming me.
You helped Madam Kao as well.
- Helping people is a good thing.
- Correct.
- But you must know your limits!
- You're just making it worse!
You are all right.
It's me that's wrong.
This is not a mistake.
It is. I have too much sympathy,
but not enough ability.
Trying to help Madam Kao
perform miracles.
You're right. I don't measure up.
Please tell her we've done all we can.
I've no more to give.
At this stage?
- When should I tell her?
- You'll ruin the marriage.
- Imagine we never helped her.
- That's rich.
Yes, I'm getting out now.
I won't tell her, I'm not so cruel.
- You...
- I won't.
- Tell her.
- No.
I'll tell her, then.
Uncle.
Auntie, Dad.
- We're not interrupting?
- Not at all.
- What's the matter?
- Mum says you're very kind.
You are very big hearted, so...
So, we'd like you to be godfather
to our first baby.
- Godfather?
- You wouldn't refuse us?
We won't keep you any longer.
Auntie.
Bye-bye, Uncle.
Godfather, what an idea.
Get all the bosses
and their women to pose as VIPs.
Why are you staring?
Is it a bad idea?
It's a good idea.
But they won't look the part.
Dress them up.
- I'll teach them etiquette.
- I'll do make-up.
- Go to work. I'll make some calls.
- Let's go.
Do you know what you're doing?
- What's up?
- He tried to run away.
Run away?
I can't cope. I just want to go home.
- How are you going to get there?
- By boat or train.
What about in a wheelchair?
I'm not going. I have work to do.
Let's go.
Everyone's assignment
is written here.
This is yours, remember it.
This is yours.
Take it easy.
I might be pregnant
and have to have an abortion.
You don't even know
who the father is. Stop fidgeting.
Please, you're ladies now.
You must be civil to each other.
She's always bad mouthing others.
She already has a gut,
and she's still eating.
Breathe in.
What are you looking at?
Straighten up. Remember your lines.
People! People!
Tong gave each of you
a piece of paper with your part.
Your name and what to say.
Remember your lines. Speak Mandarin.
Mr Wong is from Shanghai.
Don't start yet.
Just remember your part
and act like ladies and gentlemen.
Why should we?
He might be more vulgar than I am.
Who are you?
The Secretary of Education.
Education?
How could he be more vulgar than you?
- Why?
- That's why.
Your face doesn't fit the part.
Who's the Chief Warden?
Who's got that paper?
You're the Chief Warden.
Why didn't you reply?
I don't know. I can't read.
Can't read?! What do you mean?
All right, you be the warden
and you be the secretary.
- You must be crazy!
- What's the matter?
He felt me up.
Help me out here, be civilised.
It was all a mistake.
- Bastard, molesting my bird!
- You dare to hit me?
Don't fight!
Let me go!
Stop it!
Stop acting like this!
Stop fighting!
Listen to me! Stop fighting!
Listen to me.
Aren't you tired
of all this fighting and killing?
This may be your only chance
in life to do a good deed.
You might not understand
why you have to help Madam Kao.
Just think - when you're old
and your children ask,
"Dad, what are your proudest
achievements in your life?"
What should you say?
Do you tell them you were a gangster,
opening brothels, casinos, racketeering...
Does this make you proud?
This may be the only thing
you can tell them.
- Do you understand?
- No!
Tong, Tong!
I'm here!
I told you they weren't to carry guns.
I did tell them.
Ask who else is carrying a gun!
Who's still got a gun?
Me!
Take all their guns away!
I told you not to and you still did.
"The Ritz"
Here's $5,000 from the Ho's
and $5,000 from me.
That's not too greedy, is it?
That's not greedy.
I'll give you the shares.
- Do you need to count it?
- No need.
Thank you.
When did the two reporters leave?
I went back to work.
I don't know when they left.
Sign here.
Mr Wong. Will there be anything else?
I'm going to a party tonight.
- Who's that?
- Mr Wong, the Shanghai magnate.
He's the multi-millionaire, Mr Wong?
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr Wong.
Thanks for looking out for me.
No need. You've been most attentive.
If we don't look out for each other,
who will?
How much did we spend last time?
- Don't worry about it.
- I insist!
Here's $2,000 for your trouble.
- So much money?
- Keep it.
It's chicken feed to me,
but it's a quite a bundle to you.
Remember, once the shares hit
two dollars, sell them.
- Double?
- Don't be too greedy.
I'll be rich.
I can't believe this bunch of paper
is so valuable.
It's only paper.
Remember, these shares
are in high demand.
Don't tell anyone I gave them to you.
Remember, once they've doubled,
sell immediately.
I'm leaving now.
30,000 shares?
Mr Wong. Mr Wong, sir.
What about the police club?
Oh, that?
It's a good thing
I have one cheque left.
Thanks very much, sir.
Spending more money.
There.
$80,000?
That's too much!
- It's only $65,000.
- That was my last cheque.
The next time I'm in town,
I'll write you another.
I'll rip this one up.
No need, I'll give you the change.
Change?
Where are you going to get $15,000?
I have it.
Can you keep a secret?
I've got some evidence money.
I'll get it for you.
Mr Wong, there's $13,000.
Add my $2,000, that makes $15,000.
Nephew, you are so clever.
Thank you on behalf of the Ho's,
the police and myself.
Thank you, thank you.
Such small things,
unworthy of mention.
Let go.
Till we meet again.
Mr Wong, let me see you out.
There's no need.
Look after your shares.
Don't let anybody see them.
Remember, double.
Double.
Lucky me.
Hey, you, stop!
Me? What's the matter?
Don't move.
Watch him and don't let him go.
I'm a friend of Inspector Ho.
Some friend! Great! Watch him.
So that's that.
Chief Inspector Ho.
What have you been doing?
There are so many missing persons
and you haven't found any!
We've got some leads.
The gang who's doing the kidnapping
is different from the extortion gang.
- What's the difference?
- Well...
Commandant.
Chief Inspector.
- Why didn't you knock?
- It's very urgent.
This discussion is very urgent.
We haven't received any ransom notes.
Fool! Even HQ has heard about this.
Find all the missing persons in three
days or one of us gets fired. See?
Get the car ready!
- Damn him!
- Chief Inspector!
Did you send men to the Ritz?
I did so, sir!
- Remember, you are responsible.
- Understood, sir.
Idiot!
It's me.
- You come in without knocking again?
- It's very urgent.
Urgent? Where have you been all day?
- I went to King's Hotel.
- I didn't tell you to go there.
But I found something out
about Mr Wong.
I tell you do one thing,
you do another. You disobey my orders.
- Hear me out first.
- You don't respect my authority.
But...
Why did you disobey my orders?
Don't you know my boss is after me?
- I know...
- Then why don't you go after them?
I am about to be fired -
and the rest of you, too.
Nobody is looking out for me.
Why are you here?
Obstructing justice.
That's a capital offence!
- Is that true?
- He's crazy.
Any leads on the missing persons?
- No, but we found Mr Wong...
- Nothing?
After all this time?
Idiot! And your mother
asked me to promote you!
Promote you to the heavens.
What's this about Mr Wong, then? Speak!
I found out he's not
one of Shanghai's ten richest men.
He isn't. I suppose you are.
Do you look the part?
Just say who he is. Go on! Go on!
'Bastard!'
Not only is he
one of Shanghai's richest men,
but he's one of the richest men
in all China!
Well done, well done,
that's very good indeed.
I don't need you to tell me that!
Get out!
'I must get away.'
Chief Inspector.
- You still didn't knock?
- Can I take some holiday?
- Holiday?
- Mother is sick.
- Is you father sick, too?
- No.
Get out! Don't ever come back!
- You look down. Was it that bad?
- I'm going on holiday.
Be smart, like me.
I've got some new leads.
Work hard and you'll get there.
Mr Wong, you're still here?
- I'll just see him off.
- Take Mr Wong back to the hotel.
I will, I will.
I'll take him wherever he wants to go.
Bye-bye, Mr Wong. Walk carefully.
Where are you taking me?
I know where I'm going.
I don't know about you.
Chief Inspector!
- Why does nobody knock any more?
- Sorry Chief.
I saw Kuo's men with guns at the Ritz.
Something's up.
Who are they?
Thieves, criminals,
all those on our wanted list.
Then why did you leave?
Get some men over there
and arrest them!
I'll get the warrant.
Why are you standing there?
Give me my hat.
What are you all staring at?
Follow us.
And that's the truth?
Yes. Apparently,
their people are at the Ritz.
What about the two boys we sent?
No news whatsoever.
It backs up what I said.
Kuo did take two of your men.
Why are you doing this?
I just want the killings to stop.
One, two, three, bow.
That was great.
This is a dress rehearsal.
Luming will be Wong.
Make an effort.
I'm Mr Wong. And you are?
I'm Miss Foxy,
the Rotary Chair person.
You're Miss Fox, the Rotary Chair person.
What is this Foxy?
That was my Mandarin.
Stick to Cantonese.
- I'm Mr Wong, and you are?
- I'm the Governor of Hong Kong.
You're not the Governor,
you're the Minister for Transportation.
I want to be Governor.
Why?
If he's Police Commissioner,
I've got to be Governor.
I must be Governor.
Don't take it so seriously.
I must outrank him. I'm the Governor.
He insists on being Governor.
Fine! Let him be Governor, then.
- Run through it again.
- One more time. Please, cooperate.
Boss, Mrs Shun wants to see you.
Once again. One, two, three and bow.
Boss,
the police have surrounded the place.
- Right outside?
- Yes.
What is it?
- The police have us surrounded.
- Police? How come?
They're waiting for Inspector Ho
to come with a warrant.
He must think
we're starting a gang war.
We can't leave and Madam Kao is waiting.
It's nearly time.
Oh, dear,
we'll be found out for sure.
This is bad.
The poor woman.
- What shall we do?
- Search me.
- He's the boss.
Come on, think!
What shall we do?
I'll go to the courthouse
to get Inspector Ho.
- You can't go out. What can you do?
- I don't know.
We'll have to play it by ear.
I'll go out the back way.
- What are you doing?
- The drinks.
Forget that. Go up and practise.
Tell Uncle I'm going to court.
I'll contact him when I meet Ho.
Tell him to wait for me.
Move on.
What are you doing there?
- What should we do?
- Ring Fei.
Push harder.
The boys must be looking for me.
Thanks.
He's gone to the courthouse to get Ho.
- All set?
- Yeah, we know what to do.
What's that?
They found the bodies of your men.
Kuo had them killed.
He killed my men?
Where is he? What's he up to?
He's gone to get Inspector Ho.
For what purpose?
Maybe he's working with the police.
Damn it! Let's go!
I've got to leave now.
I'll look your boss up after this.
- What now?
- I'm hungry.
- Me, too.
- Let's go.
I can't find him anywhere.
There he is. Let's go!
- My leg!
- My hand!
- You broke my pots! Pay up...
- Damn you!
Hold it! Don't run!
We've got you now.
Get ready.
The guests will be here soon.
Make sure there are enough drinks.
I'll see to it. Relax.
Problems?
No, they're rehearsing the entrance.
There's plenty of time. Don't worry.
- Where is he?
- Up there.
- Get him down.
- Bring him down.
Tiger,
sorry for not having tea with you.
Damn it! I liked you.
I promise to have tea with you,
but you've got to let me go now.
It's very urgent.
Let you go?
I sent two boys to invite you to tea.
- You killed them. Why?
- I didn't. I set them free.
Where's my gun?
Didn't you hear what I said?
I didn't kill them. They'll be back soon.
Brother Fei,
tell him I didn't kill them.
But you did.
The bodies have been found.
That's impossible.
Tiger, don't believe him. He's evil.
He's making fools of us both.
He never liked me anyway.
They'll be back soon, believe me.
Where are they, then?
- They must be on their way back.
- To avenge their deaths?
Damn it, don't string me along!
Tiger, believe me.
I didn't kill them!
Tiger! Tiger!
Can you kill me later?
I've got urgent business to attend to.
Shut up! I'll kill you now.
Here they are.
I told you I didn't kill them.
- Why aren't you two dead already?
- Not yet. He saved us.
- He set us free.
- Damn it, you scared me.
Tiger, I told you
I didn't lie to you.
So, you creep,
you want to be the boss?
Tiger, I did it for you.
I would make a much better boss.
There's no way you could be better!
Release him!
Take it easy!
Tiger, I hope you understand.
I did this for your own good.
From now on,
keep out of our family affairs.
Your family affairs! No problem.
I got him. Stop him if you can.
Tiger,
I will certainly have tea with you.
Brother Fei, as you pointed out,
this is a family affair.
Let's go and sort it out.
I've got urgent business, excuse me.
Don't think
you're going to leave here alive.
Tiger.
I won't interfere, but rules are rules.
I'll keep the guns for you.
Canton kid, have no fear.
I'll make sure there's no foul play.
But I might be dead by then.
Get him and the factory is yours.
Get him!
Out of the way!
Brother, you're good.
Stop. I've got to go.
Can we finish this later?
Grab him.
He's over there!
Pull the rope.
Thank you, Buddha!
Don't jump!
I told you not to.
Stop fighting!
Don't go away. It's your turn now.
You were great.
Brother Chen Wah.
You've done one thing right,
the factory hands are behind you.
You can have the factory
and we can be family again.
- Thank you, Chen Wah.
- I've got to go now.
Canton kid, I really admire you.
Your family affair is settled.
We've done our bit. Let's be friends.
I don't have time.
Still thinking of the beating I gave you?
Hit me back, then.
Go on, don't be afraid.
- Stand back!
- Don't move!
Great fistwork.
Canton kid, you fight really well.
Now, go on, slap me.
Good friends we shall be.
Friend, I've got to go now,
urgent business.
If anything happens, count me in.
Count your ass.
What's the hurry?
Shandong man, lend me your car.
- What?
- I'm borrowing your car.
- How was that?
- Perfect, just right.
Chief Inspector, you're wanted.
Inspector Ho.
Go out and keep watch.
Inspector, take your men away.
Inspector, please...
How did you get out?
- Inspector...
- Stand up!
Inspector Ho, please, remove them.
We're doing a good thing at the Ritz.
Putting you lot away
is the good thing.
What are you doing here?
I told you to find the missing men.
Sir...
The Attorney General
just chewed my ass!
From now on, your only job
is to find the missing persons
or you'll go missing!
I know the whereabouts
of the missing persons.
- Who's this?
- The owner of the Ritz.
Is that true?
Four reporters, two businessmen, right?
Yes,
this is why I brought him to see you.
Follow me.
You too.
The missing persons' case is most urgent,
we must deal with it first.
Order them to search the Ritz.
No, they're getting ready
for Madam Kao's party.
It's an order.
The missing are not in the Ritz.
Where are they?
Free my friends and I'll tell you.
First let me make a call.
- I can't...
- If I don't, they won't free them.
Things could get ugly.
- All right, make your call.
- Thank you.
- Hello?
- Luming.
- Tell Uncle to release them.
- The reporters?
Tell Madam Kao we can't come.
Tell the brothers it's all off.
What now? What now?
One more time. Make it better.
There's no need.
Everything's cancelled.
- Why did you kidnap them?
- To keep the secret.
- The secret of your crimes?
- Hold your tongue!
- What secret?
- A lady's secret.
What has she to do with you?
Nothing, really.
I just buy a rose from her every day.
I know nobody will believe me.
We believe you,
but we don't understand the kidnapping.
That's exactly why.
You won't understand.
You see, her daughter has a rich boyfriend,
they've just graduated.
They're getting married here.
This scared the mother,
so she lied about her background.
She's got a heart of gold
and would never lie.
When I arrived in Hong Kong,
she told me to be careful.
A conman had already taken my last cent.
I bought a rose for luck.
You ladies will understand the love
between a mother and her daughter.
So I kidnapped the men,
but they're OK.
I just wanted to help
keep her secret.
- You don't understand, do you?
- Not a word.
We don't know what you're saying.
All right, I'll speak more slowly.
There once was a young flower girl.
No, an old flower lady.
She has a daughter, and...
Dad, the guest...
Sorry, I'll see to Madam Kao.
Why aren't the guests here yet?
The car behind us broke down
and caused an almighty traffic jam.
That's why. They're on their way.
Sorry, we did our best.
I know what I must do.
How do we get out of this mess?
Did you say something?
Mr and Mrs Kao,
what's this all about?
I think...
by now...
you must have realised
something was wrong.
Mum, what's happened?
Everything has a solution.
I know you came to Hong Kong
to look into Belle's background.
You have good reasons for doing so.
Guests or no guests,
we can still have a good time.
Let's go out for some food.
- Come on.
- Let me finish.
Mr Wong.
I hope you appreciate the fact...
that Belle is extremely
important to me.
To make things easier for her...
I've done things
I never dreamed of doing.
Mum, don't be like that.
Tell us everything.
We'll sort it out.
I understand now.
Whatever you do...
you get what you deserve
in this life.
Madam, if it's about the guests,
sorry for the trouble.
I didn't realise it would upset you.
It's not that.
I wish...
my being Madam Kao...
If what you're saying has nothing
to do with the wedding,
there's no need to say it.
Mum, I want you to know
I love Belle whatever happens.
That makes it even more important
for me to say it.
I want you all to know...
I want you all to understand...
Music, music!
- I am not...
- The guests are here!
King's Councillor and Mrs Lo.
Commander of the Volunteers
and Mrs Wong.
Magistrate and Mrs Benjamin.
We meet again.
Marine Commander and Mrs Gordon.
Police Commissioner and Mrs Laughton.
Head of the Boy Scouts McGeorge.
- Attorney General and Mrs Stevens.
- Congratulations.
Chairman of the Jockey Club,
General Morse.
President of the Lions Club,
Mr Chan.
Justice of the Peace and Mrs Chow.
President of the Rotary Club
and Mrs Lee.
Supreme Court Judge and Mrs Nelson.
Railways Director and Mrs Watson.
Postmaster General and Mrs Nitton.
Why are you dressed like that?
The Attorney General lent it to me.
How did you get them to come?
I told them we'd be finished
without them.
Chancellor of the Exchequer
and Mrs Harrison.
Director of Waterworks
and Mrs Johnston.
Public Works Director and Mrs Pearce.
The Chairman of the East India Co
and Mrs Banks.
What a happy night.
You finally did something good
on your own.
I wanted to do it, like everyone else,
but I didn't have the guts.
Why are you crying?
I'm going to the toilet.
Stop crying,
you'll ruin your make-up.
Do I look ugly?
Quick! The ship's about to sail.
"Former Chief Inspector Wanted
for Embezzlement of Police Funds"
You bastard!
Come and see me in Malaysia,
if you dare!
You finally did a good deed.
You played your part.
Come back any time!
Subtitles by
European Captioning Institute