If you only knew
what I just dealt with.
I mean, this guy was right in
front of me, going little...
That guy deserves a ticket.
I'm sure he's...
A-A-A woman never
reveals her age.
I've been in this
relationship for...
He was going ten miles an hour
on the highway.
I'm trying to...
"And only then
will the people of Tajikistan
know true and lasting peace."
Andie, it's brilliant.
It's really moving.
But it's never going to appear
in Composure Magazine.
God, I busted my butt
in grad school
to be Andie Anderson,
"How to" girl,
and write articles like,
"How to Use the Best Pick-Up Lines"
and "Do Blondes, Do They, Like,
Really Have More Fun?"
I want to write about things that matter,
like politics and the environment,
and foreign affairs...
things I'm interested in.
Keep busting your butt.
You're going to get there.
Hey, I've got something
to cheer you up.
You know that editor
from Sports Illustrated
that you have been
shamelessly flirting with
on the phone for... whoo,
a month now?
He made a little delivery
this morning.
Ah, ha, ha, let me see.
Oh, no.
Hey!
Tomorrow night.
What happens tomorrow night?
Only the most exhilarating
and artistic display
of athletic competition
known to mankind.
The Ice Capades are in town?
No, the NBA Finals
are in town,
and I got tickets!
Come with me?
All right, I'll go.
But I am not putting out.
Two stale jumbo dogs
and a couple of beers,
you'll be whistling
a different tune.
You know what I like.
Good morning, ladies.
Don't forget,
staff meeting in 30 minutes.
Michelle... haven't seen
her all morning.
- Have you?
- Ten to one she's wallowing.
It's my turn. I'll get her,
you get the coffee,
meet me in the corner in 20.
Wait, wait, wait.
Here, take some samples.
Samples. Samples.
Great idea.
Oh, boy.
Drama, drama, drama.
Hello, Ben.
Hey, hey, good morning, Spears.
What are you reading, girl?
You catching up on
your current events?
"Turn-On Tricks:
How to Make Him Hot."
You know, if you want
to try those out sometime,
we should get together.
Green and I have
an appointment at Composure,
the fastest growing women's
magazine in the country.
And seeing as how
our clients run a lot
of our campaigns
in their nationally-syndicated
little girlie magazine,
it wouldn't hurt you
to do a little reading.
Hey, Benny.
Good morning, Green.
You finally decided to show up?
Yes, I did.
You ready?
Ready.
Later, Ben.
Have a nice day, ladies.
Hi.
Oh!
Good morning, sunshine.
Okay, get dressed.
Get dressed.
Staff meeting, 15 minutes.
Let's go.
I'm going back to bed.
I have no reason to live.
Sun's out. Oh...
Okay, just...
Okay, now...
Cashmere?
Put it on.
It'll make your eyes
look fiercely green.
Oh!
Get up. I'm not going
to let you lose your job
on top of everything else.
- Oh.
- Come here.
Oh, Andie.
Okay.
You only dated the guy a week.
It was the best week of my life.
Sweetheart.
Good morning, ladies.
- What's up, Tito?
- Hey.
Warren Advertising.
Hi, yes, we're waiting for you.
Good morning.
What's up, kitty cat?
What's up, daddy?
Big night?
- Not bad.
- Orgy?
Where were you, man?
Not at an orgy.
Did you hear?
What, that my Knickerbockers
are now in
the championship series
and Tone "The Bone" here
owes me $20?
Pay him.
Oh, man.
Well, you were right.
DeLauer Diamonds is looking
for a new ad agency.
Warren wants to move
on it aggressively.
Yes!
Oh, oh, this is a good day,
this is a good day.
Guys, did you know
that diamonds are about
as common as taxis
on Fifth Avenue?
The value is entirely
sentimental,
maintained by a supply,
demand and advertising.
Stripes.
Now, DeLauer dominates
the world diamond market.
Meaning if I represent them,
I basically represent
the entire industry.
Tell him.
What?
Warren gave it to the Judys.
Spears and Green...
they're already on it.
No way!
Yeah, well, you know,
he's kind of partial
to hot, leggy chicks
for some reason.
Yeah, and we're the, you know,
the sneakers and beer division.
Precious gems aren't exactly
our forte.
Lips and Hips are over at
a chick's magazine right now.
I got to get to Warren
before they sink...
You can't, you can't.
He's on a plane.
Easy, pal.
The Chicago meeting.
And it's too late anyway,
because Warren's
meeting them for drinks
at Mullins' tonight
to discuss their ideas.
You know what?
This isn't happening.
You know why?
This was my tip.
It's going to be my pitch,
my account, my campaign.
- This is my baby.
- That's what I'm talking about.
They will not ace me
out of this.
- That's right.
- I heard that.
Okay.
Mullins', tonight.
"I heard that"?
Oh.
- Hi.
I-I don't really want
to talk about it, okay?
- Okay.
Okay.
Why does this always happen
to me?
Things were going great
for, like, a week and a half,
and then, all of a sudden,
it's over,
and I am mystified.
Seriously, I am mystified,
because it always starts out
so well.
Poor baby.
Let's just roll with this one.
Oh, Mike and I had
such a connection.
The first time that we had sex,
...it was so beautiful...
I cried.
You cried?
Yeah.
You mean, like,
one glistening tear
on your cheek, right?
No. I was really emotional.
I even told him
that I loved him.
After how many days?
Five.
Two.
It was how I felt.
I wanted to express myself.
Okay, well, what did he say?
Oh, Mike didn't have
to say anything.
I know that he felt the same.
But then he started
getting really busy,
and I didn't know where he was.
So I kept calling him
and calling him.
He was never home...
You kept calling him?
I didn't leave a message.
He didn't know it was me.
My number's blocked.
Oh, I-I'm sure he thought
it was one of his friends.
You know, men frequently call
their friends'
answering machines
and hang up 20 times.
Anyway...
I know why he dumped me:
I'm too fat.
- You're not fat!
Oh, Michelle, if the most
beautiful woman in the world
acted the way you did,
any normal guy
would still go running
in the other direction.
Oh, no. No guy would go
running from you, Andie.
You could barf all over him,
and he would say, "Do it again."
That is both
incredibly disgusting
and categorically untrue.
If I did the things you did,
I'd get dumped, too.
Okay, family,
shoes off.
And breathe.
Out.
Okay, Lori,
let's start with you.
Well, the "Botox for Beginners"
piece is done.
Now, it's a little scary,
but mostly upbeat.
Now I'm on
"What Your Gyno Won't Tell You,"
which is also pretty scary,
but, you know, upbeat.
I finished my research
on deadly pedicures,
about the woman who contracted
that fungus
from the unsterilized tools.
Yeah.
It's a terrible story.
Although, surprisingly...
upbeat!
Marvelous.
What's next for
"'How to' with Andie"?
Well, I've been
working on something
that's kind of different.
It's...
It's a political piece,
and it's...
No.
Andie, you work at
Composure Magazine.
We are fashion,
trends, diets,
cosmetic surgeries,
salacious gossip...
that's Composure.
- Okay, but...
- Look,
Andie, okay...
the column is new for you.
When you turn it
into a must-read,
then you can write
about whatever you want.
Until then, you can write
about whatever I want.
Understood?
Yeah.
Michelle, what have you got?
I'm sorry, Lana,
I wasn't feeling very well...
She got dumped.
Oh, no,
Michelle...
What a hellish ordeal for you.
But I must say,
you are looking fabulous.
Are we loving
the way she looks, all?
- We love the way she looks.
- Oh, you are so right.
She looks great.
Well, I haven't eaten
since the split.
Good for you!
Write about it.
I can't use my personal life
for a story.
I understand completely.
Who will use Michelle's
personal life for a story?
Oh, I will.
- Go.
- No, no, no,
Lana,
with all due respect,
Lori has no business
mucking around
in my personal life,
and I can't...
I can't let her.
- I am...
- I'll do it.
What?
I'll... I will...
I'll sort of do it.
It's... You will be
my inspiration.
For?
Look at Michelle.
- She is a great girl, right?
- Yes.
An amazing woman.
But she has a problem
hanging onto relationships,
and doesn't really know
what she's doing wrong,
which is like a lot
of our readers.
Uh-huh.
So, I was thinking that
I could start by dating a guy,
and then drive him away,
but only using
the classic mistakes
most women, like Michelle,
make...
all the time.
I'll keep a diary of it,
and it will be sort of a...
dating "How to" in reverse.
What not to do.
Yeah.
"How to Lose a Guy in Ten Days."
Yes. Go.
Bart, what's new
in the shoe world?
Wait, wait, Lana, I'm sorry.
Why ten days?
Five days is too short,
and we go to press in 11. Yes?
Okay, what we found out
is men are attracted
to purple shoes.
Now, I love...
Maybe toss in something
spiritual as well.
Who's that chic Buddhist
Richard Gere cavorts with?
The Dalai Lama.
He's fabulous. Ah!
Here's my 10:00. Welcome.
Hi.
Ladies, Judy Spears
and Judy Green
from Warren Advertising.
We're going to cook up
some fabulous tie-ins
for the fall.
Jeannie Ashcroft,
Fashion and Trends.
Michelle Rubin,
Fitness and Health.
Excuse me. Hi.
And Andie Anderson,
our resident "How to" girl.
Oh, I've seen
your column, Andie.
What are you working on now?
Oh, actually...
"How to Lose a Guy in Ten Days."
She's actually going
to start dating a guy,
and then drive him away
in a week and a half.
Sounds needlessly vicious.
It's going to be fabulous.
Now all she has to do
is run along
and find the lucky guy.
Go, go, go.
- Nice to meet you.
- Bye.
Good-bye.
Ladies, come.
Find the guy.
- Okay.
- Find the guy.
Oh, you are never going
to pull this off.
Watch me.
Tonight, I'll hook a guy.
Tomorrow, pull the switch.
Before the ten days are up,
I'm going to have this guy
running for his life.
You're not going to burn
his apartment down
or bite him or anything,
are you?
No! I'm going to limit myself
to doing everything girls
do wrong in relationships.
Basically, everything
we know guys hate.
I'll be clingy, needy...
- Yeah.
- Be touchy-feely.
Ooh, call him in the middle
of the night,
and tell him everything
you had to eat that day.
What's wrong with that?
I'm kidding.
Hello, Ben.
What are you doing here?
Phil, I'm here for
the meeting. Ladies.
But you weren't invited.
Yeah, but I should have been.
I mean, it was my tip
that DeLauer's shopping
for a new firm.
Yes, it was, but I have
to think in terms
of who's best-suited
within the company team.
Yes, sir, and that's me.
I want to handle this pitch.
Ben, you sell Joe Blow better
than anyone else in my shop,
but these girls sell luxury
better than anyone else
in the business.
We have to put our best foot
forward on this pitch.
DeLauer would be
our biggest account.
Yes, sir, they would.
Annual advertising billings
of 50- to $60 million.
And I am the man that's going
to bring this home
for you, Phil.
Why this place?
It's perfect.
Hi, Ingrid.
Hi.
Mullins' is the apres-work
watering hole
for the upwardly mobile.
Now, to date,
the diamond industry
has always targeted men,
sending the message
that the woman needs the man
to buy her the rock.
All right, they say,
"A diamond is forever."
We say,
"A diamond is for everyone."
- I like that.
- Yes
We don't.
"A diamond is for everyone"
sends the message
that diamonds are everywhere,
which means they're not rare,
and if they're not rare,
they lose their status.
Status is the reason
to buy them in the first place,
which Benjamin would know
if he understood women,
which you don't.
You can't feel bad about that, Ben.
No man does.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Oh! Sorry.
Here. Here.
Thanks.
Dum, dum, dum, dum,
dum, dum, dum...
Hey, don't pressure her.
She's perusing.
Yes, exactly. Hmm.
Hmm.
Selling a diamond to a woman
is like making her fall in love.
She has to feel giddy,
desirous, adventurous,
and desperate.
Take a look around
this room, Phillip.
Most of the women in this bar
are looking for just that.
Exactly. The skills required
to market diamonds
are the same as those needed to
make a woman fall in love, yes.
I'm not talking about lust.
A woman in lust
wants chocolate.
A woman in love...
wants diamonds.
Yeah, I'm not talking
about lust, either, ladies.
I'm talking about deep,
meaningful,
head-over-heels,
his and her towels,
let's grow old together,
L-O-V-E.
Look, I love women. I do.
Whether they're four, 40,
or my 88-year-old grandmother,
I respect women, all right?
And I also listen... to women,
and that's why I can sell myself
to any woman, anywhere, anytime.
Make a woman fall in love
with diamonds, Benjamin...
or with you?
Eh, either one.
Well, that's cocky, Ben.
No, not cocky... confident.
I'd like to see you prove that.
You would?
The agency's cohosting
a party for the DeLauers
at the Astor Museum.
The party's a week from Sunday.
Do you think you could make
a woman fall in love with you
by then?
Ten days?
Any woman, anywhere, anytime?
Any single, available,
straight woman... yes.
Yes.
I'm not trying
to trick you, Ben.
In fact, we'll choose
a woman right here,
right now, in this bar,
and then you decide.
Ooh.
So, who's the lucky girl?
Okay...
Let's see here. Ooh,
there's that blonde babe
in the leopard print.
Whoa, ho, ho!
She looks like fun.
Be nice, ladies.
Or... wow,
Miss Babylon Five.
Now, she's on the prowl.
No.
Her.
Her who?
Her, in the gray dress.
Blonde hair. Pretty smile.
Her?
Done.
What?
See the guy next
to the horrible guy
in the green shirt that I would
never even consider? Okay?
- Hmm!
- Very cute.
Right?
- Good.
- All right?
Here I go!
Okay, you're on.
But here are the stakes.
After I win this bet,
this pitch is mine.
Agreed.
- Phil?
- Agreed.
You come to that party
with a girl
that's really in love
with you, Ben...
you can make the pitch
to the DeLauers.
But, Phillip, you can't...
I've made up my mind.
To the DeLauers.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
- Mm-mm.
I was just wondering
if you find...
...exciting?
Yes. My wife and I love
New York,
especially this time of year.
She'd been here before,
and I'd...
- Hi.
This is Andie.
Hi. Um...
Oh!
You guys enjoy New York.
Okay.
Thanks. We will.
Yeah. Nice meet...
nice meeting you.
Eww!
Good luck!
Thank you, Phil.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
ladies...
I have a bet to win.
Ta-ta.
Now do you want to tell
me what's going on?
You don't recognize her?
Hi.
Andie Anderson.
I'm Benjamin Barry.
Cute.
Thank you.
I meant your name.
Thank you two times.
Unattached?
Currently.
Likewise.
Surprising.
Psycho?
Rarely.
Hmm.
Interested?
Perhaps.
Hungry?
Starving.
- Leaving.
- Now?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
One second.
I'll meet you at the door.
Hey, hey, guys.
What?
I think I got one.
He was married.
No, not him. It's the guy by
the door, but don't-don't look.
Oh, guys!
Oh! He is really cute!
I'm going to check this one out
and see if he's the keeper.
Okay.
And if he is?
Tomorrow night, we'll...
Flip the switch.
Doing this for you.
Well, good luck.
Be safe.
Call me.
Mm...
Drama, drama, drama.
No, no, no. This one.
And you get to wear
the goofy-looking helmet.
This won't look goofy on me.
It looks goofy
on just about everybody.
Look at you.
That's pretty damn cute.
There you go.
You ready to go
for a ride, Andie?
Are you ready to go
for a ride, Ben?
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Get it? Get it?
Yeah.
Mmm. So, what do you think?
About the food, or... you?
Both.
This is delicious...
Mm-hmm.
...and I'm still deciding.
Anything I can do to help?
Yeah, you could answer some
questions for me, actually.
"Some" sounds
a little too indefinite.
I'll give you three.
What do you do for a living?
I'm in advertising.
I work mostly
with alcoholic beverage
and athletic equipment
companies,
and I'm trying to break into
the jewelry market right now.
Hmm...
Saving the world,
one keg party at a time?
Yeah, something like that.
What about you?
What about me?
Have I seen your work?
I work at Composure.
Fastest-growing women's
fashion magazine in the country.
I'm impressed.
Saving the world,
one shop-a-holic at a time, eh?
Hey, all right.
Look here, Sparky,
I have a Master's
in journalism
from Columbia.
My boss loves me, and if I do it
her way for a while,
I can write about
anything I want.
Like shoes?
No.
Like alcoholic beverages
and athletic gear.
Touché. Very nice.
So, you think you got me
all figured out, eh?
Almost.
Still got one last question.
Shoot.
True or false:
All's fair in love and war.
True.
Great answer.
Good question.
Welcome.
Oh, nice place.
Thank you.
Very... tidy.
Can I get you
a cold beer?
Sure.
Can I use your restroom?
Yeah, you can.
It's up the stairs,
through the bedroom.
You are, aren't you?
The first night.
I can't believe you!
Michelle, I'm not going
to sleep with him.
Oh, you are such a hussy.
You can't hide
those lying eyes.
No, no, because I can practice
some self-control,
unlike some people I know.
Oh, really?
That hurts, kind of.
I'm going to dangle the bait...
Wait, what's the bait?
I'm the bait, Michelle.
- Oh...
- Yeah.
Okay, I'm with you. Then what?
Mmmm... Diamond
is no one-night stand
A diamond
is a long-term commitment.
Take notes.
You better be prepared...
I can't talk right now.
I have to go.
Call me later, you slut.
Okay. Bye.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Ooh.
Okay.
Hey, hey, let's not go too fast, okay?
Yeah.
We're moving too fast.
I... you're right.
It's-it's too fast.
Okay.
- Too fast.
Yeah.
I want you to respect me.
I do.
Okay.
And I want your respect.
I respect you for respecting me.
I respect that.
Good.
Good night, Andie Anderson.
Oh, you are already
falling in love with me.
I'm going to make you wish
you were dead.
Poor guy.
Of all the women
Spears and Green
could have thrown at me,
this one is amazing.
Hanging with her for ten days
is going to be no problem.
Right, so, it's only
nine days longer
than you've ever spent
with any other chick, huh?
That's why I didn't go
for the gold immediately.
Oh.
I'm taking my time.
It's a marathon, not a sprint.
Ten days is a marathon?
Okay, so it's more like
the 3,000-meter hurdle.
The point is, she's already
on the ropes, guys.
Wow, that-that's a lot
of sports analogies.
That it?
- That-that's it?
- That's it.
Have you looked inside?
No.
Do you have an ethical problem
with rifling through
a woman's purse?
Uh, yeah, I guess I do.
Well, it's hardly a purse, dude.
It's more like a clutch
or something.
Guys, a woman's purse,
all right...
it's her secret source of power.
All right?
There-there are many dark
and dangerous things in there
that we, the male species,
should know nothing about.
Oh. Unless, of course, she, uh,
left it behind intentionally
to secure a next-day call back.
Mm-hmm.
She's a very clever minx.
Oops, I'm sorry.
Oh, God. Um...
Oh, shit,
we got to clean that up.
Yeah, yeah.
Carefully. Carefully.
Oh, what have we here?
Let us see, let us see.
Oh... Knicks tickets...
Huh.
...for tonight's game.
Delivery, Andie.
Wow, look at those!
Oh, who are those for?
Andie,
oh, my God!
Where do you want these?
Who are these to?
Wait. "100 times..."
...more beautiful..."
Wait.
"...than 100 roses."
Catchy.
The guy's in advertising.
He can't help it.
So, does this mean he's hooked?
This means he found
the Knicks tickets.
You left the tickets
in the purse?
Yeah.
You are just on a whole
different playing field.
Here you go.
Mm-hmm.
Andie Anderson.
Hey, hey, pretty girl.
Guess what?
I got a really embarrassing
display of white roses.
Well, you are welcome.
Listen, I had a wonderful time
last night.
I have your bag.
Ah, I know.
I can't believe I left it there.
Yeah, well, you must need it back,
what with all the cash,
credit cards, and...
those Knicks tickets
for tonight's game.
Sounds like you've been
peeking through my bag, Ben.
Oh, absolutely not.
Tony, my Art Director,
he's an oaf,
and he accidentally
knocked it over.
Ow, right!
Yeah, I'm a clumsy man.
All right, I'm sorry, though.
I'm going to the game
with somebody else.
Not anymore.
Besides, what?
You think you left your purse
at my place by accident?
No. Subconsciously,
you are dying
to take me to that game.
Denying your subconscious desires
is extremely dangerous
to your health, young lady.
Does that psycho-babble
really work on anybody?
You tell me.
Andie, you're so bad.
All right, meet me
at the 7th Avenue entrance.
7:30. Don't be late.
You got it. Bye-bye.
Bye.
And that's how it's done.
Foul on Number 20,
Allan Houston.
Bullshit. Come on, ref!
What is that, ref?
Hey, if you're going to call it,
call it both ways!
Oh, you're soft, man!
You were soft last year,
and you're still soft.
And he's 85% on the line
all year, too.
What was that?
There we go.
One more left. All right.
Come on, bud.
Defense!
Oh, oh, oh!
That's off!
Defense!
Knicks call. 20 second time out.
All right, take your five.
Take a minute...
This is all right.
Got 20 seconds.
20 second team.
Knicks' ball.
- Whoo!
- Bring it back.
Charge!
Work your arm, baby.
Go, baby.
Hold 'em up!
Charge!
Benny?
Hold 'em up!
Work it, work it. Yeah?
Benny, I'm kind
of thirsty.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, okay.
- Yeah, yeah!
- Benny, could you get me a soda?
Yeah, just let me
tell you right now...
I'm parched.
...there's a minute and nine
left in the game,
- and then I'll go up and get it.
- I'm really thirsty.
I'll go get it.
Hey, hey, hey. You want...
you want it right now?
Yeah.
And no ice, Ben.
Thanks, Benny.
Lawrence Funderburke.
Oh, man!
Here's Sprewell with a fake.
Gets the step on Christie.
What a crossover...
Whoo, my man.
Coke, no ice.
Next line over, pal.
No ice. Hey, buddy?
Small coke, no ice.
Okay, you got it.
...beyond the three-point line, fires!
Ah... no!
Man, don't let him have that shot!
No. Does that mean no, you don't want ice,
or no, you want ice?
No. No ice.
Coke, no ice.
And Don Chaney
wants to talk it over...
Oh, did you want a small?
No, I-I want that one
right there.
You know, for 25 cents more,
you could get a jumbo?
Okay, you take that right there.
Keep the change.
All right.
Charge!
Excuse me.
Ah...
Come on! Score!
Come on, baby,
drive into the net!
Right there, right there.
Oh, thanks!
Hey, hold him, hold him.
Move it.
Set your pick! Watch
the three seconds! Traveling!
Ben, it's not diet.
- Huh? What?
- Ben, it's not diet.
Please, I'm so thirsty.
- All right, all right.
- With a lime.
- All right, okay, I got it.
- With a lime. Okay.
Shoot it!
Sprewell for the win!
Yes!
That was Sprewell!
It's all over!
The Knicks
have defeated the Kings
in the final seconds...
...Sprewell with
the game-winning shot,
and the Knicks over Sacramento:
97 to 96.
Oh, what an incredible game.
I've never seen a more exciting
game-ending play before.
Wow, well, neither have I.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's too bad you missed it.
Yep, it's too bad.
One second.
So...
you as nice as you seem, Ben?
No.
Good. Neither am I.
Oh, here.
Fifth and 12th, please.
See you later.
Horseshit.
More horseshit.
The horseshit continues.
Horseshit. Come on, people.
We've got to do a lot better
than this
if we're going to com...
What?!
There's a phone call
for Mr. Barry.
Yeah, can you take a message, Candi?
Uh, Mr. Barry, it's Andie.
- Make it quick.
- I will.
It's line two, Mr. Barry.
Thank you.
Hello.
It's me!
Listen, I'm in the middle
of a meeting.
Can I call you back
in just a minute?
I miss you,
Benny boo-boo,
boo-boo-boo.
Well, you know what?
I miss you, too.
Mm-hmm.
You busy tonight?
Uh, no. No, I'm not.
Why don't we catch a movie
or somethin'?
A movie... my choice?!
Your choice.
Oh, I'm so excited!
Okay. I'll call you later.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
Jonah!
Dad!
I always wanted a man
like Tom Hanks.
It's my favorite movie
of all time.
Yeah, me, too.
Shh!
What if something
happened to you?
What if I couldn't get to you?
What are you thinking about?
Nothing. I'm watching the movie.
Yeah, but what's on your mind?
Shh!
I like this movie.
Oh, so I suppose your mind
is a complete blank.
You are my family,
you're all I have.
Who is she?
Shh!
Who's who?
The girl you're thinking about.
Can't hear.
- I'm not thinking about a girl.
- Aah!
You can't watch Meg Ryan
- for two hours
- Shh!
And not be thinking
about another girl.
Uh...
You want to know what
I'm thinking about?
Yes.
I'm sitting here thinking
about how damn beautiful
you are.
That's what I'm thinking about.
Come on, let's watch this movie,
it's good.
Aww...
Benji.
Oh, sweetie!
I love sharing this with you.
Yeah.
Can't hear and can't see.
If you don't shut up,
my boyfriend over here
is going to come back there
and pummel your ass.
Put a muzzle on your old lady
the next time
you bring her out in public.
What?!
What is that?!
Do something about...
- You, outside.
- Shh!
Keep it down!
I mean, have a little class,
all right?
You want to talk like that to me,
we can work it out,
but not to a lady, all right?
Ben, Ben, B-B-Ben, he's huge.
I got it. I'm not looking to get
in a fight with the guy, okay?
He owes you an apology.
Oh! Oh, whoa!
Now, I'm going to go
back inside,
and finish watching
Sleepless in Seattle.
Nobody screw with me.
Son of a... bitch.
- Oh, Ben.
- Aah!
Are you okay?
- Oh...
- Ben,
- Ben, Ben,
- Ow, ah-ah-ah. Yes?
Maybe we should
get you to a hospital.
No. No, no, no, no.
No, you could have a...
Excuse me!
Uh-uh-uh, hey, hey,
can you hold still,
right there, hold still?
Okay, I'm sor...
Oh, ooh... oh.
Oh, yeah.
That's feeling real nice.
Ben... Ben...
I'm starting to feel
a little better.
Ben...
Ben!
Oh, my God!
You're fine.
Oh, you are totally fine.
Okay, come on, Rocky.
No, no...
Get up.
- Ouch.
- Huh?
Yeah.
Hey, don't feel bad.
If I had a nickel for every time
I got in a fist fight
during a chick flick, whoo!
Uh-huh, right.
It really wasn't that bad.
Really?
No. I mean, the getting punched
in the face part sucked, right?
Well...
But the getting taken care of
after the punch... it was nice.
All right! Florence
Nightingale syndrome, yeah.
You want me to tape the game
for you tonight?
No need, my friend.
I'll be watching the Knicks
from the comfort of my
own home this evening.
- How'd you swing that?
- Oh, yeah.
What's good to grill?
- No.
- Heavyweight.
You're making the lamb.
Voila.
A woman loves a man
who can cook, yeah?
Bringing out the big guns.
- Let's go deep.
- I like it.
Why do they always
forget my bacon?
I can't believe
you got that guy knocked out.
Only for a few seconds.
He was the most adorable,
unconscious man ever. Mm-hmm.
Are you dating him, or are you
contemplating adoption?
Andie, I am loving
your notes on this piece.
Thank you, Lana.
When are you seeing him again?
Tonight.
He's invited me over for dinner.
Marvelous.
I've got a feeling about this one.
Thanks, Lana.
I hate it when she pops
her head in like that.
Ahem!
I never noticed it.
I heard that.
And Andie, tonight,
take smaller bites.
Oh, my God!
Disgusting.
I can barely eat over here.
Come on in. Door's open.
- Hi.
- Hey, there.
I hope you brought
your appetite, girl.
Whew.
We got a feast tonight.
Benny isn't that sweet?
Go on and pour yourself
a glass of wine.
We got diner in about five
and tip-off in about eight.
Great. I'm starving.
So perfectly pink!
Pour la piece de résistance.
Ah...
Sheryl, Tori,
Sinead, Jewel, Fiona, Carly...
gang's all here!
Great.
Got two minutes to game time.
You walked into the party
Like you were walking
onto a yacht
Your hat strategically dipped
below one eye
Your scarf... it was apricot
Wow. Look at all this stuff.
- You had one eye in the mirror as
- Those are cute and...
...you watched
- I saw the...
- Yourself gavotte
- the new comforter.
And all the girls dreamed that
They'd be Ben's partner,
they'd be Ben's partner
What you got in the box?
Oh.
It's a baby fern.
Really? Oh, yeah?
Just like our relationship.
A helpless little baby
in need of tender loving care.
Thank you.
Sit down.
Have a seat.
Ready?
Game two. Welcome to
the front row, madam.
Oh, oh. Here.
Mm-mm-mm, mm-hmm.
Dinner is served.
Chef's special tonight.
Lamb with a cherry glaze.
Start you off
with the main dish
right about there.
A few carrots.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hey, hey.
You okay?
It's beautiful.
Thanks.
You're beautiful.
The game, the whole thing.
I wish I ate meat.
Mary had a little lamb
Little lamb...
You have to take it away
before I gag.
This stuff's for cows.
- Hi.
How you doing?
Oh, aw, it's just
a little indigestion.
- You okay?
- Mm-hmm.
All right.
Uh, excuse me, m'am?
Do you happen to know the
score of the Knicks game?
Do I look like
the kind of person
who knows the score
of a Knicks game?
No, you don't.
Is something wrong
with the barley?
No, no.
My boyfriend thinks I'm fat!
And I can't eat
in front of him!
I can't eat in front of you!
- I have to go to the bathroom.
- I don't think you're...
I don't think you're fat.
I don't think she's fat.
What's happening?
Spre just turned up;
23 seconds left.
Knicks' ball.
Get the ball, man.
Oh, come on!
Throw it!
Oh! That was in!
- Oh, man!
- Oh...
Come on, get it back.
Come on.
Get the ball back,
get the ball back!
Jackson takes the ball.
A spin by Jackson.
- Get it back!
- No!
Damn!
And the time has run out.
- Damn!
- Pick up!
The Kings have beaten
the Knicks.
Their first win in the series.
Next game.
Well, that was fun.
Okay. 11:25.
Sports.
Ah, there we are.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
Then it's Mark Jackson with
a no-look pass to Kirk Thomas...
Sorry we missed the game.
Post, post. Reverse it!
30 seconds left in the game,
Sprewell...
There we go, baby!
Oh, I can't believe
he missed that shot.
Take it, take it!
- 12 seconds left, the game...
- Pitch! Aah!
How the hell did you know
he was going to miss that shot?
...with a narrow Monroe move.
He always misses... the shot
...the way it ended...
- from the top of the key.
...as the Knicks
could not get off another shot.
Aah, man.
Houston never misses
from the top of the key.
Oh!
- Whoa.
- Mmm...
Does Princess Sophia
want to come out and play?
Who's Princess Sophia?
- No, no, no, no... no!
- Ow!
Aw, yo-yo-yo-you...
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
y-you're kidding me, right?
Princess Sophia?
Little, big, little,
big, I don't know.
We will find out!
Ah, you know,
hang on a second.
Ah, no, no.
All right, listen.
You can't name my... my member
Princess Sophia.
It doesn't...
Yes, I can.
Listen. L-L-Listen to me.
If-lf you're going to name...
my member, all right,
you got to name it something
hyper-masculine, okay?
Something like Spike or Butch,
or Krull, the Warrior King,
but not Princess Sophia.
What did you just say?
Spike.
You know what I mean?
No, no, after Spike.
Butch.
After Butch.
Krull... Krull,
the Warrior King.
Does Kr-rull, the Warrior King
want to come out and play?
- Oh, come on...
- No.
...Krull.
You know what?
Due to...
intense humiliation,
the King has...
momentarily abdicated
his throne.
- Okay?
- Oh, uh-oh!
Yeah.
Well, in that case...
I'd better get going.
Take care of our love fern, honey.
Hi. Mm.
Can I see you tomorrow?
Really?
I hope so.
Call me.
I will.
And I'll call you.
Sweet dreams.
Answer your phone!
What?
What was "icy" again?
"Arctic, freezing, frigid."
How about "glitter"?
Thayer's favorite movie.
It was underrated.
Huh?
"Glint, glisten,
scintillation."
"Scintillation..."
that's not bad.
Aw, that sucks.
Guys, let's take a break.
Huh? A little coffee
and nine-ball.
Shake it out.
Maybe I'll be able
to concentrate
since the woman
is driving me crazy.
Which woman...
Andie, or Princess Sophia?
- Ah!
- Uh-huh.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Wait a second.
I thought you said
after the Knicks game
that she was a goddess.
Oh, she was. That was
the good Andie, guys.
This amazing, fun,
cool, sexy woman.
I'm talking
about the evil Andie, now.
It's like a...
it's like a crack-enhanced
Kathie Lee Gifford.
She... she's
probably bipolar.
Well, her South Pole's
definitely prevailing.
Well, all you gotta do
is rock it for five more days.
Muffin!
Which shouldn't be
too difficult.
- Hi!
- Andie!
- My little muffin.
- Hey, sweetie.
We were just talking about you.
- Hi.
- Hello, there.
How are you?
You look gorgeous.
Oh, thank you.
Andie, this is Tony,
and this is Thayer.
- Oh, yes.
- Hey.
Benny Wenny's told me
so much about you two.
Oh, well, Benny Wenny's said
wonderful things about you, too.
Oh...
Oh, they don't look
so simple-minded.
Honey,
Hmm?
Look what
I got for us. Oh.
Look at that.
Oh, wow!
- Ooh!
- Look at him go. What is it?
Jumper.
It's a Chinese Crested,
of course.
No kidding.
- A Chinese Crested.
- Mm.
So, it-it's like a dog, right?
Oh, hey.
There he is.
Ooh, Ben. Ben.
You got a dog.
You're hurting Krull's feelings.
Krull, is it?
Krull. Krull, the Warrior King.
Well, sure, 'cause
that's clearly what... Yeah.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh, wait, there's more.
What do you got there?
Oh, nice.
- For me?
- Mm-hmm.
- Get out of town.
- Try it on.
That's like the...
inside of a raincoat.
- Medium. Oh, yeah.
- It matches! Try it on.
Now, that is going to fit
nicely, sweetie, thank you.
No, Ben, put it on.
No, you should try
it on. Otherwise,
you don't know if it's
going to fit or...
Oh, go for it.
That has never hurt anybody.
Huh? Huh?
I was just gonna save it
for a better occasion,
all right?
Check that out.
Oh, yeah, that's nice.
- Hey.
- Hmm?
You're a vision in khaki.
It's going to be
a happy little family,
Just the three of us.
We are, aren't we?
Wow.
He's our boy, Ben.
Oh, see, that's sweet.
Mm-hmm, hey, mm-hmm.
Whoa, ho, ho, ho,
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Andie, hey, it's good
to see you, too, sweetie.
Ah, I got you.
Gotcha, gotcha, gotcha.
Gotcha, gotcha,
gotcha, gotcha.
Oh...
He's just
not potty-trained yet.
- Whoa!
- Oh!
Okay, well, he's a pisser.
Come here, little tinkle king.
No, no, no.
Come here, tinkle king.
- He is a tinkle king.
- Oh, yeah.
Who's my little tinkler?
You tinkle tinkles.
Well, congratulations,
little plaid family.
We, you know,
we got a whole bunch
of work we got to do,
but we're...
we're still on for poker
at your house this weekend?
- Oh, you count on it.
- Whoo! Boys' night.
- Yeah.
- Whoo!
Yeah, it was nice meeting you,
Nice to meet you.
And, of course, Krull.
- Bye. Say bye, Krullie.
- All right.
A little soap and water
will take that out.
He goes, "Woof, woof."
Yeah, thank you, buds.
Oh, come here. Ooh.
Do you love him?
Oh, I do.
Oh, look at Krull's necklace.
He's got more ice than
Liberace, don't you?
Oh, it's just a little frosting.
Frosting?
Frosting.
We were thinking bold,
new, fresh.
"Frost yourself."
Excuse me?
"Frost yourself..."
The slogan for the campaign.
You frost a cake.
We're in the middle
of a meeting, Benjamin.
I'm talking about diamonds.
They're frosting.
As in, "Whoa, would you
check out her frosting?"
- Frost yourself.
How did you come up with it?
I got it off the woman
who is falling
madly in love with me.
Oh...
It may have possibilities,
but as far as the woman who's
falling madly in love with you,
I will decide that at the party.
If he can get her there.
Now, just think about it...
ladies, frost yourself.
Frost yourself.
Mm-hmm. We could introduce it
at the party.
It-lt should be the theme.
Yes.
Everything frosted.
- All of it.
- Martini glasses.
Chandeliers.
Ah, jewels everywhere.
The women.
The whole party...
a sparkling diamond.
All of it frosted.
Women of New York!
Frost yourselves!
Hey, frost this!
Well, I like it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, I hear you.
You have 17 new messages.
Message one. Received at 5:44.
Oh. Sit down. Sit.
Hi, sweetie pea. It's me.
Where are you?
I'm not home.
Received at 5:47.
Benny, it's Andie.
Guess you're not home.
Three. Received at 5:48.
Benny Bear, are you not
answering your phone?
Yeah, I am.
Four. Received at 5:49.
Hey, buddy.
Game three tonight. Blondie's.
Don't be late
or I will kill you.
Who is it?!
It's me.
Five. Received at 5:52.
Ah!
Ow!
What a surprise.
Tried to get ahold of you.
Yeah?
I did something kind of wacky.
Eh?
Yes. I used Photoshop
at work today
to composite our faces together
to see what our kids
would look like.
Our... Family... Album!
You don't want
to see our children?
We don't have...
children.
I hate you.
You know what?
I'm sorry. No, no, no.
I didn't mean it
like that, all right?
I... Show me, show me,
show me, show me.
Please show me.
We don't have children!
Oh, I thought you meant...
Krull.
I just want to...
Will you show them to me?
You don't want to see them.
I do. Please, please
show them to me.
I really do
want to see them.
Really?
Yeah.
Okay.
Oh, that's our wedding.
And this is our first child...
Benny, Jr.
Yeah.
Oh, there's us
vacationing in Hawaii.
Little Andie's
on my shoulders
and dum-da-da-dah,
Benjamin, Jr. On yours.
Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's little Andie.
Oh, there are the kids
in Switzerland,
yodel-odel-ing.
Our kids are really...
attractive.
Yeah!
Ah, hey, Mom.
Ah, yeah, I'm-I'm doing fine.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, she is.
Just a second.
It's for you.
Oh, great.
Hey, Glenda.
Why is my mom
calling you?
Shh.
I just showed him.
Yeah, well, he
thinks our children
will be very attractive.
Oh, no.
All right,
you go back to cooking.
Call me later.
Tomorrow. Yeah, great.
Okay, Glenda.
Love you, too. Bye.
Thanks, honey.
Yeah.
So you and my mom,
you talk, huh?
Yeah, I called
her to get some
baby pictures of
you for our book.
Hey, you never told me...
that you wore diapers
till you were five.
You know what, honey,
I got to go to the...
Uh-oh.
Ah, no,
come on, man.
You think maybe he thinks
the felt is grass?
Oh...
Oh, man.
Oh!
Ah... Ah... No, no,
No, man! Come on!
Hey, Benny Bear?
Hey!
Do you have plans tonight?
Tonight?
I have another surprise for you.
Ah... you know what?
Not a good night for me.
I-I, I gotta work.
- Of all things.
- Oh, no.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
We got a Knicks game on.
I had a broccoli-
and-asparagus casserole
planned for you and me,
right there in front of the TV,
and we're not going to be able
to do that either,
'cause I got to go in to work.
That's too bad, 'cause
I had tickets for tonight.
Tickets?