A co-production of
Golden Harvest Presentation
and Johnny Mak Production Ltd.
The lceman Cometh
ln the 5th year of Chong Zhen's reign,
the Ming Dynasty.
Co-producers: Raymond Chow
and Johnny Mak.
Producer: Stephen Siu
Scriptwriters: Stephen Siu
and Johnny Mak
Director of Photography: Poon Hang Sang
Photographers: Wong Chi Wai,
Bao Hei Ming, Ko Kwok Wah
Lam Kwok Wah and Ma Cho Sing
Production Manager: Lok Yi Ling
Film Making Manager: Wong Hiew
Film Maker: Lorraine Ho
Action Choreographer: Yuen Brothers
Yuen Wah, Yuen Tak, Tsin Ga Lok
Cast: Yuen Biao
Yuen Wah and Maggie Cheung
Director: Clarence Fok
Princess!
How dare Fung San
rape and murder Princess Nan Cheong!
Nan Cheong was of noble blood
and she was my cousin.
How could she be raped
by a degenerate?
How am l to face my ancestors?
Please look after yourself, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
as the Chief Royal Guard
it is Fong Sau Ching's duty
to patrol the Royal City,
but he colluded
in his brother Fung San's crime.
l beg Your Majesty to punish
Fong Sau Ching according to our law.
l didn't collude
in Fung San's crime.
However, Fung San is cunning
and highly skilled in martial arts.
No more nonsense from you!
l must have your family killed
and have you beheaded
at the market entrance!
Your Majesty, please spare me!
- Wait...
- Wait.
Wait.
Since you have been
loyal to me for years...
l will give you a chance
to redeem your guilt.
You have 20 days to capture Fung San.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
l will capture Fung San in 20 days
to thank Your Majesty
for sparing my life. l am leaving.
l salute you, our master's brother.
Master's brother!
Are you all right?
lt was the traitor Fung San
who did this to me.
Why did he hit you so hard?
Fung San sneaked in the night before last
to try to steal the black jade Buddha.
l found out and we started to fight.
l was hit
and he stole the black jade Buddha.
Why did he steal
the black jade Buddha?
According to the Buddhist scriptures,
after Buddha achieved enlightenment,
the devil went to Buddha and said,
''l want to follow Buddha's path.''
''However, l am full of sin.
Can l still achieve enlightenment?''
Buddha worked a miracle
and devised the Wheel of Life and Death.
The devil sat on it
and held the black jade Buddha tightly,
while saying the Buddhist prayer.
The devil went through the process of
rebirth and death 100 times in an instant.
To go through rebirth and death
100 times in an instant?
Fung San has reached the end of the road.
Does he believe in this myth
and wish to use the black jade Buddha
to transport him to another time?
But transition is impossible without
the Wheel of Life and Death, isn't it?
The Tibetan ambassador has just entered
the city to present the gifts of tribute,
and one of the gifts
is the Wheel of Life and Death.
ln seven days at midnight it will be the
time to achieve Buddhist enlightenment.
l must stop him!
Fung San, you can't escape.
Surrender now.
Stupid dog, you've come too late!
Fung San.
Stupid dog,
are you blind and without a brain?
Don't you know l'm the older brother?
The first of the ten rules
in our monastery is not to rape.
You raped and murdered
1 3 young women.
Why have you become like this?
Stupid dog, we started practising
martial arts when we were five years old,
from dawn before the rooster crowed
until midnight every day.
lt was an intolerable life.
l've practised martial arts for 25 years.
A whole 25 years!
l've finally mastered
the undefeatable martial art.
Now that l've reached perfection,
it's time to indulge myself to the full.
Raping and murdering women
excites and delights me!
You've lost your soul.
You've gone mad!
l tear my robe and our relationship
is at an end from today.
Our brotherhood has now ceased.
Your Majesty, although l can't bring
Fung San back to the city for punishment,
killing him at least
means l have fulfilled my duty.
But your servant will also perish today.
l will no longer
be able to serve Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
please look after your precious self.
University of Qing Hua,
Research Team for the Northern Region.
There's been an accident over there!
- Over there, over there!
- Go and save him!
- Quick, over there.
- Quick, quick!
- Hurry.
- He's there, he's there...
- Get the medicine, get the medicine!
- Drag him out of there!
- Be careful.
- Be gentle with him.
- ls there any medicine?
- He's fine.
Pass it over.
lt's all right. lt's all right now.
lt's showing now.
Visual Analysis System
This is such a great discovery.
This proves homosexuality existed
even in ancient times.
And that AlDS existed
a very long time ago?
- Goddamn it, stop talking nonsense.
- Yes, yes.
ln 1887, the lnstitute
of Bioresearch Centre in Sweden
resuscitated a frog
which had been frozen for a century.
ln 1 985, a university successfully
germinated a lotus seed
which had been frozen
for 20 million years.
Therefore, in theory,
the two ancient corpses
may be restored to life
by using electrodes to revive them.
Stop talking nonsense.
The bodies are being kept
at minus 10 degrees.
Attempting to revive them
means defrosting them.
lf the attempt fails,
the bodies will start to decompose.
We can't risk that.
l suggest we send the bodies to the US.
They have advanced equipment there.
- What do you think?
- Yes, yes.
And, of course, we should all go there
to conduct the experiment.
lt's a golden opportunity to apply
for research funding to go abroad.
- True.
- l've got to go.
Are you Li Pang, trying to escape
because you've killed so many people?
Chai Ling is your student.
You're the one who wants to flee.
Stop talking nonsense.
There's no hope for our country.
We should all go together.
Watch out - if 27th Army hear us,
they'll send tanks here to suppress us.
You can all relax.
l expressed my support
for the Central Government from the start.
We're experts at telling lies,
isn't that right?
No one will ever suspect me.
We can say the transport
of the corpses to the US
is an excuse
to capture the student leader Wuer Kaixi.
Carry on teaching that the government
loves its people very much.
That son of a bitch Li Pang
will certainly allow us to go abroad.
What a great speech!
lf we can find
an excuse to go via Hong Kong,
we could visit Club Boss or
The Volvo Club. That would be ideal.
- What do you think?
- l couldn't agree more.
What he said wasn't nonsense, not at all.
Here's your car.
Fat Bull,
don't you have any brains?
How can we fit all the stuff
in such a small car?
The boss is having a party tonight.
We've got to take everything in there!
l didn't know that. l can fetch a bigger car
or l can make another trip.
Start working!
Which is more expensive,
frozen prawns or abalones?
Are you stupid? Take whatever you see.
- What the hell is it?
- lt says ''National treasure''.
- How mysterious.
- Let's check it out.
We'll be executed if we steal
something of national importance.
l didn't say l wanted to steal it.
l'm just nosy and want a peep.
Get some tools to open it.
What a huge refrigerator.
Why is this in here?
What is this?
Don't you know anything?
This is called a Terracotta Warrior.
lt can't be.
Terracotta is made of ceramic clay.
lt doesn't have to be in a fridge.
Then may l have your opinion
on what it might be?
A corpse!
Oh, no!
Sounds like the boss's son is back!
He should be at the party.
That short-arse is so sly.
He even comes back to check on us.
Thank God we're smart,
or we'd be caught.
You scared me to death!
- What happened?
- Yes...
There are two possibilities.
The corpse was stolen by someone,
or the corpse has come back to life!
Shit, now that the corpses have vanished,
we'll be executed!
What shall we do?
Don't you have a brain?
Think of a way.
l have a way.
lt's horrific here.
Could this be hell?
Why are there so many monsters?
Why are my skills impaired?
- lt's cold...
- Who's that?
Who's this?
My friend, are you a newcomer?
Here for a handout?
- lf so, get to the back of the queue.
- Yes, get to the back.
The church workers are coming.
Merry Christmas! Merry Christmas!
We haven't eaten for days
and we're dying of hunger.
Merry Christmas
and a happy New Year.
- Good health...
- Thank you.
Good luck with your school results.
Merry Christmas.
- A Christmas present. Good health to you.
- Thank you.
That's for you.
My dear brothers, where am l?
- Kowloon City.
- Kowloon City?
Where is Kowloon City?
- lt's in Kowloon.
- And where is Kowloon?
lt's in Hong Kong.
So where is Hong Kong?
lt's in Asia.
Asia? l don't know any of these places.
- But do you know Peking?
- Peking? Of course we know Peking.
How long will it take to walk there?
l think probably a year.
Was l taken to the land of the barbarians
while l was unconscious?
This guy is a nutter.
We have to watch what we say.
My dear brother,
what did you do for a living?
l was the Chief Royal Guard
of the palace.
And may l ask who you are?
He is the East Factory Chief.
He's a eunuch.
Nice to meet you.
He's a eunuch?
He wasn't castrated!
- And who are you?
- l am the great emperor.
How dare you!
lt is sacrilegious to pretend
to be the emperor. l'll behead you!
Wait, wait.
Chief Royal Guard, l am innocent.
Please read my paper.
Please submit it to the emperor.
HlSTORY OF CHlNA
What are you doing?
Sister, it is very brave of you
to take on other people's debt.
But a debt is a debt after all,
and you must pay off some today
no matter what,
or l'll have no explanation
to give Big Brother.
Don't say another word, you moron.
l don't have any money now.
Kill me if you want.
lf not, let's talk after the New Year.
Don't say l'm not giving you a chance.
l have a customer
who wants some excitement
and wants you to pretend
to be raped in a car.
Are you crazy?
l'm a model, not a hooker.
Model, my arse. The customer
is paying $5,000. A fat $5,000!
No way. l won't work for a psychopath,
no matter how much he pays me.
You dare touch me?
Show her the present.
So you have some circus tricks?
- No, l won't do it.
- What do you mean? What's this?
Ask him to take his mask off.
Boss, would you take off the mask?
Be happy.
Go to hell!
Hey!
Damn it.
Tie.
Hurry up.
A deviant?
You masked pervert!
Traitor! You dare speak
in a foreign tongue? Go to hell!
Help!
Miss, are you all right?
Who are you?
They didn't say anything about you.
Boss! Boss! What happened?
Hey!
My dear brothers, can l help?
Can you help?
Big brother, that was really cool!
Get him! Get him!
Miss, it's all quiet again now.
Who the hell are you?
Why did you interfere?
Miss, l preserved your honour.
Why are you reproaching me?
A sister owed them money
and vanished.
l'm her guarantor, so l have to satisfy him.
Do you understand?
So it's forced prostitution.
Miss, you are an extraordinary person.
You sacrificed yourself.
You are brave and courageous.
l salute you.
l don't care. You've ruined this. You must
explain to Big Brother tomorrow.
No problem. l am a man of dignity
and will take the responsibility.
- l shall leave now.
- Wait. Give me your pager number.
- What?
- How do l find you tomorrow?
l've only just come to this place.
l don't have a place to sleep.
Hey, give me your lD card.
- lD card?
- You're an illegal immigrant, huh?
Don't think this is over, bitch.
l'll spray you with acid one of these days.
You dare threaten me with acid?
You son of a bitch!
Follow me home.
Brothers, you'll be fine in an hour.
See you another time.
Come in and stop acting like a thief.
Leave your stinking clothes over there
in case they stink out the whole flat.
Crazy.
How magical.
Hey, Mr lllegal, what are you doing?
- Can you tell me about this light?
- Electric lights.
- Which village are you from?
- l'm from Ji village of Shanxi Province.
- Never heard of it.
- May l ask where you come from?
- Tsim Sha Tsui.
- Tsim Sha Tsui...
Miss, we use oil for lights in my village.
My dear warrior,
we use electricity for lights.
Electricity for lights?
Does it come from thunder and lightning?
That's correct.
A giant power plant
collects the electricity,
l push a switch, through the electric wires
and here we have light.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, l entirely understand.
Do you really? Don't pretend.
Men and women shouldn't touch.
Damn you!
Did your enemies ransack your home?
l've been busy working
and haven't had a chance to tidy up.
l've never seen a woman's room
look as chaotic as this.
How dare you insult me!
l'll hit you!
Yes?
You've got the wrong number, bitch.
You're the bitch!
What is this thing?
Are you winding me up?
Haven't you seen a telephone before?
You can play with it.
Sister, the Japanese customer has arrived.
Come if you need money.
You've got the wrong number, bitch.
You're the bitch!
You're a fast learner.
You flatter me.
Miss, now what's this?
This is an electric kettle.
lt's for boiling water.
l see, it's an electric kettle.
And what about the small house
that took us up here?
lt was the lift.
Lift, electric light, electric wires,
electric kettle, telephone...
Electric chair?
Damn you.
Stop laughing. Are you an idiot?
You'll get the electric chair, not me!
Miss, may l ask...
How are you, handsome?
How are you, miss?
Come close to me, handsome.
What for?
l'm lonely. Come and hold me.
Watch yourself!
Men and women shouldn't touch.
l, Fong Sau Ching, am a man of dignity.
l will not submit to seduction.
Get away from me, evil woman!
- Let's see how far you'll go.
- l was only joking!
Stop it, you bad boy...
You degenerate!
Stop this immediately or l'll kill you!
- Don't kill it!
- Get away!
Where's he gone?
- Where are those two people?
- Who do you mean?
- This is just a picture screen.
- Picture?
A picture that can move?
How can it look so real?
- Magical pictures?
- Magical pictures? Don't be silly.
lt's acting. You must have it
in your village. lt's like Chinese opera.
People filmed it with a machine
and use the wires
to send the picture into this box,
then show it to us.
This thing is called television.
- Do you understand now?
- Yes, l understand entirely.
Mister, how long's it been
since you had a wash?
You really stink. Have a bath now.
Miss, please respect yourself.
Respect, my arse. Go and have a bath.
Wash your buttocks, toes and armpits.
Get in there.
Miss, please withdraw.
Do you know
how to use the handles and taps?
l'll know after some investigation.
l see. lt's an electric well.
l'm thirsty.
The water is of poor quality.
Let me try again.
lt's far too salty.
Let me wash my face.
Miss, men and women shouldn't touch.
Miss, why are you so frightened?
Cockroach!
- Do you mean this?
- What are you doing? Throw it away.
That's quite tasty.
Tastes much better
than ones from home.
Miss, the electric kettle.
He has superhuman powers.
l'm going to sleep now.
You take your time.
Don't touch my things.
lt's showing
an opera of the Ming Dynasty.
His Majesty summons
Princess Cheung Ping to court.
Summon Chow Sai Hin to court.
He's playing the emperor.
Our soldiers have been defeated
by the rebels outside the city gate.
The rebels got into the palace?
lt can't be true.
God decided
to destroy the Ming Dynasty.
Has the Ming Dynasty been destroyed?
lt can't be true. lt must be just a play.
''ln 1644, 340 years ago,
Lin Chong forced his way into Peking.''
''Emperor Chong Zhen fled and hanged
himself. The Ming Dynasty collapsed.''
Has the Wheel really made me travel
300 years into the future?
lt's impossible. lt's impossible!
My country was wiped out ,
my home destroyed. ls it really true?
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Your servant deserves
to die a million deaths for his guilt.
Your servant didn't manage
to protect you from danger.
l can't atone
even if l die a million times!
Your servant must die
a million deaths for his guilt!
He's so amazingly into the film.
lt's madness.
l'll be negotiating with Big Brother.
lf l fail, l'll make this sound.
You come and beat him up.
Beat him up?
What does the ''up'' mean?
That's what it means, you dumb-ass.
Understand?
l understand. To fight him with a fist.
And you look like a creampuff.
How can you negotiate looking like that?
lt doesn't look cool. Be like me.
Like how?
Shake your body, like this.
Pretend you're on stage.
Light me a cigarette.
Damn it, creampuff.
Miss Beautiful,
Big Brother wants you to go in.
Be smart.
Your men treated me badly last night.
l put up with it.
But my boyfriend can't.
You know, Chinese gangsters kill without
mercy and they're good at kung fu.
Brother Hung
learnt a lesson from him last night, right?
Normally l don't take him out.
l only brought him today
to at least apologise to you.
We should just forget
about what happened last night.
lt wasn't an electric well,
but an electric crap bowl.
Ching! Ching!
Go!
Superb, superb!
Mr lllegal, look out!
- What was that powerful hidden weapon?
- Don't you know? lt's a gun.
A gun?
l specialise in catching them.
That weapon is definitely very powerful.
- We're no match for him.
- Let's retreat.
Jump down from here.
We'll get away quicker. Let's jump.
- lt's too high. l changed my mind.
- Let's jump quickly.
No!
- No...
- Jump.
Quick, run.
Hey, bitch!
ls that your boyfriend?
What big news! What big news!
Will you just sit down?
What a dumb-ass.
- What would you like, sister?
- A coffee.
And sir?
- A glass of water will do for him.
- OK.
Check that out carefully.
This is what's called an lD card.
Without it, the police will trample on you
and you won't find a job. Understand?
Miss, you know a lot of people.
Please help me to apply for one
and also recommend a job for me.
That's not a problem.
But tell me why you're so dumb.
You don't know a damn thing.
Where the hell are you actually from?
l'm worried that if l tell you the truth
you'll beat me up again.
l won't beat you up. So tell me.
l am actually the
Chief Royal Guard to the Ming Dynasty.
To catch my older brother,
a depraved maniac, l got onto the Wheel.
lt somehow brought me
300 years into the future,
and l've now come to
Asia of Kowloon in Hong Kong.
Forget it.
Fine. So what can you do?
Although l am a warrior,
l've worked hard on music and the arts.
My interests include locks, carpentry,
fishing, hunting and folk dancing.
l learned how to look after myself
as a youth,
so l know a little about
washing clothes, ploughing land,
growing vegetables,
weaving and embroidery.
Also, l've cooked for 500 men at one time
when l was serving in the army.
That's all pretty run-of-the-mill.
All men know how to do those things.
Don't say that l'm not nice to you.
l'll do you a favour.
You can be my bodyguard
and general servant.
l'll pay you $300 a month.
Am l nice to you?
- Are you happy?
- No.
Fong Sau Ching is a man of dignity.
l will not serve a woman.
You're too chauvinistic.
When in Rome, do as the Romans do.
Women are superior here.
Only dignified men serve women.
Watch this. Watch carefully.
- You bastard!
- You poor thing, are you hurt?
Serves you right!
Don't hit me. l'm sorry.
Times have changed.
What's more, even the coins we use
have a woman's head on them.
As you can see.
Without lD, the police will trample on you.
lt's up to you if you want to leave.
l'd never have guessed that l,
Fong Sau Ching, would sink so low.
My country was wiped out,
my home destroyed.
l've no choice but to follow the example
Emperor Yue set - to bear insults.
l hope the day will come
when my country is rebuilt.
Miss, l accept your offer for now.
Good. Now practise putting two cubes of
sugar in my coffee and stirring it properly.
- lt's been stirred properly...
- How dare you?
How dare you use your fingers?
Think it over.
l'm paying a fat $300 a month to hire you.
- Don't you know how to play mahjong?
- Sister, here's your tea.
l asked you to serve my sisters, not me.
Go over there and do it.
You're such a dumb-ass.
l pay a fat $300 a month to hire you.
- Sorry about that.
- Come on, come on...
- 1 5, 20...
- l lose again!
- Have some tea first.
- l don't want any.
Sister, here's your tea.
What's this?
- Mud lemon tea.
- Go to hell! Go to hell!
My country was wiped out,
my home destroyed.
To bear the insults, accept the bitter life.
My country was wiped out, my home
destroyed. Fong Sau Ching, bear it!
Ching, what are you doing?
Be quick, l'm desperate.
l'm washing clothes.
Why is it taking so long?
What are you doing?
Hey!
How can you screw things up
every single time?
l'll go crazy soon.
Help, my home is ruined.
Fire!
The flat is on fire! Ching, get out now!
Help!
Ching, what are you doing?
l'm making you some nice food to eat.
Are you insane? Why burn logs
when you can use the microwave?
l'll go crazy soon.
Nothing will be left.
Why are there so many plants?
l grow them.
Look how many l've grown.
That's nice.
- What's this?
- An African orchid.
Are you really a man?
Damn it. What's he drawing all this time?
- That looks stupid.
- Give it back.
Give it back.
Robbery! Robbery!
How much did you get?
- Here.
- You should've taken gold Rolexes.
Jewellery's hard to sell.
Why don't you learn?
You're such an idiot.
Take it.
l'll have a bath first.
Hello. Page 996 for me.
lt's Sister calling him. Yes.
''Sister paged you.''
- Have a bath.
- Stop being so fussy.
Open the door! Open the door!
- Someone's outside. Do you hear?
- Don't worry.
- l recognise the voice! lt's my husband!
- Your husband?
Open the door!
Ching...
- You pervert!
- What is it?
Excuse me, sir...
Ching, leave him alone. Stop hitting him!
l'm fine. Since you hit him so hard,
he won't try anything again.
- Are you really OK?
- Yes.
- Be careful.
- Go back down.
l'm so puzzled.
My husband really loves me.
When a man loves a woman that much
it becomes puzzling.
What should l do?
How about you give me $5,000
and l'll send him away?
There you are!
Only $3,000?
l'm afraid it isn't enough.
lt probably is enough. l'll try.
l'll try now.
What's it like to be a model?
We try to sell
fashionable clothes to the customers.
We have to meet them all the time.
lt's fine when the customers are good.
But some take the chance
to try to rape us.
l was really scared.
Thanks for helping me.
lt's good to teach them a lesson.
lt's hard to earn a living in Hong Kong.
Now you know. lt's a hard life.
Skinny monkey, what are you doing?
l warn you, if you damage the televisions
you'll have to pay for them.
What are you staring at?
Haven't you seen this before?
You piece of shit.
You piece of shit, drink the whole can
and l may let you lick my toes clean.
Go to hell!
Darling!
Darling...
Darling, he tried to rape me!
Bastard!
You piece of shit,
how dare you try it on with my wife?
You son of a bitch!
Hung!
Let her go or l'll kill you!
But for me, you'd be a beggar.
This is how you repay me?
You've made a fortune from me.
l've robbed over ten times for you.
You never gave me a share.
Shut up! l'm the boss.
You do as l say!
Kneel down and apologise to my wife.
You don't think l'll shoot you?
l've got the bullets.
Miss has gone too far.
She treats me like a slave.
l agreed to serve her,
but not her friends as well.
To be frank, he isn't bad.
lt's crucial that he can stand your temper.
Your boyfriend is so strong.
He must make you very happy
when you're making love?
You're talking nonsense.
He's not my boyfriend.
- l treat him like a maid.
- You just treat him like a maid?
How about this: l pay you $5,000
and you sell him to me.
- l'll pay $10,000.
- l'll pay $1 5,000.
l'm not selling him,
however much you offer.
- Fine.
- lt's your turn.
By the way, does he know you use him
to cheat your customers?
Of course not.
You can't tell, but he's a moron.
He's there to be used.
Does he know what we do for a living?
How would he know? l look so elegant.
l'm not sure about you, though.
- Do l look like one?
- Not your look, but your voice.
Once people hear your voice
they know you're a hooker.
- Hooker?
- Stop it! We're all hookers.
''Hooker: another name for a prostitute.''
So l've been helping her
cheat her customers.
God, l, Fong Sau Ching,
am a respectable Chief Royal Guard.
How did l sink
to helping a hooker commit crimes?
Hey! Go and cook now. l'm starving!
No. l won't work for this hooker any more!
Am l doing this for the lD card?
My country was destroyed.
Where can l go now?
There's nothing left for me.
l feel so alone.
Even though my country was destroyed,
l still don't have to bear her temper, do l?
Have l fallen in love with her?
lt's impossible.
Can l have some newspapers?
''Cold-blooded pervert
raped and decapitated young woman.''
''Body found, limbs broken.
Rape and murder in cold blood.''
Limbs were broken?
The killer acted exactly like Fung San.
Could he be alive...
and be here too?
lt must be him.
''Arrest Notice''
''This man is Fung San. He acts
like a mad wolf and has no morals.''
''He rapes women and robs people.
All good citizens, beware of him.''
Please come up.
Follow me.
She's a model. She just needs some
fast cash. She'll only do it once or twice.
Hey, miss.
Hello? Hello? lt that Ching?
Ching. What's wrong with you?
l've been paging you all day.
l'll be going with a customer
to Pei Pa Garden later.
l'm afraid he may assault me.
Get ready to help me.
This woman wants to use me again
to help her commit crimes.
l'm a respectable commander.
l won't help you again.
996.
Yes, tell him that Sister called him.
Tell him to come to me now.
My rule is l get the money first.
- How about having a cigarette first?
- No. l don't take drugs.
l'll have one by myself then.
How about you go for a bath first?
You have a bath first.
l want to watch you having a bath.
Sure, but it'll cost you extra.
ls that enough? Take it.
Are these real?
l don't know. l took the money
from someone who cheated me,
and l've already killed him.
l'm only kidding.
We can always talk about money later.
Your muscles are so toned.
Where do you work out?
You get me so excited.
You look so fine.
- Really?
- l'll just have a bath first.
l'm a bit shy.
Damn you, Ching!
Come and rescue me quickly!
Your muscles are so toned.
l need to think through what l'm doing.
Now that l know Fung San is still alive,
l should complete my mission.
Have l really forgotten my duty to the
emperor because of an ignorant woman?
Fong Sau Ching,
you are infatuated by a ''black widow''.
No.
l must complete my mission.
You son of a bitch! Are you insane?
When my boyfriend comes,
he'll beat you up!
You're insane, you maniac!
ls that nice?
- l don't want to play this game.
- Come on.
- Please don't. l'm a model...
- You hands are so smooth.
l don't want to play this game any more.
lt really hurts!
Let me go! lt really hurts!
Hello, Sister? ls that Sister?
Why don't you speak?
l am not Sister.
Why do you want her?
Why is that voice so familiar?
That voice is familiar.
Ching, where are you?
l'm at a phone box.
Don't raise your voice to me.
l have no faith in you any more.
l won't let you use me again. Bye.
Ching, please don't do this now!
Someone wants to kill me!
He broke my hand! l'm in agony!
- You had your hand broken?
- Yes!
Who? Who broke your hand?
He looks like George Lam.
George Lam?
Who's George Lam?
Ching!
Hello? Hello?
George Lam?
Who's George Lam?
George Lam? Who is Lam?
- Who's George Lam?
- George Lam?
This is George Lam. Don't you know him?
Which village are you from?
Peasant!
lt's Fung San!
So George Lam is Fung San!
Fung San!
Sister!
- Hello...
- Stupid dog!
- Fung San!
- Go to the cemetery at Happy Valley now.
Don't do anything rash!
- Where are you?
- At the second gate, with the sculpture.
- Jump over, like the dog you are!
- Fung San, tell me where you are.
- Go into the crypt.
Stupid dog!
l haven't seen you for over 300 years.
How have you been?
Fung San.
- Ching!
- Sister!
Stop now, or l'll squeeze her head open!
You're using a defenceless woman
to threaten me?
The Jiang Hu people will laugh at you.
Don't you know that term
isn't used any more?
Let me bring you up to date.
Chong Zhen is long dead. The Ming
Dynasty collapsed centuries ago.
What are you still chasing me for?
You put my picture up everywhere,
you son of a bitch!
lt's my duty as the Chief Royal Guard.
l promised the emperor l'd capture you.
l won't give up
if it takes me a million years!
You make me sick, Chief Royal Guard.
Let me teach you a lesson
by raping and killing
your girlfriend in front of you!
Stop there,
or l'll bite into her throat!
Please don't, warrior!
l'm not his girlfriend, just his friend.
- His friend?
- Yes.
So you can relax
and enjoy our performance.
Wait!
This is between me and you.
lt has nothing to do with her.
Let her go first.
Beg me - and beg me sincerely.
Tell me you're scared of me.
Fine.
l beg you.
l beg you sincerely, and l'm scared of you.
Why are you begging me like a coward?
Give me a reason for this.
l may consider it and let her go.
l've lost patience. l'll count to three.
l love her.
l'm in love with her!
My god, that really is sickening to hear.
lt's hard to believe you're in love
with a woman of no dignity.
Prove it to me.
Fine. How can l prove it to you?
Drink this.
''The seven poisons''?
Think this through carefully.
You'll lose all your skills if you drink it.
Don't ask me why. l just dislike you
following me everywhere like a ghost.
Ching, don't drink it!
He'll go back on his word anyway!
Ching...
''The wife shouldn't be of concern,
but the hero is too romantic.''
Pity you're not a hero
but a stupid dog!
You give up all the kung fu
you've learnt in your life for a woman,
and break your promise to the emperor.
l despise you even more.
Don't let me see you again
or l'll kill you!
Go.
Big brother! Big brother!
Don't call me big brother.
- l know you'll go back on your word.
- Have l ever not?
So why did you drink it?
l had no chance if l didn't drink it,
and l may have a small one if l did.
l drank it because of the small chance...
Fung San...
we've been brothers for many years.
You know my personality well.
l'd rather die than accept an insult.
So far in my life,
apart from my parents...
the emperor and our master...
l've never bowed down to anyone else.
l bow down to you now.
l beg you, let her go!
You act like a piece of shit.
You've spoilt my interest in your girl.
You lowlife, don't let me
ever set eyes on you again...
or l'll kill you!
Ching, are you all right?
Ching...
Sister, use this to bind your hand first.
Sister, lead a better life from now on.
There's something l have to do.
l must go now.
Ching, don't go. Ching!
Ching, what are you doing?
Ching, where are you going?
Ching, come back here!
Hey, my horse!
Someone's stealing my horse!
Medicine is very advanced now! There's
still hope if you go to the hospital at once!
Ching!
You stupid dog, using gold needles
to block the pulses!
lf you force yourself to fight me,
the poison will spread
to your heart in four hours
and you'll bleed
from seven holes until you die!
Why are you doing this?
Blocking the pulses with gold needles,
l can keep my powers for an hour -
long enough for me to kill you!
Come and die then!
Damn it.
Come on, come on! Run faster
and pass them! Pass them all!
Come on, stupid dog!
Come on, come on...
Fung San, l thought you knew me better.
To keep my promise to the emperor
and protect my beloved,
l wouldn't hesitate
to sacrifice my own life.
Of course -
you're so noble, you stupid dog!
Damn! Why is a car up there?
lt's stuck... l don't want to know!
l want you to die with me!
You die first!
Stupid dog,
you want to take me to the emperor?
Shit...
Where's the stupid dog?
Where is he?
Come and catch me, stupid dog!
Faster! Faster!
Hurry!
Ching!
Stop holding me! Ching!
Rescue him! Quickly!
The poison is working and l'm dying.
Goodbye, Sister.
Ching, the doctors in Hong Kong
are excellent! They can save you!
Miss, l'll ask you for the eighth time -
and give me a straight answer.
Who is he to you?
l'll tell you the same thing
if you ask a thousand times.
He's my boyfriend,
Chief Royal Guard from the Ming Dynasty.
- How dare you try to wind me up?
- You dare to hit me? l'll report you!
l'll lick your toes clean if you can prove
he's from the Ming Dynasty!
Doctor, is he saved from the poison?
lt was carboxyl acid, but the sea water
diluted it and we managed to save him.
l always say
Hong Kong doctors are the best.
But something was very strange.
l conducted a cell analysis on him
and it suggested he's over 300 years old -
which means he's from the Ming Dynasty.
That machine really is no good.
Aren't you going to lick my toes clean?
Hey, why are you hitting her?
Miss, do you want to report him?
l can be your witness.
l just want to see Fong Sau Ching.
He's still in a coma. The earliest
you can see him is tomorrow afternoon.
You also have to get clearance
from the police.
ln theory, you're not authorised.
But the police are compassionate.
You're authorised this time.
Sir, what did he say?
Your boyfriend doesn't want to see you.
Leave now.
- You're lying!
- Why should l?
Hey!
That really hurts! Let me go!
OK, l'll authorise you one more time.
But only for a moment.
Ching! Ching!
Ching?
Ching, did you ask the police
to say you won't see me?
Stop pretending you're asleep.
l know you're just pretending.
l don't want to see you. Leave now.
Have you gone mad
from taking ''The seven poisons''?
l am Sister!
You used me.
You've been lying to me all this time.
You pretend to be a model,
but you're really a hooker.
ln other words, a prostitute.
A woman like you would have been
beheaded in the Ming Dynasty.
Beheaded, my arse!
l admit l was wrong.
l apologise. l know it was my fault.
Won't you accept my apology?
How about if l admit
that you're my boyfriend from now on?
l'll be nicer to you.
But l won't admit that you're my girlfriend.
So why did you say you love me?
lf l didn't love you,
would l be willing to die for you?
But to die for love is a different matter.
l could never be with
a woman as bad as you are.
l'm a man of principle.
Can you stop this?
Stop being so mean to me.
l'm already begging you.
What more do you want?
l can change!
One's personality is determined at birth.
People don't change.
l'm still acting as Chief Royal Guard
300 years later.
Fung San is still the same psychopath
who rapes and murders women.
l can't suppress my feelings
for an evil woman.
But l can force myself
not to see her again.
Go now.
l'm very tired and l need some rest.
Fine! Just pretend l never met you!
l can't believe you're so heartless!
Get lost!
- lt's you, miss.
- Sorry, sorry...
- Does he know l made this for him?
- No. l told him what you asked me to say.
l told him that he looked like my dead son,
so l make soup for him every day.
- Please take it.
- l shouldn't, really.
- Take it.
- Thank you.
See you tomorrow. Thank you. Bye.
You've dropped everything!
Let me help you.
You broke her things!
- Forget it.
- Are you blind?
Sorry.
- What is it?
- l just wanted to give you back the flask.
- l'm not sure if it's broken or not.
- lt doesn't matter.
Please take it. Take it.
- Why are you giving me so much money?
- Take it.
- Do one thing for me, please.
- What is it?
Thank you, sir.
He'll be back immediately
after the urine test.
Don't say a thing. Fung San is here.
Why are you covering your head?
Damn it! Reverse that bad luck.
is being exhibited for the first time
around the world.
lt will be exhibited in Hong Kong
in three months.
The Wheel of Life and Death
is more than 500 years old.
Brother San, there are six boxes
and you've counted them.
That's $488,000 altogether.
Let's see the money.
You're buying a lot of guns.
Are you starting a war?
lf you're planning a robbery, count us in.
Damn you.
l've thought it through.
l'll always be discriminated against here.
lt's not my territory. l can't compete
with Hong Kong people.
My expertise in martial arts
doesn't help me here.
l'll take the guns
back to the Ming Dynasty,
destroy the palace,
kill the useless emperor
and crown myself in his place!
Little brothers,
history must be rewritten.
Brother San, that's too cryptic.
l don't understand.
lt's better that you don't.
lt won't do you any good.
Any more national treasures arrived?
Anything interesting?
Yes. There are 1 50 items.
Let me show you.
A sword, hundreds of years old,
with no rust at all.
The Dragon Spring Sword?
Someone's willing to pay $180,000 for it.
Damn. lt really is
Fong Sau Ching's Dragon Spring Sword.
My sword was broken by this.
This sword is worth 10 million dollars.
l'll have it!
OK. Give me one million tomorrow
and l'll sell it to you.
You don't deserve the sword.
You don't even know how to use it.
Let me show you
how much it's worth.
This precious sword really doesn't stain.
What a sword!
l'll rule the Ming Dynasty! l'll rule it!
''The Wheel of Life and Death will be
exhibited in Hong Kong in two months.''
Life is full of coincidences.
The Wheel will be exhibited in Hong Kong.
ls this really ordained in heaven?
ln two months and 1 7 days at midnight...
it will be the date
to achieve Buddhist enlightenment
and the Wheel will hold supreme power.
Fung San will surely act on that day,
and l shall complete my mission then.
Are you confident you'll beat him?
No.
Then why do you want to provoke him?
Can you stop being so stubborn?
l can't. l promised the emperor
l'd bring Fung San back for punishment.
l'll be guilty of disrespect to the emperor
if l don't keep my promise.
lf l can't beat him, l'll die with him.
lf l'm fortunate enough to beat him,
l'll take him back to the Ming Dynasty
through the Wheel.
So you're leaving...
and you won't come back again?
l don't belong here anyway.
And what about me?
- You'd better leave now.
- Have you gone insane?
Didn't you say you love me?
Love is a different matter.
l must train hard for the next two months.
And l must also make a sword
to fight Fung San with.
How can l concentrate
if you're staying here?
lt's better to cut things short.
As the singer Mui said,
''Love is not meant to be forever.
Cherish it when you find it.''
l don't care. l won't leave.
Fine. Then prove that you can change.
- How can l prove it?
- That's up to you.
We'll see.
Eat more - you never know
if you'll get struck by lightning.
And l still outrank you.
Hey.
Delicious?
Your Majesty,
your servant has made a strong sword.
l promise you l'll defeat Fung San.
Please give me strength from heaven
so that l can complete my mission.
Ching, this bulletproof jacket
is for you.
This sword belongs to you.
''Sister's Sword''?
So it is mine?
How cool is that?!
There's something else.
Just wait a minute.
Ching?
Ching!
What are you doing?
The exhibition hall is closed.
''Fung San, you degenerate,
fight me on the roof
if you want the black jade Buddha.''
Stupid dog.
Fung San!
You're riddled with sin
and you've committed many crimes.
Come back to the Ming Dynasty with me.
l'll beg the emperor to spare you.
l'll blow you to bits!
Ching!
Now pay the money back, bitch.
Don't call yourself a sister
if you can't pay it back.
l haven't been a sister for a long time.
l work in a shop now.
l don't have the money to pay you back.
All l've got is $200. Do you want it?
l'll give it to you.
Aren't you afraid of the acid?
lt's just water.
Ching!
You're still alive? ls this real?
This is great!
This is sexual harassment!
The End