You've got quite a temper.
It's better this way...
You coward!
Still in a bad mood?
At least you’re speaking.
What's your name?
I didn't think the Hans
had names like that.
Relax.
If I had wanted to, I would
already have done it.
You must be dying for a bath.
Fresh water's hard to get here.
But I managed to bring some up.
You can wear my clothes
when you're done.
They're clean.
Don't worry.
I'll sing,
so you’ll know where I am.
After the bath,
you'll be calmer.
No more hitting on the head!
All this trouble for a comb?
It's mine.
It means a lot to me. A barbarian
like you wouldn't understand.
Not true. I can use it
to pick fleas from my horse.
By the way,
I'm a real Manchurian.
I'm sorry...
I guessed wrong.
I thought you were a Han.
Give me back my comb.
I don't take orders from anyone.
Give it back.
One night...
when I was a boy, I saw
a thousand shooting stars.
I thought,
"Where did they all go?"
I'm an orphan.
I used to look for stars alone.
I thought if I rode to the other
end of the desert, I'd find them.
I've been riding in the desert
ever since.
And so, the little boy
became a fearsome bandit.
He couldn't find the stars,
so he stole my comb.
Out here, you always fight
for survival.
You have to be part of a gang
to stand a chance.
Slowly,
your gang becomes your family.
All that Dark Cloud stuff
is just to scare people...
and make my life easier.
So you are still that little boy...
Looking for shooting stars.
I am a man.
And now I've found
the brightest star of all.
Your father's men
are looking for you.
They're still out there,
circling closer.
Let them look.
It is trouble for me.
Don't send me back.
You must decide.
You might get tired of this life.
You might begin
to miss your family.
If it were our daughter,
we'd look for her too.
She would miss us.
Jen...
I want you to be mine forever.
I will make my mark
on the world.
I will earn your parents' respect.
We have a legend.
Anyone who dares to jump
from the mountain...
God will grant his wish.
Long ago, a young man's parents
were ill, so he jumped.
He didn't die.
He wasn't even hurt.
He floated away,
far away, never to return.
He knew his wish had come true.
If you believe,
it will happen.
The elders say...
"A faithful heart
makes wishes come true."
Keep it safe.
Return it to me
when we are together again.
I will.
If you don't,
I'll come after you.
And I won't let you off so easy.
Wherever I went
someone always recognized me.
I really tried.
Later, I heard you came
to Peking.
I was afraid
I'd never see you again.
So I came.
I can't let you marry.
Go.
Jen...
Don't ever come back.
So it's over?
Yes.
We heard noises.
It was just a cat.
You think Jade Fox will show up?
She's out there...
but I doubt she'll show herself.
We'll keep our eyes open.
Sooner or later...
she'll come for the girl.
Jen!
Come with me!
You're mine!
Come with me to the desert!
Jen!
Come with me to Xin Jiang!
Tell me.
Where is Jade Fox?
Come with me. Hurry!
You thought she'd give it all up
and go back West with you?
She's mine.
Either way...
you are no good to her dead.
With the Gou and Yu clans...
hunting you,
you'll soon be in their hands.
I don't care anymore.
If you truly loved her,
you wouldn't say that.
Don’t you want to see her again?
All right.
I'll write you an introduction.
Take it to Wudan.
Wait there for news from me.
All right.
When will this end?
They take it, they put it back,
they take it again.
My home is turning into
a warehouse.
Come in.
Speak!
Jen has run away!
Gou found
the wedding chamber empty.
Governor Yu requests
your assistance.
You know
the Giang Hu underworld.
He wants to find her,
and keep her from harm.
Sir Te, leave this to us.
Don't worry.
What can I serve you?
This cup is dirty.
Hello.
What's your name?
Long.
It's young Master Long.
My apologies!
I'm Iron Eagle Sung...
and this is my brother in arms...
Flying Cougar Li Yun.
What brings you to Huai An...
and where are you headed,
Master Long?
Anywhere there's action.
In that case, perhaps
we could be of assistance.
Don't bother.
You don't seem to understand.
So what if I don't?
We have ways of helping you
to understand.
Are you related to Li Mu Bai?
He is my defeated foe!
Have some tea.
Shu Lien...
The things we touch
have no permanence.
My master would say...
there is nothing
we can hold on to in this world.
Only by letting go
can we truly possess what is real.
Not everything
is an illusion.
My hand...
wasn't that real?
Your hand, rough and callused
from practice...
All this time, I've never had
the courage to touch it.
Giang Hu is a world
of tigers and dragons...
full of corruption...
I tried sincerely to give it up...
but I have brought us
only trouble.
To repress one's feelings
only makes them stronger.
You're right,
but I don't know what to do.
I want to be with you...
just like this.
It gives me a sense of peace.
Please follow me.
- I want a clean room.
- We have plenty.
Your order?
Steamed whole cod,
bite-size meatballs...
a little starchy,
but keep the sauce light...
shark fin soup, mixed vegetables,
and some warm wine.
I have to order
from a bigger restaurant.
Hurry then.
That's him.
I am Iron Arm Mi.
I heard a true master has arrived.
I have come to seek a lesson.
You asked for it!
What kind of Iron Arm are you?
You have amazing technique!
I am Flying Saber.
Are you related
to Southern Crane?
Southern Duck? I don't eat
anything with two feet.
Who could remember
such long-winded names?
Li Mu Bai is your defeated foe...
and you don't know
his master Southern Crane?
Who are you?
I'm Shining Phoenix
Mountain Gou.
Gou?
I hate that name.
It makes me puke!
Too bad you're named Gou.
You'll be the first
to feel my sword today.
Hold it!
Don’t you know Monk Jing?
A monk, in a place like this?
You need a lesson!
Who are you?
Who am I?
I am...
I am
the Invincible Sword Goddess.
Armed with the incredible...
Green Destiny.
Be you Li or Southern Crane...
Lower your head...
and ask for mercy.
I am the desert dragon.
I leave no trace.
Today I fly over Eu-Mei.
Tomorrow...
I'll kick over
Wudan Mountain!
We politely asked for
a friendly match...
but she showed no respect,
and attacked us.
Everyone came by
to teach her a lesson.
Her sword was just too powerful.
I've traveled everywhere...
but never
met anyone so uncivilized.
She kept accusing me of being
Gou Jun Pei's brother.
Who is this Gou, anyway?
Her husband.
We're close
to your headquarters.
Go home and check in.
What about you?
I'll look around
and catch up later.
Not a bad idea.
Tonight we'll get a good night's
sleep at headquarters.
Mistress, you're back.
It's you!
How is everything here?
Fine.
You've been gone a while.
Yes, and I leave again tomorrow.
- Your wife was due?
- Yeah, a baby girl.
Good!
I'll be happy if she’s
half as strong as you.
Mrs. Wu...
You're back!
- How's the arm? Still sore?
- Much better.
You've been gone so long.
Li Mu Bai is coming
to stay the night.
I'll go and make up his room!
Sister Shu Lien...
Here you must be in proper attire.
I'm just borrowing some
clean clothes. I'm not staying.
I'll give them to you.
I was just passing by
and wondered how you were.
You, sister...
Look at the trouble you've caused.
Now you know what
Giang Hu life is really like.
If you think of me
as your sister...
Let me give you
some sisterly advice.
You can run from marriage,
but not your parents.
They forced me to marry!
Go back to them first.
Then you can decide about Lo.
You know about Lo?
He really loves you.
Come back to Peking with me.
We'll find a solution.
Where is he now?
Li Mu Bai
has made arrangements.
He sent him
to Wudan Mountain.
You're working together
to set me up! I'm leaving!
How dare you accuse us!
I always knew
you had stolen the sword!
I've done nothing
but protect you and your family.
And you've repaid me
with nothing but contempt.
Li Mu Bai himself spared you,
and all you do is insult him.
We wanted some peace
and you've ruined it all!
You're no sister of mine!
What do I care?
You were never a real friend anyway.
But I wonder...
how long could you last
as my enemy?
Put the sword down!
Jen!
Everyone out. Shut the doors.
Fine... the friendship is over.
Don't touch it!
That's Li Mu Bai's sword.
Come and get it if you can.
Without the Green Destiny,
you are nothing.
Don't be a sore loser.
Go ahead. Take your pick.
I'll wait.
Go ahead.
Give me the sword.
Take it!
Stop it!
You don't deserve
the Green Destiny.
Not another lecture!
On guard!
Let's end this here.
Only the sword will settle this.
I only let you go because
I wanted to see the real you.
What do you know
about a true heart?
What do you want?
What I've always wanted,
to teach you.
All right.
If you can take back the sword
in three moves...
I'll go with you.
Give it back!
- Kneel!
- Never!
Then you have no use
for the sword.
Sooner or later
they'd drag you back to Peking.
Your parents
will never accept you again.
But why go home?
We've gone this far,
we won't stop now.
You'll always be my Lady.
At last, we'll be our own masters.
We'll be happy.
That's the most important thing.
All we have left is each other,
right?
Lie down and rest.
She's crazy.
You should have killed her.
I didn't have the heart.
Well, Li Mu Bai can do it.
Is it me
or the sword you want?
You've been drugged.
Where is Jade Fox?
What happened?
Jade Fox drugged her.
How did you get here?
We followed Jade Fox.
And so you die.
And so shall you!
A poisoned needle!
You deserve to die...
but the life
I was hoping to take...
was Jen's.
Ten years I devoted to you.
But you deceived me!
You hid
the manual's true meaning.
I never improved...
but your progress was limitless!
You know what poison is?
An eight-year-old girl...
full of deceit.
That's poison!
Jen!
My only family...
my only enemy...
You can't die!
Tell us what poison you used!
Tell us the antidote!
You can't let Li Mu Bai die!
She used Purple Yin...
Purple Yin poison.
It goes straight to the heart.
It's the same poison she used
to kill my master.
My blood
will soon reverse its flow.
There is no antidote.
That can't be!
Everything has an antithesis!
Why not this?
The antidote exists.
She taught it to me.
The formula is simple...
but it takes time to prepare.
Trust me.
As you have helped me...
Let me help him.
All right.
Hurry.
I will hold on as long as I can.
Take my horse
and go to the compound.
Give this to Mrs. Wu.
She'll help you. Hurry!
Spare your energy.
I'll be back!
Where is Mrs. Wu?
Stop it!
Shu Lien
told me to show you this.
Let her in.
Mu Bai, hold on.
Give me some hope.
Shu Lien...
Save your strength.
My life is departing.
I've only one breath left.
Use it to meditate.
Free yourself from this world...
as you have been taught.
Let your soul rise to eternity...
with your last breath.
Do not waste it...
for me.
I've already wasted
my whole life.
I want to tell you
with my last breath...
I have always loved you.
I would rather be a ghost,
drifting by your side...
as a condemned soul...
than enter heaven without you.
Because of your love...
I will never be a lonely spirit.
He's gone?
Bo...
please take this sword
back to Sir Te.
Now you must go
to Wudan Mountain.
Lo awaits you there.
Promise me one thing.
Whatever path
you take in this life...
be true to yourself.
Do you remember the legend
of the young man?
"A faithful heart
makes wishes come true."
Make a wish, Lo.
To be back in the desert,
together again.