Guess what I hear...
most in my life?
Are you blind?
A blind man shouldn't go out!
Bingo! That's it
Just want to tell him...
I can
But I did not say it
Because I am mute, too
Good morning, Onion!
Living here so long,
I know everyone
like this who smells alcohol
He's Mr. Wong of the Security
Good morning, Onion!
A well-known stupid drunk
Hi, Onion!
You can tell I'm chow? So quick!
I smell...
your perfume from far away
They even give me a place to live
Why? I work here doing what?
Recording doctor's verbal diagnosis
Thanks...
the Equal Opportunity Law in HK
The salary is okay
There are many medical experiments here
I'm in...
one blind-cure project
Though we often fail
Dr. Woo and
Autumn treat me nice
Especially Autumn
I'm not born blind
At eight,
I moved from Taiwan to Hong Kong
I was the best in school,
A genius
Then problem came
My eyes were always watery
Everything I saw was tinted
One day, I went swimming with girls
Show time. I did the fancy dive
From way up
While diving in, my eyes hurt
and bred
Too late
The retina already fell off
I knew I was blind
That night, I had brain fever
and lost my speaking ability
My families left one after another...
The noisy is...
my buddy Jumboball
What the hell? You walk like ghost!
Salty Lemon Seven, your favorite!
So much salt again! Sucker!
Can't you share?
Gobbling
Alright, your turn
Stop flopping around, here you go
What's the matter?
It has problem breathing?
You have problem
Tell me!
I know you can hear bird's talk
Constipation?
With such appetite? No way!
What are you getting?
What are you doing?
Don't pass it to my bird
Leave it alone. Bug me
Come here... homework time
A couple of good ones
I dreamt of my ungrateful daughter again
Salivating. Dead. Still on drug
You are better
What?
Queuing for a massage
You've got nothing to do?
You pay me, or I pay you?
Onion!
And that's the news for today...
In...
our next program...
When I was little,
I wanted to phone-in the radio
Because ever since I was blind
Radio's my connection to the world
Hello
Hello, please talk
- Miss Autumn
- Thank you, fisherman
- Doc, your coffee
- Thanks
Is Onion throwing up badly?
Badly!
He's tough, more than others
Like last time, he didn't ask for help
And often jokes over it
I've notice. Usually you don't talk much
Except when you talk...
about the patients
Do you like music,
or jazz?
It's okay
Do you think...
listening to classical music or...
...playing sax is pretentious?
Not really. Sax's pretty good
As long as it's pleasant
Well, I know how to play it
Back in school, every time I played it,
My friends said I was pretentious
When foreigners' playing,
they said it's cool!
So, I often practice...
in the toilet
Even now, my sax comes with a taste
I think I've got too far
I have two concert tickets for tonight
Do you want to go?
No, the exam. I don't want to flunk it
That's true
Never mind, next time then
After all, failure is the mom of success
Sorry, I'm sorry, Onion...
So sorry, I'm late again
Have you been waiting long?
Sorry
It is the thirtieth time
she cuts my hair
I'm not too greedy
Just wish it happen...
863 times in my life
What are you thinking? Fallen asleep?
Did you have the apples I bought you?
You remember my birthday!
I just told you once
Thank you!
Someone said
I'm clumsy today
No? Really?
If people has...
one disadvantage
God shall give him one advantage
If you get a lousy body,
you'll get a good brain
If you are not pretty,
you'll get a nice voice
Why I have nothing,
and get fat?
It's all your fault!
Give ma all! Yummy!
What advantage do you have?
Two?
Right, you have more
You can't see...
how ugly I am
And you won't...
tell my secrets
So...
I feel very safe with you
You are the only one I can talk to
If you don't want to listen,
tell me
You really don't?
Don't like it?
Don't rub your nose!
I'm just kidding
Did you hear?
I heard it again last night
Don't know why
Every time I hear it
I feel relax
Dr. Woo said he could play it
But it's not him, I'm sure
He can't play that well
Sometimes I want to find out
But don't want to be nosy
If he stops playing, it'll be hell
Is it you?
It must be you!
I don't play... sax
Then who could it be?
It's a call...
from far away
Who talks about his love distress
I feel great for him now
Wish he could stay...
with his beloved one...
Forever and ever
If you want...
to share your problem with us
Give me a call
Let's chat in the air
Hoping that you can be relieved...
From any distress and problem
I can play sax since small
My father plays in the Taiwan Orchestra
I played sax with him together
I had performance in blind school too
Ever since Autumn says she likes sax,
I often play for her at night
Don't want her to know it's me
Even Dr. Woo can't attract her
Not to...
mention me
Better not screw up her dream
Or she might stop...
cutting my hair
Good morning, Onion!
Got to go, I'm late. Bye!
Is it good?
You are the first one to say that
Weird! Why they don't like it?
I know, you are always on my side
Did you hear it?
The sax
I just said I felt bad yesterday,
and it comes
It happens every time!
Meteor!
Did you see it? A meteor!
I forgot
How could you see it
But I've made two wishes
Is it too greedy?
Tell you?
Okay, it's about you anyway
The first one: Your eyes recover soon
And watch the meteor shower with us
What do you think?
The second one?
Okay, I'll tell you
The second one is...
I won't tell you
No pouting!
No rubbing nose!
Do you know how it's like?
No. I'll tell you
It's like fireworks in the sky
Did I see it?
No
I'm lying?
If you see a meteor gliding across
What wishes would you make?
You have two also?
I know,
all the blind people recover
How great!
And the second one?
Come on, say it
Come on. It tickles
What's the second one?
Wait!
I've got paged. Wait for me
Move, move... right...
Turn right, right...
Straight down, get move
No, no, back up, back up...
Move on, I'm late!
Oh, my god! It'll hit!
Straight down
Getting off ahead, thank you
Thanks, Onion
"Wait for me"
You look great, Onion
Got to go. Bye
What's up? You look happy
Oh, shit!
Call the cop!
I can see. Where is it?
Mr. Young, please queue here
This way
What? It's my friend. Bothers you?
Jackpot? You are the sixty billion human
travelling from the Earth...
to the Polaris
Jackpot? Am I dreaming?
You are not
This is the station to the Polaris
He knows what I'm thinking? Weird dream!
It's not a dream
You can see me, right?
You can speak. Speak
Really!
You don't remember?
You were dead. An accident
When one die, he leaves Planet Earth
to the Polaris
to continue his journey of life
One in a ten billion will...
hit the jackpot and get a wish
What's yours?
Go back. I don't want to die now!
I knew it
All five of the ten-billion did
But I can't make you alive
You can go back. You have five days
Better than none
Listen up
In five days, you are like you
But people won't...
know you
Because you borrow...
other's body
They won't recognize you
One more rule
You can't...
tell anyone
Nothing about your past identity
Even if you want to...
You can't
Can I...
see and speak?
Yes. Sure you want this?
The five before you
came back regretting
No, I won't
Just let me see her
I can't
just remember her voice and smell
I can see her every looks and movements
Then, no matter how,
I'll be fine
With her,
I know what is real happiness
When could I go?
Anytime
Thank you
Thank you, for talking to me
Even angels get bored here
Are you nut?
Told you not to talk...
to strangers
Wait till someone abduct you
Are you alright?
I'm fine
People won't...
recognize you
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm fine
Wong, you've been drinking again
Smells all alcohol
Is Ophthalmology Section on 1st floor?
Miss Chow?
You smell good. You must be Chow!
Who are you? Can I help you?
Where is...
Miss Autumn?
Down at the bus stop
She's going to her friend's funeral
Who?
What?
I mean...
I lived around. Maybe I know him
His name is Onion
Onion? My...
What date is it?
14th November
I've been away for ten days!
Are you alright?
I'm fine, thanks
Miss Chow...
What now?
I just want to say...
You look good in uniform
I know
- Is it to the grave-yard?
- Yes
Thank you, Miss Lam
Miss Chow
Joe!
Joe Chan, Miss Chan!
Wait, Autumn's not in yet
She went early. Don't you know?
This must be her. She's beautiful!
Gone
This belongs to Dr. Woo
What?! Excuse me!
What's up?
You're so upset. Are you close to him?
It's your foot. Ouch!
Not a word?
Sorry, I am sorry
It's alright. What's your name?
My name? Whatever
Whatever, are you a close friend?
He and me...
That's Onion?
You don't know him?
I do! Haven't see him for a long time
Do you have a mirror?
Yes, hang on
Do we look alike?
No
Is he better looking?
You are
Wow, good looking
Nobody ever said that to me. Thanks
You're welcome
Jumboball, I miss you!
What the hell? You walk like ghost!
Do I know you?!
You don't, but I do
I'm Onion's friend
Onion?
His friends are...
my friends
Why I never met you?
I'm his old friend,
from Taiwan
Taiwan?
Classmate?
Why didn't you attend his funeral?
Forget it
I can't help crying. Better not go
Fine. What else do you want?
Just to stay a little longer
Shut the door
when you go
Thanks
Insurance broker, Cheuk
May I have Mr. Cheuk?
He's out. I'm Siu
May I help you?
If I buy insurance...
And die,
will you indemnify the beneficiary?
Of course
How much is the indemnity?
Depends on how much you buy
Do you want to buy?
I have time. We can sit down...
Have a cup of tea, and talk
I just want the indemnity
Because I... My friend...
Who bought insurance...
from you died
Died? Mr. Cheuk's on leave
Call again some other days
Bye
You said you had time. Can we...?
Some other days...
I don't have much other days
Onion!
Are you here?
From now on, I'll take care of you
My name's Cheuk. My name card
Actually, I'm Onion
My name's Cheuk. My name card...
You!
Who are you?
My name's Cheuk. My name card
Sir?
Salty Lemon Seven, thanks
Salty Lemon Seven, boss
I'll add the salt myself
Mr. Cheuk
Not many people come for me
Most we know
That is nurses' dormitory
Water, Miss Autumn
- Thanks
- What do you have?
So much I wanted to tell her
Looking at her now,
I can't say a word
Mr. Cheuk
How can I help you?
Yes
Your friend Young, Onion...
...bought an insurance from us
And Autumn Yue is the beneficiary
Are you Autumn Yue?
Strange friend, huh?
Funny nickname...
You think it's funny?
Just a few questions for the indemnity
Your career is...
Nurse trainee
How long do you know each other?
One year and 26 days
Wow, you even remember the 26 days
What's your relationship?
I mean,
friendship?
Common, intimate, lovers?
Why should I tell you?
Because that's very important
If you are intimate
or lovers
He might kill himself
to leave you the best
He won't kill himself!
He won't!
He's tough,
full of life and hope!
Go on, go on
What's your relationship with Dr. Woo?
Whom do you like more?
Are you really Insurance Actuary?
Does it matter which one like?
Because... because probably...
You two killed Onion...
My God! What did I say?
Am I a jealous nut?
Mr. Cheuk,
you are the worst man I know
The lowest, the most caddish pest!
Autumn!
I...
Fisherman, the towel!
Do you have epilepsy?
You better have a check-up
God!
You can't tell your real identity
Even if you want to, you can't
I felt...
like you're here
So I could really yell at him
Sorry about what happened
Don't know how to explain
I am Onion, and Cheuk
It's sounds ridiculous,
but it's true
We don't disappear when we die
We live in another place
Remember...
you cut my hair 13 times?
Even cut my ear once
You asked me if it hurt
To be safe,
I'll record again
I am Onion, and Cheuk
Believe me
I know it's ridiculous
Remember the night before I died...
You saw meteor and
made wishes...
For me? Thanks
I am off at ten. Let's have dinner
I can't...
How about midnight snacks?
No trouble?
No
Really, I'm fine now
Could you have the flowers back?
Cheapskate!
How could you take it back?
You gave it to me!
Did I say that?
See!
You want it? Take it!
Sorry
I know it's for Autumn
In graveyard, your look's obvious
She has a day off, though
It's broken. I think she won't mind
Take it
Pity me?
For you, really
I get it, thanks
I feel great. Hope you are the same
You will see her
She's in her sister's. The address...
I know, she told me before
Thanks
You alright?
Why learn swimming suddenly?
You used to yell
when I washed you hair...
...and pushed your head down
Scared of water and
never dare do anything
Till it's too late
The more I scare,
the better I'll try now
Let me get a notebook
So deep,
got to jot it down
You're teasing me!
- Come on, take it
- Thanks, sis
You like someone
but dare not say it
And it's too late. Am I right?
Think I won't splash you
cause you're pregnant?
Don't you need help?
Here we are
No parking ahead. Can't go in
Three hundreds!
How far ahead?
Not far. Take this way
What's up?
Can I ask you...
What happen to my little sister who...
...used to be so strong?
Thanks for the compliments. I'm fine
Okay
Strong. Is it a compliment?
I thought it meant bad tempered
Come when you want to talk
Let me... stay still, Your Majesty
Just treat me as Queen later
Dr. Woo?
Good guess! You are here
I am just dropping by
and see if you're here
And you are
Drop by?
It takes at least two-hour to come here
Where were you?
Here, it's near... the airport!
I went to see somebody off...
So I drop by
Hungry?
You bought so much food to the airport?
Well, it's cheap there. So...
Never mind
My sister
Actually I come for you
I worry if you are alright,
so...
I bought all these nutriment...
for you
I'll go after I leave them here
You're so nice. Come on in
You're like...
door-keeping gods
This is Dr. Woo
- How are you?
- Fine, how are you?
How are you, baby?
Doing butterfly stroke every day
Bang, bang, bang. Drive you nut
You are really nice
We live so far away and you still come
Just drop by
Stay for dinner, then
Sure
My sis needs to talk to someone
Let me help. It's heavy
Are you sure?
Isn't it a bit impulsive?
You should have...
known before
Years ago
when my first patient died,
I thought the same way
Then I told myself:
Many things are out of my control
If you give up
Then you shouldn't ever start
Sis
Are you hot, or just doing facial?
Just getting to the point
She's quite funny
Yes. She's more simple
How about you?
I know what you mean
The seniors say
when you see patients die,
Go see the new-born and
you'll feel better
But he's not just any patients
He's Onion
You won't understand
I didn't believe it before
Until it happens...
to you
I can't go on
Let it out, you'll feel better
Don't worry
I won't just go
I'll stay till the end of this month
Help the new comer...
get used to things
I need time
Give me time
I can change your mind
Thank you
I feel much better now
Coming, coming
Who do you want?
My sister?
What a crowd today
So...
many people coming
Are you dropping by too?
No, I come for her
I have to talk to you
Really?
I called you
They said you were on leave
Sorry about last time
I want my indemnity
I won't reject anything from Onion
Fine, but...
You are insurance broker?
My last name's Cheuk
Mr. Cheuk
It's getting more and more complex
You come so far to indemnify. Very nice
Stay for dinner
Sure, sure
What is that?
Watch it. You'll know
I'll watch it later
Mr. Cheuk
Mr. Cheuk, he's calling you
You are hard-working
Still working while on leave
I want to settle this quick for Onion
Dr. Woo, you work hard too
Aren't you on leave?
Mr. Cheuk, I think we never met
How do you know my name?
We never met...
Doing insurance
you had to know everything
Onion died too suddenly
We had to check people out
Occupational disease. Blind guess
Mr. Cheuk, you look not well
Your lips are dark
You better have a check
It's professional. Not blind guess
I queued and
bought a cheese cake
For dessert
Try it. You'll feel better
Autumn hates cheese
She only likes fruit candies
The octagon ones in colorful cans
I can't believe it
You know even that others like to eat?
I don't eat cheese
Why do you know?
Are you checking on me?
You think I killed him?
No... How could I?
I don't mean it
In fact, I am...
Here it comes again
What's the matter with you?
How's it going?
Sis, do you have slippers?
For men or women?
Better check out...
the nearest hospital
Just in case...
Autumn?
Back in her room. She's pissed off
I didn't mean it
I didn't check on her. Please tell her
Okay, okay...
You threw...
everything up
Have some cheese cake
Sis
The doctors often suggest...
...not to eat too rich after vomiting
No cheese cake. You have something flat?
Apple
Have it
Can we talk,
Dr. Woo?
Sure
Can we donate Onion's money...
to the hospital...
...for ophthalmology studies?
He wished to help
Sure. I can suggest to the hospital...
...to launch a fund...
for the blind people
I thought you really were busy,
have no time to go to concerts
Now I know
I am quite jealous of him
Sorry,
it seems not respectful
I think...
he doesn't want to see you like that
Could we go to concert tomorrow night?
Can we talk tomorrow?
Hope to see you tomorrow
It's getting cold. Let's go in
It's late. Please go
Give Mr. Cheuk a ride, would you?
Where's Mr. Cheuk?
I don't know what you want
I won't...
let you hurt Autumn
I don't have time. Stop the car
You want to vomit?
Thanks for having taken care of Onion
Bye
Where are you going?
I won't let you go back and bug Autumn!
Would you please get in?
I won't leave
I didn't ask you to leave
I won't let you bother Autumn
Let me go back with you
Okay?
Mr. Cheuk,
personally I don't like you
But...
you are a patient to me
You might get pneumonia,
triggering epilepsy
Get in, would you?
Thank you
I must keep an eye on you
You broke my car
I have to take you to the police
You like her
You do too
Right
She told me she cared about me
You've been in our hospital?
Did she take care of you?
But the way I see it...
I think you've got it all wrong
What do you mean?
Nurses always cares about patients
Especially someone like Autumn
But it's different from...
what you think
I am not saying this because I want her
I hope you get it
Didn't she read the letter?
Will she believe it?
Maybe she never ever like me
She just pities me
I am just a common patient to her
I know you want me to regret, right?
How could angels be so unkind?
Good morning
- Good morning
- Staying late?
No, I have a date with you
Not sure if I can get up. So I stay
Where is he?
Who?
Mr. Cheuk! My car's locked
He didn't leave?
Never mind. I'll make some coffee
- Take a seat
- Okay
Could you give me a ride later?
Where to?
Anywhere, take a break, go to concert
Sure
Did you read it?
You wait a whole night here for that?
I read it
Good! You finally got it?
I am sorry... Mr. Angel
I was irrational
You didn't hear a thing
Are you alright?
Did you really read it?
Didn't miss anything?
I don't know what's in your apology card
And this tape's blank
But I accept your apology
Please proceed with my indemnity
and stay away from me afterward
If Mr. Cheuk ever comes...
to the hospital again
Do pay us a visit
We are in charge of ophthalmology
I know, I specialize in the blind
I'm always there. So I understand them
Sometimes I even touch their books
like onion's point diary
I know a lot from that
Diary?
I didn't know she'd react that way
Even ask me out tonight
She wants...
to see Onion's diary
But when did I write diary?
Sorry, I really can't...
It's okay. The show is boring
I'll take you back
No, it's fine. Thanks for the ticket
You have a date with someone?
Him
I can take care of myself
Give me a call if you need me
Diary, diary...
The whole diary in one day?
What the hell. No time
Excuse me. I am late
It's alright. I am early
This is...
I think you better not see it
You might feel upset
You know point alphabet?
Sure, more than ten years...
I specialize in the blind
Could you read it for me?
Okay
Where to start?
Where you met each other
Sunny...
That's it?
No, there's more...
October 16, 1997, Sunny, Vomit
Dr. Woo said it's medical reaction
A new nurse came taking care of me today
Her name is Autumn Yue
She is clumsy
She kept saying...
"Sorry"
She made a mess,
but I didn't pick on her
I even feel good about her
Why am I still talking fine?
She doesn't know that I am Onion
I am just someone reading Onion's diary
Go on
November 2nd, 1997, Rainy night
Autumn said she'll come give me...
a hair cut after work
It's raining so hard. She might not come
She is already 49 minutes late
Feeling disappointed,
I heard footsteps hurrying up
"Sorry..."
Sorry. I'm late again
49-minute is nothing
I was thrilled she came
Finally, she finished
It looked like an onion
She starts calling me Onion ever since
December 7, 1997, Sunday, Good day
It's the second time Autumn cut my hair
I can smell her
Just when I was enjoying
My left ear hurt so much suddenly
And I heard she keep saying...
I'm sorry
Oh, I cut you ear
You're bleeding. Are you okay...
I shook my head, saying: Nothing!
She's all freaked out, almost crying
If only I could talk, I'll say
I am so happy she comes
Just a little pain. No big deal
Enough!
Stop it
I am sorry. Please burn it
Wait!
He pointed all that,
and rub it on the street
Don't you want to know more?
What happen if I know it all?
You won't understand how I feel
Only Onion will
He's dead. What's the diary for?
To save your memory?
No
I say
Just now...
I felt Onion's back
I used to think I just pitied him
Then he died
And I realize
it is so painful without him
I love him all the time
Why didn't I tell him?
I wanted him to know
I wished he's the one playing sax
Why didn't I ask?
My second wish is to be with him
Why didn't I say it?
Now I can't
Can it start all over?
What's memory for?
Just one day...
Give me one more day, can I?
Please!
You!
Why did you crash him? Why?
None of my business...
He rushed out...
Come on! Hit me!
I have nothing after all!
I shouldn't have come back!
I shouldn't have. Let me go!
Hit me!
I miss you so much...
You always miss me, huh?
Sit
What do you want to drink?
Anything
Your daughter?
Salty Lemon Seven
Thank you
Not so much. You will drop dead
You want to die?
No, I don't
My neck sores. Give me a message
When are you leaving?
Taiwan
Two more days
Are you coming back?
No
Sit
You're leaving, why stir things up?
Can't take anything with you
I know now
I just want to see her
If she's happy, I'll be happy
Now and see
Don't think too much
If she knew Onion's leaving again
She's be upset once again
What's that?
You want a florist shop, don't you?
My investment
Can't take it with me. Not in Taiwan
Okay
I'll sent you some later
What do you want there?
I'm going
Take care
Right...
If you see my daughter
Take good care of her
I will
Don't bug others anymore. Go
Not fair occupying other's thing
Hello, it's you
Me
Can't hear you. What's your name?
Cheuk
What do you want to talk about?
I wanted...
to phone-in long time ago
But I can't
In two days, I had to go
I've done everything
So I try this
Nothing special
You've done everything,
you feel good?
Better than a few days ago
A few days ago?
You felt bad a few days ago, why?
I saw the reality of the world
Ugly world,
you mean?
No, not ugly
But seeing it through your eyes
The world's different
Through eyes, you'll have greed
You want to possess her
The eyes fool
Interesting
Give us more details
Try not to see with eyes
Quietly close your eyes
In this minute of silence
Feel with your purest heart
You may find everything different
Feel the beauty and
happiness with heart
You'll have rooms...
of imagination
You seem to know yourself
Could you hold?
We'll talk more
Now, let's go to music
Okay, audience
If you have experience...
like Cheuk's
You might want to try
close your eyes,
it may help
You scare me!
Sorry
I shouldn't call you so late
Never mind. What's the matter?
I know it is not scientific
But I really feel it, he's back
Slow down. Who's back?
Onion...
He's back with me
Very close
I don't believe in paranormal
I know how your feel
Just imagination. You miss him too much
It happens...
when a friend died
Should I come over?
That's not necessary
I know what you mean
I know you'd say that
But it's not imagination
Onion is back
Okay now
Sorry, I bother you
Thanks. Good night
Good night
this is the real Cheuk
The one we met is a crook
I've checked
He's on vacation, in US
For your own safety,
don't meet with him
Let's report to the police, shall we?
No. He didn't come again
Are you alright?
Take care of yourself
This is my final night
Why do you tail her all day?
Can you make her happy? I can help
That's not me
The one who played sax wasn't me
I don't want to lie to you
You mean Onion played it?
It's Cheuk
Cheuk!
Cheuk! Cheuk...
Come out! Onion!
Cheuk! Onion, come out quick!
I know you're here!
You're not coming out, are you?
Are you okay?
What's wrong with you?
You want to kill yourself?
Stupid!
I should have known you're Onion
And you're the one who played sax
Onion!
Freeze, Onion!
I am not him
Onion's blind and dumb, and dead
Stop imagining things
There's other for you. Such a fool!
I am the Cheuk. You know it
No, you're not
No, I'm not
I am a liar. I'm fooling you
You satisfy?
You've disliked me, haven't you?
Is there something...
you can't say?
Is there a special reason?
Why do you reject me?
I didn't...
I am not him
Fine
That night...
you just touched one line of the diary
and you told me...
everything about us
How could you know?
Unless you are Onion
It's fine you don't admit
You must have a reason
Just don't leave me alone
I am so careless
I didn't realize
until I see all the proofs
I am so dumb
Are you going now?
Yes, I had to
You'll never see me again
I am not anyone...
Forget it, Onion is dead
He never comes back
You must take care yourself
Go! Go!
Okay!
Excuse me, please wait
I have one last question
If you were him,
Seeing the one he loves so painful
What do you want her to do?
Forget me and love someone else
Live happily again
Let go of the painful memories
Okay! I'll tell him now
I've forgot his death
I won't carry the pains with me!
I will love someone again
And that's you!
But he stays...
in my heart
It's fine if you don't admit it
I don't care if you're Cheuk
But I know, I always love...
Who is the one I always love
Onion, you listen up
I love this person in front of me!
Don't go away
Don't leave me alone...
This is...
the meteor shower night
China is the best place to see it
I'll be here with you tonight
Onion told me
Your first wish was that he could watch
the meteor shower with you
It's the same you watch it with me
There's no meteor shower yet
You're a good person. God will help you
Then help me keep Onion!
Stay with me forever, would you?
That's my second wish
Onion had a second wish too
But it's already impossible...
It's 2:30 in the morning
Ten minutes to go...
for the peak hour
I wonder if Cheuk...
...will call again tonight
Hello, I'm Cheuk
I appreciate people caring about me
I want...
to say something to my love
Why not say it directly to her?
Because...
of fate
When I didn't expect anything
I owned her love unexpectedly
When I wanted her...
or made a choice
she went away, disliked me
I am leaving soon
Keeping the most unforgettable moment
Laughter or tears
I hope every bits of memory
be with the one I love most
Carry on with her life. Be strong...
Five days is very short
I want to tell friends in the air
Hold what you have
Now, or in the future
Even if it slips away...
I have no regret of this life
That's so touching
If only you were my boyfriend
May I offer any help?
Could you play a song...
for my love?
Sure. Let's go for the meteor shower
Before I hang up
I hope everyone close your eyes again
Feel the one...
by your side with your heart
You'll have better feeling
Meteor shower!
I've fulfilled my first wish
Make a wish, quick
No...
I did last time, you still have to go
Come back
when the meteor showers
"Wait for you"
Finally, I know what is meteor shower
The tears of the sky...