Starring: Yam Sai-Kwun;
Cheung Wan; Li Lu; Fung Hak-On;
Lai Man; Chin Yuek-San
"Buddha Be Praised"
Guest stars: Wong Fu; Ng Ma
Set decorator: Chin Chun
Make-up: Chan Pang-Hung
Wardrobe: Chu Shing-Mo
Props: Wong Shung-Cheong
You should work harder.
- I need more of your guidance.
- Sure! Let's go and have a wash.
- Brother.
- What's up?
How do you do the Dragon Fist
and Tiger Limb moves?
Why didn't you ask me earlier?
I forgot. Could you show me
some of your moves?
All right. But I may hurt you.
Come on.
You idiot!
You made me look like a fool.
Get up!
- Ready?
- Go ahead. I'm not afraid of you.
Good!
Four.
- It's one!
- You're always so lucky.
You lost!
Can you help me with this, Husker?
Husker!
He was here a moment ago.
Where did he go?
Husker!
Shit! It's broken.
- I could have had that for dinner.
- What's so great about eggs anyway?
If I get any more,
I'll let you know.
But isn't eating eggs
against the rules?
Let me ask the master.
There's no need to disturb him.
I'd better,
otherwise he may punish me.
Why don't you sit down?
Let's talk about it. Go on, sit.
I've got a lot of work to do -
grind down the rice, wash it...
I really don't have time
for chatting.
- I'll do the work for you.
- You'll do it?
Really?
Sure, sit down a moment.
Let's talk about it.
- OK, this time only!
- Fine. Sit here, sit down.
I got you. You broke the eggs.
I'll go and tell the master.
Husker!
Now what?
I'll do the work myself. I'll do it!
That's more like it.
Time for lunch.
Lunch is ready, Husker.
However hard you train,
you'll never be strong enough
to get your revenge.
Do you want to try me?
I know how good you are.
But I always beat you,
don't forget that.
But I never use my full power.
Use more power
to fight with me right now.
I will... some other time.
Why not now? Come on!
It's lunch time!
Well, am I strong enough?
Not bad, but you're not good enough
to fight the Manchus yet.
"However hard you train,
"you'll never be strong enough
to get your revenge.
"But you're not good enough
to fight the Manchus yet."
'The Manchus?'
You're getting in my way!
My friend.
I'm taking a shower.
This is not a playground.
- Please, stop messing around.
- We're not messing. Come on!
You old fool, why didn't you give
my man credit yesterday?
- I've come to buy the goods now.
- That's right.
- 100 kilos of noodles.
- 10 jars of vinegar.
Noodles for you, vinegar for him.
And I'll have 50 salted fish.
That's really a lot. I haven't got
that much in my little shop.
Please go somewhere else.
You don't want to do business
with us. Let's have some fun.
I'm going to break this jar.
Please... Please.
Go to hell!
What are you staring at?
Please... Please stop it.
Now see who's asking for favours.
- Get out!
- Move!
You bloody Manchus. I'll break
your arms if you do that again.
- Let's go!
Uncle Dak! Uncle Dak!
Are you all right, Uncle Dak?
I'm useless! I must get revenge!
Uncle Dak.
How sad! How sad!
We are all
under the control of the Manchus.
In their minds,
our lives are worthless.
Don't be so upset.
You should join the Shaolin Temple.
You can learn
how to defend yourself there.
The Manchus are a mean bunch.
If I wait two more years,
then more people will die.
No. I must go now.
But how can I leave
the Shaolin Temple?
Nobody leaves this place
without first passing the challenges.
'What should I do?'
Husker!
It's you?
Who did you expect?
Of course it's me.
Are they going to take me back
to the temple?
You've broken the rules, Husker.
The Abbot has expelled you
from the Shaolin Temple.
Brother...
Enough. Master ordered me
to give you the challenges
so you're better qualified
to deal with life's problems.
Buddha be praised.
The first challenge.
You didn't guard your right side.
The second challenge.
Protect both your head and your legs.
The third challenge.
Use both your hands and your legs.
Brother!
Give me the fourth challenge.
Guard your body
when attacking and defending.
Thank you very much, masters.
Buddha be praised.
Brother, thanks for helping me
while I was at the temple.
Don't mention it. Get up.
From now on, you'd better be smart
and take care of yourself.
Go to see Tak,
if you have any problems.
Here's some money,
put it in your pocket.
Thanks a lot, brother.
Don't forget.
"Hoh Heng Dye Factory"
Brother...
- Morning.
Go and do your shopping.
Don't forget today is Mum's birthday
so come straight home after work.
Yes, I know, you old nag.
- I'll find you a deaf husband.
- I'm not talking to you any more.
- Good morning.
Not bad, eh?
- What are you doing?
- You don't need to pay.
I'll pay for it later.
Are you serious? All my customers
pay for their fish straightaway.
- Bastard!
- You must pay now.
You can't leave like that.
- Pay up!
- Why should I?
Do you want to lose your business?
Bloody Manchus! A curse
on all your newborn children.
- What are you doing?
- Are you blind?
You're taking advantage of me.
Are you trying to rape me?
I'm not afraid of you!
When I was a prostitute, I could
handle more than 10 men in a day.
- Why are you going into my house?
- Please don't!
Oh, tough guys?
How dare you bully me!
If I open my legs,
you won't be able to move me.
I'm moving!
Get over there!
Come on. Come on.
- Come on. Come on!
- Go away!
- Do you want to see a live sex show?
- Please stop! You're hurting me!
Get out!
Sit down and shut your mouth.
- You're very pretty, too.
- Leave my face alone!
Help!
Do you want to have an orgy with us?
No way!
I'm not a prostitute any more.
If you rape me,
you'll have very bad luck!
You old bitch.
How dare you say such a thing!
- Keep your hands off me!
- Sit down.
Did you enjoy it? You enjoyed it!
Don't touch me!
Who cares about you?
Let's go.
You first. You first.
Here it comes!
- Where's Liang?
- Over there.
- Liang!
- Hello.
Liang!
- I'll be back.
- This way.
What's the matter? Tell me.
- Liang.
- Don't cry.
Come on, tell me, what's the matter?
Is it true?
Come with me!
Who the hell did that to her?!
- Where's my sister?
- In her room.
Sister!
Who... Who did this to you?
Who? Tell me...
Who did it? Tell me!
Sister!
Tell me who did it!
Tell me! Tell me! Who did it?
- Liang.
- Who did it?
We'd better leave her in peace
so she can rest.
They wanted to rape me, too.
Bloody Manchus!
- What? Manchus did that?
- Yes. Please... don't grab me...
Who was it?
I don't know his name,
but he had a fan in his hand.
Son of a bitch!
Sister!
- Sister! What are you doing?
- Daughter!
Daughter!
Sister... Sister!
Why did this have to happen to her?
Sister! Sister!
Daughter! Daughter!
Liang, where are you going?
I'm going to kill that Manchu.
There are so many of them.
How do you know which one did it?
I don't care. I'll kill all of them!
- Let me go!
- Liang!
Please don't go. You're
the only child I have left now.
- I have to go and kill him.
- Please don't go...
Mum! Mum...
Please... don't do that.
Get up. Get up.
OK, I'm not going.
He's very naughty,
and never listens to what I say.
- He really gives me a headache!
- Kids are all like that.
- Can I join you?
- Go away! You're blocking my way.
- Get lost!
You don't want me...
- Give it back!
- Jump and get it.
Pass it to me.
If you catch it, it's yours.
- Give it back!
You broke our shuttlecock,
so you have to buy us a new one!
- You like playing shuttlecock?
- Of course!
- Do you want me to get a new one?
- Yes! Yes!
My braid?!
You cut off my braid!
I want it back, give it back!
How do you like
your new shuttlecock?!
I want it back!
Catch!
I want it back.
Give me back my braid!
OK, I'll give it back to you.
Give me back my braid.
Here's your braid.
I want it back. Give me back
my braid. I want it back.
They all had their braids cut off.
You were trying to escape,
little bugger!
Let's teach you a lesson.
You seem to be
the bravest of the lot.
Little brat!
I'll make you cry now!
Great men shed blood, not tears.
I'm not going to cry.
Cowards!
My hair will grow long again soon.
You're just a big bully.
Pick on someone your own size!
It's none of your business.
You're just a show-off!
You're quite right. I am a show-off.
- Let's get out of here.
- OK.
Are you leaving, too?
God, you're really heavy!
OK, they've got their own back.
You can let me go now.
Let you go? Not a chance!
Come here, come here. Have you ever
played tug of war before?
- We have!
- Let's have a game.
- You pull his head, I pull his legs.
- Great!
Please stop! Please stop!
Let go of me!
The Manchu deserves all he gets.
A Manchu?
A Manchu killed my sister.
'Manchu! Manchu! Manchu!'
- Why are you stabbing him?
- Don't stop me!
Don't stop me! I want him dead.
Let me kill him. I want him dead.
- Why are you doing this?
- A Manchu raped my sister.
- Was it him?
- I don't know, but he's a Manchu.
You don't know who he really is.
Look, you've killed him. Now what?
- I've got to go. Bye!
- Stop! Stop!
Damn, they'll think I did it.
I'd better get out of here now!
- He's dead!
- We're too late!
Who would dare kill a Manchu?
It must be the people
from the dye factory.
No one else would have the guts
to do it.
OK! Get rid of them!
- You'd better come back early.
- All right.
The Manchus are coming!
Boss, a group of Manchus
are coming this way.
Really?!
Get the weapons!
- What do you want?
- Hand over the murderer.
What murderer?
Who killed him?
How should I know? I have no idea.
- Find the killer.
- Yes, sir!
He's not here.
- He must be hiding. Check inside!
- Yes, sir!
Wait! These grounds belong
to the factory.
You can't throw
your weight around here.
What if you can't find him?
If we can't find him, you'll be fine.
Otherwise you're in big trouble.
- Go!
- Yes, sir!
Follow them.
- Make sure they don't do any damage.
- Yes, sir!
No.
No! Go that way!
No, there's no one inside.
Now what?
It's not over yet.
I'll get you sooner or later.
Let's go!
"Sai Sin Temple"
What? You left the Shaolin Temple.
Brother,
I can't wait to get my revenge.
What?! You're not the only one.
So many people want to get
their revenge on the Manchus.
You're the luckiest one
because your kung fu is so good.
Many of them
can't even defend themselves.
I sent you to the Shaolin Temple
for a reason.
I was hoping after you graduated,
you could help the community.
But you're as stubborn
and selfish as ever.
You only care about
getting your revenge.
Brother, what should I do, then?
You should put aside your hatred
and be patient.
If you do that,
you'll achieve your goals.
- Do you understand?
- I understand.
- Why the long face, then?
- What do you expect?
Smile. I want you to smile! Come on!
That's more like it.
From now on, you should
at least appear to be happy.
I have a student called Liang.
His sister was raped by a Manchu
a few days ago.
When she got home she was so upset
she committed suicide.
Liang wants revenge, too.
- But I told him to be patient...
- Master!
Talk of the devil!
This is the man I was talking about.
- Master! Master...
- Liang, my colleague, Husker.
- It's you.
- You know each other?!
I met him before in your place.
Right.
Husker just left the Shaolin temple.
How do you do?
Master, your wine.
Liang works at the dye factory.
His boss is a good friend of mine.
I often teach his workers kung fu.
As you know, I'm always busy.
Now you're here,
you can teach the workers for me.
When their kung fu is good enough,
the Manchus won't bother them again.
- Whatever you say!
- That's great!
If Husker teaches us, then we can
really teach the Manchus a lesson!
There you go again!
Stop that nonsense!
You had enough boring vegetables
and tofu in the temple.
I'll get you something nice tonight.
- What is it?
- I know.
- I know. It's...
- Enough talk!
- Master, you're a hungry man.
- Let's go. Stop talking nonsense.
Very tasty!
I'll have that.
This hot pot is delicious!
It's really tasty!
Yeah! Cheers!
Why do they put the sheep's heads
up there?
They use them
to draw in the customers.
The fools think they're serving lamb
here, but it's really dog meat!
I'm thinking of going to this place.
But you're too chicken to come.
- I fear nothing!
- Oh, really?!
Yes, really.
- Have you finished?
- Yes.
- I'm ready.
- Waiter! The bill!
Roast peanuts!
Get your roast peanuts here!
Here we are!
- Are you here for some fun, too?
- Yeah.
Even you need sex.
- Let's go inside.
- Come on.
"Madame Fifi's"
Roast peanuts!
Come here!
- What's the problem?
- You're both mad!
What did you bring me here for?
- You know about my vow of celibacy.
- But you just ate dog meat.
That's different!
- Come on!
- Leave me alone!
I've had enough!
Liang, you take care of your master.
I've got to go. Sorry, Brother!
Master! What about me?
- If your wife doesn't mind, go on.
- All right!
Don't come looking for my help
if you pick up any diseases.
I only treat physical injuries.
I won't be that unlucky!
This way!
Some tea for Mr Cheung!
- This way, sir!
- All right.
I want to see Ah Sung. Quick!
Husker, Husker.
- Where's your master?
- Outside!
I want to have some fun, too.
Uncle Feng! Uncle Feng!
- I haven't seen you for a while.
- I was away.
- Are you looking for Ah Kim?
- That's right!
Come on, quick.
Were you away fishing again?
Yes, I was alone at sea
for a few months.
I can't wait any longer.
I'm desperate to see Ah Kim.
- Right. Right...
- Quick! Quick!
Hurry up!
- What's wrong with your pipe?
- It's blocked.
It was fine before.
- Is it OK now?
- It's fine. It's fine again.
- Hurry up! Hurry up! Go!
- Yeah!
I'm going! I'm going!
There, the door's closed.
How many of you?
- Do you know any of the girls here?
- I do. I can introduce you.
- I'd like to look around first.
- All right.
This way!
- See you later.
- Enjoy yourselves!
So pretty!
- Come on...
- No...
Come on! Don't be shy!
Open your mouth.
I said no.
- Why not? Why not?
- No...
You didn't mind before.
Come on, there's a good girl.
There's no need to be shy.
I don't do it on the first
or the fifteenth of the month.
What shall I do, then?
Just do it the normal way.
Is there anyone you fancy?
You're not looking for a wife!
Buy me a drink.
Don't come here if you're so shy!
Get lost!
Sorry! Sorry!
It's you two. Nice girls.
Have a good time!
Go on!
Stop!
That's the guy.
Did you kill Fang?
Was that no?!
I didn't kill him.
- Who was it, then?
- Tell us!
- I don't know...
Get back here.
So you want to leave, do you?
Then you'll have to crawl under
everyone's legs.
- Go on!
- Hurry up! Crawl!
- Crawl!
- Come on!
Let's go back upstairs.
That's all, folks.
Who hit me?
Brother, why did you hit me?
You are such a coward!
How could let them
walk all over you like that?
You're the one who told me
I should be patient.
There's a limit.
You can't let them do that to you.
- No?!
- Of course not!
You said it.
This is a donation from them
to your temple.
How could he do that?
Stop it! Please! My furniture!
Who is it?
Master!
Watch him fight.
You can learn a lot from him.
Stop moving your head, mister!
You're blocking my view.
I can't help it.
I spend most of my time at sea.
I think your real problem
is you come here too often.
- What?!
- I'm leaving!
Crawl!
It's over. Let's go!
Get up! Quick!
It's all over. Go back to your rooms!
- Master, he's a great fighter.
- Of course!
Don't forget
we learnt kung fu together.
- Brother.
- You're very naughty.
Now they're happy!
I'm very happy now.
Kao and Lo are going to help us.
They'll be here right after work.
- You think they can do it?
- They're not that great, are they?
You'll see for yourselves soon.
We'll control the whole city
in less than three months' time.
That really hurts.
Keep going!
- Cheers!
- Tuck in!
- Right! Right!
- Help yourselves!
- Tuck in.
You have this.
Let me top you up.
You two can live here.
There's something
I'd like you to help me with.
No problem! We're on the same side.
If you need help, just let us know.
I scratch your back,
you scratch mine.
This is the situation.
We, the Manchus,
control everything in this area.
However...
the Hans are the only ones
who are making any money.
The fact is, their property
should belong to us.
And we have a right to it.
The Hans are a useless lot
who work at Hoh Heng Dye Factory,
but they think
they are really powerful
and keep getting on our nerves.
I say we must get rid of them.
That's no problem.
After you get rid of them,
you can do anything you want here.
- Down in one!
Try this!
- Try this?!
- Stop it!
I'll be gentle.
Stop! Don't run away from me.
I'll catch you.
Let her go!
Don't worry.
Step aside.
Stop!
Why are you here, brother?!
They think I've been working too hard
so they gave me two months holiday.
Who was that man? He was so rude!
We've hired them to help us, brother.
I've told you many times,
don't think your brother
is a high-ranking official
just so you can cause trouble.
It won't do either of us any good.
I'm going to have a rest.
Behave yourself!
- Let's continue our meal!
- Let's continue!
Don't drink so much
if you can't take it.
Come on!
Why is the master not coming?
His brother just came back and
they want to have a good long chat.
It makes no difference which of us
goes, I also know it very well.
I need 3,000 lengths of cloth
in five days, can you do it?
Yes, I can.
You have to have them ready on time,
otherwise I'll be in trouble.
You'll be in trouble, too.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
Don't make up your mind so quickly.
If you go back on the deal,
you'll have to give me your whole
factory as compensation.
Trust me!
There won't be any delays.
Good! Good!
- Let me give you the deposit.
- OK!
Sign your name
on the bottom of this contract.
Of course!
Good! Good!
- I'm leaving.
- All right.
I'll pick up the cloth in five days.
- Have a nice day, goodbye!
- Take care!
- Liang?!
- Yes!
Cheng, take over.
- What's up, boss?
- Go and get 50 containers of dye.
- That much!
- The deadline is very soon. Just go!
I'm going right now.
- Where are you going?
- To get dye!
See you later!
We haven't got that colour.
What about other colours?
- You haven't. Never mind!
- Bye!
- How can I help?
- Do you have red dye?
I'm sorry! We just sold out.
Try somewhere else.
Sold out?!
Sold out...
- Hello!
- Hi.
Do you have any red dye?
Red? We had a lot two days ago.
- What about now?
- We still have...
- Great! Can I have 50 containers?
- ..to wait for the next shipment.
That's no, then!
If you want to order it,
you must leave a deposit.
No way!
What should we do?
If we don't give them the cloth
on time, we'll be in big trouble.
Can't we delay the order?
Are you kidding?
I've signed my name on the contract.
If I don't give it to them on time,
they'll take my factory.
- You shouldn't have signed it.
- What? I thought it was a good deal.
- But...
- Stop there.
- He asked you to sign a contract?
- Yes.
And he wants it in five days?
With no delays!
- Can you get the dye from the shops?
- No, none of them has it.
Even the wholesaler hasn't got it!
There's something... funny going on.
I think so, too.
They can't all be
out of red dye at the same time.
And also, that old man's face
was very familiar.
The Manchus must have set us up.
The Manchus!
That's it! It's the Manchus!
"Aoi Lo Ane House"
Are you sure that's it?
I've worked there for years.
Of course I'm sure.
- Husker, well done!
- Your men did all the work.
- Don't forget to reward them.
- I won't forget.
Let's get to work.
- We've got them this time.
- Yes, you're right.
My plan is really good, isn't it?
If they don't have the cloth on time,
we can legally take over the factory.
You two will be in charge of it.
You'll soon be businessmen.
You don't have the cloth ready,
do you?
It's ready.
You...
Don't waste our time.
Pay up
once you've checked the cloth.
You...
- Our dye was stolen!
- What?!
- Tell them to go over there first.
- Go over there now.
What are you doing?
Come here!
Help! Get off me!
What do you think you're doing?
Get off her!
- What are you doing?
- Bitch! Go to hell!
Come on!
Bitch!
Cheers!
- Let's have a game!
- Hang on!
We made a lot of money,
but the Manchus
really made fools of themselves.
I wish Husker was here as well.
We should celebrate with him.
We can do that another day.
Cheers, everybody!
Get them!
Stop there!
You first!
I want them all dead!
You really are useless!
Ah Chen! Ah Chen!
Master...
you're always telling me
to be patient.
My whole family has been murdered.
Even my mother was killed.
I've had enough of being patient.
Husker... This is the last favour
I'll ever ask you to do for me.
- Please...
- I know what to do.
Buddha be praised.
What are we waiting for? Let's go!
Let's make a toast.
We don't need to worry about them
any more.
Buddha be praised.
You're still alive.
Why are you here?
Don't be so surprised.
We're here for your funeral.
Bullshit! We'll kill you!
Buddha be praised.
Buddha...
Hold it!
- Brother...
- Enough. I know everything now.
This is my house! How dare you
come here and kill my men!
An eye for an eye,
a tooth for a tooth.
How dare you?! Kill them!
Go to hell!
Buddha be praised.
Subtitles by
European Captioning Institute