HAPPY TIMES
The ones I saw before
were all too skinny.
Looked like kittens.
I told the matchmaker straight out,
no skinny women for me!
I like them fleshy, nice and warm!
What does a man my age need?
Somebody to keep me cozy!
I've been married twice.
I like a woman with experience!
I've also got two kids.
Two kids?
I love kids!
The more the merrier!
Shall we start planning
our wedding?
So you agree?
Let's make our wedding
a real event!
Of course!
We can't just go through the motions.
I agree.
Everyone knows me...
I can't be a cheapskate.
We'll need 50 grand.
That's about right!
You've got 50 grand?
I shouldn't have a problem getting it.
I'll figure it out.
No problem.
Old Zhao's back
to borrow money!
- How do you know?
- Look, he's coming.
He's trying to get hitched again.
This is the 18th time!
Hasn't worked out once!
He still owes me money!
I've gotta get out of here.
Tell him I'm not home.
Fu! Stop!
Fu! Stop pretending
you don't hear me!
Zhao, what's wrong?
Stop it! You saw me.
- I didn't.
- Stop playing stupid!
You must know I need cash.
Engaged again?
I finally found one.
Look at her!
Big and round.
- Japanese?
- No, Chinese.
Don't you like skinny women?
But they never like me!
She does, she wants to get married.
- Really?
- She told me so.
- No strings?
- She said we need 50 grand.
50 grand! Did you say okay?
Of course.
If you haven't got it, why bullshit?
If I didn't bullshit,
I'd be up the creek!
Find someone else to help.
Come on.
Help your old teacher.
You're the only one I can turn to.
Zhao! Zhao!
I've got some money.
- Money!
- Where from?
Look!
From this?
Here's the woods
behind our factory...
...isn't there an old bus there?
For 7 or 8 years.
Every day, young lovers
stroll back there...
...with no place to unwind!
We'll clean up that bus...
...the lovers can use the place.
We'll charge them.
Me sell tickets?
Exactly.
I even have a name
for the place.
We provide a service for these kids.
We'll call it the
"Happy Times Hut."
Forget it!
This is a public area.
Who'd pay for this?
Why not be rewarded
for our hard work?
What I'm saying is...
...who in their right mind
would pay to go into an old bus?
You're just sitting
home anyway.
No matter what we charge,
it's money.
I'll never get married this way.
You may get someone
who'd pay...
...200 or 300 in one shot.
Who'd do that?
You'd have to be crazy!
Anyway I don't have the money.
If you don't like my idea,
my hands are tied!
You're using that color?
How come it reminds me of
a public toilet?
Stop painting!
Public bathrooms are this color.
You're right!
I found this paint in the dump.
It's all they had!
What do you expect for free?
Let's try this one.
It's so loud.
It's like "all night long" red.
That's it!
Keep them awake
long enough to pay.
Let's go with the "all night long" red.
"All night long" it is!
All right!
Not bad at all.
A good fix- up and it looks like new.
I still don't feel good about this.
There you go again.
We've got a good,
clean place here.
So people can unwind.
What are you worried about?
Remember why we're doing this.
- Wow!
- Who fixed this place up?
What a romantic color!
It's even got a name:
"Happy Times Hut."
Not bad?
Come in. Have a look.
You two did this?
There's a collection box?
Give what you want, you decide.
Have some water.
Don't worry.
We already checked.
You can't see in from outside.
Not a bad place to get out of the sun.
Excuse me, sir!
Did you fix this place up?
What do you want?
Nothing, just wondering why?
What's inside?
Nothing. It's not mine.
C'mon, we just want to have a look.
It's mine. But I'm off work.
Sir, let us take a look.
Just a peek.
You can't see a thing.
A collection box.
"Let your conscience be your guide."
Pretty unique.
Sir, are you going to just sit there?
I always sit here.
Don't you want to get some fresh air?
Am I in your way?
What are you talking about?
What are you up to, then?
Nothing.
Trying to bribe me?
Your years are catching up with you,
old man.
Giving you ideas.
I just wanted you
to buy us some stuff.
What?
A watermelon.
A big one.
A 100- yuan watermelon?
I don't have anything smaller.
Thanks for helping us out.
Sorry I haven't called,
I've been swamped with work.
At the hotel.
No, I opened it up with a few colleagues.
Why would I mention it
on our first date?
It's the busy season.
Oh, yeah, it makes money!
No matter how much I'm worth,
I won't forget you.
You're the reason I work so hard.
- Do you sell roses?
- 2 yuan each.
- How much?
Too expensive!
What other flowers
make a good gift?
That depends.
Women want roses.
It's a woman all right.
Then roses.
Anything cheaper?
Look at you, you're a disgrace!
We'd be better off if you died!
Feeding you is a waste!
Mom, some grandpa is here!
So soon!
What do you mean grandpa?
Call him uncle.
Have a seat. Excuse me
while I change clothes.
How old are you?
Can you fix my game?
No problem.
Was your mom yelling at you?
No, at her.
Your sister?
She's not my sister.
My mom didn't have her!
Whose is she?
Can't you hurry up, grandpa?
Don't call me grandpa.
Call me uncle.
So hurry up, uncle!
Okay, okay.
Roses for me?
- Must've been expensive.
- 2 yuan a dozen.
I mean, 2 yuan a stem.
Where should I put them?
When the party leaders
visit sick people on TV...
...they put the flowers
beside the bed.
Good idea.
Okay, then.
Sorry you had to hear me
yelling at the kids.
My stepdaughter really drives me nuts!
The day we got divorced,
her father flew the coop.
Took all my money too.
He agreed to pay child support.
I haven't seen a penny.
I do everything for her.
You have a kind heart.
If it were me...
...I'd get her father to take her.
Turn her out?
How'd that look?!
I'd be known as,
"The wicked stepmother!" "Evil woman!"
Let them say what they want.
You've got to look out for yourself.
A strange thing
happened at work today.
What?
A guest gave one of our employees
a 100-yuan tip.
Everyone is rich these days.
He said, "I'll be back soon!"
So your hotel is doing well?
It all comes down to the name.
I came up with it myself.
Just like the two of us
when we're together...
...I call it "Happy Times."
- Are you happy right now?
- Can't you tell?
Tell her it's dinnertime.
Why me again?
How else is she supposed to know?
Hurry up!
- So many dishes!
- I hope you like them.
Don't kick the door!
This kid needs some manners.
Dinnertime!
Please, help yourself.
- Here, have more.
- I'll help myself.
- This is your Uncle Zhao.
- Hi.
Go on, eat up.
Try some vegetables.
- Eat up.
- It's good.
Don't be polite.
Kids...
...always stealing from each other.
Stop playing. Eat!
We had a letter from Dad.
Why didn't I see it?
You weren't home.
Where's the letter?
Mom, I wasn't home either.
I played soccer.
Soccer?
You're a soccer player?
Excuse me while I read this.
What did my dad say?
Nothing, eat.
Tell me what he said.
Nothing. Eat your dinner.
Here's...
You keep it.
You eat with your left hand?
Ever since I was a kid.
What about when you write?
I do everything else right-handed.
Chopsticks too?
Not really.
- Tough, isn't it?
- I still can.
Get some ice cream for uncle too.
- No, thanks.
- Hey, Mom, he doesn't want any!
He's too polite to ask.
Ice cream is for kids.
Why don't you give her a cup?
No way! Ice cream is expensive!
Mom bought it for me.
Who ever said that?
Each of you gets one.
You're getting so selfish.
Go on, eat.
- Take care.
- Okay.
- Call me.
- I will.
Don't think just because we have company,
you can eat the good stuff!
You're listening to TV too!
Go! Wash the dishes!
Shall we put him to bed?
Let him sleep.
Your leg will fall asleep.
It's not... convenient with him here.
I can't move him anyway.
I'll help you.
- What's she doing?
- Going to the bathroom.
Like that?
Yes.
Does she know I'm here?
How could she know?
I should probably go.
Just be quiet.
Let me ask you...
How big is it?
When you say "it"...
...do you mean the hotel?
The hotel.
You want to bring us customers?
No need! Business is booming!
Don't worry about me.
I'm not worried about you...
...what about us?
- What do you mean?
Having her around
isn't convenient.
Can you find her
a job at your hotel?
No, out of the question.
What's wrong with you?
I haven't even finished talking...
And all you say is "no"!
I didn't mean anything by it...
...you tell me, what can she do?
Nothing really.
Just give her some chores!
Let her clean the bathrooms, whatever.
You don't have to pay her.
Just give her some food.
No, I really...
Don't think that
I'm dumping her off on you.
That's not my intention.
Take just now for instance...
...was it convenient when...
...she barged in on us like that?
The hotel is a joint investment.
I'll talk it over with the other owners.
Aren't you the general manager?
Can't you decide things like this?
You're the one who came up with
"Happy Times."
But I wrote, "Hut," not "Hotel!"
No sense arguing.
"Hut" and "Hotel" are almost the same.
Anyway, help me find the girl a job!
Hey, she asked you, not me!
You're the big shot manager.
Besides she can't work anywhere else.
What should I do?
What a mess!
Is this girl completely blind?
If she weren't...
...she wouldn't need our help.
So she can't see a damn thing?
- It should be a snap then!
- How?
Her weakness can play
into your strength.
She's blind,
you can tell her whatever you want.
And my strength?
Being a good bullshitter!
Stop messing with me!
Everyone knows...
...you talk out of
both sides of your mouth!
The only way to the altar
is to keep deceiving her!
Bring the girl to the old bus...
...tell her it's our hotel.
Beat-up places are
all the rage these days!
Say that our style is returning
to the simple life.
I don't think you should
be looking for work.
It's nice staying at home.
Why do you want a job?
I'm talking to you!
Why should I stay there?
It's still your home.
It's not my home!
Then what are you doing
living there?
You should be grateful!
They're nice to you.
You all hate me!
Hate you?
If I hate you so much...
...why would I give you a job?
You're only doing it for her!
What a mouth on you!
I'm over 50 years old, what's wrong
with doing something for a woman?
You wanted out
of that house anyway.
You should blame your father for this.
Would a real man ditch
his own daughter?
He never should have gotten married.
Leaving his child
for someone else to take care of!
He doesn't pay child support!
You can't blame
your stepmother for...
Hey, where are you going?
Why'd you get off here?
What if that bike ran into you?
Hey, I'm talking to you!
Don't touch your watch,
I know what time it is.
What's wrong with you?
- I'm not going to your hotel.
- Why?
None of your business!
How's it none of my business?
- I promised your mom...
- She's not my mom!
Okay, my girlfriend then.
We agreed that I give you a job.
If you don't go, what do I tell her?
- You really don't want to go?
- No!
That's just fine!
There's nothing great
about my hotel anyway.
But do me one favor,
Tell her the hotel was nice...
...but you didn't want the job.
- Can you do that?
- No!
Why not?
It's not that hard to do.
Then you tell her!
Stubborn kid!
Why are you so difficult?
You can't blame my dad!
I was wrong, okay?
Do you know how hard it is
for a man my age to find a wife?
By chance I met your mom and...
She's not my mom!
Okay!
She trusted me to find you a job...
...and I end up screwing up the whole thing.
I beg you.
Come work at my hotel.
If you don't like it, leave.
That way, at least I did
what she asked me to.
All right?
What am I going to do with you?
Will you please go with me?
Name?
We're filling out an application for you.
All employees must fill it out.
The guy talking to you
is Manager Fu.
He's in charge of daily operations.
From now on, call him Manager Fu.
- Okay, go ahead!
- Name?
Wu Ying.
- Wu Ying, that's spelled W... U...
- Got it.
Ying as in yellow.
How do you write that?
Like this!
Oh, okay, I've got it!
I'm so used to the computer,
I forgot how to write!
- Age?
- 18.
You're 18?
Don't be suspicious.
18 is 18!
Education?
Elementary school,
but I didn't finish.
Was it a school for the blind?
No, I could still see then.
So you lost your sight later?
You have to put all this in?
We need to know all about you...
...to give you a suitable job.
That's right!
Explain what happened to your eyes.
When I was little I had a brain tumor.
It swelled and put pressure
on my optic nerve.
At first I had a headache...
...so bad that I couldn't sleep.
Then, my face started to go numb...
...I lost all feeling...
...on one side of my body.
My vision started to go.
At first
I could still see colors and light...
...but gradually I went completely blind.
Let's go on.
Tell us about your mother.
She's been gone a long time now.
When did you lose her?
Back when I could still see.
So we'll write down
that she's deceased.
We're very interested...
...in learning just when
your father and that...
...that woman got divorced?
Do you know...
...whose fault it was?
Now you're being nosey.
No, this is relevant information!
When we recruit new staff members...
...we need to know everything!
We can't ignore their background.
What if her family comes
and makes trouble?
Go ahead, tell us whose fault it was.
You should explain.
Just to clear this up.
Tell us exactly what happened
with your father.
They started arguing the day
we moved into her apartment.
They'd argue all day and night.
Sometimes they got into fights...
...and threw things all over the place.
No one could reconcile them.
Finally, my dad left.
- Did she ever hit him?
- Where'd your father go?
Far away, to Shenzhen.
He said when he had enough money...
...he'd come back for me
and cure my eyes.
This isn't the main building
of Happy Times Hotel.
This branch is in a secluded
wooded area.
Can you smell it?
Fresh air!
Can you tell?
The scenery is beautiful!
But the design isn't anything fancy.
It's made up of old buses.
The older the bus,
the higher the rate.
It's all about the simple life.
I got this idea listening to customers.
Rich people love it!
Your job is easy.
You just wait outside.
When the guests leave,
you tidy up.
Once you're done, you come back out.
That's all.
I'll bring you lunch
from our employee cafeteria.
Wait a second!
Sir, how come you're
hauling that bus away?
- We're cleaning up this area.
- Who told you to do this?
The boss.
- Where are you taking the bus?
- No idea.
What are you going to do here?
Beautify the area.
What's wrong with you guys?
How many times do I have to tell you?
Keep me informed of everything.
Didn't we decide to start in 2 weeks?
So how come you're here?
Aren't I the boss around here?
I want a full report!
Now get back to work!
What a mess!
We were planning some renovations...
...but they showed up early.
You can't start work today.
Renovations will take a week or two...
...so you'll have to wait.
When you go back,
explain it all to her.
I'm not explaining anything!
Just tell her what happened.
You tell her!
She'd never believe me.
Why should she?
I don't even believe you.
Why don't you believe me?
It sure didn't sound like it.
- Like what?
- People doing renovations.
What do you know about renovations?
We're not putting up wallpaper here.
This is a huge job.
It's not your average hotel.
We're working with a group of buses.
We weren't happy with the location...
...so that crane you heard was
moving the buses to a new one...
...understand?
We are also planting flowers
and grass...
...to liven up the area.
It will still take a month or two...
...you know, for the grass to grow,
the flowers to bloom.
Explain all this to her.
I'm not saying anything!
Then don't!
But don't shoot your mouth off, either.
Excuse us!
Be careful!
How come you're back?
Hands off! That's my piano!
Mom gave this room to me!
Get out! Scram!
Get out!
I don't have room for her.
Do I look like I have
a place to put her?
I replaced her old furniture
with new stuff.
You can't expect me
to change it back?
Of course not.
Now you're talking sense.
Come and check out my new place.
It's got a great vibe.
You'll feel it.
Right now I can't feel a thing.
I'm in one hell of a bind.
Do you have a massage room
at your hotel?
A massage room? What for?
Every hotel today
has a massage parlor.
She studied massage,
she's pretty good.
Open a massage parlor.
All you need is a room and a bed.
Who knows, she might
even bring a profit.
No way. You don't know
what my hotel is like.
Listen, it's a good idea.
It's settled!
But nothing's set up.
- She's leaving!
- Leaving?
Well, go after her!
But don't bring her back to me!
What the hell are you doing?
What if you got hit?
Hold it right there!
What are you trying to pull?
How'd you run so fast?
You scared the hell out of me!
Why were you standing out there?
What, are you sick of living?
If you want to kill yourself,
at least tell me first!
How am I supposed to explain this?
What's wrong with you?
Standing in the middle of the street!
What if you got hit?
What were you thinking?
Say something!
Okay, you're right!
We leave in the morning and now...
...you don't even have a place to stay!
She did go too far!
Don't cry!
Do you have any relatives here?
You can't go off to your father broke.
And he can't come get you right away.
Come with me, okay?
Come back with me.
I'll set up a massage room.
So you can work.
I know you don't trust me...
...but I'm different from her.
I'm disappointed in her too.
What do you say?
Come back with me?
Don't cry.
- This is your apartment?
- Yes
Where's the refrigerator?
Don't have one.
A general manager would
have a refrigerator.
This is, uh, one of our
employee apartments.
Didn't you say this was yours?
My employees and I are one big family.
Their place is my place.
- So where do you live?
- I live...
...in a luxury villa.
Most of my neighbors are foreigners.
I turned on the water heater.
When you're finished...
...turn this faucet.
Don't burn yourself.
I've got a guest staying with me.
Can you lend me a room?
Did you ask your buddies?
They're overcrowded themselves.
Isn't that office of ours empty?
That office is all sealed up.
Any others?
They're off-limits.
What should I do?
How about I stay at the workshop?
Nobody's working there.
Okay. It's going to be demolished
soon anyway.
- So you agree?
- Yes.
- I'm approved?
- Sure.
What's the rush?
Why move this damn thing anyway?
Push! Harder!
Watch your fingers!
Not bad...
...it's starting to look like a room.
Not bad.
- Okay, I'm out of here.
- Wait!
Once the girl feels the sheet metal,
she'll know it's a fake!
We have to figure out something.
What?
Well, next...
...we probably should...
...make this place...
Have you ever been to
a massage parlor?
- Nope.
- You?
- Never in my life.
- And you two?
- Never.
- Me neither.
Then why waste time yapping?
Let's go look at a real one.
Forget this place, too high-class.
Too fancy for us.
- What's this?
- For breathing.
It's huge!
You said to make it
as big as a sink.
I said make it the size of a face.
Didn't you say sink?
No one can possibly
fall through the hole!
Not this side. It's too wide.
Feel with your eyes closed.
It's just like the real thing.
Not bad at all.
Something's not right.
What are we missing?
Our place is more spacious.
No, it's not that.
What's missing?
They had 2 beds...
- We're missing sound.
- What?
Sound, noise!
It's too quiet here.
Why did the other place have
so much noise?
That place was located
right on the main street!
So, there's no sound.
What's the big deal?
Don't be ridiculous!
It's got to seem real.
If the girl is with a client
and it's dead-quiet...
...who will believe
it's a real massage parlor?
We can't move an entire street
over here!
Li, don't you have
a boom box at home?
Take it to a massage parlor
and record the street.
We'll hit 'play',
and the problem will be solved!
On my wedding day...
...all of you will sit
at the head table with me.
Tomorrow when the clients come,
everything will go according to plan.
Oh, no.
Who is she going to massage tomorrow?
We don't have any clients lined up.
What are you laughing at?
I can't bring strangers
to this place.
If they say anything to the girl...
...our work is wasted.
You're my friends.
Come back tomorrow for a massage.
Come back tomorrow?
You don't have to work.
You get a free massage.
Won't she be able to feel it's
the same people over and over again?
Tell the girl she's so good,
you're back for more.
Right. This massage stuff
gets addictive.
Why thank me?
It's all for us, isn't it?
She starts tomorrow.
She's staying at our employee dorm.
Nice place.
Anyway, I just hope you understand
why I'm doing all this.
You know what
my feelings are for you.
I told you to record street noises.
What's this?
The street at the entrance
to the massage parlor.
This is the street?
Does this sound like
a street to you?
I recorded it on the street.
Where'd you put the mike?
Here's the street
and here's the massage parlor...
...I put the box here.
You pointed the mike
in the wrong direction!
Then I'll do it again.
Too late!
She'll be here any minute.
Play it from the other side
of the workshop...
...we'll see how it sounds.
Hurry!
Farther!
Keep going!
That's good!
They're here.
Right now we're going
in the main entrance.
A steel gate, be careful!
We're in the hallway.
Feel this,
over here is an arched doorway.
They really fixed the place up nice.
Feel this.
Linen wallpaper.
Turn here.
Once you come in,
you make 2 lefts.
This is the first.
Feel here.
Left again,
we're at the end of the hallway.
Check it out...
...it's a really big room.
- This massage room is huge.
- Well, our hotel is huge.
A real high-class joint.
This is the massage bed...
...it's a first-rate bed.
The hole's so big.
Whatever we do...
...we do it big.
I'm ready to start now.
I'll wait here for the customers.
Relax! I'll bring a customer
when one arrives.
Manager Zhao!
- How do I look?
- Pretty good.
This is my best outfit.
I save it for special occasions.
I want to make a good impression.
Do you like it?
Yes. It's very pretty.
You're getting massaged
so I can get married...
If you're not paying, we're leaving!
Wait, I just need to figure this out.
You guys enjoy everything
while I foot the bill, is that fair?
Cough up your share!
How much?
10, 20 yuan will do.
How about 2 or 3?
Are you kidding?
At least 5!
Fork over the cash!
I'd pay if I wanted to get married.
Keep it down! I'll pay.
When it comes to money,
you all go nuts!
How can you expect them to pay?
You dropped some.
Don't keep it
to buy a bottle of soy sauce!
Little Wu, I've got a customer for you.
This is Professor Li
from the Teachers College.
A faithful customer.
Hello, Professor Li.
This is Little Wu.
She came to us highly recommended.
This is your tip.
Go ahead. I'll be going.
I'm sorry, Professor Li.
The hole's too big.
Your head must be uncomfortable.
Professor Li,
you used to come here often?
Who massaged you?
A man or a woman?
Am I rubbing too hard?
Just let me know.
How was it?
Keep it down!
I thought I'd died
and gone to heaven.
You were right.
The hole should be as big as a face.
My head had nowhere to rest.
It fell right into the hole.
- You're really an idiot.
- Why?
You didn't act like a real client.
She asked you questions
but you didn't answer.
I didn't know what to say.
Tell her anything.
Don't tell me you don't know
how to make small talk?
Since you know everything,
you go next.
Yeah, Niu, you're next.
Zhao, you go in with me.
I'm the general manager.
I'll give it away if I go in every time.
Don't talk too much.
Pull yourself together!
You look like a bum,
not a restaurant manager!
He's worse than me.
Since when has he ever
kept his mouth shut?
If you don't believe me,
look for yourself!
Let's go look!
Keep it down!
Manager Zhao, is there
an ice cream shop around here?
You want ice cream?
I made money today.
I'll treat you.
I can't let you pay.
There's a place.
I'll go buy the ice cream.
Wait here.
Can I help you?
How much is the cheapest ice cream?
- 25 yuan.
- For how much?
One scoop.
- How big is it?
- About this big.
25 yuan for that?
That store was closed,
so I bought you a popsicle.
- Thank you.
- Eat first, before we go.
Here, have a seat.
Is this Beida Street?
Yeah. It is.
Is it very crowded?
Oh, yeah.
What's everyone doing?
Some are going home,
others are taking their kids out...
...for a walk or going shopping.
What's on your mind?
Manager Zhao, it wasn't easy
for you to find me this job.
I promise I'll work hard.
When I save some money,
I'll find my dad.
We agreed that once he had enough money,
he'd take me to cure my eyes.
You think I can be cured?
No question.
Guess what I want to see most
once I regain my sight.
Your dad, of course.
I want to see you too.
Why do you want to see me?
I want to see what you look like.
You're pulling my leg.
- No, really.
- I'm not easy on the eyes.
What do you imagine
I look like?
Can I touch you?
Touch me?
Anyone can tell that way.
Here, little head, skinny bones.
I'll try.
You tell me how close I am.
- Let's try. Should we stand up?
- Okay.
This is my head.
- Your hair is so short.
- Anyone could tell that.
- How come you're so short?
- Short? How about now?
I wasn't standing up straight.
- You have thick eyebrows.
- Right.
Huge eyes!
Do I have bags under my eyes?
Suitcases!
Naughty girl.
I'll give you 40 yuan.
I paid over 500.
That set is worthless.
It works fine.
If it doesn't,
I won't pay you a penny.
40 yuan is a good deal.
- What color is this dress?
- It's a flower pattern.
What kind of flowers?
Well... the dress is red.
The flowers are...
...they're sunflowers.
- Are they golden yellow?
- Right, with white petals.
And what kind of red?
Deep red, like a big apple.
A big red apple.
- That's my favorite color.
- Well, that's exactly how it is.
- Are there a lot of flowers?
- Tons, too many to count.
Is it too flowery?
Oh, no, it looks great.
I was afraid it might be
too small.
I have a good eye after all.
- Thank you, Manager Zhao.
- No need to thank me.
I'll cut back on coffee
and that'll be that.
Come here!
It stopped playing.
What's wrong?
- How much do you need?
- A thousand or two.
Well, which is it?
2,000.
Fill out this form.
Thank you.
I keep coming back...
...I just can't tell you
how much I appreciate your help.
- Will I get the money right away?
- There is no money.
No money!
You have to wait.
It's an emergency.
The union has money now?
Even the factory doesn't have funds.
So this form is useless.
How come nobody went in?
- We're waiting for you.
- What for?
To hand out the tip money.
To tell you the truth, I'm broke.
Zhao, we just figured out...
...how much all this
will cost you.
Pretty soon you'll be in trouble.
Each of us gives her
5 yuan per tip...
...at twice a day,
that's 50 or 60 yuan.
In 10 days that adds up
to 5 or 6 hundred.
Over 1000 yuan a month.
Plus her salary...
...meals, and everything else.
You'll end up at 2000 a month.
2000 yuan!
You can't afford her.
Guys, I need you to help me out here.
Can you spare any extra dough?
We can scrape together a little.
But it can't last forever.
You know we're all retired...
...and don't have money to spare.
She's a good kid.
We all like her...
...but there is nothing more
we can do.
Tell her the truth.
Sooner or later you'll have to.
We're getting nowhere like this.
We can't stay all day long here.
Better to tell her now.
- Not a single person showed up today?
- Right.
I wonder what happened.
Little Wu?
We need to talk.
Manager Zhao,
I want to tell you something too.
Really? Go ahead.
I don't want to work here anymore.
You want to quit?
- Uh-huh.
- Why?
No reason.
Do you want to go back home?
No.
Then where are you going to go?
I don't know yet.
Why suddenly decide to quit?
Manager Zhao,
please don't worry about me.
I just don't want this job anymore.
At least tell me
where you plan on going.
I haven't figured that out yet.
Just take me to the bus station.
I'll leave by myself.
No way! You're our employee.
We're responsible for you.
You can't just up and leave.
We'll have a meeting
to decide, okay?
Did we give ourselves away?
That's impossible!
We've been so careful.
Maybe she wants to go
to Shenzhen to look for her dad.
She needs money for that.
Shenzhen is pretty damn far.
Does she want to go home?
She said no.
If she wants to go, let her.
It'll save us trouble
and save you money.
But if she leaves, will that hurt
your thing with Chunky Mama?
For sure.
But the point is whether something
might happen to the girl.
Do you think she might kill herself?
Kill herself?
Jump out of a building,
or run into traffic.
- Nonsense!
- She'd never do that!
Don't brush it off so lightly.
You never know
what she may be thinking.
Hey, that reminds me.
Two days ago I was at her home
when she suddenly lost her temper...
...and stormed downstairs.
I followed her.
Guess where I found her?
Standing...
...in the middle of the street.
It was dark and cars were everywhere.
If I arrived a minute later,
she might have been hit.
We definitely can't let her go.
For sure.
If something happens...
...we'll all be screwed.
He's 100% right.
It's no longer just my business.
If the cops come fishing around...
...they'll question my girlfriend.
She'll tell them the girl is here.
Then you'll all be called in.
After all,
this whole place is a scam.
As soon as the police see it,
we're all screwed.
We can't let her leave.
But how can we keep her?
Where do we get the money
to pay her?
I have a new idea.
Since this concerns all of us...
...you all should take responsibility
and put out some cash.
If everyone coughs up a little...
...we can keep things going.
We'll see how things go and...
...decide what to do from there.
First things first,
convince her to stay.
Go talk to her.
We can't let anything happen to her.
We discussed it.
Little Wu, you really can't go.
Everyone feels your work...
...is top-notch.
They're reluctant to part with you.
Besides, all your customers are here.
They said if you leave,
they won't come back.
I'll lose my customers.
Especially Professor Li.
The same goes for Mr. Niu.
They really like you.
They all do.
I like them, too.
If so, why leave?
You've got to stay.
See how things go.
If things aren't good, then go...
...but if everything
goes smoothly...
...there's no reason to leave,
am I right?
Zhao! Zhao!
- Who is it?
- It's me, Auntie Liu. Are you asleep?
How come you're here?
Money?
- Did they all pitch in?
- Take a look.
This must have been...
...a lot of trouble
to scrape together.
My God, what is this?
Close your eyes and feel it first.
You can't tell it's fake.
You want to tip her with this?
Are you kidding?
Aren't you broke?
I know this is a hopeless plan...
...but it'll work for now.
How?
Try it first.
We have no options.
Can you feel the difference?
I can't.
The question is, can she?
If we can't, how could she?
So we tip her with paper money.
Do you have a better idea?
We use this stuff from now on?
For the next few days.
I'll switch it once I find
some real money.
Two bills per person, okay?
Who's first?
It was her idea.
I have to go first
because it was my idea?
You guys know
I can't keep a secret.
We can't risk sending her.
- Who went first last time?
- Li.
Go on, Li!
I'm not going first!
Isn't this dishonest?
We've been lying to her
from the beginning.
We'll be fine if she thinks
it's real money.
And what if she can tell?
Tell her it's a mistake
and you'll bring her tip tomorrow.
Crumple it up a little bit...
...otherwise it feels too new.
Did you tip her?
As soon as I went in.
We got up there too late.
Could she tell it wasn't real?
If she could,
she would've said something.
How did you give it to her?
As you said...
...I crumpled it up.
I put it in my pocket
and went in calmly.
You have to pretend
everything is normal.
Just slowly take it out
and put it in her hand.
- How many fake bills did you give me?
- Two.
Damn! I gave her
my own real money.
That money was
to buy milk for my kid.
Pay me back!
I'm not the one
who made the mistake.
I have to get it back.
How could you be so cheap?
She gave you a massage,
let her keep it.
You made me go first!
I'll pay you back, all right?
That's for you. Your tip.
Thank you.
I watched her the whole time.
Keep it down!
She couldn't tell.
We saw it from up there.
Now we can relax.
We can support her
like this for years.
- What's going on?
- We've succeeded!
We did it!
Each of us went in twice...
...and gave her at least 3 bills.
He even gave her 5.
Didn't I only give you 2 each?
I went home
to get some more paper.
You're making a circus out of this!
You'll blow our cover.
What's more,
if you keep going in like this...
...she'll be able to tell.
Impossible.
The first time, we all went in order.
The second,
we went in a different order.
She couldn't tell!
You think you're so smart.
You gave her your own money before!
You could ruin everything.
She may already know.
Little Wu, I heard you had
a lot of customers today.
I don't know why,
they just kept coming.
Good tips?
They gave a lot!
- No problems?
- Not at all!
- You put the money away?
- It's all here.
- How much do you think you made?
- Several hundred!
They were generous today!
This is the first time
I've ever made so much money.
Now I can rest easy.
Just tell me when
you want to make extra money.
We have a great future ahead.
I want to take you
and Manager Fu to dinner.
But I won't let you pay.
It wasn't easy to make that money.
Save it!
Tonight is my treat!
Wouldn't it be great
if every day could be like today?
Don't worry!
Customers love you.
We haven't even advertised yet.
When we get the word out,
there will be even more.
We get along fine like this.
Thanks to you,
we have a loyal clientele.
We take old customers
and turn away the rest.
Manager Zhao plans
everything out well.
He says it depends on you.
If you don't feel well,
we'll send in fewer people.
But when you want
to make an extra buck...
...we'll have them
lining up at the door!
We control the flow,
just give us the word!
Manager Zhao,
I want to figure something out.
If I make 500 a day,
how much can I make in a year?
Let's figure it out.
500 a day, 10 days, 5000.
30 days in a month, 3 x 5 is 15,
that's right.
So that's 150,000.
- Fu, help me out here.
- 180,000 a year.
150,000 for 10 months, plus
another 2 months comes to 180,000!
For one year?
180,000!
How much money is that?
Are you sure you're right?
Have I ever made a mistake
when it comes to money?
Good heavens!
So much money!
You wouldn't even know
how to spend it.
What would you do with it?
I'd go to Shenzhen
to find my dad.
So he could take me
to cure my eyes.
If they can't do it in Shenzhen,
we'll go to Hong Kong.
If not in Hong Kong,
we'll go to America.
They'll be able to cure
my eyes in America, right?
No question!
What a place America is!
Enough with your blind worship
of America!
With 180,000,
doctors in Beijing will fix your eyes.
And you want to go to America!
Here's to 180,000!
You're wrong again!
Let's drink to Little Wu
finding a cure!
Bottoms up!
- Here, the glass is over here.
- Raise your glass.
Kid, let's drink!
Manager Zhao, could you read
my father's letter to me?
- You saw it before.
- Yes.
I never trusted that woman.
- Do you trust me?
- Yes!
Let me have a look!
Since you trust me,
I'll read you the letter.
"Of the 5,000 yuan
I borrowed from you...
...I lost almost 4,000...
...4,000 in the stock market."
So there's over 1,000 left.
"Because of this...
...I can't return the money right now.
I put aside a portion of it
for my living expenses.
Things are expensive in Shenzhen.
But I'll return that 5,000 yuan
to you soon.
Trust me, I've always been
a man of my word."
That's it!
- What else did my dad say?
- That's it!
You heard it all. He borrowed
5,000 from my girlfriend.
And he lost it on stocks.
Only 1,000 yuan left.
He didn't mention me?
Nope!
Are you sure?
Let me see.
There is a part about you.
On the back.
He wrote so small!
What did he say?
You read it.
- You want me to read it?
- See the back.
Listen!
The characters are all squished.
I can't make heads or tails of it.
How about this...
...I'll take it and read it
once I have my glasses.
Then I'll tell you what he said...
...first thing tomorrow morning, okay?
That's fine.
Can I come see you?
No need?
You mean not ever?
Why?
You can't just change your mind.
What's going on?
Are you serious?
Then I'll come right...
It's Zhao.
So that's Zhao.
I'll put away the flowers.
You two chat.
- Who's he?
- My boyfriend!
Then who am I?!
I told you over the phone.
We broke up!
We've been together for so long...
- How can you do this?
- Stop yelling!
- Who's that guy?
- Out. I'll explain!
You really move too fast!
At least tell me why?
Why? Because you're nothing
but a liar!
Liar?
You still deny it?
What are you still lying for?
I checked you out, mister!
You don't own any Happy Times Hotel!
You've been jiving me from day one!
For instance...
You've been wearing that same shirt
since the day we met.
Is this your only one?
And you call yourself a manager!
What garbage dump
did you dig those roses out of?
They were dead the next morning!
Let me explain.
You're right about
the Happy Times Hotel...
...it was hauled away.
This is the only nice shirt I have,
but I wear it for you.
As for the flowers...
...I bought them for 2 yuan
and trimmed them myself.
But believe me, my intention
to marry you was sincere.
Do you know what I hate most?
Men that lie!
Have you ever said
an honest word to me?
If you're broke, just say so.
Who'd marry you?
You'd sell your wife for the cash.
How could I sell you off?
So there's no hope for us?
Right!
- Let me talk to him!
- No way!
- Hell, I was here before that guy.
- What do you mean?
I already married him.
We're protected by law now,
so give it up!
Don't call me again!
From now on, I don't know you!
You go your way, I'll go mine!
By the way, bring that girl back.
She won't trouble you anymore.
My man can handle things.
Take my advice...
...be honest and speak the truth!
So I'm a liar, am I?
In the end I'm nothing
but a no-good cheat!
Hello!
I may be a cheater, but...
How could she do it?
Everything was going fine!
If I hadn't gone over there,
I wouldn't even have known!
I show up...
...and she's kissing him!
I saw them kiss!
Disgusting!
I wanted a chunky one
to keep me warm and toasty!
She's cold as a fish!
And she has the gall
to look down on me?
Look at her fat ass!
A pig!
Look at yourself,
you big, chunky porkroll!
And you look down on me!
Look down at your fat ass!
What are you saying?
Let's go. He's drunk.
You got a problem?
Looking for a beating?
It's my own business!
I said that fatso is
a pathetic excuse for a person!
Excuse me.
Do you have a pen and paper?
Thank you.
Doctor!
Where's the guy just hit by a car?
You mean a truck?
- Right.
- Who are you?
- We work with him.
- He's in the emergency room.
- Doctor, how is he?
- Who?
The guy who got hit by a truck.
In the recovery room.
He's still unconscious.
Will he make it?
Any of you related to him?
We work together.
Where are his relatives?
He doesn't have any.
- Doesn't he have a daughter?
- No.
He's never even been married.
He must have a daughter.
This is a letter he wrote to her.
We found it in his pocket.
I know what happened.
Doctor, can we see him?
Across the hall.
Over there?
Zhao.
It's me, Fu.
We've all come to see you.
Zhao.
You were fine yesterday,
How could this happen?
I know what you'd
want me to do.
First thing tomorrow morning,
I'll read this to Little Wu.
Don't worry,
I'll tell her it was from her father.
Little Wu! Little Wu!
- She's not here.
- Where did she go?
"Please listen to the tape."
Hey! There's a tape here!
Look, isn't this hers?
Manager Zhao, by the time
you hear this recording, I'll be gone.
Don't look for me,
you'll never find me.
The past few days,
I wanted to leave.
It was a difficult decision.
But now I think it's for the best.
I won't trouble you anymore.
During our time together,
I know I've been a burden to you all.
But at the same time,
I experienced so much.
How should I put it?
Manager Zhao.
I suspected the massage room...
...was fake from the beginning.
I knew you were all acting...
...so I played my part.
I didn't want to let you down.
I know you were all
trying to help me.
Even though you have no money.
You all tried so hard to hide the truth.
I never once felt deceived.
Instead, I felt happy.
Honest, those days with you...
...were the happiest of my life.
Those were our happy times together.
Manager Zhao...
...I knew the money you gave me
towards the end was fake.
Maybe none of you could feel
the difference...
...but how could you expect me not to?
Even though the money was fake...
...your intentions were genuine.
I'll keep that paper money forever.
Manager Zhao...
...deep down I know...
...my eyes will probably never be cured.
But don't worry...
...I'll never give up on life.
I'm sure many more difficulties await me.
But when those times come...
...I will think of you
and I'll be able to pull through.
Good-bye, Manager Zhao...
This tape recorder is for you.
It's been with me for a long time.
Whenever I feel sad,
I listen to music.
If something makes you sad...
...listen to some music,
and you'll feel better.
Manager Zhao...
...by the time you hear
this recording I'll be gone.
Don't look for me,
you'll never find me.
My dear daughter, how are you?
I've wanted to write you
for a long time.
Since I've been so busy at work,
trying to save money...
...I haven't had time.
I'm sorry.
I hope you'll forgive me.
Your dad really misses you.
I wonder how you've been doing.
Have you gained any weight?
I bet you're getting taller.
Everything in Shenzhen is going fine,
except for a few problems.
Making money isn't easy.
But I'm sure I'll do well eventually.
I work so hard to make money
for one thing only...
...so I can get your eyes fixed.
No matter how difficult things
may be or how exhausted I am...
...I'll find a way to cure your eyes.
When I have enough money,
I'll bring you to Shenzhen.
If not Shenzhen...
...wherever they've got the best hospitals,
that's where we'll go.
When your eyes are better,
you'll see your daddy again.
You'll see all the things you missed.
You'll go back to school.
This is a promise.
Please believe in your dad...
...and in yourself too...
...believe your eyes will get better.
Wait for me to come get you.
No matter what happens,
keep your chin up...
...don't feel depressed.
A lot of things in life
don't go your way.
You may run into difficulties...
...and you may feel alone.
But none of this matters.
Don't ever lose confidence
because of temporary setbacks.
Stay strong.
Have confidence and keep going.
If you believe in yourself,
you can conquer any obstacle.
Trust your father who loves you.
Everything will get better,
it really will.