You lent me an umbrella.
Not this one.
- It's a present.
- Don't want it.
Why not?
I don't want it.
At the time, we were both
only nineteen.
We were so young and immature.
But I wonder
why we had to be so nervous.
The first phone call from you.
Our first date.
The coffee shop where we met.
The first film we saw.
If I found music or a book I liked,
I told you before anyone else.
We talked about so many things.
You told me about your childhood.
Your father was Japanese.
That's why you have a
Japanese name, Aoi.
But he died when you were young.
After your mother remarried,
you found it hard
adjusting to a new family.
You'd been alone for a long time.
And then
you came to Japan to study.
Looking for a place to belong to,
you said.
Please.
Come in.
You need slippers.
Will you have something?
How about coffee?
Or perhaps a cold drink?
Grandpa used this place
as his studio.
That's mine.
This one, too?
I stopped halfway through
that one, too.
Ice.
Where's the ice?
Here it is.
It's still hot.
Just wait.
Those ones, too?
They are Grandpa's.
I'm going home.
I'm leaving.
That first time you came
to my place,
I couldn't sleep all night
thinking about you.
All that we shared back then
remains unchanged.
That's what I believed.
But the coffee shop
we used to meet at
was torn down and replaced
by a new building.
The secondhand record shop
is no longer there, either.
They moved to another town.
Do you still remember?
The courtyard at the university
where we used to hang around?
The cello player who
practiced there?
Always playing the same piece.
Always getting stuck at
the same point.
We used to giggle at
his squeaky efforts.
We really did.
He was playing when
we kissed for the first time.
Darling Aoi...
Now I've forgotten how the tune goes.
Incoherent bits of old episodes.
Yes, it's just some
old story from the past.
Thank you for reading this.
I'm embarrassed at
how childish I was
when I saw you in Milan.
Now I'm ashamed of it.
Forgive me.
Please give my best regards to Marve.
Please take care of yourself.
Hello, Agata speaking.
Hello?
Aoi?
At last...
...I'm glad you're happy now.
To Aoi, far away in Milan.
Now I'm living a completely
separate life.
From Junsei.
Yes.
Hello?
Junsei.
Angelo?
Listen.
Last night, Giovanna...
...no one knows why she killed herself.
We'll hold a service at the studio.
Junsei?
I can cancel the wedding now.
Ciao.
See you.
Junsei.
So you came?
I'm at another studio.
Takanashi teaches restoration,
he's an impossibly strict teacher.
Giovanna would be pleased.
She felt you had talent.
I should tell you.
The painting was damaged...
...by Giovanna.
She did it soon after you left.
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Stop!
Stop that!
Let me go!
Others saw her, too.
But everyone kept quiet.
We wanted to protect the studio
by protecting Giovanna.
But in the end,
it was shut down, anyway.
The reason I never told you...
...was because I was jealous of you.
Just like Giovanna.
Jealous of your talent.
No, not just your talent.
It's that straightforward
earnestness about you.
I hate dealing with that.
I'm awkward, that's all.
I wish life was easier for me.
You're doing it again.
It upsets me.
Maybe Giovanna was in love with you.
I hear the studio's going to reopen.
Next spring.
Spring 2000
Junsei, open up.
You're there, aren't you?
Open the door.
Sorry, I was in the
middle of breaking up.
With Aihara?
No, Eriko from sales.
Junsei said he has
something to tell me.
What's going on?
I only found out yesterday.
What does it mean?
You're going back to restoration?
Restoration is...
...giving life to something that's dying.
It's the only profession that lets
you bring back the past.
That's what convinced me.
So you won't be a painter?
You're too wrapped up in restoration.
You suck.
Wait.
Just wait.
Let me go!
You don't even care about me.
Calm down.
I'll go back to Italy
to start over again in restoration.
You're a liar!
All lies!
On my own, this time.
I've long waited
for the day when you would see only me.
What the hell was I to you?
- I thank you.
- Stop it!
Don't pity me or apologize.
That's not what I want to hear.
What I really want to hear is...
...what am I to you?
What am I to you, Junsei?
All I want to know is...
Why not?
Why can't I be the one?
Tell me why!
Because I love only Aoi.
I tried to forget her.
I tried to take you in.
But I...
...I still love Aoi.
Even if I never see her again.
I will...
...I will always love her.
She was a good girl.
She said
now she could finally let go,
because you told her the truth.
Goodbye, you fool, she said.
You poor soul.
No luck with your first or second love.
And you?
Still chasing that girl at work?
She's here now.
Kana, from the secretariat.
I was about to chase another.
Do your best.
See you.
It's that string quartet again...
A man stopped by to see you just now.
- Thank you.
- See you.
Goodbye.
A long time ago a boyfriend
asked me to go with him.
But I'd just started this shop and
I thought I belonged here.
I don't want you to end up
regretting like I did.
The place where you belong
can only be found in your heart.
Spring 2001
This studio was closed down
because of that matter we call
"The Tragedy of Cigoli."
But in the short space of one year
it has been successfully reborn,
as you can see.
It's all due to the skills of
our talented restoration experts.
This was found in an old church.
The condition was poor
and the damage was extensive.
Did you work on it?
They said I couldn't do it,
but I begged them.
Excuse me.
It was the Cigoli's masterpiece.
This past year, coming face to
face with the work again,
I attempted my own rebirth.
I...
...so many times I had to
rescue myself from my feelings.
Aoi.
I wonder if you've
already forgotten...
...the promise we made.
Junsei, do you know...
...this old saying?
Will you go there with me someday?
The Duomo in Florence?
Yes.
When?
Far in the future.
When will that be?
Maybe, ten years from now.
In ten years,
we'll both be in our thirties.
The twenty first century.
Are you serious?
We'll be unchanged,
we'll still be together.
Then Junsei,
will you promise me?
Let's make it on my 30th birthday,
at the Duomo in Florence.
Alright.
I promise.
How is he?
Marve, I mean.
He's back in Los Angeles.
With you?
Since when?
Two years ago.
You came all this way?
I don't know what to say.
I didn't make plans for after this.
I doubted it would happen.
I thought I'd wait all day in vain.
That was okay.
So I'm at a loss.
I never expected you'd come.
You're in a bind.
I'm just confused.
Do you understand what I mean?
But I remembered.
I never forgot.
When do you leave?
Tomorrow morning.
Then let's go and eat.
Maybe a drink.
I have something to show you.
Come with me.
Surprised?
I'm...
...I thought to myself...
...it was a miracle.
A message from God.
Like an illusion.
A glitch in time.
Caught up in the illusion,
we loved each other passionately.
Trying to reassure ourselves.
Trying to make up for
all the missing time.
It's alright.
You can take the day off.
Enjoy yourself.
No, I'm coming.
Sorry for not calling sooner.
See you later.
Here's your coffee.
Look, I have to go now.
I'm leaving.
I'll see you off.
I want to.
Goodbye.
Now I wish we hadn't.
That stupid promise.
Be happy.
Thank you.
Take care.
I'm glad we did.
I wanted to, Junsei.
I'm so glad we met.
Farewell.
Hey.
Did you enjoy it?
You were asked to play it?
Your girl asked me to.
Last year she asked me to
come and play it.
"Next time, play it in Florence,"
she said.
Last year?
In Milan,
at the square.
She's in Milan?
Thank you!
Sorry.
The Milan train?
It just left.
If you take the next Eurostar,
you'll be there 15 minutes
before the one that just left.
Miracles don't usually
happen so easily.
The only miracle for me was
that you were waiting for me.
You stayed so calm.
What can I say to you?
How can we mend
the blank between us?
Should we even try?
Not by reliving the past.
Not just hoping for the future.
The present is all we have.
My dear Aoi,
those sad, lonely eyes...
...if I find myself in there...
...then...
...you and I...
...we'll be...
Yutaka Takenouchi
Kelly Chen
Screenplay by
Fumie Mizuhashi
Music by ENYA
Produced by Fuji Television Network
Kadokawa Shoten Publishing & Toho
Directed by Isamu Nakae