- First time to France?
- Yes.
Purpose of your visit?
- Business or pleasure?
- Pleasure.
Don't you blame it on I
Don't you blame it on I and I
Don't you blame it on I, I tell ya
Don't you blame it on Rastafari
Do you like this music? No?
Yeah, yeah.
They blame it on I and I
No
They blame it on Rastafari
Je peux vous aider?
You can put your things over there.
How long are you planning on staying?
Not very long.
Message for Mr. Smith.
- Smith?
- Yes.
Smith.
Ah.
He's here.
Monsieur, good evening.
Anything to drink?
- Water.
- Sparkling or flat?
Flat.
- Last one for the road.
- A beer?
Oh, yes.
So, how are you, pal?
Just a little pre-take off take off.
Gives new meaning to
"flying the friendly skies."
- Can I buy you a drink? A serious drink?
- No, thank you.
- Where are you from? Ah, China.
- Beijing.
My favorite. I love China.
I love the food... Chinese food.
It's the best.
Yeah, the way they cut things
in little pieces...
so that you don't have to
use all that heavy silverware.
Brilliant invention, the chopstick.
Not like us barbarians.
I mean, there we are,
sticking our forks into the food...
and hacking it up
with our knives.
- First time in Paris?
- Yes.
Mmm. Great.
Men's toilet, now.
You're gonna have
the time of your life.
Hands up, please.
My boss is dying to meet you.
Ahh.
Gun, please.
You won't need it.
You're safe with us.
So, you came all the way from China
to keep an eye on us.
- To help you.
- Yes, of course.
To help us,
since we are so incompetent.
'Cause after all,
what is our miserable history...
compared to yours?
Since we have to work together, I don't want
to spend half the day killing your name.
- You got a nickname?
- No.
Why don't we give you one.
How about John?
I like that.
Richard.
Inspector Richard.
Welcome to Paris, Johnny.
So, what's on the menu tonight?
They're talking about
the stock market.
What fuckin' time do you call this?
Don't ever keep me waiting.
You got me?
Come on. Let's go.
Ah, there you are.
Smile. Smile.
Welcome to gay Paris.
This is a few friends of mine.
This is Veronica, Susan.
Say hello.
Yeah, sit, sit.
Hey, cool it.
Hey, fuckin' cool it, all right?
I think we have a situation.
One man, two girls.
- You see them?
- Yes, I do.
Want to go to Heaven?
Let's go.
- I'm going up.
- But, boss, the meeting.
I flew 12,000 miles for a cocksucker
of a contact. He can wait for me!
I don't know if I can do this.
Don't wory.
Let Mama run the show.
- Hmm?
- Okay, let's go to Heaven.
He's leaving with the two hookers.
What should I do?
Come up... and enjoy the show.
Wow!
- Boss, we didn't check the room.
- One minute.
Let's party, big boy.
Come on, baby. Let's have some fun.
- I don't feel so good.
- Want a fix?
- No! I told you, I quit.
- More for me.
Your meeting's up, guys!
Everybody, out!
But, boss, we didn't
finish searching.
- Get out!
- Okay, guys, let's get out of here.
I have to go to the bathroom, okay?
- Yes, yes. Come back soon.
- Sure.
Oh, hey, Johnny.
Just in time.
- This wasn't part of the plan.
- It is now. Don't worry.
It's all under control.
He'll do his thing, then we'll do ours.
- Where's the other girl?
- Prettying up in the bathroom.
- You want to go to Heaven?
- Take me to Heaven!
I'm going! Yes! Yes!
I'm going!
No!
You motherfucker!
Let me up!
She stabbed me!
The dumb bitch stabbed me!
Stay calm.
Stay calm. Stay calm.
I'm dying.
Stop recording.
- Fuck!
- We need to get him to the hospital.
He doesn't wanna go to a hospital.
He wants to go to Heaven.
- Why did you kill him?
- The question is, why did you kill him?
Richard, look what he did to me!
Help me!
Thanks for the help, Johnny.
I was just in here.
I felt a little sick, and then there was
all this screaming and shooting and...
Shut up!
There!
He's on the fifth floor.
Everyone, down.
He's on the eighth floor.
Everybody, back up!
I want him dead!
He's in the laundry room!
Everyone, down!
- He's down in the laundry room!
Everybody, down!
- You, down!
Boss I think...
You! And don't think!
You and you, go to the next level!
You know, the Chinese have the best
roasting methods in the world.
But I prefer the French one.
Give me your lighter.
What do they say, Johnny?
Out of the frying pan,
into the fire.
- Get 'em out of here!
- Go!
Down, you piece of shit!
- You're still with us, Johnny?
- Yes.
All right, Johnny.
You wanna play?
Give me a green one.
No!
Oh, shit! It's in my sweeter!
Help me with this!
Go!
You're dead.
Shit!
- He's gone.
- I can see that.
He... He got the cassette.
So what?
They show nothing but a fat degenerate
with some hooker killing him.
- Except that...
- What?
One... One machine was still running.
Fuck!
Turn the city inside out.
Look at the cardinal's ass.
I don't care!
Find it!
- Get the cassette!
- And kill him?
No, bring him to me.
I want him alive.
I'll kill him myself.
Go!
Nothing's on one.
We're still looking. Shit.
Gare de l'Est.
It's a train station.
Take the direction Bibliotheque
until Chatelet. You change.
And you take line number four and...
Yes, yes.
Direction Porte de Clignancourt,
and you're right there.
Okay? Yes.
Excuse me.
Thank you for coming.
In the name of the president, I want
to personally apologize for this mess.
I want to stress that we would
not want anything like this...
to jeopardize the warm relation
and successful economic ties...
shared by our two countries.
So...
we have assigned our best man
to supervise this case.
He handled the Tehran incident
for us masterfully. And Teneriffe too.
There is no one more qualified
to bring this...
to a mutually
beneficial conclusion.
- Inspector Richard. Bonjour.
- Sir Minister.
This is Minister Tang, our liaison
from the People's Republic of China.
- It's an honor to meet you, sir.
- The honor is ours.
The minister tells us
you are the best of the best.
Well, the minister is too kind.
If that were true,
I might have been able
to avoid this tragedy.
I'm hoping that you might help us
understand what went wrong...
so that we can avoid
further bloodshed.
And hopefully, bring this matter to
a quick and satisfactory conclusion.
If we could be showed the facts.
Yes, of course.
Please.
Uh, as you know,
as soon as you informed us...
of the criminal activities of the gangster Sung,
we set our operation in motion.
We identified his heroin
smuggling routes into France.
And in the spirit of cooperation,
we graciously accepted your offer...
to have one of your people,
Liu Jian, come over...
to assist us in Sung's arrest as he
was meeting with his French contact,
who unfortunately
we haven't yet identified.
Here...
he is surveilling Sung as we were
waiting for the contact to arrive.
And here, he's observing
along with us.
And then, for some reason we still can't
understand, he went completely insane.
Left the room to pee,
and next thing we know...
he's knocked out the bodyguards,
killed Sung and the prostitute.
This is the gun
he used to murder Sung.
Chinese police issue.
Do you recognize it?
- Yes.
- Good.
Oh, we have also verified
his fingerprints on the weapon.
Well, please, feel free to verify
our findings with your own people.
We assume that your man was
part of the conspiracy...
that he murdered Sung to
keep him from being captured...
and testifying in your courts,
as you had requested.
But that is only an assumption.
We are hoping you could give us
some background on him...
which would help us in his capture.
Inspector Liu Jian was top in
all his classes at the academy.
He received the highest training
in martial arts, weapons and police tactics.
He's been decorated for bravery
in the line of duty six times,
been promoted five times,
and has never lost a case.
He has no wife, no children.
His only dedication
is to his work.
He's our best,
which is why
this is all so confusing.
Well, you know, sometimes
the best are also the worst.
It's really sad.
Any surveillance cassettes?
Destroyed as he made his escape.
Do you know if he has any relatives
in Paris? Any friends or...
He has no one.
Well, then we should be able
to wrap this up very soon.
Excuse me.
I found the emergency phone.
Oh, that's good news.
Stay by the phone.
I'll call you back later.
Inspector Richard,
we are very sorry that the...
...operation was sabotaged.
I will report back to my superiors
and get you any help I can.
- Thank you.
- Let me show you out.
I want them followed.
I want their phones tapped.
I want to know every move they make,
every word they speak.
There must be a sleeper he's
staying with in Paris. Find him.
So, I guess you will be staying...
longer than you expected.
A little longer.
Paris is a nice city
once you get used to it.
And the French are nice people
once you get used to them.
- Are you hungry?
- No.
Family recipe.
Very tasty.
Fifty men on the street,
and you can't find this son of a bitch?
- Did you try his hotel?
- The fuck never checked in.
"The fuck never checked in."
That means he has a friend in Paris,
or family. Even better.
- Who tried Chinatown?
- Here. But it's hard to be discreet.
So put on a wig and a kimono. I don't care
how you do it. Now, get out. Get out!
Get out! I want that little prick
in my office by tonight!
Oh, Jessica, my love.
Come to Papa. Come.
Richard, I tried.
I really tried.
I was only in the bathroom for a minute.
You know, I was getting
ready to do my part...
Getting ready to do what it was
that I said that I would...
What you wanted... I really... I really...
I really was ready to do what it was...
what you wanted...
Jessica. Jessica.
I know you were. I know, I know.
Coming from such a quiet place
as North Dakota,
you must have been so scared.
- Richard, I tried. I...
- I know.
- I tried. I really did.
- I know you did.
All that noise.
My poor little farmer's daughter.
Don't be scared.
You're the best girl I have.
And you know how
I treat my best girl.
I know.
So you'll keep your promise?
Promise?
Did I make a promise?
Yes... Yes. You said that
if I did it one more time,
that you would let me...
let me have my daughter back.
- You said that you'd help me
get the papers to get her out.
- Did I say that?
- Yes.
- Did I say that, Max?
Oh, yes, you did.
Well, there you go.
Two to one.
I guess you're right. So I'll have
to let you go, you and your precious.
Do you realize how much I must trust you
to let you go just like that?
With everything you know?
Everything you've seen?
One phone call from you, one word,
and I'd be locked up for the rest of my life!
I'd never do that!
I'd never give you up, ever!
I know that. If I didn't
trust you, would I let you go?
- What is he doing?
- I don't know. What are you doing, Max?
- I'm preparing a fix.
- He's preparing a fix. Do you want a taste?
Richard, I told you I quit.
You know I quit.
I don't want it anymore!
I quit!
You don't tell me when
you're gonna quit! I tell you!
You don't tell me what you want!
I tell you!
How long will it take for a fucking junkie
like you to betray me for a lousy fix?
I won't betray you!
Please, don't!
"I won't betray you! Please, don't!"
Put her back to work.
Come on. Come on.
Get the fuck out. Come on.
Move your fuckin' ass.
Get to work, you fuckin' animals!
You cocksucking pigs.
You play mah-jongg?
A little.
I love mah-jongg.
Keeps the mind sharp.
It's hard to find
good players around here.
That's why I play by myself.
This way, I always win.
Bitch!
I'm gone for five minutes,
and you think you can park
your skinny ass in my spot?
Fuck off.
You want some more?
She...
She broke my nose!
Come on! Look at you!
- Ow!
- Eh?
I haven't been home for 15 years.
- Ow!
- That's a long time.
- You stupid piece of shit.
- I have seven grandchildren I have never seen.
One 1 year...
- You are a fucking dog.
- Two twins 3...
- All right?
- Three boys 5, 7 and 9.
Get back to work.
Oh, almost 9 and 1/2 now.
And one big girl 14 years of age.
Almost a woman now.
She wants to come to Paris.
She goes to university.
Hey! Go away! Go away!
- Please.
- You don't know these women.
They say they want to use the bathroom to pee,
and next thing they're shooting up.
She only hurts herself.
Please, don't draw attention.
Huh.
Excuse me.
- Can I use your toilet?
- No.
Oh, please. I just...
I only have to pee. I won't be long.
No!
Okay.
Wait!
What are you doing?
Well, if you're gonna treat me
like a dog, I'm gonna act like a dog.
- I'm gonna pee right here.
- Stop!
Okay.
There.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
- But nothing else.
- I'm not gonna do anything else, I promise.
- Do you wanna check?
- No.
- Just hurry.
- I'm sorry to have to force you to.
It's just I have got to go so bad.
I really...
- I'm only... I'm only gonna be a minute.
- Okay.
I'm Lo, the chef.
I came for my order.
Oh! That feels so good.
- How many?
- Uh, one, two,
uh, three, four...
- I owe...
- Don't wory about paying. Come back later, okay?
Come back later. Okay.
Thank you. Thank you.
Miss, you have to finish now.
Minute's up.
You have to leave!
Miss?
Miss? Please.
- I slept long?
- Only a minute.
Oh, that's good.
I've gotta get back to work.
Every 15 minutes they come by in a
fuckin' car, and if I'm not out there...
It's just that I'm so tired.
They gave me this shot and...
Oh, my God.
Are you gonna finish this?
- This is pretty good. Did you make this yourself?
- Yes.
- Is that what you do, then? You cook, huh?
- No.
- But you make these chips, right?
- My uncle does.
I love those chips. Do you mind?
I love the pink ones.
My daughter loves the blue ones.
That's her favorite color.
Miss, you really have to go now.
Mmm!
Delicious. I'm sorry.
- It's not every day I get to eat in a Chinese restaurant.
- Here.
One for you, one for your daughter.
Oh, my God.
This is so nice.
You're the first person that's been
kind to me since I've been in Paris.
Look, I-I... I don't like
to take things from people.
Usually I like
to pay my own way, so...
maybe later on,
if you wanna, you know...
- No charge?
- No. Thank you.
I don't have any other way
to repay you.
- Don't worry.
- I'm not your type. Is that it?
I don't have type.
Miss?
I'm sorry for hitting you.
That's okay.
I'm used to it.
Quai de l´Alma. In one hour.
Follow me.
He's on board.
Let's go.
Tell me everything.
Richard, the cop in charge,
set up the whole thing.
- He is the connection.
- Do you have proof?
They recorded everything.
They said that, uh,
you destroyed all the cassettes.
Except one.
Hand it to me, carefully.
The main thing now is to get you
out of the country. I have a car.
We can go to the airport,
and from there we can...
Poussez-vous! Police!
Poussez-vous devant! Police!
Dégage! A la vite, dégage!
- Bouge pas toi! Bouge pas!
Mets tes mains sur la tete, connard!
- Pose ta tete sur la table!
Pose ta tete!
- Pose ta tete! Bouge plus!
A la cuisine!
Shit!
He's under the bridge!