Dragon Tiger Gate was founded...
by 2 kungfu masters:
Wong Jianglong and Wong Fuhu.
They promoted self-strengtheni ng. ..
to free people from oppression.
They even taught manial arts...
to street urchins.
The Gate thus became
the symbol of Justice.
While every youth
was eager to join the Gate...
Wong Fuhu's son,
Dragon,
decided to leave.
He was to part
with his baby brother,
Tiger.
Shibumi
Rosa, Ma Kun's been doing a good job.
I decide to continue our collaboration.
Give him the Lousha Plaque.
Ask him to keep up his work!
Remember, the Plaque
represents Lousha Gang.
I've given you the Lousha Plaque.
Don't let anything
happen to it.
I know. I'll do my best.
What a coincidence!
Still remember me?
- Xiao... - That's right!
So you still remember me!
Grade 5?
Not Grade 5! Grade 3!
Almost the same.
Not at all. What a poor memory!
Remember the fatso in our class?
Sure, the one who bawled all the time?
No, the one who wetted his pants!
Well, he bawled after
he wetted his pants!
I remember he liked pulling your plait!
It couldn't be! I had short hair then.
I remember you had long hair!
How can I forget I had short hair?
Like, would you forget
you're called Chan?
Look who has a poor memory?
I'm not Chan, Xiaowei!
I'm not Xiaowei!
- I'm sorry! - I'm sorry!
So what's your name?
Tiger Wong.
I'm Ma Xiaoling.
- Hey - Hey, Tiger!
Why so many people?
Ma Kun has reserved...
the whole upper floor.
Ma Kun?
The biggest kingpin in Hong Kong.
Those dudes in black are his dogs.
Some dudes in white are barging in!
They're the White Lions.
As powerful as Kun!
Black or white,
they're still bad guys!
Kun, so you got the Plaque again.
You have monopoly
over all smuggling gigs.
It takes juice to work with Lousha Gang.
You gotta work harder!
Juice? I got much more than you!
To hell with your gigs.
I want half of your cut!
You kiddin' or what?
Whoever has the Plaque
can get all the cut.
You want half? You outta your mind?
Nice food! It's pay-up time!
Mom!
How dare you welsh
on our debts?
Not that I don't wanna pay.
We're the victims!
We've paid a lot already!
Let them be. They are Kun's dogs!
Stay put! Master won't like it!
Shibumi gave me the Plaque.
Come get it if you dare!
Even if I let you go,
my boss Scaly won't!
Enjoying your food, huh?
Tiger!
Where's the Plaque?
Who are you?
Tiger Wong!
Find the Plaque...
or you can't leave!
I'll take sole responsibility
for what I've done!
Go down!
Let him go!
Why?
Gosh! Scaly has gone way out of hand!
All crap!
What you starin' at, Dragon Wong?
You wanna fight me one on one?
Why you let that kid
gojust now, Kun?
None of them were able to beat him.
And the White Lions were watching.
If Kun hadn't let him go...
the two gangs
could have started fighting.
What good would that do, you crazy dog?
Who cares about the White Lions?
You're just a bodyguard.
I could have taken him out on my own!
I'm good!
- Scaly...
- Come fight me one on one!
Scram!
You better watch out!
Why didn't you
go all the way...
when fighting the kid?
I will get you the Plaque back.
Stop eating!
Look how heavy the plaque is!
Why is the plaque with you?
I snatched it when you were fighting.
Hey! Let me see! Look!
We can fence it for some dough!
Sure can!
We can donate the money for charity.
Charity? What a waste!
So who's the boss today?
Tiger, of course!
Hey you guys!
Me again?
Come! In sum...
Tiger is virtuous and generous.
He's perfect!
Indeed! Cheers!
- Cheers! - Thanks!
Just dig in!
Pass me the whole plate!
The sushi today is so good! So delicious!
Two more orders please!
Hurry up!
Tiger is our boss today.
He'll start first.
Tiger, that's for you!
And this is for me!
Gimme the Plaque.
The plaque?
What plaque?
This one?
The plaque is your head!
You want this?
How much can you pay?
You weren't all that bad last time!
Dragon!
You got lost or what?
I come here to give you a hand!
I've put drugs in their wine!
I already got the Plaque.
I hate dirty tricks!
The plaque is ours.
They're having fun with it.
We got every right to beat them up.
What did you say before? Me dirty?
You dumbhead. Let me teach you a lesson!
Beat him up!
You dare to touch me?
Beat him up too!
You guys will need
an ambulance real soon!
I said beat him up!
Who you fightin' with?
Dragon Wong!
Didn't you say you're a good fighter?
Go in!
Beat the crap outta anyone you see!
I hate to be disturbed at my meals.
Your nunchaku sucks.
Better practice more!
Let's practice together sometimes!
You're welcome. Just couldn't stand them!
I'm Turbo.
Tiger.
Tiger?
A fierce name! Gotta split now!
You guys okay?
We're fine.
No blood was shed.
Hey, is that yours? I just found it.
Tiger!
Where's Dragon Tiger Gate?
Baldy, you snatched the plaque.
You better explain
to the Master yourself.
Stop staring. You can touch it.
I got this scar when I was a kid.
When I was at your age,
I already knew kungfu well.
Once I passed by
someone wielding his sword.
And there went this scar!
It's such a big golden plaque.
I had to snatch it.
Then this long-haired guy
asked me for it.
Of course I wouldn't give it to him.
So he beat us up.
He punched me and I parried...
like what you taught us.
And the rest is history.
We're really not to blame!
Indeed, Master! We're not to blame!
The plaque you snatched
is called Lousha Plaque.
It's the transaction permit
between Lousha Gang and Kun.
Lousha Gang is a crime organization.
You snatched their stuff...
and claimed you're innocent?
Get out and squat for 3 hours!
Would someone gimme a hand? I can't see!
3 hours already!
Uncle.
I saw my brother again.
He's Kun's man now.
So he's tied to Lousha Gang.
But I don't believe he's a bad guy.
Bring him back to the Gate.
Master,
I'm Turbo from overseas.
I was invincible in Chinatown...
But I know...
you're well versed in martial arts.
I wanna aggregate
the skills of all schools...
to manifest the spirits
of Chinese kungfu.
I'd therefore like to be your disciple.
I'll be your disciple no matter what!
You still here?
Wait!
I ain't gonna give up!
You're great in nunchaku.
Can you teach me?
I won't teach you.
But we can practice together.
Great!
Where's your nunchaku?
By the way, I'm also called the Judo Kid!
Come on!
Wow, excel lent footwork!
By the way, how you got that scar?
How you got that scar?
I can't hear you.
I said your scar...
I got the scar while practicing.
But the other guy is a limp now.
So be careful!
Dragon, Come over!
It's for Dad's safety.
Let's do it together.
Am I not good enough...
to protect you?
Come fight me!
No way! I don't wanna kill you!
Then I'll die for sure
Better rely on yourself than on gods.
I won't let anything happen to you...
or your dad.
If Dad retired,
you wouldn't need to protect us.
We'd all be safe then.
Where would you go
if you could retire?
Take this one first.
I'll go get another one.
Mom, did Tiger's mom
take Dad away from us?
I hate them!
You shouldn't hate
any member of the Gate.
Dad and I separated
not because of them.
It's my own decision.
Dragon, come out! It's Tiger!
Go away! Don't come see me anymore!
I don't wanna see anyone
from the Gate ever!
Get lost!
Why you crying?
I'll beat you till you smile!
Stop! Stop!
Stop him. Don't let him run away.
Stop!
Still running, smart ass?
Wanna fight back?
What you guys want?
What?
Beat him up!
Take his slipper!
Don't come back to this park again!
Let's go!
Hurry up, Tiger!
Okay. I'm coming!
Let me give you my slipper,
or your mom will yell at you.
What about your mom?
It won't be a problem.
Thanks!
You don't wanna know
why I was in a fight?
'Cos I know Dragon is a man ofjustice.
Unless they're in the wrong,
you wouldn't have picked a fight.
They were bullying Tiger.
So I fought with them.
Carry this jade pendant with you.
You're a member of the Gate
wherever you go.
You'll make it big in the future.
Remember you're Wong Fuhu's son.
Don't ever commit a crime.
Your life...
will be fraught with frustrations.
Never give up
however difficult life will become.
You'll know when you grow up.
Come!
When will I make it big?
Dragon, your mom
hasn't come out yet!
Mom never came out.
She was never seen again.
It's lucky
I met Kun.
Out of gratitude,
I've done reluctant things for him.
I know I can't leave here...
I'm ashamed to go back
to the Gate ever again.
Dragon!
I'm your baby brother!
I know. So what?
Am I supposed to hug you
with tears in my eyes?
And you hug me and call me Bro?
Uncle and I want you back to the Gate.
Don't work for this bad guy Kun anymore!
So you're a good guy and I'm a bad guy.
Go back to the Gate
and play your good guy!
Chan!
I'm Tiger Wong.
You're no fun!
You and Dragon are tight?
He works for my dad.
I treat him like a brother.
You're his baby brother?
You don't look alike.
You guys are brothers.
Why you act like that?
That's why I wanna help him.
Good! Gimme your phone.
Listen. Hurry up!
- Hello. - Hello.
This is my number. Remember to call me!
Aren't you gonna help me?
Sure, but I didn't say now.
I'll call you when I find him. Bye.
Thanks for taking care
of Scaly and his dogs.
They've been nothing but trouble lately.
You can always quit.
Not so simple!
What's so hard?
I've been in this biz forever.
Xiaoling is my only worry.
I've taken you for my dad,
and Xiaoling my sis.
I won't let anything
bad happen to my folks.
I believe you.
Just sleep on it.
And you? Will you go back to the Gate?
Yes,
but it's not the right time yet.
I'll wait till you've retired.
Wanna get rid of me?
Yes. Give the Plaque back to Lousha Gang.
Nunchaku Slippers! Watch out!
Playing with slippers?
No more slippers for a month.
Take them all off!
You don't wanna teach me.
At least practice with me!
You're best at nunchaku?
Yes.
Please pick a weapon, Master!
You're clueless.
Worse than the kids.
You know nothing about nunchaku.
Come back when you know...
how to grasp a nunchaku.
I'm Turbo,
invincible in Chinatown.
You're clueless.
You know nothing nunchaku.
Come back when you know...
how to grasp a nunchaku.
I was always bullied as I grew up abroad.
I didn't like that.
So I slashed a scar on my face.
I wanna scare people off.
I learnt nunchaku
'cos it's fierce and powerful.
But today I was totally beaten.
I thought I had grasped it very hard...
but he took it from me so easily!
After a long struggle,
I finally realized...
it's not a matter of strength...
but of the heart.
I can't scare people...
with a scar on my face.
I won't tell my scar story anymore.
But I'll say...
Master Wong left
a slipper mark on my face.
I will keep it up.
Thanks!
Turbo!
You know how to do household chores?
I don't, but I will learn!
Kun wants to return
the Plaque and retire?
That's good news for you.
I'll arrange for you to join Lousha Gang.
That way... we can be together.
Why you staring at me?
I want you to understand...
I can make Shibumi
let you take Kun's place.
You can be your own boss finally!
I shouldn't have rescued you that day.
Listen up, Dragon!
Whether you join the Gang or not,
we ain't good guys.
We cannot change our fate.
- Dragon, I... - Xiaoling.
You know Tiger?
Yeah.
Arrange a meeting for us,
please.
You know where we are?
You won't recall. You were just a kid.
It used to be a park.
And there was a monkey bar here.
After we were beaten,
you liked to hide here.
I'll learn my kungfu well.
I'll beat them up!
Kungfu is for protecting people,
not for fighting.
We will never be bad guys
no matter what.
Got it?
Got it.
Look! That's the direction
to the Dragon Tiger Gate.
Ever beaten anyone you shouldn't have?
No! Never!
But I have. Many times!
Many things
have happened to me,
but you won't understand.
I wanna tell you today...
I'm proud of you.
'Cos you can stick to your principles!
I also have my principles.
I know where I should go.
Let's go.
Hey!
I'll wait for you at home!
Cool. See you at the Gate!
Giving up the Plague is an insult to me!
Rosa.
Both Kun and Dragon must die!
Watch out!
Xiaoling, show us what you got!
Dad, how did I do?
Not too bad.
I'm the best
in the team.
And you call that "not too bad"?!
Your game is just kiddy stuff for me!
Cool!
If you're so good, let's play a game!
Okay, you arrange it.
But you better get changed now.
We'll go eat.
Dragon is on his way.
Cool!
Hello.
Dragon, I have to see you now.
But I don't feel like it.
You'll regret if you don't show up.
So fast! You must miss me!
Have you ever done it in the water?
I thought you had
something urgent to tell me.
Tattoo for me.
Why?
My birthday present.
You have birthday?
You saved me years ago.
To me, that's my birthday.
Forget it. I know you won't.
Turn around.
Go away!
You'll fall to your death!
None of your business. Go way!
Jump down and I'll catch you.
What's your name?
Dragon.
Yours?
Rosa.
What you staring at?
Can't I stare?
I'll be in love with you forever.
What have you tattooed for me?
I was supposed to kill you.
Double Devils are off to kill Kun.
Go to hell!
You bloody old man!
I'm good but you treat me like shit!
Better to work for
Lousha Gang than for you.
Retire? Not so easy!
Let me retire you now!
Don't hit me, Kun!
I was just kiddin'!
- You back-stabbing asshole!
- Let me retire with you.
Help! Double Devils!
Help!
Dad!
Watch over her!
Remember you're Wong Fuhu's son.
You'll make it big in the future.
You will come back to the Gate
with your head up.
Never give up...
however difficult life will become.
Will he go to heaven?
He will. He loved you so much.
Better ask when the bad guys
will go to hell!
From now on, the Gate is your home.
Even if my limps are broken,
I won't let anyone harm you.
Double Devils were beaten
by people from the Gate.
The Gate is really that strong?
Good!
Master,
we haven't found Tiger yet.
Baldy and others are searching for him!
Who's the best here?
Watch out for...
the "Black Pagoda"!
So Dragon Tiger Gate's kungfu sucks!
You're not good enough
to die under my hands!
But you can!
Find your brother.
Guard the Gate together...
Xiaoling, should anything
happen to anyone...
bring them to Mt Baiyun...
and look for a guy called Qi.
Master!
Master! Master...
Please save my friends!
Their wounds are too deep for me.
All over Mt Baiyun,
Only Qi can help them.
Where can I find Qi?
Inside the pagoda.
I'll find him once I get up there?
No one has ever entered the pagoda!
Stay put!
Pick up the prayer beads.
Pick up all the prayer beads.
Master Qi
Here are all the prayer beads.
Please save my friends.
There's still one bead below the pagoda.
You've gone an arduous way.
Your friends must mean a lot to you.
If you can jump down the pagoda...
to pick up the bead...
then I will save them.
I hope you'll keep your promise.
Did I ever go up there?
Everything is an illusion
in the mundane world.
Only your conviction is real.
The moment you decided
to sacrifice yourself...
the prayer bead was already in your hand.
Don't worry. I will save your friends.
No one at the Gate is good enough
to beat Double Devils.
I know your relationship with Dragon.
He's good.
I wanna fight with him.
Take this to save him.
He should die under my hands.
You'll be okay after the acupuncture.
Your internal power might even increase.
Don't move.
Don't say a word.
I was also adopted.
No one ever cares how I feel.
I did this for you today,
so you'll care for me.
Even if you don't love me,
I can make you hate me!
This pill can only save one person.
or yourself!
Dragon,
have you ever loved me?
Tiger, I'll teach you
"Electric Dragon Drill."
Turbo, I'll teach you "Golden Mask."
Tiger, Turbo,
I'm giving you two gadgets.
They can help you fight Shibumi.
But whether you'll win in the end
depends on yourselves.
Wait for me at the Gate.
I promise I'll be back.
Looking for your own death?
Your kungfu has improved a lot!
Let's have a good fight!
That's it?
Anything more?
Your "Golden Mask" is not bad!
Anything else?
Electric Dragon Drill! Embarrassing!
On behalf of the Gate,
I'm returning the Plaque to you.
Dragon, I've been waiting for you!
Eighteen Dragon Slaying Palms?
That's all you have, Shibumi? How slow!
We can go back to the Gate now,
Little Bro!
Tiger!
Tiger is back!
Uncle, we're back, my brother and me.
Uncle said the Gate...
should be passed on to both of us.
Yo, what about me?
Ever think about changing
your name to Leopard?
Turbo Leopard? Sounds fierce!