- This is awesome.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
This is crazy.
Oh, my God!
So incredible.
Do you want
to know a secret?
I took a Viagra.
What?
This is awesome!
Why aren't l
using this every day?
What'd you do?
Wait. Stop, stop, stop.
Stop.
What?
What's the matter?
"What's the matter?"
You just took a Viagra
to have sex with me.
I thought it
would make it better.
It was better.
It takes some of
the pressure off.
Because you can't get
hard without a Viagra?
Is it because you
don't think I'm sexy?
I thought you'd
think it was fun
for me to
super-size it for once.
That is the worst
birthday present
you could ever give someone.
I was just trying to go
turbo for your birthday.
My hard-ons are
still in analog.
This shit's digital.
I don't want
a turbo penis.
I like your
medium-soft one.
Look, I can get it up.
Just not that far up.
Where did you get this?
I got it from Barry.
What?
You got it from Barry?
Why do you care?
This is my dick
we're talking about.
Not yours.
We are young people.
We don't need
medication to have sex.
I only took it
because it's your birthday.
I thought you'd like it.
Happy fucking 40th birthday.
I am not 40.
And I don't want
to have a husband
who has to take
Viagra to get a hard-on.
I don't have to
take it every time,
but once in a while.
Fuck 40.
Forty can suck my dick.
Stop it. Dad, stop.
I love you.
Time to get up.
Your breath
smells weird.
Wake up.
I really need
you to wake up.
Wake up. Come on.
Time to wake up.
Okay.
Whoo!
Ready!
Make a wish!
Hello, Sayid.
Can I watch Lost?
You can't handle Lost.
It's too violent,
and you won't understand.
If I don't understand it,
why can't I handle it?
Because you're eight.
I can handle it.
I've seen a shark eat
a guy on Shark Week.
Shark Week is fake.
No, it's not.
All of it is reenactments.
I know, but they...
And that's scary.
You shouldn't be
allowed to watch that.
They show the reenactments,
but they actually happened.
It's gonna give
you nightmares.
I can handle a nightmare.
You're a nightmare
every day for me.
Hey.
Don't eat that cupcake.
What?
The one you just
put into the sink.
I saw you were hiding that.
This cupcake?
You think I'm going
to eat this cupcake?
Yeah.
I so don't want
this cupcake. Look.
You're still going to eat it.
I'm going to eat
that cupcake?
Just put it in the trash.
What would you like to do?
Your choice.
Anything?
Yeah, anything.
Just hang out with you guys.
Don't you want
to get a massage,
or do something fun?
Forty's huge.
I'm turning 38.
Okay, 38. We will move on.
Isn't it weird
that our birthday
is the same week,
and then we're
going to have a party,
and it's just for me?
No, I don't think
it's weird at all.
Because you're turning
40 and I'm turning 38.
Come on,
do you really want to be
one of those ladies
who's just so
insecure about their age?
And they lie, and then they
gotta remember,
and it gets all...
You don't get it.
See, you don't
understand how it works.
I don't want to shop
at old ladies' stores.
I don't want to go
to J. Jill and Chico's,
and Ann Taylor Loft.
I'm not ready yet.
I need two more years.
That is so insane,
it kind of makes sense.
What'd you get me
for my birthday?
Wait a minute,
I thought you said that
we shouldn't get each
other gifts this year.
What do you mean?
You're supposed to
get me a surprise gift.
This is a big birthday.
I'm turning 40.
Mom!
Mom, why can't I get
new clothes?
What the fuck?
Nothing fits me!
God damn it!
I'm going to go work out,
I'll be back in about an hour.
Hey, did your father call
to wish you a happy birthday?
No, but that's no surprise.
Come on.
Coming.
You got to keep up
with us, sweetheart.
Yeah, I'm in.
That's why your body
looks like your body
and her body
looks like her body.
Before, after.
You guys just
go on without me.
I'm just gonna...
I think I gotta...
Fuck.
Thanks for letting
me join this team.
It's not really a team.
It's just a bunch of guys
that get together and ride.
- I know, I know.
- Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa!
Hey! Bike lane, asshole!
It's always the guy in
the fucking lnfiniti.
Good. See,
you're getting tight here.
Yeah.
This, we need to work on.
Okay.
So, why on earth is
Pete taking Viagra?
What's going on?
I don't know.
I think maybe
he isn't attracted
to me anymore or something.
I don't know.
Well, that is ridiculous.
If you were my girlfriend,
I would not need a Viagra.
I would need
an anti-Viagra pill...
To try not to get a boner.
But everyone
gives you a boner.
Don't sell yourself
short like that.
You give me a boner.
Barb doesn't give me a boner.
Maybe things are
just getting stale.
That's why if maybe l
work out really hard...
Maybe he'll be able
to get a boner again.
Why do you need
to have sex, Deb?
Sex is the number one thing
people fight about.
You stop having sex,
there will be no more fights.
I am living proof.
I have no sex,
and I am the happiest
I have ever been.
I knew it. I knew you
were not having sex.
I can see it on your face.
It's all...
Puckered and pained.
I'm enjoying our
non-sex period,
that's all I'm saying.
Don't you miss it?
I wouldn't know, because
I don't have any
feeling down there anymore.
I have nerve damage
from my C-section,
so everything's
just kind of...
She's numb down there.
I could sit down
hard on a fire hydrant,
and I wouldn't even
know that I was sitting.
I could get stung by
a hornet down there,
and I would not feel it.
You could put
anything in there,
and I would not know
what the object was.
I used to pee
in a nice stream,
and now it just kind of goes
like a shower head.
That is the saddest
thing I've ever heard.
I think you need a family.
Don't you want a family?
No, I think
I want to Clooney it.
Clooney it?
Yup.
He doesn't seem happy.
Yeah, he is.
No, he's lonely.
No, he's not.
See, I think
he has sad eyes.
You sweet little thing, no.
He's doing sad, lonely eyes
to get the next lady.
Look, I can do it, too.
Watch.
I bet George Clooney
is really lonely.
Just him and his pig.
You'd fuck him.
I wouldn't.
So would you.
I would.
I wouldn't feel it,
but I would.
You'd fuck him
with your numb vagina.
Yes, you would.
Ocean's Thirteen Inches,
that's what you'd find out.
Do you think?
I mean,
that was idiotic, though.
You have to understand that.
That's the one
thing you don't do,
is tell her that
you used Viagra.
I think that's even
on the warning label.
We're in one of
those phases where
everything that
the other person says
just annoys
the shit out of each other.
All the time. It's a blast.
Don't worry about it.
You just gotta
ride that out.
This sounds terrible.
Okay, I like it.
But...
Do you ever wonder
what it would be like if, say,
you were separated
by something bigger.
Like death? Like her death?
I have given it
a fair amount of thought.
Not in a painful way,
just quietly slid into death.
Like a gas leak.
Absolutely.
It's gotta be peaceful.
I mean, this is the mother
of your children.
You want her to die...
No, I'd want it
to be a peaceful...
...gentle, you know.
Yeah, just like drift
into a coma from which
she never awakens.
And then you move on.
Then you are a widower.
That's just it,
people love widowers.
They love widowers.
It's like the polar
opposite of divorced guys.
It's the best.
It's like,
"Oh, that poor widower.
"lf I could only
make him happy."
"Somehow, ease his pain."
"Cock-suck
away his sadness."
Do you know that this song,
Pixies did this song,
it's about a Salvador Dali
short film called
Un Chien Andalusia.
This music doesn't
make people happy.
This song kicks off Doolittle,
one of the best albums
of the last 30 years.
Look how angry you get
while listening to it.
An important record.
It's my birthday.
You don't control
the radio on my birthday.
I do.
I control the radio
on my birthday.
Sadie's watching Lost.
Sadie, how many times
have you watched
Lostthis week?
I only watched 11.
But I have eight more,
and then I'm done, so...
How many are there?
114.
Are you kidding me?
You can't watch
over 100 episodes
of a show in five weeks.
It'll melt your brain.
It's not melting my brain,
it's blowing my mind.
That's really bad, Sadie.
You're not allowed to do that.
My relationship with Lost
is not your business.
It's extremely personal.
Stop!
Stop it.
Be nice to your sister.
You guys are going to
cherish each other one day.
Stop it! Stop!
It's your birthday.
You don't need to
go to the store.
No, just five minutes.
Desi and Jodi are fighting.
All right, five minutes,
but then I'm pulling you out.
Hi.
How's Jodi treating you?
Jodi?
Oh, Jodi's my new BFF.
She's like a little kitty-cat.
Sometimes she comes
and rubs up against my leg.
And you're a ball of shit.
She loves me.
Huh.
Can you do inventory
so that we can do
the sidewalk sale?
And you really need
to pay attention
to the numbers
because we have
$12,000 unaccounted for.
I think it's probably Desi.
She's been having
a really hard time
using these simple computers.
It's because she's stupid.
I think she might be stealing.
She's not stealing.
She's our best employee.
She made nine
grand last month.
How much did I make?
You brought in $2,000.
That's not bad.
Well, it's not that good.
I mean, I'm not comparing you,
but you're not as good.
All right. See you.
I don't think she's
wearing underwear.
What?
It's all dark up there.
Why are you looking?
I didn't mean to look.
I just said, "Hey, whoa."
And there it was.
Maybe she's wearing
dark underwear.
Yeah, maybe she has underwear
that has a picture of
a vagina painted on it.
Stop looking.
Some deep oranges and browns,
and maybe some dark greens.
That would really
play up your features.
I'll just take out my AmEx
and you pick what
stuff you think's good.
Whoo!
Good job!
Where's Daddy?
I think he went to poop.
Pete!
Q-A-T.
Suck on that, bitch.
Hey.
What are you doing?
Going to the bathroom.
We're all downstairs,
waiting for you.
You've been up here
for a really long time now.
I'm almost done.
I'll be down in a second.
Charlotte just did
her first flip
on the trampoline
and she landed on her feet.
She was really
proud of herself.
That's great!
And you missed it.
She'll do it again.
It's the fourth time
you've gone to
the bathroom today.
Give me a break.
Why is your instinct
to escape?
It's not my instinct
to escape from you.
It is my instinct to
come into the bathroom
when I need to go
to the bathroom.
How come I don't
smell anything?
It's because I shoved
an Altoid up my ass
before I came in here.
Let me see, then.
What?
Let me see.
No, I'm not going
to let you see.
You're not
going to let me see,
because you're
not taking a poop.
I've been flushing as I go.
You're flushing as you go.
Who takes a half-hour
to go to the bathroom?
John Goodman.
Don't press "Enter."
I'm not sure I want
to make that move!
Thank you. Wow.
You know, when I
first started this label,
my dream was to work
with musicians and bands
whose music
I just admired so much.
The person that I thought,
"My God, wouldn't it be
incredible to work with, "
was Graham Parker.
Tonight, we have him, solo
because we couldn't afford
to fly in The Rumour.
Graham Parker.
It's just not
my kind of music.
Really? What is
your kind of music?
I like Lady Gaga.
Oh, God, of course you do.
What?
Shallow dance music.
It's not. It is fun.
And it's about
release and sex and power.
You don't have to like it.
It's really not for you,
that's fine.
This is a job.
This is not a hobby.
Can't you love him,
just as a hobby
and sign a 15-year-old
hot girl so we can eat?
Graham Parker & The Rumour
had two albums
in the Rolling Stone Top 500
Best Albums of All Time.
Two of them.
If I can just
sell 10,000 records
to his hardcore fanbase,
we're golden.
The last of Graham
Parker's fans just died.
I do know. Hardly.
That sort of music
depresses people.
Hi, Charlotte.
Sadie. Sadie,
what are you listening to?
Okay. This is music
that makes people happy.
And this is what people buy.
What?
Right, girls?
Come on, Sadie.
Okay.
Why did you take it off?
Now, something
that really rocks.
This is called good music.
From somebody's heart.
This is bumming me out.
This isn't fun.
Just listen to
these words, okay?
Just listen to the words.
I don't understand the words.
This is lyrics.
This is poetry.
This is what is
going to survive
in a hundred years.
It just doesn't
make people happy.
Makes me happy.
I can dance to it.
But you're the only one
in the room who's happy.
Sometimes I wish just
one of you had a dick.
Well, we don't want one.
Is there something
that you can do
to be helping me right now?
Yeah, I'm ready to help.
Just tell me what to do.
Can you go get
a lunch box or something?
For me or for them?
Charlotte!
I've got a test!
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Charlotte,
I'm going to kill you!
Hi, Debbie.
Hi. Any day now, huh?
Not really.
Three months, still.
Hi.
Katie's dying for a play date.
Let's hook these two up.
That would be great.
Okay, I'll call you.
Great.
Okay, great.
No.
No, what?
What?
No.
She's sweet.
She's evil.
Hello. Hi.
Hi.
Listen, Charlotte
really needs to get
here on time
because she needs
the extra time
to just settle in.
Oh. We are on time.
Being on time
means being early.
Okay.
It's nice to see you in class.
We'd like to see more of you.
I come to...
Hi, Debbie.
Grandma Molly.
How are you?
I'm so happy about
the science fair.
Thank you for coming.
It's going very well, I heard.
Yeah.
I love you.
You look so beautiful!
Happy birthday.
I just learned
that you're 40.
Are you 40?
Yeah.
I remember when I was 40,
and then I blinked,
and there I was,
going to be 90.
My God, where did it go?
One day, you're going to blink
and you're going to be 90.
And I won't be
around to see it,
and that makes me very sad.
I'm telling you.
I'm warning you.
Don't blink. Don't blink.
And then you missed
the mortgage payment,
and that's
the second mortgage.
You gotta tighten your belt.
You gotta go home, sit down,
Iook at your expenses,
come clean with Debbie.
Oh, God.
I can't tell Debbie.
You've got to tell her, Pete.
I mean, she knows it's bad,
but she has no
idea just how bad.
If you sell the house,
it'll really
buy you some time.
No, Debbie's not really
into selling the house.
As your business manager
and your friend,
I can't recommend that.
Hey, how funny would it be
if I bought your house?
Okay. Bye.
Hang in there.
From the retro label,
Unfiltered,
comes the first
Graham Parker & The Rumour
record in 30 years.
When we play together,
the magic was just ridiculous.
And I think what we've
got is just so great.
What are you doing?
I'm contextualizing him
as one of the great
figures in rock history.
You can't show him
in his prime in '77,
and then jump
straight to him
as he is now.
It's terrifying.
You have got to reverse it.
You have got to show him
as he is now, very briefly,
and then show him in 1977.
You have got to
Benjamin Button it.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
All rock stars are older now.
Steven Tyler,
David Bowie,
Mick Jagger...
Paul McCartney.
Okay. Stop it.
Everybody that
you are mentioning
looks like an old woman now.
You're just mentioning
a bunch of Jessica Tandys.
Keith Richards
gets away with it.
But that's
because Keith Richards
looked 70 when he was 40.
And now that he's 70,
he looks 69.
He's regenerating.
I like it, and I think
Graham Parker's sexy.
Well, would you fuck him?
Yes.
You'd...
You'd fuck him and
you won't fuck me?
I mean, I kind of
fucked you once,
if you could
have finished.
Oh. I finished.
Okay, enough of
who fucked who
and who finished what.
I finished.
Look, it's a retro label.
That's our niche,
that's our market.
It costs money to
break new bands.
I can't do that.
Okay, and also,
you're the guy who
turned down Arcade Fire.
Everybody turned
down Arcade Fire.
It's crazy.
There's so many of them.
We don't have the money
to market a new band.
We just need to make
Graham seem relevant.
Who's he talking to?
The Jewish Journal.
The Jewish Journal?
Apparently, old Jews
are the only ones who still
buy hard copy of records.
Because they don't
like to download music.
Because they don't know
what "downloading" means.
Why is this album
different from
any other album?
It isn't.
What is he wearing?
It's a hat with
the Oreo logo on it.
Why?
I don't think
he's being ironic.
I think he just
really likes Oreos.
Look, Paul Westerberg
record did okay.
Frank Black record
did all right.
The Haircut One Hundred,
not so much.
We have to break
this record. Otherwise,
we're not here next year.
He's coming, he's coming.
Oreo Man is coming.
Hey, guys, how are you?
Good, man.
Aren't cookies the best?
Yeah.
Jewish Journal guy
loves the record.
Great!
Got a bit of
a problem, though.
A touch of gout.
Gout?
My whole family,
they all had gout.
Jesus.
That's very unfortunate.
My auntie Queenie,
she had a foot like this.
It's like a size
of a small pig.
I've got a photo of it.
I'd love to see that
photo of that gout foot.
And a couple of
bunions as well.
Fuck.
I've got to go
to the podiatrist,
and I hope he can
shoot me up with something.
Yeah, well, let's get
you to the podiatrist.
Bye, Graham.
See you later, Graham.
Good luck with your gout.
Rock and roll, baby.
The happiest period
in people's lives
is from age 40 to 60.
So, this is it.
We're in it right now.
It's true.
Says who?
Says a lot of people.
Most people say that.
Oh!
We have everything
we need right now
to be completely happy.
We're going to blink,
and be 90.
What?
So, let's just
choose to be happy.
Yeah. Yeah.
Your eyes are
kind of glazing over.
No, I'm processing it all.
Some of these,
I wrote for you.
So, we have to
exercise every day.
Mmm.
Spend more time
alone together.
And we have to go
to the therapist, every week.
It's a little pricey.
No stressing over tiny things.
Yeah, that's good.
You should do that.
Mm-hmm.
We have to get more
involved in school.
Yeah.
Have more
patience with the kids.
And we need to
work on our anger.
Yeah, I think it would be
good if you could take
care of your anger.
No, I said both of us.
That's what I said.
Our anger.
Okay, and no more smoking.
Yeah, you gotta
cut that out.
I don't want to make
this about a fight.
I want to just be positive.
Yeah. Sorry.
Okay, and then no more
holding onto resentments.
We have to just let that go.
So, you're saying
that if we're arguing,
and I apologize,
you'll let it go?
And not throw it
back in my face later?
Well, I don't do that,
but I will continue
not to do that.
And what did you write?
All of that.
That's plenty.
That's a lot.
And you're going
to eat better?
Oh, yeah.
I've been doing
a decent job.
But I don't think
there's anything wrong
with having some
fries every now and again.
And then I'll smoke that day.
That's not the same thing.
It is the same thing.
I like fries.
And the other thing
is your dad's stuff,
the not letting him
guilt-trip you all the time
because that puts a lot
of pressure on you,
and stress,
and then
the whole family feels it.
And he is a grown man,
and he's not our
responsibility.
And you're not giving him
money anymore, right?
No. No, I haven't
been giving him money.
I haven't done that
for years. I told you.
Can you please put that down?
A lot of people are RSVP-ing
to your birthday party.
You sure you don't want
to just do a joint
birthday party?
No.
We always used to.
Did Jodi tell you she
thinks Desi's stealing?
Are you serious?
How much?
$12,000.
Oh, God.
And Desi's taking it?
Well, I don't know.
That's what Jodi said.
We really need
the store to work.
It is.
Don't put that kind
of pressure on me.
No, no. It's not
what I mean. I'm just...
Are you nervous
about money?
Are we okay?
Yeah.
All right.
Maybe we just suck it up
because she's clearly
earning so much more
than any other
employee we have.
Oh, yeah, for sure.
We can't fire her.
We're barely
breaking even with her.
That's why we
have to keep her.
Look at this.
She's making
out with somebody.
Is she screwing him?
That might be
like a dry hump.
Look at the position
of her skirt.
That's too grainy
to know for sure.
Oh, my God. This is in
the middle ofthe day.
Customers could be in there.
At least
she's getting some.
What did you say?
"At least she's getting some"?
Yes.
What are you talking about?
We had sex the other night.
You gotta give me
a little credit for that.
It's not about credit.
It's about...
We need to have
more passion.
Like this.
That's not passionate.
It looks
passionate to me.
What?
What is she doing?
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my gosh.
Don't do that.
What am I doing?
Don't fart in the bed.
I'm not. It's the springs.
This is why
we never have sex.
That's disgusting,
you're gross.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You're so...
God!
Sadie, Sadie,
Sadie, Sadie, Sadie
Charlotte,
I'm doing my homework.
Okay, watch this.
Watch this.
There's a haunted cow
back here.
I'm pretty sure
it does not have milk.
Moo.
Moo!
See that?
They took me away.
You're no fun.
You never want to play.
Charlotte, how many times
do I have to tell you?
Sadie, Sadie, Sadie
Sadie is boring
You're so mean
since your body
got weird.
Close the door.
You're no fun.
If you can just move
just a little bit more.
Oh, shit.
Okay, okay.
Ah!
Ow. Ow.
No, my boob is in there!
Did I tell you
that my son's
going to Stanford?
No, that's great.
Great for us,
and great for him.
Cough again.
Great school.
Everything looks good.
Your face is close
to my face.
Descending colon.
I'm about four
feet in right now.
That's what he said.
Are you a grinder?
Do you grind your teeth?
I grind all night.
Oh!
I think we need to
turn the gas down.
Turn it up!
No, we're going to
turn it down.
Turn it up!
Ooh!
Do you have to breathe
right on my neck?
Sorry.
What are you all
doing for Christmas?
Um, I don't know.
You have a tree
and everything?
Mm-hmm.
Isn't that fun?
In the spirit?
Sorry, I just had
one quick question.
On your form,
you said you
were born in 1974,
but your paper, it said '72.
So I just need to
know which it is.
It's 1974.
Oh, wait.
Because on your last form,
you said that you
were born in 1975.
Didn't you tell me
you were born in 1976?
No.
That's funny.
So, you want to
go with 1974?
I'm not gonna "go with" 1974.
It is 1974.
Okay.
Just remember to write
"1974" every time.
It's okay. It's 1976.
I lie about my age, okay?
Okay.
Okay? Okay? Okay?
You're tightening up.
Oh, my gosh.
I know how old you are
by counting the rings.
A little gyno joke.
Oh, my God. Please.
What are you doing?
Getting ready to
go for my ride.
You want a blow job?
Yeah. Why?
I really want
a cigarette right now.
Wow, happy to help.
Charlotte,
where is my backpack?
Hello?
Mom's busy!
Why are you
locking the door?
Mom, what's going on
in there?
Mom, I can't be late
for school. I have a test.
Mommy can't talk
right now!
This isn't funny, Mom.
I need to go!
Mom, let me in!
Please!
That's not gonna help!
Put on your shoes.
We'll meet you in the car.
Ow. Sadie hurt me!
I didn't!
So, hit her back!
She's faking.
I'm not!
Go downstairs!
Please! Sadie gave me a...
Stop crying!
Stop it!
God damn it!
Quit killing each other!
Mom, please come out.
Shut up!
Stop it!
- Open the door!
- Go away!
Open it up!
Please!
Forget it.
No, don't forget it,
don't forget it.
Don't, don't...
Oh, God.
Hey, boychik!
Hey!
It's the 11:00
from London.
Drop something valuable,
you shit!
How you doing?
How are you, bubeleh?
That's loud.
Every eight minutes, buddy.
You look pretty good.
Your hair is different.
Yeah, I'm growing it out.
I'd get it cut.
Daddy, you never
play with me.
I do, but right now,
look who I'm talking to.
Hi.
It's your brother!
You don't look
like my brother.
I told you, honey,
that's because
of the egg donor.
Remember?
I came from a test tube!
How's business?
It's not good.
Nobody wants curtains.
They think of it
like a luxury.
It's not a luxury.
You need shade.
You need privacy.
Who wants to have
other people watch you fuck?
I know how you feel.
My business is going through
some growing pains right now.
Daddy!
Don't jump on Daddy.
Be careful,
don't jump on Daddy!
Remember,
Daddy has high blood what?
High blood pressure.
That's right.
My daddy's old.
Can you go outside
without me for a little bit?
Yeah.
Don't go near
that little pool!
All right?
We're going to
pee in the pool.
Do The Three Stooges routine
you were practicing.
I can't tell them apart.
I swear to God,
I need tattoos.
Look, I wanted to
talk to you about
scaling back a little bit.
You know, Deb and I are...
We're thinking about
selling the house.
I think that house
is more than you need.
I think it was too big
of a purchase
when you made it.
Yeah. In the meantime,
I'm going to have
to make some changes.
I'm going to
have to cut back.
I understand.
What do you mean?
With you.
Oh.
I'm sorry. What?
I can't lend you
any more money.
No, that's a bad idea.
That's not the way
to cut back.
I have three children here.
What about Claire?
Can't she get a job?
Claire takes care
of your brothers!
What do you want
her to do?
If she goes to work,
then I gotta hire somebody!
Well, you've got to
figure something out
because I can't do it.
I can't do it.
Okay, fine.
Why don't we kill them?
Come on,
we'll kill two of them.
I'll keep the best one.
Really, it'll save us
both a lot of trouble.
Come on.
Line up!
Line up for murder! Come on!
Who wants to be killed?
I do!
Okay, we're eliminating
one already.
We're cheaper. You're gone.
Murder me.
Okay. Boom. Dead!
I'm dead!
You're dead! You're dead!
Kill me, kill me!
All right,
the kids are murdered.
That will save us some money.
Daddy is the best!
Why would you have
three kids, anyway?
I mean, you're 60 years old.
You have no money.
Because Claire wanted a baby.
If we didn't at least try,
she would have left me.
She was 45 years old.
Nobody thought it would take.
The doctor,
when we're doing in vitro,
is winking at me like...
"Don't worry, don't worry."
We were very unlucky.
And now,
we have these three
beautiful children.
Come on. I gotta
tell you something.
What?
Your mother
wanted you aborted.
Oh. Jesus Christ.
No, no. It's the truth.
You know, it was the '70s.
We were 22 years old.
That's what everybody did.
You did some blow,
had sex, had an abortion.
Really?
Yes.
We were on the way to
the doctor's office.
I said, "Let's stop,
have a pizza, talk about it.
"lf you still wanna
do it after lunch,
it's okay."
The pizza saved your life.
But don't give me money,
because I'm not worth it.
So, how much
do I owe you
for saving my life?
I don't have a number.
You just keep giving
like you're giving.
Hey. Oh, hi, Pete.
Hey.
Why aren't you
playing with the kids?
We were playing
all day with them.
Pete is just talking to me
about his 40th birthday party.
Whatever I can do to help.
Okay. Did you feed them?
I fed half of one.
Half of...
Let's go, we'll feed them.
Mommy will feed them.
Who wants tuna with
a side ofjet fuel?
Hi, I'm looking for my dad.
I mean, an older man.
So, how's Sony treating Pete?
He's not with Sony anymore.
He went out on his own.
Now he's able to
focus on the artists
that he's really
passionate about.
Hmm.
How's Sadie doing?
The last time I saw her,
she was throwing her
Cheerios on the floor.
What a mess.
Right.
She just got her period.
Well, I guess she's not
a little baby anymore.
It would be nice to
see more of each other.
Well, we can
certainly arrange for that.
I'd love to see the girls.
That would be nice.
Mm-hmm. It would.
Do you have a day
that is better...
A good day?
I would say the weekends,
but our weekends are hell.
Soccer competitions,
kids' exams.
Right, right.
I mean, we're both so busy.
I have young children,
you have young children.
I don't think we should
judge ourselves too
harshly about that.
I know, I wasn't...
I didn't say anything.
No, I'm glad we're here.
I think this is a good start.
And then, we can spend
more time together,
it'd be nice.
It'd be nice.
Do you want to see
pictures of the kids?
Oh. Yeah.
This is Kel, my son.
He's handsome. He's 13?
Mm-hmm.
And that's Alexandra,
my daughter.
She's a real perfectionist.
A lot like you.
That's the whole gang at Cabo.
Excuse me, dear,
I gotta go to the restroom.
Be right back.
Okay.
Daddy and I are
making some changes
so that we can be
happier and healthier.
And we're starting with
this meal that I prepared.
I think it looks great.
Doesn't it look good?
What is that,
grilled cheeses?
No, baked tofu.
Oh.
It's actually really tasty.
And the lettuce is
so fresh and tasty
that you forget how good
lettuce tastes on its own,
without dressing.
No, dressing always
gets in the way of the
natural taste of the lettuce.
And another
thing we've decided
is to cut back on
all of the electronics we use.
Basically,
what we're going to do,
is get rid of the Wi-Fi
and only use the computer...
What?
...from 8:00
to 8:30 at night.
How are we gonna
go on the computer?
We're gonna have
a hard line in the kitchen.
Yeah. We'll supervise that.
You can't do this.
You can't take away
the Wi-Fi.
No Wi-Fi!
A-ha-ha.
You don't spend
enough time with the family
when you're constantly
on your iPhone
and your computer.
And, you know, you're only
here for five more years.
So, you won't see
me after five years?
No, but you won't
be living with us.
And you should get to
know your little sister.
You've got
the perfect friend,
right here.
I don't wanna be
friends with her now.
I'll be friends with her when
she's 20 and a normal person.
I don't wanna hang out
with her when I'm in my 20s.
You're on the computer
too much as it is.
You need to get outside more,
do some playing outside.
Yeah, you could build things.
You could build
a fort outside.
What?
Yeah, build a fort.
Play with your
friends and have...
Make a fort? Outside?
And do what?
Do what in the fort?
When I was a kid,
we used to build tree houses
and play with sticks.
Nobody plays with sticks.
You and Charlotte can
have a lemonade stand.
Play kick the can.
Look for dead bodies.
It's fun. That's fun to do.
Get a tire and then
just take a stick and
run down a street with it.
Nobody does that crap.
It's 2012.
You don't need technology.
No technology!
Charlotte, put that down.
I don't need to be monitored
all the time on the computer.
I don't do anything bad.
Nobody said you were bad.
I don't do things
I'm not supposed to.
I don't illegally
download music.
I don't look at
porn like Wendy.
She is up to no good.
She's not allowed
to come over here anymore.
What's porn?
No, she said "corn."
This isn't turning out
the way I wanted it to.
I'm not hungry.
No computer.
Listen to your mom.
I need to use it
for my homework.
She's outplaying us.
I know. She's tough.
This is the best
birthday present.
It's good to get away.
We haven't been to Laguna
without the kids in years.
I know.
If we're happy,
they're happy.
Yeah, I mean,
I can't take it.
With the hormones,
and the crying.
Jesus.
And "do my homework."
Them's lil' bitches.
Bugging us for
shit all the time.
And they never
appreciate anything.
No! God, no.
They're selfish assholes.
Aw, I feel bad.
I love them.
I know.
I miss them already.
Should we go home?
Nah.
Why do we fight?
I don't know,
it makes no sense.
It makes no sense.
When we get in a fight,
Iook at my eyes and let's
remember this moment,
right now,
and know that we
never have to fight.
But you're such
a dick sometimes.
I know, I am a dick sometimes.
People think I'm so nice,
but I'm such a dick.
Thank you for admitting that.
And you get so mad at me,
I feel like you
want to kill me.
I do want to kill you.
How would you do it?
I don't know. I'd poison you.
I'd poison your cupcakes
that you pretend
not to eat every day.
And just put enough in
to just slowly weaken you.
I love it.
I would enjoy our
last few months together.
Me too.
Because you'd be
so weak and sweet.
And I could
take care of you...
But while killing you.
See, you know
what I love about us?
You can still surprise me.
I figured,
for sure, you'd knock me out
with one fell swoop of poison.
But you would extend it
over a series of months.
Have you ever
thought about killing me?
Oh, yeah.
Really?
Sure.
How would you do it?
Wood chipper.
A wood chipper?
Yeah.
A wood chipper.
Wow.
I know. Did you see Fargo?
Yeah.
Ugh.
That's a bad plan.
The cupcakes is
a way better plan.
It is. You're right.
You know what?
I won't murder you.
Aw!
I love you.
I love you, too.
Do you know what I brought?
What?
A medical marijuana cookie.
Ben gave it to
me last Christmas.
What?
Yeah. I brought it.
You did?
Chocolate chip kooky.
Should we do it?
Let's eat the cookie
and then we'll order
a bunch of cheeseburgers.
Let's order the entire
room service menu.
Just get all of it.
You deserve it,
you really do.
Wouldn't you
rather have me around
for less years
and I'm incredibly happy,
than longer and miserable?
Yes, and I just
realized that right now.
Go get the cookie.
I'm getting the cookie.
Ow!
Should we watch porn
when we eat the cookie?
Yeah. Should we
get a block of porn?
I don't think we
need 24 hours of porn.
But you know, two porns
costs just about as much
as a 24-hour block.
I think that's
too much porn.
We don't have to watch it all,
but for the value,
it makes sense.
How much are we
supposed to eat?
I don't know.
I think six or
seven cookies, right?
Plus, it's old,
it probably has
lost some of its...
Potency.
We should have sex more.
I mean,
girls have it so easy.
You just show up
with your sexual organs
and you're good to go.
All the pressure
is on the guy.
It's true.
And I look at guys...
Like, I look at a guy
like Prince,
and you know that guy fucks.
Yeah.
I know I don't
fuck like Prince.
Uh-uh.
Prince can fuck.
Uh-huh.
I fuck like David Schwimmer.
You do.
You know, I fuck
like Ross from Friends.
Mmm.
Looks good.
How does he do it?
The floating spoon.
Check it out.
It's my dick and balls.
Oh, my God.
I don't eat my own dick.
I ate my dick!
Kelly, I think
this room has rodents.
There! Just saw it.
Have you seen my starfish?
Where did I put my starfish?
My God.
I'm gonna deep
throat this clair.
I wanna make out
with you so bad.
I felt like
I was gonna choke!
That was nice.
Mom, Charlotte's crying
because she's got
an ear infection again.
I didn't know
what to do.
We're home.
Are you okay?
What's the matter?
I wanna rip my ear off,
it hurts so much.
I told you that pediatrician
didn't know what
he was talking about.
Come on, you can't
blame it on our doctor.
Ear infections are
common in little kids.
Not in kids
over six years old.
We're going to
the Eastern doctor.
If she's in this much pain,
then we should
call a real doctor.
Are you kidding
right now?
I know. Okay. Yup.
What we should do
is easy and simple.
No more dairy,
no more wheat,
no more sugar.
Sugar, wheat
and dairy. Okay.
Yeah.
What the fuck is left?
Sorry.
Isn't everything sugar,
wheat, and dairy?
She can have
vegetables and fruits.
Oh, but she can eat fruits.
Fruits. Yeah.
Any kind of fruit?
Mangos, pineapple.
It isn't,
there are safe fruits
and then there
are unsafe fruits?
No, no.
What about French fries?
Could we do
something like that?
Are you okay?
Would you like to
come on the table?
I'm okay, I'm...
Why don't you go
on the table?
I don't wanna go
on the table.
No. It looks like you
need to get on the table.
I don't wanna
get on the table.
Pete!
God damn it.
What are you doing?
I need you to look at
something. In my butt.
Why?
I think I got
something in there,
and I'm not
limber enough to see.
I need you to look
at it, all right?
I think I might have an
anal fissure, or a hemorrhoid,
or a worm or something.
What are you
doing with your phone?
I'm trying to take pictures
of it so I can compare it
to something on Google.
Can we just keep
just a small shred of mystery
in our relationship, please?
Look, I saw you
have two babies, okay?
Seriously, I need you
to get up all in that.
I do not want to
investigate your anus.
Payback time.
It's a hemorrhoid.
Thank you.
Now, erase that
from your memory.
Where'd she get those clothes?
Those are expensive clothes.
Think. Where do you think?
I don't want
this to sound harsh,
but everything that comes out
of her mouth is a lie.
Everything that
goes into it is a dick.
goes in is dicks?
A dick.
Don't say that.
I'm sorry.
I'm just being
protective of the store.
I'm going to go
talk to her.
Hey, Desi.
Hi.
Is that your new
Acura out front?
Uh, yeah.
It's so nice.
Do you love it?
I mean, it's not a fucking
Porsche, but it'll do for now.
Huh.
Hey, Desi,
would you mind wearing
some of the clothes that
we have in the store?
Yes. Yeah, I'm sorry.
Will that be okay?
Yeah.
Perfect.
Good?
You know, I actually
made this one myself.
Did you?
Yeah.
The tiger, I did it on a piece
of paper separately,
and then I actually
transferred it to the T-shirt.
Wow.
So, you stenciled
on the tiger?
I drew it on
a piece of paper and then
I transferred
the drawing to the T-shirt.
You have an amazing body.
Really?
Yes. Are those real?
My boobs?
Yeah.
Yeah. Do you wanna
touch them?
Really?
Touch them.
Okay.
Wow.
Huh.
Jesus.
I mean,
they really are amazing.
That's firm, for real.
They're like
a memory mattress.
It's, wow, like
Tempur-Pedic, you know?
They look amazing.
My kids just sucked
the meat right out of mine.
No.
Yeah.
There's some meat in there.
My boobs are just gone.
Since I had kids,
my boobs are just gone.
They didn't even
say goodbye, you know?
They just left.
By the time I'm 40,
these are gonna
go National Geographic on me.
I feel bad about
myself right now.
I think this is
a really good offer
on the house.
We expected more.
I know it's a bad market,
but that's still way under
what we were looking for.
I know, but based on what
the market's like, it's like
you're gaining money,
because it's so much
more than what you deserve.
But these people are from Iran
and they don't really know
that they're offering
too much.
Is there any chance
that Debbie will go for it?
I doubt it.
I mean, I don't know.
There's a lot of
inventory out there.
I mean, what is her problem?
She has
unrealistic expectations.
I'm faster than you!
We're Jewish!
Hey! Did you miss me, Travis?
It's Jack.
Hey, Jack.
My daddy
doesn't know my name!
Okay, come on,
let's go.
Can I go show them my
crystals before they leave?
Yeah, really quick.
It's all right with me.
Elevator down!
Okay. Go play with
your tiny uncles.
- Let's play murder!
- Yeah. Let's go.
So, what are you doing?
Spring cleaning?
I'm getting rid of
everything in the house
that has gluten or sugar.
Why? What's wrong
with gluten?
Gluten's really bad for you.
I don't think so.
It's wheat.
Don't you watch Dr. Oz?
As in, "The Wizard of"?
Hey, Mom, we were wondering
if we can use
the computer to iChat?
Remember the rules?
8:00 to 8:30.
Yeah, but I have
a friend over.
Hi, Wendy. Yeah, I know.
Why don't you guys go play?
You could go build a fort!
Hey, remember the Alamo?
Have you ever
built a fort, Wendy?
Like, on Facebook?
I will take this
if you're gonna
throw it away,
because at our house,
we're wheat-eaters.
But don't you want
to live long enough
to see your kids grow up?
That's up to God, honey.
No, but that's really
not good for the kids.
Eh, the kids eat grass,
this is fine.
Wendy's mom lets her go on
whenever she wants.
Yeah, my mom's
pretty cool about it
as long as
I finish my homework.
Yeah.
Well, I guess
I'm not the cool one,
but the rules are just
different in our house.
Well, I get better
grades than Wendy.
She does. She's so smart.
Let me just grab
the candy worms.
See, your rules
are ridiculous.
Don't sass me.
I'm only sassing you
because you're throwing out
all the food in our house
and I'm freaking starving.
You're being stupid.
Wendy, could you go stand
in the other room, please?
Yeah.
Mom.
Give me your iPhone, now.
The nougat things are good.
I have all my
contacts in there.
Okay, if you don't give me
your phone right now,
then I'm gonna
have to take away
your phone and your computer.
Jesus Christ, I need
my computer to do homework.
That's it.
No phone, no computer.
This is B.S.
This is a bunch of F-ing S.
You're acting like a B.
Kids! Time to go!
You go to your room,
right now.
You are not allowed to use
iPhone, iPad,
iPod Touch, iTunes, Netflix,
Pandora, or Spotify.
She's a little pip,
just like her mommy.
So, I might have
a job tomorrow.
At least, I'm gonna go
try to give an estimate.
Do you mind taking the kids
for a couple of hours?
Um...
Okay.
This is nice.
You and I don't spend
enough time together, do we?
We spend enough time together.
We do?
It's quality time.
Then we do.
I'll go with what you think.
What else did they say?
All right,
some kid named Joseph...
I know Joseph.
You do?
He's making
a "hot-or-not" list.
What?
Sadie said, "That's so lame
and immature that
you're doing that."
And then Joseph says,
"Yo, girl,
we're just having some fun.
"So don't be a bitch, yo."
That is not nice.
So then Sadie said,
"Don't call me a bitch."
And Joseph said,
"l didn't call you a bitch.
"l said don't
act like a bitch.
"And by the way,
you're in
the 'Not-Hot' column."
Who made him
the judge of "hot"?
Do you realize what that
could do to her self-esteem?
What a little fuckhead.
I'll kill him.
Then Sadie said,
"You're in the
jackass column.
"l gotta go,
I'm bored of you."
That is cool.
That's taking the high road.
And then,
for some reason,
there's an emoticon
of a panda doing push-ups.
I wonder what that means.
I don't think it
means anything.
I think it's just adorable.
Aww.
Well, she's a good girl.
She was polite and she
stood up for herself.
That's pretty cool.
What?
Shit.
I thought she was coming in.
Oh, my God,
that scared me to death.
If she caught us,
she would kill us.
She would.
She would kill us.
Huh.
I gotta make a call.
We sold how many?
612 album downloads.
Wait a minute. There
are no zeroes after that?
There are zeroes,
but all of them
are before 612.
There are none after.
How is that even possible?
Well, out of
300 million Americans,
612 people chose
to download the album.
You could personally call
everyone who
bought this record.
We're fucked, we're fucked.
Here's the deal,
I want you to meet me
tomorrow morning at 8:00.
I want a list of at least
30 ideas of what we can do
to change this.
We have to change this.
I started a record label
because I couldn't get a job,
so I have no other options.
What financial problems?
Well, I mean, for one thing,
you were right.
You are missing about
$10,000 from the store.
And then, Pete's
record not selling well.
Pete's record
not selling...
I thought we weren't supposed
to hear for three weeks.
We heard.
You heard?
And they're bad.
It's that and it's the money
that he's been
lending his father.
That's creating a strain.
How much have we lent him?
Eighty thousand.
Did you say 8,000 or 80,000?
80,000, over
the past couple ofyears.
And then you missed
the mortgage payment.
On the house?
And you missed
the rental on the office.
Does Pete know that?
Yeah, we're on
the phone all the time.
Look, I know you're
going through a hard time.
And I want you guys to know
that we're here for you, okay?
Anything you guys need,
that's why we're here.
We're here for
times like this.
What are you gonna do?
There's not much I can do.
What are you doing?
I'm drawing the album cover
for Van Halen's Diver Down.
If you spent a little bit more
time focusing on Graham Parker
instead of
drawing album covers,
I wouldn't be in
this predicament.
I'm focused on
Graham Parker.
You're supposed to
help me with him.
call the companies.
You're supposed to
get people to the show.
I've done
everything I can, Pete.
You had me
pushing around a corpse.
It was like being in fucking
Weekend at Graham's.
What should we do?
I'm out of ideas.
You fly in The Rumour.
I can't sell a reunion
concert without the band,
it's ridiculous.
With what?
I can't afford it.
You put this on yourself.
You wanted the responsibility.
Take it on the fucking chin,
and stop acting like a bitch.
What did you call me?
Chin.
Pete. Wait, Pete!
Hey, I have an apartment.
I have health insurance,
I have car payments.
I have responsibilities.
You have responsibilities?
Don't talk to me
about responsibilities.
I have a life.
I have a family.
I can't afford to
sit in my apartment
getting high, jerking off,
and then going to
Tommy's Chili Burgers
at 3:00 in the morning.
That's not even the order
that that happens in!
I have everything
to lose, here.
Everything.
Yes, because you spent
thousands of dollars
on shit we don't need.
You really need
to spend $30,000 on
a fucking neon sign, dude?
Which is inside,
it's not even outside.
We know where we work.
If you want to sign a band,
you gotta look like
you're the real deal.
Princess Labia, how much is it
to fucking fly The Rumour in?
It's 12,000.
$12,000!
All right,
you know what? Fine.
Fly in The Rumour.
Put it on my AmEx.
No, you said
it was impossible.
I don't think
I said "impossible."
Yeah.
I usually don't
say "impossible."
I like to leave
some wiggle room.
You said that my fibroid
was like a giant boulder,
Iike the one from
the Indiana Jones movies
blocking up my uterus.
Uterus.
And I need to stop using
that reference
of Indiana Jones.
I think that that's not
appropriate when talking about
the reproductive system.
It's okay.
Anyway, somehow the
Eastern medicine has worked,
and the fibroid
has dissipated.
That's great!
Yes.
Wow.
Your fibroid
shrunk and somehow
it allowed you
to get pregnant.
What?
You're gonna have
your third baby.
Congratulations.
No.
Yes.
Would you like some water?
That's good news.
Another baby.
At 40.
Debbie?
I am thrilled.
And Pete is gonna be so happy.
So, you're okay?
What a relief.
Because I can finally
relax now, you know?
It's been, like...
It's okay.
I'm so happy,
though, you know?
I really am,
because, I mean...
It's good.
Great. Great.
Hey.
Why are you in a bathrobe?
It's the middle
of the afternoon.
I took a late shower.
Why are you busting my balls?
I'm sorry about the record.
You're going
through financial shit.
This is what I live with.
This is a horrible
time in human history.
What is that?
It's something that might
help both of our situations.
This is
a drawing by John Lennon.
I got it 10 years ago
for $5,000.
I don't know how
much it's worth now.
It could be five,
it could be 20.
I don't want this.
I don't even like it.
I'm not gonna hang it up.
It's not for you to hang up.
It's for you to sell.
That way, I can give it to you
and you make some money,
and Debbie won't know
that I'm giving you anything.
You're not giving me money.
You're giving me a project.
I don't know how to sell this.
I'm not an art dealer.
I don't know.
Sell it online.
You know, do some research,
make some calls.
Or is that too hard to do
with your high blood pressure?
All right.
Don't get snippy.
Just because you
write a great song
doesn't mean you can draw.
It's incredible.
John Lennon drew it.
I think it's a Ringo.
Don't beat me up if
I get $300 for it.
Don't take anything
less than $6,500 for that.
It's very valuable.
It's important to me.
I want you to sell
it so I can help you.
Okay.
All right.
I'll see you at my party.
What should I bring?
You want wine or something?
No, don't buy wine
with my money
and give it to me at my party.
That's mean.
I love you. Bye.
All right.
How do I call eBay?
I mean, he called me a bitch.
What am I supposed to say?
But I think maybe that
might mean he likes me.
I don't know.
It's making me really...
It's really awkward.
I think he might like you.
She's so cute.
She's so tall.
I know.
How did that happen?
Do you ever wish we
had a bigger family?
No.
Never for a second.
Never.
Never?
I love what we have.
One? A breeze.
Two? Brutal.
Three?
Put a bullet in my head.
Ugh.
You know, I think about that
gray-haired pregnant lady
from school,
and I just feel bad for her.
And I feel bad
for the kid.
Can you imagine?
All the other little kids,
"Where's your mommy?"
"Oh, she's the one
sitting in that scooter,
eating a soft cracker."
Kids don't want to
have old parents.
You know what?
It would also be nice for
us to spend some time apart.
Kind of rediscover who
we are, individually.
It'd be so great to not
see you for a chunk of time,
so that I could
really just miss you.
Remember when we
used to miss each other?
Hey! Hey, you.
Yeah, what's up?
Hey, I'm Sadie's mom.
Sadie?
Sadie, the one you
chat with on the lnternet.
No, man. That ain't me.
Well, it was you.
I saw your picture.
Did you make a hot list?
And not put Sadie
on the hot list?
She was not on my list, no.
You know
what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna make
my own hot list.
And you know what?
You're on the not-hot list.
How does that feel?
It doesn't bother me.
I'm comfortable
with the way I am.
Maybe you shouldn't be
so comfortable with yourself.
You know why?
You look like
a miniature Tom Petty.
How's that feel?
You think that
haircut's cool? It's not.
It looks like you
put your Justin
Bieber wig on backwards.
Are you still
comfortable with yourself?
Why are you wearing
a tank top? Huh?
So you can show off
your little bald pits,
you little hairless wonder?
Cool tank top,
man. Huh?
So next time you think about
writing something nasty
on my daughter's
Facebook page,
just remember me.
Remember me.
I will come down here,
and I will fuck you up.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Wait a minute.
Hey, hey, hey!
Wait. You're not...
Are you crying?
Just let me go.
Oh, my...
I'm sorry.
Okay.
I'm not in my right head.
I understand.
My mom's going
through menopause, too.
It's a hard time.