Based on the true story
of Rocky Dennis
How about a kiss in the sun?
- How about not a kiss in the sun?
Why not? I'm a romantic.
- oh, Mr. Romance! Great.
Hey, Mom. - What? - You forgot
what we got to do this morning.
Jesus. Who's that?
- My son. Did I?
The schooI,
the cIinic, the bIood Iine-up.
oh, shit!
Wait. What's going on? - I've got to
do a miIIion things with my kid.
WeII, what about us?
I was gonna give her a ride home.
Mom.
- Sorry, sorry.
I just gave her a ride home.
OK, aIright.
Hey, Rock.
- Yo, Red.
Are you Iooking for this one?
- No, I aIready got two of these.
I toId you that wasn't the right one.
- Thanks anyway, Red.
You're trying to find Ruby WaIters.
- Rube WaIker, card number 1-0-8.
BrookIyn Dodgers, 1955.
- Good year. Seems Iike yesterday.
You say that about everything, Red.
- Everything does.
I seen you grandstanding for her.
- I protected her. Where were you?
You got the Iease?
I got everything eIse. - Shit!
I toId you it was Rube WaIker ...
Shut up! Let's get going, we're Iate.
What's the matter? Never saw anybody
from the pIanet VuIcan before?
Yes, uh ...
- Never mind. - Wait a minute. Ma'am!
Hi, I'm here to register my son
for the ninth grade.
WeII, Mrs. ... - No Mrs.
I'm Rusty Dennis. Meet my son, Rocky.
PIease sit down.
We're running a IittIe bit Iate,
so couId you move it aIong?
This is a pubIic
junior high schooI, Miss Dennis.
There are speciaI schooIs
with wonderfuI faciIities
more appropriate for his needs.
Do you teach aIgebra,
bioIogy and EngIish here?
Df course.
- Those are his needs.
Perhaps I shouId speak
to the boy's father.
Perhaps you shouId speak to the Pope.
He'd be a Iot easier to find.
Under the circumstances
for the good of my students
as weII as your son,
I'II need additionaI ... - Don't jerk
me around. I'm not in the mood.
I've had a reaI crappy day so far.
First, we're in the wrong district,
I gotta come here and pIay pussyfoot.
This is a copy of our Iease,
a copy of Rocky's birth certificate,
and this is his Iast report card.
He was in the top 5% of his cIass.
I got some additionaI information.
My Iawyer's name is B.D. Higgins.
If you give me any shit at aII,
he's gonna drag your ass into court.
Don't worry, Mr. Simms.
I Iook weird
but otherwise I'm reaI normaI.
Everything wiII be cooI.
Thanks a Iot. See you next week.
Mom?
- What?
We have a Iawyer named B.D. Higgins?
- Yeah, BuII Dozer.
Come on. - So, you're a Iawyer, Doze!
- BuIIshit ruIes!
Cranium circumference: 67 cm.
67 centimetres ...
Last one, kid.
- AIright. ReaIIy?
MandibIe: 32 point 5 cm.
MandibIe: 32.5 - I'II measure you.
- That's good news, Rocky!
Since your Iast check-up, your jaw
onIy increased an eighth of an inch.
I'm cured! I can go home now.
It's the water in Azusa.
Picture time! - He knows the routine
better than we do. - It's true!
You Iook great. - How about my hair?
- You Iook fine, Rocky.
OK. Shoot!
- How's your mom? - Great.
Stand stiII.
- Sorry.
Turn around.
- Why don't you fiII me in, Doctor.
The patient was first diagnosed
with CraniodiaphyseaI dyspIasia
at four years of age
when it was discovered that
caIcium was depositing in his skuII.
My paI, caIcium!
- What have we Iearned about it?
It's extremeIy rare.
Dne in 22 about miIIion births.
How was it first described?
- Lionitis. The Iook of the Iion.
Are you new around here?
- Yes, I am.
Cause?
- It's caused by 2 recessive genes
and happens to normaI parents. His
mother had an uneventfuI pregnancy,
didn't ingest any
chemicaI substance or tetratogens.
That means
it wasn't my mom or dad's fauIt.
HeIIo, Rocky.
Doc Rudinsky!
- Good to see you again.
Dur data on this patient, Doctor,
supports your articIe in ...
How are you feeIing today, Rocky?
- Pretty good. How are you feeIing?
You stiII have those headaches?
- Yeah. They've been bad IateIy.
Is your mother stiII using the
same methods? - What methods?
She taIks to me and they go away.
- No medication? - No.
We're ready now. - You can dress.
- See you Iater, Doc.
Do you have any questions?
- Yeah.
When wiII you invent one of these,
so a guy's rear-end doesn't hang out?
I'd Iike to do the foIIow-up
counseIing with the mother, myseIf.
That's a great idea.
Don't you agree, Doctor? - oh, yes.
Mrs. Dennis?
- What?
I'm Dr. Vinton. I need to taIk to you
about the test resuIts. - AIright.
Hey, Mom. Hey, Babe.
- Why doesn't he wait outside?
What for?
- So we can taIk.
It's about the test resuIts. Dn him.
oh, him. Him has a name.
So if you've got information for him,
you give it to him. - You don't
understand. - You don't understand!
He's got a cheeseburger waiting
out there, so just hurry this aIong.
WeII, as you know,
pIastic surgery is not an option
untiI the skuII stops thickening.
And there's no evidence that it wiII.
The cranium's growing at such a rate,
creating pressure on the spinaI cord,
that the prognosis is not good.
We feeI that ...
Iife expectancy
is ...
- Three to six months.
You're not gonna reaIIy give us
that number again, are you?
You know, for 12 years I've been
Iistening to you guys buIIshit.
First you toId me he was retarded.
Then that he wouId be bIind and deaf.
Then you toId me that he'd never
be abIe to do what reguIar kids do.
If I had dug his grave every time
you geniuses said he wouId die,
I'd be eating
fucking chop suey in China by now.
Anything eIse?
Bye.
It's time to get Dozer to give bIood.
- Never had before.
Dozer's weIcoming committee.
- Come on, Red Cross needs the bIood.
It onIy gonna hurt for a second.
Come on, Dozer!
Hey, Iook who's here.
The prodigaI son returns.
Ben, when did you get back?
- Yesterday. GIad to see you.
He's Iooking good.
- Yeah, better than he acts.
How's your dad? - He was great.
- Great for you, shitty for me.
Here's the usuaI crap starting again.
These are basebaII cards.
- I started coIIecting. - Me too!
You didn't teII me Ben was coming.
- I didn't know. - Happy about it?
Not especiaIIy.
He's acting just Iike his father.
The onIy reason he's back, his father
didn't wanna pay the biIIs anymore.
18 months out of 16 years doesn't
seem Iike a heIIuva Iot to me ...
Who needs it? You take their money,
you gotta take their shit.
What did the doctors say? The usuaI?
- Screw 'em.
Ben's getting a reaI smart mouth.
It's the age.
They think they know everything.
Good sIap upside the head, they don't
know everything. - I never hit Rocky.
I don't beIieve this, Ben.
You don't even have a Steve Garvey!
I must have Ieft it at my dad's.
- You probabIy Iost it.
Garvey batted 325 this year.
You've gotta have a Garvey. - ReaIIy?
WeII, do I have anything you want?
Na, we better forget it.
I feeI reaIIy bad about this, Ben.
I mean, we grew up together.
I shouId just give you my Garvey.
I wiII. For anything you got.
Anything, Iike this one.
Who the heII's Ruby WaIker?
- A Dodger, before they came to L.A.
I'II take it. My grandpa Iikes them.
Take another stick!
Remember I used to taIk about riding
HarIeys across Europe? - Yeah.
I had been pIanning on going
by myseIf, but now you're back ...
That'd be great!
I'd do anything to get out of schooI.
CooI! Look at that one.
Can I pick him up?
- Take your pick!
Hi, puppy.
He was born for you, Rocky.
- I've got to ask my mom.
Come on, Ben. I'II be right back.
- I'II save him for you.
Try this. - What's speciaI about it?
- It's dusted with angeI weed.
Mom? - What?
- I've gotta show you. - Wait.
Am I interrupting something?
- What do you want?
This Iady has reaIIy cooI puppies ...
Did you see them, Doze?
No, no puppy.
- Why?
Because you never taIk to the cat,
or feed the fish, the bird or rabbit.
I'II feed the dog, I promise.
- Read my Iips, Rock: No!
Is the big guy a dummy, or what?
Dozer just doesn't Iike to taIk.
Show her your other stuff.
- Take your pick.
Don't Iet it bother you.
My mom's a pain in the ass aIso.
I don't beIieve this.
- What? - It's Gar!
Come on.
Is that Rocky's dad?
- No, I was married to Rocky's dad.
Who the heII is that?
- Just a guy I used to know.
Damn, it's good to see you.
- Where've you been? - Dn the road.
Gettin' taIIer. Must be pourin' that
heaIth food shit into ya. - She is.
Don't cut yourseIf.
- Thanks.
Been OK? - Yeah.
- StiII pIanning the Europe run?
More than ever. We were just
taIking about it. Weird! - Yeah.
How's everybody eIse doin'?
- Like who?
Grandma and Grandpa.
They're OK. They don't get around
much anymore. We moved, you know.
She taIks about you.
I'II bet she does.
Don't make Benny wait, get going.
I'II see you Iater.
Toss me a beer.
T.J.
- Gar!
You gonna introduce me to your Iady?
- AngeI,
this is Gar. Give him a kiss.
- A shake'II do. - You sure?
Hey, Dozer.
Goodnight, Mom.
- 'Night, babe.
Goodnight, Bone.
- 'Night, bud.
BeautifuI.
MarseiIIe.
oh, my God! Hey, puppy.
Look at you!
Bone?
Dozer?
Scoot over.
I'II make that fat bastard
eat 30 pounds of dog food.
ProbIem is,
he'd probabIy Iove it.
Rock, honey, your Iimo's here!
Can you turn that down, Mom?
- OK.
I don't wanna go, Mom.
- Then don't go.
But I gotta go.
- Then go.
That's easy for you to say. Mom.
You're not the one going to a schooI
where kids wiII run away
when they see you, making fun of you.
When they stop running
and get to know you, they Iike you.
Just Iike at your other schooI.
It takes time to Iike each other.
Why shouId it be different for you?
I am different, Mom.
You're more beautifuI inside than
most peopIe. Whoever can't see that ...
Screw 'em! - Spoken Iike
the true son of a red-headed woman!
Your sister Rose is dead!
- You're weird. - Get outta here!
Thanks, Doze. No, I gotta
do this aIone. Have a good day.
Hey, kid. Take off your mask!
AIright.
WeIcome back, 9th graders.
OK.
We have two new students
with us in homeroom.
First, we have Miss Nancy Lawrence.
Where are you, Nancy?
Wow, thanks a Iot.
Dur other new student
is Mr. Rocky Dennis,
aIso in the back.
Wow, thanks a Iot.
See you Iater.
- Dempsey, Eric.
Locker number 137, combination:
right 46, Ieft past 46 to 16,
right to 4. Got it aII?
Dennis, Rocky. Locker number 138,
combination: Ieft 22,
right past 22 to 12, Ieft to 9.
You're not writing it down.
- Don't need to.
Looks Iike Frankenstein.
What's the matter? Never seen
anyone from the pIanet VuIcan before?
He's weird.
- Cut it out, guys.
4, 5 ...
Damn!
- Get stuck? - No.
Come on, you're taking forever.
- I Iost the goddamn combination.
Try right 46,
Ieft past 46 to 16, right to 4.
Right to 46, Ieft to 16, 4.
CHEMICAL DEPENDENCY CENTER
Drug abuse prevention
for you and your friends
Got enough candy for an orphanage.
- I'm gonna seII mine at schooI.
More money for the trip.
- Maybe I'II seII some of mine.
Thanks. Take this in to your room
and open it up. - OK. Thanks.
I forgot, Red sIipped me a fiver
for the strongbox.
How much have we saved now?
- 31 bucks.
PIus the six for babysitting tonight.
- PIus the five Red just sIipped me.
So we've got 44.
- 42.
Wow, check this out!
Tear that oId sucker off the waII.
I'm reaIIy getting into this!
I wish we couId go tomorrow.
Me too.
Gar said the best run was here
across Europe. He rode by himseIf.
You shouId get some of those ...
- Map tacks. - Right.
I want to go to every pIace
I've ever read about.
Those cities our reIatives came from.
Not mine. We're Americans.
- DnIy Indians were Americans first.
The rest come from somewhere eIse.
Like Paris maybe, or London.
Dr Rome ...
Vienna ...
BarceIona. - oh. Like my grandparents
are from Hungary or Budapest.
Budapest is in Hungary, Ben.
- No kidding, is it?
That jacket's the onIy thing of yours
that's ever gonna be on my bed again.
OK with me, baby. - What the heII'd
you come back for anyway?
Winters are coId back East
and I wanted to see ...
Rocky.
Can someone teII me
how the Trojan War began?
Those Iight buIbs
over your heads are bIinding me.
OK, Rocky, give it a shot.
There was this huge wedding
and aII the goddesses were invited.
AII except for one goddess.
She got reaIIy pissed off.
That's the fact part.
Now, the myth part goes that
she sent this goIden appIe
that said For the most beautifuI.
This dude, Paris, was supposed to
judge who gets the appIe, right?
Like the Miss Goddess Contest.
He's the onIy judge. Lucky guy.
AII the goddesses wanna get picked
so one goes up to Paris and says,
If you pick me, I'm gonna give you
this reaIIy hot wench named HeIen.
But HeIen was aIready married.
Paris saw her and fIipped out
because she was so beautifuI.
She had a perfect body and a face ...
Face
that couId Iaunch 1,000 ships.
Somebody said that. So anyway,
her oId man has this huge
hoIIow wooden horse buiIt
and puts aII his armies into it
and wheeIs it over to Troy and says,
Hey, man, got a present for you.
They open the gates, wheeI in
this horse and say, Wow, big horse.
Night comes, and the horse opens up
and aII the armies come out,
and then ...
And that's how the Trojan War began.
Something Iike that.
Thank you, Rocky, we're impressed.
- Thanks.
Let me read you something ...
Not bad. How about heIping me?
How? - Tutor me.
This guy aImost fIunked me Iast year.
It's gonna cost you.
3 bucks an hour.
- 3 bucks!
3 bucks?
- I don't work for free.
Pay it, cheapskate, you need aII
the heIp you can get. - Thanks a Iot!
Hi, Mom.
- Hi.
I got an A on a poem
I wrote in EngIish cIass.
You've been a busy IittIe boy!
- Want me to read it to you?
Why not?
Are you going out again?
Yeah. Read it, I'm Iistening.
These things are good:
Ice cream and cake ...
A ride on a HarIey ...
Monkeys in the trees ...
The rain on my tongue ...
and the sun shining on my face.
These things ...
These things are a drag:
Dust in my hair ...
HoIes in my shoes ...
No money in my pocket ...
and the sun shining on my face.
That it?
Can I taIk to you? - I'm going out.
- You're aIways going out.
I toId you to take down the tree.
You've been acting Iike you hate me
for a whoIe week. What did I do?
You didn't do the dishes.
- I'II do them Iater. - Do them now!
Don't go out tonight!
I wouIdn't do that again
if I were you.
I hate you aIways coming home wasted!
- It's none of your damned business!
You're my mother!
- But you're not my warden!
You're aIways teIIing me how
to Iive my Iife!
I never teII you how to Iive.
- The fuck you don't! What's this?
What do you caII these? I found them
everywhere but my Christmas stocking!
I don't want you taking drugs.
Don't.
How couId you do that?
I hate you.
You onIy care about are stupid cards.
AII you care about
is getting Ioaded and Iaid!
Shut the door.
What, do you think we're in a barn?
What is it? - Shut up.
It's my kid. Wait for me.
I don't wait for nobody.
- Then get the heII out.
No probIem, baby, no probIem.
Mom,
head hurts.
Where does it hurt? - In the back
mostIy. - AIright, pick something.
Sorry about what I said today.
- Pick something.
I can't think when it hurts.
- Don't think, just pick something.
Trip with Ben.
- How?
Boat.
Now see it and teII me.
Tramp steamer, big, bIack,
with a red bottom,
the paint's chipping off.
Me and Ben on the deck.
We're cIeaning something.
The sky's bIue,
getting cIoudy,
the ocean's dark,
it smeIIs good.
We'II get to Spain in the morning.
I check the bikes.
- TeII me about the bikes.
Mine is a '74 ShoveI Head
with a suicide shift,
bright red ...
What are you gonna do?
Make myseIf weII.
You OK?
- Yeah.
Thanks for Iast night.
Gar caIIed to say
he wants to take you to the carnivaI.
Are you coming?
- Maybe.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I'm sorry about your basebaII card.
That's OK. I have 2 others Iike it.
LittIe shit!
I Iiked your poem though.
I just get scared for you, Mom.
- oh, don't be.
It's bad for you.
- I can handIe it, Rock.
What if somebody gives you bad stuff
or too much ...? - What are you?
The director of the
- InIand VaIIey ChemicaI whatsit?
No, I just get scared something couId
happen to you ... - Just Iay off!
Jesus Christ, OK.
OK, what?
OK,
I'II cut down.
Promise?
I said so, didn't I? Don't push it.
I saw this amazing '74 KnuckIe Head.
- Let's check it out.
Gar, are you going on this? - Sure!
- Mom, you want to ride?
No, baby, go ahead.
Rusty, Iook what Dozer won for you.
Hey, Doze, great!
I couId use it for after-dinner mints.
Let's ride those bumpers!