When the dim moonlight is on the spring
I think of you"
Really?
Is that what it says?
Gee!
Oh my gosh
Sang-min must really like me a lot
You have to give it
to me tomorrow, okay?
Okay
I have no reason to see him anymore
He wants to be with Soo-gyung now
When the sun shines on the sea...
When the dim moonlight is on the spring...
Are you done?
Wait a little longer
Hand in your manure
in an envelope after lunch
- Got it?
- Yes, sir
Those who didn't bring it hurry and go take a shit!
Got it?
Let's get together!
One! Two!
Joon-ha
I'll close my eyes and run so you guide me, okay?
I'm really closing them
Okay
Joon-ha
Wanna come with me to learn the folk dance after class?
folk?
I'm gonna meet Joo-hee there
It's my dad and his friend's idea
They want us to meet at a healthy recreation
A lot of girls will be there
so you pick one up
- Gonna come, right?
- I don't know
Tae-soo!
Joo-hee, this is my friend Oh Joon-ha
She's the one I told you about
I'm Oh Joon-ha
Nice to meet you
Hello
Are you two friends?
Know each other?
No, we don't
He's my best friend
This is my friend, Na-hee
Hi, I'm Na Na-hee
- I'm YOON Tae-soo
- I'm Oh Joon-ha
Everyone please have a seat
Come on!
Anywhere is fine
Today I will teach you the folk dance
- Sounds fun, right?
- Yes
Folk Dance is...
I missed you
Me, too
I didn't know you were Tae-soo's friend
I want to be a woman anchor
So I always practice my speech
Can you do this?
Peter Piper picked
a peck of pickled peppers
Did I do okay?
I can do it faster
Peter Piper picked
a peck of pickled peppers
Shall I do it faster?
Peter Piper picked
a peck of pickled peppers
Give it a try
Peter Piper a pecked
of peppers pickled...
You'll need a lot of practice
Repeat precisely after me
Peter Piper picked
a peck of pickled peppers
We should split up now
I'll take Joo-hee home
so you take care of Na-hee
Okay?
See you later
I had fun
Good night
Bye, Joo-hee
What are you doing?
Let's get going
Joon-ha
then try something easier
Try this
She sells seashells by the seashore
Easy, huh?
Give it a try
Pardon?
I said give it a try
Give what a try?
She sells seashells by the seashore
Give this a try
I can't
Please don't ask me to
You can't do this?
She sells seashells by the seashore
It's easy
- Have a good...
- Yes...
Good-bye
The card
I should've known there'd be a card for me
Ji-hae?
Oh, hello
Where are you headed?
To the library
That far?
It's not far
I won't get so wet if I stop at each building
Then I'll take you there
With my special umbrella
Think of that building as a shed and run
One, Two, Three!
How are you?
Thanks so much
But you're soaked
I was going to get wet anyway
I should be going
Thanks again
- Okay, I'll see you later
- OK!
I didn't think we'd meet again
But why does the library have to be so close?
She hasn't mailed me back yet
- Joo-hee?
- Yeah
- Why not?
- I don't know
I'm not the type to fall in love with one girl
But I must really like her
Tae-soo!
Tae-soo?
Hi
What are you doing here?
I was waiting for you
Please take these flowers
I like you, Joo-hee
Please write to me
It's so strange
Is it because I'm too tall?
Why do I keep fainting?
I'm out of breath
It's because of Tae-soo, right?
What do you think I should do?
Tell me
Tae-soo is a rotten bastard
No, Tae-soo is nice
He's a rotten bastard because he's too nice
Tae-soo is waiting for your letter
There's no hope
There's nothing we can do for us
Don't say that
There's a way
No, there's nothing more we can do
Nothing
We'll only get hurt
It'll work out
I won't see neither you nor Tae-soo anymore
I'm serious
I won't see anyone
Hey, limousine boy!
Come here
Limousine boy!
Forgot to bow?
So you don't wanna bow
is that it?
If you have a chauffeur you don't have to bow, huh?
Your badge is upside down and your shirt's unbuttoned
Fine, today I'll give you the worst beating ever
I'm gonna beat you all starting from the left
The first one gets hit once the second one gets hit twice
From the third shout out your turn
- Got it?
- Yes, sir
- You sissies, I can't hear you!
- Yes, sir!
Seven
Stay still!
- Ouch, my back
- Stay still, or I'll break your arm
You get one more beating
Get into position!
Listen to what I said and get into position!
What's the count?
I said what's the count?
Then I'll tell you
You're nineteen
One
Two
Three!
Hey, get up!
Get up!
Hey, Hey!
What's wrong with you?
It's about Joo-hee
I don't think she likes me
I gave her flowers and even kissed her
but there's no response
You kissed her?
Yeah
When the sun shines on the sea
I think of you
When the dim moonlight is on the spring
Take this and go home
Stay out of the rain
Dummy
Do you want to get electrocuted?
You're crazy
I don't want to split up like this
Let's talk just for a moment
Nothing can change
There's no use in talking
Let go of me!
Here's your letter
I don't want it anymore
Why?
There's no response and because of my conscience
I'll write it myself from now on
And tell her the truth
It's a golden opportunity
I heard she's very sick from the rain
So she's in the hospital
She's very sick?
Because of the rain?
Yeah
I'm going to see her
If I visit her when she's sick then I can score
I'll confess to her that I didn't write the letters
I won't tell her it was you
Actually
I'm not the type to like one girl
but I really like her
Oh Joon-ha!
He's calling you
Yes?
Twenty four, twenty seven
Thirty, thirty two...
I have to eat all this?
Look at this
Mawworms, intestinal worms
hookworms, roundworms...
You have everything
What the hell did you eat?
Because of you our class has the most parasites
But sir it wasn't my manure
Then whose was it?
You're the only one who'd have
this many parasites, Eat it now!
YOON Tae-soo
Eat three
But it's the same manure
Yeah, but some spots have more parasites and some don't
How'd you know I was here?
Why are you covering your face?
Stop it, I haven't washed my face, and it's dirty
But you're still pretty
- How'd you know I was here?
- I heard from Tae-soo
Why are you laughing?
I heard you ate 32 worm-killing pills
Tae-soo, that bastard has a big mouth
Did he say anything else?
After being silent for a while that's all he said and left
- Really?
- Yeah
He's so odd
- Are you very sick?
- Yeah
I'm sorry
I must be really stupid
Besides liking you
I'm not good at anything else
No, there's a lot you're good at
Like getting drenched and eating worm pills
Don't laugh
This is serious
I have to tell Tae-soo about us
Then we can clear our conscience
See you later
Is this her room?
My poor daughter-in-law!
How'd you get so drenched?
No, lie down
A cold can't be taken lightly
You can catch pneumonia
So, are you eating well?
You should eat well to recover
I'm sorry
This must be the wrong room
Wrong room
Clench your fists
Raise them like this
Now hit me
Why should I hit you?
Hurry and hit me!
I don't like hitting people or getting hit
My dad hit me too many times
I like Joo-hee
Actually, she gave me this necklace last summer
Are you okay?
Damn it
I've fallen again
Don't worry
And don't let my dad see that necklace
He'll get furious
That necklace was a gift from my dad
To Joo-hee
Oh Joon-ha!
It's your letter!
Later on, we went on school break
And I thought I couldn't see her again
I miss you
I miss you so much I'll die
And I'm curious how much our river has changed
Say hi to our haunted house
the shed, and our row boat
Say that I miss them and that I'm doing okay
Yesterday, Tae-soo came to me with your Uncle's address
He also confessed a shocking thing to me
That you were the one who wrote the letters to me
How could you hide that from me?
Anyway, it's okay
I almost threw away those letters
but now I can read them again and think of you
Tae-soo also made a suggestion
That you put Tae-soo's name on the letters you send me
Then my parents will think
that I'm exchanging letters with him
Look outside the window
If the branches swing gently in the wind
then the one you love is loving you, too
Right now it's snowing outside
When it first snows
they say you should stroll with your beloved
But I'm just writing a letter
Joon-ha, I miss you so much
I'm going to get permission to go to Grandpa's house
If I do
I'll send you a telegraph
Open your ears
If you hear your heartbeat
then the person you love is loving you, too
Close your eyes
If there's a smile on your lips
then the person you love is loving you, too
I want to send a telegraph
Then please sign up here
Okay
But fate must not be on my side
One of my letters
was returned back to Tae-soo's home
Joo-hee is in love with Joon-ha
I'm not in love with Joo-hee
Both of them really love each other
So that's why I gave up
Two people in love should be together
It's okay with me
No, I love her, too
I won't give up
Are you mocking me?
You always want things your way!
So your parents mean nothing to you?
Do you know who she is?
She's a congressman's daughter!
Know what that means, you punk?
You deserve to die
You can't even hold on to a girl
It was the end of a winter break?
I had hoped so much for
Know what this is?
A belt?
No, it's a whip
This bastard hits me
My dad doesn't want it to
but it keeps wanting to hit me
That's why I caught it
How should I punish it?
The death penalty
That's exactly what I thought
Kill it slowly and painfully?
Or starve it slowly to death?
Or give it sleeping pills?
Strangle it to death
Good idea
Joon-ha
Take good care of Joo-hee
Tae-soo!
Somebody help!
A person's dying!
Tae-soo, you bastard!
Tae-soo, hold on! Hold on!
Someone help me!
Somebody's dying!
Tae-soo! Tae-soo!
I told you to kill the belt
not yourself
Tae-soo, wake up!
Open your eyes!
Don't die. Don't die
Don't die, you bastard!
Breathe! Breathe!
Breathe, you bastard!
Go inside
If you're with him
he'll wake up faster
Hurry
Wait here for me
Hurry and get well