"Written and Directed
by Jackie Chan"
Gong Saang Textile Factory
has immediate openings...
for 250 positions.
Self-motivated young men
are encouraged to apply.
Eight dollars a month,
thirteen-month contract.
First month's salary is
the referral fee.
Pay $2 to apply.
Line up at the register, please.
Must be aggressive
and hard-working.
Agency will take the first
month's pay-- that's too much.
Maintain order, please.
250 positions open.
Two dollars to apply.
A great chance you can't afford to miss.
Apply at the register.
One position open for cashier.
Must be elementary-school graduate.
Twelve dollars a month.
- Referral fee required. Any takers?
- I'll take it.
Come over here.
- What are you good at?
- Kung fu and acrobatics.
Those are useless.
Can you handle math?
I can.
You have any references?
- What about money?
- I sure do.
Good. Thirty dollars.
Your name?
Cheng Wah Kuo, from Canton.
Do I have to pay right now?
Of course.
And the job is yours.
- Say, do you want the job or not?
- I do, but I only have 25.
You can pay me the rest later.
Hold on to this paper and
report to the factory tomorrow.
Hurry! Gong Saang Textile
has 250 job openings.
Hurry before your chance is gone.
See how lucky you are?
Line up over there.
- Thanks.
- Two dollars to apply.
What are you guys doing here?
This is not Gong Saang Textile.
Each of us paid $2
to work here.
Two dollars? We're not hiring.
The address is correct,
but there's no such company.
It's hard to find a job
in Hong Kong.
Please leave.
You were conned.
You'd better leave now
or I'll call the police.
Help! Thief!
- Now what?
- He took us for a ride.
We're lucky.
One fool paid $30 to be a cashier.
- That poor guy.
- Pays to be cautious.
Hong Kong!
Everything is ready.
- Be careful.
- I know.
Are you all right, boss?
You don't look well.
- I can't find his stomach medication.
- What?
How could you forget to bring it?
Morons, all of you!
Who the hell
does he think he is?
Those jerks forgot to bring it.
Let's postpone the meeting.
- No, we can't back down.
- But, boss, the situation--
Maybe we can talk sense with him
if he's a reasonable man.
You talk like an old lady.
In our business,
only the toughest survive.
That's why I like Fei.
He's tough.
My sunglasses.
You're late.
No, you're early.
You don't look well.
Are you okay?
Just get to the point.
Why did you want
to meet with me?
Good! Let's get to the point.
- Pai, remember your old partner Yang?
- Yes, but he's dead.
He owed me some money...
so he promised to give me
his partnership in the Ritz.
He might have, but I didn't.
Calm down.
No need to get angry.
Are you here to talk or not?
I came to tell you...
no one makes bargains with me!
You set me up?
Screw you!
Fire!
- Are you all right, boss?
- We'll cover you.
Buy your hot dumplings here!
Care to buy a flower, sir?
No, thanks.
Don't be too quick
to turn me away.
I'm not buying.
My rose will bring you luck.
First time here?
Yes.
- Be careful.
- After yesterday, I sure will.
Obviously, you're not careful enough.
Look at your luggage.
You need to be more careful, sir.
Wait a minute.
I'll buy a rose.
It will bring you good luck
from now on.
I hope so.
Thank you.
Watch out!
Let me help you.
Go away.
What do we do now?
Hold it right there!
- Don't shoot! I'm here to help.
- Thank you, young man.
Don't move.
Let's get going.
Boss, are you all right?
- What happened?
- Young man, give us a hand.
Who are you guys?
- I'll give you $100. Do it.
- One hundred dollars?
Hurry! This way.
- Where should I take him?
- Just get him out of here.
Go now.
Which way?
You're killing me.
Put me down.
Put him down.
Boss, are you okay?
My stomach! You're not helping.
- Over here.
- Keep a lookout.
Boss, how's your stomach?
Boss, are you all right?
Who should be your successor
if anything happens?
He-- Oh, my stomach--
Him?
- What?
- Boss, you really choose him?
I meant he--
Boss!
You all heard him.
We must obey his order.
It's not safe to stay here.
Boss, we'd better get going.
- From now on, you're the new boss.
- Me?
You're really fortunate
to be named boss.
I've spent all night trying to explain,
but you still don't get it.
See, you have fancy clothes now.
The way you make your living
is quite dangerous.
If it were safe,
I would take the job.
- What did you say?
- Nothing. Just do as I tell you.
Fei, the boss always called you
his right-hand man.
You could be the new boss.
If he didn't name me
his successor...
that means I'm disqualified.
Fei, you're the man.
But he's a nobody, isn't he?
- Right. Let's wait and see.
- Sure.
Sir, can you spare some change?
Take the money and leave.
Thank you, sir.
Make sure the coast is clear.
We'll enter from the back.
What if there's nothing happening?
Then you can polish the car.
How about buying a rose, sir?
- Beat it. Leave us alone.
- Let's go.
I'd like to buy a rose.
Wait.
I'll buy a rose.
Good luck to you.
- Thank you for your kindness.
- Go now.
We'd better get going, boss.
Why isn't Fei the new leader?
- You want to work for him?
- What about you?
Anyone is okaywith me,
except him.
Even you could be
the new boss.
We're in the majority.
That gives us the upper hand.
Fists are more powerful than words.
Let's fight it out.
I can't do this.
Don't make me do this.
We can't make you do it.
Take the back door and leave.
- Thank you.
- But you must be careful.
Why?
We won't protect you
if you're not our boss.
And if Tiger gets you,
you'll be in big trouble.
Why does Tiger have to pick on me?
I helped your boss--
Just why did you want
to help him?
I don't want to know
what there was between you two.
But I must obey his orders.
So whether I agree to be boss or not,
I'll be dead anyway.
Don't worry.
I'll help you.
See, you look like our late boss.
Just read this paper.
Let's go.
Teach him a lesson.
Don't be scared.
Guys, you all know that
Cheng Wah Kuo is our new boss.
Say something.
My dear brothers.
My dear brothers--
Can't you speak
without looking at the paper?
Honestly, I really don't know
how to be your boss.
If you ask me, I'll tell you no more
robberies or other crimes.
No shady deals,
no illegal operations.
Our new boss has
quite a sense of humor.
You need more than a sense of humor
to be our boss.
He has to really have something.
That's right.
Go arm wrestle with him, Tung.
- Me?
- Yeah. Arm wrestle with him.
- No problem. Ken, go with him.
- Sure.
Go.
Fatty, you'll be the referee.
Give us some room.
Ready? One, two, three.
Who burned me?
Gosh!
He's even stronger than Tung.
Great job, boss.
You're the best.
Seriously, someone
played a trick on me.
If it was about arm wresting, then Tung
should have been boss years ago.
Our business requires
fighting skills.
Yes.
Then you fight him.
You're on your own this time.
Let's both take him at once.
I believe you can handle
both of us at the same time.
Help!
Get him up.
Boss.
Our boss is the best.
He's the best.
Where's my letter?
And the hotel stationery?
Here.
Be careful with it.
The manager is watching.
He'll fire me if he finds out.
He won't. Take this rose.
It'll bring you luck.
At the gardenparty today...
Mr. Chow, the host,
asked about you.
Then I received your letter.
You said
Yen treats you very well.
I'm so happy for you.
He must be a handsome young man.
When your stepfather has time...
heand I wouldlike
to visit you and Yen in Shanghai.
We have to go to the dinner banquet
at the Indian consulate tonight.
I'm sure the main dish
will be chicken curry.
I'm sending you more money
this month.
I know you need more
because you're a big girl now.
The weather is getting cooler.
Take good care of yourself.
The chauffeur is waiting.
We have to go now.
I'll stop writing now.
"Mother"
This balance sheet is a mess.
The figures have been doctored.
What's going on?
You don't know Tiger.
Yang was framed by his plan.
I was trying to stop him
and protect our rights to the Ritz.
Can't we stay out
of such business?
You're the boss.
I'll do whatever you say.
Our guys will agree
as long as they can make a living.
Do you know some way to make
the restaurant more profitable?
I'll never run a casino.
How about a strip club?
Uncle Hai, a Miss Yang
wants to see you.
Miss Yang, this is Uncle Hai.
I'm Luming.
My father was the co-owner
of this restaurant.
You are Miss Yang?
I heard your father died in Shanghai.
Yes. That's why I've come:
because of my father's debt to you.
This is our new manager, Wah.
Before my father passed away,
he said he lost all the Ritz's shares...
and I should pay the money
back to you.
It's okay. Don't worry.
He meant you can pay us back
whenever you have the money.
I have a couple dollars on me.
Your father owed us
a couple thousand dollars.
- I could work for you for free.
- What can you do?
I was a performer
in a Shanghai nightclub.
Why did you quit the job?
The nightclub was closed down,
but it wasn't my fault.
Let me sing for you.
Hong Kong at night
The city that never sleeps
Pearl of the Orient
Listen to the symphony
of waves and tides
- That should be enough.
- Right.
We can open a nightclub
and make her our next hit.
Great idea.
One, two, three, four--
- Hurry up.
- No problem.
Be careful.
How much altogether?
- I am not an accountant.
- Bullshit!
Not here. Over there.
Take it back.
Someone is looking for you,
Uncle Hai.
Mr.Geung. Nice to see you.
I need to talk to you.
Are you remodeling the restaurant,
Mr. Kuo?
- Yes.
- Good luck to you.
Thank you.
Be careful!
- Boss.
- What's your problem?
Why does it take you so long?
Do you know how to write?
I'd be a teacher
if I was good at it.
Are you ready?
Look at the camera.
Okay.
Move it over here.
- Welcome, welcome.
- Step aside.
- Right here.
- Any reservations?
Tiger needs no reservations.
This way, please.
Thank you for coming.
This place looks nice.
This is Cheng Wah Kuo,
our new boss.
Kuo? What was your relationship
with Pai?
I was sure you were
one of his bastard sons.
Luming, hurry up.
What brings you here, Tiger?
I'm not trying to take over
this time.
You spent a lot on this place.
Let's consider what Yang owed me
to have been reinvested.
I am therefore entitled
to half of the Ritz.
Tiger, I think--
- Are you the manager?
- No, he is.
Then you'd better shut up.
We have no responsibility
for Yang's debts.
It cost us a lot, but we're not looking
for outside investors.
Gentlemen, allow me introduce
Miss Yang...
direct from Broadway
in New York City.
Don't test my patience.
Step back. Make way.
Turn on the lights.
This is a search.
Stop the music.
Remain in your seats.
- Turn off the spotlight.
- Bring up the house lights.
My name is Ho, chief inspector
for Hong Kong.
- We're here to check IDs.
- Check them out.
You are disturbing my customers,
Mr. Ho.
- Call me "Inspector"
- We have a business license, Inspector.
And we have a search warrant.
I didn't bring my ID.
Don't bother me.
What did you say?
No identification?
- What's the big deal?
- Prison-- that's the big deal.
How are you, sir?
- How's your supervisor, Mr. Laughton?
- He's fine, thank you.
You don't need to check their ID.
Go check other people.
What are you looking at?
Inspector,
we have a business to run.
I can come to your nightclub
whenever I want...
today, tomorrow,
or the day after tomorrow.
- Are you the owner?
- No. He is.
I'm Cheng Wah Kuo, the manager.
So you're the new boss.
Today is our grand opening.
I apologize for the inconvenience.
You look like a decent businessman.
I'll let you off this time.
But I would like
to have a word with you.
Sure. No problem.
Now what?
That's it for now.
This way, Inspector.
Please, have a seat.
I didn't come here
to have a seat.
- I am here because I found something.
- You found something?
Yes, something
that doesn't belong here.
I think there must be a mistake.
Everything you see here is paid for.
- I'm talking about you.
- Me? I don't belong here?
Look at those people downstairs.
They're nothing but a bunch
of thugs, thiefs and gangsters.
Don't you argue with me.
I think you are
the only one here...
who is a man of his word.
I want to save you
from this den of iniquity.
I want to give you
a special mission.
- Special mission?
- Yes.
From now on--
If you inform me
of all their criminal activities...
then I can put them behind bars.
You and I could become the greatest
crime fighters in Hong Kong's history.
I'm going to catch
every last one of them.
I do hope
you won't be among them.
- Actually, I've been thinking about--
- You don't have to answer me now.
Think it over
and give me a call.
I have confidence in you.
Don't let me down.
I brought you two some tea, boss.
Thank you,
but I was about to leave.
What did he tell you?
Excuse me. I forgot my hat.
Carry on.
- What did he tell you?
- He said I'd better watch out.
No way. He thinks you are the only one
here who is a man of his word.
Did he give you
a special mission?
- No.
- I don't believe it.
Did he ask you to be his partner
and fight crime with him?
Did he say he has confidence in you
and you shouldn't let him down?
- How do you know everything he said?
- It's not just me. Everybody knows.
Even the doorman knows.
Let's go.
Sorry for the interruption.
The show will begin right away.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome Miss Yang.
Rose, Rose, I love you
with an aching heart
What is your future
Now we have to part
Standing on the jetty
as the steamer moves away
Flower of Malaya
I cannot stay
With an acting heart
Make way, oh, make way
For my eastern Rose
Men crowded in dozens
Everywhere she goes
In her rickshaw on the street
or in the cabaret
Please make way for Rose
You can hear them say
All my life I shall remember
Oriental music
and you in my arms
Perfumed flowers in your traces
Lotus-scented breezes
and swaying palms
With your almonde yes
Fragrant and slender
Beneath tropical skies
I must cross the seas again
And never see you more
Way back to my home
on a distant shore
My ship is in the bay
Kiss me farewell now
There's nothing to say
East is East and West is West
Our worlds are far apart
I must leave you now
But with you
I leave my heart
Good.
Tell your boss that
I want to meet with him.
We should each mind
his own business.
Then we can forget about the past
and start all over.
No one is more open-minded
than you, Tiger.
I would take your offer
if I were him.
Kuo is young and impetuous.
Uncle Hai is the real trouble.
- Just bring the message to him.
- I'd better get going.
You've paid off all your debts.
Here's your note.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
- I'm waiting for Tong to bring my rose.
- You won't use it to propose, right?
- Cheng Wah.
- What?
- Do you ever think about the future?
- Of course I do.
Everybody is waiting for you.
We'll talk when I get back.
Anyway, I need three more years.
Three more years?
Don't you know this gang has had
seven bosses in two years?
I can't find Madam Rose.
- Can't you go without the rose?
- That's not exactly it.
- Good. Let's go.
- Get in the car.
Good luck to you.
Thank you, miss.
- It's a beautiful rose.
- Yes, it is.
You guys cover the back alley.
- Rush in as soon as I drop the cup.
- Got it.
- Second floor, please.
- Just a minute.
Please sit down.
Not bad, young man.
Sit, please.
Waiter!
I have no time for your stories.
Since you're here,
I'm determined to get my share.
Young man...
sign here and you can go home
in one piece.
Half of the Ritz?
I don't care
what you think of us.
Just sign here
and we'll be partners.
We'll work together.
Okay?
- But we--
- Who the hell are you?
Do you sign the contracts?
If not, shut up!
I'll sign.
Now you finally get it.
But one more clause
needs to be added in.
We're entitled to half of your income
from casinos and banks too.
What did you just say,
young man?
Say that again.
Say it.
You want half of the Ritz,
and we want half of your income.
Damn you!
Don't move!
Morons. We outnumber them
ten to one...
and you guys can't catch him
without your guns.
Put your guns away
or I'll kill you.
I'll see you outside, young man--
if you make it!
Kill me if you dare.
You old bastard.
Our boss is in trouble.
You're good, young man.
Pick him up.
Don't push me.
Let's go.
Don't push.
I'll go myself.
Hurry up. Move it!
Hurry!
Sign the paper
and I'll let him go.
Let's go.
Police.
Is the fight over already?
Too bad I missed it.
What did you say, Inspector?
So it's you, Mr. Tiger.
Was there a fight here?
I don't understand your Mandarin.
Speak Cantonese.
Cantonese?
I heard there was a fight here.
Were you involved?
A fight?
I didn't see anything.
- Nothing happened?
- No.
And you saw nothing either?
Do you have anything to say?
We were having lunch together.
Now lunch is over.
- See you some other day.
- No problem.
If you admitted he threatened you,
I could arrest him.
I don't know what
you are talking about, Inspector.
Your luck may run out.
I may show up too late next time.
Now I understand.
Good-bye.
Lunch is over.
Let's get going.
They did fight.
Do you really believe what he said?
I'm not stupid.
Dismiss the men.
Dismissed.
It's because of that inspector,
not the rose.
I'm not going anywhere
without the rose.
Superstition!
Uncle Hai, do we need
to take the car to a body shop?
- Yes, you take care of it.
- That'll be quite expensive.
I suspect Fei is
behind the whole thing.
- You suspect him?
- Don't you?
He's an experienced hand,
and he messed up with no good excuse.
You mean he's up to something.
To stay in this business,
you must remember:
Trust nobody.
I don't like that.
You don't have much choice.
- Do you need this?
- No, I don't.
- Where are you going?
- To America.
- Without telling me?
- Tell you?
We never have time to talk.
You only have time for business.
A vacation there
will do you good.
I'm not coming back.
How come?
- I'm going to get married.
- I told you the time isn't right.
Married? To whom?
To Mr. Lu. His parents are
very excited about this marriage.
Ask someone else to wait
another three years.
- You can't go like this.
- Why should I care?
Don't go.
Listen to me!
- You ruined my dress.
- Help me!
It's none of my business.
Carry on.
- You can't go. What about us?
- You never have time for me.
What do you think I am,
a money tree?
No, of course not.
Say, what do you think she is?
- What do I think who is?
- She was asking us a question.
- A money tree, of course.
- See? Don't deny it.
He's lying.
Don't believe him.
Yeah, I lied.
What exactly do you want me to say?
Keep your mouth shut.
You know how much I care about you.
- How much you care about me?
- You know how much I care for her.
I really don't know.
My hearing is bad.
You're not helping at all.
Don't go, please.
Are you really giving up
everything and leaving, Luming?
It's now or never.
I don't want to see you get killed.
- God forbid!
- Aren't I right?
No, I heard it wrong.
It's none of my business. Go on.
None of your business?
She wants to leave.
Then that'll become my business.
Talk her out of it.
- Luming, how about two more years?
- Do you think I'm gonna buy that?
- I really mean it. I swear.
- Save it. Don't stop me.
Let go!
I'm begging you to stay, Luming.
You deceived me.
No, that's not true.
I paid off my father's debts, and he
didn't really even owe you anything!
How can you do this to me?
I worked so hard for you.
- I told him not to cheat you.
- I don't remember you saying that.
See, he's telling the truth.
We did deceive you at first
when you were a stranger to us.
Later, I didn't know
how to tell you the truth.
I never touched that money.
It's yours.
So you cheated me
because he told you to.
- I didn't know you then.
- But you know how to shift the blame.
Shut up, you!
Forget about the money.
I just want to leave.
- Listen to me.
- Let me go!
Listen to me.
Boss.
Mr. Lu would like to know
when you are leaving, Miss Yang.
What business is that of yours?
- The car battery is dead.
- Ask him to leave.
- But the battery is dead.
- Right.
- We might have to do a push start.
- Tell Lu to get lost.
- Tell that guy to leave!
- Tell him to leave! Sure, sure.
- Can't you make your own decisions?
- If someone gives me a hint, yeah.
- Luming!
- Let go of me.
I won't let you go, Luming.
Please don't go.
Give me one good reason.
Reason? What's a good reason?
We don't act based on reason.
Would you stop drinking?
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
I'm really sorry.
He won't leave
without saying good-bye to her.
What should I do now?
Gun him down.
Run him off.
- Help me get up.
- Please don't leave.
You can't hold her here
like a thief.
Kiss her and she'll stay.
- Kiss her?
- Why don't you take his advice now?
I will, I will.
Now leave!
I'll go polish the car.
Don't touch me!
I am sorry, Luming.
Why are you carrying luggage?
Are you going on vacation?
My manager fired me.
He thought I was stealing guests'
letters and giving them to you.
- Where's the letter?
- The manager took it.
- Excuse me.
- She wants to see you.
How may I help you?
There's a letter from Shanghai
addressed to Madam Kao. It's for me.
For you?
But you're not a guest here.
How come there's a letter for you?
I used your letterhead and envelope.
Throw her out.
That letter
is very important to me.
I must have it.
Please give it to me.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have used your letterhead.
I'll never do it again.
Calm down, calm down.
Is there a letter for her?
There was,
but I returned it.
No, that letter
mustn't be returned.
The boy is about to send them out.
- Madam!
- My letter!
What's going on here?
Go back to your work.
- Everything is okay.
- I found it.
Thank you.
- Everything is fine.
- Thank you.
I'll let you take care of it.
I am going out for dim sum.
We'll meet at the restaurant
with some local businessmen.
No problem,
but I can't speak for my boss.
He doesn't seem to be
a bad guy to me.
Trust me.
I know him better than you do.
The Cantonese are too cunning
to be trusted.
And where are you from?
Well, Canton.
But I'm very trustworthy.
Remember,
dim sum in the morning.
I'd better go now.
People like him can never be trusted,
no matter where they come from.
I'll say it once more:
The big shot you're about to meet
used to be a coolie.
Now he has hundreds of coolies himself,
and he has influence over the pier.
But don't be humble
before him.
I know.
The coolies work for us too.
Are you going out for business?
The Black Dragon gang is powerful.
They've invited me over for dinner.
Don't look at him
when I'm talking to him.
- Boss, I got your chrysanthe mum.
- Are you new here or what?
- But a chrysanthe mum is a flower too.
- Get out and polish the car.
But a chrysanthe mum
is a flower too.
Hurry up. We're out of time.
Forget about the rose.
Don't be so superstitious.
Let's go.
No. I'm not going
without my rose.
I know you're looking at her.
It's good you can make
your own decisions.
- We can't find Madam Rose.
- I was told she was sick.
Sick?
Mr. Kuo, this way please.
Hey, he's here!
Mr. Kuo.
This way.
Okay, here's the flower.
Let's get going.
I'm here for your flower.
Are you all right?
Drink this.
- Does she have a fever?
- No, she's cool to the touch.
She doesn't have the flu.
That's not the right remedy.
Who cares? Just get the rose.
He needs it for luck.
Do you ever think of others?
She needs help.
How can you be so coldhearted?
Go get a doctor. Hurry!
Even a doctor couldn't help her now.
She's in shock.
Tell me who did it
and he's dead.
Tell me what's going on.
Maybe I can help.
- Is it because of her?
- Who is she?
It's her daughter.
I don't believe it.
They don't look alike.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean it.
It's okay.
Don't cry.
I got it.
Her daughter's dead!
Shut your mouth!
Go polish the car.
- We're out of time.
- How can we leave now?
They'll be offended
if we show up late.
- Let me buy the rose first.
- Then what are you waiting for?
Mr. Kuo, this is for you.
Good luck to you.
And good luck to everybody.
You should be proud
to have such a beautiful daughter.
Did she do something wrong?
Where is she?
- Is there anything I can do to help?
- She goes to school in Shanghai.
All of a sudden, she's decided
to come visit her mother.
- Does she need money for the ticket?
- I'll pay for her.
Her boyfriend and his father
are coming with her.
She's planning to marry
her boyfriend.
Madam Rose never told her daughter
how she makes her living.
She used the flower money
to send her to college.
Madam Rose didn't want her
to worry about money...
so she told her that she is
wealthy and famous in Hong Kong.
So if the daughter finds out the truth,
she will be very disappointed.
And if the father and son find out,
there will be no marriage.
- Why are you looking at me?
- You're the only one who can help.
The only one.
Of course you should help her.
Her rose always brings you good luck.
- How can I help?
- It's simple.
Move her to the best hotel
and dress her up.
Easier said than done.
That takes money.
We raised some money for her.
Here it is,
but it may not be enough.
It's okay.
Don't worry about the money.
Just do whatever you think is right.
I'm behind you all the way.
Wonderful!
I have to leave.
- Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
- I can't thank you enough.
- I'll leave it to you.
- Thank you.
See you.
- It's gonna be trouble.
- It'll be easy. I'm glad we can help.
Easy?
This way.
- Miss Yang, everything's ready.
- Take care of Madam Kao.
Madam Kao, please.
This is nice.
Turn on the lights.
How do you like it, Miss Yang?
Say "yes" if asked
If it's Madam's suite...
but say "I don't know"
if asked anything about her.
This will be your home,
Madam Kao.
Cheng Wah, over here.
- What do you think?
- It's wonderful.
Money talks.
I really don't know how to thank you
for your kindness and generosity.
- He loves to help people. Right?
- Right.
- They're here.
- Come on in.
This way.
- Who are they?
- Makeup artist, tailor, hairdresser.
They're all here for you.
We have to give you a makeover.
The tea is ready.
- Who is he?
- The housekeeper.
- Housekeeper?
- Mr. Kuo.
Madam Kao has to have
a housekeeper.
- Uncle Hai, we're leaving.
- Thank you.
- I'll let you take care of everything.
- No problem.
- Now what?
- She needs a husband.
- A what?
- The one she mentions in her letters.
- So what?
- Get her a husband.
You want me to get her
a husband?
- Where? How?
- How should I know?
And you said it would be easy.
A husband!
Don't even think about it.
Where do you want me
to find a husband for her?
I have the perfect candidate.
- Who?
- A friend of mine.
- What does he look like?
- Who cares? Just bring him over.
Okay.
Don't you go anywhere.
I don't care what the job is,
as long as they pay me.
Follow me.
I'll sign anything
if I can just live here.
Mr. Kuo,
this is my friend Tung.
From now on,
he's your boss.
Mr. Cheng Wah Kuo.
Have we met before?
I don't think so.
Say hello to Mr. Kuo.
Mr. Kuo, how do you do?
I believe I've seen you before.
That's impossible.
Thanks for your help.
Gentlemen, Madam Kao.
This is the bride-to-be.
Don't be afraid. Relax.
Mr. Kuo.
Aren't you going
to introduce me?
Miss Yang,
this is Tung, the groom-to-be.
You? Come over here
and stand next to her.
- Yeah, you look all right.
- I'll look even better in a nice suit.
Are you done with your part?
Luming, may I go now?
- Yes, you may.
- Finally.
You go on ahead.
Let's go.
- Wait! Hold it right there.
- There's more?
We're going to pick up
her daughter tomorrow.
I don't have to be there.
You can go without me.
Let's not do things halfway.
All right.
- Okay, you can go now.
- Let's talk over here.
What are you staring at?
That's Madam Rose.
I remember now!
I know who you are.
Let bygones be bygones.
I am the groom-to-be.
- What's the deal?
- Nothing.
What's the matter?
I saved him once.
It was a long time ago.
Let's have some tea.
The ship has docked, boss.
Hurry up.
We found a really good spot.
What will Belle think
when she sees me?
She'll be delighted.
- Thank you for everything.
- Don't mention it.
The ship has arrived.
The ship is here?
How about our sign?
- Why is it so small?
- Easier to carry it in my pocket.
- How about not bringing it at all?
- You are late!
- I was busy with work.
- There's a bigger banner there.
- Someone else is here for them too.
- We're here to pick up the same group.
We can't let them pick up
Belle's boyfriend and his father.
They'll discover Madam Kao doesn't
exist, and our plan will be ruined.
- What should we do now?
- What do you think?
- You have to stop them.
- Get rid of them.
Hey, you bumped into me.
Remember,
he's an old friend of my teacher.
You'd better behave yourself.
- I couldn't make him leave.
- Why?
It's that inspector.
You take care of it.
Inspector, I've got something
to tell you.
Don't you want to know
what Tiger's up to?
- What is he up to?
- Not here. Let's go some place else.
- No, I'm here to pick up my friends.
- This information can't wait.
Then tell me now.
- I told you: not here.
- Keep your voice down.
All right, then.
- Did you take care of it?
- Don't worry. Leave it to me.
You two, come with me.
Thief!
Help!
Ignore them.
Hold the banner.
It's none of our business.
What a coincidence!
How's your kid?
- Fine. What are you doing here?
- Looking for a fight.
- Did you send the money to Mom?
- I did.
She insisted she didn't get it!
- Go over there and kill him.
- It's ridiculous.
It's not our business.
Hold the banner. Higher.
Who's Inspector Ho?
- That's me.
- So it's you.
You piece of shit!
- Why are you standing here?
- To pick up your friends.
Pick up your brains!
Go and get him!
You're not getting away.
- Do you see her?
- No.
Can you identify her?
There are so many people.
I can't.
I've only seen her picture once.
- Do you see her?
- Not yet.
Do you see her?
Belle.
- Belle!
- Ma!
That's my Belle!
Belle.
I see my mother.
She's down there.
Let's get off the ship.
- Which one is she?
- I'm not sure.
My daughter is back.
Belle!
- Which one is she?
- I'm not sure.
- Do you know which one she is?
- No.
Do you see her?
Mr. Ku is one of the richest men
in the country.
Take more pictures.
- Who are they?
- Reporters.
What's going on?
Two reporters are here
to interview Ku.
Reporters?
Tie them up.
It's against the law.
Let's get moving.
- We're detectives.
- What are you doing here?
We're reporters,
here to interview Mr. Ku.
- I'd like to have a word with you.
- But the passengers are arriving.
Or maybe you prefer
a nice long vacation?
- Let's go.
- What are you doing?
- Do I look all right?
- Sure. You look great.
You've done a good thing.
It's not over yet.
This is your stepfather.
Dad.
- Why don't you introduce your friends?
- Of course.
Mr. Hsin Chuan Ku.
- Mr. Ku, I've heard so much about you.
- My son.
How are you?
Thank you
for taking care of Belle.
Actually, it's she
who takes care of me.
It's so noisy here.
Why don't we get back to the hotel?
This is--
This is her cousin.
- Right, right.
- An uncle on her mother's side.
Uncle.
- This is my wife.
- Auntie.
Ma, you never mentioned
this cousin.
His business dealings
are a little shady...
so the family doesn't talk
about him too much.
Let's go to the hotel, Mr. Ku.
My other friends
have come to see me too.
Don't worry. I've told ever yone
to meet you at the hotel.
How's that sound?
Let's get going.
- Uncle?
- How come they didn't introduce me?
I'll go get the car.
Not getting a raise
could make an employee depressed.
Depression could lead to suicide.
Suicide means disappearance.
It's all connected.
The two missing reporters
are my assistants.
I am a good friend
of your boss, Mr. Laughton.
Your stupid questions may also lead
to your unemployment.
Sorry. I was only asking
routine questions.
Trying to put pressure on me!
I've got work to do.
Miss Yang.
You're going to meet the fishermen
who sell their fish on the pier.
It's so hot!
Let me tell you something.
You should see how happy they are.
- They tell us--
- By the way...
can you ask Tong
to drive us around tomorrow?
- You can ask him yourself.
- He's your man. You ask him.
Have you finished?
- They hope we'll go easy on them.
- But we've never been hard on them.
Tong, I don't need you tomorrow.
You take Mr. Ku sightseeing.
And sit in traffic all day?
Can't I do something else with them?
Whatever you want.
Just keep them out of sight.
Have you finished or not?
Let's get down to business.
- Call Inspector Ho for me.
- Certainly.
Tomorrow we'll go
to the park first.
Then the government house.
Bring the camera.
We'll have seafood for lunch,
then go to the shrine after that.
Could you please stand in one place?
You're making me dizzy.
I'll do as I please!
Do you remember what I said?
The fishermen have invited us over
for lunch to show their appreciation.
Mr. Kuo, please.
Boss, telephone for you.
My shoe is not an ashtray!
This is Chow. Mr. Ku wants me
to get Inspector Ho for him.
The inspector? Now I have to find
a stand-in for the inspector too?
What's the matter?
You were gonna take care of everything.
Now we need to find an inspector too!
Did the call go through?
Yes.
- Hello.
What?
All taken care of.
I'll go polish the car.
Is it in fashion now
to hire a Philippine maid?
- It's a new fad.
- Bring us some tea.
It's hard to find
a Philippine maid.
- This cut isn't big enough.
- How come they get a bigger share?
Fei, you put up with it out of loyalty,
but we can't.
You've been good to us
for so many years.
- We won't forget it, right?
- Right.
You have our full support.
Just say the word.
Thank you for having faith in me.
Trust me and be patient.
Good days are yet to come.
Let's go.
Where's Ming?
He left early
without saying a word.
- Have you found Mr. Ku?
- Still looking.
- Who are you calling?
- My cousin at the shipping company.
I asked him to check
the passenger list for me.
Inspector?
- Where have you been?
- Five Continents Hotel, Luk Kwok Hotel--
I told you to look for Mr. Ku.
Is he at Five Continents or Luk Kwok?
- Neither.
- Then why did you go there?
But I found out
he's at King's Hotel.
Then why did you go
to those other places?
- I found it! I found it!
- Found what?
Ku is in Hong Kong.
I'll check the hotel.
Who told you to check on Ku?
Check on the two missing reporters.
Why do I have to do everything?
I never tell a lie.
Now I'm so afraid.
We must not disappoint them.
We're more than an hour late.
Tiger says it's a firm date.
- Is this going to be a trick?
- We'll keep our eyes open.
All right.
I'll go buy a rose.
Let's go.
Boss, we've kept Tiger waiting
the whole morning.
I know.
Invite him for lunch.
He won't accept.
He wants to see you right away.
But I must buy a rose first.
- Let's get going.
- Boss.
- Tiger's men are here.
- Who the hell do they think they are?
- What's up?
- Our boss has been waiting for you.
- Tell him I invite him to dinner.
- Don't move!
- You have to come with me.
Come on, this is our turf.
Uncle Hai.
I'll go with them.
Tell our men to--
How dare you threaten us with a gun!
Tie them up.
Let me go!
I'll go see your boss
after I get my rose. Let's go.
My boss won't let you go
that easy!
Mr. Ku, do you plan
to issue stock here?
Yes.
- When will that be?
- It will be soon.
You are--
We're here to see Mr. Ku.
We're his friends.
He's not here right now.
Not here? But the front desk
told us he hasn't gone out.
He doesn't want to be interrupted
while having breakfast.
- We're not just his friends.
- We're his business associates.
Mr. Kuo,
they are here to see Mr. Ku.
- What should I do?
- You got yourself in this mess.
Come with me.
- That's kidnapping.
- Just close the door.
Do you have any idea
how many people you've kidnapped?
So you have a steel plant too?
- Morning.
You're up early.
- How's everything, Mr. Ku?
- How should it be? This place is great!
- Mr. Ku says he's having a good time.
- Is everything all right, cousins?
Everything is great!
The flowers are beautiful.
Good luck to you.
What's that for?
This is our family tradition.
- Yes, tradition.
- Family tradition?
Wait for me!
The inspector
is here with two men.
There's an important phone call
for you, Mr. Kuo.
Excuse me for a moment.
Inspector Ho is here.
He's coming up.
Now what?
Cousin!
That's you.
You forgot we have
a business appointment.
- Business appointment?
- They called to remind you.
I totally forgot.
Make yourselves at home.
He's always busy like this.
Get a suit for him.
- The inspector is here.
- Inspector Ho?
Over there.
Take this.
Hold this.
Go with him. Hurry!
Mr. Ku.
I'll be back very soon.
You must be Mr. Ku.
And you must be
Inspector Ho.
Your humble servant, Mr. Ku.
Why didn't you meet me at the boat?
You must have been really busy.
I went, but something came up.
I'll explain later.
I'm leaving.
Let's talk outside.
- I'll be back later.
- Very good.
Who are these men?
My assistants.
You two keep an eye
on the door.
That was close.
Tiger is up to something
and you're busy with this nonsense.
I'm tired of this farce.
You teach me how to dress,
how to walk, how to talk...
how to deal with other bosses,
how to get the job done.
I'm nothing but your puppet.
I'm tired of it!
I'll go polish the car.
- All those things are part of your job.
- That's what you say!
- Then what do you want to do?
- What I'm doing right now.
- Are you happy with what you're doing?
- Yes, I'm very happy!
All right, then-- keep doing it.
I will! I certainly will!
But I don't really know
what I'm doing right now!
The imported goods here
are great.
Do you have
any Hong Kong dollars?
- I'm waiting for money to be wired.
- I can lend you some money.
When will your stock be issued?
Very soon.
Backed by a gold mine.
The stock is strong.
And a shipyard and a steel plant.
Why don't you do your jobs
and go find the missing reporters?
How much a share?
One dollar.
$2.80 after it goes public.
- More than double?
- Outsiders are not allowed to buy.
Will I be able to buy, Mr. Ku?
Aren't you an outsider?
We have mutual friends.
Ho, Chairman of the Police Club
Organizing Committee.
That's the police clubhouse.
I'm the fund-raiser.
You not only have
to enforce the law...
but you also have
to run the police benefit.
Good man!
Thank you.
- Are you all right?
- Just heaving a sigh.
Sighing won't change things.
I'm sighing because the clubhouse
needs $80,000...
but I've only raised $15,000
in three years.
You're only $65,000
short of your target.
After the stock public offering,
I'll try to help.
Mr. Ku-- Sorry.
I was sure I'd found the right person.
Your word is all I need.
Careful, don't get too excited.
My son will treat Belle well.
How could I say no to you?
Thank you for your time.
It's nothing.
Write down how much I owe you.
I'll pay you back.
Consider it a deposit.
Deposit?
You promised
to sell me the stock.
Of course.
Take these to my room.
Should we sign the contract
in your room?
No, I'll meet you at your office
tomorrow. I'll have the stock then.
- You should go now.
- Okay.
I'll walk you back
to your room, Mr. Ku.
- You don't have to.
- I insist.
I feel like having
a cup of coffee.
I'll buy.
Fine.
- Don't you want some coffee?
- I feel like going back to my room.
- Why don't you call your office?
- Call the office?
To see if anything has happened.
- Don't worry. Nothing ever happens.
- Call or I'll feel guilty.
- Don't feel guilty. I'll call.
- I'll wait here.
- I'm going to the ladies' room.
- Shall I go with you?
It's okay.
Your mother is waiting for you.
- Why did you bring him here?
- He doesn't want to leave.
- Get rid of him.
- I'll do my best.
Are you leaving, Luming?
- What's up?
- Inspector Ho is here. Get rid of him.
I'll be back soon.
Kwong On Bank, please.
- Sir, what are you doing here?
- Just looking at the lights.
Inspector.
- Why are you here?
- Two gangs are up to something outside.
- Can't you see I'm busy?
- You're a detective-- do something.
I don't need you to remind me
of my duty.
Is this Kwong On Bank-- Go away!
Sorry, I didn't mean you.
Are you waiting for someone?
Why don't you join us?
- Did you finish your business?
- Why did you bring them here?
Try to come up with something.
I have something to tell you.
Where's Cheng Wah?
- He went to the rest room.
- What is it?
I can't leave yet.
- Sit down and we'll talk about it.
- I don't have time to sit.
It will go public within three months?
Not many people will be able to buy it?
Thank you for the information.
Good-bye.
Excuse me.
Just a second.
What is it?
- Is Mr. Ku staying here?
- Yes.
- Is he--
- Over there.
- Is that your friend?
- Yes, he's a business client.
I'm gonna be rich!
Mr. Kao has such a short workday--
he must be doing well!
- Sit down and have some coffee.
- I think I have another appointment.
- How's your eye, Inspector?
- Who are you?
- I gave you the black eye.
- Are you turning yourself in?
Not exactly. I've come
to take care of your other eye!
I'll get you!
Stop! I'll get you!
- What's the matter?
- It's over. Don't worry.
I think there was a fight.
I have to go.
- Come over for dinner tonight.
- We'll be there. Bye!
Forget about the business.
I'll stay for some coffee. Sit down.
- Be careful. Don't take them out.
- I can't keep them in all day.
You'd better stay here
and keep an eye on them.
- Me again?
- Take them back to their room.
I prefer to stay here
and have lunch with you.
All right.
The press, Mr. Kuo.
- How did they get in?
- Bribed their way in, I guess.
That's why I came to Hong Kong.
- May we take a picture, please?
- No problem.
Cheng Wah, I'm glad you're here.
Come over for a group picture.
Everybody, come over here.
- Dad, let's go take a picture.
- This way, Madam Kao.
Okay.
All together.
Ready. Smile.
Thank you.
It's time for dinner.
- Where are you two from?
- The Daily Sun.
- When will it be published?
- Tomorrow. We'll send a copy over.
Get your rose and go.
- Good luck to you.
- Are you always this busy, Cheng Wah?
- Why do you have to wear a rose?
- It's not superstition.
Aren't you going
to introduce your friend?
Why does he hide behind you?
He's shy. Doesn't talk much.
Excuse me.
Wait a minute, Cheng Wah.
I have something to say.
About what?
Madam Kao has consented
to Belle's wedding.
The ceremonywill take place
in Shanghai.
In Shanghai! Congratulations.
Madam Kao, thank you
for your hospitality...
and your consent
to this marriage.
Don't mention it.
My trip is so short that
I can't meet all the family.
I suggest
an engagement ceremony.
Invite your friends and all
the upper class in Hong Kong.
What do you think, Cheng Wah?
Me? I have no objection.
Then it's settled.
We'll kill two birds
with one ceremony.
Please excuse me, Mr. Ku.
They want to invite all the upper class
in Hong Kong for the ceremony.
I know. You take of it.
You understand
what this means?
A Chinese- or Western-style
ceremony?
The Western is more formal.
The Chinese is more relaxed.
Do you have more Chinese friends
or foreign friends?
About the same number.
I have a lot of friends.
- Let's combine the best of both styles.
- Cousin--
- Cousin.
- That's you.
Excuse me.
Shall we discuss the guest list?
- You too, Luming.
- We'll talk about it later.
- Excuse us.
- It's okay.
We'll be right back.
Madam Kao,
any other ideas?
How many foreign friends
do you have?
Listen, the two of you:
How are we going to do this?
How can we get all the notables
in Hong Kong to attend the ceremony?
You seem to be able
to do anything!
I'm touched
by your profound faith in me!
Why don't they have it in Shanghai?
Why does he have to throw a party here?
It's all your fault!
You said it would be easy.
A few clothes, some makeup,
a hotel suite -- that's all!
But it's one thing after another!
Kidnapping reporters and businessmen.
Beating up police.
- Getting me into trouble.
- But you said you were happy.
Shut up!
It was your idea--
you take care of it!
Isn't it a little late to blame me?
You wanted to help her too.
- Helping people is a pleasure.
- That's right.
But one must act
according to one's ability.
- Don't you dare insult me.
- It's not your fault. It's mine.
- It doesn't matter whose fault it is.
- Wrong!
I have too much compassion,
but no ability.
Trying to work a miracle
for Madam Rose.
You're right.
I don't measure up.
Please tell her
we've done our best.
Now there's nothing I can do.
Right now?
- Do you have a better time in mind?
- The marriage will be ruined.
- Let's pretend we never tried to help!
- You can't back down now.
Yes, I'm backing down.
I won't tell her that.
I can't do it.
- Are you going to tell her or not?
- No.
I'll do it myself!
Uncle.
Auntie, Dad.
- I hope we're not interrupting.
- Not at all.
- What's up?
- Ma says you always help people.
You have a big heart, so--
We decided to make you
godfather of our first baby.
Godfather?
You won't refuse, will you?
Don't let us hold you up.
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, Uncle.
Godfather! What an idea!
Get all our men and their girlfriends
to pose as celebrities.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Is that a bad idea?
No, it's a good idea,
but they won't look like celebrities.
- Get them fancy clothes.
- I'll teach them some manners.
- I'll help the ladies with their makeup.
- Let's get to it. I'll make some calls.
- Do you know what you're doing?
- Of course I know.
What is it?
- He tried to give us the slip.
- Why?
I can't handle it.
I want to go back to my hometown.
And just how would you go?
By boat or train.
How about in a wheelchair?
I'm not going.
I have work to do.
Let's get to work.
Read the card first.
It states your role.
This is yours. Remember it.
This is yours.
Be gentle.
I may be pregnant.
I have to be careful with the baby.
You don't even know
who the father is.
- Don't move.
- Watch your language.
You are supposed to be ladies.
Keep that in mind.
She's got a filthy mouth.
You ate too much.
Look at your waist.
Take a deep breath.
What are you looking at?
Never seen a woman before?
Remember your lines.
Everybody--
Tong gave each of you
a card....
stating your name
and the lines you are to say.
You must speak Mandarin,
because Mr. Ku is from Shanghai.
You don't need
to say your lines right now...
but you must remember
your role...
and act like
ladies and gentlemen.
Why? He could be ruder
than any of us.
- What role are you playing?
- The secretary of education.
What? You can't be
the secretary of education.
Why not?
Just because.
One look at you
and people will know you're a fraud.
Who's the chiefwarden?
Who's got that card?
You're the warden.
Why didn't you answer?
I didn't know.
I can't read.
You can't read? Jeez!
All right, you be the warden
and you be the secretary.
- You must be crazy.
- What's your problem?
He's bothering me.
Can you behave yourself?
Be a gentleman.
- It was a mistake.
- Bastard! That's my girlfriend.
Keep your hands off her
or I'll kill you.
How dare you hit me!
Stop fighting!
Stop acting like this!
Listen to me carefully.
Look at yourselves.
Aren't you tired
of fighting and killing?
This may be the one time
you can actually do a good deed.
You may not know
why you should help Madam Rose.
Just think about it.
One day your grandchildren
may ask you to name...
one thing you're proud of.
What would your answer be?
You want to tell them
you make your living...
off of extortion, prostitution
and gambling?
This could be the only thing
you'd be proud to tell them about.
- Do you understand?
- No.
Tong.
I'm right here.
I asked you to tell them
not to carry their guns.
I did tell them.
Could you please ask again
and see who's armed?
Who else is carrying a gun?
Could you please
get these guns out of here?
I told you guys
not to bring guns.
Give it to me.
20,000 shares for Ho's clan,
and 10,000 shares for me.
You're a good investor.
Let me give you the stock.
- Don't you want to count the money?
- I trust you.
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
When did the two reporters leave?
I showed them the way
and then went back to work.
- I didn't notice when they left.
- Sign here, please.
Is there anything else, Mr. Ku?
How about the party tonight?
Everything is ready.
Who is he?
Mr. Ku, the Shanghai magnate.
- That's really him?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Ku.
- Thank you very much.
- Don't mention it.
You've shown me around for days
since I came to Hong Kong.
I must repay your hospitality.
How much do I owe you?
It was nothing.
No, no. Here's $2,000 for you.
- So much money.
- Keep it. It's chicken feed to me.
- But it's quite a bundle to you.
- That's right.
Remember, sell the shares
when they've doubled in price.
Don't be too greedy.
Amazing! I can't believe this stack
of paper could be so valuable.
It's only paper.
This is a very popular stock.
Don't tell anyone that
I gave it to you.
Remember, sell the stock
when it's doubled in price.
- I'm leaving.
- All right.
Thirty thousand shares.
Mr. Ku.
The police clubhouse--
No problem.
Fortunately, there's one check left.
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
It's very generous of you.
$80,000.
That's too much.
Just $65,000.
This is my last check.
How about if I send you another check
when I get back to Shanghai?
- Tear this one up.
- Don't. I'll make up the difference.
What?
Where can you find the cash?
There's some cash here
that was seized as evidence.
It's in the evidence room.
I'll get it for you.
Mr. Ku, here's $13,000.
With my $2,000, that's $15,000.
You are so thoughtful.
Thank you on behalf
of the Hos, the police and myself.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
Don't mention it.
Let go.
Until we meet again.
Let me see you off.
You don't have to.
Be careful with the stock.
- Remember: Sell when the price doubles.
- Doubles.
Bye-bye.
How lucky can you get?
Hey, you. Don't go.
Me? What's the matter?
- Don't go.
- Me? What's up?
- Watch him and don't let him go.
- Inspector Ho is my friend.
Friend? Right.
Keep an eye on him.
- Gotta go.
- Inspector Ho.
What have you been doing?
People are still missing,
and you have no clue.
We do have a clue.
We now know no ransom is involved
in the case of the missing reporters.
- How do you know that?
- Because their families--
Inspector. Superintendent.
- Why don't you knock first?
- It's very important.
Our conversation is important too.
We have received
no ransom note.
You idiot! Even the governor
has heard about it!
Find those missing persons
within three days.
Otherwise, one of us gets fired.
Understand?
And damn you, sir.
Have you sent people
to the police commissioner's party?
I took care of it, sir.
You are responsible
for the party's security. Moron!
Why do I have to do everything?
- It's me.
- Why don't you knock?
- I've got something very urgent.
- Urgent?
- Where have you been?
- I went to King's Hotel.
What did I tell you?
To check out the missing persons.
But I found out something about Mr. Ku.
Didn't I tell you to follow my orders?
You never listen.
- Hear me out first.
- You don't respect authority.
- But--
- Why didn't you do as you were told?
- They're jumping all over me.
- I know.
Then why don't you work on that case?
I am about to be fired.
All of you. Nobody respects
my authority around here.
What crime did you commit?
He's charging me
with obstructing traffic.
Obstruction is a capital offense.
Come into my office.
- A capital offense?
- He's crazy.
Any clues
on the missing persons?
None, but I found Mr. Ku--
No clues!
After all this time, no clues?
You're not doing your job.
And your mother expects me
to kick you upstairs!
I'll kick you upstairs, all right!
Speak up.
What about Mr. Ku?
We discovered he is not
one of Shanghai's ten richest men.
He's not one of the richest?
And I suppose you're gonna say you are!
Just tell me who he is.
Bastard!
He's not only
one of Shanghai's richest men...
but also one of the ten
richest men in China.
Good job!
I don't need you to tell me that!
Get out.
I've gotta get out of this job.
- Inspector.
- Can't you knock?
- I need to take a leave.
- Take a leave?
- My mother is sick.
- Is your father sick too?
No.
Get out.
Don't ever come back!
Why the long face? The inspector
gave you a hard time, right?
- I'm going home.
- Be smart like me. Your day will come.
Work harder.
You'll be promoted.
Mr. Ku, you're still here?
Let me see him off.
Escort Mr. Ku back to his hotel.
Be careful.
I'll take him
all the way to his hotel.
Bye-bye, Mr. Ku.
Where are you taking me?
That depends on where
you want to end up.
Inspector.
- Why does nobody bother to knock?
- Sorry, Inspector.
I saw Kuo's men at the Ritz.
They were armed.
Who are they?
They're all on our
"most wanted" list.
Then why did you leave?
Get our men there to arrest them.
- Yes, sir.
- I'll get the warrant.
Why are you standing there?
My hat.
Why isn't anybody moving?
We're going to the Ritz.
- Did he tell the truth?
- Yes.
I've heard their people
are at the Ritz.
- What about those two guys I sent?
- Haven't heard from them.
You should trust me.
Kuo took two of your men.
Why did you do this?
I want to stop the killings.
One, two, three, bow.
Good job.
Let's rehearse.
Luming will be Ku.
Can't you do a better job?
I'm Mr. Ku. And you are?
I'm Foxy,
chairman of the Rotarians.
That's "Folksy,
chairman of the Rotarians."
Foxy.
What language are you speaking?
- Mandarin.
- Stick with Cantonese.
I'm Mr. Ku. And you are?
I am the governor of Hong Kong.
You're not the governor.
You're the minister of transportation.
I want to be the governor.
Why?
That bastard
is police commissioner.
So I have to be governor.
I've got to be governor.
Don't take it so seriously.
I must outrank him.
I'm the governor.
- He demands to be the governor.
- Let him be governor if he wants.
Rehearse them for me
a few more times.
One more time.
Cooperate, please.
Boss, Miss Shun
wants to see you.
One more time.
One, two, three, bow.
This place is surrounded
by police.
- Surrounded?
- Yes.
What is it?
- We're surrounded by the police.
- Police? Why?
I overheard that they're waiting
for a warrant.
That inspector must think
we're having a gang fight.
We can't leave and Madam Rose
is waiting. Time is running out.
They'll find out the whole thing
is made up.
- Oh, no!
- That poor lady.
- What do we do now?
- How should I know?
- What can we do?
- He's the one who makes the decisions.
- You have to come up with something.
- What to do now?
- I'll find Inspector Ho.
- You can't go off without a plan.
I know. But we don't have
much choice here.
I'll go out the back.
Someone is coming.
Why are you two down here?
Get up to the rehearsal.
Tell Uncle Hai I'm going to the station.
I'll contact him when I find Ho.
- Tell him not to go anywhere.
- Okay.
How come you guys
are still here?
- What should we do now?
- Call Fei.
Harder. Push me up there.
My men may be looking for me.
Thanks.
He said he went to get
Inspector Ho.
Is everything ready?
Don't worry.
We know what to do.
Yes? What's up?
They found the bodies
of your men.
Kuo killed them.
He killed my men?
Where is he?
What's he up to?
He went to look
for Inspector Ho.
Why is he looking for him?
He may be working
with the police.
Damn it! Let's go.
I can't take care of you two
right now.
I'm gonna be talking
to your boss soon.
The street is closed.
Go around.
What now?
- I'm hungry. I want something to eat.
- Me too. Let's go.
I can't find him anywhere.
He's coming.
Let's go get him.
Freeze!
You can't escape now.
My legs!
My hands!
- You broke my pots. Pay for the damage.
- Pay for your pots, my ass!
Hold it. Don't try to run!
Hurry!
You've got nowhere to run.
Come on.
Prepare yourselves.
Guests are arriving.
- See if everything is ready.
- Yes.
I'll figure out what to do.
Don't worry.
Is there a problem?
They're rehearsing
how the guests are going to enter.
We have enough time.
Don't be nervous.
Where is he?
Up there.
Bring him down.
Tiger, I'm sorry I missed
our appointment.
Damn it. I really liked you.
I promise to have dim sum
with you.
But I have something urgent
to take care of. Please let me go.
Let you go?
I sent two of my men
to invite you for dim sum.
- You killed them. Why?
- No, I didn't. I set them free.
- I'm telling the truth.
- Give me the gun.
You don't understand
what I'm saying?
I didn't kill them.
They'll come back soon.
Fei, tell him I didn't kill them.
You did.
The bodies have been found.
That's impossible.
Tiger, don't believe him.
He's a scoundrel.
You're a good man, and so am I.
He didn't like being under me.
They'll be back soon.
Believe me.
You said you didn't kill them.
Where are they?
I'm sure they'll be back
any minute.
- It's time you paid for their lives.
- Damn it, I'm not a fool.
Tiger, believe me.
I didn't kill them.
Tiger! Tiger!
Don't kill me now. There's something
I must do and then I'll come back.
- Bullshit! I'll kill you now.
- They're back.
I told you I didn't kill them.
Aren't you two
supposed to be dead?
Not really. He tied us up.
- But he set us free.
- Damn it, I was worried about you.
Tiger, I told you
I didn't cheat you.
You thug! So you're the one
who wants to be the boss!
Tiger, I did it for you.
I'd make a better boss.
Shit! You wouldn't be better!
- Release him.
- Hurry!
Tiger, I did it for both of us.
Keep that in mind.
It's between him and me now,
so you stay out of it.
Between you and him?
Okay, I'll stay out of it.
I caught him,
but you're gonna have to hold him.
Tiger, I promise to have
dim sum with you some other time.
Good.
Fei, as you said,
it's between you and me.
Why don't we resolve it
at home?
I've got something urgent to do.
Excuse me.
I'm not gonna let you go
so easily.
Tiger.
I won't meddle in your business,
but rules are rules.
I'll keep the guns for you.
Don't worry, young man.
I'll take care of any snipers.
If you promise,
that means I'm dead meat!
If you get him,
you can have the factory.
Great! Good job.
Stop fighting, please.
We have an urgent matter here.
- We'll resume the fight after that.
- Get him.
Where is he?
Pull the rope.
Lord help me.
Don't jump!
I told you not to jump.
Stop fighting.
Fei, don't run away.
It's your turn now.
You're great.
You've done
at least one good thing.
All the factory workers
are behind you.
When you repossess the plant,
we'll be brothers again.
Thank you, Cheng Wah.
I've got to go.
Time is running out.
Young man,
I admire you more than ever.
Your dispute is settled,
and our misunderstanding is cleared up.
Let's be friends.
I don't have time to make friends
with you now.
Because I beat you up?
You can hit me back.
Go ahead, hit me.
Don't be afraid.
- Get him.
- Stop!
That was great.
Young man, you fought well.
Here, I still owe you a slap.
We will be good friends
from now on.
I really have to go now,
my friend.
If anything happens,
count on me to help.
With friends like you...!
- What's the hurry?
- Tiger, lend me your car.
- What?
- I need to use your car.
- Did I say that right?
- Yes, perfectly.
Inspector Ho,
someone is here to see you.
Inspector Ho.
- Go out and keep watch.
- Yes, sir.
Please call off your men,
Inspector Ho.
How did you get out?
Stand up.
Please call off your men.
We're doing a good thing at the Ritz.
I'm sure catching you all
will be a good thing.
You didn't search
for the missing persons like I told you.
Why did you send your men
to the Ritz?
Sir--
Don't "sir" me. The attorney general
just told me everything.
I'm telling you...
from now on, your only job
will be to find the missing persons.
Or turn up missing yourself.
I know the whereabouts
of those missing persons.
- Who's he?
- The owner of the Ritz.
- Do you really know?
- Four reporters, two businessmen?
- That's why I brought him to you.
- Follow me.
- You too.
- Yes, sir.
You must solve the case
of the missing persons first.
The Ritz owner knows
their whereabouts.
Search the Ritz.
No, they're preparing a party
for Madam Rose.
- An order is an order.
- But they're not at the Ritz.
- Where are they?
- Free my friends and I'll tell.
- First, let me make a call.
- I can't promise you that.
My men won't free them
without my call.
- And things will get worse.
- All right, make the call.
Thank you.
- Luming.
- Yes?
- Tell Uncle Hai to release them.
- Free the reporters.
Tell Madam Rose we can't come.
Tell our men the party is cancelled.
What now?
One more time.
Make it better.
No need to practice.
The party is cancelled.
Why did you kidnap them?
- To keep the secret.
- A secret about your crimes?
It's not your turn to speak.
- What secret?
- A woman's secret.
Does she have anything
to do with you?
Nothing. I just buy a rose
from her every day.
I know no one will believe me.
We do believe you.
We just can't figure out the kidnapping.
That's why I had to kidnap those people.
Oh, you wouldn't understand!
Let me put it this way.
Her daughter has a rich boyfriend.
They came back to Hong Kong
and want to get married.
The mother has panicked, because
she had pretended she was rich too.
She didn't want to lie to her daughter.
She's got a heart of gold.
The first day I came here,
she told me to be careful...
because it's easy to get conned
in Hong Kong.
A con man had taken
my last penny.
I depended on her roses for luck.
You ladies will understand,
I'm sure...
a mother's love
for her daughter.
So I kidnapped those reporters.
But I didn't hurt them.
I did it out of good will...
because I wanted
to help her keep her secret.
- Do you understand?
- Could you put it more clearly?
We don't yet understand.
All right, I'll speak slowly.
Once there was a flower girl.
No, a flowerwoman.
She had a daughter and--
Dad, the guests--
- Sorry. I must see Madam Kao.
- Stop the music.
Why aren't the guests here yet?
A car broke down
and blocked the street...
and all the guests
are stuck in traffic.
But they're coming.
I'm sorry.
We did our best.
I know what I must do.
- We tried so hard. Why can't it work?
- Are you talking to me?
Mr. and Mrs. Kao...
what's this all about?
I think by now...
you must have realized
there's something wrong.
What's happened?
Don't worry.
There's a solution to every problem.
I know you came to Hong Kong...
to look into Belle's
family background.
You have sound reasons
to do so.
Whether the guests
come or not...
we can still enjoy ourselves.
Let's have something
to eat first.
Let me finish.
Mr. Ku, I hope you appreciate
the fact...
that Belle
is very important to me.
For her happiness...
I would do anything.
Ma, I don't want
to see you like this.
Tell me what has upset you.
Now I realize no matter
how hard you try...
you can't have something
you don't deserve.
I'm sorry I insisted
on having the engagement dinner.
I didn't realize
you didn't want to do it.
It's not that.
I was saying...
my identity as Madam Kao--
All right, Madam Kao.
If it's nothing to do
with the wedding...
you don't have to say it.
Madam, I want you to know...
I love Belle too.
That's why
I have to speak the truth now.
I want you all to know
that I am--
Music, music!
- I am not--
- The guests have arrived.
King's Councillor and Mrs. Lo.
Commandant of Volunteers
and Mrs. Wong.
Magistrate and Mrs. Benjamin.
Marine Commander
and Mrs. Gordon.
Police Commissioner
and Mrs. Laughton.
Chief Boy Scout McGeorge.
Attorney General
and Mrs. Steeves.
Chairman of the Jockey Club,
General Morse.
President of the Lions Club,
Mr. Chan.
Justice of the Peace
and Mrs. Chow.
President of the Rotary Club
and Mrs. Lee.
Supreme Court Magistrate
and Mrs. Nelson.
Railways Director
and Mrs. Watson.
Postmaster General
and Mrs. Nitton.
Why are you dressed like that?
The attorney general
lent it to me.
How did you get them here?
I told them their presence
was mandatory.
Water Works Director
and Mrs.Johnston.
Public Works Director
and Mrs. Pierce.
Chairman of the East India Company
and Mrs. Banks.
I'm so happy tonight.
You finally did something good
on your own.
I wish I could do
something good like that...
but I don't have the courage.
Why are you crying?
I'm going to the rest room.
Stop crying.
You'll look awful.
Do I really look that awful?
Ma.
Bye-bye.
Hurry up!
The ship is about to sail.
"Wanted for Abuse of Power"
Damn you!
Come after me if you dare!
- You finally did a good deed.
- And you were part of it.
Come back and visit us
whenever you have a chance.