I'm coming, I'm so sorry...
I have just gone for pissing,
I'm so sorry!
Where the hell has boss gone?
So many cars are queuing up!
How can I finish all these?
Kiddy, I will give you $20 dollars.
Park this car for me, OK?
Twenty dollars?
How about I give you two hundred
and you fix the queue for me?
Shit! A traffic police is coming!
Damn it! I'd better run!
Sir, I'm sorry, the cars are going
to be driven away!
If you can make it by yourself,
just do it.
One minute.
Sir, aren't you giving us face?
Just one minute, OK?
That's right! Why not
be a little bit nice?
Alright, just one minute.
What are you doing here?
You can't park your car right here.
You are too comy!
Please don't fine me, OK?
Sir, go ahead!
Boss, where have you been?
I can't manage all these by myself!
I went to look for my woman!
Got her or not?
It's shit!
We quarreled this morning,
then she went away with our son.
What the hell!
It's Ruby, I've found your honey now.
Where the hell has she gone?
Do you want a talk?
Sure...
Let daddy use it for a while,
come on.
Well, I won't drink again.
I won't go to disco anymore, OK?
But you would fool around
in some place else.
Come on!
Please give me a break!
I knew you two so well!
Your son is already 2 years old,
but you two are still like kids.
You should thank Ruby.
If now were her honey lips,
I would have left you.
Thank you.
Why not find her a boyfriend?
Good idea! I know two men,
one is called Sun-sa,
one is called Gutsy Chuen.
Which one do you like?
Save that for your God-mother!
It's hard to find a nice guy now.
I'm one.
Why don't you marry me too?
Let's go to the registry tomorrow,
so, we will have a sweet family.
Good idea! Ruby is my best friend,
I won't let you court any
other woman, except Ruby.
Come on! Please cut the bull shit!
Sai-fai.
Cheung-dee, what's the matter?
Who is staying with Prince?
There're 5 people
inside the VIP room.
But I think there is
a gang waiting outside.
I can tell from their gesticulations
that they are a gang.
Is that anything wrong?
What's the matter? Anything wrong?
I don't know, I'm going to take look.
Take care.
This place is under my supervision.
Crazy Ball, the Police has got
enough evidence to nail you.
How dare you fool around
instead of hiding up?
That's why I'd like
you to pay your debt.
Just three million,
I haven't added interest.
I've given you face, you know?
I have nothing but guts.
I will not pay except on the
gambling table, are you green?
I know your old man
is the boss of Hung Tai,
but this doesn't mean you can
refuse to pay your debt.
The whole district is under
the supervision of Hung Tai Group.
You're sitting at the turf
of Hung Tai too.
I love doing what I want,
so what?
You should pay your bill
before leaving.
Are you crazy? How dare you
pull off a stunt in my place?
You would end up going
into fugitive, you know?
Right! So I'm planning to run,
and I want to leave tonight.
Call you damn father Mei
to pay me five million.
Otherwise, I will cut off
your flesh piece by piece.
Take him away.
Something's wrong, right?
Don't bother your man
from working, let's go.
You...
I can't make it.
I can't run!
Run!
Ruby, I'm not leaving,
take care of my son.
Cindy, no! Cindy!
Cindy!
Police! Freeze!
Cops are around. Let's run...
Cindy, how are you?
Mom...
My name is Cheung-dee,
I've been a rascal for five years,
always want to be a gang leader.
I saved Prince, and thus
made me become a gang leader.
But, what I couldn't imagine is that.
being a leading light isn't as
gorgeous as what you see in movies.
Yip... Do you have any pain-killer?
Shut up, someone has
come to pay your bail.
Thank you...
Cheung-dee, this way.
Madam, this's the file of Cheung-dee.
Sir, do you have...
You had a fight
in a nightclub last night,
Fat Chow is in hospital.
I thought I was beaten.
This is Sandy Leung, your lawyer.
Sign the paper and
you can leave now.
You are charged with assault.
You want me to sign
anything you asked?
Do you have any name card?
Show me first.
Sandy Leung.
Barrister? Take it back.
My classmate is used to
pay you bail, he is on leave now.
This time, I think you'll
be in deep trouble.
I always have trouble, please...
fix this as soon as possible,
I want a sleep.
No, Tai-hung's teacher wants to
see you! At twelve, please.
You go for me, OK?
No, his teacher wants to see
you this time, personally!
This is shit!
Miss...
can you disguise as me
and meet my son's teacher?
Would you do me a favour?
Please.
Mr. Wai, Wai Tai-hung's
done well in school.
But I notice that he has
violent inclination.
Once he disagrees with someone,
He'll fight.
Why do you fight?
He said you are bad.
Kids will fight
when they are challenged.
Especially his classmate
insulted me, you see?
Come on!
Please teach you little students
to behave well.
Any lighter?
You can't smoke here.
Are you sick?
I'm sorry.
Damn it! You are Dicky Keung!
Prince called for me?
What's the matter?
Lion King? That scum!
He is a betrayer!
We'd give him a good lesson.
Of course.
It's alright, call Gutsy Chuen
to gather enough fellows.
I will kill him, I swear.
I remember that.
I will take my son
there as soon as possible.
Deal.
Where were we?
The kids... said you are bad...
In fact,
I think they've wrong concept...
What? I don't look like a bad guy.
But I like the teachers here.
I think she'll be understanding
to be educated here.
Ruby, what kind of school is it?
Why can't I see any student here?
You son is punished
to stay behind school.
Right.
Cheung-dee, I think you'd stay
more time with your son.
Tai-hung is quite eccentric.
Isn't her?
Lady, I have to work.
In these years,
you seem to be gorgeous.
Everynight, you enjoy much.
But you can't make much money.
You son's growing up.
He needs your company.
As your wife's best friend,
I don't think I can do much.
I know, but I'm the boss.
I've to attend
many business parties.
And, the VCD factory held by
Prince and me is making big money.
Right...
- We have a new production...
- What?
named "Lustful nanny, baby creep",
do you want to watch it?
No! Don't show your son
any bad things.
You are so bad.
May I take you to the birthday party?
Where is Uncle Mei?
Meeting...
Not sleeping... No sleeping...
Thank you.
Drink?
Water...
Thank you.
You stay here with the kids,
I'm going up for a business talk, OK?
I dislike this place.
Why not? There's swimming pool,
and you have snacks.
So many children will play with you.
There are rabbits, ducks,
everything's so cute!
I really dislike this place.
I don't care, anyway,
you'll wait for me right here.
Cheung-dee.
Why are you so late?
They are all inside.
I'm sorry, I took the minibus,
that's why I came late.
Say hello to auntie, come on.
How are you, auntie?
It's all right, help yourself to
any food you like, OK?
Speak up or not? Speak up...
Uncle Mei.
Brother Pao-wing, Prince,
Uncle Pui, Uncle Fatty, hi!
Go to hell!
To hell with you!
Let me do it.
You bastard! Speak up or not?
To hell with you!
Speak up or not?
I would kill you, I swear!
Pao-wing, his mouth is stuffed,
how can he tell you?
Kid, if you want to say,
just nod you head.
Otherwise he would kill you!
Nod now?
Where will Lion King go tonight?
If I tell you, He'll kill me too.
If you don't tell us,
you'll die at once.
Uncle Fatty has just
told you the truth.
Creep like you
deserve to be sent to hell!
How can you work for such betrayer?
Brother Cheung-dee, I have a family.
Save you breath and cut the crap.
Let's shoot him to death.
Come on, hold him...
No! Don't kill me!
Brother Prince, please let me go!
Don't kill me!
Forget it! He is our fellow anyway.
Kid, you know very well that,
Lion King took 200 fellows of mine
to join the Tung Sing Group.
We lost face, you know?
If you confess now,
you can be rewarded instead.
I will pay you $300,000, cash.
And a ticket to Taiwan.
You can then take your family
there some months later.
And start a new life,
isn't that good idea?
Confess now!
Uncle Mei is so kind to you!
He'll collect a debt at the
Poultry Market at 3 p.m.
Good!
My place is dirtied!
- Bury him!
- Yes.
Three p.m. at the poultry market?
Who will do it?
How about Cheung-dee?
He is the best.
Good idea, Cheung-dee is the
best fighter in our group.
After killing Lion King,
He'll gain fame again.
Happy birthday to you...
I know he has lots of fellows.
But they pushed me to do it,
I can't refuse it.
Anyways, get me
some men and weapons.
Wait for me at the
poultry market, OK?
Make a birthday wish!
Bravo!
Let's cut the birthday cake, come on!
What's the matter?
Let's go.
Good boy, you stay here,
I have to work.
OK?
I will ask Ruby to pick you up, OK?
Cheung-dee.
- You're going to be rich!
- Really?
Well, when will we get the bonus?
Very soon!
Come on, I'm in need of money...
Woo woo woo! You always
pretend to be poor! You bastard!
Be good,
when I finish my work,
I will buy you a superman.
Dad, you'd be very careful.
I know!
Who are you?
My daddy is Cheung-dee.
My daddy said
your daddy is a dog!
No!
I said, you daddy is a dog!
My daddy said your daddy
is a dog! A dog which eats shit!
You daddy eats shit...
Can you go now? You're a trouble!
I'm almost ready, wait!
That bastard hasn't come yet.
Bastard! Someone is going to die!
Would you hurry up?
Cut the crap!
Let's go.
This is shit!
Isn't that Brother Cheung-dee?
Hey, Lion King, why are you here?
I've been informed that
Uncle Mei asked you to kill me.
Are you kidding me?
No, it's not true.
- Not true?
- No!
You really have guts to come alone.
- Come to kill me now.
My daddy said your daddy
is a dog which eats shit!
How about fight with me?
You bastard!
Kill me!
Bastard!
Kill him!
Beat him up...
Stay where you are!
Beat him...
How dare you run!
Peter, charge up...
Beat him...
Why do you fight? Get up...
How dare you fight?
Are you a good fighter?
Boss.
It's fixed.
You will take the prize.
Brother Prince,
they are no match for me.
We have got nerves...
Chuen followed me...
Come on... take a seat.
Chuen followed me to tail them...
We scared the shit out of them!
Ruby, come here!
What's the matter, Brother Prince?
What's wrong with you to bring
such monsters to me?
I just want you to keep me company.
I don't mind staying with you now.
I worry that you'll lose your temper
for I'm not going to entertain you.
It's easy, just do it.
No way! I won't sleep with
my clients, you know that!
And, Brother Prince
won't like me too.
Why do you work here as a mamasan?
Why not be my woman?
You'll be rich and famous, you know?
I'm not as attractive as
the little girls!
They are young and fresh.
Really? Let me check.
This one ... Look at this!
I think this's better, this's better.
Brother Prince,
this is good for screwing!
If you have guts to screw her,
just go ahead.
Of course I have guts! Boss.
I have guts to kill,
how come I dare not screw her?
Any problem?
Cheung, you are great!
Have my toast!
Take this seat, come on!
Thank you, Brother Pao-wing.
You know what
Cheung-dee is good at?
What?
Go ahead.
He is the best bluffer!
My boys witnessed
how he killed Lion King.
They saw you hiding yourself
under the car, you chicken!
Brother Pao-wing,
you must be kidding!
Dare you deny that?
Yes, you know what?
I slipped down carelessly,
and thus I rolled under the car.
They didn't see the other side
of the car, did they?
I rolled out from the other side.
Then fought with those bastards.
- Sounds great, huh?
- Yeah!
It's Gutsy Chuen
who killed Lion King.
Not you!
I couldn't stand any more! Actually
I didn't want to blame you!
Brother Pao-wing, you fellows
were told to standby,
why didn't you ask them to help me?
If you couldn't make it,
my fellows would help.
If you could make it,
I just didn't want to take you pride.
Cheung-dee, what I should say is...
you are useless!
You fixed Crazy Ball
fiercely years ago,
I wonder, didn't you
get stoned for that?
You are going worse!
I'm sorry, I want to piss.
Back to you work, I'm fine!
What can I do?
Do you think I should go in
and let them take my advantage?
Those are beasts!
You have totally changed.
You dress well now.
Yeah, there is something
you don't know.
Now, my whole family
is being covered by Prince.
Beggars can't be choosers.
You know what people
talk about you?
What?
People said you are a dog of Prince.
Who said this?
I would beat that creep.
Prince said this.
I'm alright, I'll go back soon.
Don't you want to
take care of your son?
Have you taken him home?
I took him to the doctor.
What's the matter?
Why did you fight?
Why did you fight with other kids?
Answer me.
They said you are a dog.
Why do you care?
I have told you many times.
I told you not to fight
with others, you know?
I've told you many times!
Are you a dog?
Dad isn't a dog.
I'm a pig, OK?
Prince slapped him.
Damn it!
What's the matter?
He is just a kid!
How could he slap him?
Brother Prince,
why do you come down here?
Where the hell have you been?
Well, I just want to
take some fresh air here.
Let's go to the VCD factory now.
We are making big money! A new
film is under production now.
I'm sorry about
what happened today.
The kids fought among
themselves and you son got hurt.
Never mind, children always fight.
I told you, we are making
big money in these days.
Take your bonus
in advance, $100,000.
Thank you!
I'm really in need of money!
The school fee, and the lawyer,
you know?
And...
There is a contract for you,
you are the license holder.
Just for taxing purpose, no big deal.
It's written in English,
I don't quite understand it.
You are my fellow,
I won't harm you, you know?
Sign where there is a mark.
I'll show you something.
See, how great it is!
Once a new film is finished,
right after first show,
we will move directly to the
theatre and shoot it, then produce.
Brother Prince...
please advice your fellows,
they always shoot badly.
The vision isn't sharp,
and too many people
walking to toilets.
It harms the quality.
You stupid fool!
It's useless to shoot sharply.
Those bastards pay $25 for the VCD.
So what?
You are talking about
quality with me?
Are you too stupid?
The customers will complain!
Just ask those bastards
not to buy from us.
Move to the theatre,
then they can ask for quality!
They pay limited money
for these VCDs.
It's just like receiving loot.
We make the VCDs,
we know how bad the quality is.
But we can't help,
they just want to stuff us money.
Should I reject the money? Go!
Well, who cares!
It's great!
Boss, you are really great!
Rascal.
Where is the new attraction
"Fung-wen"?
That's shit! Damn poor vision!
Do you know grabbing
the film and then copy it?
They won't let us do it
Are you sick?
You are a triad member.
Are we doing decent business?
Go to a theatre in remote area,
if the guys refuse, beat them up.
If they still refuse to let you
copy it, beat them again.
Refuse again? Then beat them up,
until they say yes.
I don't think they are superman.
Do you see my point?
Any foreign films?
Over the corner.
My son is learning English.
What are you doing?
What are you doing here?
That guy is taking cocaine!
We will be in deep shit!
You bastard!
Brother Prince, please let me go.
Don't stop me, I want to kill him!
No! Run! Run for you life!
Bastard!
It's alright.
On March 7, at karaoke,
a guy named Chow Tai-man,
nicked-named Fatty Chow,
had a fight with you.
You attacked him with weapons,
is that right?
You badly injured him. Am I right?
I don't know,
he has many foes, you know?
I don't know who did it to him!
Mr. Wai,
if you answer like this in court,
ou'll let the judge think you're
a slippery customer, it's not wise.
Who are you? What are you?
He is your solicitor.
Who are you?
I'm your barrister.
What's the difference?
Formally speaking,
you can't hire me.
You should hire him first,
and then He'll hire me.
I'm a barrister, he is Solicitor.
I don't know what the difference is,
I just think that you
want me to pay more!
What did you use to hit him?
Damn it, you change the topic.
I don't know you're
helping me or attacking me!
Miss Leung is trying to let you
practice how to answer in court.
We hope you can
answer in a proper way.
I'll tell the judge the answer which
you're going to teach me, OK?
I can't teach you how to answer.
I can only help you
according to the facts.
Actually, did you hit him?
What the hell is it?
Are you threatening me?
Can you leave first?
Don't worry, he won't overhear us.
OK, can you tell me now,
whether you beat him or not.
I mean with weapon.
It's just a fight.
I thought he would
call his fellows to help,
so I couldn't control myself but...
His head hit the ashtray
in my hand accidentally.
This is the case.
That means you hit him
by the ashtray.
No, I didn't say so,
you can't put it that way.
Mr. Wai.
You know you are a poor liar?
I... I know how to
tell the judge in court.
I'm smart.
You've just acted like a kid
who lied in front of his mom.
You're scared after lying, that's it.
You haven't looked at me.
I think,
you can't lie to anyone in court.
Well, just admit your charge,
I'll beg for mercy for you.
No way!
No way! I promised
my son not to go to jail.
You hurt people!
I know, but...
You didn't see that guy!
He was so disgusting!
If you saw him,
you would have beaten him too.
You can't smoke right here.
Doesn't you boyfriend smoke?
He doesn't.
I don't want my husband dies
of lung cancer at his early fifty.
Well, I listen to you and
should listen to me too.
Try to let me out of this case.
I promised my son,
I can't walk into jail.
I can't let others tease him
of having a prisoner daddy.
You remember, OK?
Don't worry, I don't want you
to go to prison as well.
OK, I have to leave now, bye bye.
Sorry! Something has kept me busy,
that's why I'm late.
Never mind.
Where are we going to?
You know Cheung-dee Wai?
He is my client,
I'm helping him now.
It's wise of you not to stick with
such kind of person.
You promised not to care
the job of each other.
I know, just to remind you.
I heard that you've
recruited many fellows.
Not many! Just a queue of kids
will greet you as boss, that's it.
See that guy David?
Which one?
The smart looking guy.
He will be a good pimp!
Handsome boy, huh!
Just like me!
Why do you add that much?
It's rather hot.
I feel itchy lately! You know?
I heard people
saying this can kill germs.
Let me tell you.
this is for external use,
you just soak your dick inside.
- You mean it.
- Sure!
Brother Sun-sa.
Are you going to work?
This girl always smiles to me.
I think she likes me.
I'll juice her up!
You are lucky!
Have you screwed any girls lately?
Sure I have! Please use your brain!
But, I don't know
I should be frank or not.
Go ahead.
Ruby is so nice!
She has been with
your family for ages.
And she's given up many chances.
Come on!
I saw many nice guys
proposing to her.
But she refused them.
You see the point?
She is waiting for you!
Please! Please cut the crap, OK?
If you don't shut your mouth,
I will cut your dick off, I swear.
You scum!
Boss!
I know you!
My name is David.
Greet him boss, that's it.
- Boss.
- Good boy!
You may call me Brother Cheung-dee
from now on.
Brother Cheung-dee, I'm your fan.
I remember I saw you riding along
the Prince Margaret Road.
You were a great rider!
Forget it, I don't ride now.
Are you kidding me?
Will you teach me riding?
You young man,
you'd better learn making money.
Making money, can you hear me?
Brother Prince...
It's right.
What? Are you free?
Cheung-dee, I tell you! Tonight...
I won't let Ruby go!
You should stay away from us.
I won't care, OK?
You leave us alone!
OK, I won't care.
He drinks that much,
will he make any trouble?
I will take a look,
I'll can you if I need help.
OK
Brother Prince.
Are you bored? You can
only find more girls there.
Why not move to Lan Kwai Fong?
You can find more girls there.
Cheung-dee, I warn you!
You should leave us alone tonight.
Just stay here and watch.
I've just seen 2 blondes in
Disco 97, they are really pretty.
They are sexpots!
I warn you!
I don't care whether
you're Ruby's man or not.
Tonight, no one can save her.
No woman can cheat me, you know?
Brother Prince, just forget
what I said, OK?
I'm sorry.
- Sit over there.
- Sure!
Brother Prince.
I'm sorry about
what happened yesterday.
You know, one of my sisters go sick.
- Really?
- I sent her to hospital.
Well, I don't mind. But I just
want you to sleep with me tonight.
Come on! I won't sleep with
my clients, you know that!
Let's play a guessing game.
I will guess first.
Five.
Another five.
You are stupid! You're thirty
something, how can you cheat?
You are punished! Get out now!
What?
Dare you cheat me?
Who do you think you are?
You work in a club, do you
think you are Miss Hong Kong?
You are a mamasan, don't you
think you need not serve me?
I want to screw you right now.
- Brother Prince...
- Help!
Have you gone too far?
No! Do it next time, OK?
Let me go!
Am I breaking you heart?
Let go of me!
Help!
Bastard!
Do you still deny your affair?
Brother Prince.
You seem to have
two on your chest, right?
Same tattoo!
What? Eagles of love?
Brother Prince, would you
please give me face?
Of course I'm giving you face!
I will share the woman
with you! You first.
Come on!
Please let her go, would you?
Use your brain! Are you moron?
You turn me on,
and you ask me to let go of her?
Alright, I will spare her,
but you should show me,
screw her in front of me.
If you do it well, I will let her go.
Get lost!
Brother Prince, I'm not a moron.
But I feel a bit high.
Don't scare me.
You bastard!
Do you know
what you are doing now?
You want me to kill
your whole family?
Don't scare me!
Let her go! Let her go!
Let go of her!
Don't come over!
Let's go.
Don't cover over.
Brother Prince, I'm sorry.
I think I have drunk too much!
I'm sorry.
Brother Prince, please don't
blame me! I'm sorry.
It's alright! Forget it! It's over.
Cause you are my buddy,
you know?
For this woman? No way!
Come on, let's have a drink!
It's alright!
Kill this scum for me!
Got you!
To hell will you!
Are you pretending to be cool?
Don't you recognize me?
It's okay,
I just fell and hurt myself.
I'm sorry.
I think, it's me
who should apologize.
It's been five years!
You have helped me so much!
If I didn't give you a hand,
I think,
even I would despise myself.
- But Prince...
- It's alright.
I can fix it. Don't worry.
Let me put some medicine
on your wound.
Alright.
What's up?
When did you make it?
Last year.
For me?
You know and you still ask!
Why didn't you tell me?
You are so bad!
Are you crazy?
Why do you bite me?
I've fallen for you
since you knew Cindy.
You know,
Cindy fell crazy for you.
How could I tell
how much I love you!
After her death,
I burn her incense everyday.
I beg her not to blame me.
Well, she has nothing to blame.
Yes!
I take you as my man.
Don't you believe...
I always take you as
Tai-hung's mom?
I'm sorry. Sorry...
You ordered too many food!
- Love it or not?
- I love it.
If only Tai-hung loves it,
just do it.
I don't like it.
What do you want? I order for you!
I want dumplings in fine soup.
It's just been ordered.
Don't you remember me?
How about this?
You seem to be very afraid!
Aren't you the most capable
fighter in Hung Tai Group?
I can tell from you eyes that
you are wondering why I'd
be released from prison.
What are you looking at?
Just eat you food.
In these five years, I spent all
my money for an appeal.
Finally I've discovered that
the judge made a big mistake...
to mislead the jury.
That's why I appealed successfully,
and I'm free now.
So what?
I tell you, this is a public place.
I've almost forgotten that!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry...
I really envy you! You've a cute son.
And your girl has nice figure!
But I tell you!
From now on, I'm always free.
That will make you feel unhappy!
- So?
- It's alright.
Let's go.
He just wants to threaten you!
Don't give it a damn!
But I really...
He is insane you know?
Put a knife under his neck,
I wonder he won't be insane any more.
He just wants to threaten you!
But I think...
I'd better talk to Uncle Mei.
Come on! Do you think
he will help you?
Why not?
This is difficult to say.
Boss, please come here.
Boss, you know what it is about.
I know it very well,
Uncle Mei will never help except
he finds advantage.
He will leave you alone if there
isn't any advantage for him.
About Crazy Ball's matter,
you'd fix it yourself.
How can I kill him?
I'm helpless.
Boss, you slashed him once,
so you can do it the second time.
You can only live once, you know?
What are you considering?
I know, but I...
All of us will back you up!
Boss, see you bike! Now if
becomes the attraction of my shop.
I clean it everyday.
Do you have any feel?
If yes, take a ride.
I have no feeling!
I haven't ridden for ages.
I don't want to lose face.
Let's stop here! I'm leaving now.
Boss, do you drive?
I will take the minibus.
What's wrong with boss now?
He lames when he walks!
He hasn't been our leading
light for ages! Let's go.
Cheung-dee Wai claimed
himself a triad member.
He came in and wanted
to blackmail me.
I'm decent citizen, you know?
I would never be
blackmailed by a triad.
So I counter attacked.
He broke my head
with an ashtray.
Mr. Chow, you emphasize
the word "Blackmail".
What does that mean?
Well, the triad members always
want to take advantage.
They will set us up
and grab money from us.
Say, they will frame us
of doing something bad.
Or, they'll force us to admit to
courting their girls, so and so.
Anyways, just doing something bad.
They will put all the blames on you!
You know Wai
is a triad on that night?
Everyone knows he is a triad member.
See the eagles on his chest!
And a dragon on his back.
Who will believe that
he is a decent person?
It's you who walked straightly
into his VIP room on that night.
You know he is a triad,
why did you move to his room.
Didn't you worry that
he would beat you up?
Such fight wouldn't have
happened in the past.
That means you went into
his room many times before?
I have forgotten.
Let me tell you the truth.
More than once.
You know Wai very well.
He wanted you to pay
the gambling debt, and you refused.
So you started to fight.
At last, you fought each other.
And you were no match for him,
is that right?
Don't frame me!
Witness, just answer
straight to the question.
I don't know him well,
and I didn't owe him money.
I'm so strong, he is no match
for me if we fight.
He attacked me.
From the back?
Of course.
But you hurt your forehead.
Yes.
That means, he held the ashtray...
stood behind you, and aimed at
your forehead, right?
It could be possible.
How tall are you?
Five feet 11 inches.
Mr. Cheung-dee Wai
is five feet nine.
So he had to act like
a basketball player,
to jump tall enough and
hit your forehead from behind?
I think, such action will only
appear in action films.
Nothing further.
In March 7, 1998, did you
hit Mr. Chow Tai-man...
at Yeah's karaoke with an ashtray?
I did fight with him.
And you claimed yourself
a triad member, is that right?
No.
Well, are you a triad member?
Yes.
You threatened Chow Tai-man.
You said you'd beat him up
if he didn't pay back, right?
No!
Although I'm a triad member,
but since five years ago,
I haven't joined
any triad's activities.
I promised my son,
I won't let his dad
become a prisoner.
During a gang fight 5 years ago,
I lost my wife accidentally.
In all these years, I...
I'm the father and mother
of my son, so...
Why did you hit Chow Tai-man?
I didn't hit him.
It's self defense.
I asked him to pay me back.
He refused, and said...
something dirty.
What's that?
I don't think it's proper
to tell right here.
Go ahead.
He insulted my mom and my wife.
Did you attack him from his back?
I said I didn't hit him.
We fought.
He grabbed a bottle
and intended to hit me.
I grabbed and ashtray to resist,
but I hit him accidentally.
I thought this was
a normal reaction.
I won't deny that we fought, but I...
Your honor, I...
I really want to say something.
Go ahead.
Yes, I'm a triad member.
I regret to be a triad member,
because...
It makes my son feel shame.
I try so hard to go straight.
I hope you to give me a chance.
To let me become
a model daddy of my son.
Finished?
Adjourn now.
You know, you're
great in court! So great!
I think you have potential
to become an actor.
Can't you see the judge?
You've fixed it, no problem!
I'm really scared!
If I didn't promise my son...
Be gentle please!
Why not toast to Sandy?
Thanks.
This is my job.
Why hasn't your boyfriend
come yet?
Here he is.
He is cool.
Michael, this is
Cheung-dee Wai, this is Michael.
How are you doing?
You boyfriend is really smart!
Where do you make a fortune?
We can't make a fortune.
Organised Crime And
Anti-triads Bureau.
Are you hungry?
Want to order something?
I heard that you're
making a fortune lately.
Don't be silly! I'm not.
Your VCD factory
is running good business!
We don't produce pirates.
Michael, why don't you
order some food?
OK.
What a perfect match!
How long have you been in love?
It's been three years.
Beautiful and capable girls
are always men's dream girls.
If I were you,
I would have married her.
Nowadays,
men don't like getting married.
Are you a cop?
Yes.
Why do you stare at my dad?
Since you father is cute.
How cute?
Well, judging form you look now...
you would be a good daddy
and a good husband.
If I were a woman,
I would have fallen for you.
But for something deep,
I don't think anyone will know that.
If you want to know it,
go ahead to get it.
I have finished my food,
if you want to order something,
better separate the bills.
I think it's not wise of me to stay
and ruin you appetite.
Never mind, I have to go now.
My boss paged me.
You'd better leave first.
OK. Excuse me.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Wai.
I'm sorry,
I don't like to see you actually.
When you see me next time,
maybe it will depress you.
You boyfriend is really bad.
- I'm sorry.
- Never mind.
We're used to be teased by cops.
I shouldn't have asked him to come.
None of your business.
Is that your boyfriend
who sits inside the car?
He has tailed us for one night.
Should we say hello? I worry my
fellows would beat him up.
Just kidding.
Since you boyfriend isn't around,
let's go to eat dessert.
Sure!
What do you want?
Red and white? OK?
Man, two bowls of red
and white please.
No, she wants red and white
and I want black and white.
- Come on, take a seat.
- Thanks.
What is red and white?
What is black and white?
Red mixed with white, and the
other is black mixed with white.
What's that?
This is red and white.
- Red bean soup plus bean pudding.
- Thank you.
This is black and white,
sesame soup plus bean pudding.
- It's like you.
- Why?
You seem to be black,
but actually you are white.
In fact, I think you are nice.
Thank you!
But, why do you become a black...
I mean a triad member?
This is hard to say.
When I was small,
my dad was a triad member.
My mom has left us for ages.
I'm the most
educated son in my family.
I finished form two.
But let me tell you,
if I don't become a triad,
I will never achieve anything
to the society, no way!
But you can go straight.
Yes, I have!
I'm producing VCDs.
But they are pirates. It's illegal.
Everyone does that.
One day I went to the cinema,
I saw a person...
shooting the screen.
I was offended!
That's why I beat him.
- You seem to be righteous.
- Of course.
Because I was shooting too!
You know?
He was taking my advantage,
I should beat him!
Help! How can you do this?
Let's go.
I haven't finished yet.
Let's run now.
Check please.
What's the matter?
I will tell you later.
Why do you run that fast?
Come on!
Run!
Cindy!
Cindy, run!
Thank you.
Bye bye...
Take care.
You called me Cindy.
Who is Cindy?
I think... I was confused.
Is that Tai-hung's mom?
Yes!
Who wanted to kill us?
I think they must be my foe.
Leave it to me! I will be fine.
I'm leaving now.
You haven't got a helmet.
Yeah.
How about this? OK?
I think it's not easy
to be noticed, bye bye.
Why do you come so late?
Would you treat me
to a cup of coffee?
You embarrassed me.
Sorry.
I think... if we meet more...
our problem will be slowly solved.
But it's not a question
between you and me.
Sandy, you can't stay
close with Wai.
First, we've trustable information.
his foe wants to kill him.
We've just met that.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Go ahead.
We are now investigating him.
Once we get enough evidence,
we'll nail him.
Why?
Confidential.
Anyways, you can't stay with him.
I won't do it
if I don't know the reason.
We've checked him for 7 months.
His factory
is actually the biggest
distribution center for cocaine.
He may be the biggest
drugs dealer in these ten years.
Impossible!
He can't even pay my lawyer's fee,
how can it be?
He need not let you
know how rich he is.
Anyways, once we get enough
evidence, we will sue him.
He will be put to jail
for at least 20 years.
I'd see Crazy Ball leading a team...
I was almost killed by him.
Pao, what do you think?
Did he mess up our place?
No, he didn't do that.
That means it's between you two.
Brother Pao-wing,
I fought with him for Prince's sake.
Uncle Fatty, I'd like to turn
the conditioner to high cool.
No one feels hot here.
Only you are hot.
Uncle Mei, he picks on me,
it's same as picking on Hung Tai.
You can't put it that way.
We didn't ask you to kill him.
It's you who wanted to be hero.
Now, he comes back to take revenge,
why should we offer help?
Pao, you can't put it that way.
He is our buddy, right?
Cheung-dee,
this Crazy Ball isn't a triad,
he is a thief.
If we help you,
the other groups will tease us
of bullying a dummy,
you know?
You'd better be smart.
You are shit!
We'll lose face because of you!
You'd better fix it yourself.
If you can't make it,
finally we will help.
Cheung-dee, you can make it.
You'd better fix it yourself.
If you can't make it,
we will support you!
Cheung-dee, you can make it.
How is it? What did Uncle Mei say?
Nothing.
Boss, this bike is really great!
Really? How dare you
drive boss's bike?
How about a car accident?
Can you pay for it?
Never mind, this bike is
for riding, not for exhibiting.
Give it to me. Take me the jacket.
Yes.
Cheung-dee, I've something
important to tell you, contact me.
Did your boyfriend tell you that?
Have you sold cocaine?
I'm a triad member.
But I haven't touched such thing.
Why do they suspect you?
I don't know, I think...
It's the problem of the VCD factory.
I share it with Prince.
But I won't go there
even once a month.
Are you the license holder?
How can you sign the paper?
I think we are a family,
I don't think he will set me up.
I hope you haven't cheated me.
Why should I cheat you?
The Americans can check it out
if anyone sells drugs in Hong Kong.
Think, if the FBIs join
with the HK police,
whoever they pick on,
whoever can never escape.
I'd see many guys go into fugitive.
I'm not very smart,
but I'm not stupid.
If you are not involved,
please make everything clear.
Otherwise, no one can help you.
I know.
I have a question for you.
Go ahead.
Why do you help me?
Because...
I think you are not that bad.
This isn't the reason which makes
you betray your boyfriend.
Well...
Maybe I love helping rascals.
This sounds good.
Don't worry.
Still working?
Why do you come?
I just want to check whether
there is any new production.
Brother Prince told me that
you can't come here along.
Are you sick? I'm you boss!
Brother Prince didn't mention that.
I tell you, leave me alone.
Let me give Brother Prince
a call first, OK?
Good!
What are you doing?
Speak up!
Stop fighting!
It's none of my business! Stop!
Speak up! Tell me,
when did Prince
start to sell cocaine?
I don't know, that's none of
my business! Don't beat me!
OK, I'll tell you...
Speak up.
Right after this factory was set up.
Boss, you are trapped this time.
David.
Yes!
Take all the cocaine away.
Boss, cops are coming!
Pal, work now.
Go there and check.
Search every inch of here.
Uncle Mei, this is Cheung-dee,
I have something to talk to you.
I will come to you now.
Brother Cheung-dee,
do you know who I'm?
Crazy Ball, what do you want?
I hope I haven't got
a wrong address...
Now, I'm staying with you son,
I'm fooling him!
Leave him alone.
I'm squeezing his face!
Dad, help me! Help me, dad!
Don't lose your mind.
Since I'm staying at your home,
I can do anything I want.
I've forgotten to tell you, do you
want to say hello to your woman?
Don't come back.
Can you hear that?
If you don't show up before ten,
we'll chain rape your woman.
And I'll throw
your son the to the street.
Stop!
Stop, off the engine.
Get down.
Stay calm, don't lose your mind.
Squat...
We are from the Anti-drugs Bureau,
Wai, you're now under arrest.
My son is in danger!
Slow down...
I beg you!
Let me go home to save him,
You dad is gutless chicken.
- No!
- I said he is a chicken!
Leave him alone.
Don't move! Stay calm.
Stay calm! I have to go. Please...
Don't hit auntie...
Bitch, how dare you hit me?
How dare you!
No! Don't hit her!
Don't mess up!
Drag her inside and enjoy yourself,
I'll be the next.
Stay cool...
Take him back!
My dad will come back to kill you!
Kill me!
Let me go!
Michael, let me go!
Micheal, let me go...
Tell me what's happened.
We're sorry about what happened...
at you home last night.
Tell me.
Crazy Ball did go to you home.
Your friend Ruby Kwan...
was chain raped and assaulted
by more than one man.
She's safe,
and is now in the hospital.
Go ahead.
I'm sorry.
You son Wai Tai-hung...
his eyes were stabbed
by hard substances...
he may become blind.
Why?
- Sit down...
- Why?
I told you many times and
you didn't trust me! Why?
Why?
Cheung-dee, stay calm.
You are his lawyer,
please talk to him.
Stay calm,
would you control yourself?
Don't move.
No, OK?
Why?
Why they allied to pick on me?
It's happened.
I'll try my best to help you!
I'll try hard to let you pay the bail.
What? The judge let him pay the bail?
What are you doing?
He will escape.
Two councilors and a priest?
So what?
It's useless to keep
his travelling document.
He doesn't need to take a plane
for fugitive, you fool.
Henry, I want two teams to
keep an eye on him round the clock.
Inform me if anything happens.
Nurse, where is Wai Tai-hung?
Cheung-dee.
Thank you.
There is a cop.
Where is Tai-hung?
Let me see him.
Is that Sister Ruby?
- No, it's daddy.
- Daddy.
How is it? Does it hurt?
I don't want you to go to prison.
If you go to prison,
no one will love me.
Don't worry.
I won't go to prison, I won't.
Daddy, please don't cry.
I promise, I will study hard.
I know you are a good boy.
Daddy promise,
I won't go to prison.
I promise. Who bullied us...
Will be very sorry.
He will regret deeply.
Daddy!
Daddy...
Why do you follow me all day?
It's me.
How did you get in?
Do you have any food here?
How can you do this?
This is my home.
Except this place,
I have no where to hide.
Why do you hide? You paid
the bail, why do you hole up?
Don't be naive!
You boyfriend sends
two teams to tail me.
I've just brushed them off
at the hospital.
And, the Crazy Ball
is still searching for me.
Would you stop messing up?
I want everything to be fine too.
If I don't act like
what I used to be,
I can't save myself.
Don't be silly.
If you were me,
think of what happened
to my son and Ruby.
Can you still sit right here?
I'm upset too...
- But...
- I know!
So, please help me.
It's Michael.
Go into that room first.
Has Wai contacted you?
Isn't he in the hospital?
He brushed my men off.
I haven't agreed to let you come in.
Would you please separate your
job and your private matters?
It's you who can't.
Do you come here for business
or for private purpose?
Private.
For private matters, I don't
want you to come in, I'm tired.
We are still in a cool war.
If for business,
please let me see you warrant.
You are my fiancee,
why do you help Wai?
Because he is my client.
No!
Cause you like him.
No matter what you said.
You are a wise woman.
- I hope you won't be impulsive.
- I'm not.
OK, I won't bother you.
No matter what,
if you can't find Cheung-dee,
get ready you coffin then.
Uncle Mei,
you should help Cheung-dee.
If he is in deep shit
because of serving the group,
of course I will help him.
But he is selling drugs,
how can I help him then?
You know very well that
he isn't involved.
Silly girl, are you sure
he hasn't done that?
How do I know whether
he is dealing drugs or not?
Crazy Ball harmed Tai-hung and me...
he will avenge Cheung-dee too.
Cheung-dee is safer than us.
Cause he is protected by cops,
you know?
Red wine of 1982?
It's great! First-class cigar!
Uncle Mei,
if you don't help,
no one can save him then.
Let me think!
You know, drugs trafficking
is a serious crime.
If I offer help...
the cops will think I'm involved too.
Brother Prince.
Well, it's nice to see you here.
Enjoy you time
if you still have a chance.
I think you would
definitely be put in jail.
That's why I would
like you to help me.
You need my help?
Are you kidding me?
I want to borrow money
to hire a better barrister.
I think it's useless,
you will be shit this time.
You'd better talk to Uncle Mei.
Would you seek help from
the gang to fix Ball, OK?
I've told you!
The gang won't get involved into it.
Brother Prince, please help me.
If you don't help me, I'd be shit!
I beg you!
Brother Prince,
please help Cheung-dee, OK?
Are you begging mercy
on his behalf?
This is different!
I always love dealing with women.
But it will be a trouble to help him!
Well, you'd better
stay with me tonight.
If you serve me well,
then I'll call Martin tomorrow
to give you a helping hand.
Just so simple.
Think carefully!
We are leaving,
you pay good attention,
take good care of Cheung-dee.
If there is anything wrong,
you'll be in deep shit.
He will pay your dinner,
understand?
Yes, boss.
- Ruby, you'd better be smart.
- Got you!
Don't you worry that
I can't feed her well?
Boss, I saw Prince's fellows
going with Cheung-dee.
And Prince is staying with
Cheung-dee's woman.
Which motel do you like?
Let's go to your favorite one.
Start a cocaine party first
to warm us up, OK?
You creep!
What the hell? It's your man who
asked you to serve me.
Go home for your mom.
You bitch!
I can kill your man
just by one call.
Damn it! You'll regret for this.
Smart guy! Long time no see.
Where is Cheung-dee?
It's great!
Would you let me go first?
Let's talk! Let me go first, OK?
Please tell me where Cheung-dee is.
I've told you!
He went with my fellows,
but I don't know where he is.
You are not sincere enough!
This is very hot.
77292929, you'd better call him.
77292929?
Who is calling for Cheung-dee.
Prince! My number is 94938032.
This is Cheung-dee,
who is looking for me?
Where are you?
Where are my men?
They've gone.
Come to my place right now.
Where are you?
I'm staying at your turf,
you know that.
I'm informed that Crazy Ball
is looking for us, better be careful.
Save me!
Where is your turf?
What turf?
He told you about the turf?
I don't have any turf!
He cheated you!
You bastard!
How can I be nice to you?
I haven't lied.
- It'll kill you...
- No...
You ask for it.
I have no turf! He cheated you!
Don't trust him!
You love screwing women
by force, don't you?
Have you been screwed by force?
Tell Pao-wing and Uncle Fatty,
no matter what and no matter
how much it will cost,
get Crazy Ball to sleep
under my son's body!
Yes!
Freeze... Stay where you are!
Where is Crazy Ball? Tell me!
Crazy Ball, stay where you are!
Stay where you are!
Kill him!
Stop!
There! go
Do you want him go! Never!
You have finally shown up!
Freeze, police!
I've been an undercover next
to Chuen for one year.
I know you are a nice guy.
But this is my duty.
You've been a cop for 1 year &
I've been a rascal for 10 years.
You are really great!
You are bleeding badly!
I'm fine!
I don't want to see you like this.
- Let's call the ambulance.
- No! No!
I'm leaving,
I want to go to Mainland China.
Why do you come here?
I... After seeing you now.
I don't know
when I can see you again.
Come on!
You'd better go to the hospital, OK!
No...
- Please surrender yourself.
- No way!
I promised Tai-hung,
I can't go to jail.
But...
I know...
I come now...
Just want to make sure one thing.
What?
I would like ask one thing
which I haven't asked before.
Have you ever fallen for me?
I understand!
I just want to know the truth...
before my death...
You won't die. You can't die.
I can't find a way out, you know?
Why not surrender yourself?
No! No! I said I can't go to jail.
I have my way to set you free.
Stop!
You come to surrender yourself?
I come to report my presence.
After the bail, right?
You are not supposed
to confess now,
but what you said will
become evidence in court.
You are now under arrest.
You are suspected to kill a man
named Chan Kam-ball.
If you have enough evidence,
you can charge me.
But, I come for another thing.
You want to know
who is the man
behind the VCD factory?
I want to become the stain witness.
You just want to get the man
behind scene, right?
What are you doing here?
Interpols against drugs.
You need not say anything now.
But your words will
become evidence in court.
Sir, why do you arrest me?
We are investigating...
Sir, this isn't mine,
these are gifts sent by my friends.
Better talk to the judge.
- Take him back.
- Yes sir.
Pack up and take everything back.
Sir.
You claim this is a testimony?
Tell me how you worked
as an undercover.
I lost consciousness.
When I woke up,
I didn't remember what happened.
Tell me, how can I nail him
by this testimony?
Sir, my duty is
to tell you the truth.
I don't have to nail Cheung-dee Wai.
He'd be free from
the charge of drugs trafficking.
If we can't charge him
with murdering,
he can walk out
from court with pride,
do you see the point?
Sir, I'm sorry.
It's you.
How do you know I'm here.
You are not at home,
and you'll attend court tomorrow,
so you must be here
for some preparations.
But... I have much to do tonight.
Actually I cherish
very much about our love.
Can you stop defending for Wai?
We are going to court tomorrow.
No matter who will be the winner,
I know we can no longer
stay with each other.
I know.
Many things happened between us.
I don't want to know.
I just want to
marry you after this case.
Let's go back to Canada.
Michael, I've mentioned that for one year.
It's you who doesn't
want to get married.
- Now, I want it.
- But I don't.
I hope you'd consider it carefully.
Wai doesn't match you.
He will be killed
by foes sooner of later.
I know.
Please leave, I will think about it.
OK.
Sandy...
Be rational.
Court.
Detective Li, you are ordered
to be the undercover...
Chan Kam-ball,
nick named Crazy Ball...
Did you witness
how Chan was killed?
Or, did you reach the scene
after he was killed?
Did you see him face to face?
How could you tell that was Wai?
I have your medical report.
It states that you had
a stroke on that day.
So, you reported
to your boss something...
which you were not that sure.
You didn't see the guy
killing Chan Kam-ball.
Court adjourn now,
it'll be continues at 2:30.
Sandy, will Cheung-dee be guilty?
I'm not so optimistic.
I can't find any alibi to help him.
You should help him, please!
I will! I will try my best.
I wish I were the one being sued!
I don't want him to be in jail.
You really care!
We have been in love.
Really? How long?
About a month.
Don't worry,
I know what to do then.
Sandy, anything wrong?
I feel pressure.
I don't know what to say...
What pressure?
I feel that... no one can be trusted.
Any more witness that the defense
counsel would like to summon?
Your Honor, my I have a request?
Go ahead.
I'd like to stop defending for Wai,
because of a personal reason.
Are you sick? Do you worry that
we can't afford your fee?
Order.
Chan and Ma has hired
Mr. Wong Lik-kan
to take my place.
Your approval is
very much appreciated.
Because there is a change of
lawyer for the defendant.
The court is now adjourned.
It'll be continued
on June 6 at 10 a.m.
Court.
I would like to get off
anywhere ahead. Thanks.
If his head wasn't hit strongly,
theoretically speaking,
there is no harm to the brain.
Dr. Cheung, are you sure that
detective David Lee's memory...
will not be affected by that punch?
I can only say that the influence
may not be significant.
Your Honor, nothing further.
Both lawyers have finished
their cross examinations.
They will proceed
to their final address...
I'm sorry, Your Honor,
the defense counsel would
like to summon a new witness.
Objection.
The witness listed
have all been cross examinated.
Your Honour,
this witness is very influential.
She provides very important
alibi to my client.
Please come here.
What reason makes you
summon this new witness?
And, what will she say?
OK, your request is approved.
I, sandy Leung,
swear that I would...
tell everything that's true...
Miss Sandy Leung,
on May 10, 1998.
Where were you in the afternoon?
I was at home.
Who did you stay with?
Chueng-dee Wai,
the accused of this case.
The whole afternoon?
To be exact, two days!
From May 9th to May 10th.
We haven't left my apartment.
So, what were you doing at home?
We're studying a case in which
he is charged with drugs trafficking.
He has become
the stained witness now.
He was dispensed with any charge.
Why did you stay 48 hours
at home to study the case?
Wai is my client,
and he is my boyfriend too.
Why didn't you choose to be the
witness from the very beginning?
Because my ex-boyfriend is on
the side of the prosecutor.
I don't want to disclose the
affair between Wai and me.
But until now, I have got no choice.
That means, during the 48 hours,
Wai and you didn't
leave the apartment.
Yes, in these two days,
all the meals were cooked by me.
Order...
You said she didn't
cook anything to you.
First,
the jury had to consider
a very important question.
That is, whether you believe
the witness Sandy Leung or not.
If yes, the accused
should be pleaded not guilty.
You need not consider the evidence
provided by the prosecutor.
If you don't believe Sandy Leung,
you should consider all possible
doubtful points stated,
and grant all benefits
to the accused...
and to reach a verdict beneficial
to the accused.
Jury, have you reached any verdict?
Your Honor,
we have reached
an unanimous verdict that,
Mr. Wai is pleaded not guilty.
Mr. Cheung-dee Wai
is pleaded not guilty,
he is acquitted at once.
Court adjourn.
Wai, you fell happy now?
Do you think I've ruined her?
I'm impressed that
she is very much fond of you.
What are you laughing at?
What will you do next?
I just want to say sorry.
What I have done is
what you've planned.
Ball and Prince died.
Uncle Mei was put behind bars.
Michael has lost faith and face.
You've got what you want, right?
Now, you need not go to jail.
I'm so happy to know that Tai-hung
won't have a prisoner daddy.
Give me a chance.
I have had a careful consideration,
it's not possible.
Even we stay together,
we'll separate 1 or 2 years later.
For some time,
I really really loved you.
But such feeling...
I know it won't exist again.
Why not leave us a happy memory?
When we get old,
it will still be sweet.
Cheung-dee, after this glance,
go back to take good care
of Tai-hung and Ruby.
After this glance,
I will never look back.