In the early Ching Dynasty,
Emperor "Ti-chao" suddenly fell ill,
And would die any time
It is believed that there is
a strange flower on Mount "Shin Fung"
It blooms every twenty years
This flower can bring
a dying man back to life,
change white hair into black
The court decided to send people
to the mountain to look for this flower
Mount "Shin Fung"
I, Chief Yeh Li Nieh Tang of Ching,
have come specially
to visit you Mr. Cho of Wu Tang
His majesty is now indisposed
They say your flower can bring...
a dying man back to life
What time is it now?
Still 4 hours before the blossom
I mean the year?
It's now exactly 10 years
since the foundation of Ching
Ten years
You may leave!
Sir, only if your flower
can revive His Majesty,
the Court will reward you handsomely
This flower is not for you
Cho Yi-hang, hear what our General said?
Who ranks higher than His Majesty?
A woman, in my eyes
I waited for her for a decade
I wonder if she knew
my master was the Chief
of the 8 clans in Chung Yuan,
and Priest Tzu Yang of Wu Tang
He often told me...
about the underworld
love-hate relationship
In his words, all the clans are bad
except the 8 big clans
Yi-hang, remember
there's always controversy
between good and evil
Yes, master
I answered him the same always
Have you mastered Moon-Breaking sword...
I taught you?
Yes, completely
Yi-hang
Concentrate by combining heart
and sword into one
Draw!
The sword protects the body
from being soiled by petals
Heart-piercing stab!
Master, I've already come up
to such a level
Can I have a few days' rest now?
Learning is unlimited
Continue if you wish to become
the future Chief of the swordplay world
In fact, I've never cherished
such an ambition
But, occasionally...
I resort to chivalrous acts!
I should've let you be captured
by those rascals
To save you,
I don't now even know where I am
Oh, no,
Master will reprimand me for sure
I've been afraid of 2 things
since childhood
Thunderbolt and...
Hsiao Yang,
time for you to repay a favor now
I'm leaving. Take care!
Help...
Master, help, master...
Sister, brother, help!
Uncle Pai Yun, help!
Desperate!
Help! I don't want to die! Help...
Master, help me... master, help me...
I can't believe it
There're really miracles in this world
At that moment, I really wanted
to get to her and say "thanks"
Have a clearer look at her face
But...
I was really too tired
When I knew him,
he was only an ordinary officer
Unexpectedly,
he later became Gen Wu San-kuei
who changed the history of Chung Yuan
This time you're lucky
Next time I'm not sure
if you'd be as lucky
I'm sober while the others are all drunk
Come on!
Come again if you've the nerve!
I enjoy company with him
because I can do anything prohibited
by Master
Come on!
Yi-hang
Fear not accusations
from a thousand fingers
if you're innocent
A life under others' influence
means no life
It's as good as dead!
Have you grasped what I said?
Never knew a furious man...
could be so kind-hearted
Sometimes I doubt if he was nice to me
only because...
I'm an orphan!
Cho Yi-hang
You stole a sheep from farmer
Ho Tor-niu's home 1-17
Do you plead guilty or not?
He stole my sheep and
gave me a swollen face. Look
I meant to save it...
from getting butchered
Master told us to be chivalrous
And they wouldn't
even let go a small sheep
Do you plead guilty to hurting Tor-niu?
He called me beast and creep
I should've fed him with dog shit
What's so funny?
Chief, as a disciple of Wu Tang and
an heir to Chief, what Cho Yi-hang did
is a disgrace to the clan and
Wu Tang's reputation
In fact, Uncle Pai Yun is not bad,
but he's overambitious
He wants to have his daughter succeed...
as the Chief against tradition
So I'm his eyesore
Calligraphy like swordplay
calls for stamina
He's my brother Lu Hsing-cheng
For any clans...
stamina comes
from the brush and strength
Practice energy with spirit
Move the brush with energy
Waist more erect than brush
Raise wrist
Arm like a dragon
Sister is late
Sorry, dad!
Sit down now!
Practice calligraphy now
Cho Yi-hang, copy 500 times
to atone for your mistake
I already knew it
Never be perverted by poverty
She's my sister Ho Lu-hua
Didn't you notice she often smiled at me
And she passed food for me
to eat to cheer me
It means however rich you're,
you must restrain yourself
Yield not to prowess
It means no submission
to powerful influence
Understand?
Cho Yi-hang, don't abandon yourself
only because the Chief spoils you
Look at them, writing without eating
You eating buns here?
Follow your sister: still as a virgin,
crafty as a rabbit
You're carefree and an idle eater
I know sister is clever
The brothers are all at puberty
You, an elder brother,
are naughty yourself
You frolicked while learning
Do you admit guilty?
And in Feb you came personally down...
to kill Kaifeng constable
Fang Tien-cheng
Do you plead guilty or not?
No
Uncle Pai Yun, I stabbed him once only
Why call it "Kill"?
What manner is that?
Right
What's the penalty
for a Wu Tang disciple?
Isn't it agains propriety?
You admit everything then?
I admitted I killed a lackey, but...
With the proof here,
don't argue any more
I have nothing to say now
But that lousy mandarin's folks do!
Uncle
Ladies and gentlemen,
don't misunderstand swordsman Cho
My son was to blame and he deserved it
Yes! Yes!
Luckily swordsman Cho helped me
Otherwise,
that bastard would've raped me
He even tried to kill my daughter!
Thank you swordsman Cho for your help
Thanks...
Get up...
Silence in the palace
Thank you...
Pai Yun, what wrong did my pupil do
to have troubled the presence
of you 8 elders?
In the name of the Chief's adopted pupil
Cho ran rougshod and
bullied other clans' pupils
With proof and the witnesses here,
he can't deny it
Yi-hang, what have you to say?
Chief, they're the descendants
of the 6 big clans
If I alone could beat them all 6,
it means Wu Tang's more powerful
in martial arts
On this score I admit!
Shut up!
Brother has hit the nail on the head!
Quiet!
Ma Yu of Kung Tung,
did Cho injure you?
No, overexercise brought me this
And you, Liu Cheng of Tien Chuang?
How did you get your wound?
I injured myself while playing!
How do you explain your wounds?
I dropped into the well
getting water out of it!
I was pursued by a tiger!
I was only joking
Get down! All stuff and nonsense!
You!
I wounded him because he wouldn't pay
at Wan Chun brothel
You
You hogged others' farmland in
conspiracy with bureaucracy, didn't you?
And you
You bullied a scholar
with your martial arts...
Cho Yi-hang!
Yes!
You came down
without the master's permission
Now face the Buddha (in the palace)
and repent
without drinking for 3 days
Yes!
Aren't you tired of this?
Always putting on airs!
You see me
whenever you think of me, right?
Hungry? Let me get you something to eat
Thank you
So you don't mind
even such coarse food as buns!
They're nice! Eat!
Cho...
Cho,
we didn't mean to testify
against you this morning
Priest Pai Yun forced us to!
Yes...
Would you bear us grudge?
No, I forgot everything already!
Thank you...
Next time remember to pay at the brothel
Yes...
Cho, try red kaoliang of Shansi
Good
Cut it out!
Can't you see...
he's carrying sister's 2 big buns?
Don't you know
this is the palace of Wu Tang?
Wine and meat, you may ruin me! Get out!
Get out quick!
What about me?
You, too!
I'll go back to retire
You stay to sleep with brother
What are you doing?
This jade heirloom came from my dad
Keep it and
promise not to break it
Stay!
What are you doing?
I need it
Help me to hold on first
Brother!
Right, it's now time for us to
serve our country
Kill rascals and remove evils! Kill!
Yes!
Brother!
Stealing military supplies is
a serious crime. You may get beheaded!
People in our tribe get beheaded
for plucking the weed only!
Dying of struggle is better than
starving to death
Come here. There's something to eat
Don't fight! Everybody has a share!
Let me do it if you can't
How dare you lay hands
on the Ming Court's provisions?
Kill!
Darling, are you alright?
I can't hold on. I must deliver
Don't...!
Darling, come out quick!
Kill these beggars!
I'll kill you, demon
I'll chop you to 8 pieces
Exactly 8 pieces
Run quick!
Darling, bear with it
Darling, it hurts badly!
I must deliver
There's light in front
Let's go and seek help. Come quick!
No one is around
It hurts badly!
Swordsman, we didn't steal!
Don't kill us!
I didn't steal! Don't kill us!
Darling...
Darling, are you alright?
Swordsman, can you deliver?
Please help us
To help you deliver?
To help us deliver, we beg you!
Darling bear with it
Darling, what now?
Can you deliver? Please do us a favor
Darling, we've got help!
Darling, harder!
Harder, harder, darling!
Darling!
Darling...
Darling, we have gone
through the most difficult times,
why do you leave us at this moment?
Don't be sad!
A son has hope
Keep it to run a small business. Come
Get out of here!
Swordsman! Thank you, swordsman!
Who are you?
Why are you following me?
Miss,
you bring us closer yourself
Right! It's better to keep
a distance between us
Whoever sees me shall be blinded!
Do I have to perish
having seen your whole body?
Miss, control your temper!
Oh, I forgot to tell you I'm Cho Yi-hang
Chief of the cult, killing ensures peace
Today
Our chief bodyguard sent an Army
to wipe out many lackeys
We want to let them know
that our tribesmen are not ants...
under their soles
The chief bodyguard frightens demons
through blood practice
Those old people of Chung Yuan's 8 clans
are too old even to hold a sword
All they know is to pay lip service only
They pay lip service
to bewitch the masses
They not only plan to unite Chung Yuan
but to dig out our ancestors' graves
What a nuisance
Only if...
we wipe out those old leaders,
the 8 clans of Chung Yuan
will be dissolved
Wipe out the beasts!
Increase my longevity
Why is it so icy the whole night?
We've been hiding 20 years
waiting for this day!
Now is the time to return a favor
Kill them for me!
Your heart's beating hard!
Let me feel it
Have you finished ordering?
What's so funny?
Buddy, you look so pitiable!
Having hardened her wings,
you've no right to touch them!
True love is mutual
I'll wait for you!
Right, compulsory love has no happiness
Priest Tzu Yang,
the cult is getting more powerful
in Manchuria
It may menace the safety
of the people of Ming
As the Chief of 8 clans,
you should contribute some effort!
Chi Wu-shuang appears again
The underworld is again rife
with witchcraft
We must wipe out the cult
before it come to power
They're not so easy to wipe out!
I hear they're quite powerful
in martial arts
Chief,
we shouldn't have
let that traitor go that year
No point mentioning the past!
We must decide immediately
which clan will lead the expedition
What's your opinion?
As the Chief of 8 clans,
Wu Tang should do!
Right
Right you are
Hsin Cheng
Why, master?
Where's Yi-hang?
Where have you been?
Master is meeting with the 7 clans
on how to cope with the cult
Halt! What about the jade I gave you?
Why ask me about it now?
Where's the jade?
Why did you give it to someone else?
I feel he needs it more than I do
I'll kill him. So you don't need him
Brother, master wants you
Sorry, Chief, I'm late!
Yi-hang, the 8 clans have decided
to send troops to suppress the cult
and you'll be in command
Chief, this is a herculean task
I'm afraid I'm not equal to it
Wu Tang is full of personalities
Why have you only him in mind, Chief?
Have you got a better choice?
I venture to suggest
my daughter Lu-hua...
as the best choice
Right
Sister is brilliant and
a fast swordswoman
None's better suited than her
as the commander
Oh, no, it's against the rule
Do you agree?
Right!
What's your opinion?
Chief,
how can a female undertake
such a heavy assignment?
Yi-hang
A military order is as rigid as a
mountain and you can't go against rules
You command the 8 clans' pupils...
with Lu-hua as your side
Set out by night
Your order is understood
Yi-hang, I've covered you up
in the presence of the 8 clans
Why go against me?
Master, master!
Listen
I spent years' efforts
teaching you kung fu,
hoping you may succeed me...
as the Chief of the 8 clans...
after my death
I know that as the Chief
to lead the masses
I must do many things against my will
Right!
So a kind heart is a defect
Kind heart?
Listen, if some day
Chi Wu-shuang wants to suppress Wu Tang,
can you ask her to spare us?
And if some day
we unite Chung Yuan and
must kill all hans,
can you use your heart to move them?
This is the so-called underworld rule
So you have no choice
Yes, I do
I may quit the underworld
Quit the underworld?
Easily said than done
Listen,
what else can you do besides kung fu?
Returning home to till the land?
The Chief himself has promised to
relinquish his post to you
All the 8 clans
have been eyeing this post
You take no interest, but I do
Child,
take a longer sight
If you really become the Chief,
we can join forces
Quite possibly we may even change
Ming's territory
General, we've again caught
some foreign spies
Chop!
Yes! Chop!
We're innocent...
Uncle Kuei, why did you...
Given present circumstances,
killing 100 wrongly is
better than letting one go
The cult tries to cover
the eyes and ears of the world and
the Manchus are getting
increasingly rampant
Our duty as military men is
to protect the territory
and kill them all
Yi-hang, remember,
heroes make the times!
Why is brother still not here?
Let's not wait for Yi-hang any more
Better plan how to deploy...
to cope with the cult
But Chi Wu-shuang's advance
in martial arts
and we're in the dark
about the cult's surroundings
Such a move is too dangerous
Let Kung Tung clan back out...
if it prefers
I don't think our 7-clan coalition...
can't cope with Wu-shuang
And the wolf girl?
And we have Wu Tang's
72 cyclical swords
And Hua Shan clan's...
7 Fatal Arrays
Shut up, I know
And O-Mei clan's dragon-tiger
conquering skills
And Kun Lun's fantastic
King Kong swordplay
If we stab her unawares
Let alone a wolf girl,
even a dragon girl
may be chopped by us... into minces
Elders
Let me ask you a question
Foreign tribes bear us on grudge
Why kill them?
Brother
You want to kill?
Let me ask you
Have you heard of the sounds of a sword
chopped on human body or bones?
Cho Yi-hang,
as the commander of the 8 clans
you speak baldy to disrupt
the Army morale
You were ambitious to spread your name
So you're most suited...
for the commander post
Patrolling at this late hour?
It's freezing!
Something in front must be wrong
Nobody!
Are you drunk? Only a tree!
Brother...
Wake up, brother
Sister, isn't it against the rule?
He's against the rule
He got drunk in defiance of discipline
and even forsook his emblem
How is he to answer to master
on return to Wu Tang?
Men of the cult are here!
Where are they?
Here
Be alert!
Form an array
Bleeding, I'll die for sure
Only a bruise!
Stop!
Are you crazy? I'm not an enemy
Miss
Know me?
In the ancient city,
I must kill you, a Chung Yuan native
Come on
Cho Yi-hang
Don't move
Don't blame me
It would be too late
if I didn't help you now
In my view
he may have been bewitched by that witch
I don't think it's as simple as that
That witch even spared his life
and followed him
They exchanged glances and
might have been intimate
Shut up!
How can one bewitched by a wolf girl
command Chung Yuan to fight foreigners?
Brother, you'd better reconsider...
a more suitable candidate
Shut up! Bring him back quickly
and let him explain to me personally
Brother, don't! Retire now!
Girls? I can give you 100...
much better than she?
No, I want her!
Are you out of your mind?
That bitch helped us
kill so many Chung Yuan men
Can she get away?
I must let her know...
she brought me the agony
Any agony can't compare
to our expulsion...
by that old Tzu Yang traitor
20 years ago
Chi Wu-shuang
You two got twisted...
by the cult
and brought mess
to the Chung Yuan swordplay world
Expelling your family
without killing you...
you're lucky
Kill them...
Quiet, chiefs!
These 2 rats are much condemned
for their crime
But as an orthodox clan,
we mustn't go too far
Chi Wu-shuang, we'll give you a chance
As of today,
don't ever set foot on Chung Yuan
Brother, we shouldn't cherish
any feeling for anyone
We must hate him, control him
We adopted the wolf girl to
utilize her to kill...
all Chung Yuan scoundrels only
She's merely our killing instrument
Remember that, understand?
Only we've friends
you can't afford to lose
Get out!
You're the most despicable
Why follow me? I don't want you
You don't want me? You must!
I want wolf girl...
No one would want you...
the way you look
How come there's a word 'Lien' on you?
I only know it's my surname
I have no name
Everybody should have a name
I've been living with wolves
from childhood!
Chi Wu-shuang adopted me and
brought me to the cult
She taught me kung fu and
made me her killing instrument
Let me give you a name
Lien...
Lien Wu-kung (practice martial arts)?
Lien Wu-kung?
I remember now,
when I first saw you,
you were standing...
on the mountain-top
and glittered with your dress reflected
by the moonlight
You should be named Lien Ni-chang
Lien Ni-chang?
Let's get out of the underworld together
Don't you begrudge Wu Tang?
Don't you begrudge the post of Chief?
The underworld doesn't belong to us
Let them fight for it
What would you do if
I should grow old
with silver hair years later?
Don't worry
Have you heard of a fabulous flower
blossoming each 2 decades that,
once taken can bring eternal life?
If you should go silver-haired,
I'll bring the elixir to you
by any means
Promise me, promise me
What?
Don't ever distrust me
I hate people who do
I swear
I swear under Heaven
I would be condemned
if I should ever let Lien Ni-chang down
Why? Why let me down?
Speak up
Don't get excited!
Adopt another wild one...
from a wolf lair
and woo her when she grows up
The only worry is your kung fu
would've been disabled then
Shut up!
I expended so much effort on you
Can this be done away with?
Once I decide on the course to take,
I won't turn back
Is this your excuse...
for leaving the cult?
What do you want?
You knew what my brother wants
Only if you let me leave the cult
you may do anything you like
Brother, no point licking all over her
Her heart is already somebody else's
You picked a junk
I've been your twin for such a long time
and you don't even know
a female's normal reaction
You're getting out of your mind
Have you given it to others?
Did you follow that Wu Tang scoundrel
when you last disappeared?
He's not a scoundrel! He's Cho Yi-hang
What has he given you?
A name
I'm now Lien Ni-chang, not a wolf girl
Everybody should've a name on birth
Brother, what a common name
So she wants only to be a common person
Lien Ni-chang
You want to be a common person
Now leave the cult like a commoner
Uncle Kuei then became...
a General he dreamt of
Only then did I sense the meaning of
what he said to me in Shanhaikwan
Never expected that a hero that claimed
to wipe out foreign tribesmen
would've let the Ching troops in
at this juncture
Undress
Go
Hell with you!
Remember,
don't use your martial arts
Love, thy spell is irresistible
Shut up!
Stop!
As I said, none can pass this
Can I leave now?
Yes
Sister, your bridal dress
Cho Yi-hang
Traitor Wu San-kuei led
the Ching troops into the pass
At a time
when the Ming empire is critical
and needs men to defend its territory
you're having a tryst...
with a rival
Ni-chang and I have both decided
to quit the underworld
Yi-hang, so you'd rather
let your name stink in history...
because of that witch
You may leave
Goddamn disciple
You betray the one closest to you!
Brother, in any case,
considering the master's upbringing,
you should return
to explain everything to him
Hold it!
Since you left, the Chief seldom spoke
I think he's really peevish this time
Think carefully how to explain to him
What's wrong?
The master's body...
Where's the master's body?
Find it! Find it now!
Yes
Uncle... Uncle
Brother
Chief
Hsin Cheng! Hsin Cheng
Brother
Hsin Cheng
It hurts badly
Hsin Cheng, tell me who did it?
Who did it? Tell me!
Tell me now. Hsin Cheng! Who did it?
While you were away,
the wolf girl brought men to kill us
Never thought Wu Tang
would end up this way!
She didn't do it!
What?
She was brought up by a wolf,
she must be brutal
You brought rack and
tuin to Wu Tang
Why don't you wake up?
Cho Yi-hang, wake up
I've come to see Cho Yi-chang
Witch, to see him
after resorting to killing?
What?
Lu-hua
Damn witch
Let's go
We only want to ask you one question
Did you do it?
Their death is not linked to me
All I want to know now is
will you follow me?
Why did you do that?
Why?
Don't let her get away!
Kill this witch!
Why don't you trust me?
Don't ever distrust me
I hate people who do
I swear
I swear under Heaven
I would be condemned
if I should ever let Lien Ni-chang down
The witch is possessed. Kill her!
Ni-chang
She's dead
Yi-hang
Come here, come here
Master
Yi-hang, why didn't you take...
my advice all these years
but go against me in every way?
Yi-hang, you're doing me an injustice
for bringing Wu Tang to such a state
Master, I...
Idiot
Congratulations on your match
May you have a long and happy union
You may die tragically
Come out
Come out!
Brother, why take
such an attitude towards me?
Watch out!
What have you got to take away my girl?
You want to know?
Brother, gouge out
that bitch's heart for me
Come out
What are you waiting for?
Kill her! Kill her!
Kill her!
Hear me? Kill her!
Come on quick!
Why don't you kill her? Kill her!
Brother! Never knew...
you'd be stung by your own conscience
So it's great sleeping this way
Ni-chang