Up! Up!
Hurry!
Don't push!
Up the tree, quickly!
Pull him down quickly. Quickly!
Catch the flag.
Wait.
Don't let him get down!
Hurry!
Careful!
Calm down!
The winner this year is...
Ai Bak Tim!
Sawadee everyone...
from Ban Nong Pradoo.
We are gathering for good merit at this festival,
to give robes to the monks, and Ong-Bak,
who is the protective icon for the well-being of our village.
This festival...
is to remind us that...
in 7 days we will be...
celebrating Ong-Bak.
The last time...
being 24 years ago.
This means...
all prosperity will return to us once more.
Where is the amulet?
It's not good.
There is a little damage...
Not quite perfect.
200,000 baht for this is not cheap.
Why don't you want to sell it?
Ow! How much do you want?
Don. I'm not selling.
Ow! Why did you change your mind?
I came a long way from Bangkok just for this.
I've never given you any promise...
to sell it to you.
I want to give this to my son, Bak Hum Lae,
the day he's ordained here as a monk, for Ong-Bak.
Call me whenever you want to sell it.
No, no. I don't have a telephone.
I'll give you my address,
so whenever you want to sell,
you can write to me.
Is this good enough, grandma?
I made it for Ai Tim for his ordination.
It's good.
Where did Ai Tim come from,
and how come he grew up in the temple?
He's now a man.
Ai Tim is an orphan.
He was left at the temple by someone...
when he was a baby.
Pra Kroo took pity on him,
and adopted him.
And everyone says...
he has grown up well under Ong-Bak.
Hitting the earth!
Crocodile whipping tail!
Confronting elephant!
Hanuman (Monkey) giving ring.
The threatening fight.
The rear kick.
Both elbows attacking...
followed with high knee.
Raising the army.
Getting high strength.
Cutting through the enemy.
Avoiding danger.
Putting your head down.
Knight throwing an axe.
Wave smashing the shore.
Meet friend, join friend.
Knight catching monkeys.
Breaking the joins.
Snake chasing lizard.
Cliff shaking.
Sticky water.
Throwing the spear.
Breaking the sword.
Raising the body.
Horse replacing bird.
I'll teach you all these styles...
but I forbid you to use them for money.
Do you understand, Bak Tim?
I understand, Pra Kroo.
Good.
He has gone.
You said you understood. Really?
There is a story that...
Pra Kroo learnt this boxing...
from the ancient books.
Then Pra Kroo wanted a challenge.
He went into the boxing ring for money...
and he hit his opponent to death.
He felt very guilty,
so he became a monk.
Thai boxing is very dangerous.
I don't want you to use it,
unless it is absolutely necessary.
Understand?
Or are you still not clear?
Come, fight with me.
Ai Bak, here.
- Uncle!
- Come on!
Who is there? What are you doing?
Hurry!
Bak Don...
is the one that cut off the head of Ong-Bak.
He took all the donation money too, Pra Kroo.
Bak Don! Evil son!
If Pra Ong-Bak has no head,
our village will be faced with disaster.
Calm down. Calm down!
We must try to get Ong-Bak's head back...
to our village before the ceremony day.
Where can we find it, Pra Kroo?
I will bring Ong-Bak back here myself.
Who knows where Bak Don is?
The hopes of the people of Ban Nong Pradoo Sukon...
are in your hands.
In this tube is a holy herbal medicine.
My teacher told me...
it belonged to Kroo Dum.
Keep it with you.
This is the address of Bak Don.
And this is a letter to Bak Hum Lae.
Tim, you must return with Ong-Bak...
to our village.
This is the money for your journey.
All my hopes are with you.
My mom gave me this ring before she died.
Warn, please look after grandma.
We've all contributed together...
for the fares.
He's losing.
Hey! What bike you using to race?
Why did you lose so easily like this?
Hey! Why are you speaking that way?
Win or lose is normal in any bet.
It isn't fair to blame me.
Why did you use a woman to race with me?
Why not?
What's wrong with being a woman?
Ow! You dare race against me!
You cow!
If you rode as fast as your mouth, you'd probably win!
Hey! Hey!
Hey! Why don't you pay me in cash?
You bet me with drugs, didn't you?
You told me it was okay to use drugs instead of cash.
Okay.
I'll give you only 10,000...
after deducting the 10,000 you owe me.
I pay you interest every month,
and the loan is not yet due.
Can't you give me all the money now?
Do you want it or not?
Okay. Better than nothing.
Hey! Give me all of that.
What!
Give me!
You've already got my money.
Can't you give a few tablets to my friends?
You can find this drug anywhere...
you don't have to take mine.
Better not to use my drugs.
They're too strong.
Your friends may go into shock.
Believe me.
Huh?
Son of a bitch!
Eh! You're back at last. My money!
Give me my share quickly. Quickly!
Ai Keng caught me.
He knew we bet with fake drugs.
He took all the money back.
What? Don't tease me...
It's not funny at all.
Muey, look at my face.
Do you think I kicked myself?
Damn!
Oy! Why are you poking me?
I'm still in pain.
Oh, well. How come you got caught?
Forget it!
Do you have 200 baht?
What!?
You lost all my share and still asking me for my money?
Listen, Muey...
When I won, you took the money.
Now I've lost, so you must share the loss too.
Ow! You're stupid to get caught,
and lose the money in your hands.
So I'm stupid and you're clever!
Ai Keng gave me only 3 days.
If I don't pay back his loan he'll hit me. Hit me!
Ai Hum Lae?
Is it really you, Ai Hum Lae?
Hi.
Er... Muay, is he your friend? Your friend?
How could he be my friend?
He is calling you, isn't he?
Do you know him?
Remember me?
I'm Bak Tim from Ban Nong Pradoo.
Hey! Fool! I don't know you.
Fool! Understand!
I've just told you I don't know you!
But I know you, Ai Hum Lae.
Hum Lae? Hum what!?
What a stupid name! Hum Lae!
Bad luck! I warn you... you're fool.
Ow! No need to lie! Ai Hum Lae... Oops...
Sorry! Slip of my tongue.
Mind your own business.
Get out of my sight! Out!
Okay. You said you were from... Ban? Which?
Ban Nong Pradoo.
That's it. Ban Nong Pradoo.
Okay, I'm leaving.
So you're both from Ban Nong Pradoo.
You can have a good chat!
Very funny! You've made your point!
Go! Go away! But give me the money first.
Here! For your medicine.
I'm going now, Ai Hum Lae.
Listen, peasant!
You should return to your hometown.
Go!
Ai Hum Lae, I have to give you a letter.
I told you I don't know you! Get out!
This is my place.
Don't be angry with me. Close the door.
Don't let mosquitos in.
I'm in a bad mood and depressed.
Ai Hum Lae...
Our villagers are in serious trouble...
because Bak Don stole the head of Ong-Bak.
The Chief sent me here to see you,
so you can help me to find Ong-Bak.
I have Bak Don's address.
No need to talk yet,
and put your things down here.
You better have a wash first.
Go. Go now!
Here. Here is the washroom.
Go in.
I don't have any other clothing.
Don't worry I'll give you my towel.
Go in. Go!
I'll turn on the light for you.
Soap is on your left, toothbrush on your right.
Mind the slippery floor.
Hello! Muay!
I'll meet you at the stadium...
the boxing stadium. Okay.
Do you still accept the bet?
Do I have time?
Yes.
Here! All of them!
Do you have the amulet?
The chief changed his mind and didn't want to sell, Boss.
But I have the head of Ong-Bak, Boss.
This is the most holy thing in the village...
The thing that they all worship, and the most valuable.
This broken head...
Why did you bring it to me?
I'm not interested. Take it away!
My head is hurting enough without...
you spoiling my mood.
Today, Captain seems to have little to please him.
Look at your fighter, Pearl Harbour.
I think he's losing to Arun, my fighter,
with his Kamikaze technique.
Defeat's certain!
I don't have the money yet...
still trying to get some.
I'm not asking for money.
I can find that myself.
Now you're selling drugs too!
Yes.
My fighter will win the next competition.
If you think you will win,
then why not increase your bet?
Any sum you like!
You need not preach to me.
You don't really understand me.
Just because of one stinking male...
you turn yourself into this low-life.
Muay! You're not my mom!
Because we have no parents,
you've become this bad.
Yes, a bad person like me,
who has brought you up until now.
From now on,
a good person like you should leave me alone.
Yes, tell me whenever you want it.
Strike, strike.
Knock out.
Get up and hit back.
Yesss...
The next one is coming.
Tell me if you still want to bet.
The winner is... Pearl Harbour.
Damn!
Pearl Habour is the Number One.
Two wins two minutes.
Where are all my things?
What?
My money bag. Where is it?
I don't know. I didn't take it.
Him.
Two and one...
Oh! A fresh challenger.
Taking bets now, taking bets now.
Aw... How come that peasant is in the fighting ring?
Yeh... Ai Tim is surely dead.
I'll give you 10 to 1.
But you'd better not dare to bet.
Okay.
I'll bet one million, if you'll dare to accept it.
I accept.
I'm not here to box. I want the money.
Calm down, I'll give you the money later.
Start!
We have a new champion tonight.
What's your name?
Tim from Ban Nong Pradoo.
Tim Pradoo Prew!
Prize for the winner!
I don't want it.
I only want my money bag, there.
What an idiot!
Hey! Hey! Why don't you take the prize money?
Why are you so stupid?
Tell me if you want to fight again.
You have the skill to win.
I can see lots of money... lots and lots.
You ask me to fight for money.
Ai Hum Lae...
Why did you steal the villagers' money
to play gambling?
For the investment...
To get enough money to help you find Ong-Bak.
- You really want to help me?
- Yes.
This is Don's address.
Could you take me there?
Keep it. I'll take you there later.
Now could you give me some money.
Give me... for the investment.
When I make a profit, I will pay you back...
and I'll go anywhere you want.
Absolutely sure!
Go! Go away! Damn you!
Peasant! Can't talk to you, stupid!
Huh! Where will he sleep tonight?
I don't care! Or he can sleep with you!
You're crazy!
What shall I do? Ai Keng will kill me.
Muay! Take these drugs to sell in Yai Lao's den.
When we have enough money,
I will pay you back.
I'm sure to earn money.
I know this place well.
After the last one,
you still haven't learnt anything.
I told you before,
I don't want to sell drugs.
You must help me out.
I don't want to be hit again.
Okay?
Yeah. Yeah... I will try.
But it'll have to be tomorrow.
Okay. Now I feel much better.
You don't have to look so happy.
From the takings,
you'll get 30, but I'll get 70.
Muay! 50/50.
70/30.
50/50.
The money you asked for starting your business in Bangkok...
I don't have it.
Because we had a very dry season,
and Ong-Bak's head was stolen by Ai Don.
Dad wishes that you help Bak Tim
to find and return Ong-Bak to us...
and save us from disaster.
What nonsense!
Warn! The pool is dry.
Where are we going to find drinking water?
I pray to have Ong-Bak back with us soon, please.
Ai Rung, are you alone?
Ai Piew, are you betting?
Brother, I'm here.
Damn Ai Yod.
Where have you been for months?
I had to see my friends.
You are fully aware that I'm short of staff!
Assist me first. Hurry!
Not now. I have to meet a friend.
Don't make an excuse. Help me now.
Not today. Some other day.
No, now. Quickly!
Take it.
Go away. You deal cards badly.
Put down your bets now.
At your age you should stay at home,
looking after your children.
What are you looking at? Get out!
Go to that desk...
And change your hair colour, too.
The colour that suits me,
and you have to copy it.
Put down your bets... to lose, to lose.
Betting and losing is not my fault.
Turn the cards.
19 and 19 both hands.
Pay the money.
More bets down. Bet, bet.
Here's mine.
Do you have money?
Here it is. 3,000 real money.
You want to play? You will lose...
all your money and your belongings.
- I bet 200.
- Okay, 200.
No card swapping.
Oh! 18 points.
- Pay the money.
- Wait... mine is 19. Pay me!
This is 400.
- Ai has only 6 points, 1 card.
- Mine is 9.
- 8 points 3 cards.
- 9 points.
What sort of cards are these?
She's lucky.
- It's luck. Good luck.
- 9 points.
- 8 points again.
- 9 points again.
Damn cards, take it.
8 points again.
Got you. Pay!
- Damn! 8 points again.
- 9 to beat you.
These cards are impossible.
I must check if she is cheating.
She got all 9 points for 15 games.
Took most of my money.
Why do you pay her?
I want to see if you will get 9 again.
You're cheating me, bitch!
I know I got 8 without turning the cards.
Points? If 9...
I'm certain that you cheat.
Look! Loser! She got 4 points.
I don't believe it.
I'm sure that she concealed some cards.
I want to search her.
Wait... Calm down!
You should search her.
Hey! Do you hide some cards?
- No, I don't.
- Let's see.
There are none, I told you.
Any hidden in your bag?
Let me check her myself.
Don't trouble yourself.
Come here!
Okay, you can go.
You've got to search her everywhere.
All done, everywhere. You can go. Go now!
Don't come back here again, bitch!
Winning every game like that is bad for my place.
Let's continue. We can beat these people.
No point to win, they're all broke.
Broke! Broke!
She won all their money. Nothing left.
Don't you have a go at me.
Total 8,000. I give your 3,000 back.
Why is it only 3,000?
You won't need so much anyway.
What? No profit for me at all.
Er... You take this money first.
Don't spend too much.
Give me another 1,000.
3,000 is enough for you.
This will merely cover my college fees.
Hey! Seem to have a lot of money.
That guy is here.
Lend me your money.
- This is my money.
- Er... I'll pay you back.
Will pay you back.
Hi! I was on my way to pay you,
but you beat me to it. Here!
That is my money.
What?
8,000. I'll give you the rest later.
Don't look at me so menacingly.
I'm not bothered too much about the rest of the money.
But when you two try to cheat me,
I can't forget!
- Hold him! Beat him!
- No, I won't fight you.
Ai Tim! Ai Tim!
- I won't fight. I won't fight.
- Help! Help!
You cheated me, here!
You want trouble?
Here's some!
Will be seeing you!
I have to thank you, Ai Tim.
And I will help you to find Ong-Bak.
Could you fight one more time?
Wait... Listen to me first.
You saw just a minute ago. They beat me.
If I don't pay them, they will kill me.
Could you help me?
One last fight for me.
Okay. It doesn't matter anyway.
Stupid peasant!
Stupid village, stupid villagers!
Relying on only one boxer...
to find and return Ong-Bak to their village.
Are you crazy?
If Ong-Bak is so powerful,
why let a thief cut his head off?
It's only made from pieces of stone and earth.
Box me! Why box me?
You are from the same village.
Don't kill each other.
He boxed me!
Never mind that! There!
The people you want to kill are over there!
Ai Peng! Haven't you had enough?
You want a kick to send you to sleep?
Umm... You have too many.
Ai Yod. You know very well what to do.
Muay. You know what to do.
Use your individual skills.
Don't leave me.
After them!
Follow them. I'll go to block the other way.
- You!
- I'm going!
Get out, get out!
Oh! How can he pass?
Ooh! Is my bum still okay?
I don't know how I crossed them.
Let me borrow the chopper quick.
Come near me and I will slaughter you.
Knives! Knives!
Big ones, small ones for sale.
"Chilli Powder"
Get him! Kill him!
Ai Tim! Help me!
I won't help.
You have to fight them yourself.
Ai Don! Yes, I know his address. I'll take you.
Ai Tim! I know where Ai Don is.
Who's next!?
I used to see Ai Don hanging around here,
selling drugs.
Ask Muay, if you don't believe me...
But today...
That boy is here, Boss.
Bring him here to fight until the stakes are high...
then I will get rid of him.
Depends on how brave you are to take a bet.
Hey! You! Aw!
You are a maniac!
Champion! New champion!
Tim Pradoo Prew!
Come on! Come and fight me! Come on!
What are you waiting for?
Let's go, you hear! Come on!
What? You're scared? Let's go!
Come on. What are you waiting for?
What's the matter, Yod?
Ai Big Bear is challenging Ai Tim to a fight.
Come on! Thai boxing has had its day.
You should try freestyle.
You lot I'll fix next.
Thai people are not strong enough.
That's why Thai people come to my country to look at it.
Come on! I'll show you.
Come on! I'll fight you!
I'll teach you Thai boxing! Come on!
Fuck you!
Come on! You want to fight me now. Fight me!
Have you seen Bak Don?
No, but I've seen a Thai man being beaten.
You are a coward.
Come on!
Are you going to help him?
Without help he'll die.
Come on! Come on!
- Ai Tim!
- Come on!
If I knew you were like this,
I wouldn't have helped you to find Ong-Bak.
Huh! You can do that later.
But now you must help him first.
I'll kill him.
No!
Next fight! Big Ben and Tim Pradoo Prew.
Lay down your stakes!
Lay down your stakes now!
Lay down your stakes... quickly.
I'll give you 2 to 1. Want to bet?
Okay. Put me down for three million.
Begin!
Fight me now! Come on!
Fuck Muay Thai!
Attacking Enemy.
Hanuman crosses the city.
If my man wins, I want to collect the money
Okay, I know!
Thanks.
Ai Tim! Ai Tim! The best!!!
I think you've had enough.
No chance to win your money back today.
The next fight!
Tim Pradoo Prew and Toshiro!!!
Well done! Well done! The best!
- Muay, give me that.
- No.
- Half then.
- I don't have to.
- Trust me.
Do you have any real contenders?
Yes, but do you dare??
Oh! No problem.
Retreat! Mother of God!