Oh, my God...
Freedom.
I feel like my
mascara's running,
is my mascara running?
It looks good.
Like the cover
of Courtney Love's album.
You just need a crown.
There's a crown.
Hey, Noel, Noel,
can we borrow your crown?
We just need it
for like a second.
Wow.
We just got the royal finger.
I never liked her.
What did we
just go through?
I mean, what was that,
a prom or a Celine Dion
listening party?
Don't shoot this part.
Okay, what is this place?
Tell us...
You'll see when we get there.
Okay,
we're doing 20 questions.
What is this place?
Do they have food?
Not have 20 questions.
What,
you can't just ask a question?
Aren't we just
going to the hotel?
I'm very confused.
I just want to say,
"Hey, what's up?" to
all of the future
versions of ourselves
watching this right now.
I hope that
we all learn to be as
happy and beautiful
as these two right here
'cause they are going to
have the best prom night
of any of us.
Hold on, let me get this.
Tonight could've bit ass.
Except it didn't
because we were together.
Don't make me cry.
My mascara is already
fucked up enough as it is.
You look pretty!
Guys, I love our group.
Guys, what are we doing?
Chill out, just live a little.
We're not going to get caught.
This is not legal.
Danielle, you're going to love
that you did this later on.
And Savannah's getting naked.
Oh, no. No, no, no.
No, Danielle.
If we get a rare disease
from this water,
at least we'll
all die together.
I'm not leaving my dress
on the wet ground.
It's dry-clean-only
and my mom will kill me.
On the count of Celine Dion.
One, two,
Celine Dion!
No, no, no.
You can no longer work
on your taxes from 1998.
Yeah, I cannot amend
your '98 return. No.
Hi, Dad.
No, no, no, I'm not
laughing at your situation.
Yeah.
No, there's a strict
statute of limitations.
So sorry,
I'm so sorry.
I didn't realize
my dad wanted me
to work until 6:00.
I can't believe
you're still filling in
for your dad's old sign girl.
Yeah, you know,
I'm just still
trying to figure out
what kind of counseling
I'm going to do.
- Okay, Al, it's show time.
- Let's see it already.
The decorator just put
the finishing touches
on it yesterday.
After you!
Oh, my God.
Sorry.
That's okay.
Whoa!
Oh, my God.
You have outdone yourself.
This is impressive.
I thought you were
gonna have, like, a fish tank.
Look at the nipples
on this guy.
Oh, my God, we're going
to be so popular, Savannah.
That is the VIP section.
We can come any night
of the week
and have our
own special space.
It is so sexy.
I love that we get to be VIP!
Okay, girls, getting ready...
Let's get this party started.
My God... No!
- Last one, grab your penis.
- Thank you.
Turn them on like this.
I love it.
Hey, no, look,
my balls won't light up.
Oh, my God,
that hat is too much.
I mean it truly is the tiniest
hat I've ever seen.
It is, it's like
suitable for a mouse.
You need to wear
it to your wedding.
I can't, I have a veil.
Okay,
games, games, games, games.
All right,
the way this game works
is you write a caption
for what you think
the woman in this scene
is saying to her husband.
But here is the thing...
Look, look, look.
Look, look. Yes,
you have to make it dirty.
It'll be fun, it'll be fun,
so, all right. Ready?
Set, go.
All right, stop.
Stop, stop, stop,
pencils down.
I will go first.
He said he had
a package for me.
All right, Danielle,
you go.
I love getting mail.
But I spelled it m-a-l-e.
Oh, wow.
It's perfect. All right,
Meg, Meg, Meg, you go.
All right.
So, I wrote...
Hi, Matt,
this is to certify that
this is the big
fat cock I ordered.
Wait, why would you
put Matt's name in it?
Well, this is supposed
to be about you, right?
No, they're about marriage,
they're not about my marriage.
Right, but it's a joke,
like everyone else's.
Well, it's not
like everybody else's.
It was a joke.
It wasn't a prediction.
You know.
A joke.
How about we do another one?
And why would you
tweak the nipples
on the Buddha?
That seemed,
like, disrespectful.
Disrespectful to who? To you?
Did you convert to Buddhism?
No, that's disgusting.
I'm not Buddhist.
It's... That's Buddha.
That's Buddha!
Right, right. But you know
that was a joke about nipples.
Right?
And not Buddhism.
Yeah, Buddha is sacred
to a lot of people,
but that is...
This is a party, so
let's just forget about it.
Okay, yeah, no, forgotten.
Um, I mean,
we can do
another one of these.
Yes.
So this lady has a plunger
and there's a butt crack.
Hey.
Hey, sleepy head.
Good morning.
Oh, wow.
I shot these on Tuesday.
They were such
an amazing couple.
They were so open
to all of my ideas.
Great. Where is that?
Over in Seattle.
We had to go near
the shipyards though
so we could get
something a little more edgy.
'Cause I mean,
look at that wall.
Yeah.
Hey,
weren't you supposed to go
to that career
counselor today?
Yeah.
Yeah? You should...
Yeah. Yeah, okay.
I'll go get ready.
Good.
Hello, is somebody there?
It's me,
you don't have to come out.
What's this?
What's what?
I'm just gonna watch some TV.
Megan, I don't think
I like this new habit.
I spoke with Anthony,
and he said you were
meeting with the
career counselor today.
My God, I know exactly
what she's going to say.
It's just a waste of time.
Megan, honey,
I don't want to see you
throw away your education.
You have an advanced degree.
I know.
And your father should have
never given you
that stupid job
because now...
Is that my girl?
Hey, what are you doing home?
It's his home.
Taking the day off.
Yeah, me too. Hmm.
Wanna stay for dinner?
Yeah.
Ed.
Hey, is it
"make your own pizza"
night?
Sure, great idea.
Great idea.
Yeah.
I promise to love you,
to cherish you and to hold you
and to be the rock
in our relationship
for the rest of our days.
I promise to be
your baby's breath
when we wake each morning.
And to be your evening rose
at day's end.
And I promise
to be your safe harbor
when the boat is rocking
and when it's not rocking.
I give you
the bride and the groom,
Mr. and Mrs. Wanamaker!
And here they are
dancing to the song
Mrs. Wannamaker
has picked for their
first dance together
as man and wife.
My dad used to
make yipping sounds
when I first
started to take you out
because he said
it was puppy love.
I know.
I remember.
Yeah, well, you know,
but it wasn't puppy love.
No... I mean,
unless we stayed puppies
for a seriously long time.
Listen...
What?
Look...
I know it's taken me
a really long time
to get here.
What are you talking about?
Okay, well, you know how
I took that guy's
seminar last month?
Right.
Well,
I took a personality test.
And the test came back
and the type that I am...
Is a procrastinator.
Anth, I mean...
Who makes up those tests?
Come on.
Experts.
Right.
Like really smart people...
But that's not important.
What's important is that
I've been such a bonehead
in waiting to do this
for so long.
No, no!
Whoa, get up, get up!
Okay.
Get up...
Okay, I'm up,
and listen, I know
we have had our trouble
in the past
with recognizing our moments,
but this is it.
This is our moment.
No, this isn't our moment,
this is Allison's moment,
this is her wedding.
I know,
and it's totally cool.
When I first had the idea,
I ran it by her
and she was
so happy for us.
And today, at lunch,
I got a fortune cookie
that said, "Carpe diem."
Carpe diem?
Yes.
Hey, hey, guys, hey. Megan,
can you find my mom?
She has the next
dance with Matt.
I think I saw her
out in the garden.
Yeah, I'm... I'm...
I'm gonna come... I'm...
I'm just a second...
Right.
Sorry but she has
to find my mom.
No, it's fine.
Okay.
It's fine.
Uh, I'm going to go
and put the rose petals
in the bridal suite.
Right this second?
Yeah.
Don't you do that
just before they leave?
No, no,
it's cool right now.
Okay, I'll...
Later right? Later.
Meg?
Meg...
Hey, excuse me.
Yeah?
You look like you party.
I guess I'm technically
coming from one.
Cool. So...
We can hardly believe this,
but we all forgot our ID's.
And I mean,
normally we would just
go buy some beer ourselves...
But I guess we look under 21.
Which is crazy, right?
I know. Um, so...
If we gave you some
money or something,
would you help us
straighten this
whole problem out
and just buy us
a six-pack or something?
Oh, God.
Um, you could
totally keep the change.
Okay.
Someone did this for me
when I was your age,
so I'm going
to do it for you.
It's like a rite
of passage, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, I... I had
a good feeling about you.
That makes one of us.
Hey, yo,
can we get some coolers too?
And some red wine.
And can you get
some white wine also?
Thank you.
You don't have to get
all that. Thank you.
Yeah!
Here you go.
Drink responsibly.
Sweet.
Okay, I'm out of here.
Goodnight, you guys.
I'm really sorry.
Can I have a look
at that for a second?
Yeah go for it.
Okay.
Almost.
God, I haven't done this
since I was in eighth grade.
Okay, okay, one more time
and then I'm going.
Okay, all right,
thank you so much.
Come on,
where are you going?
Hang out some more.
Come on, stay.
I mean,
maybe I've got an hour.
Yeah.
What are you up to?
- Guys, I'm really impressed.
- This is truly art.
Oh.
Oh. Okay.
Come on, Megan.
Go right now, go.
Shit.
You know when you
go to a party drunk,
and everybody else is sober.
Or no. Or maybe like,
maybe you're the sober one
and everybody else is drunk.
God, you'd think that somebody
who you've known for forever
would have known
what you meant about nipples,
and it's like, hey, hey,
maybe like, using Buddha
as a restaurant decoration
is the bigger joke, right?
Or maybe...
Maybe actually
they're the ones
that are telling the jokes
and I'm the one
that's missing them.
You know?
It makes me really sad
what you're saying.
It's sad...
I don't even know
what you're talking
about but still...
Oh.
Don't get sad, Misty.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
No, no, like,
you shouldn't get
drunk and get sad.
I mean,
look at Patrick.
Patrick's sad
and he hasn't even
touched his wine.
His folks are splitting up.
His dad's being
a massive dick
in the divorce.
Oh.
That's why we TP'd his house.
That was his house?
Yeah.
Huh?
So you don't want
to go out together
as friends then?
Just take the sophomore.
You know,
just take a real date.
All right, whatever Annika.
Whatever you want.
I'm sorry. I just...
I totally interrupted.
What, me and Junior?
No, we were just
talking about the prom.
You know, stupid stuff.
I saw my dad cheat
on my mom tonight.
Really?
I think he was
about to get a hand job.
Yeah, my...
My mom left my dad and I,
like, seven years ago now.
It was out of nowhere.
We don't know why she did it.
You know why your dad did it?
I don't.
Well...
If you ever want to talk,
call me.
You're giving me a phone?
I have a bunch of them.
Misty's dad sells them.
I just pretty much
just use that one
to hide stuff from my dad.
Thanks.
God, I don't even
know what time it is.
How do I, um...
Oh, no...
This one?
Oh, shit.
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
Bye,
thanks for the awesome time.
Megan, what happened to you?
Where have you been?
I'm so sorry.
I, uh... I...
I...
You know, I was more wasted
leaving the wedding
than I knew...
Okay.
And by the time
I got to the store,
I realized I shouldn't
even be driving.
And then I got sick
and I was puking
in some bushes,
and then my dress got dirty,
and then I had to
leave the car there
and take a cab here.
And now I'm back.
I thought
you got upset about,
we'll call it the kneeling,
and that you didn't
come back on purpose,
but that didn't
seem like you.
No, no, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I got scared, I'm sorry.
I just...
I don't know.
Oh, God,
I'm a mess right now, look,
can we... Can we talk
about this tomorrow?
Well...
Well, baby, no...
No?
No.
We can't.
Right.
Because we have
wasted so much time...
We should have
just made it official
and our time is now.
I know why you're hesitant.
Why?
It's the planning
and the pressure
and all the trappings
of all that.
But we don't have
to do it that way.
No?
No, because we...
We can elope.
I was thinking.
We don't have to
tell our parents,
we don't have to
tell our friends.
Really?
We could go to
a beach or Vegas.
I was thinking Vegas
'cause we could just
check that step off
and we could be
married tomorrow.
Would you do that?
Yes. I would do that.
Okay.
I would do that.
Wow, we have
Matt and Allison's
brunch tomorrow.
But we can do it
the day after.
We can go
the day after tomorrow.
Yeah.
I can't the day after that.
What do you mean,
why? Why?
My God,
I really wanted to...
To go to that
personal development seminar.
Wait, really?
Yeah.
On Orcas?
Yeah, right.
Ah, because, you know...
I'm twirling a sign
for my dad,
and I don't know what
to do with my future.
That's awesome, Meg.
Yeah.
I'm so all for that.
That's amazing.
You know...
They do this thing
where they give you
an animal to help you
visualize new
behavioral patterns.
And mine was a shark.
And it helped to remind me
that I need to
keep progressing,
otherwise I'll just sink.
Yeah, so...
After your seminar
on Orcas...
Uh...
Will you...
Megan Burch...
Run off to Vegas with me?
Yes, I will.
You will.
There it goes.
I love you.
Mmm-hmm.
I love you so much.
What happened to you
last night?
I'm so sorry.
I got sick.
Sick?
She had a few too many drinks
and ended up
vomiting in a parking lot.
I'm sorry.
Why would you
possibly drink that much?
Now you are not in any
of the table pictures.
You are missing
from the video.
Megan Ashley Burch...
You had everyone
scared to death.
Where the hell have you been?
I got sick.
Oh.
She said she got sick.
I just, uh...
I just need to...
I've got to go
and do something.
It's okay, baby.
Hon.
I was just leaving.
Wait...
What's going on with you?
What's going on with me?
Yeah.
I saw you.
So right now I don't
even want to look at you.
Let's just quietly talk
about this for a second.
Talk about what?
I'm sorry, talk about what?
I don't know.
People grow together,
they grow apart.
It's always shifting.
Oh, right.
Three decades of marriage
to Mom
and you're going to describe
what I saw as shifting?
Wait.
Hey. You okay?
Yeah.
Okay. Savannah and Theo
want to talk to us.
About what?
I don't know. Come here.
Okay.
Oh, good,
there you are. So...
Theo and I have
been talking it over
and even though
you guys aren't
technically married...
You know, you're doing
the whole Goldie Hawn thing.
You know, you've been
together the longest
and you are young
and you are fun...
So fun.
And, you know,
if we're being responsible,
you're stable.
And what we wanted
to ask you is...
Is...
Ready?
Would you be our
baby's godparents?
Whoa!
- Are you kidding?
- No.
Sure...
Yeah, we would.
We would be honored.
See, I told you.
Is it official?
You are looking at
Juppiter's godparents.
There they are.
Juppiter?
Yeah,
nobody has that name.
No one.
Oddly.
I bet not.
Like the planet.
Except two "P's," two "P's."
You know, I think
this is going to be
really good for me.
Me too.
It's like you're having
your bachelorette party
but at a seminar.
Yeah.
Maybe you'll get a shark too.
Maybe.
All right, bye.
Drive safe.
Bye.
Hello?
Hey, what up?
It's Annika.
Uh, huge emergency,
could you come
down to my school
and pretend to be my mom?
Whoa, what?
Yeah, I'm supposed to
have this parent/teacher
conference today,
but I threw the note out.
So my counselor said
she's gonna call my dad,
but he will be super pissy
if he has to
come sit down here.
So I told them
my mom already knew about it
so basically my point is,
could you just come down here
and pretend to care about me
for like ten minutes?
I'll owe you,
and I know I already
owe you for the beer,
but I will really,
really owe you.
But, but I don't
look related to you.
Maybe I'm adopted.
What the fuck does she know?
Probably not much.
So will you come?
Hi.
My God,
you actually came through.
And you have
the fake wedding ring.
Nice touch.
Mrs. Hunter?
Hey.
Hello.
So,
I'm becoming concerned that
Annika is not taking
steps towards her future.
Got it.
Well,
I'll be sure to talk to her
about it at home.
So, we're good here?
Mrs. Hunter, I realize
you must have
a very busy life. But...
I was hoping that
we could all come up
with a plan today.
Okay, sure. A plan.
Do you have one?
Oh, uh...
I don't know. I mean...
It kind of
seems stupid to plan
that far in advance
when you're just gonna
change your mind
anyway, right?
I mean, say you had a kid,
and then you realize
you didn't
really want the kid.
Was there a pregnancy?
No, she's talking
about her mom. Me.
Her mom.
And as her mom,
I'd say that...
I'm sure it does
seem kind of stupid
to make some
sort of rigid plan
for the future. But...
It's stupider not to
start paying attention
to who you are
and what makes you happy.
Otherwise, you just float.
So...
There's the start of her plan.
Good meeting, Mrs. Halpsky.
You've given us
a lot to think about.
Yes, well... Yes.
So this is kind of
an interesting
job to have, huh?
What kind of licensing
does it take?
Are you questioning
my qualifications?
No. No. Never mind. I...
I was just curious.
Come on.
You worked her over.
You can take that
stuff off now, you know.
She totally bought it.
Remember half an hour ago
when you said
you'd really owe me?
Holy shit. You collect fast.
I need to lay low for a week.
Your dad works, right?
So, my dad usually
comes home around 7:00,
but he's going to some lame,
divorcee mixer,
so he'll be late.
This is the living room.
And this...
Ooh, this is Lynn.
Jesus Christ.
Yeah...
My mom bought her
when she saw Finding Nemo
'cause she thought that
turtle was cute, but...
Then she realized that
this kind doesn't swim.
So she ditched you, too,
didn't she, Lynn?
You don't really have
to do anything for her.
Just don't step on her.
She likes to hide back here.
Do I need to feed her?
Um, you can try,
but we're pretty sure
she's an anorexic.
Cool pet.
So, this is the kitchen.
You can basically
eat whatever you want.
But this is his box of wine.
So if you have some,
use the funnel
with the Tupperware
and fill it up with
a little bit of water.
It's what we do.
I don't think
he really notices.
And tonight, this guy Dan
has invited some people over
'cause his parents
are out of town.
So if you want to do that,
we can do it.
And then we'll just
sneak you back in.
Okay.
And I'm using Humid.
It's a really gorgeous green.
Under.
Yeah, on the edge. All right.
You ready?
Yeah.
You know, I always
wanted to try a smoky eye.
But I thought it
might be too much on me.
I don't know. I like it.
Hey!
Whoa!
You're supposed to knock.
Write a letter.
I don't know you.
Megan.
Craig.
She's a new friend.
You're supposed to
be at that mixer.
Yeah, well,
I came home to change
so I don't look like a lawyer.
Wow.
High school students
are looking
rougher and rougher
these days.
Just graduated.
God,
you can be rude sometimes.
Look,
she's a new friend, okay?
We're just gonna
go to the movies.
Right well, let me know
if the teen vampire
gets the girl.
And be home by 10.
I know I'll be.
You know,
why doesn't he just stay out
if he wants to be less lonely?
I don't know. Come on.
Is this turning
into a college party?
Where's the fucking beer?
This way?
Junior!
What's up?
Hey.
Long time no see
since Econ.
Yeah, that goes on
around him all night.
Yo. Yo, Annika!
Hey.
Oh, yeah,
let's do this!
It's not a party
till we start.
Who's gonna help me
get this going!
Here.
Yeah. This is
definitely having people over.
Oh, yeah.
I've always loved Neil Young.
I just discovered him.
Okay,
I'm gonna put the ice cube.
It's gonna be good.
Okay, on the count of three.
One...
Two!
Okay, girls.
We need the hoop.
Come on. Hand it over.
Yeah, thank you.
Hey, I think it's
past your curfew,
so we should probably go.
This is my mom.
Wow, that's your mom?
Yeah, she models
for catalogs now.
I've come across them before.
I don't even know
who she is anymore.
You don't see her?
We did phone calls for a bit.
It didn't really last.
Do you know where she is?
There's an address.
On the child support check
she sends my dad.
He puts them in a box
labeled, "No, thanks."
God, I'm sorry.
I'm really
emotional tonight.
I was already upset
about Junior,
and then I came in here,
and I saw her.
You like him, huh?
Yeah.
I might even be
in love with him.
Wow.
Well, are you sure that
he doesn't like you, too?
Sure he does. As a friend.
Oh, right.
You know,
he's probably
checking her tag
to see what cycle
to wash it in.
Yeah.
Mmm-hmm.
Uh, Megan, can I borrow
your car keys for a second?
I think I left my
sweatshirt out there.
Yeah. Sweatshirt's
a really good idea.
Thanks.
You know...
When I was in high school,
there was a guy that
everyone said liked me.
It was all I heard about
from my friends.
But he never acted on it,
so I kept getting unsure.
Well, did he ever
do anything about it?
Yeah.
Sophomore year,
he asked me to be
his girlfriend
in front of everyone.
Oh... And did you like him?
Yeah. He was cute.
Kind of artsy.
He noticed these details
about the world
and talked about them in a way
that no other
high school guy would.
And he was always...
He was always
taking pictures and...
Pulling quotes out of nowhere
which I thought
was pretty deep.
But, but maybe it was
the start of a habit
of waiting for other people
to make decisions for me.
You know?
Okay.
Ooh, okay.
Okay. He's going
to be waiting inside
to do a whole deposition
on me.
So just go straight
to my room
and wait for me there.
You don't have to
take your shoes off.
Hey. Where you been?
Whoo! God!
That movie was so long.
Hi.
Hey.
Did you find
everything you needed?
Yeah.
Yeah? All right, cool.
Are you in trouble?
No. He just made me tell him
the plot to the movie we saw.
And then he read
the same plot
to me back online
to see if it matched.
But I just told him
a movie I saw
last week
when I ditched school.
Ah-ha!
Yeah. I didn't think
you had
an interest in ventriloquism.
You. Downstairs.
We need to talk.
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
Who are you?
Megan. Burch.
Mmm-hmm.
And I get that
this can sometimes be
sensitive information
for a woman,
but how old are you?
I'm in my 20s.
Uh-huh.
And why are you
sleeping over at my house?
Or I guess
the larger question is,
why are you hanging out
with my daughter?
It's kind of hard to explain.
I bet.
No, I mean,
I've never really tried to.
Not even to myself.
I like hearing things better
when they're not rehearsed.
All right, uh...
I grew up around here.
Well, no, I didn't,
I mean, you know,
across the lake
on the east side.
Uh...
I got "best couple"
with my boyfriend
in high school.
And I started
an alternative dance team
with my friends
meaning that
we danced
to Beastie Boys
instead of top 40.
It was kind of cool.
After college, I worked
some random jobs,
time went by.
I'm gonna skip to...
Okay, I went back to
grad school to get my marriage
and family therapist degree
because I thought
I wanted to have
honest conversations
with people.
Mmm-hmm.
But... But...
I did my internship
and I...
I couldn't relate
to any of my clients.
I felt like a total fraud.
So, you know,
I kind of found myself
in this place. Like...
This kind of weird
in-between place,
you could say, you know?
And, I don't know,
I was kind of floating.
And, and then I met Annika
at the grocery store,
and I skateboarded
with her for a minute.
And, and it was
really fun, you know.
I liked skateboarding.
I missed it.
I think it was just nice
to hang out with somebody
that cut me some slack
for a change.
I'm sorry. This isn't
gonna make any sense.
This is...
You know, this isn't...
It's not gonna make any sense,
so just fucking sue me.
I'm sorry, that wasn't
meant to be a lawyer joke.
It's not a joke
if it's not insulting.
I don't think
I know any lawyer jokes.
Oh, no, wait, I do.
I've got one from my dad.
What do you call
5,000 dead lawyers
at the bottom of the sea?
A good start.
Hey, did you hear the one
about the grown woman
who started hanging out
with a bunch of
pubescent kids?
No, what?
No, I'd never heard
of it before either.
Come on,
you gotta help me out.
So what... What were you like?
Uh, well...
Senior year, I was
voted "best gorgeousness,"
and most likely to pump gas
when I get older.
And then I realized
it would be fairly easy
for me to argue
for a living if I wasn't
doing it on my own behalf.
And then there was
this intensely
poufy white dress.
It gets a little hazy because
of all the tulle or taffeta.
And then there was a kid,
and then the taffeta
floated out the door.
And that brings us to tonight.
Tonight.
What a cluster fuck.
You talking about the mixer?
Yeah.
Mmm.
At these things,
women insist on
touching your forearm
in this very
deliberate manner.
These touches are
meant to communicate
gold-star level skills
in listening...
In connectedness.
Oh, yeah.
Do you know about
this kind of gesture?
Yeah. You mean this one?
Yes. Do go on.
Do go on.
Right?
Yeah.
That's it.
Um...
Dad, you do know
you can't lecture her
all night, right?
She's not a kid.
Oh, really?
You snuck your friend
into my house,
I think you're
lacking say-so here.
If you let her spend
the night in your locker...
No, that's school's property.
If you let her
spend the night in your
backpack. Yes. No, that's...
Actually I paid
for the backpack.
Okay.
So I guess that's my property.
I don't know.
Why don't you put
a case together.
And come back.
All right.
When you got something solid.
I'm gonna go to bed.
You sure?
We can talk about this more.
Okay, goodbye.
Good night, honey.
The property argument
is inelegant
but it ends things quickly.
Uh, listen,
I deal with a lot of scumbags
on a daily basis.
So I've developed
a real appreciation
for the truth.
I've gotta think
that if you were lying,
you'd make up an excuse
that's less fucking weird.
You do realize that
reverting to a teenage life
and sneaking into my house
is weird, correct?
Right.
And why were you
trying to sleepover?
Uh...
The lease on my
apartment ran out,
and I can't get into
my new place for a week.
And my, my friends...
I just,
I didn't want to, uh...
I didn't want to
involve them or my parents.
All right, um...
Fuck it.
I'm not gonna kick you out
at 1:00 in the morning.
Oh, thank you.
You're not sleeping on
the floor of my kid's bedroom.
I'm putting you
in the guest room.
Got enough pillows here?
Yeah, yeah. Thank you.
Please don't let this decision
become bad parenting
on my part.
I won't. I really...
I really won't.
Wait. He let you stay?
Yeah. I'm in the guest room.
I'm gonna let you do
something too, Annika.
I'm gonna let you
do additional chores
for two weeks.
Oh, no, hey, look,
it's my fault
she got in trouble.
She's the one
who made the decision.
Hey, throw another
tart in there
for me, will you?
It's your house.
It is my house. You know,
I think I'm gonna
work from home today
because I really have
no good reason to trust you.
No offense.
None taken.
Yo, your ride is here.
Patrick.
What happened to us, man?
You don't write anymore.
That's a great shirt.
Listen.
I know you want
to kill your dad.
Sometimes I do, too,
but I'm doing my best
to keep this case civil
on his end,
and toilet papering
isn't gonna help.
So if you want to take
some aggression out
on a father figure...
Let's get scrappy, man.
So you can move on.
Whoosh!
You're a divorce lawyer?
Yeah, he's my dad's.
Wait, do you live here now?
All right.
Yeah,
we should go to school.
Dad, stop. Just go.
Thanks for the banana,
Mr. Hunter.
Seriously, Patrick.
Help me out, okay?
I'm not...
I'm not kidding actually.
Mmm. Good.
I think I cracked
her eating disorder.
Really.
She is feeling
so confident
about her body.
Yeah. I can see that.
Did you see the mail come?
No, not yet.
Show me something.
What have you got?
Well, okay,
I'm working on a flip.
So you flip it around and...
Whoa!
And then you get on.
You wanna go?
Come on.
I'm middle-aged.
No, look. Have a go.
Come on. Come on.
Okay.
Just sort of like stand there.
You want to stand to
make it go, like, this way.
Okay.
Oh, geez.
That almost hit my dick.
Okay. That's not good.
Maybe we should get
the training wheels for me.
Have a good day, you guys.
Can I trust you?
Yes, you can.
Okay, if you need anything,
key's under
the stone tortoise.
All right. Bye.
Bye.
Hey.
Hey!
I was just
retouching some guy's
back zits out of
his baby shots.
That sounds lovely.
Oh, it was amazing.
It was amazing.
How's the seminar?
It's so weird being away.
I mean, with you being gone,
I've just been
holed up working, and...
I'm afraid to see everyone.
'Cause I feel
like if I see them
I'm just gonna
crack and tell them.
I've just been pretending
to be some complete loner.
When really
I'm a secret fianc.
So are you getting
a lot out of this?
Yeah. Yeah, you know, uh...
My animal's a tortoise.
Go figure.
A tortoise?
That's sweet.
I miss you.
Oh, hey,
your dad has left
like three million
voicemail messages
so you should
probably call him.
'Cause I'm assuming
he doesn't know
you're on Orcas.
Oh, yeah, no, I was...
I was being
a secret seminarian.
Makes sense.
Yeah.
Wise choice.
Thanks. I thought so.
Look, I've gotta go.
I gotta go.
Okay, right.
All right.
I love you.
Glad I caught you.
Love you, too. Bye, baby.
Bye.
Oh... Hey.
Will you go with me
to see my mom?
Sure.
All right.
My God.
What is this?
Um...
I don't know. It...
It just kind of felt
like something I should do.
God.
She's been in there
making lemonade for,
like, 20 minutes.
I don't think
she's coming out.
Just take her and
put her in the car
and tell her I'm sorry.
And whatever else
you need to.
What could I
possibly tell her?
That I thought I'd
be the really cool mom
that took her to concerts,
and she'd want to
borrow my boots?
But then one day I realized
there's no such thing
as a cool mom.
That the cool mom is
really just the bad mom,
or the mom
who has become a joke.
Are you Craig's girlfriend?
Is that why
you're here with her?
No. I'm just her friend.
What does she expect?
That you serve some lemonade,
and you ask her
five to 10 questions
about her life.
You treat
somebody badly enough,
you just assume
they'll be happy
to let you go.
She had... Said she
had to get something.
So, after I...
You know...
I started doing a lot
of catalog modeling,
and I ended up
doing a lot of lingerie.
Yeah, I know,
I've seen your pictures.
Oh.
Well.
Anyway,
they send me home with so many
things from these
stupid photo shoots.
And I just thought
that since, you know,
obviously, well,
you're a growing woman...
And, well,
maybe there might be
some things you like in here.
Um...
Do you like this one?
Yeah, it's really nice.
I think that's about right.
I mean, do you like black?
Is black a color you like?
Sure.
Great.
Great, I have more.
What about florals?
I mean,
do you wear nightgowns? Or...
I have thongs.
Are you into thongs or no?
I like that one with the bows.
Great. Yeah.
That's cute.
Got room for that?
Yeah.
You know, I really
needed a strapless bra.
You did?
Yeah. For my prom dress.
It's actually really good
that she gave me one.
Yeah. Yeah, no,
it's really good.
You should come.
Where?
To the prom.
Saturday night.
It's on this boat
in Lake Union.
Oh, no,
I've gotta go home Saturday,
remember?
You know, I've gotta get
into my new place
and sort everything out.
I mean, I can't just
float around forever.
No.
Come on.
You belong there with us.
Hi. I'm so sorry
to keep you waiting.
Can I take your order?
Can we have two
mondo chococinos
and two
boysenberry muffin tops.
We're celebrating.
10.50, please.
There you go.
Thank you.
Megan?
Hey. Coinky-dink.
Anthony told us that
you were working on yourself
on Orcas Island.
And that you probably weren't
checking your messages,
so that's why you
weren't calling us back.
Oh, did you call?
No, my...
My phone's been off.
Megan.
You missed Savannah
having her baby.
And you are the godmother.
The godmother!
Juppiter?
Yesterday!
No, and they went
with Callisto
because someone
at the hospital had
a Juppiter last week.
Oh.
Callisto is one
of Jupiter's moons.
Oh, I only knew about Io.
Yeah, I learned there are 64.
Anyway, the baby is here.
And you're not
out of town at all.
You're not immersed
in some seminar
trying to get your life
moving in the right direction.
You are driving around
getting chococinos with...
Who the hell is that?
I don't even know who that is.
Oh.
Meg...
Is that your drug dealer?
No.
No. I'm not on drugs.
Okay, look, here's the thing.
No, I'm not...
I'm not on Orcas Island.
But I am on Orcas,
if you think about Orcas
on a bigger level.
Like symbolically.
I just, you know...
I just needed
a second of personal time.
You know, I mean,
it's a week,
but in terms of my life,
it's more like
just a second to
get my shit together.
And then...
Then I'm going home
in a couple of days. Okay?
I feel like I should
really tell Anthony
that you never left.
What are you talking about?
Oh, my God.
You're supposed
to be my friend.
I mean, it was you and me
and Savan and Danielle
before he ever
even asked me out.
But I'm not going to tell him.
Thanks.
Because he bought a ring.
And he's going
to propose to you.
Yeah. That's right. He did.
I helped him pick it out,
and it's, like, incredible.
So I bet that makes
you think twice about
how ridiculous you're being
with this fake Orcas stuff.
Meg...
I really want
this wedding for you.
And it's not even the wedding.
It's that we're friends.
It's like how our prom,
it wasn't just a dance,
it was us
getting ready together.
And then how we all
lied to our moms together.
And stayed at the cheap hotel,
and went swimming naked
in that nasty pool.
And we all thought
we were so cool.
But if you had
stayed home that night,
then the stories wouldn't
have made sense to you.
You wouldn't have been
a part of everything
that night meant.
And I just think
now that we're adults,
our lives are that times 10.
What are you saying?
I'm saying that I'm not going
to mess things up for you.
Just...
Don't mess them up
for yourself.
All right.
What was that all about?
Oh, she just had
a message to give me.
Um, I need
to get a baby gift.
Hey.
Where you two been?
Um...
Megan took me to
get some new bras.
Oh.
How was that?
Was that fun?
Fun?
I'm gonna go and
lie down for a while.
All right.
Um, Misty is gonna come over
and have a sleepover
'cause we have
no school tomorrow.
No school, why is that?
Yeah,
it's a staff development day.
Okay, well, keep Misty away
from our valuables.
I was joking.
That was a joke.
Yeah. I know.
Goodbye.
Want some poppy snaps?
I totally forgot
about this guy.
Oh, my God.
Herschel Thrasher.
What was his mom on?
You really don't
have a chance in life
if your mom wears
a belly chain.
Look at
Tiffany Wilmington
with her real teeth.
Oh, my God.
Who is she dating now?
Uh, Kyle Stempano, I think.
Is that right?
I really wouldn't know.
I'm gonna go get
some snacks, okay?
Okay.
Bye.
Later.
Peace!
Hey.
Come in.
Yeah?
Thanks for knocking.
It's okay.
Thought I'd be polite.
Them's the rules.
Mmm.
Can I complain to you?
Sure, go ahead.
I'm so fucking
stressed out right now,
all I want is a drink.
I went for the box wine
in the fridge,
and it's funny how much
that vintage
tastes like tap water.
Yeah, you know, I'm, yeah.
The box stuff really
is never very good.
Ah.
So, what are you working on?
A letter to opposing counsel.
During mediation
my client agreed
to give back two
of her handguns
to her husband,
and now she's decided
they were
anniversary gifts to her.
Wow. That's romantic.
Are you gonna win?
I hope so because
it would kill me to
see a mother separated
from her guns.
Hey, um...
No, never mind.
What?
You want to come
get a drink with me?
Now?
Yeah.
Well, I'm supposed to be
in the middle of a sleepover.
Oh,
they're like little animals.
They're like gerbils.
They have next to
no sense of time.
Aren't you leaving soon?
Yeah.
One pop.
Careful.
Okay, we gotta hurry.
Don't slip.
Thank you.
Hey.
Anybody here? All right.
Waitress won't
give it to 'em.
Right.
So he says, um...
Hey.
Hey, how you doing?
Just about closing.
Oh, well,
that's perfect for our needs.
We just want a round of shots.
Bourbon.
Bourbon. Hey.
Wow. Like your style.
Thank you.
Bourbon in
a Mexican restaurant.
Can I get a Pacifico?
Of course.
Uh, I think doing
cheers is cheesy,
so if you need to
touch glass to glass,
use my watch.
So do I.
Mmm.
You have time for another?
Yes.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Twist my arm.
So, uh, what's up
with that Junior kid?
Is my daughter in love
with that Rico Suave kid?
Whoa, that's
friend-friend privilege.
Can't talk about that.
Not much going on
between the ears on
that one, is there?
Oh, you know, at the moment,
she doesn't need
him to be smart.
Thank you.
Yeah, I guess it's easier
when you're young.
All you need from someone
is to feel stupid around them.
What do you need
when you're older?
You need to
feel like you're on
the same side of
what seems stupid.
Oh.
You really like
hanging out with her, huh?
Yeah.
You genuinely like
hanging out with her?
I genuinely think
she's really cool.
Huh.
You know, good for her.
I like that kid.
I do, I do. I love her.
Good.
I'm a little hard on her.
Maybe I haven't
been giving her enough credit.
She's a good kid.
At least she didn't end up
paying attention to me.
You know. Could be worse.
I can't go back
and fix my own
fucked up head but...
She doesn't have to
get bitter
in the first place,
does she?
No.
I think
we need another drink.
Let's have a drink.
No cheers.
Right?
You know, so,
monks and priests, right?
They say they get
their calling from God.
But that means that it was
from something outside.
It wasn't from
something inside, right?
And everybody thinks
that that's just great.
Yeah.
Right?
What the fuck, right?
Sorry, guys.
You're gonna have to
close your tab out.
- Going home.
- Aw, man.
I... I...
This is your coat.
So I don't have any money.
No, no, no.
My responsibility.
Okay, good.
I dragged you out.
Put your money away.
Here, it's on me.
It's on...
It's on you.
It's on Blockbuster.
Gosh darn it.
That was fun.
Yeah.
Yeah, I just...
I just wanna...
I just wanna say
thank you for...
For what?
For letting me stay.
Well,
I loved having you, you know.
You're good people.
And uh...
Oh, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait...
Wait, wait, wait.
I just... I just, uh...
I don't think we should
finger-bang in the street.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know?
Of course.
No, no, no, no, no.
We should go to my...
The house.
House, yeah,
yeah, the house.
Well, maybe we take
Annika's tee-shirt off.
Yeah.
Maybe that's a little creepy.
Yeah. That's hot.
Yeah, I'm just wearing,
like, a little tee shirt with,
like, crotchless panties.
Who's she talking to?
Our math teacher.
Does he know it's her?
No.
Okay, good.
I'm just gonna...
I'm just gonna
brush my teeth, okay?
Yeah, yeah, you're good.
Hey.
Got a headache?
Yeah.
This is an old
hangover cure from college.
You want one?
Yeah.
It's very scientific.
I'm not messing around.
No.
You know...
You can stay
here a little longer
if you need to.
Yeah, you know,
I've gotta get back
into my new place.
So...
Okay.
All right. I'm calling
Patrick and Junior again.
Laggies.
Do I have
something on my face?
Yeah. My dad's saliva.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
How about that?
I think you're pretty but...
That's my dad.
I... Oh, God, I...
Annika, I...
I don't know what happened,
you know. I mean...
I was thinking
the whole time like,
"What are you doing, Megan?"
No, no, no, no.
I really don't need details.
Look,
I've had a couple of hours
to think about it.
And I just keep thinking
about how lonely he's been.
You know, and how hard
he's been trying
with me lately.
And as much shit
I talk about him...
I love him.
You know,
and I want him to be happy.
And I want you to be happy.
You know, so if you two
are happy together, then...
It might be kind of cool.
And obviously,
he can't come with us
when we go out. But...
You know,
if he wanted to take you
to the movies, or whatever,
I've decided not to
lose my shit over it.
Annika,
I don't think that dating
is in the future
for your dad and me.
Did I just hear
you're boning Mr. Hunter?
No, it's not like that.
Ew. Gross.
Yo, finally.
Fucking drop it already,
I'm here, okay?
Oh, bad mood.
Hey, the tux place
is at the other end.
All right,
so we'll meet back here
in like an hour?
Sure. If you can live
without me that long.
I'm not sure I can.
You've gotta dance
with him tomorrow night.
I mean, who's to say?
Okay, I'm trying this one on.
It's you.
I know.
No.
No?
You wear white to your
wedding. Not to prom.
Shut up. I like it.
This is it.
This is it!
I look so fucking good, man.
I don't even know
why those other chicks
are even gonna
bother to show up.
What do you think?
Oh, you look so cute.
Good?
You should buy it. Yeah.
Do you have any gum
in your bag?
Right there.
Little shorter.
You can't take
it a little more.
Yeah, but like, shorter.
You want my ass out?
No.
She wants my ass out.
"A and M.
Best couple forever."
He had it engraved?
Are you married?
I'm only engaged.
Only engaged.
Who's the A?
You don't know him.
My dad know about him?
No.
Are you going back to him?
Yes.
God, you're even worse
than my mom.
You know,
at least when she pulled
my dad into her bullshit,
she didn't know
she was gonna leave.
Oh, shit.
God, Megan,
don't even turn around
and look at me right now.
I'll swear on whatever
you want me to swear on.
I really like your dad.
I wasn't faking it.
You're a huge fucking liar.
Even your fake ring
was fake at being fake.
Who knows what else
you're trying to
lie to me about.
She's really hurt, Megan.
Oh, shut up, Junior.
You pulled your own
bullshit with her, too.
Oh, don't you even try
to bring him into this.
Can you please stop
the fucking yelling
while I'm driving?
Who gives a fuck about
your dad's love life?
He helps break
up other people's
relationships
every fucking day.
Don't be a dick to Annika
just because
your dad's a dick
and her dad's trying to
bring home some cash.
Shut up, Misty!
How does any...
I don't know
what crawled up
your ass today...
You want to hear
what crawled up
my ass, Annika?
Oh, God!
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
Is anybody hurt?
- Is your neck okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Okay.
I'm drunk, Megan.
He's sending me to
boarding school next year.
And she didn't
even fight him on it.
I opened the bottle
of wine you bought me,
and I put it
in the OJ container.
I just didn't
want to care anymore.
Okay.
Okay, everyone out of the car.
Out of the car right now.
When the cops get here,
I was driving.
The wheels slipped.
I think my palms got sweaty.
Can you touch your nose
with your left hand?
With...
Are you able to recite
the alphabet backwards?
Uh...
Z-X-Y-V...
No, W, W, V... Oh, God.
I don't think
that I could do that
even if I hadn't
been drinking.
Have you been drinking?
No.
Please, stay here a moment.
I just wanted
to say that
what you're doing
for Patrick
is pretty solid.
This officer thinks
I've been driving drunk,
and I might be legally drunk.
I don't know.
I had some gin this morning.
What the fuck, Megan?
Miss Burch,
I'm going to ask you
to take a breath test.
Is that okay with you?
Yes.
I want you to
blow into this tube.
Continue to blow
until I say stop.
Is that understood?
Keep blowing please.
Keep blowing.
That's good.
Miss Burch, I'm gonna
ask you to turn around
and put your hands
behind your back.
Hold your hands together,
please.
Wait, no, she...
She didn't do anything.
No, chill out, Patrick.
Please, relax.
This way, ma'am.
Annika,
can you please call your dad
to come, please?
Watch your head, please.
Are you in?
Yeah.
What are you gonna do?
Burch.
Your lawyer's here
to see you.
Thank you,
Officer.
Well,
I've planned your escape.
It's gonna
involve a lot of soap.
We're gonna have to
roofie this guy over here.
But I think we can do it.
Annika didn't tell you.
She told me.
I know Patrick was driving.
And I know
what you did for him.
I think it's
a really stand-up thing.
Craig...
Uh...
I've got
something to tell you,
and you're gonna hate me.
I doubt that.
Uh...
I am not waiting
for a new apartment.
My boyfriend,
the one that I got
"best couple" with,
he proposed.
And I needed some time.
I'm engaged to be married.
So you...
So you didn't lose your lease?
That's not why
you've been staying over?
No. I just...
I needed to get
my head together,
and I gave myself a week.
When are you
getting married?
Tomorrow.
You know,
I mean, if I'm not in jail.
I, uh, we're eloping.
I'm getting married tomorrow.
That's really something.
Yeah.
Tomorrow. Huh.
Congratulations.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
No, that's...
I'm such a shitty person.
I really want to
tell you everything.
The first time I met the kids,
I bought them alcohol.
It never happened again,
but that's where
Patrick got the wine from
and I went with Annika
to see her mom.
So you met, uh...
Shit.
I'm gonna stop there.
That's all the lies though.
You know, the...
The rest is true.
However,
I acted around you,
that was true.
Whatever happened between us,
And I know that
I shouldn't have
kissed you.
I know I shouldn't
have done that.
It just got so confusing.
'Cause I had this feeling
like I was already
in love with you.
Say something.
The number
you blew at the scene
was borderline.
The number you blew
at the station was under.
So they're gonna release you.
Something else?
Like what?
That I haven't felt connected
to anyone I've flirted with
or casually seen or dated
or slept with for years,
for I don't know how long.
That this was a rare deal.
That right now I'm
aware looking at you,
this could be it for me.
I never anticipated
still having
to find a place
where I'd fit in
by the time I was
an adult either.
I thought you
automatically got one
once you had
a job and a family.
But it's just you,
alone.
Thanks for coming.
Hey, no problem.
I'm happy to.
Do you want to
tell me what happened?
No, nothing. It was a mix-up.
They're not pressing charges.
Good. Good.
Listen, honey...
Dad, no, I...
I need you to know
that I fucked up, too.
So I'm in no position
to judge you.
What are you talking about?
You can totally judge me.
I did something
really stupid.
And it's gonna
take a long time
before your mom can
think well of me again.
You told her?
Yeah.
I wasn't going anyplace.
I just had
a moment in time where...
You know,
I lost sight of who I was
and what was important to me.
So you're staying together?
Yeah, we're gonna work on it.
She wants to work on it.
Do you still think
you were just shifting?
Well, that's what,
you know,
relationships are, you know?
Not the cheating part,
that was my problem.
But you know, you don't
just get into one
and then that's it.
It's work,
and it's always changing.
It's always changing.
Yeah,
I think I know what you mean.
Look, I was just happy
to hear from you.
Even if it was from jail.
Hey.
Baby.
Welcome back.
So I, uh, checked
the chapel's photographer out.
He's no me,
but he's done some okay work.
I think we're
gonna have to paste
in the Caribbean behind us
so our parents think
we went further away
and couldn't invite them.
Who's that?
I don't know.
I got it.
All right.
Hey-o.
Misty.
Uh, what are you doing here?
Well, I brought the stuff
you left behind
from the crash.
Here.
Oh, thanks.
Oh, and by the way,
Patrick's dad wants you
to pay for his car repairs
out of pocket.
Out of...
Nobody does that
unless it's a scratch.
Yeah, well, he's a dick.
Oh, my God.
Anywho, um...
I'm also here to tell you
that you need to come to prom.
Misty, I can't.
I know.
You and Annika are having
a lot of issues right now.
But if you stop
being friends after this,
she's gonna become, like,
secretly tortured about it.
That's how she is.
I know she looks up to you.
That trip you got her to
take to her mom's was huge.
And all this time
you've been
spending with us fucknuts.
Hey.
Hi.
Who's this?
Uh, I'm Misty.
Hi, Misty.
Yeah.
Megan's been mentoring me.
Right. At the seminar,
she was in the junior program.
The junior program.
Oh, wow, that's cool.
What was your animal?
I'm my own animal.
Ah.
Right.
I like that.
I respect that.
Okay.
Nice meeting you.
Yeah, you too.
He's cute.
Thanks.
Well, we bought you
a ticket as Patrick's date.
Just come.
Attention, passengers.
Flight 514 has begun
general boarding to Las Vegas.
Please, line up to
the right of the podium...
Oh, my God.
Here we go.
Okay. Wait. Hold on a second.
I know it's going
to be bad quality.
But I need to
capture this moment.
Right.
Of course.
All right. Just gonna
send this to the group.
They're over at the soft open
for the restaurant.
We've got to
celebrate with those guys
as soon as we get back.
Why do you need to do that?
I'm not gonna send
it to our parents.
I know that's
a whole other conversation.
And... Done.
Why did you need to do that?
Well, I figured
'cause they can't be here,
it's our way of
bringing them into it.
Oh, look,
Allison already wrote back.
Oh, my God. I can't do this.
What?
Oh, are you thinking...
You're thinking we need
to have a real wedding.
I know, and you know what?
That would actually make me
a whole lot more happy.
No. No, I mean that
we can't be together.
Wait, what?
Oh, my God...
Oh, my God, I think...
I think I might throw up
that I'm finally doing this.
Doing what?
What are you doing?
Okay...
Um...
How am I gonna
explain this to you, right?
Right,
the animal thing, right?
The animal thing, okay.
God, Anthony.
That could never be my speed.
But... But if it helps you
to understand
what I'm trying to say to you,
then...
Anth, I'm a snake.
I'm a snake
that's been dragging
my old skin around with me
for way too long.
I'm a snake.
No, you're not.
No, no.
You have to see this about me.
I'm dropping out.
I'm dropping out of the group.
Okay, I mean, that's okay,
'cause that's them,
and you can just cut down on
the amount of time
you hang out with them...
'Cause that's just them.
That's not us.
No.
No, you're still
part of the group.
You and me, we're...
We're somewhere back there.
You know, we're in the past.
Holy shit, Meg.
All this time?
No, no, God, no.
Not all of it.
Well, however long.
Holy shit.
This is it.
Yeah.
This is what it
comes down to.
Yeah.
Waking up in the morning,
and never being able
to see your face...
Ever again.
No, we can still be
in each other's lives.
No, we can still...
We can still talk?
Yeah.
Yeah, right.
Sure.
Hey.
Hey. You came.
The smoky eye looks great.
Thanks.
Okay, what I did to
your dad was wrong. But...
I just really,
really fell for him.
Annika...
I broke it off
with my boyfriend.
Yeah, well...
I guess I know what it's
like to forget yourself
when you really,
really like someone.
Okay,
I'm gonna tell you two things
that I've gotten
some perspective on
after being out of high
school for a while now.
The first is that
a lot of the math
they're teaching you
that they swear
you'll use
in your life, you won't.
You're never going to
need to use parabolas
and you really,
really don't
need to know shapes
that have more than
eight fucking sides.
The second...
The second,
which I've only got some
perspective on recently,
but it's this.
You can't keep
putting aside what you want
for some imaginary future.
You've just got to suck it up
and go with your gut.
All right, guys.
This is it.
This is the last song
of your prom.
Make it good.
You gonna sit here?
All right.
Fuck it.
I'm gonna do it.
Good.
Hey.
Um...
I wanted to tell you, um,
I have serious
feelings for you.
And I would
like to cut in.
And also...
Junior, I'd like to
be your girlfriend.
So you're saying that
you want to try
and be together?
Yeah.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
So...
Did you hear the one
about the grown woman
who fell in love
with the really
pissed off lawyer?
Is it funny?
It's really funny.
Come here.
Close the door.