Aah!
What did you
run into me for?
I didn't mean it, mate.
That guy pushed me.
What did you
run into me for?
What are you
doing here?
What are
you doing here?
Let me tell
you something.
I want you
to listen to me.
This is not
your country.
Get the yellow fuck!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Get him!
You like it, gooky boy,
you like it?
Fuck off!
Chickenshit.
Where is he, inside?
Yeah. He hasn't
come out yet
but he's expecting you.
That was Pommy Bill.
He's come to help.
Did he hurt you?
No, but he's
been hitting
the roeies again-- the
worst I've ever seen.
Are you
all right?
Perhaps if you stop
struggling, sir.
Have it your way.
You like punching out
little girls, sir?
The junkies like punching up
little girls, do they?
Have you been taking
the phenytoin?
Yeah.
Where is it?
I don't know. I'm busy.
You haven't, have you?
Seizures been bad?
No.
You've got a bloody
chemist's shop here.
The one drug
you really need
you don't
bother with.
I need some
money, Martin.
Missed you badly.
I don't
want that.
Can't you just
be nice to me?
Pick up your things
and let's get
out of here.
You bastard!
I'm going to
fucking kill you.
I can't stay
with you, Martin.
Come on.
You're the one who
always starts it.
Hey, boys.
Sorry.
The men are here.
The big men
have arrived.
Hey, we need
your muscle.
Rob and Chris
kicked us out.
Three jugs,
Harold.
Fucking Rob
hit me, too.
Stomp him
for us, Davey?
Hey, hey, hey.
Get him out.
I'm not serving any kids--
get him out.
if he doesn't leave,
i'll turn off the beer.
Ooh!
Now!
Come on.
Yeah...
Get your mother
to read you a story.
Piss off, Max.
Go home!
Hey, Rollo
says you had
some gooks in here
last week.
What's it to you?
Why were they here?
It's our place.
No, this is
my fucking place, mate.
Oh, yeah, but you
had gooks here, eh?
Doesn't bother me.
You got a problem
that's your
fucking problem.
Who's that?
I don't know.
A space monster,
if you ask me.
You mean
space cadet, love.
Hey, mate,
you going
to give us
a drink?
Come on, mate.
No, give us a drink.
Wow.
That smells like shit.
Hey, can we go?
Hey, What did you
just call me?
Hey, what did
you just call me?
Just leave it,
and let's just go home.
Don't lean
on my face.
Yeah, fucking whatever
I surrender,
you motherfucker.
Gee, look at that jacket.
it's beautiful.
You want that jacket.
Move!
Nice jacket.
Yeah.
I hope it
was worth it.
It's bleeding.
No, it's not
even deep.
Little bit of glass
in it, though.
You want me
to operate?
It's still bleeding.
This is pretty clean.
Oh.
This is home.
Do you like it?
Yeah, what is
this, a squat?
Squat be fucked,
we pay rent here.
What is this?
Do you love me?
Oh!
Well, you're awake.
Brought my bag up
from downstairs.
I didn't get to salvage much
from the place
where I was living.
Some idiot tore it all up.
These are for tap dancing, see?
But they don't
fit me anymore.
That's a picture
of my mum.
isn't she beautiful?
Everyone says
I look like her.
I'm not saying
I'm good-looking--
I'm not
saying that--
but we do
look alike.
She's dead now.
It was a car accident.
She had her head chopped off.
I think it's good to be able
to talk about these things
without cracking up, you know?
Besides
I know she's still
with me somehow.
I think that when I have kids
she'll be one of them--
you know, sort of reincarnated.
When you see the yellow scum
coming up the road
Will you turn the other cheek
just like a gutless toad?
Or will you stand
your sacred ground
inform him of the facts
Tell him he's not welcome here
then give him several smacks?
Smack him if he's yellow,
smack him if he's black
Smack him till he fucks off
and doesn't come back...
What are you doing?
Fucking keep your mind
on the fucking job,
woman!
What?
Hando,
uh, Magoo.
Magoo.
Way to go!
What are you
doing here?
Didn't have time to
tell you we were coming.
Didn't know
we were coming--
forgot to
fucking stop.
Check this out.
Joined up a couple
of months ago.
What for?
I needed a job,
didn't I?
They put you
through school.
I still get to keep
the hair short.
You're a hippie
with hair that long.
Hey.
I thought you wanted
to shoot guns, mate?
I want to get
into a fucking sub.
Fire torpedoes.
How are you?
We're the handsome
Canberra boys
come to see the ugly
Melbourne boys.
This is my mate Magoo.
That's Jacqui
and that's Flea.
Hi.
Got something
for you, boys.
Macka pulled it
from the basement
of the war museum.
Standard issue
for the Hitler youth.
Wow!
Cheap alloy.
Not that good--
made in '45
towards the end
of the war.
They were running
out of metal then
weren't they?
I'll take it.
50 bucks.
$30.
$40, then.
Ow!
Come on, Davey
you robbed me
of $50, mate.
That's all I got.
All i can stand for.
Come on!
Here. Pay me back
next dole check.
Magoo.
Champ man.
Hey, how's Billy?
Look's all right.
It will be
all right.
I'll change
that bandage later.
He's going to
fucking kill him.
Any parties happening
in this sh-shitty town?
Pulling on the boots
and tightening up the laces
Shaving our heads
and strapping on the braces
Now you are a skinhead
looking for a fight
Skinhead, skinhead,
running through the night
Making lots of trouble,
starting lots of fights
Skinhead, skinhead,
getting really pissed
tattooed on my wrist
Lurking in the laneway,
waiting for the scum
Smash their yellow faces,
kick their fucking bums
When they plead for mercy,
we will show them none
Skinhead, skinhead,
till the job is done
putting in the boot
Looking for a street fight,
looking for a root
Skinhead, skinhead,
running through the place
stomping on your face
When the coppers see us,
at first they pull their gun
But when they see us come
towards then they start to run
When we wear our badges,
it makes us real proud
Skinhead, skinhead,
shout it out loud
running through the night
Making lots of trouble,
starting lots of fights
Skinhead, skinhead,
getting really pissed
tattooed on my wrist
Skinhead, skinhead,
running through the night
Making lots of trouble,
starting lots of fights
Skinhead, skinhead,
getting really pissed
tattooed on my wrist
Skinhead, skinhead,
putting in the boot
Looking for a street fight,
looking for a root
Skinhead, skinhead,
running through the place
Skinhead, skinhead
stomping on your face!
Skinhead, skinhead.
Wow, Bubsy!
Davey, cop a drink?
Nice party, mate.
I've got to get
the first bus back to base.
You enjoy being cannon fodder
for the system?
It's a job.
See you, Hando.
Hey, Flea.
You look
like shit, Davey.
Stupid little bugger.
Why do you go in
for all this stuff?
Because I don't want to be a
white coolie in my own country
because it's not
our country anymore
because rich people
and powerful people
brought in boatloads
of human trash--
cheap labor, gooks mainly
and there's going to be more.
I want people
to know that I'm proud
of my white history
and my white blood.
One day,
it might be all I have.
But I don't want to go
the same way as the fucking abo.
See that map?
That's all the gook properties
on Barcley Street.
A few years ago,
that was a white area.
Mein Kampf.
You know it?
It's about war, isn't it?
This book was written
by Adolf Hitler
and turned into a joke
by the people
who don't want you to know
Hitler's view of the world.
It's simply about the ongoing
struggle of the white race
and the enemies it faces.
if you don't know
who the enemy is
you can't
win the war.
Listen.
"AII the noble cultures
of the past declined
"because the purity and vigor
"of the originally
created race faded out.
"They were
compromised
"by the seed
of lesser races
"who were attracted
to the works
of the superior men."
"The undeniable reason
for their decline was then
"due to a kind
of racial blood poisoning.
"Racial blood must,
then, be preserved
in its purity at all costs."
The money will
be transferred
to your account
in 30 days.
Did you finalize your plans
for the old place?
We will turn
the place
to the restaurant
with bar
for my sons to run
when a little older
if they are
smart enough.
Well.
You going to
root it, Bubsy?
I don't care.
Fuck Harold.
I'm just going out
for about an hour.
Mister...
his sons want to have
a look around.
This red's going to do lovely
things for your eyes.
Just watch
my makeup, okay?
What are you eating
that rubbish for?
You got rocks
in your head?
Geez...
I'm not living
with no fat bitch.
Hando, gooks down
at the railway hotel.
Fuhrer, fuhrer,
what have we done?
Our land is being overrun
by Jews and Blacks
and yellow scum
Fuhrer, fuhrer,
what have we done?
But I want to go.
Stay here.
Piss off, Bubs.
Fuhrer, fuhrer,
what'll we do?
Fuck you, you bastards!
Did your best
to discourage the Jew
Fuhrer, fuhrer,
what'll we do?
Fuck you, I'm going!
Fuhrer, fuhrer
Want to come?
Our day will come
We'll crush the scum.
How you going?
Shit!
Get the gooks down here.
Shut up!
Door, Brett.
Right!
Shut up!
Time to die, gook.
Time to fucking die!
Shut up.
Oh, let's break
some fingers.
Tiger, fucking
skinheads!
What are you
doing here, Bubs?
You were told
not to come.
Fuck off,
shithead.
Let me
through.
Fuck me!
What's happening?
What are you
doing here?
Hey, why don't
you bloody well
do what you're
told, woman?
I told you
to stay.
They're
only kids.
Who says?
We hate you, gook.
We'll never
let you go.
This is our
place, gook boy.
Our place!
What are you
doing here, eh?
The only thing
for you here is pain.
We don't love you.
You understand?
I hope you do, mate
because I don't
speak monkey talk!
Give him
smack-in-head special.
Maybe you got him enough?
Go on, hit
one of them.
Come on, go for it.
Hando.
Hando, Hando!
There's gooks!
Thousands of them!
Monkeys! Monkeys!
Come on!
Magoo!
Fuck! Gooks!
Cunt!
How do you
like it?
You fucking
like it, man?
How do you fucking
like it, huh?
Brett!
Wait for Brett,
you bastards!
Oh, fuck!
Fourth Reich fighting men,
that's who we are
We're living in the sewer,
but we're gonna go far
You see our numbers growing,
we're shouting, "Hurrah"
Fourth Reich fighting men,
that's who we are
We're fighting the system,
fighting the war
You think there's
not enough of us
There's gonna be more
We're gonna change
the country
We're gonna change the laws
and Fourth Reich fighting men,
winning the war
Fourth Reich fighting men,
that's who we are
We're living in the sewer
But we're gonna go far
You see our numbers growing,
we're shouting, "Hurrah"
Fourth Reich fighting men,
that's who we are
We march so proud,
carrying the flag
Beating up vermin,
beating up slag
Beating up the fairies
for dressing in drag
Fourth Reich fighting men,
carrying the flag
that's who we are
We're living in the sewer
But we're gonna go far
You see our numbers growing
We're shouting, "Hurrah"
Fourth Reich fighting men,
that's who we are
At last united
Fighting as one
The fighting isn't finished
till the job is done
The battle isn't over
Till the war is won
Fourth Reich fighting men
fighting as one
Fourth Reich fighting men,
that's who we are
We're living in the sewer
but we're gonna go far
You see
our numbers growing...
Go!
Fourth Reich fighting men,
that's who we are
Marching in the alleys,
marching in the streets
Terrorizing scum with
the sound of marching feet
When the marching is over,
it'll be all right
Everyone will live together
In the Fourth Reich.
Fuck this!
Fuck those fucking dogs!
But we're gonna go far
You see our numbers growing
We're shouting, "Hurrah"
Fourth Reich fighting men,
that's who we are
We're living in the sewer
but we're gonna go far
You see our numbers growing
We're shouting, "Hurrah"
Fourth Reich fighting men,
that's who we are
Fourth Reich fighting men
Fourth Reich fighting men...
Fuck this!
Fourth Reich fighting men
Fourth Reich fighting men...
Make fucking room!
Fourth Reich fighting men
Come on,
you wankers!
Fucking wankers!
Gooks!
Come on!
Fourth Reich fighting men
Fourth Reich fighting men.
Wankers!
You fucking asshole fucks!
Fuck you!
Gookie!
You fat,
fucking cow!
Jesus, we're getting crushed!
Fuckers!
You fucking
gook bastards!
Fuck you!
What happened?
What are we
going to do?
There are fucking
thousands of them!
Shut up!
Shut up, I said!
They got Champ,
Luke, and Magoo.
Why didn't you
all stop and help?
What do you expect
you fucking little
dickhead?
Where is Jacqui?
We should have stopped!
Bullshit!
We're in
for it.
Like fuck, Sonny.
They're at the front door.
Oh!
Come in.
Come on.
You fucking filthy,
slope-head scum.
You filthy, yellow monkeys!
What the fuck are you afraid of?
This is
our place.
No more running.
We stop
them here!
You look like a bunch
of scared fucking rabbits!
Through the manhole,
across the roof.
All right
Davey?
Go!
Fucking
move it!
Don't fucking
rush me, you...
Bubs.
Move it!
Let's go!
Keep your
head down.
They don't know
we're here.
Gabe!
Where's your jacket?
Davey!
Fucking next time, mate!
Rob! Oh, come on.
Rob!
Rob, open the door!
Rob, open up!
Rob, is that you,
prick wife-basher?
What are you
doing here?
Can we talk to
you for a while?
How long
is a while?
I don't know.
Where's Tracy?
I'm here, Rob.
How come you stopped
making love to me?
That's it.
Get lost.
She smoked my
fucking stash.
Rob, I know we haven't
known each other for long
but we feel bad
about what happened.
We'd like to
give you money
to pay for
the food we ate.
You have money?
Pigs!
Rob, don't
be a bastard.
We want to make it
up to you.
Well, stick it
in the hole.
if you want
this money
then have
the decency
to see us
face-to-face.
Serves you right,
you wanker!
I'll kill you
for this, Megan!
Shut up!
Ha, ha, ha!
Hello!
Oh, come on, guys.
Let him go.
How's it going?
Oh, yeah.
"Oh, yeah."
Is that all you got
to say for yourself?
Hello, Chris.
Let's have a tonguey
for the skins.
Come on.
Tonguey for the skins.
Fucking faggots,
are you?
Tongue, faggots!
Faggots!
Sonny!
We're going to stay here
for a while.
You guys don't want
to hang around, do you?
Do you?
Now, I'm going to ask
you nicely to leave.
if i see either one
of you again...
I'm going to chop
your legs off.
Okay?
Stupid shit.
Hando.
Hando,
I'm starving, man.
Hippie degenerates.
Oh, hot food.
Yeah, so do you
do much cooking?
Sometimes.
Really?
My mum was a good cook.
And I liked
home ec at school.
They had a great kitchen
at Linley.
Where?
Linley Hall,
it's my old school.
Well, one of them.
What is this shit?
Vegetables and pasta sauce.
Anything else?
Well, I used everything we had.
Hey, Sonny.
i can put different sauce
on it if you like.
Like the disposal unit?
Bloody wog crap!
Thanks for helping.
Sometimes I live
like a slob, you know.
But when I
make the effort...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. It
was an accident.
Don't!
Stop it.
No!
All right.
It was an accident.
Gabe?
What are
you doing?
Davey, do
something!
What's wrong?
She's a spastic.
So, what's the matter
with you, then?
Does it happen often?
Sometimes.
I'm not crazy or anything.
No one said
you were:
I just get these
fits sometimes.
There's stuff
i can take for it.
I say we get a shotgun
and spray Harold's window.
Shotguns are for
Elmer Fudd, dickhead.
I vote we get
a .45 automatic
and blow the head gook
back to Singapore.
Saigon, stupid.
i fired a .45
at a range once.
it was far out.
You never used a .45.
Don't shit me, Sonny.
What would you know,
baby Bubs?
An anti-static gun's
big news for you.
We can get any sort of gun
we want from Bully.
All we need
is the cash.
We need it
up front.
if you lot are going
to shoot people...
We're going.
Then go.
We don't want any
fucking passengers
from here on in.
So fuck off.
Sonny...
Do you want
to come with us?
No.
I want to kill gooks.
Gooks.
We could go
fruit picking.
i hate the fucking country.
Don't I?
All right, then.
You'll all
end up fucked.
You'll end up fucked
if you don't piss off.
You fucking moles.
I want guns.
Luke, Magoo,
Champ, Brett.
I want revenge.
Bully handles cars, eh?
Yeah, fuck cars.
Let's do a burg.
You want to knock
over a house, do you?
What about it?
I know a place you could do.
It's better than anything
you got on your minds.
Hi.
Ow. Ow.
Fuck your mouth.
You're not going to hit
me again, are you?
Ha!
How are your
renovations going?
Ah, bloody endless.
More Bundy, less Coke.
See, I remembered.
Are you going to stay?
No, this is
just a visit.
Oh, God!
I love you.
Do you know that?
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Sorry.
I'm going to go
to the loo.
I'll be back
in a sec.
Ha!
Nice place you have here.
Who the hell are you?
We came to wreck everything
and ruin your life.
God sent us.
Cheers, mate.
Good on you.
To Martin, the big,
fat, rich pig.
Fucking sack of shit.
Oh, fuck, mate.
You hit me
in the eye, there.
Gook.
Thanks, Martin.
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck, mate.
What's in it?
Whack it
in there, mate.
in there.
That's shit, isn't it?
Could be worth something.
The guns will be worth a lot.
Hey, Gabe.
Bubs.
Hey, Hando.
i found one
without the barrel filled in.
It doesn't work, though.
None of them work, Bubs.
The firing pin's
been ground down.
Still looks good, though.
So what does this bastard do
anyway?
Well, he used to be
in advertising
but he made films.
He did Mortal Blade
and Last Blood.
They came out
last year.
Did you
see them?
So how do you know him?
He's my dad.
He won an award
for this poster.
It's good, isn't it?
Did you see it?
He's very talented,
you know.
I'll play you.
Go on, then.
Oh, you fuck.
Hurry up,
come on:
Let's get it
fucking loaded
so we can piss off.
What a
fucking tragedy
breaking this up
for parts.
Cackles!
Just be fucking
careful, all right?
Martin really
loved this car.
Hmm.
Blotted his
copy book
with that piece
of shit, didn't he?
Jap crap.
Bubs!
Come on.
Why are you doing this to me?
I want to see you squirm.
Incredible little bitch.
I loved you.
That wasn't love.
Let me go, Gabrielle.
Why didn't you love mum?
Did she know about us?
Did she?
Sometimes... I think
she killed herself.
She died in an accident.
An accident,
that's all there was to it.
I loved her...
and I loved you.
Shut up!
And you wanted me!
Next time,
I'll aim at your skull.
Check this out.
Timmy and Ted
went to bed
Dressed in red
dressing gowns.
Who's Timmy and Ted?
My cats.
I used to always do this.
That's my brother,
Nicholas.
He's gay now.
He's cute, though.
You're cute, too.
Give me a look.
Oh, it looks all right.
See, Hando doesn't act
like he likes me.
He likes you, though,
doesn't he?
He's my best mate.
I want him to go away
on a holiday with me.
Just him and me.
And you.
You'd like that,
wouldn't you?
You like me, don't you?
Don't you?
Quelle etrange
ardeur s'allume!
Quel feu nouveau me consume!
Ta main repousse ma main
De nos coeurs
I'amour s'empare
Et nous change en ennemis
Non, que rien
ne nous separe!
Non, rien!
Non, rien ne nous separe!
Jurons de rester amis!
Jurons...
Oh, oui!
Jurons de rester amis!
Oui, c'est elle,
c'est la deesse...
I'll kill you, boy!
C'est elle,
c'est la deesse...
He's got a gun!
Ayons meme sort!
Soyons amis
jusqu'a la mort.
Gabrielle!
Stop doing that
to your hair--
You look fucking
pathetic--
and while
you're at it
keep the fucking
noise down as well.
I told you to shut up!
What's wrong with you?
You, you dumb slut--
shut up.
Don't go crazy at me
just because you and your mates
fucked up.
You had it all
on a plate
but no, you had to play
silly buggers with the car.
Why couldn't you just
take his stuff and go?
You're a loser.
Don't call me that.
No one ever calls me that!
I was going to give her
to you, anyway.
I want you to go.
i'm sick of
looking at you.
Go!
We're finished.
You're out.
Just like that?
Yes.
All right.
You...
You'll all end up...
Shut up.
You live like shit!
You can't even
look after yourselves!
You're just... hopeless!
Where the fuck
are you going?
I'm going home.
Well, good riddance
to you, too, boy!
Maybe you'll get
that fuck you've been after
for so long!
Davey...
What are you leaving us for?
You leaving us for her?
You're a suck.
You're weak!
You're piss-weak
and gutless.
Fuck off, little Bubs.
I thought
you were strong.
You're weak,
you're weak.
You're nothing!
Gabe?
Leave me alone!
Gabe!
Look...
There's something
I've got to do.
Can I come?
No.
Have you got
a piece of paper?
No.
Bubs.
Look... if ever
you need me or want me
I'll be at this address.
Is that Footscray police?
Listen, um...
I know where there's some people
that you might be looking for.
Shut up,
fuckhead.
All right!
it got cut off yesterday.
Anyone know we're here?
No.
No way.
Is there a tap outside?
I don't know.
I thought you were
supposed to be my scout.
Fourth Reich fighting men
Fourth Reich fighting men...
Drop it!
Bubs!
Right.
Pick him up,
Pick him up!
Oh, no.
Copper, you murdering
fucking...
You fucking...
Fuck off!
You fucking pig!
Les-slut!
Oh, fuck you!
i'll fucking kill you!
I surrender.
Too fucking late.
They're smiling at you.
You have a lovely smile too.
Thank you.
David.
David!
Hi, Gabe.
Why don't you
bring your friends
into the house
and entertain
them in there?
They're okay
out here, Gran.
You don't look right
without your jacket
with all the badges.
Well, my grandma--
she doesn't know about that.
She doesn't like
the badges or anything.
I don't want to upset her.
It's her place.
What's this?
That's my
matchbox collection.
My dad...
He's an industrial diver.
He travels all around the world.
See?
Amsterdam,
San Francisco
Venice, Perth
Naples.
I think he's in Sydney working
on the Sydney Harbour tunnel.
I haven't got a box
from there, huh?
Ow!
I love you.
I love you too.
Don't ever leave me.
Hando!
They killed Bubs.
What?
The cops come.
They took everybody else.
They killed Bubs.
How did they know
where to get us?
No, she's been with me
since she left the squat.
She hasn't told anyone.
David!
What is wrong?
Why are my liebchens
barking so?
It's just a cat.
They've seen a cat.
I'm alone, Gran.
You can't come in,
I'm not dressed.
They'll find
you here.
They'll come
looking for you.
Yeah.
I think we should
stick together.
Past is past, right?
You're all I've
got left, Davey.
What do you want
to do?
I've got a plan, mate.
Don't kill him!
Shut up!
No, he's fucking
killed him!
Oh, Jesus!
Is he dead?
is the car full?
is the car full?!
Is he dead?!
Yes.
is the car full?
The fucking Jerry?!
Yes!
Hurry up!
Why did you fucking
kill him?
We'll dump this piece
of shit in Adelaide.
I haven't been
to the beach in years.
Be all right if
we stay here a while?
Not long.
I think we should
go west.
I'll get you through this,
I promise.
Davey!
We just have
to stick together.
i'm not afraid.
She's sick, mate.
She's trouble.
She doesn't
really want you.
She'll just use you.
You won't get nowhere
with her, Davey.
She needs medicine
or something.
She's my problem,
isn't she?
Listen to me.
Take your hands off me!
I'm sick
of listening to you!
She's desperate!
She'll drag
you down, Davey.
She doesn't love you,
if that's what you think.
Is that what you think?
She's fucking desperate,
that's all.
Davey, she's going
to drag us both down.
Besides which...
you don't want
her involved
if we get caught
for last night, do you?
We've got to
get rid of her.
She can have a share
of the money.
Can't be fairer
than that.
Do you want
to tell her?
I'll tell her
if you want.
You're not just
dumping her.
We'll give her, uh...
We'll give her fucking...
We'll give her fucking
200 bucks, all right?
You've looked after her
as far as you can.
Are you going
to tell her?
I'm with her,
and she's with me.
Well, Davey, I tried.
What's that?
That's where
the fucking car is!
What happened?
What happened,
you mental bitch?
Mental bitch, ha!
I heard what
you two said.
I know what
you're going to do.
You suck, Davey.
You can't do anything
without him.
It was me
who called the cops.
What?
I called them.
Davey!
Hando!
I told you,
you stupid cunt!
i fucking
told you!
i fucking told you!
You bitch, you're fucking dead!
Fuck!
Stop!
Stay.