The guys we meet...
are ruthless
They know our dot. com is going
to be a big hit
They want to get it
Remember to keep a high profile
What do you mean?
Be cool
We don't need answer what they ask?
I won't sign any deal
less than $10 billion
No kidding
Sooner or later
we'll have that much of money
But we don't have it now. Brother
Any new plan in mind? Tell me
Did you feel my punch down there
- I was about to beat this level
- Really?
Hey!... Pass the bridge...
tidy up yourself...
We want to go...
to a restaurant "Green Leaf"
in China Town
Which restaurant?
My son works there,
he makes a lot of money
Do you have the address?
On what street?
I don't have the address with me.
No address
English...
We are Taiwanese, we don't know English
China Town,
a restaurant named, Green Leaf
They're Taiwanese and
want to go to Green Leaf Restaurant
in China Town
Green Leaf Restaurant?
I heard of it...
China Town, well... Yeah...
Okay, let's go
Thanks ...
Sorry
Bob, you're happy too early.
It's not firm yet
Why did you turn down the deal?
To do business is just like
chasing after girls
When she says no, that means maybe
When she says maybe, that means okay
Okay means to take off your clothes fast.
Come on
You knew how it plays, right?
You've so many women around you
I never bring women home
Why?
Just like acquisition of a company
Women will bring
in their cooking utensils, clothes...
What can I do?
Too much pressure
That's right. Once they come,
they'll bother you all the time
Invade your privacy and ruin your life
No more sexual fantasy. Impossible!
No way! No...
Finished
Don't worry!
Yes, take it easy
Why?
Pay the fare
That's so easy
Isn't it normal?
Genius like you must win the game
It's lucky that
you didn't break the computer
Come on... Stop playing
Come on... Drink some
Be a good boy.
Give me some great ideas...
...to be proposed at next meeting
Wow, once it's signed,
we can easily get the $10 billion
Give me some more time
Cool, man. Look
See anything?
This place is filled with inspirations
Smell it?
Don't worry.
If you're hungry, I'll get you some food
If you want woman, I'll get you one
If you want man, I'll be at your service
Okay, I'm going to buy some food
Will be back. Don't go out
Mike, do you know why I brought you here
You completed your first...
search engine at this place
Give me another mind-boggling idea!
Please don't go
I'll get you some shark fin soups
and abalone
I'll be back soon
Ellen
Your son Scott is really something
He's a genius
What are you doing?
I want to marry your son
Don't be silly!
My son is only ten years old
Mom
Yeah?
I found something
inside uncle Wong's car
Scott
Listen up. Scott...
Mike, I can't find
any shark fin or abalone
How about having a hot dog and Sandra Ng
Mike...
Mike
Dance one more time
Your son is really something.
Amazing. Look at him!
What did you found in the car?
Quick, come here, watch him
Sunny Boy
Aunt Chiu
Mel G
What are they playing?
Tell me! What is it?
He found this
Scott
Look like it?
You'd better stop. Let's go!
Come! Stop...
Aunt Chiu, check the engine for me
It's slower than the cable car...
driving on California Street
Mel G. One more time
See, this is the best size-big
You're big! You're bigger
You're bad! It's sick!
Hey, stop! Don't take it...
Mom, you hate to see me
playing the vibrator?
Of course!
Mothers don't like their children
playing this kind of game
Also, don't copy whatever they teach you
Understand?
Mom, I taught them
Oh! Really?
Mouster is here too!
Tina said it's normal to have a vibrator
Every woman has one in her drawer
Don't you dare look at my drawer?
Okay
Take your meal, I'm just kidding
Scott, no...
You chicky monster!
Hey, Baby, come meet me
Where are you?
Friday Night, come and have a drink
I met...
a Hugh Grant here
I'm not going
I've saved...
you a Richard Gere, salt and pepper hair
You keep him for yourself
- Mom, you aren't going out?
- No
Remember to brush your teeth
before sleep
Hello?
Ellen
What's going on?
Hugh Grant left...
with a Spanish girl!
How about your Richard Gere?
I want a friend now, not a man
No way
Yes
How come?
Come and keep me company
It's too late. I'm not going
Ellen, I want you!
Can you just enjoy yourself?
I threw up 3 times, Ellen
Uh?
Ellen, I'm feeling bad
Come, please
Alright...
Richard Gere?
Thank you
Me too. Come...
I don't want to play
Come on
Okay
What? What is it?
Can I quit?
One second...
Okay...
Okay, what's your name?
Ellen
I'm Mike
We create a fantastic San Francisco.
Okay?
I've told you, you did it!
Help me out
I get off work
What do you want to do with my car?
What you want?
Wait
Alright. Pretty!
Why'd you piss on it if it's pretty?
It's a beautiful painting.
Come closer to have a better look
Really?
What is it?
Sausalito
Sausalito?
How do you know?
It's Sausalito
Really?
I don't think so
I paint it. I say it is
- You paint it?
- Yes!
A great scenery,
like Sai Kung in Hong Kong?
You live there?
I can't afford it
Just kidding. Don't get too serious
Right?
I don't really know you
My home is not a good place
So is mine
Please, don't stare at me
No... the other side
A little bit more...
Keep still!
Good morning!
Morning!
Have you seen my shoe?
No
No? Impossible
Where is it?
Just buy another pair
No! This one...
Forget it! Go...
Back...
Alright
Where are you going?
303 Central Street
Mike, your favorite curry chicken
It can go with bread or corns
Enough for several days
If you've time to have a nice dinner
at our restaurant
You pan is badly burnt
You ignore me!
I'm trying to be nice to you,
to cook for you!
You don't care at all!
Can you say a word?
I am only your landlord
You're very sick!
Your muscle is really tight
Bob called the restaurant
to look for you
Did he make trouble at your restaurant?
He dares not,
but he scared my honey though
He's insane
But when he goes nuts,
he scares us stiff
Actually, why you're hiding from him?
I'm not
I just want to take a break, can't I?
Scrape for a few more times
San Francisco is humid
If you don't scrape your back well,
you'll have rheumatism
You nag all day long!
Last month it's on the 5th
it should be on the 8th this month
Should be okay
Mom, where did you go last night?
I came to this place
Don't lie to me!
It's bad for mommy to lie
Mom, I am not coming home next Saturday
Try to scare me
I'll go to Foster...
with Charles' family. Okay?
You go with Charles
or his sister?
Let's go to work
Wow, you've many scratches on your back
Did it last night?
Yes
Where?
Sausalito
Mom
When will we move to Sausalito?
Soon. Very soon
Scott, do you want to have a dog?
But you can't take it home
For couple times?
Yes
With a woman?
Of course!
It eases my worry
Mike, it's about time
So, what's her name?
Mom, what should I call it?
Call it Mike
Let's go home
Did you fight with Charles?
Really?
Don't stay up too late
I'd know
I'm home
Hello
Tina, you still at home?
Not feeling well. Not going anywhere
Really?
Sick on Saturday night of all nights
Get some rest, don't go out
That's fast
What do you mean?
With that guy
Why not?
Except banning indoors smoking,
San Francisco is a great place
If you follow the rules of the game,
you'll have fun
What's the rules of the game?
Take it easy
Relax! Don't make other people
and yourself unhappy
Want to be serious, then go ahead.
Get it?
You came all the way...
to tell me to take it easy?
We're friends
If that guy was tough and
took three hours,
you would be here waiting for me
Waiting for a woman
who had a one-night-stand with you
Tell her to take it easy
What a caring man!
Does it mean take it easy?
Forget about last time.
Let's start all over again, okay?
Not in the car this time
Wait
Why you keep looking at me?
Can't I?
I've pressure
Mike? You can't fool me.
I've been looking for you
Please return my call
I know you're at home.
I'll come to get you!
Come see me at once. Mike...
I was in college at that time
Except chatting up with women at bar,
I know nothing
When I came here,
I completed a search engine programme
And bankers started to visit me. They
supported me in launching my own startup
The first miracle in my life began
At that time, I found earning money easy
I devoted myself to my work
But then...
I thought I'm a step ahead
Others are 3 steps ahead of me
I got a lot of pressure
It doesn't matter, Mike
Just quit!
You don't need to fabricate story, okay?
Is it really your home?
Does it make a difference?
You just sounded like a rich man
impossible to live at this kind of place
I came here at the age of 14
I hung out in Chinatown...
...and followed the orders
of the triad boss here
Do you remember the case
of Golden Dragon Restaurant?
Yes. Many people got killed
I was there
Really?
Yes
That's why the FBI is tracking me down
No wonder you don't want me
to took at you
That's right
You're better off not to know too much
Hi, are you looking for Mike?
I want to give him something
But he hasn't got up this early
Can I pass it to him?
Alright. Thanks
Sorry, you're his friend?
Come in to have a seat?
Just get him out of the bed
That's okay. I've to go to work. Bye
Sorry, what's your name?
Ellen
Goodbye
No bad!
Good morning
Morning
My dear. How are you?
Your car has been fixed. I drove it back
Thanks
Mike
I know it's none of my business,
but are you serious with her?
The millennium has passed,
why did you buy so many stuffs?
To stock up for the new year?
Two frying pans?
I only bought one
Another was from Ellen
Which one you want me to use?
This girl is very caring
Toothbrush, toothpaste, and towel!
I forget to buy them
Wow... there're more
Whose bag is this? Yours?
This is mine. And that bag is hers
What are you doing? Mike!
Can you give me a minute?
Sorry, please wait for a second?
What's up?
You forgot your stuffs
I bought them on my way. It's for you
Don't eat too much can food.
It's bad for your health
I don't like people leaving
their stuffs at my house
It's nothing. After you eat it,
nothing is left at your house
How can I eat up the towel,
toothpaste, and pan?
You told me to take it easy, right?
Okay, I pay you the money
Pay me back?
You pay me for the small things
I bought for you!
Then...
...should I pay you
for what you did last night?
Okay...
How can you do this to me?
Alright, I'll pay you next time, okay?
It's my purchase, okay?
Forget it. Give me back!
Stop...
- Who are they?
- Triad gangsters
Stop! Mike...
Ellen, Sunny Boy's on his way
with Scott to meet you for lunch
Copy
Where are you?
Tina, call our guys to come and help!
Help!
Hurry up!
You give me the $10 billion?
$10 billion...
Are you able to pay me the money?
You bastard!
Why you're hitting him? Stop...
Stop!
Hey... stop...
How dare you hit my mom? Want to die?
Kid, you don't move! Stop!
Ellen, what happened?
Triad gangsters!
What gangsters? Bullshit!
Who are the triads? You? Triad!
Come here if you've gut...
Mike, come over here!
Show her my card
This is my name card
I'm not in the triad, he isn't too
He's my cousin
I'm just kidding last night
- Didn't imagine you would be...
- Serious, right?
This is me
Let's go!
It's fine. Get back to work
Mike, I've an appointment with C&G...
I don't want to sell!
Why don't you call me
to go out to have fun?
You look just like the time
when your husband divorced you
Sorry
Something in your mind?
You did it better in high school
Dessert?
I don't want to nag you
But you can't be unrestrained
all your life
When you realize
you can't put it down...
Then hold on to it
I experienced that in the past
Not too bad though.
At least I've someone with me now
It makes your life easier...
...if you can pull out every time
You'll enjoy yourself more
the next time
When you find that hon can't put it down
you gotta face it
Seriously, every woman needs...
...a warmer
It's true! It's not a bad idea to use
men warming up our feet in winter
You haven't tried it?
Mike
If you can't put it down,
don't force yourself,
you know
My boy!
Ellen...
Copy
Some one has called for you
Where?
Castro
Copy that
Hi, my landlord wants to invite you
for dinner. Would you come?
I'm sorry. I've to work
What are you doing?
I'm not for delivery
You care only about yourself.
I can't do that!
Sorry
You're the first woman in my life
I said the most "sorry"
It's a simple dinner
And you can leave anytime
Let me introduce you...
to my landlord, Robert
- Hi
- Hello
Ellen, right?
Yes
We met before
My dear, Ellen is here
Come to say hello
My honey is a good chef
I'm sorry to bother your wife
I don't have a wife
Don is my husband. I'm his wife
Hello, nice to meet you
Hello
Mike, go to help Don
I'll keep Ellen company
When Mike was 14,
he moved here with his parents
They rented their first house from me
But his parents died not long after
Then, Mike stayed with me.
I bought him up
He's quite a good boy.
When he has time, he comes to see me
He earned his way to college
Don't worry.
I never make advances to him
I've treated him like my own son
You know we're gay
How can we teach him to be a real man?
That's why he's not
too serious about life
I don't know how to teach my son, either
Sometimes, I feel he's stronger than me
Really?
Okay
Let's cheers for two unqualified mothers
Sometimes Mike is wrong
But he's no bad intention
Sometimes,
he hurts people without knowing it
I'm fine. Don't worry
But he isn't fine
You're the first woman
he's willing to bring home
Never mind,
who knows what will happen next
Cheers!
Ellen, try Mike's cooking
Mike is good at two things
One is barbecue chicken
The other is burned the pan
You've talked too much. I know I'm bad
Give me a piece of pork!
Good
A toast to mike's chicken
and self-criticism
I don't mean to keep quiet,
but I've nothing to say
No way! You must say something
Or, drink up
Don't force her. She has nothing to say
What?
Ellen doesn't look like a taxi driver
Why you chose this job?
Alright
First, my old classmate Tina...
operates a taxi rental business
Second...
I can't think of any other job
that can earn money
with your back facing customers
Third,
I can look at handsome guys
from my mirror
Is that good enough?
Yeah!
Let me share with you my new plan
Great!
I plan to design a global community,
a nation-state on the Internet
I'm the president there
People of different nationalities...
can be naturalized to be the citizens
It's just like
the real life...
...with everything available
It has a bar,
and you two can be the bosses
You can install a view camera...
...to see the faces of each other
Everyone can see what you're doing
You can listen to music together
This jazz music is created
by some friends on Internet
If you don't like music,
you can watch a movie
There're a lot more
what a meaningful idea!
Nonsense!
For you...
I'm sorry,
there's no taxi on the Internet
But it doesn't matter. You love drawing
You can post your drawing
of Sausalito...
...on the Internet
And to share your inspirations...
...your affection for Sausalito...
with them
Well, I wish this dream can become true
Let's cheers!
Okay!
Cheers for our gay bar!
In fact,
I don't really like San Francisco
I'm tired of all the hustle...
in my life
Can you read palm?
Not this. That one
It represents San Francisco
No love line, no life line,
no career line
It's doomed to have...
...no accomplishment,
and it won't live long
But it has its own charm
Like earthquake,
every thing will be destroyed
with seconds
What can they do?
We should treasure...
...our time together
You gave these sweet-talks
to your other women?
Honestly
I start to like it...
Nirvana
Nirvana?
What did you say earlier?
Empire? Emperor?
A global community on the Internet
Called it Nirvana
Do you like it?
It's suitable
Good morning!
Morning!
Breakfast'll be ready in a second
I don't know where you live
That's why I drove you here
It's your house?
Yes. Like it?
It's burning
That is my style
When I work on something,
I become very focused
I will forget what I did in the past
Even at home,
I've burnt so many pans each year
Is it really your house?
I mean...
...your own home
I've most of my underwear here
Yours want to join in?
How can I afford it?
I mean... we both live here
Okay?
You're kidding me
No, I'm serious
Where is my car?
At the door
I go to work now
Can you think about it?
Mom, where were you last night?
I went to my friend's place
Oh! Wo Wo?
Mom, do you know that?
I have a holiday in every year
But you don't, you must have a holiday!
I hang out with you
whenever you've a holiday
Then, I won't have any vacation?
Sick of me?
I'm afraid that you are sick of me
I'm ten, but I can already
take care of myself
Do whatever you like!
Aunt Tina taught you to speak
to me like this?
I think she's right
Go ahead, mom!
Let's see
Wow! Handsome!
Go wash your head
Thank you, mom
I love you. Go
Hi
Hi, come in, please
I want to tell you,
the kid who hit your cousin...
...was my son Scott
I know. He called you mom
How old is he?
Ten
I got a divorce when he's two
Good
The only thing I'm grateful
for is my ex-husband
let me have Scott
I don't know why I slept with you
the first time we met?
And slept with you again
at the second time we met?
I wonder if we'll have the third time...
At the third time you slept here, we...
I feel sorry for Scott
Come in and talk. Okay?
How old are you?
33! And you?
Me, too
A 30 something woman is no fun in a game
Right. What's the fun?
A man has dealing...
with a woman of 30 something
You think
I want to see with your choices,
not being able to turn back
Why me?
I love you
I don't want to give Scott
too high an expectation
Let's try first?
I want to tell you one thing
In fact I'm 35 years old
Why you like Sausalito so much?
Don't you think it's like Sai Kung?
You lived in Sai Kung before?
I bought a house there
when I got married
Why divorce?
Because I was married
Do you miss your ex-husband?
If you don't remind me of him,
I've already forgotten about him
Hey, you can't make a mess. No!
Virginia, just wait for one moment...
See! He has come. Mr. Mike!
Let me introduce, Ms. Virginia Chow,
the CEO of C&G
Where did you go?
To watch Scott play baseball
Play baseball?
Mr. Lau, What did you say?
I just said bullshit!
I usually like to be on top
when l'm with a woman
This time, we have big trouble!
What was this being on top
Couldn't you change a position
once a while
What can we do?...
The only way out is to secure a loan
from a bank!
Bank?... Bullshit!
The bank is not your ATM
Everybody is doing...
IT now
We gotta come up
with some new gimmick...
to fool those suits
Hey, friend, my new proposal
Don't trick me!
A suicide manual? Check?
We can go public
completely redeemable...
for cash at the bank
You look nervous
I just want these!
You should have given me
this much earlier
Problems solved
I also hate the women being on top,
no taste
By the way, why you call it Nirvana?
A peaceful and tranquil city
A peaceful and tranquil city?
A wonderful name!
It works. Great!...
Ellen will invite you to join her party
Good name! Wonderful...
Nirvana
Nirvana Kingdom...
I'm 2nd in line
What?
I'm talking about Mike
Go to hell! Have some biscuits!
You don't like him, but I do
Don't eat too much candies
I know
Mike, Ellen is really nice
Don't let her go
Robert, this is for you
- Easter present
- Thank you
You are welcome
How about me?
No, I forgot
How about it?
I just said it
Happy Easter!
Come over here
Mike, I want to talk to you
About what? Sit down first
Over here
I've a good news and a bad news for you
The good news is
I read through your proposal
And realized that you're a genius!
But the bad news is...
I'm the only person recognizes
The bankers rejected the proposal
We can't get the loan
We can find other banks
I talked to...
over 20 banks,
but they all rejected your proposal
I heard...
...that Virginia has been...
bad-mouthing us
So...
If we can't get a loan,
we've to pay back our debt
I talked to Virginia on the phone
Next month she'll come
to San Francisco and stay one day
We must meet her
This time you let her ride
you just for once
Okay?
Mom
When can I move in with you?
Soon
Also,
Wo Wo said he would take us
to Sausalito to see new houses
Really?
I don't want it! Go!
Come on... listen to me
Just see her once again... Shut up
Why didn't tell me earlier?
I wanted to, but I couldn't find you
You didn't try at all.
You keep me in the dark
How I can find you? My master!
Call me!
I called you,
but the line was alway busy
Get out!
Mike, what happen?
Shut up! It's none of your business
Mike, there're guests here
Okay, I'm leaving
Goodbye, everybody
Let's get something to eat over there
Okay
Mike
What happened?
What's up?
Nothing
Didn't you take precaution?
Yes! I do! But it's not yet come.
I just check it for safe!
Safe?
Yes
That good
Yes, nothing
Be careful next time
No problem
Anything?
I'm going to pick up Scott
It's okay. I'll go by myself
No. Let's go together
Mike, let's play baseball?
You go ahead
Come on. Just play few games
Scott, I'm working
Ask your mom to play with you
Scott, mom plays with you, okay?
Mike, listen
I can't implement your proposal...
at this stage
Hire someone to help us
I'm in debt
How can I find money for a new hire?
Okay, I'm a programmer,
I'll write it myself
You're happy now?
Whatever!
Mike, how long you want to hide?
I need some more time
We have no money
I know,
I should get a mortgage on my house
My business also start from zero, okay,
I would come to talk to you
Mike
- I want to talk to you
- Go ahead
Tina has a taxi available.
I want to work
It's up to you!
Mike, why are you here?
You're not inside
Ellen!
Where should I go that you like? Tell me
Sorry. I'm in deep trouble recently
My company runs into debt
The bankers no longer support us
I've great financial difficulties
Didn't Bod say someone wanted
to buy your company?
Don't follow them to talk
about the god damne buy
I won't sell my company
Anyway, you won't understand
Leave me alone!
I know
I'm ignorant and can't help you
I just want to take care
of your house and
cook you a nice dinner
I didn't ask for too much
Do whatever you like, it's up to you
Satisfied
Tell me,
have I done too much or too little?
You've given me too much
It's my fault. You are very kind to me
I think, it's better for Scott
not to move in
No. Let him move in
I didn't expect to meet you here
I thought we would meet at the office
Your company's style is too free.
Not suitable for me
You've something to say?
You never say sorry to a woman?
If it's too hard on you, it's okay
In fact,
I should be the one to apologize
I did tell the bankers
not to loan you the money
I make it happened
because I appreciate your talent
Bob showed me
your Nirvana City proposal
It's very impressive
We didn't have
enough communication before
So we had some misunderstandings
Then...
can we be frank to each other today?
How about we go back to the office...
Contract? Don't worry
The contract is up to my decision
- Mom
- Copy
When will you come to pick me up?
I'll get off work soon
Tina will take you home first, okay?
Alright!
See you soon
Good afternoon
I would like to go to the Majestic Hotel
Sure
Don't worry
Tomorrow I'll send my assistants
to discuss the details with you
Okay
You come to my place, tonight
No
Alright, whatever
Shit!
Ellen
Tina, Mom will take me to Wo Wo's house
Hi
Mom is home
Are you slept with Virginia?
Ellen will be sad if she finds out
She left!
It maybe a good thing
I sold all my shares to C&G
They'll hire me as financial controller
They want to kick you out
from the board of directors
Don't sell!
I've no choice
The take-over announcement demands
for your withdrawal from the board
That means
they want to own the company 100%
But kick you out
Obviously, she just playing you
What's your plan?
No! Under this circumstances...
...it's better to sell it
Did you hear me. I don't sell them
Don't you know our situation?
We've no choice
If we don't sell it, we should both dead
Banks will liquidate us
What do you mean?
We're on the same boat
Do you understand? We've no choice!
You betrayed me
You sold our company to her!
Why did you sell it to her
as she kick me out?
You're out but I'm still in
We're on the same boat
We create this project together
This is betrayal!
How can I possibly betray you?
If I betray you,
I won't wait until today
Am I insane?
I've been taking care of you and
acting like your dog
Why would I betray you?
Where is your mind?
Had I betrayed you,
I would have done so much earlier
I've been standing by you
all these years...
...only because I like you. For what?
I must be crazy. It isn't easy at all
to serve a boss like you
Well, it's normal
We cannot get marry!
Because you are my cousin?
Don't be too stubborn
Sell it when you can
Otherwise, carrying a debt all your life
I got paid, at least you won't have
to scramble to make a living
Alright
Am I being kept by you?
It's no big deal. Right?
You'll be used to it
It's okay
What's up?
We'll come back. Then, sell it
Absolutely
To rebuild our own world,
a fantastic new world
No one dares to bully us
How's Ellen?
Will see
Then, I've chances
No!
Why not? Crazy!
Yes
Why you tell me now
you are gay?
Where's your mind?
Take out your hand!
I'll pay you
You've to give me some advantages...
Are you crazy?
Any questions?
Hello
Okay
Whose call?
Bill Gate!
Thank you. Excuse me!
See you later. Thank you...
Ellen...
Robert, why you have it too?
What happened?
Ellen
What happened? Who are they?
Forgive Mike, please
All of them are Nirvana citizens
Yesterday, Mike chatted with them
on the Internet about you
He told them the story about you
He feels guilty
Mike told you to do that?
No... we ourselves want to do it
Many people told me that you're here
How are you?
Alright. Just the same
A big shock to you?
A little bit
They said it all for you
Would you forgive me?
Don't mention it
Congratulations, your dream comes true
You're part of it
You chose the name of Nirvana
People in Nirvana enjoy their lives
Sorry
Don't be silly
Don't be kidding
I'm not kidding
I'm serious
Would it work this time?
If I were you, I'd already said yes!
Come with me again?
No
Why?
Tell your friends not to be crazy
I can't take too much surprises
Bye
You said no to him?
If I were you,
I would have dashed to hug
and kiss him say yes
Ellen, why?
I rejected him down already.
I can't take back my words
Why not?
If you still love him,
you can change your minds for 100 times
Taking back my words it simple
The problem is...
do I want to start all over again?
what's wrong with it?
He may play the tricks again!
Who knows what will happed next?
Right?
Okay
I forgot to buy some butter
Let's get it for you
Let's kiss first
Be careful your mom, she's so angry!
Eat faster!
It's no big deal,
you can post it on the Internet
Perhaps Miss World will come
for interviews, right?
Why you're running so fast?
Do I have any chances?
Fine! I won't ask you anymore
I shut up and leave you alone
for a while
Just only give you a second
Oh, my god. Scott, come with me.
This way
Stay here
Ellen
Are you both allright?
We are allright, Tina,
come to take care of Scott
Mike?
Your shoe I found you!
Are you allright? Scott is safe?
Do you get any hurt?
I was worried about you
We'll ask the house owner,
if he'd sell it or not?
If he won't?
We build a new house next to his!