Beware the beast man,
for he is the Devil's pawn.
Alone among God's primates,
he kills for sport or lust or greed.
Yea, he will murder his brother
to possess his brother's land.
Let him not breed in great numbers,
for he will make a desert
of his home and yours.
Shun him,
for he is the harbinger of death.
Nova.
Where will you go?
Follow the shoreline.
Don't try to follow us.
I'm pretty handy with this.
Of that, I'm sure.
All my life I've awaited your coming
and dreaded it.
You're afraid of me and you hate me. Why?
The Forbidden Zone
was once a paradise.
Your breed made a desert
of it ages ago.
It still doesn't give me the why.
A planet where apes
evolved from men?
There's got to be an answer.
Don't look for it, Taylor.
You may not like what you find.
Zira, Cornelius, untie me.
What will he find out there, Doctor?
His destiny.
Beneath The Planet
Of The Apes
Damn you all to hell!
No, Skipper. It's...
It's me again.
Just me.
Brent...
did you contact Earth?
I tried to, sir.
Not a crackle.
Skipper...
I took an Earth time reading
just before reentry.
What did you get?
3955.
3955?
A.D.
Almighty God.
Well, we were following
Taylor's trajectory.
So whatever happened to us
must have happened to him.
What about us?
Where... where are we?
Well, in my opinion, Skipper, we've...
we passed through a Haslein Curve,
a bend in time.
I don't know what planet we're on, but...
...fact is we're both of us here,
we're breathing, we're conscious,
we got...
...plenty of oxygen, water.
Here!
We're going to be all right, Skipper.
Gonna be alright.
As soon as you feel better, we'll...
...we'll run
a navigational lesson.
God, if I could only see the sun.
It's up there all right.
You can feel it.
Yes...
but which sun?
I don't know.
I don't know. Our computer's shot.
We're lucky to be alive.
Lucky?
No.
If it's 3955 A.D...
Oh, my God.
My wife...
my two daughters...
dead.
Everyone I ever knew.
Everyone.
Hey!
Who are you?
I... Don't be afraid.
I just...
Just tell me where I am.
Can you understand me?
My name's Brent.
Brent.
No... No, I don't want to hurt you. I...
I just want to know where I am.
Where are you from?
I mean, your people,
where are they? How do l...
How do I get to them? Which way?
Can you... Can you talk?
Right, right, so you can't talk.
Taylor!
Where is he?
Taylor.
Nova.
Come on.
That's the idea.
Taylor.
Nova.
Here.
Taylor.
OK, here's the prize.
Go to the head of the class.
Why don't we settle down
and found a colony?
All the kids will learn to talk.
Sure they will.
Now, where in hell
do we go from here?
We might make it yet.
Taylor.
Just tell me what happened to him.
Is he hurt? ls he alive?
Where is he?
It wasn't here.
A minute ago, that wasn't here.
I'm not the only one.
She sees it, too.
Listen.
Listen now.
If you lose me...
me,
try to find Zira.
Remember?
Zira. Go find Zira.
Zira.
This tag,
did he give it to you?
Where did you get this?
Look, is there...
is there someone...
some other... someone who can talk?
Look.
You...
take me...
to Taylor.
Taylor.
Taylor now.
Which way?
My God, it's...
It's a city of apes.
I'll tell you one thing
that every good soldier knows.
The only thing that counts
in the end is power.
Naked, merciless force!
Members of the Citizens' Council,
I am a simple soldier,
and as a soldier, I see things simply.
I don't say all humans are evil
simply because their skin is white.
No.
But our great Lawgiver tells us
that never,
NEVER will the human
have the ape's divine faculty
for being able to distinguish
between evil and good.
The only good human is a dead human!
It's a bloody nightmare.
But those fortunate enough
to remain alive
will have the privilege
of being used
by our Minister of Science,
the good Dr. Zaius.
Zira, stop. You're in danger.
So is the future of science,
with a rebel rouse fomenting
a senseless military adventure.
The Forbidden Zone has been
closed for centuries,
and rightly so.
However, we now have evidence
that that vast barren area
is inhabited.
By what or by whom we don't know,
but if they live, and live they do,
then they must eat.
Now we must replenish the lands
that were ravaged by the humans
with new improved feeding grounds,
and these grounds we can obtain
in the once Forbidden Zone.
It's therefore our holy duty
to enter it,
to put the marks of our guns
and our wheels and our flags upon it!
To expand the boundaries
of our ineluctable power.
And to invade.
Invade!
Zira, please!
As your husband, I beg you to stand.
Only for my principles.
All right, for your principles and mine.
Only please stand!
I got to get out.
Yeah, I got to get back up there.
I don't know how or what with, but...
...I'm not staying here.
General, I only pray
you know what you're doing.
How can you have any doubt, Dr. Zaius?
You're aware of the reports
we've been receiving
of strange manifestations
in the Forbidden Zone,
manifestations which you,
if I might add,
as Minister of Science,
have been unable to fathom.
12... 12 of my finest scouts
just disappeared,
vanished into thin air.
11.
Huh?
Very well, 11 ...
11.
And the 12th returned
with incredible stories
of huge walls of fire,
strange violent earthquakes,
his... his mind gone,
shattered no doubt
by some unsimian torture.
Well, General,
- I still think you're being hasty.
- No, Doctor. Decisive.
Now we invade or we starve.
It's as simple as that.
And as dangerous.
What is more dangerous
than famine, Doctor?
The unknown.
If I had any proper sense
of scientific purpose, Cornelius,
I shouldn't be cutting up
the healthy heads of humans.
I should be dissecting
the diseased brains of gorillas
to find out what went wrong.
And how would you put it right?
I've wet-nursed their babies
on the milk of chimpanzees
and milk of kindness.
At least our child, when it's born,
won't be breast-fed on bile.
You know, my dear,
the trouble with us intellectuals
is that we have
responsibilities and no power.
I think I'll make a chocolate icing.
Do you like chocolate?
Oh, what, dear?
No no no no.
Of course you don't. But I do.
If we had that power
here in our hands,
we'd be worse than them.
I don't agree.
Gorillas are cruel
because they're stupid...
all bone and no brains.
Zira, my dear,
I wish you would not talk like that.
Somebody is liable to hear you.
Nova!
What are you doing here?
Taylor?
No, not... not Taylor.
My name is Brent.
You talked!
That's impossible.
In a whole lifetime
devoted to the scientific
study of humans,
I've only found one other
like you who could talk.
Taylor.
Is he alive?
Have you seen him?
Where? Where? Tell us.
Where? Where?
I don't know where, I...
I'm trying to find him.
The longer I stay here,
the less I'm beginning to care.
Oh, now, we loved Taylor.
He was a fine, a unique specimen.
Why, if it had
not been for Zira here,
he... he would still be here,
a stuffed specimen
in the great hall
of the Zaius Museum,
with his two friends.
With his two friends?
Well, I don't plan
to stay around here
quite that long.
Look, can you get me
some food, some... some water,
a map... a map,
so at least I'll have some
idea where I'm heading?
You'll want that
taken care of, too.
I'll get the map.
Now,
if you will look up here,
ah, yes, towards the north.
This was the last place
that we saw Taylor and Nova.
What is that damn stuff?
You wouldn't know if I told you.
Just relax.
Among other things, I'm a trained vet.
Oh, great. Go on, go on.
Taylor was riding with Nova here,
between the lake and the sea.
Yes, they were heading
deep into the territory we call..
Yes, I know. The Forbidden Zone.
Who told you that?
Hmm? Your glorious leader back there.
Quick!
Cornelius, open the door.
Put the things away.
Open it!
Oh, Dr. Zaius, how nice.
We were just about
to have something to eat.
Not until I talk some sense
to that headstrong wife of yours.
Where is she?
Good day, Dr. Zaius.
Has there been an accident?
Cornelius hit me
for my bad behavior at the meeting.
I don't blame him.
I don't resent it,
but his nails need clipping.
Enough of this nonsense.
Are you so blind,
you two psychologists
that you're unaware
that we're on the verge
of a grave crisis?
You heard the Ursus' speech.
Militaristic tripe.
Zira!
Perhaps. But now he has
the incident he requires
to go on a rampage of conquest.
But that is appalling!
To remain silent
while this bully Ursus
is permitted to..
to destroy everything
in his path
is no longer possible.
As Minister of science,
it's my duty to find out
whether some other
form of life exists.
Where are you going?
Into the Forbidden Zone with Ursus.
Another manhunt, Doctor?
Someone or some thing
has outwitted the intelligence
of the gorillas.
- That shouldn't be difficult.
- Shh, Zira.
We apes have learned
to live in innocence.
Let no one,
be it man or some other creature,
dare to contaminate that innocence.
Why, is innocence so evil?
Ignorance is!
There is a time for truth.
And the time is always now.
Are you asking me
to surrender my principles?
I am asking you
to be the guardians
of the higher
principles of science
during my absence.
I am asking for a truce
with your personal convictions
in an hour of public danger.
And you shall have it, Dr. Zaius,
or I shall hit her again.
Let us have no
violence, Cornelius.
Now, I'm relying on you both.
We are counting
on you, too, Doctor.
If I should fail
to return from the unknown,
the whole future
of our civilization
may be yours
to preserve or destroy,
so think well before you act.
Good-bye, Dr. Zaius,
and good luck.
Let me finish this up
and get you out of here!
Yeah, get me
out of here, please.
I've seen the delicate, humane
way they treat humans here.
I don't much care for it.
Have you a horse?
Yeah, out in the scrub.
I'd better get you
another set of clothes,
the kind fit for humans,
like yourself.
You'll pass. Get rid of this.
And this, too.
If you are caught by the gorillas,
you must remember one thing.
What's that?
Never to speak.
What the hell would I have
to say to a gorilla?
But you don't understand.
Only apes can speak.
Not her, and not you.
If they catch you speaking,
they will dissect you
and they will kill you
in that order.
Cornelius is right.
Be very careful.
And get out of these
things you're wearing
as soon as you can.
Thanks.
Thank us by finding Taylor.
Yeah, if he's still alive.
Scissors.
Sergeant, wait!
This is a type-E cranium.
Very unusual.
With occipital development.
Substandard lobe.
Female.
It's been a long time
since we've been able to study
specimens of such extraordinary
clinical interest.
Bring them inside.
No!
No, you can't have them.
They are marked
for target practice.
Take them away.
I'll take the key.
To the target range!
Uh, wait! Wait!
I'd better double lock the door.
Good luck.
All right!
God Almighty.
This used to be my home.
I...
I lived here,
worked here.
What... What happened?
What... What could've happened?
My God, did we finally do it?
Did we finally really do it?
Oh God,
bless, we pray You,
our great army
and its supreme commander
on the eve of a holy war
undertaken for Your sake,
and grant,
in the name of your Prophet,
our great Lawgiver,
that we, Your chosen servants,
created and born
in Your divine image,
may aspire the more perfectly
to that spiritual Godliness
and bodily beauty
which You, in Your infinite mercy,
have thought fit to deny
to our brutish enemies!
So be it.
There they go,
Dr. Zaius trotting
along beside them.
Don't be too hard
on the old boy, Zira.
His motives are honest.
He has only one motive:
to keep things exactly
as they have always been.
I say that's
time for a change.
Zira, we chimpanzees are too few.
How can we take initiative
when they're in control?
Love, yes! War, no!
No more lies!
No more crying!
No more guns!
No more blood! Stop!
Stop!
Stop the war!
Freedom! Freedom!
Whoa!
Freedom! Peace!
Peace and freedom!
Get off the road, young people.
Freedom! Peace!
Get them out of the way.
Wait.
We don't want martyrs,
do we?
We want peace!
We want freedom!
Major, do it quietly.
We want peace!
We want freedom!
Peace!
Freedom! Peace!
Freedom!
Peace and freedom!
Battalion.
Are you what we were
before we learned to talk
and made a mess of everything?
Did any good ever
come from all that talk
around all those tables?
- I wonder where the hell they are?
- I wonder where the hell WE are?
Do you know what I think? We're near
the Forbidden Zone. That's what I think.
Hell, that's where the army's headed.
That real nice.
They'll roll right over us.
Why can't we go
back to our outfits?
Because the sarge says
to keep looking until we find them.
Nova.
Nova, Nova, wake up.
We've got to get going. Come on.
That hum...
You hear it, too?
All right, come on,
we're going to follow it.
Well, whoever or whatever...
something's guiding us.
Whatever they are,
they breathe air.
Well, there's an intelligence
working in this place.
That sound, good or bad,
it's either a warning
or some kind of directional device.
It doesn't much matter.
They know we're here.
Put my hands...
around her throat.
Off!
Hold her throat!
She...
dies!
Get out!
Get out of my head!
I reveal my inmost self
unto my God.
What did you say?
What do you mean there's no point?
Will they hurt her?
No, maybe not
physically, but here.
Here, you can hurt here. I know.
Your lips...
don't move.
But I can hear.
No, I mean...
I know what you're thinking.
Nothing. I...
I saw nothing.
Who are you?
Brent.
Oh, I see.
The only reality in the universe.
That's nice to know.
I got here by accident.
How did you get here?
Oh wait, you got it all wrong.
Why would I want to spy on you?
I'm not even sure you exist.
Of course I know who I am!
I'm an astronaut!
I was sent here
on a rescue mission
to find a fellow
astronaut, Taylor.
We're from this planet, but...
...from another time,
2,000 years ago.
I know l...
I know I sound insane.
And it's my insanity.
No, no, I don't know how to get back.
We...
We came through a defect,
a slippage in time.
That's what must have
happened to Taylor.
I'm sure he tried to get back.
Yes, my Skipper is dead.
I'm... I'm alone.
Who?
Nova? What's that?
Some star? A galaxy? What's Nova?
All right, all right, yes!
I know her. I know her.
No, no. She's harmless.
Let her alone.
All right, just tell me
what you want to know. Tell me.
She helped me
to break out of ape city.
No! Wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute!
Stop it!
I can't understand you.
You're all screaming at me
at the same time.
I can't separate it!
He's right.
He has only limited intelligence.
We should speak aloud,
and one at a time.
You were in the city of the apes?
Yes, two days ago.
What sights did you see?
You're talking.
Certainly we can talk.
We use speech when we must.
When we pray.
When we sing to our God.
You mean that..
that thing out there,
an atomic bomb, your god?
You don't understand.
The Bomb is a holy
weapon of peace.
Holy weapon of peace!
Peace.
Mr. Brent, we're a patient people,
but we are determined
to know what the apes want..
war or peace.
Try to understand.
The only weapons we have
are purely illusion.
You just imagined that he hurt you.
Traumatic hypnosis
is a weapon of peace.
Like the visual deterrent..
or the sonic deterrent..
Let me make a last appeal
to your reason
before we inflict more of this on you.
These are weapons of peace, Mr. Brent.
Like all our weapons.
Mere illusions.
Mere illusions? Damn your hypocrisy!
Is that bomb out there,
is that an illusion?
It's operational, isn't it?
The firing mechanism..
it's intact, isn't it?
We very much need
your help, Mr. Brent.
Why?
We are the keepers
of the Divine Bomb.
It is our only reason for survival.
And yet, as you see,
we are defenseless,
defenseless against
the slaughtering,
monstrous, materialistic apes.
I'll help nobody.
So go ahead. Annihilate each other.
I forgive you your language.
Sometimes your sanity
is about to give way.
I hope that does not happen.
I hope you can tell us..
Exactly what the apes are planning.
We've caught some of their scouts.
They're hideous creatures.
We've had them here,
standing precisely where you are now.
Either their skulls were too thick,
or they really
knew nothing at all.
Neither do l.
Can't you understand that?
I don't know anything!
You make us very sad, Mr. Brent.
She can't help you.
She can't even talk.
Don't harm her.
We never harm anyone, Mr. Brent.
You're going to harm her.
The apes sent me out to you.
You're lying.
How do you know?
How do you always know?
Nova.
Now..
Tell us of the apes.
The apes...
are marching on your city.
Bugler,
sound the advance.
Ursus!
Ursus, I warned you.
Look what we're faced with!
I told you you should wait!
Brutal butchery!
I swear, those responsible
shall pay with
torture and with death.
If you have any pity,
give orders to shoot
our poor people.
I can't order them to do
what the Lawgiver has forbidden.
Ape shall not kill ape.
Hold your positions!
He bleeds.
The Lawgiver bleeds!
The spirit of the Lawgiver lives!
We are still God's chosen!
This is a vision!
And it is a lie!
The vision was false!
Bugler,
sound the advance.
Advance!
Stupid animals.
They don't have the brain
to hold our illusions.
We have no defense.
Except our Bomb.
Call our people to the high sanctuary.
Do you know the range
of their city?
Yes.
Set in the mechanism and wait for me.
I want a public thought projection
at adult and infant level.
Adults to the cathedral,
infants indoors.
Is nowandevershallbe
World without end
Amen
The heavens declare
the glory of the Bomb,
and the firmament
showeth His handiwork.
His sun has gone out
unto all the land.
And gives light
unto the end of the world.
He descendeth from the
outermost part of heaven,
and there is nothing
hid from the heat thereof.
There is neither
speech nor language,
yet His voice is heard among them.
Praise Him.
My strength and my redeemer.
Glory be to the Bomb
and to the holy fallout
as it was in
the beginning, is now,
and ever shall be,
world without end.
Amen.
Amen
Almighty and everlasting Bomb,
who came down among us
to make heaven under Earth,
Iighten our darkness.
Instrument of God,
grant us Thy peace.
Almighty Bomb
Who destroyedallheavens
Andcreatedangels
Behold His glory
Behold the truth that abides in us.
Reveal that truth unto that Maker.
I reveal my inmost self unto my God.
Unto my God.
Unto my God
All things brightandbeautiful
All creatures greatandsmall
All things wise and wonderful
The good Bomb made us all
He gave us eyes to see with
And lips that we might tell
How great the Bomb Almighty
Who made all things well
Let everyone go
to his private shelter.
Empty the streets.
They're to find
the city of the dead.
May the blessing
of the Bomb Almighty
and the fellowship
of the Holy Fallout
descend on us this day
and forevermore.
Amen
I trust this simple ceremony
convinced you of
our peaceable intentions,
and I'd like to thank you
for your cooperation.
When may we hope
to be set free?
You may hope whenever
you please, Mr. Brent.
How could we
hope to let you go
on the eve of war, Mr. Brent?
You know too many ofour secrets,
Iike your friend.
Taylor!
You're Brent.
My God, Taylor!
Brent! How in the hell
did you get here?
Spaceship, ape city, subway..
Byyourself?
No, Nova found me.
Nova? ls she with you? Where?
I don't know. They separated us.
They tried to make me kill her.
Mr. Taylor, Mr. Brent,
we're peaceful people.
We don't kill our enemies.
We get our enemies
to kill each other.
I'm fighting it.
I'm fighting it off.
Taylor.
Taylor!
Unto God...
I reveal my inmost self.
This isn't exactly sterile.
We'll do the best we can.
Taylor.
Taylor, they've got a bomb..
Atomic bomb.
It's operational.
They intend to use it.
What type is it?
I don't know.
I don't know what type.
I've never seen it before.
Didn't you see a series number?
No numbers, just some
letters on one of the fins,
Greek letters.
Alpha...
And omega.
What?
The doomsday bomb.
My God.
Another lovely souvenir
from the 20th Century.
They weren't satisfied with a bomb
that could knock out a city.
They finally built one
with a cobalt casing,
all in the sweet name of peace.
Those bloody fools.
They don't know what they've got.
They pray to the damn thing.
If they shoot it off,
it could set off a chain reaction
in the whole atmosphere.
Burn the planet to a cinder.
How's that for
your ultimate weapon?
This must be what
your scout reported,
a subterranean passage.
I think it's worth exploring.
What will you do, Holiness?
Everything necessary.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
I'm thinking just that.
Nova.
Ah, God!
Should let them all die..
the gorillas, every damn...
When it comes time.
It's time it was finished.
Finished.
Taylor.
Come on, come on.
The bomb.
Yeah.
Why not?
They're obscene!
Follow me!
Sergeant!
Arrest that creature.
This is the instrument of my God.
He can speak.
Your God, eh?
Sergeant.
Your God didn't
save you, did he, huh?
Ursus!
That weapon is built by man.
You can't shoot it
down with bullets.
If we can't shoot it down,
we'll pull it down.
Rope! Block and tackle!
You don't know what you're doing.
It will kill us all!
I'll find a way to stop it.
Men, over there!
Ursus, someone at the pillar!
Zaius.
Taylor!
It's dooms day.
The end of the world.
Help me.
You ask me to help you!
Man is evil,
capable of nothing
but destruction!
You...
bloody bastard.
In one of the countless billions
of galaxies in the universe
Iies a medium-sized star.
And one of its satellites,
a green
and insignificant planet,
now is dead.