Dr. Wai In The Scripture With No Words
I'm an adventure story writer.
My father was an adventurer…
Fortunately, he kept an amazing journal
He was known far and wide as:
"The Adventure King"
- Hey, stop them!
- What!?
- Where is Dr. Lu?
- Inside of the Ox.
And indeed he is inside the ox.
Oh wait, don't get me wrong.
This young is not my father.
- He's my father’s student, Pao Sam-Chao.
- Dr. Lu, get out of there.
Why are you yelling?
You should not disturb a mad scientist at work!
- Master said no one should touch this before he gets here.
- Your master is a fool!
This ancient relic is
a fantastic find.
We can't leave it here,
someone might steal it.
- Get out!
- No way!
See?
I knew something would happen.
And here he comes, my father Dr.Wai.
Take a good look at him,
how handsome he is.
How dashing!
- Master!
- He looks straight out of Hollywood.
Master, come quickly.
It's a Disaster!
Time for dad to do his stuff,
He is my hero.
If I had his courage,
my life would be perfect.
Thank you everyone for your help.
Adventure King, you'll die for this!
You ruined this ancient Ox!
If I'm gonna die, you're gonna die first.
Why are you all holding rocks?
Adventure King Sir,
an urgent message.
It's from general Lone.
You must fly to Xian immediately.
First class! Take me with you sir!
I always wanted to meet the general.
Good, then come.
Master,
who is this General Lone?
He is the head of
the secret agents.
Just listen and don't talk.
General...
Thank you for the invitation,
what can I do for you?
Right, let’s get to the point.
You're an archeologist
and an expert in finding ancient valuable relics.
Adventure King, find the scripture with no words
complete with its box.
Adventure King, you must not refuse me.
- What kind of scripture? Can my master help?
- The whereabouts of the scripture is a mystery.
The only thing heard about it...
is that it was last seen late in Ming dynasty.
The leader of the sultan Tuen Ming knew
that some Tibetan Llamas had it.
So he put together a gang of his own
to attack these Llamas...
His plan was to steal the
scripture and its box.
They met in the desert and had a
terrible battle... The legend has it
that the desert sand turned
bloody red for square miles.
- Give me the scripture, or die now!
- You'll never get the scripture from me...
- If you open the box, it your peril.
- Fine.
The box is over there.
Do not look inside.
No one emerged from that battle alive,
people who found
the bodies later, says the place is haunted,
but refused to say another word.
Except that General Tuen Ming
turned into a ghost...
and to stole the scripture,
then disappeared.
Brilliant, I'm sure I found
the right guy for the job!
I haven't agreed to do it.
The future of the Humanity
depends on this scripture.
Who to possesses it will have the future
of the world in their hands.
Finding the Box,
will lead to the scripture.
You cannot refuse.
All right, where do we begin?
All the information we have,
is in a letter
it's from a team of archeologists.
The letter is with the Japanese
ambassador, in Shang-Hai.
Excellent one, we will go at once.
Find me through the 7th heaven night club.
It's owned by my buddy Chu Fat Pai,
he'll be around.
Shanghai, Paris of the east.
Where my father’s adventures started.
- Tell Ting Ling to avenge me.
- Who's he? Probably to busy.
Master that wasn't very sympathetic.
Look, we're here on business...
and don't have time for every
bleeding heart story.
Dr. Wai, my boss
is waiting for you. Come in.
I'll get cold fatty!
Mr. Chung,
long time, no see!
Adventure King,
you got a nerve!
You staid away for far too long.
You come to see me at last.
All right boys, forget the guns.
Come, sit down and have some fun.
- So friend, you're here to tell me something?
- You’re gonna love it.
- Need to sneak into the Japanese Embassy.
- But that will be no fun at all.
But it’s necessary to steal something.
- A confidential letter
- That's more like it, cheers!
I feel an idiot.
Mr. Chun, are you sure about this?
Don't you trust me?
Follow me!
Why do women dress like this?
- To attract the men.
- I prefer my women naked.
Gentleman and Mrs. Chan,
of the Bank of Wing.
- Mr. Chun, of the 7th Heaven.
- My first wife...
The others are concubines.
Lucky me!
See what it takes, the sacrifices
an adventurer has to make?
My father would do any thing
to discover the truth.
Sometimes it was a real drag...
- So much to eat! Mustn’t get fat.
- Miss, may I have this dance?
- I do not know how to dance.
- And I am married.
Don't worry about it.
More drinks!
It's too bright
to make the robbery.
What did you say?
Where is the main switch, General?
That's easy,
in the main switch room.
Nobody deceives you, right?
Keep and eye on him.
- Oh dear, our poor husband.
- Is he all right?
He is so drunk, let's take him home.
My wife does not understand me.
General, he is drunk.
Follow him.
I'm not sure this plan is so great.
Dump him, dear.
Kill the lights.
- Oh my!
- Crowded with guards.
This is hot.
Things need to cool down.
Just a minute.
You're coming apart.
There.
Let me do it.
- Thank you
- Japanese Girls know...
how to make a man feel great.
- We did a good job!
- Shut up.
- Is this is part of the dance?
- I don't know.
- This must be it.
- Get rid of these clothes.
- Let's find the safe.
- Right.
I'll search this side.
Master, I think I found it.
What are you doing?
Now we're in trouble.
What’s this?
Confidential.
To Miss Kwan Siu Wan.
Who is there?
It's you!
I beg you’re pardon.
I went to the wrong bathroom, I just came
out and there you were, we meet again.
But... you were a woman then.
Not really, just pretended to be a woman.
Sometimes, I'm man.
You're disguised as woman?
I am a woman, it's not a disguise.
I can see that.
You are very attractive.
- You're a very attractive guy.
- You, mean that?
Scouts honor.
We didn't find anything.
Keep on alert.
You never saw me.
I can hear a voice.
Come out!
Hi, want me?
Round one to me.
Take him!
Are you all right?
Never felt better.
My stomach aches
and I'm loosing.
No, not again!
Take this!
No closer!
If I move,
the pen will set his gun off.
Put the guns down!
Here it is my autograph!
Must be "Adventure King"
The Adventure King
Don’t let him run away.
- Gee, stay over.
- Another time.
- Are you crazy, you almost killed me.
- I'm sorry, general.
Don't hang about.
Look for the letter.
Master, too many soldiers.
- Safe, under the nose of the enemy.
- Go in, go on.
- Where are you going?
- Under the enemy's nose.
- Who said that?
- You did.
- Wait here!
- Master, sometimes I don't understand.
Don't go anywhere, let's talk all right?
OK, you were right.
I was inside...
But then I came out over there.
But now I'm over here again.
And that's how I run into you guys.
It must be our destiny?
Well, if it’s faded,
better go along with it.
Why do you guys take your duty so seriously?
It's just salary staff.
- Why am I back here?
- Miss, wait a minute.
Rats!
I can't let him see me looking like this.
- Miss, isn’t you the woman I just spoke to?
- What are you dong here?
Is it you?
It's so dark.
Miss, are you sleepwalking?
Noble approach to water beds.
What are you doing here?
I am taking bath.
Oh gee, I just saw everything!
Must be a secret code.
In... deep waters...
What is going on?
Be a gentleman,
don't do anything you'll regret.
Turn of the light.
This is hard!
- C'mon I like to see you.
- Got a headache?
I got some whit flower oil.
Oh, dear!
It's all gone wet.
It doesn't matter,
faster penetration.
Give me some.
A massage?
I can't.
- Sure you can.
- I am very shy.
- What is it?
- You’re wet, dry yourself up...
or you'll look like a drowned
chicken with wet feathers.
- Hey, I was born in the year of the chicken!
- And was in the year of the rabbit.
Turn of that light.
Let the chicken and bunny have a bath.
First, tell me who you are.
Careful, father, can be a trap.
I am the actor Jet LI.
You should never tell lies
with the light on.
Look, its out!
I don't want much out of life.
Just to be the King everywhere on the planet...
and have thousands
of loving wives.
What's this?
Master, help me.
Piece of cake.
Fetch!
How come the obey you?
They you're relatives?
- Go and ask him.
- I'm not that stupid.
- There you go, all you do is play?
- I was tricked.
- Serves you right!
Wait for me Master, I'm exhausted.
I read the letter. It does not say anything.
It doesn’t refer to the Box.
As I imagined. But somewhere in
the letter is a way to find Ming.
- You're great.
- Speak up
The one who wrote this probably
failed language class, it's chicken script.
- Ignorant pig!
- Go on
He wanted to get a divorce from his wife,
but didn't mention anything
about alimony.
- Go on.
- Listen to this.
Jesus!
In fact he was happily married...
but the obsession of the Box
destroyed his marriage.
That idiot!
Giving up the wife for a box.
You better than that?
I don't want the Box,
give me a woman.
Women are more fun than boxes.
And more trouble.
Ah, you know?
- Any other clues?
- Like what?
Try looking at this newspaper.
Read it carefully.
- You got a map?
- Sure.
What's it for?
The news office, moron!
- There are so many in Shang-Hai.
- We will visit one at a time.
They have the letter,
if we're not careful,
we'll be in trouble.
What trouble?
You had the letter a long time
and did not discover anything.
- Nothing yet, but I...
- Adventure King is exceptional.
And I set out to trap him.
I want him to find the Box for us.
If we tail him to tight,
he will immediately suspect us.
If he gets any bright ideas,
he will inform the Chinese government.
That's when we'll move in.
In the following day,
dad ordered Pao Chao...
to show the letter
to all the press offices.
Everybody got on his case.
But he found a place...
Is this it?
Really difficult to find, look at it.
Hurry up sir, pay and go.
The money, please, Come on!
This is only press office
that uses this lousy quality paper.
Come on.
Close this stinking old rag!
- It is catching fire.
- WOW, they're really organized!
- Keep quiet, let’s go in.
- Just showing appreciation.
- They thought you were mocking them.
- You're prejudice against me, based on pride.
Monday’s newspaper was
Tuesdays table cloth.
Tuesday’s newspaper,
Wednesdays wrapping paper.
Do not give up, tomorrow will publish again!
How dare you publish this garbage?
- We live in a free world.
- Get out of here!
Today’s newspaper will be
used for wrapping old knives.
This will demonstrate our force.
- Honesty and Freedom!
- Freedom!
Be quiet.
- Who are they?
- We're looking to discover.
We're looking for part time work sir.
Very well!
What are you holding?
Oh goddess, I'm in love.
Why on earth would you work here?
I believe in honesty, freedom
and I want to work in a team!
Hogwash!
You saw through it?
Have no work for you, go.
- We do not want money.
- Come on, we'll try later.
- Are you the manager?
- Yes I am?
Every day you publish lies
about the Japanese.
Have you got a personal vendetta?
No, my father killed Japanese,
I can see why you're angry.
You cretin!
We'll stay here.
You bastards!
I'm sorry.
Game over.
Burn the entire office.
I'll see you again.
Every time you see a pretty girl...
- ...you melt to pieces.
- They are the hormones.
You sure?
I think it's in your head.
- I'll cover it then, so you can't see...
- That hope.
It is a great way to make a living
threatening people.
You bunch of no-goods.
Fight me if you dare.
How dare you talk to us like that?
Get her.
This will cost us.
You’re not kidding?
It will break us.
Hold it, cowards!
Picking on a defenseless female like this.
Forget it.
Think about it,
they're not so smart.
Fight me if you got the guts.
He'll never learn.
Make way.
He fights well.
Your money.
- Want more?
- No, let’s go.
Stop youngsters.
Scumbags, never try to burn my office again!
Hey miss, wait!
How about thank you?
So we just going to stare are we?
No chance.
Thus you do not go.
We have to.
You want to be guards?
- They seem weird.
- No weirder than us.
I am an idiot.
The master always deceives me.
I do not know what to do.
Anyone here?
Nobody?
Meet guy!
Get to work!
Who is that?
They are using garbage can on the head!
- What is it?
- Very strange thing.
- Very strange?
- Yes.
Strike generate in France.
The strike you generate cause chaos...
in the public transport
and affects some sectors...
of the population are affected...
business is good, sales grew 50%
The agriculture suffers
and the crops were affected.
The strikers are not weakening...
and the perspectives are bad.
Some people use the advantage to gain money.
Master, let me help you.
About time. I thought that you were imitating
those French strikers.
Point taken.
Master need not worry about me, I won't strike.
But I do not know...
how the other will react.
You better take care.
I know. Therefore I dressed me
as my departed father.
So they'll think I'm a ghost
and they'll work harder.
Do you really think this disguise
is gonna change anything?
Mysterious Appearances
inspires the staff to work harder.
The only mysterious thing
is in your head.
Not so.
Those two new faces are mysterious.
Use expensive clothes and
had come for specific reasons.
Best to keep them here,
where we can watch them.
You're probably right,
do you think they are looking for that box?
She's not only beautiful, but also intelligent.
I love that in a woman!
Stop that disgusting talk, its horrible.
What is inside of the Box, anyway?
Have never opened it. My father opened it and
he transformed into subspecies.
All I know it's powerful
and it never must be opened.
When we find it, we'll better take care.
Not to worry.
It is very well hidden.
It's hidden in a secret room
behind the printing machine.
Nobody knows how to get in there,
only your incredible master knows...
Don't worry about anyone finding it.
Master, you’re on only handsome
but also incredible smart.
I love an intelligent man,
it's such a turn on!
The shelf!
Quickly!
Luckily the box is fine.
A dog!
A snake!
The dog is strong as a bull.
The snake is stronger!
That strange noise!
- Let's go!
- My foot is stuck.
- Let's hurry
- It is stepping on my foot.
A giant large rat!
Right, let’s tell General Lone.
Come on!
See? I didn't lie to you.
That box can turn you into anything.
Or it can make you disappear.
No doubt about that.
Master, aren't you worried
if somebody finds out about this.
Of course not.
They may look, but they won't find it.
- What are you up to?
- To order a telegram.
Miss Yu Fung!
Wait for me.
You?
The Japanese embassy is looking for you.
- If you don't tell, he'll never know.
- Don't worry, I won't say anything.
- Are you on a job at the moment?
- I got a new job.
- Are you hurt?
- I'm fine, thanks.
- My sandal.
- I'll get it.
Here.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
Anything more you'd like?
You sure?
Good bye.
- What is it?
- I'm worried I won't see you again.
- I must see you again!
- Whenever you want.
I am free every day.
Just give me a call, and I'll come over.
Really?
I need to go.
- When will I see you again?
- I'll call you.
How about that, he really believed
I was born in the year of the rabbit.
Dad strikes again.
He made a rabbit from a linen handkerchief.
And won the lady's heart.
Dad, remember where you are!
I did it!
Quiet!
Shut up!
You come here.
Now!
I do not want to be a guinea pig.
Help!
Get in there.
I heard you're the strongest guru
in the world, Master Kar Tam.
I'm interested to see if you can withstand
the poisonous gases in my experiment room.
Let me out.
It works.
Disgusting one! Get him out of here.
You will have the honor to test
our experiment.
Why do you not thank the general?
What a lot of bull, I'm not impressed.
Filthy little goblin.
Get in here.
How dare you disobey!
You could die for this.
Guru Kar Tam, this will not happen again.
I promise.
- Take him to his room.
- Yes.
Fascinated by murders?
He's only a silly old monk.
And a human being.
Japanese had come to China...
to create the great economic
market of the Asian East.
This attitude
does not benefit anybody.
I believe the intent was...
Will it kill you to be quiet?
Any more interruptions and you go to a cell.
- Please no, I just...
- I'm giving you a little mission.
What?
Dr. Wai found the scripture box...
in righteous news daily office.
He told General Lone,
who will now come to Shanghai.
- And what has that to do with me?
- Bring Sicko Sam.
- He and his gangsters are notorious lowdown scum.
- We'll tell the gangsters to steal the Box...
then take it and they'll handle all the killing.
What a clever plan.
- That guru was so accurate.
- On what!?
That you're full of bull.
Thank you for the kind words.
That stench.
Why are you so late?
Got the relics? Hand them over!
And the red jade?
Damn!
Not a wise move.
Here it is its jade of blood.
Now, the money.
I'll pay up...
- I have more jobs for you.
- And what is it?
A simple job.
Go to the righteous daily news,
and bring me a box.
- And what's in this box?
- Mind your own business.
Bring us this box
and your dreams will come true.
It is time to leave.
Go get your luggage.
No problem, I'm ready.
Where you going?
Somebody is waiting for you.
- Master, what is it?
- Check it.
Master, we are surrounded.
Looks like we won't get
the last edition out today.
Pansy, our luck is finished.
Master!
What's important is the box.
Guard it with your life.
I'll hide.
Hold it.
Heroic one, it isn't a good time
to leave the building with anything valuable.
You could be in trouble.
Take care,
if those guys get it away from you...
you couldn’t begin to stop them.
True, so I decided to give this to you.
Take care of it for me.
I'm so embarrassed.
You're trying to trick those gangsters,
but those guys are no fools.
They will not be deceived so easily.
Master, they cut the electricity.
They're gonna storm in.
You get out, I'll handle it.
That won't work.
There's a whole gang outside.
Can you fight them all?
Let's divert their attention.
They are only interested in this.
We do it like this, we all leave
with box in our hands.
When we get out,
we run in different directions.
You're the only one
that knows where the box is, be careful.
I'm sorry, I misread you...
You're one of us!
That is not important, is it?
Time is running out, let’s go.
Let's go.
Hey, I know you'd like a mature boyfriend...
- But he already got a girlfriend.
- That doesn’t matter.
I don't care if you're both gay.
You're hot tempered!
No time to talk.
Let's get this clear, I'm a single
man and I are interested in you.
I'm calling you, right?
- Right
- Kissing time.
Enough.
You are nearly history.
Are you ready?
Let's go!
Hang on a sec.
I must say something.
You know what I mean, don't you?
I can read your mind.
And you're a nice girl.
And you are thick as cow tongue.
That's fine, I can handle that.
Flowers grow beautiful in Kao Dun.
Kill everyone in the press office,
then search.
Here's the box.
This way master.
Let's take a rest.
No one is chasing us.
We got lucky.
- Oh yeah?
- Who is there?
No one is chasing,
but someone is waiting.
- Give us the box tough kitten.
- Dream on.
Pansy, don't do it.
You're no match for him.
Don’t kill her.
I gave you what you wanted,
now give the Box to me.
As my friend saved,
I'll tell you the truth...
The Box is dangerous
and will kill you.
So why hasn't it killed you.
Now, let's se how much
of this you can take!
You'll die for this.
- Who are you?
- I am your conscience...
and I came here to say
that you must stop to killing all the time.
Give it up, find another job.
This is not good for your karma.
If you're not careful, in your next life...
you'll come back as a punch bag.
No chance! This is for
your father, your mother...
your sister
and all your family.
Even with a gun you're hopeless.
Change profession, friend.
- Hey, Sicko, satisfied yet?
- Got more of those pens handy?
I have.
You want an autograph?
No way out, doctor.
So go.
Well, hi there.
You were great. Even without a
trash bin, you were able to defeat that jerk.
You are a real hero.
My powers are yours. Passed on to you today
along with my students. Where is she?
Pansy!
Oh, my love.
I do not want to live
without you, Pansy!
Pansy! You are alive.
You broke my wrist.
Really?
Sorry.
Know what, you won't be
able to look after it.
You better give it to the government.
Hey, Trashcan.
You saved our lives you know.
Take that thing off, and talk to us.
Don’t shout like that, why so angry?
If I was him, I would stay in that trashcan.
You loudmouth bitch, I'll teach you!
Listen, you don't want the Box
taken by gangsters?
Hmm you have a point there.
He does. Tell me where the
box is, I'll look after it?
I haven't thought of
getting rid of it.
I've decided that you will be
employed as my body guards from now on.
- Trashcan, I...
- Listen...
I get to call the shots around here, not you.
Sobbing again.
Let's go.
Don't walk off, while I'm talking to you.
Calm down.
No need to push it.
General Lone arrives tomorrow,
he'll decide.
If I was 20 years younger,
I would teach...
those two a lesson.
- Let's go for a drink?
- Good idea.
Let's go for a drink.
Aw... more drinking...
Sam, General arrives today.
Let's kill him at the station.
Master, look!
We'll use the gas.
Tell the guys to prepare it.
Too risky.
This place is full of innocent people.
I will do it.
General, this could
call for the ultimate sacrifice.
Don't state the obvious.
Follow me.
- Soldier, it's gas time.
- But the general is...
Relax; she can take care of herself.
Trouble!
The gas.
What is this, I said not to use the gas.
General Lone!
Yu Fung!
Someone got the general.
Get after them.
Stop that train!
- Faster.
- You drive it.
Tell Pansy not to worry, I'm all right.
Now
I am a love
when they treat me well.
Don’t let the train pass.
No, no.
This is not beautiful, I'm inexperienced.
Can you drive?
I can hardly stand,
forget driving.
Out of the way!
A pilot what's needed, I'll better invent it.
Am I dreaming?
You better get off.
I am dying.
I got you on this train and I'll get you off it.
I'm a responsible man, honey.
Difficulties do not scare me.
Yu Fung, hang in there.
You're strong and courageous,
nobody treated me like this before.
I'll treat you like this forever.
Yes, Adventure King,
now I can die.
Yu Fung, Yu Fung!
- Do these things work?
- Of course, it sucks off the poison.
Doctor, you know where Pao is?
The Japanese captured him.
That's terrible.
I'll get him out, relax.
I want to say something privately.
Sorry, can you leave?
Hey, doctor...
My intuition says that
she is not was she seems.
I think she's fine.
The truth is that I am
a Japanese spy.
And I've been betrayed by my country men
they released the poison gas when I said no.
You better go and rescue Pao
before they use him ...
for an evil experiment.
What is the address?
76 Lu Bo Road.
They’re bunch idiots,
won't even tell us where we are.
That fool knows nothing.
No point of keeping him here, a waste of rice.
- All right, kill him.
- My thought exactly.
No pest control please.
What is this?
It's horrible.
Young fellow, save your breath,
that is poisonous gas.
Do not breathe for one hour
and you'll be all right.
- Stop breathing?
- Can you...
I can not!
No time for jokes.
He's not moving, help.
Quick, come on.
Welcome.
Is that the best you have to offer us?
One shot and you are dead.
It’s not loaded.
You got lucky today.
The dumply brothers.
You can not see me.
Fantastic, master.
How did you do that?
It's all Tai-Chi, energy here,
energy there...
The energy increases...
and it concentrates to face the enemy.
Understood?
- Try again.
- No, let's eat.
Good idea.
Master...
Pansy and the others have disappeared.
Must have gone to get the Box.
But where?
Shang-Hai is so big...
and the very small Box
is easy to hide.
The press office.
They're all so weird in there.
The Box is very small...
Where could it be?
- I asked you that.
- You know?
- I do not know.
- So get the car.
Immediately.
You need to be smart.
I want to sit up a little.
You must rest.
Can you help me?
Are you all right?
Yes, I am.
Mans intuition is no good.
I'm sorry.
You wouldn't listen to the whispers...
now you'll hear the screams.
A bit late.
Master...
Master, are you dead?
Tell me if you’re dead.
Why are you on the floor?
Why do you never think?
You'll be joining me.
How?
Master, if you're lost,
why don't you ask?
We've walked all night
There's nobody around to ask.
We would seem suspicious.
Get the box.
Master...
Someone is here.
You two fools are finished,
give me the Box.
Dream on.
Pansy, run away.
Master, be careful.
I will kill you.
Give me the box.
Show me how it works.
I'll read the instructions.
Dry clean only, no bleach, no spin.
Shut up.
Don’t open it.
I'll kill you, monster.
Master.
I've got a splitting headache!
There's my chance, better grab it.
Master.
Go and get the box or I won't be
able to face my ancestors.
Master, please, don't die.
Pansy.
I'm very sorry.
Have you worked out,
where the Holy Scripture is hidden?
Where is the diamond
that you promised to me?
Right, turn this.
Ga Yu?
Ga Yu gate!
Tell the captain to go to Ga Yu gate.
I heard that, the one with the scripture...
will have an enchanted life...
All their dreams will come true.
Is it ok if I keep it then?
I'm doing this for love
to my country.
What a pity, you can't see
the way benefiting both sides.
General, why not gain a little extra?
I am loyal to Japan.
Good for you, let's drink to it.
All right.
In the opposition, I would have
made a very different decision.
Self interest is not a crime.
But, it pays to be careful.
Greed can lead to an untimely death.
But the people are naturally greedy.
At least you’re honest,
and told me what's on your mind.
Cheers!
You again?
How did you get here?
Without me, how could you
pull off this stunt?
Which one?
I know you know.
I have no idea.
- Come here.
- Yes.
No, damnit.
We had an agreement.
I am the boss or not?
You should be happy there are many of us.
You play boss to me like this!
Would you two stop it?
Mind your own business,
it's between the two of us.
- Listen, arrest them.
- Yes.
- Arrest her.
What a shock,
we all agreed I'm in charge here.
I was not trying to cheat,
I am an agent.
Scumbags.
Open the door!
Inform control:
Spy on board, we are returning.
Yes...
Dry clean only, no bleach
What are you talking about?
It’s you, don't move.
I am the commander
of this airplane, you surrender.
That wasn't fair, they're all against me.
Who's against you?
You, take over.
- I do not know how to fly.
- Just do it.
It's an order!
You pretended to be very sick,
just for my sympathy.
I was very sick.
Just that you were a pushover.
Pushover?
Open the door.
- Quiet.
Remember that night?
You lured me into that bath tub.
Trying to make me peep at your boobies.
What nonsense,
I tried to keep you off!
In the truth, I tried
to please a little bit.
Just a little bit?
I thought it was a lot.
You are very arrogant,
it think you have the...
hots for the little girl out there.
Pervert.
I haven't finished.
Nobody moves.
Wait, don't be hasty.
You're so beautiful,
why would he be interested in me?
Your skin is so soft and...
We all die together.
- You do not have courage.
- But I have the weapon.
I am a secret agent
and I am ready to die.
Good one.
Very heroic.
Nationalism at 30.000 feet...
such devotion to the duty.
Listen up...
These two are sacrificing themselves for us?
Right, let's go guys.
Don’t be stupid.
- Adios, love bird.
- Why are you still here?
All with the happy couple.
Have lots of children.
- With much health.
- Good luck you.
A marriage made in heaven.
Idiots, they're going to hell.
- Happy landing.
- That worse, what’s wrong with good bye.
What a devil is that?
I'll get revenge, you won't get away.
You're going to hell!
The monster.
Do not force me.
I don't mind dying with you.
He's speaking for himself, not me.
We'll all die.
Give me that box.
Another lucky break, Master,
I kept it for you.
Cut the crap.
Save the Box.
- Turbulence.
- I am not a good pilot.
I can see that.
I am starting to learn.
Don't panic.
We do not have time
for romance.
The Box.
Together.
- You go first.
- And you?
There's only one parachute.
- We go together.
- It will break.
See you later.
Now I finally understand love.
Look at my dad...
sacrificing his life
for the woman he loves.
And her wanting to die with him.
You should let me go.
The parachute can't take the weight.
This way we both die.
Better than life without you.
I am thinking...
if this is the end for us,
then I don't mind.
I agree.
You see?
God must be on our side.
Master...
God must be on our side, we found the box.
I think God's gone now.
Bad timing, Co-Pilot.
Come on.
- I don't understand.
- I do.
As we stand here,
it's the top of Ga Yu gate...
From what the sutra said,
the scripture with no words...
is in the palace beneath the wall.
The entrance must be
on the top of Ga Yu gate.
The Box must be the key.
It's the only way to enter.
The doubt is:
Where is the door?
Search the place thoroughly.
Master, come here.
Put it in.
Take it out.
Master, there's the scripture with no words.
- It is.
- Keep away.
Look around, it may not be that simple.
Many people
have died here.
Taking the scripture could be difficult.
I think I give up.
This is not necessary.
Let's go, what we don't have, we won't miss.
No way, I've come this far, I won't give up.
Careful.
Catch it.
I will not let you take the scripture.
Be careful...
She’s got the scripture.
- Give it to me.
- Catch it.
- Die.
- You'll die.
Evil monster.
No advantage,
I'm out of here.
It won't work, I'm immortal.
Never wanted this scripture.
A wise person would know that we could die.
This isn't the time or place
to lay the guilt on me!
She was rude to me.
You women always say these things.
Couldn't you just talk about this later?
Help me pull him up.
- Now what?
- Try again.
I got the scripture, come and get it.
Take this.
How dare you?
Die, die
Die, die.
The scripture!
Can’t hurt me.
Run, Pansy.
Master, you take the right arm side and
the girls take his left hand side.
I can handle it!
No chance.
The Box.
- You remember the rat?
- What?
The rat in the press office.
The light from the box will make him die!
Do it again.
It will make the thing die.
Don't touch the box.
I'm coming.
Master,
not a good idea.
You'll die.
Hang on, Master.
Sign of what you're are thinking.
That you get me to vanish, too.
No chance.
Monster, I will kill you.
The last chance.
- These are yours or mine?
- They must be yours.
Open the Box.
Shine the light on it.
Don’t do it.
I can't hold it.
Hurry.
Shine the light on it.
Hurry, open the Box.
Open it now.
Then what.
- What to do?
- I have no idea.
All this is an illusion.
I am the Monk Yuen Chong,
the scripture is not of this planet.
You're at our power vortex.
So I can't send you away
without a glimpse of glory.
Does the future interest any of you?
You bet it does.
Will I be married, Mr. Monk?
Your destiny states, you will be married.
That is you!
What’s wrong with that?
We’re good together.
And I wanna see my greatest achievement.
It's the same one.
We should never have asked.
Don't be sad.
Adventure King...
aren't you interested in
what the future holds?
The scripture had the key, we forgot why.
Is our greed an illusion you think?
They are, thank God.
Humans fear life.
So they fight it, and try to control it.
Bad actions catch up with people.
But what goes around comes around.
If you let it, love is stronger than evil.
Japan surrendered.
Love is not exclusive.
Each human being is loved equally by God.
In that way, humans must
learn to love each other.
This will end fear, and people will realize...
that knowing we are all one, will create peace.
It all becomes clear,
Controlling comes out of atrocity.
If we start trusting god,
we won't need to fear life.
After this Pao stopped working for my dad...
in the search of the truth.
Instead... he went off to raise a family
Pansy did as foretold,
and were very happy.
But my father could never settle down.
This story ends here.
But Adventure King had many more adventures.