- What?
- We gotta go. We gotta go.
- What? Where?
- I have an idea of how to stop this.
Stop what?
- Joely.
- Come on, Clem.
- Smell my armpit! Smell my armpit!
- No!
- Don't tickle me! Don't make me smell you.
- Smell my pits!
- No.
- Good.
Concentrate, Clem.
We gotta get back to the office.
There was a tape recorder.
No, not the picture.
Not the picture.
Where is it? Back here.
Come on!
Oh, look at me.
Hey, I look good there.
Look, our files are confidential,
Mr. Barish,
so I can't show you evidence.
Suffice it to say that Miss, uh...
Miss Kruczynski...
was not happy and she wanted to move on.
Good. Now, tell me about Clementine.
- That's what he said. Then...
- What did we see that day?
- No, wait.
- Oh, look! Hey!
- Shit!
- We're going to see my grandma.
- Joel, why... No, I don't want to... Joel, please!
- We're not going on a train.
- Don't make me run anymore.
- Come on!
Mierzwiak!
- Do we always have to run?
- Mierzwiak!
Please.
So, why don't we begin
by you telling me...
everything you can remember.
Mierzwiak! Wake me up!
Oh, l-I'm sorry, Mr. Barish.
I thought you understood
what was going on here.
I don't know.
You're erasing her from me.
You're erasing me from her...
I don't know.
You've got this thing.
I'm in my bed. I know it.
I'm in my brain.
I'm part of your imagination too, Joel.
How can I help you
from there?
Uh, I'm inside your head too.
I'm you.
Sorry.
Look. Who's that?
Oh, he-he works for us.
That's, uh, Pa-a-a-a-atrick,
baby boy.
He's stealing my identity.
He stole my stuff.
He's, uh, seducing my girlfriend
with my words and my things.
He stole her underwear.
Oh, Jesus Christ!
I could die right now, Clem.
I'm just happy.
I've never felt that before.
I'm just exactly where I want to be.
I want to go home.
Hey. What?
Clem!
Wait. Clem!
Clem?
They're erasing you.
I'm here!
Clem, focus.
I hired them, okay?
I'm sorry, I'm so stupid.
Sweetie, calm down.
Enjoy the scenery.
I need it to stop before I wake up
and I don't know you anymore.
Okay, well, you know,
just tell them to cancel it then.
What the hell are you talking about?
I can't just cancel it. I'm asleep.
Wake yourself up!
Okay. You want me to wake up?
Okay. Great. All right.
- Okay, here we go. This make you happy if I try?
- Yeah.
I'll try really hard. Here we go.
That was a great idea.
Yeah. Okay.
Boy, that's working
like gangbusters.
- Don't! That tickles me!
- Oh, my goodness.
Oh, my God. What is that?
Jesus Christ! What the...
It's a birthmark!
It did work, for a second,
- but I couldn't... I couldn't move.
- See?
Oh, well, isn't that just another one
of Joel's self-fulfilling prophecies?
It's more important to prove me wrong
than to actually...
Look, I don't want to
discuss this right now, okay?
Fine.
Then what? I'm listening.
I don't know.
You erased me.
That's why I'm here.
That's why I'm doing this in the first place.
- I'm sorry.
- You... You!
You know me. I'm impulsive.
That's what I love about you.
- I have another idea for this problem.
- Mm-hmm?
This is a memory of me,
the way you wanted to have sex on the couch
after you looked down at my crotch.
- What?
- Joel, the eraser guys are coming here,
so what if you take me somewhere else,
somewhere where I don't belong,
and we hide there till morning?
Oh, man.
I can't remember anything without you.
That's very sweet,
but try, okay?
Okay.
"Row, row, row your boat
gently down the stream"
"Merrily, merrily
merrily, merrily"
Row, row, row your boat
gently down the stream
"Row, row, row your boat
Merrily, merrily, merrily, merrily"
Life is but a dream
Merrily, merrily
merrily, merrily
Life is but a dream.
Row, row, row your boat
It's working!
You're a genius
Joel?
Where'd you go?
I'm supposed to come too!
Listen, I'm just gonna go get a salad bowl.
Can you stir the soup and keep an eye on Joel?
- Sure.
- He just likes to be near me.
- Absolutely!
- Clem?
It worked.
My God, look at this! Wow!
It worked! Look!
Look at this dress, man!
Oh, my God! Look at it!
I wish I could take it with me.
Who am I?
- Mrs. Hamlyn.
- Right. Mrs. Hamlyn.
I must be about four.
Oh, my gosh.
Found the salad bowl,
so I'm serving salad and string beans.
Is he okay under there?
Peanut, are you all right?
God, honestly, I feel like
I could clean up all day.
- Listen, would you hate me if I asked you
to clean some string beans?
- No, not at all.
Oh, my God.
I love this kitchen.
- Thank you so much.
- She's not looking at me.
She's busy.
She's not looking at me.
No one ever looks at me.
I want my mommy.
Oh, babyJoel.
Hey, Joely! Joely!
- Is every little peanut under there okay?
- Mm-hmm! He's fine.
Do you have something to drink?
Would you drink a cocktail at this hour?
I mean, I know it's not 5:00.
- I would die for a vodka.
- Oh, hang on. Let me check if I have that.
Okay! I'm just gonna wait right here.
Joel! Hey, no, sweetie.
Uh, Joely.
Your mother wants me to mind you.
Get back under the table.
- Ice cream.
- No, not until after, you know, you've had your dinner.
Come on, Joel!
Joel, grow up!
Don't leave me, Clem.
Oh, my God, Clem.
- This is sort of warped.
- I'm scared.
- I want my mommy!
- Don't cry, babyJoel.
BabyJoel, it's okay.
Joel. Joely. Joel!
Stop it! Look, I think it's working.
Look, we're hidden, Joel. Look!
Hey, honey, look.
Wait there.
My crotch is still here,
just as you remembered it.
Yuck.
It stopped.
- What?
- It stopped erasing.
Oh, shit.
This is terrible.
He's off the map.
- Where?
- I don't know where! What do you mean?
I don't know where!
This is bad. This is very, very bad news.
Where are my glasses?
Okay. Crap.
Okay. What do we do?
What do I do?
- What shall we do?
- I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do.
- Crap. Crap. I don't know!
- I just said that I don't know what to do.
- I'm sorry. What do we do?
- I don't know.
- Now, look, you're freaking me out. Mellow out.
Well, you have to do something.
He could wake up all half-baked.
Quiet. You're freaking me out.
Shh. Shh.
All gooey and... and half-baked.
Hmm, that sounds so good.
- Oh, shit!
- I'm hungry.
- Oh, shit.
- Oh! Oh!
What? Oh! What, what?
What?
- We should call Howard.
- No way. No, sir, man.
This is my...
I can handle this.
- I can't call Howard.
- He's an unbaked cookie.
He's... There's no time to fuck around.
- I got this under control.
- What are you talking about?
- Stop fucking around!
- Okay, I'll call Howard.
- Hello.
- Hello, Howard? Hey, it's Stan.
Um, I'm working on this guy down here,
and we seem to have lost him for a moment,
and, uh, I can't...
I can't bring him back up.
Okay, uh,
tell me what happened before he disappeared.
Well, I wasn't sure, really,
'cause I was away from the monitor for a minute...
and I had it on autopilot
because I had to, uh...
I had to pee.
- Where's Patrick?
- Patrick? Patrick had to go home sick.
Ah, geez.
- Okay, what's the address?
- I know. I'm so sorry.
That's okay. Come on.
- Yeah.
- Apartment 1 E. Rockville Center.
- Mary? He's coming right now.
- Yeah?
I'm staying.
- Get your stuff, Mary.
- I'm staying.
- I think you should go.
- Hell, no.
Mary... Shit.
- I am so stoned.
- Please, Mary.
- You have to go.
- Stop being stoned, Mary.
I don't want him to see me stoned.
- Mary, you have no idea how much trouble
we're gonna get into if Howard comes...
- I look like shit!
Joely, stop it! Joel!
Look! Hey, Joel!
- Joel!
- I want her to pick me up.
- It's weird how strong that desire is.
- Joel, look at me! Look.
You'll remember me in the morning,
and you'll come to me,
and you'll tell me about us, and we'll start over.
Pat? I just... Pat?
I thought we could have a little cocktail.
That Patrick guy...
he's copying me.
What Patrick guy?
- That guy!
- What?
He's here in my apartment.
He's one of those eraser guys.
He fell for you when they were doing you,
and now he's introduced himself
like he doesn't even know you,
and you guys are dating.
Really? Is he cute?
Clem,
there's nothing wrong with you.
You're the most wonderful person I've ever met.
You... You're kind,
Beautiful...
and smart and funny...
and... nice.
What?
Okay. All right.
Okay. Oh!
- Move, move, move! Come on. Let's go.
- Careful, careful.
Fine.
Oh, my God. I'm still stoned.
Those eyedrops you gave me
didn't do shit.
Be cool. Cool.
- Hello, Mary. What are you doing here?
- Oh, hi, Howard.
She was just here to help out.
I wanted to understand as much
as I could about the procedure as possible.
I think it's important for my job
to understand the inner workings...
of the work that we do.
Well, not that I do,
but the work that is done...
by people... where I also work,
the work of my colleagues.
All right, well,
let's see if we can, uh,
get to the bottom of this, shall we?
Uh, yeah. Um...
Well, that's odd.
I already tried that.
- Did you try going through the C-gate?
- Yeah, of course.
I mean... yes.
Yeah.
All right.
- You want to get linked up?
- Yeah.
All right.
I already...
I ran the utility programs,
and I had nothing there,
so I checked all the memories
against the printed logs.
- Here, Howard.
- Okay.
- I got you a chair. There you go.
- Oh, thank you.
You're welcome. Whew!
All right, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna go through the entire memory,
see if something comes up.
"Oh, my darling"
"Oh, my darling Clementine"
I love being bathed in the sink.
Such a feeling of security.
- I've never seen you happier, babyJoel.
- Hmm!
There it is.
I don't understand
why it's off the map like that.
What the heck
was he doing there?
His eyes are open.
- Has this happened before with him?
- No.
Oh, this is...
this is not good. No.
I'm gonna have to...
I'm gonna have to give him this.
Can't you see I love you, Antoine?
Okay, we're back in.
Wow.
That was beautiful to watch, Howard.
Like a surgeon or a concert pianist
or something.
Thank you, Mary.
Um, Howard, you should get some sleep.
I-I think I'll be fine now.
Why can't you see I love you, Antoine?
Hmm. Lucky me.
Lay one on me.
Don't call me Antoine.
- My name is Wally.
- Yes, I know,
but how can a woman love a man
with a name like Wally?
Oh! Oh! What was that?
- Hey.
- My God, there's people coming out of your butt.
There is?
- Got it.
- Tangerine!
- What, Joel... What are you doing?
- We gotta go.
Go on.
Please, please, go. Please go!
You can run,
but you can't hide.
Clem, come on!
There I am.
That truck.
Doc? Please.
All right,
let's begin by you telling me...
everything you remember...
That's strange.
He's in a memory that we've already erased.
Oh, well, at least we know where he is.
He's back on track, right?
Come on, Clem.
He seems to have developed some sort
of resistance to the procedure.
- I don't want to run anymore.
- Shit.
- Come on, come on.
- Hide me somewhere deeper, somewhere really buried.
- Where?
- Hide me in your humiliation.
Humiliation.
I'm sorry, okay?
Let me drive you home.
No!
- Bye, Howard.
- No, wait. Howard.
He's disappeared again.
- Oh, dear.
- I'm so sorry, Howard
Humiliation.
- Hu-mi-lia...
- Joel.
I don't like it either.
I'm just trying to find
horrible secret places to...
Joel, honey, I have a surprise...
I just... Oh, um...
Uh, you know what, honey?
I'm just gonna ask you in the morning.
Good night, sweetheart.
No.
- I'm sorry, Joel. Joely.
- Shut up.
Look! Joel!
- Joel, look!
- What?
Look where we are!
Whoo!
Clem, this isn't good.
Then hide me somewhere...
somewhere really buried.
- Hit it! Hit it!
- I can't! I gotta go home.
I'll do it later!
Come on, you big sissy!
Ooh!
Ooh, he has a girlfriend!
- Wait. What am I doing? You know something, Freddy?
- And he loves her!
You don't scare me anymore.
Ow! Ow!
Joel!
- Joely, get up. Come on, it's not worth it.
- Hit him! Hit him!
They're not worth it, Joel!
Tra-la-la-la-la! He's not listening!
- Come on, Joel.
- Stupid!
- I'm so ashamed.
- It's okay.
- You were a little kid.
- Yeah?
Come on.
That's where I live... lived.
I wish I knew you when I was a kid.
Do you like my pink hat? Here, look, feel better.
You can really kill me this time.
- It's my turn. Go. One, two, three.
- I can? You're really gonna die though.
- Okay.
- One, two, three.
You're dead.
Oh, my mom.
It's... It's okay. We're playing.
- Hi, Joel's mom. He's killing me.
- It's not real.
Okay, are you dead yet?
You're dead!
Uh, I think I got the hang of this.
I still don't understand it,
but I'm finding him quickly enough.
Clem!
Jo... Joely?
Are you okay, Joel?
Joel? Joel?
Oh, my God.
That was terrible.
- Okay, okay.
- That was like three seconds.
- All right. Let me do it one more time.
- One more, then I get to go.
Okay.
- Whoo-hoo-hoo!
- Whoo!
- Look at this.
- This is so cool!
Cool. Look out! Look out!
Ah!
- Shit!
- It's fluff.
Our house!
- Whoo-hoo!
- Come on.
Come on. We gotta go!
Whoo!
Come on!
We gotta go. Clem?
We gotta go.
Aah! Come on!
- No!
- This is a really bad time for this!
Get off me! Oh, God!
- I don't even know where we're going.
- It's gonna be fun. Come on.
- It's the best place. No, this way.
- No, this way.
No, no, no. This way.
You're no help at all.
What's wrong with you?
Let go of me, Joel!
I like watching you work, Howard.
I guess, uh...
I guess I'll go out for...
for some air,
if nobody minds.
It looks like
you have everything under control here.
Yeah, that's, uh...
that's fine.
Do you like quotes, Howard?
What do you mean?
Oh, you know,
like famous quotes?
I find reading them inspirational,
and in my reading,
I've come across some I thought you might like too.
Oh, well, I...
I'd love to hear some.
There's one that goes,
"Blessed are the forgetful,
for they get the better even of their blunders."
- That's Nietzsche, right?
- Yeah.
And here I thought I could tell you
something you didn't know.
Oh, no. It's... It's a good quote.
I'm happy we both know it.
Yeah.
Oh, and there's this other one I like.
It's by Pope Alexander,
and it goes...
- Alexander Pope?
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, shit.
It's just that I told myself
not to say "Pope Alexander" and sound like a dope,
and then I go ahead and say it.
- It's no big deal.
- You're such a sweetheart.
The quote goes,
"How happy is the blameless vestal's lot?
"The world forgetting, by the world forgot.
"Eternal sunshine of the spotless mind.
Each prayer accepted and each wish resigned."
I want to be a great big, huge elephant...
with a huge trunk like that.
Clem? Clementine?
I haven't heard that one.
It's lovely.
I just thought
it would be appropriate, maybe.
I really admire the work you do, Howard.
- I don't mean to be so familiar.
- Oh, it's fine. It's fine.
I-l-l-l-I...
I'm happy to hear...
I'm sorry.
I've loved you for a very long time.
- I shouldn't have said that.
- Oh, Mary, no.
It's... It's...
You're a wonderful girl.
But I...
You know, I have a wife and kids.
You know I have a wife and kids.
Oh, Mary.
Oh, Mary, we can't do this.
Oh, whoa.
Well,
good morning, Mrs. Mierzwiak.
- What?
- Oh, my God!
Who is it?
Uh...
Thank you, Stan.
Thanks a lot.
Hollis. Hollis!
Hollis!
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Hollis.
- I knew it, Howard.
- Hollis, it didn't start out to be like this.
I came here to work.
Hollis, this is a one-time mistake!
- I'm a stupid girl with a stupid crush!
- Yeah.
I swear I basically forced him into it!
Don't be a monster, Howard.
Tell the girl.
Tell me what?
Oh, you poor kid.
You can have him.
You did.
What?
Oh, uh,
we have a history.
I'm sorry.
Y-You wanted the procedure.
You...
You wanted it done...
so you could get past, uh...
You could... Yeah.
Um, I have to, uh,
finish the work in there.
It's almost morning.
We'll talk later.
Okay?
Hey.
Let me give you a lift home.
Fuck this thing. Damn it.
- Hi.
Didn't figure
you'd show your face around me again.
I guess I thought you were... humiliated.
You did run away, after all.
I just needed to see ya.
Yeah?
I'd like to, um,
take you out or something.
You're married.
Not yet. Not married.
No, I'm not married, no.
Look, man, I'm telling you
right off the bat I'm high maintenance,
so I'm not gonna tiptoe
around your marriage...
or whatever it is
you've got going there.
If you wanna be with me,
you're with me.
Okay.
Too many guys think I'm a concept,
or I complete them,
or I'm gonna make them alive.
But I'm just a fucked-up girl
who's looking for my own peace of mind.
- Don't assign me yours.
- I remember that speech really well.
- I had you pegged, didn't I?
- You had the whole human race pegged.
Hmm. Probably.
I still thought you were
gonna save my life,
even after that.
Mmm. I know.
It would be different...
if we could just give it
another go around.
Remember me.
Try your best.
Maybe we can.
Okay, so just tell me what you remember,
and, uh,
then we'll take it from there.
Okay.
I liked you immediately.
You didn't come on to me at all.
I liked that.
I was so tongue-tied around you at first.
I wanted you to think I was smart.
I couldn't wait to come to work.
I had these fantasies of
us being married...
and having kids and... just...
Oh, Howie, I can't do this.
We agreed it's for the best, Mary.
Yeah, I know.
Oh, God.
- I'll take the bottom and you...
- Uh-uh-uh! No, no, no. Here.
- I can take that.
- So you want me to carry that?
- Help me with that. Can you get the cooler?
- Honey, the cooler is...
- That's light, huh? Oh, I can get that.
- You can get it.
No, no, no, no!
- Don't take anything.
- I can take the plane.
Put the thing up.
Put the gate back up.
This is the day we met.
You were down by the surf.
I could just make you out in the distance.
I remember being drawn to you even then.
I thought,
"Wow, how odd. I'm drawn to someone's back."
You were in that orange sweatshirt
that I would come to know so well...
and even hate, eventually.
At the time I thought,
"How cool! An orange sweatshirt."
Hi there.
Hi.
I saw you sitting over here...
by yourself,
and I thought,
"Thank God.
Someone normal who doesn't know
how to interact at these things either."
Yeah.
I don't ever know what to say.
I'm Clementine.
Can I borrow a piece of your chicken?
And then you just took it...
without waiting for an answer.
It was so intimate,
like we were already lovers.
I'm Joel.
Hi, Joel.
So, no jokes about my name.
You mean like...
Oh, my darling, oh, my darling
Oh, my darling Clementine
Huckleberry Hound,
that sort of thing?
Yeah. Like that.
Oh, no jokes. No jokes.
One of my favorite things when I was a kid
was my Huckleberry Hound doll.
Oh.
I think your name is magical.
This is it, Joel.
It's gonna be gone soon.
I know.
What do we do?
Enjoy it.
- You married?
- No.
Let's move into this neighborhood!
I do sort of live with someone though.
- Male or female?
- What?
Female. Female.
At least I'm not barking up the wrong tree.
- You know these people?
- No, of course not. Come on.
They might have a dog.
There's no dog.
What are you doing?
- It's freezing out.
- I can't believe this.
Hoo-hoo!
- Clementine!
- There we go. Whoo-hoo!
Come on, man.
The water's fine.
Nobody's coming here tonight.
Believe me.
It's dark.
So, uh,
what's your girlfriend's name?
Naomi, but we're not really...
I mean...
- We're...
- Whatever.
So this is great.
Now I can look for, um, candles, matches...
and the liquor cabinet.
Oh, God.
I think we should go.
There's no phone line.
What?
- I think we should go.
- Why?
It's our house...
just for tonight.
We are "David and Ruth Laskin."
- Which one do you want to be?
- Uh...
I prefer to be Ruth,
but I can be flexible.
What are you do...
- Alcohol!
- Oh, boy.
So, are you okay with wine?
- I don't know.
- Well, you choose the wine.
I'm gonna go find the bedroom
and slip into something more... Ruth.
- I'm Ruth-less at the moment.
- I really should go.
I've gotta catch my ride.
So go.
I did.
I thought maybe you were a nut,
but you were exciting.
I wish you'd stayed.
I wish I'd stayed too.
Now I wish I'd stayed.
I wish I'd done a lot of things.
Oh, God, I wish I had...
I wish I'd stayed. I do.
- Well, I came back downstairs, and you were gone.
- I walked out. I walked out the door.
- Why?
- I don't know. I felt like a scared little kid.
I was like...
It was above my head. I don't know.
You were scared?
Yeah.
Thought you knew that about me.
I ran back to the bonfire,
trying to outrun my humiliation, I think.
- Was it something I said?
- Yeah.
You said,
"So go"...
with such disdain, you know?
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Joely?
What if you stayed this time?
I walked out the door.
There's no memory left.
Come back and make up a good-bye, at least.
Let's pretend we had one.
Bye, Joel.
I love you.
Meet me in Montauk.
"I didn't crash the plane.
The plane crashed.
I didn't crash the plane."
"You were operating the plane
with the remote control, and then it crashed."
- "It was fucking windy."
- "Come on, man."
"You're stoned, and you're driving."
"Yeah, the pot balances it out.
The pot brings you back up."
"That's why I smoke it.
If I'm going to be drinking, then I'll smoke it."
"It does.
That's a medical fact."
"It was proven on the Science Network."
- "Honey, just watch the road."
- "I can't see shit."
"I saw you talking to somebody pretty."
- "She was nice."
- "Yeah, man. Who was that?"
"She was, um, just a girl."
Okay.
So I gotta...
I gotta drop the van off.
Thanks, Stan. Thanks.
We'll talk.
Hey!
Hey.
- You got a lot of your stuff there, I see.
- Yeah, that's right. My stuff.
I take it you're not coming back.
I wouldn't come back if I was you either.
- Do you swear you didn't know?
- I-I swear.
- So you didn't do the erasing?
- Of course not. God, no.
And you never even suspected we were together?
Once, maybe.
I was coming back from a job,
and you were at his car.
I saw you two talking.
So I waved to you,
and you giggled, you know.
How'd I look?
You looked happy.
Happy with a secret.
And after that?
I never saw you two together again like that,
so I just...
I don't know.
I just figured I was imagining things.
"Montauk train now boarding on track B.
All aboard."
I really like you, Mary Svevo.
You know that?
Thanks.
Let me get my toothbrush.
Yeah. Just...
Where are you, Clem?
I'm worried.
- La-la-la-la-la.
- I feel like you're mad at me,
and I don't know what I did.
What did I do?
I love you so much.
I'll do anything to make you happy.
Tell me what you want me to do,
and I'll do it.
Listen, I'm gonna stop by this morning
just to make sure you're okay.
Oh. Whew.
Vámonos, señor.
I-I had a really nice time last night.
Nice?
I had the best fucking night
of my entire fucking life...
last night.
That's better.
- This is weird.
- "To all patients of Dr. Howard Mierzwiak."
"My name is Mary Svevo.
We've met, but you don't remember me."
"I worked for a company you hired
to have part of your memory erased."
- "I have since decided that this is a horrible...
- Some kind of teaser ad or something."
"In order to correct this,
I'm sending everyone's file back to them."
"My name is Clementine Kruczynski."
"I'm here to erase Joel Barish."
- What is this?
- I don't know.
"He's boring.
Is that enough reason to erase someone?"
"I've been thinking lately
how I was before and how I am now,
and it's like he changed me.
I feel like I'm always pissy now."
"I don't like myself when I'm with him.
I don't like myself anymore."
"I can't stand to even look at him.
That pathetic, wimpy, apologetic smile."
- "That sort of wounded puppy shit he does, you know?"
- What are you doing?
- I'm not doing anything.
- "The bloom is certainly fucking off the rose at this point."
- Are you screwing with me?
- No!
- You are screwing with me.
- Joel, I'm not!
- You clearly are.
- Look! Ok, let's just take a minute and...
Patrick, get the fuck away.
- Oh, sweetheart...
- Get the fuck away from me!
- Can we talk about it?
- No! Get the fuck away!
Joel Barish.
- Hey, Clementine.
- Hey.
Nice to see you. Yeah.
Yeah.
"Really very educated."
"I mean, she's smart, I think,
but not educated."
"I couldn't really talk to her
about books, you know?"
"She's more of a magazine-reading girl."
"Her vocabulary leaves something to be desired."
"Sometimes...
I was embarrassed in public..."
- Hi.
- "Because she would pronounce..."
- library "libary".
- Hi.
"Libary. Libary."
Look what I found.
"I think if there's a truly seductive quality
about Clementine,
it's that her personality promises
to take you out of the mundane."
You made me look skinny.
"Amazing, burning meteorite...
will carry you to another world
where things are exciting."
"But what you quickly learn is that...
it's really an elaborate ruse."
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
- It's okay.
- "So flashy in a kind of obvious way."
- "But still, it seduces you."
- Joel, I really like you.
I hate that I said mean things about you.
- Let me turn this off, okay?
- Hey, it's... it's only fair.
"Where's the real Clementine?"
"I mean, the whole thing with the hair...
it's all bullshit."
- I really like your hair.
- Thank you.
- I do.
- "The world's a goddamn mess."
- "Is it some kind of a revolt? Change your hair color."
- You want a drink or something?
Do you have any whiskey?
"No, I don't think her sex is...
motivated."
"I saw it clearly the last night we were together."
"It wasn't sex. It was just sad."
Hey. Sorry.
I thought there was more.
"The only way Clem thinks
she can get people to like her...
is to fuck 'em...
or at least dangle the possibility
of getting fucked in front of'em."
"And she's so desperate and insecure...
that she'll, sooner or later,
go around fucking everybody."
- I don't do that.
- I wouldn't think that about you.
- Because I don't.
- I know.
Because it really hurts me
that you said that because I don't do that.
- I'm so sorry.
- I'm sorry about all this. I'm gonna... go.
I'm a little confused.
I don't really think I can be here.
Um... bye.
Bye.
- It was nice meeting you and all.
- "But I don't know her at all."
"What a loss
to spend that much time with someone,
only to find out that she's a stranger."
Wait.
- What?
- I don't know.
- Just wait. Just wait.
- What do you want, Joel?
I don't know. I want you to wait for...
just a while.
- Okay.
- Really?
I'm not a concept, Joel. I'm just a fucked-up girl
who's looking for my own peace of mind.
- I'm not perfect.
- I can't see anything that I don't like about you.
- Right now I can't.
- But you will. But you will.
You know, you will think of things,
and I'll get bored with you and feel trapped...
because that's what happens with me.
Okay.
"Change your heart"
"Look around you"
"It will astound you"
"Now, I need your lovin'"
"Like the sunshine"
"And everybody's gotta learn sometime"
"Everybody's gotta learn sometime"
"Mm-mm-mm"
"Change your heart"
"And look around you"
"It will astound you"
"I need your lovin'"
"Like the sunshine"
"And everybody's gotta learn sometime"
"Everybody's gotta learn sometime"
"Mm-mm-mm"