Comrades,
Japan belongs to the People!
Not the Emperor,
not the military!
Long live the People!
The Black Dragon Clan is coming!
Kick the Chinese out of the school!
Maintenance is important.
Do not allow
the fluid to enter the reservoir
nor the engine.
The function of the pump
is only then maintained.
And never try to repair
it without the help of an engineer.
Stop writing!
All Chinese get out of here!
You can't enter here!
This school is not for
Chinese people!
Get out now!
Behave yourself here!
Are you alright?
Rotten scum!
What do you think you're doing!
Who are you to speak to me?
Yamada Mitsuko.
The one who looks down at you!
Chicken!
I don't care who you are.
Before I count to three,
you better disappear.
One!
Two!
Three!
Master...
He is Funakoshi Fumio
Master of the Black Dragon Clan.
Have you already given up fighting?
Violence is no solution.
Now you see the result.
Didn't you learn anything in my school?
Professor Watanabe.
Excuse my pupils.
Be thankful for his mercy.
You could all be crippled if he wanted you to be.
Who did you fight with?
Me.
You alone?
Your Kung Fu is quite efficient.
I am Funakoshi Fumio
from the Black Dragon Clan. And you?
Mitsuko, why are you here?
Uncle Funakoshi,
my pen has been broken by your pupils!
It was very expensive!
You know I am poor.
Why tell me about it?
Do you guys have some money?
Satisfied?
Just like your blessed father.
Impossible to satisfy.
Don't you worry nobody will marry you?
No problem at all.
Chen Zhen is all I want.
Chen Zhen?
Yes. Chen Zhen of Jing Wu School.
Jing Wu School of Shanghai?
- That means Huo Yuen-jia...
- Is my Master.
Impressive...
Is there a problem?
I just received...
a telegram from Shanghai.
It says that Master Huo
was killed in a Kung Fu match by...
his opponent Akutagawa
Ryuichi of Nijiguchi.
He is from our clan.
lmpossible!
I am verry sorry. But this is what I was told.
Excuse me.
Too bad I missed the opportunity
to challenge him myself.
Chen Zhen!
Where are you going?
Chinese embassy.
To check if this is really true.
A Japanese could never have beaten your Master.
Stop the Japanese invasion!
Long live the People!
I warn you! If you
stay too long I will look for someone else.
Chen Zhen!
Are you coming back to Japan?
When they leave China,
I will come back to Japan.
They are only going to Tsingtao
to fight the Germans.
You better be right about it,
because Tsingtao belongs to China.
Both Japanese and Germans
are invaders to China.
Chen Zhen
Do you hate the Japanese?
I don't know!
Being in this area,
we have no choice.
Take care of yourself.
Chen Zhen!
JAPAN AND UNITED KINGODM FORM ALLIANCE
KARATE MASTER AKUTAGAWA
MATCHED WITH MASTER HUO
Some small change!
I don't have anymore.
I really don't have more.
Go away!
- Good Morning.
- I am not Japanese.
You are not?
Me neither!
Please sit down.
- Where shall I take you?
- Jing Wu School.
Jingwu School?
To learn Kung Fu?
Yes, I want to learn Kung Fu.
Please go!
Don't go to Jingwu.
Everyone here knows Jingwu was number one,
but this is over.
If you don't wanna take me there
I will take another drive.
Wait, wait. As you are paying me,
I will take you anywhere you want.
Attention.
Let's go.
JING WU SCHOOL
Now that Master Huo is dead
there is no future for Jingwu School.
Are you sure you don't want to
try another school?
They are really finished.
5th Senior!
- Are you the 5th Senior?
- Biu!
- Let me take this.
- Thanks.
- You are...
- Chen Zhen of Jingwu School.
Jingwu School is not finished.
Wait and see.
What are you waiting for?
5th Senior!
Master Ngai.
This is my ancestral tablet.
If you want a challenge
let's go outside.
Master, are you alright?
Master Ngai.
Thank you for the fight.
I am no match for you.
The victory was unjustified.
You must be tired from your
journey. Come later for a rematch!
Have you finished your studies?
Anyway, i am happy you are back.
Uncle Nong.
I was worried that this might affect your studies...
so I did not notify you about Master.
How did you hear about it?
It was all over the newspapers.
The Japs must be very happy about it.
Well... Let's pay our respects to my Father.
Wait! What are you doing?
He is not a Huo.
He is not allowed to wear this.
Uncle Nong.
He was brought up by my father.
He is a part of the family.
Before the duel,
father's asthma was already getting worse.
I tried to talk him out of it,
but of course he would not listen.
TOLERANCE
Please go ahead!
What are you doing?
Master Huo personally made this board!
Uncle Nong
Chen Zhen is right.
Foreigners have been doing whatever
they wanted to do in our country.
That's because we have tolerated them doing it.
As long as I live
we won't tolerate it anymore!
I will look for Akutagawa.
Chen Zhen.
You must make a challenge first.
Forget about it. I will go now.
Not even our police can enter Nijiguchi.
If anything happens to you,
what will become of the Jing Wu school?
- Even your father could not beat him.
- Uncle Nong...
Your father left you in my care.
I am responsible for your safety.
Lun, Cheung, follow Chen.
Notify me if anything happens.
- How nice!
Get out!
Chief, a phone call!
Who is it?
Yes, Yuen-Kui's speaking?
Nong Jin-Sun.
Is it that serious?
I will be there right away.
We have to go to the Nijiguchi Area.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Idiots!
- You are like girls!
- Dismissed!
Who do you think you are to walk
in here with your shoes on?
I am Chen Zhen of Jingwu School.
I am looking for Akutagawa Ryuichi.
No Chinese are allowed in here!
Get out!
Here is China. I can walk where I want to.
Bastard!
I don't want to fight with you.
Get your master out!
This will be a fair duel.
If either of us should die,
there mustn't be any vengeance!
My master fought you using the Huo Fist.
I shall do the same.
I can see that you obviously never could have been
a match for my master.
Master!
Nobody is allowed to enter except Japanese!
Are you sure you saw him enter?
I saw him go in there myself!
There he is!
Are you Japanese?
No.
Salute!
- What is going on?
- Nothing!
Mr. Fujita, Mr. Ambassador...
Everything is ok.
Don't create an incident!
Patrol one. Fall in!
- 5th Senior, how was the match?
- I won.
Bravo!
Ask Ting-En and Uncle Nong
to join me at Master's grave.
- It hasn't beensealed yet.
- That's even better.
Be careful.
What are you doing?
- What are they doing?
- Examining the body of Master.
Why did you let them do it?
What can I do?
Chen is a student of the Jing Wu School.
Chen, tell me
why are you doing this to my father?
Akutagawa could never have beaten Master.
I suspect he was poisoned.
Yuen-Kui, have you ever suspected anything?
Master Huo was hit by his opponent
and vomitted blood.
Lots of people saw it. Nothing suspicious.
I rather want to be called disloyal and disrespectful
than not to know the truth.
I must find out the truth at any cost.
If you want to stop me,
you better kill me right now.
But who did it?
That is for you to find out!
Come on everbody.
Let us bury Master with the respect he deserves.
The Japs could never have beaten Master so easily.
They will get what they deserve now!
Luckily 5th Senior came back in time!
I don't understand...
how did they poison Master?
For some people it is not very hard to do it..
Master prepared this fight for a whole month.
He did never get out!
That's right.
The bad guy must be among us!
Hsiao-Wei!
You brought the meals to Master?
Yes, why?
Are you suspecting her?
Not really.
I am just asking myself,
who else had access to Master's food?
Me!
I do all the cooking in this house!
Are you suspecting me?
Cheung, go check the kitchen for poison!
See if there are any dead rats in there!
- Calm down!
- Why don't you go check?
Go and see if there is
anything poisonous in there!
Hurry up! Go!
Please, don't get mad!
I must clear my name!
Ting-En, what is going on?
Uncle was suspecting the food was poisoned
and Uncle Gun thinks we are accusing him.
I never said I was suspecting him!
Ok, very well! From now on you can eat
whatever you want, but not from me!
Master Huo was brought up by my cooking!
And you dare
accuse me of poisoning him?
Enough now, let's eat!
Chen Zhen
be careful, it might be poisoned.
Master has eaten together with all of us.
If your food was poisoned,
we would all be dead already!
That's right.
Nong Jin-Sun, did you hear that?
Suspecting me!
Eat!
The Japs may come back for revenge,
so let's eat before they come!
I will visit Dr. Smith later
to see the analysis
of the poison that killed Master.
Ana... lysis?
Chemical analysis.
JING WU SCHOOL
- Have you seen this before?
- No!
- Great!
- Wonderful!
You are incredible.
Will you teach us some boxing too?
Sure! Right now?
Fancy moves not effective.
And die-hard training will help.
Challenge has one objective:
beat the opponent.
You need: reflexes, speed and power!
Simple and direct offense will work best.
To attack an opponent...
first learn to take an attack.
But we can hit him before they attack!
What if you don't have enough power? You can hit him
ten times but he will not go down.
So you need more power.
Sir, they have come to
learn Kung Fu.
Will Chen Zhen be our Master?
Yes, we want to learn from him!
He will not teach you.
Ting-En is the Headmaster.
- Four-legged form?
- Exact.
You look so shaky. Try a kick!
Where is the power?
Let me show you.
There is a form of side-kicking
in Japanese Kung Fu.
Go on.
- Simple but effective.
- Show us.
Get ready.
Are you alright?
Concentrate the whole power of the body
and kick sharply at the point.
HSlAO HUNG
- What's the matter?
- Please stay.
It's late.
Stay with me.
I am the Head Master now.
I must go back.
You were afraid of your father.
but now you can stay.
You can do what you want.
If someone sees me here
I will lose all respect.
I don't believe it. Who would not
respect Master Ting-En?
Please? Will you stay?
I have to go before dawn.
I want to know
every move of these people.
But they're all Japanese!
There will always be ignorant
idiots who go against history.
Sorry, I am late.
Are you still scared of Chen Zhen?
Are you even too weak to knock the door?
I wanted you to rest,
that's why I did not invite you here.
I only have one question.
Did you hear about the autopsy on Master Huo?
You get out!
What's this? Secret affairs?
It really was you who poisoned him, wasn't it?
The Japanese Empire, regarding
technology, industrial achievement
and military power, is ahead of China.
We put our hopes in you, the warriors,
to break the Chinese Martial Arts Legend.
But you have been a big disappointment!
So we had to think of something.
Shameless!
It's only military strategics.
This is for military only! This is no way for a samurai!
The match was to be fair and square!
You shameless bastard made me lose all respect!
You dare to speak of the samurai spirit?
Let me tell you about the samurai spirit!
Justice is secondary!
To serve the Emperor,
I will risk becoming a criminal in history.
This is wrong.
I will show you.
According to Dr. Smith
Master was poisoned with a slowly growing drug.
It damaged his lung functions,
seeming like an asthmatic disease.
Is there a traitor at Jingwu School?
Chen Zhen, why did you come back?
Why do you ask me?
You have become an idol here at Jingwu School.
Did you ever think how Ting-En must feel?
I did not...
Since you've been back, have you ever talked with
Master Ting-En about the training?
You do what you want here.
Can you think once
about what you are doing here?
You are very talented,
but always bare in mind...
that Ting En is the
Head Master of Jingwu School!
It's getting late.
Think about it.
- 5th Senior, going out?
- Yes.
Working so hard.
Master Chen!
Out here so early in the morning?
I brought some friends with me.
They all want to learn from you.
Don't follow me!
Overslept?
Master!
I WILL KILL ALL CRIMINALS. CHEN ZHEN.
Hold on!
Violence is no solution!
General!
Move!
Good Morning master!
Where have you been the whole night?
- Where is Chen Zhen?
- He went out.
Tell me when he's back.
I am in my room.
The Japs are coming.
Everyone out!
Little Master!
- The Japanese are here!
- Calm down.
Something bad will happen.
Call the Police.
- What do you want?
- Where is Chen Zhen.
Chen Zhen? He is out.
Maybe he went beating some Japs.
He has a strange habit.
If he does not beat one Jap a day he feels sick.
Wait!
Chinese Bastards, you killed Master Akutagawa.
You Japs only know how to blame others.
Enough talking.
We won't leave without Chen Zhen!
As I see you carry swords,
I know you mean business.
Close the doors!
Protect Master's shrine!
Hurry!
- Shoot the Japs!
- Stop that!
Draw your swords.
You better leave now!
What? Just let them go!
Both sides have been injured.
This straightens it out.
We will not leave until we have Chen Zhen.
Sakamoto, give me some face.
Who are you talking to?
5th Senior!
Don't move!
Old man, you will not shoot!
I won't.
But my finger could slip...
Shoot the first who moves.
Take Chen Zhen away!
Why are you doing this?
Akutagawa was murdered.
We must question him.
- I did not do it!
- Take him away!
You all better leave now or we will be forced to shoot!
Come on... sit down!
Jie is handling this case, so no need to worry.
Chen will be alright.
Why are you in this uniform?
This case is too big for me. I can't do anything here.
And what about Chen Zhen?
- Let Fate decide it.
- Fate? Wait!
Captain, you have
four witnesses, don't you?
Yes, our Police Department has four witnesses
who all claim to have seen Chen Zhen kill a man.
Strange.
Where did they come from?
I saw Chen Zhen with my own eyes.
There is no way it wasn't him!
It's true! I saw him
stab the deceased with a knife!
It's him. He killed the murdered with an axe!
How many fingers can you see?
Two.
No no no, four!
Could you come a little bit closer?
No need.
That's ridiculous!
I was at Jingwu School
with my fellow students.
They can speak for me.
Your Honour,
the Jingwu Students cannot be taken
as witnesses, as they are very close to him.
What are you talking!
Your witness has just arrived.
Your Honour, I have another witness to present!
I don't think a
Chinese witness can be heard!
My witness is Japanese!
Japanese?
Miss, please identify yourself.
I am Yamada Mitsuko.
The daughter of Yamada Mitsuo.
Minister of Education.
Chen Zhen said he was at
Jingwu School at the night of the murder.
Can you confirm this?
He is lying.
He spent the whole
night with me in my motel room.
He did not leave...
- The whole night?
- Yes.
What did she say?
What if he sneaked
out while you were sleeping?
That is impossible!
We didn't sleep the whole night...
We were busy doing other things.
What things were you doing if not sleeping?
What else can you do in a bed...
when you don't sleep in it?
- What did she say?
- No idea, and you?
The Japanese said, she slept
with Chen Zhen the whole night.
Are you sure?
Congratulations.
Let's go.
The Chinese Hero
is nothing but a womanizer!
How come you are here?
I have abandoned everything for you.
Now you must take care of me!
Cook for her?
Don't even think about it!
Chen Zhen, your Master sent
you to Japan to learn new technologies.
To beat the Japs with knowledge.
Never forget your Master's
wishes because of a woman!
What will we do now?
Jingwu School does not want to be
linked to the Japanese in any way.
Chen Zhen
You are a student of Jingwu.
You can't have affairs with Japanese here.
Chen Zhen, did I cause you any trouble here?
It's alright.
You should not worry about getting a wife.
A hero should not be sentimental.
You want to destroy
your life for this woman?
Uncle Nong, Mitsuko has
given up everything to help me.
And she testified in court
for me, what can she do now?
Maybe that's how Jap woman behave?
Here at Jingwu, we can't
tolerate any Japs, whoever it may be.
It's your choice.
Either you leave the woman
or you leave Jing Wu School.
Little Master, you
obviously want to kick 5th Senior out!
What is it, are you with the Japs now?
- You want to frame me?
- Why are you talking trash then!
- Say that again!
- Then what?
Enough!
Chen Zhen
If this goes on,
Jingwu School will be finished.
I don't want any
in-fighting because of this.
There is only one solution...
To see who is
Head Master of Jingwu School!
Once and for all.
I don't want to be the Head Master!
I don't care what you think.
Here are some students
who don't want to listen to me anymore!
I will challenge you now
to see who is worthy of being the Head Master.
If you win, you must become
the Head Master and this woman mustn't leave.
Little Master!
Beat the Jap friend out of Jingwu School!
Are you alright?
Are you ok?
I lost.
You are the Head Master.
I don't want to be.
I will not seperate from Mitsuko.
If I have to make the choice...
I will leave Jingwu School.
Are you going back
to Shangtung? It's chaotic there!
Mitsuko, wait here.
Boss, any rooms?
Yes, please enter.
They have a room.
A Japanese? Impossible!
She is my wife, please let us stay.
- Isn't that Chen Zhen?
- Damn Japanese traitor!
Jingwu traitor!
You are harming my business.
Leave!
Let's go.
GRAVE OF HUO YUEN-JlA
A mouse! On the furniture!
A mouse?
- Where?
- I saw it over there, really!
It's gone.
Mice like such places very much.
I don't like this place.
It scares me.
They were here first.
In fact we scare them!
I think you are right.
I am very sorry...
To live with me in such a lousy hideout.
After all it's a nice place.
Wonderful landscape.
Much better than in any hotel room!
Is that what you want?
Let's move to a place like this then!
Are you giving up Jingwu School then?
Jingwu School has given up on me.
After all, at least I can
relax without this burden.
This doesn't sound like Chen Zhen.
Why?
You are lying to yourself.
You can't live without Jingwu School.
How can you relax!
Chen Zhen is lying.
Mitsuko has found out the truth!
Really?
Uncle Nong, have some Tea.
Thanks. Have you eaten yet?
I am not hungry.
Ting-En still hasn't returned?
He has a hard time,
he's never lost a fight before.
The match against Chen Zhen
must have been a great burden for him.
He has a bad temper.
Maybe he is not willing to come back.
But who can be the Head Master then?
Huo's Michung Fist must stay in the family!
How can Master rest in
peace if nobody carries on with it?
Who is teaching at the moment?
Cheung and Biu.
What should we do if a challenger arrives?
My mother wrote a letter.
It says that Jingwu offended the Japanese.
She asks me to leave here.
So what? Will you leave?
I don't know what to do!
Don't worry. This is still British territory!
The Japanese can't enter here, can they?
You Chinese love to waste everything?
Two serving for one table!
What is it?
I want to see your Head Master.
He is not here.
What do you want?
The champion of the the Black Dragon Clan,
Master Funakoshi Fumio
wants to challenge your Head Master.
What are we going to do now?
- Find Ting-En!
- Useless, better find Chen Zhen!
We don't want a traitor!
- Mind your words!
- Isn't he a traitor?
Stop it! Don't argue!
This will lead us nowhere!
Find Little Master!
Hurry up!
Uncle Gun...
Cheung.
- Where did Little Master go?
- How do I know?
What's up Uncle Gun?
Don't pretend!
Where is my son?
We can talk about this at night.
You said if I poison
Master Huo you will release my son!
Listen, it isn't that easy!
Your son is a
convicted murderer in Shangtung!
You promised!
Did I promise?
The Japs said that!
My daughter-in-law told me
that my son was
already killed in the prison!
You already killed Huo,
so what can you do about it?
Besides we paid you very well!
You didn't hesitate when we gave you the money?
If the Japs promised you,
your son is surely alright!
Now stop the talking about this matter!
You told me the drug will not kill Master Huo.
If I had known that beforehand,
I would rather have let my son die.
Help!
Uncle Gun has
commited suicide!
Help me get him down! Quick!
Help me! Hurry up!
We found this under his body!
What is it?
This is for Master's asthma,
Tien-En's friend brought it from Nang Yeung.
Hey! Master Huo was the only one at Jingwu to eat this!
Gun could have used this
food for poisoning Master Huo...
Then he felt too guilty and commited suicide.
He is already dead.
Please don't make it public.
If people hear of this,
it will hurt Jingwu's reputation even more.
Jingwu will perish anyway, no matter what!
Chen Zhen has left,
Ting-En has disappeared.
You need a new Head Master, and this very soon!
Where have we come to?
What would Master Huo say about all this?
Captain, what shall we do?
You are the Captain today, why ask me?
Please help me out.
Take this stuff for analysis.
Please help me look for Ting-En.
I will, don't worry!
Miss, are you looking for someone?
Please tell me,
is Nong Jin-Sun here?
He is inside,
please follow me.
Uncle Nong, this Lady wants to see you.
What is it?
Ting-En is at my place!
He refuses to come
back here, no matter what I say.
Where is he?
Can you bring me there?
- Dizzy Star House.
- A brothel?
What's your relation with Ting-En?
I know him for two years.
He must have spent lots of money on you.
Don't worry. I will leave him.
Ting-En isn't as bad as you may think now.
He always hoped to establish Jingwu School.
He told me he wants it to
be better than it was under his father.
This is the truth.
Uncle Nong, you have to help him!
Beat him!
Let me fight them!
Let me go!
Little Master!
Sing, Biu, let's go home.
What are you doing here?
Something wrong with Jingwu?
The Nijiguchi School has challengend Jingwu.
What about Chen Zhen?
The Head Master must meet the challenge.
Not Chen Zhen.
Forget it. Let's go.
Wait!
I will go with you.
You think you can make it?
I won't let people look down
on Jingwu School, even if I should lose!
One moment!
What about this lady?
You can't leave her here all alone.
This is no way to treat a woman.
Get the chief.
I want you to bail her out!
Hsiao-Hung, won't you miss your shiny dresses?
It's an honour that I can dress like you do!
This cloth looks old.
I will find you new ones tomorrow.
I've checked.
Funakoshi Fumio is the
number one warrior of the Black Dragon Clan.
But he is too old.
Uncle Nong.
Now you look decent!
You better use your real name
from now on, So-Lan.
Why didn't you treat Mitsuko the same way?
That's different.
Mitsuko is Japanese.
Ting-En, we only have 10 days until the duel.
Thanks. Biu, go on.
You treat Ting-En very well.
Everybody's treated the same way.
Is his Kung Fu the best at Jingwu School?
- Yes.
What about Chen Zhen?
They are equal.
Sorry, Little Master.
- Are you ok?
Go on.
What's wrong with him?
- He seems to be somewhere else.
BLACK DRAGON CLAN
FUNAKOSHl FUMlO
Spirit Table of
Akutagawa Ryuichi
Master Funakoshi, we have
sent the ultimatum to the Jingwu School.
Make sure that I chose my opponents.
And not the military.
Have you got that?
All the expenses of the Black Dragon Clan in China
are paid by the Japanese army.
That does not matter.
You can leave the
Black Dragon Clan if you want to.
Your chairman won't agree to this.
Don't try to opress me with the chairman.
I am only a martial arts master.
Not a politician.
CHALLENGE
Already awake?
Good Morning.
Are you Master Funakoshi?
Uncle Funakoshi?
Mitsukotu, why do you live so far away?
I would have taken a
carriage if i had known before!
Did father send you?
I haven't seen your father for a long time.
Then why are you here?
Because of him.
Chen Zhen?
Are you two married?
No.
But aren't you living together?
Neither Chinese nor
Japanese would accept if we married.
Lucky you aren't married.
If he dies, you won't be a widow.
What did you say?
If you should die,
I will send your ashes back to Japan.
Young Man, you are quite confident.
You want to fight?
Why didn't you tell me before?
Men don't have to tell everything to women.
Chen Zhen, come.
Tell me, what is the most powerful stroke?
Concentrate all your energy on one focal point,
then hit!
This is really powerful.
But stones don't hit back like humans do.
What will be the most powerful stroke then?
Enough theories. Let's do some practice.
How about the best defence?
Attack!
Why waste energy defending,
when you can attack?
Strike the opponent in the shortest time possible!
Huo style seems similar to Karate.
Based on attacking first.
You don't understand, do you?
Hard without soft only wastes energy.
Soft without hard can't strike either.
Old Master, how do you teach your students?
Has your master taught you that?
Bad temper is the weak point in a match.
Young Man, you will lose with this attitude!
My master never talked that much.
Are you going to fight?
Wait!
I am old. I must warm up a bit first.
What kind of style is this?
Don't ask. If it wins, it's a good one!
Are your eyes alright?
I'm fine.
I don't want to take any advantage.
It's over!
Are you alright?
It's not easy to be so young and so talented!
Very rare!
You have much energy for such an age!
Chinese say:
"The Old fear the strength of the Youth"
It's true.
But, I have lost!
I adopted your fighting style.
Chinese martial arts always
emphasize on personal well-being.
Not the battles.
You actually surprised me.
The objective of matching is to beat the opponent.
Wrong, young man.
The best way to beat the opponent
is to do it with a gun.
The goal of Kung Fu is to maximize one's energy
and to develop a higher physical level.
To achieve that, you must
understand life and the universe.
Never forget that.
I have to go. Take care.
Aren't we fighting?
Fighting is for animals.
The fight ended in a draw.
However, I am not representing all Japanese warriors.
In Japan, there are many even more powerful than me.
Master, aren't you the best in Japan?
To say he is the best, is to speak of his wisdom.
Not his expertise in killing.
Master Huo Yuen Jia, I have lost.
I never would have expected you
to have such a good student.
Now, the best at the Nijiguchi
is Fujita Gou, called the "Killing Machine".
Young Man, take care of yourself.
I have won!
Your Go skills have improved.
Too bad life is not as easy as a Go game.
Only a few years ago, Dr. Sun Yat Sen
was a good friend of the Kokuryo.
Now they have changed.
Just like the military...
..they want to conquer China.
Conquer China?
They are daydreaming.
It's not a dream!
The Japanese army based in China
has already more than half of China's military strength.
I learned from you already
that Japan is now like a very strong ant
which wants to eat a sleeping elephant.
While the Elephant sleeps,
the ant seems to gain some advantage.
But once the elephant wakes up, the ant has no chance!
Don't you agree on that?
But as I see it
the elephant is still asleep.
Thus, there is more than one ant looking for a chance...
The elephant will wake up.
Of course. Too bad...
that most of the Japanese won't believe you or me.
For the past decades
Japan received the majority of benefit from winning wars.
Japan wishes to become a strong Empire.
People like General Fujita
are not seldom in Japan.
Seeing all these factors.....
a war seems inevitable!
You are back!
Good evening.
- Where is Chen Zhen?
- He is out.
Have a seat.
Have some tea.
Thanks.
You learned to speak Chinese?
A little.
You speak well.
Chen, you are back! Mr. Huo is here to see you.
Where have you been? Keeping you busy?
I found a job in the telegram station.
- Did you really give up Jingwu?
- Doesn't matter now.
As I am not at Jingwu School,
my current job is meaningful too.
Jingwu needs you to come back.
I also brought Hsiao-Hung back.
From the Dizzy Star?
Haven't you met her?
Congratulations!
You can bring Mitsuko along to Jingwu.
She is Japanese.
They won't accept her...
She has done so much for you.
She is a nice girl.
But what would outsiders say?
Jingwu School's reputation would be affected.
I can't be so selfish.
I've learned a new style lately.
- Which one?
- Let me show you.
It's like the Huo Fist!
Yes. It's the Huo Michung Fist.
Master said this style is not for others but for Huos.
This is to be kept among Jingwu forever.
Chen Zhen, promise me.
I have to go to the challenge tomorrow.
If anything happens to me...
teach it to the others at Jingwu School for me.
Sorry, I decided to leave immediately.
There are things in life more important than love.
While I am not with you
you can achieve even more.
Fulfil your promise to Ting-En.
When the Japanese army returns to Japan,
I will wait for you in Kyoto.
I will take only Lun with me.
Ting-En, I am very worried.
Don't you need more people?
Nothing to worry. The Japs
will think we are scared if more people go.
Right.
Wait for me.
Hsiao-Wei, please take care of Hsiao Hong.
Ting-En!
I can speak Japanese, let me help you!
Let's go!
They are going together. It will be alright now.
General, Master Fumio left for Shanghai early this morning.
Stubborn old man!
If he doesn't cooperate, he is the enemy of the military.
Send the news to Tokyo!
General, should we cancel the
challenge with the Jingwu School?
No. We don't have to rely on the Kokuryo Clan anymore.
I will handle Jingwu myself.
Both of you are here. Excellent!
Mr. Huo, I have good news for you.
We found the Murderer.
Come in!
He was bribed...
...to put the poison in your father's food.
He is a traitor.
No need to be afraid. Take him out.
Nobody is allowed to enter without my order.
Everybody out!
SICK MAN OF ASIA
If you lose, I will give this sign to you.
It's my personal hand-writing.
Catch!
Can you walk?
Don't move!
General.
Mr. Ambassador, General Fujita is dead.
Don't move or we will shoot!
Take it easy!
- You ok?
- Yes.
You are only the police for the Brittish territory.
I am not here as a policeman,
I am here as a Chinese!
Chen and Huo will be brought back by us!
What?
You think you can leave here safely?
Don't move!
Just try it, you even will die before me!
Stop this!
Everybody put down your weapons!
I am sure we somehow can solve this peacefully.
Fujita is already dead.
It is not neccessary to sacrifice anymore lives for him.
- Lieutenant!
- Yes!
Take your men out of here.
Mr. Ambassador!
I am the highest official here.
Do you want to disobey my order?
Attention. Fall out!
Mr. Jie...
A Japanese officer has been killed.
I need the murderer for the governmental report.
You must understand that.
Otherwise, the Japanese military won't give up on this.
So, if I don't die, the military will
make use of this to start a war?
In this case, I will sacrifice myself.
Great! You are a real hero!
Back off. Nothing to see here.
Looks like Chen Zhen.
Is he dead?
Why does the police treat the Japs so friendly?
It's not their fault. They are all the same.
They are working together to bully the Chinese.
All they can do is bully the Chinese!
Chen Zhen was a real hero!
He beat all his enemies in the Nijiguchi Area.
It was fantastic!
Too bad he had to die at such a young age.
- What is it?
- Nothing. Keep on talking!
To imagine Cheung was the traitor.
He was so nice.
At least he was of use as Chens replacement body.
5th Senior, were are we heading?
Which part of China would a battle
with Japan take place first?
- Tungshan Province.
- Let's go there then.
English Subtitles by [spannick]
and dRuNkEn@!M*~~
Corrected by SuntUrioN