Production / Tae Won entertainment
Produced by/ Tae Wan Jung
Ji Woo Choi
Jae Wook An
Kyung Young Lee
Hae Jung Yoo
Producer/ Joon Jong Kim
My first love?
Everyone wants a dramatic
love story of their own
Like a woman wanting the child
of the married man
she's having an affair with
or the loyal woman waiting for the man
who's been convicted for life
I wanted a more serious relationship
I want a touching love
where I stay by my love
who suffers from a fatal disease
and I would cry until
my eyes pop out
My first love was too healthy
Director/ Tae Kyoon Kim
Turned out to be
a bummer I mean
It got to a point
his good appetite
and his healthy work-outs
made me sick to my stomach
I couldn't ask him
to drop dead
and so we broke up
Hey, won't the readers
think I am stupid?
What's wrong?
Low battery
Please go on
So we broke up
It was a special relation
Miss Song
What's wrong?
You're not yourself
What?
What happened?
- What?
- Your first love
Did he die?
I told you
We broke up
Ah, right, right
Myjaw hurts...
the whole day...
God, I'm stressed
I hate these kissing scenes
- Kissing is that hard?
- You've never kissed before?
No!
Look at the time!
Everyone get ready
That's my cue...
Were ready to roll
Stand by
Ready!
Okay, Let's shoot!
Retake scene 36
cut 14
Action!
Cut!
What the hell!
Uh, oh!
FIRST KISS
I'm sorry I'm late...
About yesterday...
I'm really sorry...
I just didn't know...
Actually...
- Where, did I put the tickets?
- Yun Hwa!
Ithink...
Let's break up
lam tired of this
I can't take this, any more
Let's just break up!
Entertainment World...
Yes? Uh, huh...
hold, please, I'll put her on
It's for you
Cherry Hong's manager
He says he wont
do the interview
Hello? This is Yun Hwa
Mr. Kim... huh?
Why?
the deadline is this weekend
and I need the interview this week
If you don‘t want to do it forget it
Why are you screaming?
Okay forget it!
Who gives a darn
if that star of yours
wears gold lace panties
to bed, big deal!
Stupid, jerks!
Forget it!
Yun Hwa
What did you say to Mr. Kim?
he's really ticked
He said Cherry Hong has
no time, so I said forget it
Forget it?!
You said what?
Who's going to fill the cover?
If you don't want your nudes
on the cover, get the interview
Got it?!
Geez!
Well, he's the boss!
Knock, first
Want them to know about us?
Chicken!
Why did you sleep with me
in the first place?
What's wrong now?
Fire that Yun Hwa!
I can't stand it any longer
I told you
don't let her bother you
I can't, she's driving me crazy!
She's better now since
she hooked herself with a man
Don't make me laugh!
And what's this?
Oh, that...
It's just...
It's good for my image, 'family-man'
Okay, Okay...
Is that better?
What's wrong?
You love the 'Melodrama' section
Do you have something
that'll make me sleep?
Would you do business like that?
My panties, it's flying away
My husband's finally talking
Answer the phone!
Uh... hello?
Hello, this is the research facility
Oh, you stupid...
Oh geez...
But you're not stupid enough
to starve yourself!
Look at these stacked dishes...
My sister had to have you
Come here... Look
What is so hard?
That's not hard, huh?
You don't have to do anything
just close your eyes
Here, let me show you
Please, leave me alone
Why do you hate her so much?
She drives me nuts!
I'll move her desk... alright?
I want her gone, permanently!
Oh, you're bad, Be nice!
She's not so bad
You want to sleep with her, too?
How did I get mixed up with you
Really!
Why do I waste my time with you?
You know why
I'm you're ticket to success!
That's disgusting!
So what, you're a newlywed?
Jealous?
Get yourself a new wife!
Just you wait
it'll be over in 3 months
Kyong-hee
You girls like to bite
when you kiss?
Your bride must've been hungry
Hey, Yun Hwa
Come in here!
You have your own
work hours, now?
You've been late 27 times
this month alone!
Wake up!
I ought to fire you!
Say hello to each other
This is our newcomer
And that's our senior reporter
and a bad role model
Hello, I'm Kyung-Hyun Han
at your service
I'm sorry, your name is...
Save that for later
How's Cherry Hong's
interview going?
Did you phone Mr. Kim?
No
I warned you
Your first assignment...
Take her nudes
What?
Get out
Either her nudes or
Cherry's pictures and interview
Get going!
Hello!
I'm Kyung-Hyun Han and I'm new
lam very happy to be here
I'd like to introduce myself...
- Hey!
- Yes?
Yun Hwa!
Get to Apkujung now!
Mr. Kim said he'll do the interview
with Cherry during her lunch
30 minutes only!
Send someone else
Don't push it!
What happened
to our angel Yun Hwa?
Someone please tell me
Me, me!
- Don't just stand there
- Yes
- Move it
- Oh, yes
Yun Hwa?
It's really a pleasure
working with you
Is something wrong?
Don't call me by my name
I just thought...
you looked my age
I thought we...
Miss Song!
Where are you going?
- To the subway...
- Umm... I have a car...
- What car?
- My car
So?
Huh? No, it's just...
You like to read?
The ending is pretty bad
They both die
without meeting each other
Pretty sad, and it still sells
Miss Song, you don't wear
any makeup?
Cherry, be nice
Otherwise, she's
not going to mention
your gold lace panty...
- Why did you become an actress?
- 'Cuz it's fun
You'll have time later for pictures
Don't let me bother you
I don't like to take posed shots
Over here
This is so natural
Please continue your interview
Go on
- What kind of actress do you want to be?
- A popular one
Cherry, You have a shoot at 2:00
So hurry up with the interview
When do I get to eat?
- Grab a burger on the way!
- But I, want noodles, too
Who's your favorite male actor?
Don't care for any...
Order noodles for me
and have them deliver right away
or I'm not moving
You want trouble
with that producer, again?
Come on hurry up
Can I use your phone?
Noodle House?
Give me your
biggest bowl of noodles!
You want dumplings
on the side?
Why'd you do that?
Don't let these clowns bother you
And what makes you the expert?
Well, I just thought...
Miss Song!
The subway is this way
Miss Song, it's me
Kyung-Hyun
Where are you?
Are you working
on the interview article?
Please call me, I'll be waiting
She won't call back today
Thank you
I'm, Kyong-hee Park
I think we can be good friends, later
What's wrong with now?
Uh, alright
I like your style!
Not so bad yourself
Your outfit and stocking's are nice
Good color coordination
I bet you're photogenic
Really?
But the make-up...
Try red wine lipstick
Red wine?
Really?
Can I ask you something?
- Anything
- About Miss Song...
What about her?
Is she always like that
or is she just in a bad mood?
She's always like that
A sorry case
she's hysterical all the time...
it's gotten worse
ever since she broke up with her boyfriend
She's a downer...
You know what she did while
she had a boyfriend?
She must have written
volumes in her diary
That's primitive
She's that old-fashioned?
- You're telling me
- Bet that relationship...
- didn't last
- Right
Obviously
Really, red wine?
What?
My lips, you said red wine
From a professional view
Try to tone down
Go with more earthy tones
that icy look is out
Really?
A good study case
Huh?
Miss!
Wake up
Go home and sleep
Ouch, ouch
Easy, easy
Okay, here
What are you doing?
We're looking at his sore tongue
I spent the night making out
with my wife
Show-off!
- Ouch
- Oh, biting kisses
What do you mean?
Where the woman
bites your tongue
She bit you all night
and you don't know why?
That boring thing, all night?
Want to know something
much better?
What's that?
Is it hot?
Air Cleaning Kiss
You breathe into
each other's mouth
Breath in and out!
Then the air becomes warm and
your body is hot for each other
Whoa!
Try that in the back of the bus
You'll think you are flying!
You're a pro
Women won't leave me alone
It's Kyung-Hyun...
where are you
What are you going to do
with the interview?
Second message...
Miss Song, it's Kyung-Hyun...
Third message...
Forth message...
Miss Song, it's Kyung-Hyun...
Fifth message...
Miss Song...
You have no more messages
He's cute
How old is he?
Three years old
This is crap, do it over!
Dinner, anyone?
Deadline's tomorrow
who's got time for dinner?
Treat us next time...
What you'll do for a lousy salary
How about a welcoming party
for the rookie?
Whatever...
Hey, where's Yun Hwa?
I paged her countless times
but she won't answer
Where the hell is she?
I don't know
Kyung-Hyun...
Anyways, be nice to her
Huh? Why me?
Just do it
Don't ask questions!
How're the pictures?
Work of art!
Did you strip her?
Huh?
Get the pictures
and the article on my desk
Got it?
What?
I can't get in touch with her...
smack, smack, Kiss!
- You must like children?
- Kiss, Kiss
He's so adorable
Kiss, smack
Smack, smack, Kiss!
Get ready
Good, that's it...
You're back
Who's that?
He's cute!
Forget it!
He's gay
That's 'cuz he's never been
with a woman like me!
How's the new work?
How's my uncle treating you?
The office sucks
and your uncle is a bully
This is the thanks I get
Couldn't you find better work for me?
I mean I took thisjob
because you asked
but if the other company calls
I'm gonna take it without question
I'm an artist!
Let's try a different pose
Give me a powerful look
Hey, are you busy?
Now, what?
All we had was time
But, we didn't spend that time loving
Just like a one-eyed fish
that's how I want to live
If I'm alone
all alone...
I hope to be saved quickly with the will
to survive like the one-eyed fish
to have the will
to love 'til the end...
What do you think?
That's corny
You don't like it?
that get these stupid books
They don't even help!
Not like that
Come on, fix it
- Brighter!
- I don't get you
I told you to take
computer lessons
Save your speech for another day
This isn't work for you
Then you do it!
Okay, okay
I'm sorry
Who's she?
Another actress?
No
If she's not an actress
why's her picture here?
I work with her and I happened to have
some extra film so I used it
No, you can't fool me
I sense love and emotion
in these shots
Shut-up! Let's finish it
so I can get some sleep
You're the devil
I feed you
give you my house, a job
I even gave you my car
- And you want me to work all night?
- She's really not calling
If you turn in the work
already edited like this
what am I supposed to do?
I didn't mean to...
Don't try to explain
Hey, Yun Hwa!
What're you...
You call this crap, writing?
Who told you to write it like this!
Did I say you could do that?
If you can't take it then get out!
That goes for all of you
He doesn't appreciate great work
Where were you?
What's this?
Resignation?
Just for that?
Are you making a statement?
It's not that at all
Good vocabulary but too long
But, sir...
Next time when you write an article
use your own words, understand?
If I didn't throw that fit
they'll think I was favoring you
and who knows
what they'll do
Here, go and mail this
But I quit...
Don't just stand there
get going
But I want to quit
Can you tell me
you won't regret it?
See, you can't!
Hurry, get going!
Miss Kim's at school
She's got finals
Next time just page once
Don't tie up my pager
Kyung-Hyun, go out
and get a cake, now
Why?
Today's Yun Hwa's birthday
No, not again
She's been down lately
Let's cheer her up
- Kyu ng-Hyu n
- Yes
You be the clown today
and cheer her up...
Sure, I've done this
many times in school
What?
I mean, Okay
She's coming!
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday dear, Yun Hwa
Go on, blow out the candles
Blow the candles
Blow out the candles!
Happy Birthday!
Miss Song, I'm sorry, but...
Miss Song
Oh that idiot
Now, she'll be pissed for a year
Miss Song
Wait, I'm sorry, really
I didn't mean to upset you, it's just
We always use to do this
to our friends...
Miss Song
I even got a present ready...
Entertainment World...
Yes... alright
- How's my column?
- It's out already?
Yun Hwa's came out
Good job, everyone
The boss is ecstatically happy
with this month's issue
Hey, you two!
Cherry called to thank you
for the pretty column
And I'm stormed with calls from
other actors asking for their interviews
Can you beat that
they're asking to be interviewed
Really, that many calls?
Just a figure of speech
Personally, I'm not happy
that you did it on your own
- But, good work
- Sir, phone call
It's Bobae's manager
See, what'd I tell you
Yes, this is Entertainment World...
You haven't spoken to me
for a whole week
Did you know?
Have you ever thought about
wearing contact lenses?
From a professional view
your glasses don't look good
on your face
I'm not trying to pick up on her
Take off your glasses
Please, just once
Please, Let me just see
Look, you don't even have
bad eyes
Stop it!
That temper!
If that skinny Cherry
could look that good
Boebae's gonna look great, right?
Right?
Let's hurry and get it over with
You're just gonna take pictures?
What about the interview?
Interview her
Why do you want to act?
I like living the lives
of different people
What do you do
in your spare time?
When I have time
I read, or see a movie
and try to learn new stuff
Are you seeing anyone?
This isn't right...
Are you interviewing her
or harassing her?
Bobae, smile, please...
That's good
Which poetry will go
with this one?
My picture is going to be
a work of art, again
Art
How about you writing
the article this time?
What?
I heard you're a good writer
The boss said that
you're the best writer
in the office
Why are you
looking at me like that?
Why are you so nosy?
Who, me?
He's told me, I never asked
Let me see...
Here, take it
Your birthday present
Just waited for the right moment
Oh gee... You just take it
and say 'thank you'
Then I could say, 'my pleasure'
See?
Here
Miss Song!
The subway is this way
- We're back
- Kyung-Hyun!
- Right on time!
- Why?
I've got a story
and I need some shots
Huh?
She doesn't want me
She wants a healthy bachelor
Hurry, we're gonna be late
A guy called while you were out...
When?
About an hour ago...
Did he leave a name?
No, he just hung up
So, I don't know
Honey, it's done
Okay
Delicious!
Did you cancel the noodles?
The line's been busy
I'll do it when he delivers
Did you order noodles?
We want to cancel
I hate customers like you
Noodles, anyone?
Scene Six, two, one!
Cut!
That was good, but...
The psychological aspect
is pretty weak
It's weak, that's what! mean
Think of Immanuel Kant
all psychology!
You know, Kant!
Get it?
- Change the pasta!
- Hi
Let's start the interview
I heard this movie is different from
the conventional
romantic comedies of Korea
Something new and
innovative and with a statement
- Can you explain?
- You're only too kind
I wanted to be more honest
Romantic comedies used to
sell like hot cakes
For a short time
Men, women
comedy, romance
They don't work anymore
Shakespeare, Kant
Amuro Namie
- They're all gone
- Oh, yes...
Men, women, desires, sex...
The point here is that fashion
is deceptive
and the future of mankind is grim
We need to advance
That's why we need noodles
The dialectical
materialism of paradigm
God!
Calling themselves 'artists'
- Let's go!
- Go where?
Let's take a breather
We're gonna be caught in traffic
Let's get something to eat first
Let's go out for some ribs
- sashimi
- Yun Hwa, are you coming?
Let's go out for drinks
Not today
My wife...
I'll go with you
Did Kyong-hee leave, already?
She didn't come back
Aren't you going home?
Yes
What's wrong?
You're usually the first one out
- Hello?
- Hello? Miss Yun Hwa Song?
Speaking
Who is this?
- It's the video store
- So?
Can you return the videos, please?
You called me for that?
Well, no one's answering
at your home!
Must I call you morning
and night for the videos?
Did you call this afternoon, too?
Sure did! I'm not gonna stop
until I get my tapes
Stop being so stupid
and pathetic!
Stupid!
Aren't you eating?
Huh? Yeah
Indigestion from lunch
You seem to like fish!
Yes
Do you have a girlfriend?
Used to have many
but got rid of them all
Why?
Kind of got boring
and just wasn't for me
You talk like an expert
I've become quite the expert
Ask me anything about love
You're that sure?
You said it
See those two behind us?
They'll break up in a month
and the next table over
those four are all hot
for the other's partners
You can tell by their eyes
Poor souls...
One more side order, please!
And a bottle of Soju
Where is she?
What happened to our date?
She thinks this is fun
Fool
you have a wife and beautiful kids
what are you doing?
Whew!
I think you've had enough
I'm fine
It's only my 10th glass
Ifl don't have one more
I'll be fine
You know how many shots
it takes you to get drunk?
Sure
Have you ever slept with a girl?
Huh?
Where did that come from?
Yes or a no
Someone as old as me?
Who, which one?
Someone I was in love with...
You slept with her
because you loved her?
Sleepy?
Why're you giving me
the first degree?
Tell me, I'd understand
Well...
I feel that... someone...
You know so many ups and downs...
Do we need to discuss this?
Go on
Your glass is empty
Here...
Cheers!
Go on
Well, in the end it's the same thing
The problem involves morals
but the way people are nowadays
you just don't know what to think
What are you smirking at, fool!
Move your legs...
Now the head
Wake up!
Where's your house?
You!
You're no better
I've been in love too
But...
I like you
You're under my spell now
Nobody can get out of that
You're mine now
Hold on
Hello?
Is this Kyong-hee's phone?
Yes, it is. Who is it?
- I'm just...
- Wait is this...
I'm hot
Please, now...
Wait...
Now...
Hurry...
Honey...
What?
You look beautiful tonight
Just tonight?
Here, eat
No, you go ahead, dear
We haven't done this since
I was pregnant with our youngest
That long, really?
Thank you, dear
For what?
For remembering me...
Why don't you order some more
Oh my legs...
What am I doing here?
- What are you doing?
- I know, I know
I don't have time for games
Games?
Hurry, move your car!
Can't you see how far
I've pushed my car?
- Let me get some air
- I don't care how far you pushed it
Just pay and move your car!
Gosh
Hold your horses
I'll move!
See, it's here!
You're no friend!
How could you drive around on
an empty tank and no cash?
What were you thinking?
And look at you!
Shit happens...
I'll pay you back, all of it
No lipstick?
Didn't you like the color
I got for you?
I picked it
What kind of man are you?
Leaving a girl there alone!
Sleep well?
What do you take me for?
Good morning
Did you get a good night rest?
You have a call
- I'll take it in my room
- Yes
Kyong-hee, see me later
During dinner, she drank
a little too much and...
Good work!
Don't worry
You can afford it
It's our tradition for the newcomer
to buy lunch
Who's worried
Enjoy yourselves
Kyung Hyun!
That 'air cleaning' is fantastic
Have you tried it?
My dry cleaner doesn't
have that service
It's a kiss
What are you saying?
I thought it about it all night
But as a husband...
and father
I must stay with my family
I'm sorry
But this is best for both of us
Do you really mean it?
Yes
I mean it
Okay, have it your way
Aren't you mad?
Upset? For what?
Anything more?
Are you really okay?
I told you before
To let me know and you did
Gee, that was easy
- Coffee, anyone? Bring change?
- Yes
Uh, I...
Did you say something?
What is it?
You can tell me
Here...