Good morning, Bastian.
I had another dream, Dad, about Mom.
I understand, son.
But we have to get on with things, right?
Bastian, we each have responsibilities.
We can't let Mom's death...
...be an excuse
for not getting the job done, right?
Yes.
Son, it's time you and I had a talk.
I got a call from your math teacher
yesterday.
She says that you were...
...drawing horses in your math book.
Unicorns. They were unicorns.
What?
Nothing.
She also says you don't
do your homework on time.
I'm very disappointed you didn't even
try out for the swimming team.
As to those riding lessons you wanted...
You say you love horses
but you're afraid to get on a real one.
You're old enough to get your head down
out of the clouds and...
...and keep both feet on the ground.
Okay.
Stop daydreaming.
Start facing your problems. Okay?
There, I think we've had a nice talk.
We should have more.
Have a good day, son.
Don't be late for school again.
But, yesterday I wasn't.
Hey, it's the weirdo.
Weirdo, you got any cash for us today?
Let's get him!
You can't get away.
You're dead, chicken!
We'll get you!
- Where's your money?
- I don't have any!
No money? Mamma's boy is holding out.
If you ain't got money,
you go in the garbage.
Maybe the chicken can lay an egg in there.
Who said you could get out of the garbage?
Get back in there.
Not again.
Not again!
Where are you going, wimp?
- He went that way.
- Which way?
Get out of here! I don't like kids.
Are you still here? Didn't you hear me?
You're hiding, aren't you?
The video arcade is down the street.
Here we just sell small rectangular objects.
They're called books.
They require effort and make no beeps.
On your way.
I know books. I have 186 of them at home.
Comic books.
No, I've read Treasure Island...
...The Last of the Mohicans, Wizard of Oz...
...Lord of the Rings,
20,000 Leagues Under the Sea, Tarzan.
Who are you running away from?
Some kids from school.
Why?
They threw me in the garbage.
Why not punch them in the nose?
I don't know.
What's that book about?
Oh, this is something special.
Well, what is it?
Look.
Your books are safe.
While you're reading them...
...you get to become
Tarzan or Robinson Crusoe.
But that's what I like about them.
But afterwards you get to be
a little boy again.
What do you mean?
Listen.
Have you ever been...
...Captain Nemo...
...trapped inside your submarine
while the giant squid is attacking you?
Yes.
Weren't you afraid you couldn't escape?
But it's only a story.
That's what I'm talking about.
The ones you read...
...are safe.
And that one isn't?
Don't worry about it.
But you just said it was...
Forget about it.
This book is not for you.
Koreander's.
What can I do for you?
They run maybe 300, 370...
It will take me a couple of a weeks.
Math test. Oh, no!
"It was midnight in the Howling Forest.
"The wind whistled
through the tops of the ancient trees.
"Suddenly, something enormous...
"...crashed and rumbled
through the eerie woods."
What's that?
Excuse me...
...but would it be all right
if I joined you this evening?
You see, I've been traveling all day.
Now I see why you picked this camp.
A delicious looking limestone rock!
Nice bouquet.
Must be a real vintage year.
Yes, you're right.
Those delicious rocks
are the reason we've camped here.
- Is he a nutcase?
- No, he's a Rock Biter.
A Rock Biter!
- Sorry.
- Poor baby.
Pardon me.
That was limestone, with a dash of quartz.
Very tasty.
Where I come from in the North,
we us to have exquisite gourmet rocks.
Only now...
...now...
...they're all gone.
I know how it happened.
I swear it wasn't me.
I think I know what it was. Tell us more.
Near my home,
there used to be a beautiful lake...
...but then...
...then it was gone.
Did the lake dry up?
No. It just wasn't there anymore.
Nothing was there anymore.
Not even a dried-up lake.
A hole?
A hole would be something.
No, it was Nothing.
And it got bigger and bigger.
First, there was no lake anymore.
And then, finally, no rocks.
If he keeps stuffing his face like that,
soon there won't be any rocks here either.
Night Hob, this could be serious!
Rock Biter...
...what you told us is also happening
where I live in the West.
A strange sort of Nothing
is destroying everything.
Yes. We Night Hobs live in the South
and it's there, too.
So, it's not just in our part of Fantasia?
Maybe, it's already everywhere.
Maybe our whole land is in danger.
What can we do?
My people are sending me to
the Ivory Tower, to the Empress, for help.
We are on the same...
We are on the same mission.
After all, if the Empress can't save us...
...who could?
Then why are we all just sitting here...
...instead of taking off for the Ivory Tower?
What are we waiting for?
Yes. Let's go now.
Wake up!
Come on, old girl.
We can't just hang around here.
Wake up! Ready for takeoff.
Oh, stupid bat!
We can't wait for a snail. Can I carry you?
Don't worry. It's a racing snail.
But we can't even wait for a racing snail.
It really is a racing snail.
Nobody gives a hoot
about me and my stupid bat.
Maybe I'll take a few of these
yummy gourmet rocks, for the road...
The Nothing!
Look!
There it is!
The heart of Fantasia!
I never knew it was that beautiful.
Stay awake!
I told you to stay awake.
The home of the Empress.
She's our only hope.
Friends, I know why you are all here.
The Nothing...
...is destroying our world.
I also know that you...
...have come to beseech...
...the Empress for help.
But I have terrible news.
The Empress herself
has become deathly ill.
There seems to be a mysterious link
between her illness and the Nothing.
She's dying.
So, she cannot save us.
But there just might be one chance.
The Plains People
who hunt the purple buffalo...
...have among them a great warrior.
He alone has a chance
to fight the Nothing and save us.
He is our only hope.
His name is Atreyu.
Atreyu.
"The Empress had already
sent for the great warrior.
"When he finally appeared
on the terrace of the Ivory Tower...
"...he carried with him
the hopes of all Fantasia."
A little boy!
I'm sorry, but this is not
the time nor place for children.
You must leave.
If you don't want me here,
you shouldn't have sent for me.
Is he a nutcase?
It was not you we sent for.
We wanted Atreyu.
I am Atreyu.
Not Atreyu the Child.
Atreyu the Warrior.
I am the only Atreyu of the Plains People.
But I'll be happy to go back
to hunting the purple buffalo.
Wait!
Come back, please.
If you really are the Atreyu we sent for...
...you would be willing to go on a quest?
Yes, of course.
What kind of a quest?
To find a cure for the Empress...
...and to save our world.
No one can give you any advice
except this:
You must go alone.
You must leave all your weapons behind.
It will be very dangerous.
Any chance of success?
I do not know.
But if you fail...
...the Empress will surely die...
...and our whole world will be destroyed.
When do I begin?
Now. And you must hurry, Atreyu.
The Nothing grows stronger every day.
Take this.
The Auryn!
He who wears the Auryn
speaks for the Empress.
It will guide and protect you.
Wake up.
Farewell, Atreyu.
Take care.
"At the same time...
"...elsewhere in Fantasia,
a Creature of Darkness...
"...also began his quest."
"They had been traveling aimlessly
for almost a week...
"...but they could not find a cure
for the Empress.
"Neither Atreyu nor his horse, Artax,
had the vaguest suspicion...
"...that the Creature of Darkness,
the Gmork...
"...was already tracking them down."
What is it, Artax?
Is it time to go already?
I know what you want. It's time to eat.
Good idea.
No, it's a great idea!
No, not too much.
We still have a long way to go.
"Atreyu and Artax had searched
the Silver Mountains...
"...the Desert of Shattered Hopes
and the Crystal Towers...
"...without success.
"And so, there was only one chance left.
"To find Morla, the Ancient One...
"...the wisest being in Fantasia...
"...whose home was the Shell Mountain...
"...somewhere in the deadly
Swamps of Sadness."
Come on, boy. Come on.
That's it.
It's okay.
"Everyone knew that
whoever let the sadness overtake him...
"...would sink into the swamp."
You're doing fine, Artax.
Come on, Artax.
What's the matter?
What's wrong?
Come on, boy.
What's the matter?
I understand.
It's too difficult for you.
Artax, you're sinking! Come on!
Turn around! You have to! Now!
Fight against the sadness.
Artax, please.
Don't let the sadness
of the swamps get to you.
You have to try. You have to care.
For me.
You're my friend. I love you.
Artax, stupid horse.
You got to move or you'll die.
Move. Please.
I won't give up. Don't quit.
Artax!
The Shell Mountain.
Morla, the Ancient One.
Morla.
But that's impossible.
They couldn't have heard me.
Are you Morla, the Ancient One?
Not that it matters, but yes.
Please help me. Do you recognize this?
Well...
...we haven't seen...
...the Auryn in a long time.
We?
Is there someone else here, too?
We haven't spoken to anyone else...
...for thousands of years.
So we started talking...
...to ourselves.
Morla, I bring terrible news.
Did you know the Empress is ill?
Not that it matters, but yes.
Actually, we don't care.
If I don't save her, she'll die.
There's a terrible Nothing
sweeping over the land.
Don't you care?
We don't even care...
...whether or not we care.
Do you have a cold?
No. We're allergic...
...to youth.
You know how to help the Empress,
don't you?
Not that it matters...
...but yes.
If you don't tell me and the Nothing
keeps coming, you'll die too. Both of you.
Die?
That, at least, would be something.
Please help me.
You said you knew the answer.
We're tired of sneezing.
Go away! Nothing matters.
That's not true.
If it didn't matter to you, you could tell me.
Clever boy.
Tell me, please.
We don't know.
But you can ask...
...the Southern Oracle.
How can I get there?
You can't.
It's 10,000 miles away.
But that's so far.
That's right.
Forget it.
Give up.
No.
Atreyu wouldn't quit now.
Oh, boy!
"After days and nights
of unconsciousness...
"...Atreyu slowly opened his eyes...
"...and found himself
in strange surroundings.
"He was clean and
his wounds were dressed."
Leaving so soon?
I was just going to...
I have to...
- I was trying to...
- Sneak away?
Yes. I mean, no.
I like children.
For breakfast?
Never. I'm a luck dragon.
My name is Falkor.
- And my name is...
- Atreyu. And you're on a quest.
How did you know that?
You were unconscious.
You talked in your sleep.
Could you get around...
...and scratch behind my right ear?
I can never quite reach it.
Here?
That's so good.
Thank you.
So, little fellow, you're on your way
to the Southern Oracle?
Yes. But it's hopeless.
- It's too far away.
- I wouldn't necessarily say that.
You know how to get there?
Sure. It's right around the corner.
How did all this happen?
With luck.
You brought me the entire 10,000 miles?
No. Only 9,891...
...as the dragon flies.
You're amazing.
Having a luck dragon with you
is the only way to go on a quest.
Things will work out fine.
Never give up and good luck will find you.
It's good to have a friend again.
You have more than one.
Look.
Get out of my light, wench.
You're disturbing my scientific work.
You and your scientific work.
What the boy needs now
is one of my potions.
The boy will need
my scientific advice much more.
But not until he's well.
Get back to your own corner, Engy.
I'm always finding you in my place.
He's well.
Now it's my turn with him.
No, you don't!
I'll decide when he's well.
It's your turn when I say it is.
Well, little man, still in pain?
It's all right.
I like that.
The patient telling the doctor it's all right.
It has to hurt if it's to heal.
Drink that.
Good?
That's my bat-wing broth.
There's eye of newt in there,
tree mold, old lizard brains...
...scales from a rancid sea serpent.
Just where did you
and your dragon come from?
What are you on to?
Anything of interest
to the scientific community?
My name is Atreyu.
I came to find the Southern Oracle.
Here we go again.
You've come to the right place, my boy.
I am somewhat of an expert
on the Southern Oracle.
"It is my scientific specialty."
It is my scientific specialty.
Why don't you sit down
and be quiet for once?
You keep quiet, wench.
It's my turn.
My name is Engywook.
She's Urgl. Ever heard of me?
I don't think so.
You don't move in scientific circles.
I am the expert on the Southern Oracle.
You've come to the right place.
There's no fool like an old fool.
Wait! Stay here.
The observatory. To the winch, wench.
Come on, lazybones!
Can't you go any faster?
I've been studying
the Southern Oracle for years.
Some day I'll publish my book:
A Century of Studying the Southern Oracle,
by Professor Engywook.
Volume I: The Early Years.
Have you ever been
to the Southern Oracle?
What do you think?
I work scientifically.
Look.
Is that the Southern Oracle?
No. It's the first of the two gates
you must pass through...
...before you reach the Southern Oracle...
...and get me the final information
for my book.
Of course, most people...
...never get that far.
Why?
The Sphinxes' eyes...
...stay closed until someone
who does not feel his own worth...
...tries to pass by.
Here comes one that looks fancy.
Let's see what he really thinks of himself.
Go on, scaredy-cat!
It's my turn. Let me see. I'm the scientist.
He's going on.
I think he'll make it.
The Sphinxes' eyes, are they open or shut?
Let me see.
They're shut.
The eyes are opening!
Did he make it? Did he?
Fancy armor doesn't help.
The Sphinxes can see
straight into your heart.
Listen.
Next time let me see what happens.
It's my telescope.
I'm going to try.
Don't go yet.
I haven't told you about the next gate.
It's even worse than this one.
He'll never make it.
Don't start to doubt yourself. Be confident.
Be confident.
Run, Atreyu!
Run! Now!
He made it.
He made it!
You could use a dose of juicy vitamins, too.
Atreyu made it through the Sphinx gate.
- I always said he could do it.
- Good.
But that's no reason
to fall out of the basket again.
I knew he'd be safe.
Nonsense. You don't understand anything.
The worst one is coming up.
Next is the Magic Mirror Gate.
Atreyu must face his true self.
So what? That won't be too hard for him.
That's what everyone thinks.
But kind people find that they are cruel.
Brave men discover
they are really cowards.
Confronted with their true selves...
...most men run away screaming.
Now, this is going too far.
What if they...
...really do know about me in Fantasia?
The Southern Oracle?
Do not be afraid.
We will not harm you.
We have been waiting for you a long time.
Are you the Southern Oracle?
Yes, we are.
Then you must know
what can save Fantasia.
Yes, we do.
Well, what is it? I have to know!
The Empress...
...needs...
...a new name.
A new name? That's all?
But that's easy.
I can give her any name she wants.
No one from Fantasia...
...can do it.
Only a human child...
...can give her this new name.
A human child? Where can I find one?
You can only find one...
...beyond the boundaries of Fantasia.
If you want to save our world...
...you must hurry.
We don't know...
...how much longer
we can withstand the Nothing.
Falkor!
Hurry, Falkor! The Nothing's everywhere.
Don't worry.
We'll reach the boundaries of Fantasia.
- Do you know where they are?
- I have no idea.
Then how do we find a human child?
With luck.
Faster, Falkor! We have to hurry.
All right, hang on tight.
What a shame they don't ask me.
My mother...
...she had such a wonderful name.
"On and on they flew
until they reached the Sea of Possibilities...
"...where they could go no further."
Look, Atreyu. The Nothing.
Atreyu.
Falkor!
Where are you?
Atreyu! Where are you?
They look like big...
...good, strong hands, don't they?
I always thought that's what they were.
My little friends.
The little man with his racing snail...
...the Night Hob...
...even the stupid bat.
I couldn't hold on to them.
The Nothing...
...pulled them right out of my hands.
I failed.
No, you didn't fail. I'm the one who failed.
I was the one chosen to stop the Nothing.
But I lost the Auryn.
I can't find my luck dragon.
So I won't be able to get beyond
the boundaries of Fantasia.
Listen.
The Nothing...
...will be here any minute.
I will just sit here...
...and let it take me away, too.
They look...
...like good...
...strong...
...hands, don't they?
Morla?
Artax!
If you come any closer...
...I will rip you to shreds.
Who are you?
I am Gmork.
And you, whoever you are...
...can have the honor
of being my last victim.
I will not die easily.
I am a warrior.
Brave warrior.
Then fight the Nothing.
I can't. I can't get beyond
the boundaries of Fantasia.
What's so funny?
Fantasia has no boundaries.
That's not true.
- You're lying.
- Foolish boy.
Don't you know anything about Fantasia?
It's the world of human fantasy.
Every part...
...every creature...
...is a piece of the dreams
and hopes of mankind.
Therefore...
...it has no boundaries.
Why is Fantasia dying then?
Because people have begun
to lose their hopes...
...and forget their dreams.
So the Nothing grows stronger.
What is the Nothing?
It's the emptiness that's left.
It is like a despair...
...destroying this world.
And I have been trying to help it.
But why?
Because people who have no hopes...
...are easy to control.
And whoever has the control...
...has the power.
Who are you, really?
I am the servant...
...of the power behind the Nothing.
I was sent to kill the only one...
...who could have stopped the Nothing.
I lost him in the Swamps of Sadness.
His name...
...was Atreyu.
If we're about to die anyway,
I'd rather die fighting.
Come for me, Gmork. I am Atreyu!
Falkor!
Atreyu!
"That was the end of Fantasia.
"Only a few fragments of this once...
"...rich and beautiful world
had been left by the Nothing."
Good old Falkor.
- Can you see anything? Anything at all?
- No.
All the land is gone.
I know. And all because I failed.
You tried.
Could the Ivory Tower still be standing?
Let's hope so, Atreyu. Let's hope so.
Let the Auryn guide you.
If the Ivory Tower still stands,
take us there.
The Ivory Tower!
The Empress.
Go on.
Why do you look so sad?
I have failed you, Empress.
You haven't.
You brought him with you.
Who?
The earthling child.
The one...
...who can save us all.
You knew about the earthling child?
Of course. I knew everything.
My horse died, I nearly drowned.
I just barely got away from the Nothing.
For what? To find out
what you already knew?
It was the only way
to get in touch with an earthling.
But I didn't get in touch with an earthling!
Yes, you did.
He has suffered with you.
He went through everything
you went through.
And now, he has come here...
...with you.
He is very close, listening...
...to every word we say.
What?
Where is he?
If he's so close, why doesn't he arrive?
He doesn't realize
he's already part of The Neverending Story.
The Neverending Story?
What's that?
Just as he is sharing all your adventures...
...others are sharing his.
They were with him...
...when he hid from the boys
in the bookstore.
But that's impossible!
They were with him
when he took the book...
...with the Auryn symbol on the cover...
...in which he's reading his own story...
...right now.
I can't believe it.
They can't be talking about me.
What if he doesn't appear?
Then our world will disappear.
And so will I.
How could he let that happen?
He doesn't understand that he's the one
with the power to stop it.
He simply can't imagine...
...that one little boy
could be that important.
Is it really me?
Maybe he doesn't know what to do.
What do I have to do?
He has to give me a new name.
He's already chosen it.
He just has to call it out.
But it's only a story. It's not real.
It's only a story.
Atreyu, no!
Bastian!
Why don't you do
what you dream, Bastian?
But I can't.
I must keep my feet on the ground.
Call my name.
Bastian, please!
Save us!
All right! I'll do it!
I'll save you. I will do what I dream.
Why is it so dark?
In the beginning, it is always dark.
What is that?
One grain of sand.
It is all that remains of my vast empire.
Fantasia has totally disappeared?
Yes.
Then everything's been in vain.
No, it hasn't.
Fantasia can arise anew...
...from your dreams and wishes.
How?
Open your hand.
What are you going to wish for?
I don't know.
Then there will be no Fantasia anymore.
How many wishes do I get?
As many as you want.
And the more wishes you make...
...the more magnificent
Fantasia will become.
Really?
Try it.
Then my first wish is...
Falkor, it's even more beautiful
than I thought!
- Like it?
- Falkor, it's wonderful.
Falkor, it's like the Nothing never was.
Atreyu and Artax!
What would you like to wish for next?
Look, there they are.
It's a monster!
Get them, Falkor!
Let's see how you like it, chickens.
Down here.
We're going to get you!
Bastian made many other wishes...
...and had many other
amazing adventures...
...before he finally returned
to the ordinary world.
But that's another story.