100% honesty, right?
Shouldn't you at least tell me
why you're mad?
Why'd you tell Sung-hae
you don't have a girlfriend?
Meet 1000 guys
and they're all the same
One and the same
- Do you have a boyfriend?
- Excuse me?
Boyfriend, do you have one?
Yes, but we fought yesterday
Really? Why?
My love for him is like
a watermelon
but his love for me
is like an apple
So that's why we fought
Still, I think apples taste better
Hee-jin's sooo lucky
- What's that?
- Ji-suk sent it express
Is it Ji-suk's?
We didn't even do it
Then Jun-ho?
Did you tell Jun-ho?
Are you crazy?
He's so simple,
I just know what he's gonna say
Why am I always like this?
Let's go to the hospital.
And then forget about it
It's really easy for
you to say
I'm not saying it lightly
The more you think,
the harder it is
Think of it as
stepping on poop
What? Poop?
Is getting pregnant
stepping on poop?
Why are you getting mad at me?
It's what you said!
Stepping on poop!
So my baby's poop?
Is that a thing to say
to a pregnant friend?
Hee-jin Lee!
What is your problem?
That's not what I meant
Sure it wasn't
Then again,
you never had a boyfriend
What would you know
about being pregnant?
Well, as I live and breathe!
So you're pretty,
you get all the guys!
What am I? A dog?
It's bad enough
I don't have a guy!
On days you bring
a guy home
I can't even go inside
Do I have anywhere to go?
So I end up
at a game room
Did you ever think of me
sitting there killing time?
Did you?
Asters mean
'Don't be mad anymore' Ji-suk
Have you heard
from Hee-jin yet?
Not yet
What did I tell you?
A cake's better than flowers
If I only knew, I would have
made a real pretty cake for you
Too bad
Shall we go to a movie tomorrow?
Hee-jin
It's Hee-jin
She wants to go to
a movie tomorrow
Flowers are okay, too
We're done for today
I always came at this time
You want me back, right?
Yoo-jung called today
Said to go see you
If you want
we can hook up again
Jun-ho Kim,
that's your problem!
Just cause some
silly girls dig you
it doesn't mean
all women want you
You know
what that's called?
An error from
over-generalizing
Are you okay?
If I had an ounce of love left for you
I wouldn't have left you!
How do you want it?
Erase my name
from your phone
You're only 10 minutes
late today
Did you get the tickets?
Let's go
I'm going home tomorrow
I took some time off
To Pusan?
You're still mad, aren't you?
Okay
when I read Sung-hae's mail,
I got a little excited
So when she asked me,
I told her
I didn't have a girlfriend
I know we promised to
be 100% honest
but I felt so bad
I couldn't tell you
It's okay, dude
Thanks
I have something to tell you too
What?
Ji-suk, I'm pregnant
What Ji-suk Kang likes
Reading, taking walks, thinking for
l-o-o-o-ng periods of time
What Hee-jin Lee likes
Computer games, shopping
changing hairstyles
We are so different
Why are we going out?
Let's just forget our deal
We can't say 'Let's break up'
before the month is up
I've been wanting to
see the ocean
We'll go together Pusan
What about your paper route?
I told them to suspend
the papers tomorrow
Is that supposed to be a joke?
Why, was it bad?
Why are you so good to me?
Why? Because
you're my girlfriend
Of course,
I'm good to you
How many days
are left in our month?
Ji-suk Kang!
Hee-jin!
What are you two doing?
Are you guys going out?
8 across, 7 letters
made by Orson Wells
director of Citizen Kane
B&W film based on one of
Shakespeare's 4 great tragedies
- Othello
- Correct
9 down, 13 letters
road movie with Susan Sarandon
and Geena Davis
- Thelma & Louise
- Correct
What exactly is a road movie?
- Oh, that's when
- The characters leave home on a trip
and the movie is about
what happens
I'm a film major after all!
Do you know the director
Wim Wenders?
I've heard of him but
I haven't seen any of his films
He's my favorite director.
He makes a lot of road movies
Ji-suk, see any of his films?
I like Wenders' films too
Yeah? Did you see
Paris, Texas?
I liked it so much
I saw it twice
Ry Cooder's music
was really good too
Yeah, nothing beats
an acoustic guitar
to show the desolate,
lonely desert
Ji-suk, you and I think alike
Wenders really likes
Polaroid cameras
So I bought one too
I'll take your picture
so strike a pose you two
One two three
This is the one and
only copy of this picture
Who wants it?
I get on the bus across the street.
What about you two?
- The subway
- Oh, yeah?
Well, it's good-bye then.
Get home safe
Remember, the concert's
tomorrow at 7
You both gotta come! Okay?
Saving 100 boy names
on your phone
Why do you want to do that?
When I first started at the salon
I worked from morning to night
with hardly any days off
I had no time to eat or poop
That's how I got to
where I am today
One day, I looked around
and no one was there
I felt like crap
I had no name
to save on my phone
After you fill it up,
what are you going to do?
I don't know.
Maybe change phones?
I used to come here a lot
when I was in school
Yo, goodie goodie,
you ever hang out here?
It seems like
yesterday but now
I'm already 25
I'm not ready to
be an adult yet
You can take your time
By the time we die
people will being living till 125
So we still have
100 years to go
Ah, so that's why
you're so relaxed
I want to live like
I'm taking a walk
feeling every moment 100%
I want to run like
in a 100m dash
We really have
nothing in common
I remember the day
we biked in the rain
Shall we go get wet?
You're the one who said
it's acid rain
Let's go!
You want something
warm to drink?
Oh no, that's okay
Are you okay?
Read to me
Where'd you read up to?
Just read from the beginning
Okay, here I go
It was the summer that
men first walked on the moon
I was very young back then
but I did not believe
there would ever be a future
I wanted to live dangerously
to push myself as far as I could go
and when I got there
You have gook in your eyes
Hee-jin
When are you gonna to go
to the hospital?
As soon as I get to Seoul
Let's go together
Meet you at 2 tomorrow
at Pusan Station
Mi-hee told me that
in junior high,
Sung-hae liked you too
Inside never-ending memories
All that I have left disappears
I won't hide anymore
What I have left is no more
I'm sorry, Doctor
No matter how much time goes by
When morning comes,
everything's gone with the night
No matter how much time goes by
In another beginning
in another beginning
Like a dream,
you come back to me
Do you play 'Fortress?'
No, isn't it a waste to spend
our youth on stuff like that?
I started cause
Hee-jin taught me
It's actually fun!
I haven't won yet but
It's probably cause
you're a pacifist
You didn't go home yesterday,
did you?
Home?
You're dressed
in the same clothes
That means you were
with Hee-jin
Why'd you come alone?
Did you guys
have a love spat?
We didn't fight but
we couldn't come together
Hee-jin's going through
a rough time
I want to be there for her
but it's kind of hard
Hey! Then you have to go to her!
What are you doing here?
I knew it when you said
you were solo
'I only know books
I know nothing of love'
You have that written
on your forehead
Sung-hae!
I liked you back in school
So I hesitated
before coming tonight
If we become
more than friends
then it'll be harder
on Hee-jin
I liked you back
in school too
That's why I e-mailed you
I was crazy curious
to see how you turned out
When we met up again,
you turned out better than I thought
I thought of
going out with you
But seeing you here
as my friend, I like this better
Mom, aren't you done yet?
Are you just looking
at the pictures?
My goodness,
you're a fast reader
How can tea taste
so good?
I put a little
hiroppon in the tea
So second hubby
sleeps out a lot, huh?
Don't even go there
He's gambling away
somewhere again
Poor mom,
no luck with men
First hubby dies early,
the second sleeps out
every day
It just seems, I should be
looking for number 3
- Mom?
- Yeah?
- Mom
- What?
Mom, um
Do you know
what a road movie is?
What are you talking about
You don't, huh?
It's when the characters
go on a trip
A road movie's about
what happens during the trip
- You mean like Whale Hunting?
- Right
That's a road movie
The last movie your dad and I
watched together at the theater
was Whale Hunting
Hello. I'm Hee-jin's friend,
Ji-suk Kang
Yes Um,
Hee-jin's in Pusan
She's not back yet?
No. She's staying
a few more days
Oh, I see. Thank you
Good-bye
Ji-suk's gone
I'll take a day off.
Let's go to the hospital on Saturday
I'm going to have it
Are you crazy?
What's crazy about
a pregnant woman having her baby?
Oh, no
Don't look at me
so pathetically
I hate myself, too
Why is life so hard?
What's with you?
What are you doing?
It tastes better this way
Ji-suk, man,
stop being a sap
Forget her and come to
Australia with me!
- Australia?
- Yeah
Why would I go there?
I'm going for a year,
on that working holiday thing
What about
the Public Servant Exam?
That's right,
I was gonna do that
But a few days ago,
I read a book,
50 Things You Must Do In Your 20s
One of the things
is to poop
in as many countries
as possible
Wow! As soon as
I read that
I got shivers up
and down my legs
So you're going all the way
to Australia to take a dump?
Come with me?
Nah, I'll just poop
in my home
Hey, what about Yae-eun?
Yae-eun
Didn't I tell you?
- What?
- We broke up a few days ago
Why?
She and I finally
went to a motel
We're just about to do it
when she confesses
She's not a virgin
She already did it
with a guy at her church
Eun-chul,
is that all you're made of?
You broke up
cause she's not a virgin?
- It's not that
- Then what, bastard!
All that time,
pretending to be a virgin
'lf you love me,
if you love me, you'll wait'
All that was crap!
It gives me the chills, man
Really, it creeps me out
You still have a book out
Oh?
You have Moon Palace, right?
Oh, yes
It's quite overdue
Please have it back
by tomorrow
Yes, thank you
Did I keep it too long?
I feel like I learned a lot
from you in a month
No, I learned a lot more
I'm at the second bullet level
at 'Fortress'
I didn't get anything
for today
White freesias mean
'I'm lucky to have
such a good friend like you'
So we're breaking up?
The last condition
After a month,
we part ways grandly!
Hee-jin,
remember what you said?
In a month,
I'd be in love with you
To then say I love you
- Hee-jin
- Ji-suk
I'm gonna have it
I'm gonna have the baby
Hee-jin,
is everything
so easy for you?
Why are you being
so dumb?
You know I'm pretty simple
I like it, I do it
The end
As a quarter of
my life was ending
she came looking for me
Maybe
as the second quarter of her life
was beginning
I went looking for her
It's hard to choose.
I'll come back
Whatever you choose,
timing's most important
I'll give you a good deal
Come see me
Thanks
Hey! You and I need to talk
- I have nothing to say to you
- You sure about that?
Let go!
I said I have no feelings
for you!
Where are we going?
Stop the car!
Stop the car now!
Are you crazy?
Why do you keep
messing my life?
Those should be my words!
What about
the kid in your belly?
Forget talk,
let's just get rid of it
I'll pay for it
Just grab a date
You seem to
have the wrong idea
It's not yours
What?
It's not your baby
so stop messing with my life.
Stay out my life
But why doesn't it fit?
Because my waist is 38
- What? You said 34
- Well, we were dating and
- You lied to me?
- Aw Wait!
Try this one. And this
- Hmm, it's good. Yummy
- I'm a good cook, right?
- Oh, I actually used that ladle
- That's okay. Why not?
- I'm embarrassed, that's all
- Embarrassed
- You get embarrassed?
- Sure
How's the rice?
The rice?
- Very, very good
- Great
Now, we just need the curry
- It needs to boil down more
- It does? Okay
It's raining so let's hurry!
Hee-jin!
What happened?
Taxi!
Ji-suk! Ji-suk!
Hee-jin
Can you hear me?
Are you okay?
Does it hurt?
Still, he's a good kid
He went away cause
mommy's having a hard time
When you're ready
to be a mommy
when you have someone
who really loves you
he'll be back
Are you okay?
You were here all night
How's Hee-jin?
Good
I'm sorry but Hee-jin's not up
to seeing anyone right now
Please take good care of her
Don't worry
Um, are you Ji-suk?
Yes. And you are?
I'm taking over for Man-ho
- Man-ho quit his job?
- Yes
Man-ho asked me
to give you this
I have to go now
- Thanks
- Good-bye
Hey, Mr. Writer!
I got a job at a hotel
It's in the country
so I had to leave right away
Though we met on the route
a proper good-bye
is still in order
No one enjoyed my cooking
more than you
You know about
good cooking
so I'm sure
you're a good writer
Take care
Hee-jin, which color?
This one's smart
and this one's sexy
The sexy one, please
Okay
But isn't too much?
You said you might go
all the way with him tonight, right?
Right. Why hide my sexiness?
No word from Ji-suk yet?
You said his name
so give me 10 bucks
Here, here
What do you think?
Really sexy, huh?
Why, don't you like the color?
- The color's not the problem
- It'll look prettier on me
This color's a beauty!
Have a good trip
Yeah, I'll send a pretty postcard
from Australia
Ji-suk
Yeah?
I thought about it a lot
Why did Yae-eun came
clean about not
being a virgin at that
crucial moment?
Probably cause
she really loved me
But what can I do?
The boat's already sailed
Well, see ya
Bon voyage, buddy
Ooh, f-e-e-I that sun!
I love the sky!
It's never boring
When I don't want to see it,
I don't have to
And when I want to,
I can see it from anywhere
You really do love me,
don't you?
You smile at
whatever I say!
You want it cut short?
Uh, no
I want to color it
It's not my first time
so it'll sting less, right?
We'll it might sting more and
be more painful than the first time
Yeah?
Well
Let's try again, you and me