Miss! Miss!
- Come over!
- What is it?
Very hot!...
- It is her, kidding with you.
- It's not me!
What are you up to, kid?
1,2,3... 1,2,3... 1,2,3... 3!
You're lost!
Stop nagging and go get us something.
You two are evil.
Your girl is very accommodating.
So are you, old devil!
Hey, are you serious this time.
Don't say nonsense.
I knew it as soon as I saw you two.
Hey, can you help me sell this motorbike?
Are you sure? Such a pity.
Well, if I had some money.
I can go into 2nd hand car business.
What? Do you want to go straight?
Nine out of ten remain that way.
It won't be that easy, Ah Dee!
Those kids came to bother me last night.
Want me to retire.
Says this street is theirs.
They don't know
what they're getting into.
Don't disappoint me.
Don't come back if you fail.
I've been here for over ten years.
I'm not afraid of them!
Forty dollars!
- Sorry to bother you.
- Thank you!
This is rough area.
Aren't you afraid being alone?
I am meeting someone.
I know, you're meeting Wah Dee.
Just a piece of advice.
Do you think he is serious?
He's nice so you won't identify him.
You are being used.
What are you saying?
None of your business!
What is it?
That case is not finished yet.
I'll get you someday.
Are you finished.
- Have some tea, Miss Yuen!
- Thanks.
It's not Yuen, it's Miss Huen!
It's O.K., call me JoJo.
- It's English.
- I know.
Can you stop singing?
What should I call them?
Just call us moms.
What do you mean 'Moms'?
What's wrong with it?
We raised him since he was very small.
Please take my little present.
Ask him whether we are his moms or not.
Stop talking and open the door.
Oh, I forgot to leave a note outside.
Hey, man, no.
- I'm not available today
- Then what about the other two?
All 3 busy, go home and get your mom.
Something urgent came up,
I can't take you home.
I'll call you.
Keep quiet! Let me see what it is.
- Let me see!
- Give it back to me.
You shouldn't do it, you're our guest.
That's OK, I like doing it.
Wah Dee seldom brings friends home.
His mom was cruel, jumping from the roof.
"Plop", and there she was on the ground.
Left this little burden behind.
Where's his father?
Even his mother doesn't know who he is.
Does he have any other relatives?
I hear he has a grandfather in Macau?
What is it Ah Sang?
Why are you so late Miss?
- Sir and Madam just got off the plane.
- Really?
- Daddy.
- Good girl.
I'm so happy to see you, my good girl.
I missed you very much.
Come over here!
These are
Canadian Universities' brochures.
I've chosen two,
you pick out one yourself.
We're going up now.
Don't come back so late next time.
Come up, Ah Sang!
- Has he returned the call?
- Not yet!
Try again then.
Big Brother!
Wah Dee, why are you this late?
How is Godfather?
He's having his operation.
Bastard, let's get rid of them.
Don't get so excited, Trumpet?
We don't even know how Godfather is yet.
If Godfather dies,
I don't care if he's young or old.
I'll kill them.
How is it?
I've told them to go to the restaurant.
I asked you to call him earlier.
What are you saying?
Go wait whether or not there's any news.
Everyone waits at the restaurant, get it?
I'm sorry, we did all we can.
Fuck, let's all go!
- Mummy!
- Why aren't you sleeping?
I'm waiting for my friend's call
from U.S.
- Is it important?
- No!
Go to sleep then if it is not important.
Alright!
Are you trying to scare me?
I've been around much longer than you.
I'm telling you, old man.
I talk to you just because you're old.
Talk to my Big Brother
if you're unhappy.
Go ask your Big Brother Trumpet.
Who was around first.
He wants to have fun.
I'm telling you.
I don't want to see you here tomorrow.
Understand? Let's go!
Rotten kid, trying to scare me.
Would I be scared? Damn it?
Are you O.K., Bo? Where is Wah Dee?
How do I know where he is.
You said he was hurt in a fight,
you must know where he is.
Leave him alone,
he'll always be like that.
Please tell me where he is?
You two are impossible.
Can you tell me if Wah Dee is here?
He's upstairs!
Thank you!
Are you his grandfather?
Grandfather!
I won't be able to give you anything.
Come over here!
Will you regret?
"Striding together in the sky."
"Put away strife and conflicts."
"My heart is full of romance."
"Laughter between us,
is the best moment."
"Never mind if it is real or false,
though wrong, we'll never part."
"Free to be naive again."
"Hope we will always stay close."
"I can finally be with you."
"I can see clearly all over."
"Being ordinary is so good."
"Laughter between us,
is the best moment."
"Never mind if it is real or false,
though wrong, we'll never part."
"Free to be naive again."
"Hope we will always stay close."
Come, today is Mid-Autumn festival.
Let's have a piece of moon-cake.
I don't like moon-cakes.
Grandfather, sit down and eat something.
Yes, grandfather, eat something first.
With Wah Dee leaving this time,
I don't know when he'll be back.
These two pillows are for you.
Thank you!
There's this other one.
Wow, it's very beautiful.
This needs one too.
You scare me.
Kid, you are enjoying yourself.
Oblivious to what's around you.
Her parents have filed
kidnapping charges.
I'm telling you now.
Go back to H.K. right away
and you'll be O.K.
Also, your Big Brother is having trouble.
Daddy, Mummy!
Come with me!
Wait for me!
Get on!
Ah Sang!
- Go home, Miss!
- Let me go!
C.I.D.!
Her mother filed the charges, not me.
Ah Sang, get her into the car.
- Wah Dee!
- Go!
Let him go, why are you detaining him?
Wah Dee...
What? This is none of my business!
It's her mother who's charging you.
And there's the jewel-factory robbery.
Eventually I'll get you.
Hey! Chan Sir!
Yes, let the kid go!
What do you mean let him go?
What exactly does she want?
She's not laying any charges.
We'll discuss it in my room.
JoJo is just a kid, it's not up to her.
I'll take her to Canada for schooling.
I don't want so much trouble.
Don't worry, Shirley.
It'll be alright, we're school mates.
Thanks a lot, John!
Why is it like that Chan Sir?
She's canceling the charges.
You're canceling the charges.
What, close the case,
we haven't got him yet.
I'm taking you off Miss Huen's case.
It's obvious she's protecting him.
You don't want any part of this?
We had a deal, I get your daughter back.
And she'll be our witness, what now?
Are you playing games?
Shut up, what are you saying?
- John, I'm busy, I've got to leave.
- Good!
- When you're free, visit me in Canada.
- Yes, I will!
Let's go, JoJo.
Still no clues to the jewel robbery case.
Is this the way you work.
Don't just stand there, get going!
Yes, Sir!
Here's a good spot for you.
What do you expect for a few dollars?
- What is it?
- None of your business!
- Hey, come on, what is it?
- Nothing!
Run, I'll see where you can go?
- What's wrong with your face?
- Nothing
I got beaten up.
Don't make trouble, Ah Dee!
- Don't stop me.
- Leave it, don't make any trouble.
You've been bullied and we do nothing.
Your Big Brother and the others
are looking for you.
There's enough money for everyone.
I can still earn my living.
Look at you, you're degrading me.
If you got the guts,
we'll get even with them.
If I've got the guts I'll be Big Brother.
Not just doing cars.
You think I'm happy with this?
Depending on the gang.
So you have the guts.
But you're still stabbed and on the run.
Brother Seven is in trouble now.
I haven't interfered in the past 2 years.
But Trumpet won't leave me alone.
What does he want?
He wants to be the head.
Will the men accept him?
Brother Seven is better
whichever way you see it.
Shut up!
Trumpet is like a mad dog now.
You've all stepped on his toe before.
I don't want fighting between ourselves.
Trumpet wants to meet us at AA.
This is it, who does Trumpet think he is.
I've been around much longer than him.
Brother Seven, I'll support you tomorrow.
Go get me a pack of cigarette.
Brother Seven?
Go on.
- Brother Seven!
- Rambo!
The police want Trumpet
to hand over someone.
Big Brother, I'll always listen to you.
I'll go up tomorrow!
It's because of him
you're going to Canada.
Later on, you'll know you were right.
Bring more clothes, it's snowing there.
If not enough,
we'll buy some more over there.
- I want to get off the car.
- No, you cannot.
We just have you.
Even if we're wrong,
it's for your good.
- I want to get off the car.
- No, you cannot.
Stop the car! Stop the car!
- JoJo!
- Miss!
JoJo! You cannot go.
I'll go to Canada with you,
but tonight I have to see him.
Don't drink too much, have some food.
What is it? Are you drunk?
Ah Bo, get me a hot towel, quick!
Where are you going?
To the toilet!
I'll go with you.
No need!
How was the money today?
Go...
Let it go, Ah Dee!
Don't beat him up anymore!
Have a good look.
This street is Rambo's, is that clear!
This is the last time I can help you.
Are you alright?
I am alright, you can go.
I'm leaving, I'm leaving.
He's in a bad mood, I'm leaving.
- Go!
- I'm leaving!
Take care of him, he drank too much!
I've washed all your clothes.
Hang them up if it's sunny tomorrow.
I bought some food, it's in the fridge.
The lighter is behind the flowerpot.
I don't like my place so tidy.
I don't like it so clean...
I'm in the triad.
Closed.
Trumpet, what do you want?
A snake cannot be without a head.
The top spot is mine.
You can retire to care for your pets.
If your men want to, they can follow me.
If not, just disappear.
But I want him.
Trumpet, you're asking too much.
Ah Sang, sit down!
Trumpet, even if I am willing to go.
Will my men listen to you.
So there's nothing else to discuss.
We're all family...
Go to die.
Killing me will not help you much,
Trumpet.
Run!
Wah Dee, get in the car!
Fuck, I knew Trumpet would do this.
Good thing I was smart.
Don't panic, Wah Dee!
I'm not Rambo if I do not get him back.
Lung Bui, it's Rambo.
I am looking for him too.
He's not in Wan Chai for sure.
What's Snake's phone and call number?
You call him up for me right away.
Say I want to find Trumpet.
Let me know when you find him.
I have to leave for Canada. Take care.
No regrets in loving you. JoJo.
Get someone to fix the kitchen freezer.
Get in the car first, JoJo!
Cut off this branch, it's a bit long.
Get someone to paint the outer wall.
Also, change the water tank on the roof.
If the piping needs to be changed,
do them.
"Made the decision, no regrets."
"Don't ask why it is."
"I don't care even if it's wrong."
"My fate is still unclear."
"Unable to tell between
reality and ideals."
"We were never apart."
"Life is short, no regrets spent with you."
"Shuttling between the sky and the shores."
"Remembering a scattering
and fading sight."
"Don't forget my true affections."
"Understand my loss of freedom."
"A moment of romance is enough."
"Without a word, please forgive me."
"Enduring to the end alone."
"I want to ask why is love so short."
"Trapped in sadness."
"Life is short, no regrets spent with you."
"Shuttling between the sky and the shores."
"Remembering a scattering
and fading sight."
"Don't forget my true affections."
"Life is short, no regrets spent with you."
"Shuttling between the sky and the shores."
"Remembering a scattering
and fading sight."
"Don't forget my true affections."
Station 161.
Password.
Rambo says Trumpet is at Happy Sauna.
Asks you to go at once.
Thank you!
JoJo, whatever you wish for us.
Pray to God.
Wah Dee!
Wah Dee! Wah Dee!
Wah Dee, come over!
He should be out soon.
He has two men with him, I'm not scared.
I'm not scared,
I want to kill the bastard.
How are you?
Are you alright?
It's nothing!
I'm O.K.!
"Forgive me for being silent."
"Life is still with you."
"You have searched for the lost sounds."
"The day has set and gone."
"We all hope to keep youth with us."
"Missing you. I can hear sighs
for you in my dreams."
"If I cannot spend my life with you."
"It's not because I do not want to."
"I've told you how I feel inside."
"Like we're in different worlds."
"We long for what is past."
"Life is short.
To enter into where you left off."
"Just a glimpse."
"Let the flames of love forever burn."
"Youth please return."
"To keep me company."
"If I cannot spend my life with you."
"It's not because I do not want to."
"I've told you how I feel inside."
"Like we're in different worlds."
"We long for what is past."
"Life is short.
To enter into where you left off."
I killed Trumpet, I did it.
"Just a glimpse."
"Let the flames of love forever burn."
"Youth please return."
"To keep me company."
"If I cannot spend my life with you."
"It's not because I do not want to."
"I've told you how I feel inside."
"Like we're in different worlds."
"We long for what is past."
"Life is short.
To enter into where you left off."