Stop
Good
Boss, bring me some good wine
Ok...
Wine is coming
So windy
Master, please drink wine
Thirteen cold-blood eagleScare
the ghosts and gods
You want to treacherous plot
Master Chu
You are "Big Dagger" Hon-Chung
You are "Old Eagle" of thirteen
cold-blood eagles, aren't you?
If I know you intrude this matter
We will go immediately
For your killing, raping and robbing
The court offered money
If I let you go, how can I get
the money?
Uncle Yi
Ok... "Little Dagger"
Don't fool around. Calculate it quick
Fire-Eagle
Whip-Eagle
Chain-Eagle
His looks is all ruined, how can
we get money
Big and Little Bewitchment
- Rob the corpses, quick
- Yes
Hey
What
What are you doing?
I'm accosting men to go to bed
Are you interested?
You better stay here
Don't snatch my business again
He hasn't died yet. How can you say
that I snatch your
The better one can snatch the business
Three thousands
Five thousands
There are eight thousands
Sister, if you can catch "Old Eagle"
We can make a hundred thousands
Uncle Yi, try your best
Lady, I don't mean to philander you
Please forgive me
I don't care you mean it or not
You've taken the benefit.
I must marry you
Fung Lady. Don't get cold
I don't take the clothes.
I must marry you
Marry me. Hey
Uncle Yi
Don't call me Uncle
Everybody has gone
Hey, call me Brother Yi in the public
Not Uncle Yi
Brother Yi. Fung Lady and Fung Ling
Snatched away all the corpses
I know it
It's a small amount. Forget it
We have to rush to the city
There is a big business waiting for us
Powerful Eagle
Correct
This money is for brothers
Thank you
Sergeant Ling, I want to ask you
some questions
I will tell whatever I know
They are Han's brothers
They always catch thieves for money
But we snatched away all the corpses
Why don't they chase it back?
It must be something wrong
- Go and buy some new clothes
- Ok
They go to city for big business
What kind of business
Oh
Please come back
Thank you, thank you
Sister, why do they go to city
Don't ask. Let me ask you first
Do you like Hon-Lam?
That Guy is so stupid
How do I know?
I think that two guys
must die in our hands, right
Last month on eighth
Nine Tails Fox secretly entered here
at midnight
He stole my best treasure and
a lot of money
I don't care about the money
But when my couriers saw him
he got mad
And killed my folks forty-one persons
Also killed my only daughter Cindy
after raping
My poor Cindy was only thirteen
years old
I would lie to spend all money
For catching "Nine Tails Fox"
I will revenge in front of my
daughter's tomb
Are you so sure that this guy
is "Nine Tails Fox"?
Nine Tails Fox must leave a fox tail
After he committed a crime
Everybody thinks that
his lightness work is very good
Also he is good in designing traps
And feat of arms
He is a slicked guy, and he has
many places to stay
It takes at least a month to find him
I know he is in "Chu's family town"
The distance will take about seven days
I have prepared swift horses for
both of you
They will bring you there in five days
And the price is...
One million, are you satisfied?
You are right. The head of
Nine Tails Fox
costs this price
First give you three hundred thousand
first
If you have caught him, seven days later
We'll meet in "Choi Sun Inn" of
Chung Ka Hau
I will give you the balance
Ok. Keep your promise
We will start immediately
I return these to you
We better leave this place
If "Four Gods of Death" come
there will be trouble
You better go, they caught "Big
and Little Bewitchment"
That will hold them for few days
They don't kill people these days
Are they interested in women?
No, they trained themselves in evil work
They are never interested in women
But they have caught
Big and Little Bewitchment
They just want to revenge
for "Thirteen Cold Blood Eagles"
I think they are in
"Death Men Woods" tonight
after killing Big and Little Bewitchment
Uncle Yi, how is it
They will come out
We have to rush before the sunset
These two women always snatch
our business
And Always get us trouble
Somebody cut their heats for us
That is good
Then we...
Don't expect me to help them
Let's glory the "Gods of Deaths"
No dirt, no dust
These guys are so strange
The guy in the front is
"Fight until Die"
The one next to him is "Must Die"
The one behind the altar
is "Never Die"
The one who is sitting down?
Is "Die will one bout"
Thank you. Uncle Yi
Don't thank me
I thank you for "Big and Little
Bewitchment"
Don't mix up
I just do what my conscience
ask me to do
I will kill people
And you escort the Bewitchment
Move
You are really "Never Die"
Fung Lady, Fung-Ling, we are coming
to help you
They are not "Big and Little
Bewitchment"
They are glamouretts
Good. To hell with glamouretts
Two women paid us
to flirt these four men
They can play whatever they like
It's none of your business
We have been cheated by these
two women again
Sorry for interrupting
That is a misunderstanding, bye
How can you go like this?
He died
This is called "Die with one bout"
Brother...
You knew that he is called
"Die with one bout"
You still slap him, no wonder he die
Sister, what shall we do
I guess
"Four Gods of Death" will hold them
for a whole day
We must catch "Nine Tails Fox"
in "Chu's family town"
Will they be hurt?
Don't worry, you lover won't get hurt
Let's go
"Four Gods of Death" is not as goods
as legend
Legend is always exaggerated
They said that we never miss a dagger
in legend
So what
We always miss
So, that is
One more
You kill him, then, let's eat
Can't he die?
I slap him hard
- How is it
- Ok
Let's eat
Let's go
You can't stop me. It hurts
Don't talk. Let's go
Hey, Don't go
It's good to run fast
Return the hand to me
It's bad to run slow
Don't go, hey
Uncle Yi. Return it to him
It is nothing to do with me
It's the hand holding my buttocks
Return the hand to me
You are bad
I am not bad. It is fun when
we try some more bouts
What do you mean by "no"?
It is on the book
My waist is almost broken.
I don't play anymore
- Hey. Play a little bit more, wife
- I don't play
Hey, hey...
I stole this book
From "Tien Chuk Monk" difficulty
It is called "Yoga"
This work is good for thinking
You don't know that I consider
about you
It's not so good
You stole this garbage
You should learn it from me. See
I stole a good sword.
It's sharp
What kind of sword do you have?
See my "Gold Dragon Dagger"
It's number one dagger
You stupid. My "Flying Phoenix Sword"
is better than yours
Don't say it
My "Gold Dragon Dagger"
must better than your sword
It is the best one. Do you know it?
If you want to fight with me
Then you must lose
and withdraw the battlefield
Shit
Exaggerated. Self concerned. Nonsense
My "Flying Phoenix Sword" can chop
everything
Shit
Look at you
You are not so cantankerous
before I marry you
Oh, you always listen to me
before marriage
And you promise everything
And you treat me as a sucker now,
don't you
Husband, I don't want to
- You listen to me when you love me
- Yes
Ok, let's say "Flying Phoenix Sword"
is better
You are stubborn
If you say "Flying Phoenix Sword"
is good
Stubborn
You kill your husband for a sword
I say the right thing
I say you are crazy
Come
Hey, wife
Wife, where are you
Wife
Bloody Fox
Husband
Don't scare me
Husband, are you alright
You broke my "Flying Phoenix Sword"
It's not my fault
You abuse me
You ask for it. I told you already
I said you was bad
All the bad thing
will return to you
It is impossible that I am bad
You must apologize within 3 seconds
- One
- No
- Two
- It is not my fault
You can't say "Three"
Hey, wife
Hey, lover
Are you kidding, you are so slick
We agreed to count from one to three
It's just nonsense
I lost my wife and my dagger
She has gone
Let me check my record
The record of my wife's disappearance
The first disappearance for one month
in seven years ago
The second disappearance for fifteen
days in five years ago
The third disappearance for seven days
in three years ago
The forth disappearance for three days
in one year ago
The fifth disappearance for one day
in three months ago
Oh, That means she will return
within two hours
Let me read the Scripture in toilet
You come back so early
You have done whole-body beauty.
You are much prettier
And you come to apologize
with someone else
Two women serve a man
I will try my best
Are you "Nine Tails Fox"?
And you've changed your voice as well
You are completely different. I love it
We are satyr-catchers. Our names are
Big and Little Bewitchment
I have known you...
If I know there is a satyr
I will let you know
That is alright. You can go now
But the case happened in Master Lui's
house was beheld
Who is Master Lui? I have not heard
this name
Still not to admit
Go
Still coming
Procuress
Watch
Holy Fox eliminate
If I know it is so easy
I won't spend half day
It waste my time
Hon-Lam. Don't run so quickly
Help me
Not so hard. You might tear
my good trousers
You tore it. I am very sad
Return the hand to me
Hide, hide
I know you are hiding
Don't make noise
Return the hand to me
Come out. Come and fight with me
I "Never Die" means never die
Oh, You are not die yet
Why do you defiance me
Who defiance you
You learn it in a wrong way
Eat well in the future
You've come out
Help
Please release us quickly
It's no use to shout. Nobody can
hear you
I can do whatever I want this time
Bastard, release us
I will come to you
You are screaming so loudly
I come to you first
Hey. Are you mad? Aren't you a man?
Look. She is just a kid
Ok. You come to her
Come to me first, come
Don't shout
I will come to you later. I listen to you
You little beauty. So noisy
I draw a turtle on your head
Hon-Chung
Two more men are coming
Don't let them know that I am here
I know
You can't tell
Hey. You pretend that I am not here
Hey. I call you husband.
Please help me
He is "Never Die"
I can't help myself
Never Die. It's valuables
People would like to see it in exhibition
I don't believe it, let me try
How can "Never Die" die
When I slap him
Hero escorts the beauty
I'm tired. Thank you
Don't come closer
Too strong. Don't give me trouble
Let me take a rest
Hon-Lam, I implicate you
It's none of you business
We will die soon
- Let me ask you something
- Please ask
Do you like me?
I like you very much
It's so glib
He must be afraid glib talking
Hey. Say something glib. Quick
Hey. What do I say?
Anything. I love you. I kiss you
I do it for you
Hon-Chung. Let me say it
I love you. Please hold me
I belong to you
Ok
I come secretly and I go secretly
When I wave my sleeve, it takes away...
Your bra
It's so glib
He is afraid of glib talking
Be quick. Say some more
Ok
Ok, I say
Hon-Chung. Will you love me
in the rest of life?
Will you treat me as a part of
your body?
I do
I would like to eat the food you cook
I can't stand it
I drink your human milk
Not enough. Not enough
Say more exciting one
I can't say it. I am shy
Go on, that's right
I caress you hands
Can't you listen Mandarin?
- Why. Why doesn't he scare it
- How can I say it
Act. Do the action
How to act
I grab
Ok
I really grab it
Grab it. Grab it
Don't come any closer. I really grab it
I grab. I can't grab it
I kiss
I want to know how you "Never Die"
Hey. Sorry Don't be silly
Throw out
It will be more comfortable. That's Ok
Are you alright. Be careful. Ok
Hey
Do you know who I am?
I don't care who you are.
Why do you hit my vital point
Let me tell you
We are "Big and Little Flying Dagger"
- I come to catch you
- Hey, I helped you
You are heartless, you...
Miss Fung
When we were fighting
the content we talked
- What
- That speech is completely
What
- What
- Not true
Not true
Every man is heartless
What we have talked
- Is not true. Is that right
- Yes
Uncle Yi. What do we do with
Nine Tails Fox
Now, you are talking about this
Don't argue. Listen to me
We escort him to Master Lui
And share one million dollars
Do you agree?
Ok, but you can't be slick
Ok
Let's go
It's so strong
Husband, husband
Where is he? He might hide somewhere
for scaring me
So terrible
He might be hurt
Don't worry. I have a replay machine
Why did "Big and Little Bewitchment"
come here?
Bastard. He want rebel me
They are also interested in man.
It made me mad
Why was he caught by "Big and Little
Flying Dagger" and Bewitchment
Old Guy
Why didn't you help my husband?
I am in charge with the scene
I don't care anything else
Absolutely stupid guy
Hey
This chicken is very delicious. Try it
Hey. You can't maltreat my grateful
buddy
You know
We are kind. How can we maltreat you?
Yes
I don't blame you that you hang me
You are sitting here for dinner
- You want to starve me
- Ok
I give it to you
I don't eat chicken tail
I eat chicken leg
You are satyr. You think you are
superior
Don't you want chicken leg?
You two coquettes are accosting
boy friends
I can't stand it
Keep quiet or I cut you tongue
I don't believe it
You sit down first
No need to argue with him
You let him talk to himself
He will stop when he is thirsty
I won't stop
until tomorrow morning
Hon-Lam, when you finish
you go to bed
We have to go to "Choi Sun Inn"
tomorrow morning
Let me tell the truth for you.
You two lusts
You want to catch women when I sleep
I know it, but I don't care
Whores met fancy men this time
I pretend to sleep, then you won't be
embarrassed
Hey, Nine Tails Fox
You don't have to talk so much
We won't let you go
You can sleep
But if I want to urinate at midnight
Will you think that it is raining?
Hon-Lam give me a rope to strangle him
Then it won't rain tonight
Hey...
Boy, don't fool around
You abject, Cad, Cur
Nine Tails Fox, keep quiet
or I bury you.
Sorry
Ok, Let's sleep
Everybody is sleeping. Let me escape
with "special escape method"
Not so painful
Don't go
Fanciful censer
You want to catch me. You are stupid
Don't come any closer
I am poisoned
Hon-Chung
Go way I feel hot
Brother Yi, how about you
- Your face are burning
- So do you
Hold me
I can't stand it. I want to hold you
I can't stand it
I want it.
Hurry
Take away your hand
Hon-Lam. Be hurry
Punch my chest
Hurry, I can't stand it
Didn't you say to punch my chest.
Let me take a rest
Sister
- Hon-Chung. I want it.
- Please come
Virgin boy's urine is a detoxification
of fanciful censer
Virgin boy's urine Hon-Chung
- Sister. You don't make it
- It is coming
Virgin boy's urine Sister
I am hot
What did I do?
We are lucky that you get virgin
It's not mine. It's his
His
So embarrassed
Master Nine Tails Fox
Oldest Lady, how are you
Second Lady, Third Lady, how are you
Bad guy, why are you so late
Forth Lady, I love you
- Master Nine Tails Fox
- Fifth Lady
What kind of wind blow you here?
It doesn't matter
It is not a lie
I want all the ladies except you
My wife keep watching me all days
I can do whatever I want now
Flower in Spring, "Moon in Autumn"
come out
Everybody come
Come, hurry up
This is the only town within hundred
square miles
Unless he walked twenty four hours
Otherwise he will stay here
But if I were he
I must go as far as I could.
I wouldn't stay here
It is right
What will we do?
Let's chase him fifty miles more
- Strange hand
- Why are you here
This hand is very strange
- Of course. It belongs to "Never Die"
- Yes?
It seems to take us to somewhere
Do you think it know "Nine Tails Fox"
where about
- Follow it
- Master Nine Tails Fox, do you feel comfortable
- Good
Do you feel happy?
Good
What
Beauty comes and drinks with you
You cover your face, how do I know
you are beautiful or not
Come, come. Let me see you
I can't stand. My floor
You are bad girl
And the bad boy, treacherous plot me
Don't fight, don't fight
Fanciful censer
Stand firmly
I took you belt
Why don't your trousers loose?
I hit your vital point
And you can steal my belt
Why don't you fall down?
You are a cad. How can you steal
my belt?
Tie him up
Four people, fight with one person
are not heroes
We've never said that we were heroes
World's changed. World's changed
I was the only thief in the past
Now everybody is a thief
I will never use a belt in the future
I want it
What do you want?
No. I don't want it
I know you've smelt fanciful censer
I can't stand it
I got detoxification
Don't push me, don't be hurry
Go in
- I will give you detoxification
- Good
Uncle Yi
What happened. Uncle Yi
Don't say it
Come here
I planned to give her detoxification
But she was so quick
I don't know the reason
And she bit it away
Hon-Lam, you got to be more careful
in the future
And learn more
Uncle Yi can't take care of you anymore
I have no more detoxification
It's so suddenly
- Dinner is ready
- Be quick
There are only buns. Why on dishes
Wait it for a moment. When I got money
I will take you a better restaurant
Sister, let me pick up some flowers
for you
Hey, Feed me. You always look at girls
Why are you here
Eat it
Give you
Hit the satyr harder and harder
- Odd
- Even
Open it
Odd...
Two, four
Six
Eight
It's even
Even. I lose this time
Wife
Can't I eat these flies? The taste is bad
That's good
Ok if you make love with me
Will you throw out if you make love
with me?
Yes. I won't throw out if I eat all the
flies
But I will throw out if I make love
with you
When I marry you...
You said that I was so beautiful
And you don't like me anymore now
Somebody is coming
Sir, Good morning
Sir, what would you like
We want four good rooms
Ok... Ah Ming
Take them to the good rooms
This way, please
Please
Let me drink
Are you crazy?
Wife, I am thirsty
I want to wet my lips
Do you drink wine again?
Don't you remember you bad habits?
You will tell the truth after drinking
You should be careful
Then, I don't drink
Wife, why do these Japanese come
They are malicious
I guess they are Japanese "Yi-Ho"
sorcerers
Yi-Ho sorcerers
They have no point to come here
Boss
Beauty. What do you want?
We want two good rooms
- Ah Ming...
- Yes
Take these girls to good rooms
Ok, this way, please
No need to hurry
- So beautiful
- Yes
Please go upstairs
Be careful
- No need to hurry
- What are you doing
They are "Number One thief Flying cat"
And her sworn sisters
You are so knowledgeable
Do you know this one?
- I know
- You know?
It comes from mystic country in the west
Egypt. This thing is called vampire
Also called "Mummy"
Mummy
That's me. I am "Number One Thief"
I am handsome smart...
A women's adoration
I am Nine Tails Fox
I've never heard this name
What are you holding me?
What
- Waiter
- Yes
We want Two goods rooms, right
Ah-ming, take them to rooms
Four rooms
- Four rooms
- So generous
Take these girls to rooms
They are VIP
You think that Master Lui will pay
for you
He says the foul languages
Do you feel too hot?
How can you talk when you are tied up
like this?
You are smart
I buy you dinner tonight
Thank you
But you can't to go to toilet.
It's a kind of your torture
You are a cad
You can come and see it
Don't sneak
In the quiet city
To see two handsome guys
That's good
Right, thank you for your praise
Waiter. Please take him to room
Ok, Ah-Ming. Take him to room
After our dinner
We have to catch Nine Tails Fox
The we will kill "Big and Little Dagger"
and "Bewitchment"
After dinner
Not only dinner they will drink and
sing as well
Cheer
I think they are treacherous
We should be careful
Do you understand?
Do I look like an idiot?
Yes, really
I know you are stupid
I look like an idiot
I can tell that
They are treacherous by first sight
It's on use to be careful
Let's eat
Shit Shit
He looks down on you
- You look down on me for him
- Yes
You look down on me
No... I didn't
I am full
I can't eat
Open your mouth I don't eat
I am "Western Ace"
I never lose
Who want to challenge me?
There is no fun at all
Who want to lose? Challenge me
Oh, this wine is so strong
They don't take the wine
Are you angry?
Chung
Come and eat first
Come. Don't be angry
Shit
Where have all the champions gone
I am so happy. I feel happy
Come and challenge me
Hey... I don't want anything
I just want to have fun
Oh baby, oh take me baby
You are a cad
Are you happy?
Cad
Do you feel comfortable?
Oh come one baby, light my fire
Good, fantastic
You can go home now
I like it aha...
Bye
Don't worry
He is my old customer. He is a gay
He likes to be maltreated
Since his best friend "Oriental Ace"
left him
He started getting mad every night
Then I will whip him
for comforting him
One more time
Sorry. It's not finished yet
Blow it
Happy birthday, baby
Go to bed
It's Ok
Let's eat. Nothing happened
Excuse me. Excuse
I buy sausage only
Shit
- Chung, he look down on you again
- Shit
Hon-Lam. Take him to room
Hey, feed him some bananas
Then give him some pineapples
- Shit
- Be quick
Oh, shit
Cheer
Shit
Drink it again
Drink some more
No, I am drunk
You can drink. Let's drink
Ok
Cheer
I am drunk
Ok. That's enough
Some girls use this method before
How can you copy it?
What
You are so lascivious
I come to help you
Can't you say something better?
I say it again. You are beautiful,
intelligent,
cute
Good. Hey, wife
They are fighting now
Let's watch it
Good. Good
Don't get mad
You just want to catch the thief
When
did "Yi-Ho" work for city hunter?
Off-duty
The dagger was so fast
It's a sword, not a dagger
Flying cat
You two chicks caught my husband
Your husband is a satyr
Are you are not better than him
Your husband worth a million
You must worth fifty thousands
Caught you
Let's make money for cosmetic
All of you have to die
Japanese dogs, Get away
Wife. Do your best. I support you
Be careful of me
Let me do it
Hon-Lam, be careful. You are not so
strong
Don't worry
I must catch you this time
Wife, you let me down
I fail this time
We are in same situation
The courier of Tak-Chuen General
want to see Old-timer Dicky Lui
This is a place of "East-Frontier"
There is no Old-timer Dicky Lui.
Leave
You have killed all the guards
And don't recognize it
Leave or I will kill you
No
I think you are "Erotomania Man
and Evil Lady" of "Yi Ho"
Tak-Chuen General sent me to help you
Old-timer Dicky Lui's helmet have been
stolen by Nine Tails Fox
There is a letter inside it
The general said
If you can't get it back
We have to try our best to destroy
the letter
So, you send people to Choi-Sun Inn
to catch Nine Tails Fox
It is very stupid
I have arranged everything
Hon-Chung will give him to me
tomorrow
Now you spoilt the plan
I don't care anything about Hon-Chung
We just have to destroy the letter
Even you don't care about the alleging
of treason
The general doesn't want to stay
in China
To be a joke for people
It is good
I know the Kungfu of "Yi-Ho"
is very strong
You can take the letter yourself
To save my time
I can pretend as Master Lui as before
When I get the Nine Tails Fox
and the letter
Then I can tear away my mask
Your virgin course is unbeatable now
Yes
Don't let other people knows
Six person died, and three person
escaped
One person was hurt
One room is four dollars
Five rooms are twenty dollars
You have to live half a year
And one thousand dollars
for keeping secret
Also clearing charge and miscellaneous
charge
That is seven thousand and
eight hundred dollars totally
They have killed so many people
They could kill two
They can save that money if they kill us
Don't kill me, don't kill me
Don't be afraid
We work for the police
We are entitled to kill the robbers
Ok. You can kill the bad guys
But don't kill the good guys
What are you talking about?
They are thieves
They killed many people
in Master Lui's house
They raped and robbed. I got their loots
They said that they are good guys
We just stole the money.
We never killed
He killed Master Lui's daughter
after raping
You really killed and raped
No, wife
I was with you at that night
You knew that I didn't do it
Wait a for a moment
But you went to the toilet alone
What, It just took a few minutes
How could I kill a girl after raping
I am coming to help you
You are a cad
I am so bad
You send me to Omei Mountain
to be a tonsure
But Omei Mountain is so far
I can't ask you to go
Or you can release me, I go there myself
How can you say it?
Do you think he is an idiot?
- I just try it
- Just try it
Chung, I think that the business
There is something wrong
Why did Master Lui ask us
to release them here?
Why didn't he want us to take them back?
Also, when we come here
Japanese want to snatch Nine Tails
Fox as well
Can you explain it?
I look like an idiot. Why do you ask me?
Let's sleep
Chung
Where is our room?
I want a suite
- Uncle Yi
- Not Uncle Yi
Call me brother Yi in front of the girls
Come here
I just pretend it. There are many people
on the top of the room
We pretend to return to room
To see what will happen
Go to bed after urinating
Nonsense
You don't look like idiots
- Why can't you know they are not real
- Yes
Come out, wife, be quick
Let's watch it
Good, good, harder
That's good
Yes
Good
No, let me help them
Don't help them
Be shameful, I must go down
I say no
I can't stand it
If you help them
I divorce with you
You should say it earlier
Who are you?
I was taken the five awards
To win the competition
And got the goodwill of Kungfu fighter
I am Leslie Cheung
This is my wife Anita Mui
Anita Mui
Is something wrong?
Why do you come to this?
Because I had got too many awards
So I retired
I got it
- Don't be afraid
- I am alright
I am here
You just lose. You don't have to kill
yourself
This is the liquid of centipede
No, she is showing us the Japanese
Kungfu
She make herself full of toxic
Then she will use the "kissing course"
You are so clever
I hide... hide
Hide... hide
Is that good?
Sorry, I forgot to tell you
The last award
I got is unbeatable ring
And the penis protector
Is that right
Go away
You can come when you are free
Kissing course
Chung
What, are you alright
You tell me
Big deal
Chung
- Fung
- What
I know I am poisoned. I will die soon
Before I feel painful
You better kill me
No, you are poisoned because of me
I must get the detoxification for you
No, after I die
You can carry someone else.
I can't take care of you anymore
But, on the first, fifteenth
On the second, sixteenth,
third, seventeenth
- forth, eighteenth
- Don't talk anymore
I am not finished
When Ching-Ming, Chung-Yeung
Christmas, New Year
You have to offer me some sacrifice
Also
- you have to take care Hon-Lam for me
- Brother Yi
Forget it, you can call me Uncle Yi
To be more comfortable
Chung
I belong to you forever
Either alive or die
There is a method
He got toxic of "Kissing Course"
He will feel fancy after one hour
When he feel fancy, he will
It is not suitable for children
- We are eighteen years old
- Is that right?
You go to the wood
Yes, go out
Go out. Go out
Don't listen to this, go out
You are under eighteen years old
Don't fool around
You have to make love with
woman nine times
Then, the toxic will be disappeared
And this woman will carry a strange
fetus
- Strange fetus?
- Yes, it will take three days
The baby will be delivered
three days later
That you can cook the strange fetus
and eat it
- Then the toxic will be disappeared
- Really?
Yes, there will be a strange fetus
I am not talking about the strange fetus
I ask if he will completely recover
Wake up...
What a nice hairstyle
Look and you'll see
I have come around
Really
Let's go and neutralize poison
Go and neutralize poison
Luckily I'm not poisoned
Or I'll suffer
By eating ox's penis as nutrition
I am lucky. I got the liquid of centipede
I have been waiting for twenty years
Let's have honeymoon
And fever all night
The moon is so bright
Idiot. You always talk about the moon
The moon is so beautiful
Can you talk something else?
What does my Uncle Yi do
with your sister?
Let's talk about ourselves
He is not so stupid
You are quite naughty
Do you like it?
Yes
What
Don't be afraid
I believe that Hon-Chung and
Fung Lady
won't give us the thieves easily
So I need your help
Old-timer... did you meet an enemy
No, I got caught by my wife
I am convinced
As you're aged already
You should get on well with your wife
Anybody will be jealous
When I am so old
I can't do it
Lend me your chair
Why are you here?
Old-timer
You don't think that you threaten Madam
Then I will be afraid
- Madam released us
- Yes?
They are innocent
That is the fault of the helmet
There is a letter inside Master Lui's
helmet
Let me see
Satyr, how are you
Still coming
That Master Lui
is Dicky Lui of East frontier
He also involve with Japanese
Can't I read?
I am not talking to you.
I am talking to him
Oh, you don't read
- Let me explain it for you
- Don't explain it anymore
Good, Madam
How do you know there is a
letter inside?
You are so stupid
- Don't you know who I am?
- Don't tell them
- Tell them
- No
I let you drink wine
We are the top detective
Pang Ting Hong
Do the right thing
So many people are angry with me
Although I can tell who is good guy
or bad guy
But the court still punish me
To eat shit thirty pounds
And send me to the frontier and
clean the toilet for three years
This is not the worst
They also punish me to marry her
She has married for nine times
She gave birth of child on the
wedding night
But the child had not the buttocks
Enough, don' tell them
The child had not the buttocks
Can you help me please
You were the top detective
Sorry for misunderstanding
Hon-Lam and Fung Ling have gone to...
Come
Hon, I know you have done your work
Congratulation
But you know the bad friends
You released Nine Tails Fox
He is the bad man. It's so pity
So I invited your cousin and Fung Ling
to my place for guest
Please come to my place with
Fung Lady
Nine Tails Fox, Flying Cat
and the loots tomorrow
To be happy together
Dicky Lui
You bastard, you traitor
I must cut off your head
I must behead you and kick it
Husband, why are you so rude?
Sorry, that is because I am so angry
Dicky Lui
kidnapped Hon-Lam and Fung-Ling
- We have to help them
- Yes
Hope you will be succeed
We have something to do, excuse us
- I am so scared
- Sorry
Are you alright
- I am alright wife
I am alright
Hey, sorry
They asked for four persons to go
They are just kidding
Sister
- I almost die
- Don't rock
You are welcomed
Release Hon-Lam and Fung Ling quick
You are reliable
You come with "Nine Tails Fox" and
Flying Cat
I should give you hundreds thousand
dollars
I don't want your money
Give them to us quickly
Let me check everything and take back
the loots
Then I will let you reunite
No, no. Even you throw us
they can kill us as well, stupid
We are just pretending
Don't rock
I brought them here
If you don't release the hostages
I won't give you face
- Stop
- Hon-Lam
See
Are you still alive?
Drunkenness, still alive after soldiering
You come here for rebelling me again
There are evidences. Come to get it
Come
Luckily that I am fast
If that is not take is not taken away.
It's difficult to hold it
You miss it
- Of course, it is hard to find
- Cad
Stab him
Feel fancy
Husband, let him try stronger one
Flying Fox in Snow Mountain
Flying Fox...
Fox and Cat mix-up
Sorry, are you alright?
I am alright. Let's mix-up next time
Fox tail gang
Try harder, wife. I support you
Husband, I succeed
You succeed,
but my tails have been broken
I don't know what to do in the future
Don't worry, I learn a new one
I also learn a new one
Help him first
Ok, I kill all of the people
Be careful
I want all of the people die
Holy Fox pass air
It can kill you
Stink, what's the smell?
Hold it, everybody
Don't be sucked by him
Please keep holding
We succeed
Good, Hon-Lam is good
Hon-Lam, help me quickly
Hon-Lam, I hate you
Good
- What is the matter?
- It hurts
What
Wife, don't scare me
Alright...
Don't be afraid
What kind of pain is it?
The Strange Fetus is being deliver
Strange fetus
I am in hurry
Why does it take so long?
Don't walk or the floor will break
I am very sad
Why does a father have to stand this?
In hurry...
Congratulation, he is a boy
Daddy
He's "Never Die"