Well, seeing you get angry
I think he must be real, Who is he?
I said there's nothing
to talk about
Anyway, good luck, Don't be too
difficult like you are with me
Be nice to him
I'm surprised
Hooking up with boys...
It's not like that!
Aquarius? Sorry, but you'll have
bad luck with boys all month
No way I've got
3 blind dates next week
Really? You know, I'm an expert
on juggling guys
Can't I go there
instead of you?
Why you?
I should go
Stop fighting What's yours?
Let's decide from the sign
I'm a Capricorn
You go! You've got
terrific luck with love
Of course!
- No way! It's the same sign...
- Hey...
Can I see the Zodiac too?
Lucky color - Orange
Lucky icon - Pink heart
Wow, your maid is
really a fantastic cook!
Did you take this picture yourself?
Yes, in Hawaii
I went there as an assistant
making a fashion catalogue
Hmm... not bad
It must be nice to travel
But Hawaii's a little stale
Hawaii is "stale"?
How about Europe, then?
I began to like Hawaii so much
after I visited there
So I studied about it, and now
I am an expert on Hawaii
I even studied
the Hawaiian language
Ohno means delicious
Thank you
is "mahalo"...
You always listen to
this song, don't you?
Yes, I like it
Don't you think the lyrics are
a bit too depressing?
Really? What do they mean?
Well, it's just...
Will Neil and Armstrong become
big like this turtle one day?
Hey, is this brain totally empty?
Hello! Anyone here?
This is a different species from them
Look here! Even where they live
This one lives in the sea but...
Neil & Armstrong live in a fish bowl
You're so ignorant
Then is that why you look ugly?
Because you're so smart?
Now I know why I liked him
a lot from the beginning
Is your father an alien, too?
Before the main shooting
I need to get some
rough cuts first
I'd like to take some pictures here
before rehearsal starts
Shall we?
- Wait a minute please
- Yes
Would you like to try this on?
- Oh, No thanks
- It's okay
You can try it
- Shall we start now?
- Sure
Now, hold this bar, and try this
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
And move your foot like this
One
Two
Three
Four
Repeat
One
Two
Three
Four
Now, shall we try?
Why don't you take
off your glove? It's slippery
Oh, okay, yes, holding the bar
Like this... One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Hey!
Miss! Are you okay?
Mina! Mina!
What happened?
I don't know
Suddenly...
Mina! Are you okay? Mina!
Look at me!
Someone call 911!
Mina! Mina...
Are you okay now?
Where am I?
The hospital?
No, you're at home
Then why is she here?
How can you speak so cruelly?
I came to see if you're okay
Are you going to put me
in the hospital?
She says you don't need to
Don't worry
The hospital is all full anyway
You wouldn't get in even if you begged
This IV is to rehydrate and give you
vitamins, Now go to sleep!
Misuk, why don't you go and work?
Don't stay home because of me
Okay
You can go now too
I'll pull this out after it finishes
Yes, let's leave together
I'll give you a ride
Yun-jung!
You think I'm wrong
for discharging Mina
from hospital like that?
No
The reason I let Mina stay
at home is because
I want to live with her
even if it was
forjust one more day
Mina...
When she was hospitalized
again last year
she cut her wrists
When I got back to her room
after admitting her
her sheets were all red
So...
Don't blame me for not
doing anything for her
Ah, nice
You see?
Isn't it cool and fresh?
- Aren't you cold?
- I'm okay
I feel much better now
I was itching to go out
after staying inside all day
It seems that you enjoy going
out a lot these days?
Hey, why don't you stand up
and push me?
I'm a patient
Right, you stay there
and I'll push you
Weren't you thinking I'd say that?
Stop nagging and push me
- Is this why you gave birth to me?
- Yes
How did you feel wearing
toe shoes today?
It was okay
I think ballet isn't as elegant
as I thought before
It's very hard work
That's why I didn't want
you to do ballet
They say 30% of ballerinas
are in chronic pain
Okay
So don't work too hard
And don't skip any of your medicine
And if you're feeling a little anemic
Boring, stop it
Okay, I'll stop
But please keep pushing me
No
If you push me, I will take you
to Europe next month
Next month?
- What about school?
- You can skip it
That doesn't sound like
what a mother would say
How about going to Hawaii
instead of Europe?
Why? Didn't you want to go to
a ballet performance in Europe?
There's something I want to see
more in Hawaii
Really? Then we could go to Hawaii
It'd be cheaper anyway
You know, I've been thinking
about it and...
I guess we don't want to go
as part of a tour group
Of course not
That's not our style
But it's dangerous for 2 pretty
young women to go by themselves
Especially as my beauty is so
well-known internationally
That's right
And if it's just us, we can't take
pictures of us together
Oh, you're right
Then maybe we should
take someone with us?
As a carrier and bodyguard
As a photographer and tour guide
Can you come with us?
- It would be an honor
- Not you
My pleasure
- It's done, now
- Thank you
You see? I knew
it would be great
That's because my face is pretty
- Now, your turn
- Oh, I'm...
Why don't you have
a seat anyway?
Please make it really pretty
lam a real genius to think of this
Such a great idea
It's the first time for you
to have a manicure, right?
Pedicure, It's for the toes
Give me a break
Whatever it is, this is the
first time for me too
Oh, my lighter!
I finally got it!
Hey, let me use it again
to light a cigarette
No way
Here, I'll light it myself
Where did you get that?
It's my father's
He didn't give it to me actually
Misuk was hiding it and I found it
Was he in the navy?
Yes
What kind of man was he?
We never talk about him
Misuk and I... felt that
we would get too sad
Hey I think I will feel awkward
whenever I go to pee
Why?
Because you'll always see me
Ah!
Cold! Too cold!
You'll end up an alcoholic
if you keep drinking like this
I am Okay, okay
You seem worried
No
Why would I be worried when
I have such a pretty daughter?
My Mina... Will you live well
without me?
Why? Do you want to
marry again?
Will you?
Worry about yourself
I'll be fine
Yes, you'll be fine without me
Well... do you like the
downstairs dude?
I don't know! What kind of
silly question is that?
Tell me I'll help you
It's not like that
Then what is it?
It's just... He's fun to be with
and he's nice to me
How nice I should thank him
Mina... have a great time in Hawaii
There's no way I can repay you
but I can reward Mina, so I'll do
as much as I can for her
So you must help me
Help our Mina to
only have happy times
until she goes to you
Help me...
Kang Mina!
Mina!
Hey, Mina!
You... your eyes are puffy?
- I drank some beer last night
- Alone?
You drank alone, too
Wow What a nice surprise
Oh, right, it'll rain today
Hold on, I'll get an umbrella
Mina, your umbrella!
Hey, excuse me
- That girl?
- Yes
Something happened in the class?
That poor guy is pathetic
Losing his love
being left alone
Being crazy because of love
He seems like a happy person
Not everyone can have that kind of love
And he'll live with his love
forever in his heart
Mom!
Yes?
If I lie here like this
I can only see the sky
I feel like I'm on an airplane
You've never taken a plane
Do you think I can?
We will go to Hawaii soon
Right
Isn't there a regular customer
in this restaurant who likes you?
Didn't you know? All the guys who
come here, come to see me
I mean it, someone who's serious
Someone who's nice
who you could marry
Now, with a little make up
you look nice
But what will you do
after you get old?
Children are no use
when you get old
What? now you have a boyfriend
You don't need mom anymore?
It's just...
I think you'll be lonely
after I get married and leave...
Don't worry
I worry
If you insist
I'll find a nice man soon
a rich and kind guy
Are you sure you'll
call him dad?
No way! I even call you
Misuk, not "mom"
I'll just call his name
Hey, Bubba! Like that
No! Never!
You will call him, Leonardo!
What!
Nice, the smell of dawn
Are you sleepy?
Of course
I just fell asleep
- What?
- This...
This is a present for a good kid
who got up early
And...
Take these too
Why? Don't you like them?
I don't need hostages anymore
Now, I trust you
Let's take a picture together
- Now?
- Yes!
Because I'm very happy now
Right this moment
I want a witness who'll testify
that I was happy
You, Neil, and Armstrong
all in a picture together
But looking like this?
Now is the best you've looked
since I've known you
Hurry! Hurry!
Mina! What are you looking for?
A sea turtle
Where is it anyway?
Why? You'll go to Hawaii
to see one soon, anyway?
Didn't you say it would be hard
to find one, even in Hawaii?
Of course, not all people can find
a sea turtle, but I will help you find one
No matter how difficult
So don't worry
The sea turtles aren't on display
They're having their regular checkups
Why so disappointed?
I'll show you a real one soon
One not locked up in a tiny Aquarium
but one in the real Pacific...
Let's get something nice to eat
Mina! Mina!
That poor guy is pathetic
Losing his love
being left alone
Being crazy because of love
Now, I trust you!
I want you to take this back
I should've noticed something
was wrong from the beginning
I thought it was a lot of money
just to spend time with your
daughter and take pictures of her
If I take this money, it means
I met Mina because of money
I can't do that
If I do that
I could never see her again
Sorry
I am sorry really sorry, Young-jae
Unlike what most people think
Hawaii has distinct seasons
These distinctions are
clear to Hawaiians
It is summer when the ripe
mangoes begin to fall
and when you smell
ginger flower in the wind
The signs of winter are the rains
and huge waves
that surfers love
The people who live in cool places
such as Kauai and Maui Islands...
gather by the fire
around Christmastime
Hawaii has a warm climate all year
Rainy from October to March
Dry from April to September
However, the weather changes
only slightly between seasons
so you can enjoy sunny skies
most of the year
You can often find sea turtles
along the coast
And the turtles are waiting
for Mina to come
to see them
Why don't you get some rest?
I'll stay here
Let's go, Misuk
What are we going to
talk about today?
Oh, yes
We'll go to the west beach
and see the "green flash" sunset
You can only see it on totally
clear day
at the last moment when the sun
sinks beneath the horizon
Some say it will give you love
Some say it grants wishes
What is this?
- Is that a real human hand?
- It's creepy
Yeah, it's creepy
Let's go!
We've graduated
All the good seasons are gone
Now, what am I going
to do for living?
Whatever you do
just take care of yourself
Broken arms and broken legs...
So pathetic!
Should we commit some kind of
wild scam together?
- What?
- To make some money
I am so sorry
I know that I did
a terrible thing to you
Please understand it as a
selfish mother's love
and forgive me
And one more...
This...
To my dear Youngjae who shared
the happiest time of my life
To my dearest Mom...
I know it must've been hard for you
to do this for me, thank you
I don't know how many
more days I have
but I'll be happy
I want to give this to you
as a present, before I leave
And I am really happy now