Report to Holy Master,
the Government is allied with the
Dutch Navy. They come to attack us.
Treat them the bomb.
How dare you!
Asia the Invincible
gathered 30,000 soldiers.
They are ready to fight to the North.
it seems that,
he is planning to rebel.
'To unite the world of martial arts.'
'Long life to the Sun moon Sect.'
Long life to our Holy Master,
Asia the Invincible.
Holy Master,
Wu is leading some swordsmen
to the Black Cliff.
They are approaching the palace.
They can do nothing to me!
They are here.
Kill Asia the Invincible.
Wu.
They killing Hook.
Watch my needles.
Ling!
Essence absorbing stance!
- I won't give you any shelter.
- Watch my Wonder Swords.
Who will you save first?
Asia the Invincible.
I will never tell you.
I want you to remember me
and regret for your whole life.
"Ming Dynasty, Wan Li Year 33"
That's the flag of
Asia the Invincible.
In the past,
The demon and his army
were destroyed here.
Yes, how can you imagine that
after his death,
the Black Cliff is still full of
arrogant and haunted atmosphere.
I can feel...
Asia the Invincible hasn't died.
This must be the Black Cliff.
Right, according to the report
of the Chinese officers,
This sailing route is leading
to the Black Cliff.
Officer Koo, isn't it
the base of Asia the Invincible?
General Golida,
Asia the Invincible
sank the Dutch warship...
right here?
Is Asia the Invincible
that horrible...
as you have mentioned?
The world of Han's martial arts
is hard to predict and understand.
There are many rumors in the world,
no matter they are true or not.
I do want to learn about it.
Brother Koo, we are ordered
to lead the Spanish here,
The purpose is to find the goods
from the sunken Dutch ship.
Why should we go up
to the Black Cliff?
I think Golida's intention is not
only the stuff from the sunken ship.
What are they doing?
They are having a sacrifice.
I believe they're scared of the evil
and would like to drive it away.
If they are so scared,
why do they still insist to go up?
yes, should we ask them why?
Golida said he was curious
about the Black Cliff.
In fact, me too.
Asia the Invincible was a name
of astonishment in the past.
Here, the Black Cliff, is his base.
Curious? What made you curious?
- Chin, Ling.
- Yes Sir.
You stay behind, I am going up first.
Woo, he can fly!
This is some sort of kung-fu
in our world of martial arts.
What is the world of martial arts?
it isn't a name of a place.
We called the place where swordsmen
gather the "World of Martial Arts."
So what is the place
where swordsmen gather?
Well, the place where
swordsmen live...
That's the place where
the swordsmen living around.
We just call it
the world of martial arts.
We are far behind, let's go.
Do you understand
what he has mentioned?
You are good at Han's dialects.
Don't you understand?
Sure I do.
Okay, let's go to
the world of martial arts.
The Notorious Evil:
Asia the Invincible.
Wu!
Who?
Asia the Invincible, if your soul
wants to see me, come out.
But you are already dead.
Why should you mention
the history again?
Stay calm,
there is something strange.
This is a land of souls
and evil spirits.
It's not wise of the living people
to visit here. You'd better leave.
Who are you? Human or devil?
Don't get mad, don't shoot.
The Black Cliff hasn't been
so busy for a long time.
I am the warden of this Holy Altar
for 3 generations.
I have seen the ups and downs
of the masters.
Asia the Invincible
misleader our Sect,
death is his only end!
You mean Asia Invincible is dead?
What? Hasn't he died?
Don't be afraid.
Impossible!
His corpse fell down
to the cliff together...
with his powerful kung-fu.
Just over there.
Would you take me there?
Go.
This is the grave of
Asia the Invincible.
Asia the Invincible!
Thank God,
this demon is locked right here.
I can't totally believe
that he is dead,
Why?
The only way to prove
he is dead or not,
I to look at his corpse.
Brother Koo,
do you want to dig his grave?
Maybe there is nothing inside.
Let me do it.
General Golida.
look at the corpse,
these are what left
by the notorious demon.
What he has left the world
is a notorious name.
The Notorious Demon:
Asia the Invincible.
What are you looking for?
I've spent great effort,
come here from afar,
only for one thing.
Don't stop me.
What are you searching?
His Sacred Scroll
If this is his dead body
I've heard that his mysterious
kung-fu came from the Sacred Scroll.
General Golida,
I am ordered to take you here
for the sunken ship.
But not for the Sacred Scroll.
You fool!
If I didn't use this excuse,
Your Majesty wouldn't
have been deceived.
And you wouldn't
have taken me here...
to find the thing I wanted
Koo.
You got mysterious Kung-fu,
I got science.
Asia the Invincible is a legend.
Now, he was buried underground.
We Hans have a saying,
"Respect the Heroes".
Even you don't respect him,
you'd give him some face.
You can't insult his skeleton.
We sail for treasure
is the funniest thing.
You can't even explain clearly
what the world of martial arts is!
If I can't get the Sacred Scroll,
it will be with you.
Golida,
if I let you touch the body
of Asia the Invincible,
Koo will have
a notorious name forever.
Get lost.
You have science,
I have mysterious Kung-fu.
You do despise the warden
of the Sun Moon Sect!
Take it back!
Follow me.
Let's go for Koo.
Thank you for saving my life.
A courtier tried hard
to protect a grave.
You are appreciated.
- Wine can stop pain.
- Thank you!
Not many people in the world
appreciate good win.
But I won't believe your identity.
Because I can tell,
you are Asia the Invincible.
What made you suspect me
to be Asia the Invincible?
I know pretty well about
the history of the Sun Moon Sect.
Since you are the warden,
and you have great power,
Asia the Invincible and Wu had
many severe fights among themselves.
They won't allow you,
such a guy to stay in his Sect.
Besides,
you're so skilled in kung-fu.
Why you are not renowned?
So, Asia the Invincible
is still alive.
You are Asia the Invincible!
If I were Asia the Invincible,
then you would not leave here alive.
I won't mind being killed,
that's my wish!
Don't you feel regret
to see Asia the Invincible?
Why should I regret
if my wish come true.
Okay, I will make
your wish come true.
Koo, 14 of your valves
has been closed by me,
you're dying.
Just because I have found out
you're Asia the Invincible?
That's what I presumed.
Asia the Invincible,
since you want to kill me.
You should keep your promise.
Let me see your real face.
Does if worth?
It's the fact, why do you
still ask this silly question?
Fine!
Koo, does it worth
dying for a glance of me?
Sure!
- Your are the big fool of the world!
- Wait!
Are you scared?
Don't you think no one knows...
you are hiding at the Black Cliff?
Do you know how many
Asia the Invincible...
are there in the world?
Although you hide yourself,
there're still many
Asia the Invincible.
Bull shit!
You close my valves, because
you don't want me to die so quickly!
You cunning guy, I want you
to feed the fishes with your body.
Are there many fake
Asia the Invincible?
Right, after you missing,
Many people tried to rule
over the world in the name of you.
Although you feel regret
under the Black Cliff,
Many Asia the Invincible
are still fighting for power.
You didn't kill, but many
innocent people died because of you.
What a troubled world.
Koo, since my name
is still a disaster.
Take me to stop the
fake Asia the Invincible.
I can do that,
but you must promise me.
Never kill again.
Good!
If you disclose my identity,
I'll kill not only
the innocent people, but you too.
Let's go for the
fake Asia the Invincible.
A ship is coming!
Be alert!
Report to our Holy Master.
We've discover that
a ship is approaching us.
Mo Yan Lu Chong.
Are your goods ready?
I have brought you the gold.
30000 guns, 100 cannons,
8000 baskets of gunpowder.
Our ship is dangerous under the sun.
If not cool it with water.
Our ship will explode any time.
Mo Yan Lu Chong,
you know sound transmission too.
But you are exaggerating.
How can you cool
such a big ship with water?
Asia the Invincible, but you are
more exaggerating than me.
My ship left Japan 8 years ago.
But I am always well informed
According to the report of my ninjas.
Asia the invincible died
4 months ago...
at the Black Cliff.
If this is the fact,
you are not Asia the Invincible.
It's lousy trick!
The Japanese ninja!
How can you fool me?
Raise.
I, Mo Yan Lo Chong is coming.
I will let your fellows
to fight with you.
Watch my sword!
- Come here.
- Master!
Try my Iron Balls.
Watch out!
A Japanese ninja is nothing special.
I sank down into the sea.
Turn to the East,
get ready the cannon.
Fire!
Dai, I want you tonight.
The opium is the tribute
from Ryukyu Islands.
Such precious thing should be
shared with our Holy Master.
Holy Master.
I haven't slept with you since
you've been my concubine,
do you know why?
I don't know.
I suspect that you are a man.
look, he is the betrayer!
The Japanese ninja...
is really great!
When did you find out I am a ninja?
Because when you looked at me.
Your eyes are different
from other concubines.
But why don't you
take action earlier?
I want you to tell me
how to trace Mo Yan Lu Chong.
Pigeon!
I need this to find Mo Yan Lu Chong.
What are you crying?
The one you loved
is right in front of you.
But, how about my lover?
Where are you?
Koo, you are quite good at flying.
You are still capable
to follow me after an hour.
But still I can't get ahead of you.
Do you want to?
The universe is endless,
the stars are bright.
The sun rises from the East,
I an the Invincible!
The universe is endless,
the stars are bright.
The sun rises from the East,
I an the Invincible!
Our Holy Master, Asia the Invincible.
Please honor me
the light of thousand generations.
Asia the Invincible
is just a normal guy.
Somehow he is worshipped as God.
People do not really understand
Asia the Invincible.
They don't need to understand
They only want...
Asia the Invincible, our Holy Master.
Burn me to death!
I am willing to die for you!
Hurry up.
Oh, Blood Sacrifice.
Hurry up!
Who are you? Why are you here?
What you are worshipping,
Is in fact the origin of evils.
Do you know it?
Why do you worship him?
Who are you?
You can't insult our Holy Master.
Holy Master?
You abuse the name of Asia the
Invincible to fool these Highlanders.
Do you want to offend him?
I an designated by
Asia the Invincible!
I rule over them according
to the will of Asia the Invincible.
Bull shit!
You haven't seen the
real Asia the Invincible.
You will be punished.
Only me who can communicate
with Asia the Invincible.
If you insult me, you are
insulting Asia the invincible.
Do you know who I am?
Tell me, who are you?
Who exactly are you?
How dare you talk to me like that!
Our Holy Master, Asia the Invincible!
What power has Asia the Invincible
evincible given you?
There are continuous
disasters in Highland.
The government is oppressing us.
Only Asia the Invincible
can protect us.
Foolish! I will kill those
who keep on worshipping me.
Because I am the real
Asia the Invincible.
Bull shit!
You believe the fake one
but not the true one.
Now you should
believe in what I said?
We can't surrender, I want to
devote my heart to the Holy Master!
We can't surrender!
If you want to devote your heart,
dig it out now.
No one can affect our love
towards the Holy Master.
Who suspects, who is going
against Asia the Invincible!
Do you see our strength now?
You want Asia the Invincible,
I will give you Asia the Invincible.
Give me your hearts.
Stop murdering!
Asia the Invincible! You promised me
that you wouldn't kill.
What the hell are you? It's the
business of the Highlanders.
There is nothing to do
with the government officials.
I had said, who disclose me,
who should be killed.
It's you who disclose yourself,
not me.
If you want to kill me,
not a reason is needed!
I want the whole world
to hate Asia the Invincible.
I want to slaughter...
those fake Asia the Invincible!
Is this the logo
of the Sun Moon Sect?
I am the government officials,
who dares cuff me?
Shut up!
Tell me how many government
officials are there?
Tell me, so I will keep you
a complete corpse.
Asia the Invincible?
Another Asia the Invincible.
How dare a little dog tease me?
I want to make your mouth shut,
let's see how you laugh again!
I think you wouldn't mind
somebody tease you.
The real Asia the Invincible
doesn't want to admit his identity.
And you, try every means to claim
yourselves to be Asia the Invincible.
I don't know you real identity.
But, the kung-fu of Asia the
Invincible came from the Sacred Scroll.
Show us the Sacred Scroll...
to prove yourself the
real Asia the invincible.
You fat-headed, since there are
so many fake Asia the Invincible.
There will be fake Sacred Scroll!
Let's see how long can you stand.
broken!
- Brother Ko.
- Officer Koo!
You are here!
We were caught
when hiding form the Spanish.
look!
- The Navy of Ming Dynasty!
- The arms of our government.
Right!
We bought these from the navy...
who stole the arms from their camps.
That's why it will soon be
the end of your dynasty soon.
I know your warships are coming...
South to go against us.
During our fight.
I will hang you up.
Let's wait and
see your dog face then!
It's useless,
we've tried this before.
This is our chance to survive.
Stay back.
Don't move, once they are in a mess.
The nearby navy camp
will hear the explosion.
At that moment,
we can get rid of all
fake Asia the Invincible.
How smart is your fat-head.
Officer, is that your trick?
You want to keep my life not because
you want me to cover you.
Because you want to know where is
the real Asia the Invincible.
You are afraid that
he will show up anytime.
Why did you say
that's the real Asia the Invincible?
It's useless to kill them!
It's not necessary for me
to tell you, he will show up soon.
Don't worry, he will come to you.
You are so anxious
to know he is real or not.
Sure your purpose is to find out
the real Asia the Invincible.
Have you waited him for a long time?
They are not
at the front of the ship.
Report to our Holy Master.
We've searched everywhere, but we
can't locate the sound of the flute.
We can't tell
where the sound comes from.
It's always like he finds others.
No one could find him out.
Here he comes.
It's we who leaded him here,
how can we send him back?
Raise the logo of our Sun Moon Sect.
Greet our honorable guest.
You return finally.
- Snow!
- I can hear you calling my name.
My coming here is not for you.
Then why did you come?
I came here for burying everything.
Forget Asia the Invincible.
The ship ran aground.
Sir, the gate of the prison
is ruined.
Okay, rush out!
Go to the head of the ship now.
To stop Asia the Invincible
destroying this ship again.
Catch it.
Take it back!
Asia the Invincible.
Holy Master.
Koo,
I have killed many
fake Asia the Invincible.
Asia the Invincible,
you are always superior.
But this is your Sun Moon Sect.
Stop another massacre please.
Koo, I want you to see how I return
to the world of martial arts.
And I want you to see my massacre
in the world of martial arts.
I am wrong. My holy Master
I lead the Sect in the name of you.
Because I am waiting for your return.
To let you lead us again,
and establish our own kingdom.
On your knees.
On your knees. Hurry up.
He is the real Asia the Invincible.
Snow, let bygones be bygones.
Master, I won't
let you leave me again.
I am a notorious demon.
I will go my own way.
Whenever you go, I will follow you.
You want to bother me?
If you want to follow me,
I will break your legs and hands.
Stop.
Just leave,
what do you want to proof?
None of your business.
You are my woman indeed.
You don't scare of death!
Death is not horrible. It's really
a great pain for one to live alone.
Okay, I will leave you,
the rubbish to be alive.
I want you to be painful forever.
Why do you hurt
the one who cares for you?
I don't need others concern,
what I want is the hatred of yours.
On your knees.
He is the real Asia the Invincible.
The powerful Su Moon Sect.
To unite the world.
Long life to our Holy Master.
Asia the Invincible,
the Sun Moon Sect.
Those who are longing for my return,
I tell you!
History can be changed!
Is Asia the Invincible so horrible!
This disaster will begin
from this ship.
And it will spread over
the whole world of martial arts.
Why do you still trust in
Asia the invincible?
he had abandoned you.
You'd better stop the wandering life.
Why don't you surrender
and join our court?
How ridiculous!
We always rule ourselves.
Who do you think you are? Damn it.
If not for Snow.
Our Holy Master won't abandon us.
That's right!
Snow, you deceived us.
You are the sinner of our Sect.
Snow, you sinner!
What else do you want to say?
Speak up!
I have made a deadly sin.
Kill her!
Ching, protect Snow.
Kill that 3 damn officers too.
Hang them to death and air dried them.
Right, that's a good idea.
Send the 3 damn officers to hell!
Execute the law of our Sect.
Brother Koo, save Snow now.