Any more cakes? Hand them over!
Make it quick!
You're driving me crazy!
I've forgotten to tell you one thing,
If I get vampire teeth, remember,
Kill me at once!
At once.
No! No!
Don't die!
Don't leave me alone!
I promise, I'll be your best partner.
I'll listen to you!
I won't fight with your sister again.
Wake up, please!
Do you want me to tell you everything?
I really love you!
Can you hear me?
I'm alive!
But I don't know what you just said.
What? What is it?
I said... I am not that easy to kill.
I couldn't hear what you said.
It's just too noisy.
Okay, I'll shut up!
Let's take a rest now.
Your cake is really delicious.
Your coffin is so comfortable.
Bye!
Are you looking for trouble?
That kiss was okay,
but you're not allowed
to kiss me again.
What you said before...
I heard everything!
Is anyone home?
Miss Momoko,
what a coincidence to see you here.
Mr. Prada,
I've brought you some papers to sign.
And I've brought you something else.
Please wait.
This is the last chance!
I'll bite her neck.
And you can choose
any position you like.
Pulse, or inner thigh, or an armpit.
Let's bite her together,
and then suck her blood.
I told you many times! I don't suck.
Okay, I'll suck her blood
and put it into a jar.
I'll serve you
with a glass of it, okay?
You used to serve it like that to me.
But that's all over now.
Forget the past!
I'm telling you for the last time.
I won't suck blood.
I see! You have fallen for that girl.
Tell me, you think
you're fit to be a vampire?
Have you got
what it takes to be a prince?
Are you qualified
to succeed the throne?
Are you giving me a lecture?
Try to tell her tomorrow,
tell her that you're a vampire.
See if she's generous enough
to give you her blood.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Is it urgent?
I want to tell you what I am.
Don't turn your back to me.
I'll get angry.
Let me be frank.
I am not a human being.
You're certainly not acting like one!
How can you talk to me like that?
I'm a vampire.
So?
Look at my eyes.
Cool!
Where did you get those contact lens?
What are you yelling about?
See? I want to suck your blood!
That's not the right way to suck.
Suck like this.
Let me go! Off!
I know what you're doing!
You want to dump me, right?
I'm a vampire!
Do you want
to fall in love with a vampire?
So what's a vampire?
Can a vampire brush
his girl off like this?
I know! You think I'm too sassy.
But most of the girls
in Hong Kong are sassy!
Don't you believe me?
Go find another one.
If you dare!
I have some dogs at home.
I don't mind having a vampire.
The only problem is
that my brother may not like you!
I am a vampire,
and a useless vampire, too.
What do you mean?
I haven't eaten for days!
What are you doing?
I am taking you to find food.
You stay here!
It's better for me to go alone.
Be careful!
It's time to eat.
Something's wrong, let's run!
Did you get caught?
Can you hear that?
What is it?
Bats.
If there are bats around,
it means vampires are around, too.
Let's run!
Why is the hospital alarm ringing?
Has there been a robbery?
I think it's just a mistake.
I don't think any thief would be
stupid enough to steal from a hospital.
Who knows? Thieves are everywhere.
Your car could even get stolen.
Speak of the devil!
What's the matter?
Who are you?
I am so glad to see you again!
I saved you last time.
Would you help us now?
Your friend is dying!
That's right! I think he's dying!
He has to get to another hospital!
Please take him there now.
But I have to take
something to the hospital.
The "something"
you have to take is him.
Take him there now, or he'll die!
Come on! Hurry!
Let's go! Please!
Are you feeling bad?
Do you want to suck my blood?
Of course not!
I can treat your teeth
like mosquitoes!
If you don't eat, you'll die!
Jackie, drive faster please.
What's up?
Who are these guys?
Help!
Be careful!
I don't know how to drive!
Hold the wheel tightly!
This is bad!
Are you okay?
What the hell are you?
This is terrible! I ran someone over!
Vampires! They are vampires!
Vampires?
He can fly!
Come on up!
- Throw me another bag of blood!
- Okay!
It's working! This is type AB.
Are there really vampires?
It works!
What did you give them?
It's a kind of tranquilizer.
It should calm them down.
They ate so much!
It's making them go crazy!
Turn on the music now.
Drink it.
Come on! I brought it for you!
Do you feel better?
Well...
Jackie asked me to return it to you.
What does this mean?
The ring is too tight!
I can't get it off.
Good morning.
Good morning!
You help my brother
to iron his clothes?
I'll iron them from now on.
Congratulations!
You've found someone you can love.
Haven't you fallen in love
with someone too?
He's great. He's just terrific.
But sometimes,
he's not that good to me...
The harder it is to fall in love
with him, the more I love the feeling!
Anyway, there is something missing!
So I just couldn't fall in love.
What's missing?
That is...
What is it?
Something is missing...
He is the "thing" you
and my brother hate most.
Have you fallen in love
with a vampire?
But he's a good vampire!
Vampires suck blood and kill people!
How can that be good?
He'd rather starve than suck blood.
He is really nice!
Could you say something on our behalf?
Your brother and I
are vampire hunters.
Please help us! Please.
I beg you to help us!
My dear sister-in-law!
Come on! Please help me,
"my dear sister-in-law"!
We are a family!
Family! As your sister-in-law,
I'll help you, right?
I always said my brother is lucky!
At the first sight,
I could tell you were really nice
as well as pretty.
Hey,
how did you win my brother's heart?
Watch this!
Superstar!
Can you do that?
It's terrible!
But your brother likes it.
No way! He's got special tastes!
He likes trashy girls,
but they must be simple.
Besides being simple,
she must be ordinary.
Do you have any better suggestions?
Does it work?
How about this?
Can you do that again?
My dear sister-in-law!
Do you have a date?
What do you think?
You put on perfume!
We can go now.
Do you like it?
How pathetic to find
a vampire living here,
in a church!
Now, where is the fifth prince?
This is for you.
What is it?
Why is it black?
Vampires wear black wedding gowns.
Really?
Well, you search over there,
and I'll check over here.
Why should I go there?
What are you doing? Let go!
Don't you love me?
Why did you let them go?
They're in love!
That's my sister,
and that's a vampire!
What did we swear
before joining the League?
When I took my oath,
I didn't fall in love.
Now, I know what love is!
Once you love a person,
you won't care about anything.
You can tell that from
what I'm wearing.
Didn't you promise
you'd do anything for me?
I've got it! I'll wait for you here!
Reeve,
right where you are least expected!
Good to see you again, old friend.
This is my room.
This is my bed.
May I lie down?
Just for sleeping?
Go ahead,
well, it's good to take a nap.
Our beds are not just for sleeping.
See, it's bigger than yours.
Are there other ways to use it?
Such as?
Well, chatting!
Many people love chatting in bed.
Haven't you ever heard of
"pillow talk"?
No. Shall we try now?
Sure!
Why don't you talk?
What's up?
Someone's here!
My dear sister-in-law, you're home!
Come with me now!
What's up?
Your brother is in trouble!
He's the only one person
who can save your brother.
Kazaf, how long have I waited
for this moment?
I didn't come for you. Let Reeve go.
You still dare to act like royalty?
Bow to me,
and I may grant you an easy death.
You still need my blood,
If I spill it myself,
it's worthless to you,
Let him go.
Why should I?
Your friends have already
gone to rescue Reeve.
Perhaps,
I should free this one instead?
Reeve!
Drop the knife and he shall be free.
No chance! Release him!
No...
Let him go!
Reeve!
Reeve! It's me!
I'm your sister, Helen!
So I see you are
stronger than your brothers!
Reeve!
Gypsy!
In this world,
there are still some vampires.
And there are
three more vampire hunters.
One of them is me.
One is my sister-in-law,
who's now become a semi-vampire.
And the other one
is a sentimental vampire!
I've brought you something to eat.
Come on, try some!
I really love to eat!
So, go ahead.
I've brought you some papers.
Take a look, see whether
you've got any questions.
I can do the amendments for you.
I think something is wrong.
What's the problem? Just tell me.
You're disgusting!
I feel so itchy!
Do you always act like that?
I haven't tried that before.
Honey, I told daddy that
you're "dickson"...
It should be decent.
You're "dickson"
I just wanted to speak faster.
I am sorry.
Decent.
Again.
No way, I have to deliver
something to the hospital.
Look at his hand!
His hand is right here.
No!
I said that's you,
you don't have to move like that.
I don't know.
You can just put it here.