I was thinking.
You have doubts?!
Objection!
Don't hound him.
Rephrase the question.
How long did it take you
to go down the hill?
And was the bus always in sight?
For a while my view
was blocked by the hill.
Could it be that another bus
overtook the first one at that point?
There was only one bus!
You're lying!
Sustained!
Defence should rephrase his question.
Could you be mistaken?
No!
There are four different bus routes
on that road.
On two routes,
the buses run every five minutes.
The other two,
the buses run every six minutes.
So 88 buses run back and forth
on that road every hour.
That's more than one bus a minute.
So what?
How long did it take you
to go down the hill?
About two minutes.
Exactly?
Two minutes and half.
So at most eight or night buses
could have passed by.
But you said there was one.
I say you're lying.
Don't you know the buses are always late?
All right. Let's give you the benefit of the
doubt.
Assume there was one bus
and you could see it
all the time.
Which part was clearly visible
to you?
The body.
How much of the body?
All of it!
You're lying!
What's he doing?
You could see only one side of this bus.
At most, only half of it.
You couldn't see the other half.
Am I right?
Yes.
And anything
could have happened
on the side you couldn't see.
Yes.
So if someone jumped off,
you couldn't see him, could you?
No.
Speak louder.
I could have jumped off, he couldn't.
Just answer the question.
I mean it!
You try jumping from a moving bus!
Control yourself!
If that's not him
why did he bribe me?
Why would he do that?
He offered me money to let him go.
If it was you and
someone pointed a gun at you,
what would you do?
Objection!
Objection overruled!
Answer him!
I'd give him all my money.
That's what happened
to my client.
Am I right?
No, I'd already identified myself.
There are many cases where
criminals pose as policemen.
Sustained!
Court will ignore that remark.
Confine yourself
to this case.
I'm sorry!
Consider this,
a businessman
is carrying company cash on a bus.
A policeman chasing robbers stops
the bus and points a gun at him.
So the businessman thinks
the policeman is a crook.
So he tells the policeman
to take the cash and let him go.
Inspector Chan, isn't that right?
Objection!
The witness needn't answer.
We already know the answer.
He doesn't need to say it.
I conclude.
Wonderful!
Now what?
I know what to do.
He'll get off the hook.
He won't.
Your Honour, we request an adjournment.
Our prime witness was delayed.
Objection!
The Crown has failed
to establish a case.
There is insufficient evidence
to convict my client.
I request a dismissal.
Your Honour.
We have taped evidence
from our witness.
Tapes can't be accepted as evidence.
That tape is key to this case.
Objection.
I will not adjourn or postpone
the hearing.
That would be unfair to the defendant.
I will grant him bail.
But we will
hear that tape first.
Please turn up the volume.
It's a cheap tape.
Thanks.
Wait! I didn't erase that.
Just let it play!
It's coming up!
Oh, you! That hurts!
What did I do?
You really poked me!
You're breaking it!
Don't push too hard!
What an ugly thing!
Go away!
It's the only one I got. It's my treasure.
It's only a cactus!
What's happening?
You got me all wet!
Let me wipe it for you.
Please, no more! No, don't!
That was only orange juice!
That wasn't what you think.
Be gentle! That hurt!
The sofa's hard. It's not very comfy.
Let's go to bed now.
Let's go to bed.
OK. But where can I sleep?
On my bed.
And you?
Next to you.
You're so protective.
It's exciting!
Come on!
Please be cooperative.
Stand back, please.
No photographs!
Ka-kui!
I want a written report.
Boss!
Here!
No pictures!
Get back.
John, reserve a room
at the country club.
We're going to celebrate.
I'm leaving now.
Thank you very much!
Next time let's hire him as prosecutor.
This is Crime Story.
I'm so happy to see you all again.
Our guest today is
a brave police officer.
Sitting next to me is
Inspector Chan Ka-kui.
Hello!
Hello! Hello everyone!
After cracking down on the biggest
drug racket in Hong Kong,
you've become very popular
amongst the people.
Would you share this particular
experience with us?
The success of this operation
was due to team work.
I was just a part of it.
We were well prepared for the operation.
What makes your department so special
in the police force?
To be one of us,
you have to be
strong, alert,
smart, and...
Boss.
What's up?!
His photo is all over
the papers and magazines.
And he had won the
Brave Policeman Arrests Drug Tycoon
and our Thai source is out of stock.
What? Are they crazy?
They've sold everything to Uncle Joe.
They want hard cash.
Boss, Mr Cheung is here.
Please come in.
Mr Chu, I've received your cheque,
thanks a lot!
I should thank you!
How's my case now?
All evidence must remain
with the court
until the case ends.
What does that include?
Your passport and bank account.
You can't use them now.
If you're found guilty,
your assets will be confiscated.
And besides, the bastards could jail me.
Phone call for you, Boss.
Excuse me!
Salina.
It's boring here.
I want to go somewhere else.
Not just yet.
Can I come and see you?
Not now. You should stay where you are.
The police are looking for you.
I'm planning a trip to Europe for you.
Once you're there, you'll be fine.
You just have to wait.
It's for your own good.
Where were we?
We were lucky
to bail you out.
It would have been different
if they had found Salina.
I doubt they'll ever be able to find her.
Very well.
I must leave. See you.
Bye.
Your lawyer is right.
Salina's a big problem.
You can't hide her forever.
True.
Snake Eyes says that stupid cop
is looking for Salina everywhere.
We should send her abroad.
On a one-way ticket.
Let's use that stupid cop
to kill Salina.
Be sensible.
Chicks like her aren't difficult to get.
Inspector Man wants to see you.
Let him in.
You paid him off, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
But he says he wants
to retire and start a business.
What does that mean?
He wants more money!
This way, Inspector Man.
Hello!
Hello.
Sit down.
I'm OK.
I came to see you about...
Yes, I know.
You want to retire and start a business.
Good idea.
Thanks for your money.
I know you're a smart guy.
But I want one more favour.
What is it?
I want Chan Ka-kui to disappear for good.
You want to be a hero.
I'll make you a tragic hero.
I'll book you for that!
Hi, there! Follow me.
Inspector Chan!
If anything happens,
you can reach me...
Reach you with telegram.
My home.
But you're on patrol.
That doesn't mean
I can't pass by my house.
I'm going to the toilet, you stay here.
Don't stay there for too long.
Hello, Police Station.
You called, Inspector Chan?
Of course, any news?
On Salina? I need more time.
It's not easy, you should know.
Then you won't get paid.
I know.
I'm doing my best.
What?
Wait a second!
Police Station, hold the line.
Three more days, Snake Eyes.
What?
That's not enough time.
I'll give you four days.
Or you'll be in trouble,
when I get back to town.
I'm hanging up now!
Can I help?
I've been waiting for ages.
You want to speak Inspector Chan? Hold on.
Phone, Inspector Chan.
Right, thanks!
Hello, this is Inspector Chan.
It's me.
May.
Who was that?
That rude guy?
Wait. I'll give him a lesson.
Didn't I tell you to be polite on the phone?
You're so rude!
I'm really sorry!
Right. I just told him off.
How's it going?
What are you doing now?
Me?
Now? Now I'm talking to you.
Have you had lunch?
Not yet.
I'm cooking some noodles.
Have you eaten, then?
No.
Wait a minute.
Police Station, hold the line.
May. I'm back.
Mum wants to have dinner
with us on Sunday.
Is that so? That sounds great.
Hold on.
Police Station.
My husband...
Your husband what?
He's beating me up.
Who's beating who up?
My husband's beating me up!
You husband's beating you?
Don't cry. I'll put you through
to a different department.
I'm coming on Sunday,
wait a second.
The line's busy.
Police Station, how can I help?
I'm missing a cow.
Hold the line.
I'll get you the right department.
The line's still busy.
Police Station.
I was raped!
Really?!
I have to write down the details.
When were you raped?
I wasn't raped, but my husband's mad.
Oh! It's you,
I'm still connecting your call.
It's taking so long!
This is a big police station. Wait!
Who's been raped?
Me!
I'm missing a cow!
When were you raped?
Last year!
Why didn't you report it?
Are there any pills I can take?
Pills?!
I'll find out for you.
Hello, Police Station.
I'm missing a cow.
All right.
But you need to bring in
a photo of the cow first.
Hello.
May, I'm very busy.
She wants me to name a place for dinner?
Give me a minute first.
Hello.
Where shall we go?
The Family Planning Clinic.
Take a double portion of contraception pills.
Free.
May.
Tell your own mum to take
contraception pills!
What?! May!
I was saying that to someone else.
Hello?
Tell my mum to take contraception pills.
My mum doesn't need those pills.
Police Station.
I'm testing the line, bye!
What?!
Stuck in traffic?
No, not traffic.
You're late.
If the roads were congested,
I wouldn't be here at all.
You're having dinner with us.
Mum hates it when anyone's late!
May, listen.
I've been waiting all day.
You're off that case.
Forget about it.
I can't.
I need to make a phone call.
Hold on to the car.
The hand brake doesn't work.
Don't let go.
It's me, Snake Eyes.
Chu Tu's hiding that witness
you're looking for
in his Kowloon villa.
You sure?
Better hurry.
They don't plan to keep her alive.
Is it true?
Would I lie to you? Hurry up!
May.
Are you coming?!
That was Snake Eyes.
I know where they're hiding Salina.
Don't go!
If Chu Tu kills her, he'll go free.
I've got to save her.
I can't let her die.
What's up?
Your car!
What now?!
Taxi!
Call someone to tow the car away.
And say sorry to your mum for me.
Be careful!
Keep the change.
Thanks!
What happened?
I don't know what they're up to.
Is anyone else here?
No one. They just disappeared.
Now you know what Chu Tu is like.
If you had listened to me,
you wouldn't be in danger.
It's lucky I got here.
Otherwise, you'd be dead.
Let's get out of here.
Go.
Stop!
Step aside.
How did you know I was here?
I have my ways.
You can't be...
Surprised?!
That's not the only surprise.
We were supposed to kill him.
That's right.
The boss wants us to use a police gun.
One cop kills another.
What a perfect set-up!
Who's killing who?
Let's get out of here!
Move it.
No, I can't do it!
No!
Jump!
Move it!
Stop!
Go get her!
You little prick! We'll teach you.
You'll wish you'd never interfered.
That's enough!
Take care of him. I'll go down.
Ka-kui didn't shoot Inspector Man.
We can't take your word for it.
We need evidence.
If he didn't do it,
Where did he go with his gun?
The bullet that killed Man was fired
from Ka-kui's gun.
Explain it.
Policemen make lots of enemies.
Someone is trying to frame Ka-kui.
If it were anyone else but Ka-kui,
would you feel the same?
You're the boss.
Don't always go by the book!
Show some feelings for your men.
I don't want people thinking if a cop kills,
he gets away with it.
There'll be no cover up!
One law for all.
You want to nail him
even more than the crooks!
Enough!
If you were me, what would you do?
Hi, May.
I know.
I'll wait for you.
One Cop Kills Another. Policeman Is Killed
What should we do?
My mum is really worried about you.
Ka-kui, be careful!
Ka-kui's back!
Ka-kui!
I didn't kill him.
We believe you.
But where have you been?
I don't know.
You must remember something.
Were you drunk or with your girlfriend?
I was fighting Chu Tu's men.
Inspector Man appeared
and pointed his gun at me.
They took my revolver
and shot Man with it.
That's all I remember.
Nothing else?
You disliked Man,
and the bullet was from your gun.
Don't you know?
I wouldn't kill him over
some petty differences.
Who would believe that?
We must have proof!
That's how the law works.
But I'm glad you're back.
Give me your gun.
Call Homicide.
Tell them
we have the suspect.
Ka-kui, don't worry.
We'll do our very best to help you.
Lock him up.
And charge him... with murder.
How could you?!
Freeze!
Ka-kui, what are you doing?
I didn't kill anyone!
Don't you believe me?
I believe you.
But based on the evidence,
I must charge you.
Can't you see I was framed?
You're bloody stupid!
I'll conduct a very thorough investigation!
Don't give me that!
Let him go!
What?
What you are doing is dangerous!
Dangerous for him!
While we risk our lives out there,
he's sitting back thinking of chicks.
We've arrested so many bad guys,
but he's never satisfied.
He just considers the result.
And he uses dirty tricks to catch Chu Tu
and that stupid idea of protecting the witness.
So easy?!
You only have to open your mouth
and we have to risk our lives!
Ka-kui!
Shut up!
You got promoted at our expense.
Have you ever thought of us?
If any of us dies,
you need only write a report
and turn up for the funeral.
We have families, too.
If it wasn't for us, you'd never have
this office and all this other crap!
Ka-kui.
Go away!
Come any closer and I'll blow his head off!
Ka-kui, don't do that!
Open the door!
Don't move!
Don't push me!
Keep back!
Don't worry about me. I know what I'm doing!
Ka-kui's holding the Super hostage!
What?
Calm down!
Stay cool! Ka-kui, calm down.
Stay back!
Ka-kui, calm down.
Let's talk about this.
Don't come over.
Don't do that.
Let's talk.
We'll sort this out.
Put your hands on the table.
Now!
You're being stupid.
Give up before it's too late!
We'll help you.
Calm down!
Trust us!
We'll sort this out.
I trust all of you,
but I can't depend on you.
You're making it worse!
Stop!
Don't move!
Ka-kui.
Don't push him!
Don't push him.
Call in the snipers. Alert all units.
Easy, everybody!
Ka-kui!
Get in!
Drive out.
Let them go!
Don't go after them!
It's more important to keep Super safe.
Where are we going?
Stop.
Get out.
I wouldn't have shot
even if you had run.
I'm not sure how to help you,
but you'll have a head start.
They'll start hunting for you once I get back.
I'll get Chu Tu
before your men get me.
Be careful!
Thank you, sir.
No one knows where this Salina is.
Let's get a couple of chicks
and have some fun.
I didn't set you up, Inspector Chan!
It wasn't me.
I had no part in it!
It's for you.
I'll have it then. I'm starving.
Boss,
I heard that stupid cop
is on the run.
Wasn't he arrested?
He's run away!
He's got some nerve!
We should have killed him, too,
once and for all.
Where is Salina?
Mad Wing and Snake Eyes
are looking for her.
We've heard nothing from them.
Salina could be with that stupid cop.
What's up, boss?
Someone's stealing my data.
Who is it?
It must be Salina.
Only she knows the password.
Go get her.
Alert our men.
Call Mr Cheung.
Yes.
How long do we need to wait?
You're impatient.
I'm not,
but I'm scared.
You two stay here.
Up there.
What?
Call Inspector Chou!
Get that briefcase
or we're doomed!
Quick!
That way!
Ka-kui!
Why didn't you go to the police?
Chu Tu's men are here.
You witnessed Man's murder.
I'm counting on you.
I've got evidence on Chu Tu.
They're here!
Take her back to the office. Quick!
What's going on?
Not your business.
Let's go.
Beat him.
Off.
Come on!
I'm not going.
Kill him!
Catch!
It's there! Go and get it!
May!
Are you all right, Ka-kui?
Don't worry about me.
Get the briefcase!
OK.
Go to hell!
Chu Tu!
Quick!
Hurry!
Ka-kui, stop!
Don't do it!
Calm down!
Put that down.
We'll sort this out!
Ka-kui!
This is between him and me.
He's not worth it.
There's no justice. I have to take
the law into my own hands.
I'm helping the weak ones.
Don't do anything foolish.
I'm going to kill him right here.
It was Danny Chu who killed Inspector Man.
All the evidence is in the briefcase.
Are you all right?
May is hurt, Ka-kui.
Take care of her first!
Take all the suspects
back to the station!
You're abusing your power
as police officers.
You're hurting innocent people.
You're not above the law.
Justice is for everyone.
I'm going to sue you for kidnapping,
threatening and assaulting my client.
I'm not going to let you
get away with this!
You threaten,
beat up good citizen.
I'll sue you..
You lot are a menace to society!
He just proved it.
Ka-kui, let go of him.
This is entrapment!
You're going to jail.
How dare you treat a lawyer like that?
We're so glad you're here, Mr Cheung!
You...
You'll have to help me with that report.
Pardon?
Let's write it together.
I didn't see anything.
That's enough!