Jackson, you going to go to Hong Kong?
I love anything full-contact.
I need a few more scars on my face.
I heard you can get killed at that kumite.
Only if you fuck up.
Tomorrow we leave for the kumite.
Sir?
Excuse me.
Col. Cooke would like to see you
before you leave.
What's the problem?
He found out you're going to Hong Kong.
He wants to talk to you about it.
Tell him I'll be right there
after I take a shower.
But I'll have to wait, sir.
Okay.
What's taking so long, Captain?
Captain?
Shit!
Sir!
Where's Dux?
He was at the gym, like you said.
He took a shower,
I waited, and he disappeared.
What do you mean, disappeared?
One minute he's there, then gone.
Jesus Christ!
If anything happens to Dux in Hong Kong...
Get Helmer and Rawlins
on this right away.
And I don't want to see your face again
until Dux is beside it!
Understand?
How is he?
He's resting now.
He'll be so happy to see you.
It's so good to be here again.
I'll tell him you are here.
Thank you.
Look at the sword!
Let's get it.
Come on, Frank.
What's the matter, you chicken?
- No.
- Then get in here.
Frank, you want to hang out with us,
then come on!
You just going to stand there,
or are you going to grab something?
Shit! They're coming back!
Let's get out of here!
Come on, Frank!
Forget him! Let's go!
That's enough, Shingo.
Go to your studies.
You cannot get katana sword by stealing.
It is a very special sword.
You must earn it.
I wasn't going to steal it.
You didn't flinch. You have fighting spirit.
You're not gonna call the cops?
Not if we make a deal.
What kind of a deal?
Your son and my son
are in the same school.
Frank sees my son's skill...
...and he desires
to learn martial science, too.
Yes, but what do you mean
by martial science?
Frank has told me
you came to America to grow vines.
Yes, that's right.
I work at the Verne vineyard.
I came here to grow fish in my hatchery.
We both grow children.
You use science
to make vines grow better.
Like vines, children need training.
Martial science provides a way of training.
It brings mind, body, spirit together.
That's enough. That's all for today.
Not yet.
Why don't you quit, round-eye?
Go practice your katas.
How come you coach him, but not me?
I brought you here
to help me train my son.
Don't question me!
If you expect me to be his punching bag,
you can forget about our deal.
Someday...
...I'll fight in the kumite
and make my father proud.
Shidoshi, I feel like
I've lost part of my family, too.
Shingo and I were close friends,
like brothers.
And you and Mrs. Tanaka...
...have treated me like a son.
What will happen now?
No more training.
I stop now.
But you have so much to teach.
You don't understand.
In the war, I lost my first family...
...my son, daughter, and wife.
They lived in Hiroshima.
I left Japan because of the war.
War was wrong.
I came here to start over...
...begin a new family, have a son...
...another chance to pass on the teaching.
For 2,000 years...
...knowledge passed from father to son...
...father to son.
When Shingo died...
...it stopped.
Teach me. I can do it.
You are not Japanese!
You are not a Tanaka!
You taught me
using any technique that works...
...never to limit myself to one style...
...to keep an open mind!
Why?
To honor you, Shidoshi.
Practice until you can meditate...
...and nothing can distract you...
...so that you see and feel nothing...
...except your own energy.
Are you awake, Shidoshi?
Do you sleep with your eyes open?
How are you feeling?
Like an old man.
And how about you?
I'm going to Hong Kong.
You sure you want to do this?
To honor you means everything to me.
I have poured all my knowledge into you.
When you fight, my spirit fights with you.
In kumite, you will need it.
Hey, babe,
want to go out with a real big man?
No, huh?
Too handsome for you, honey?
Is this your first time in Hong Kong?
You two are here for the kumite,
aren't you?
Kumite? What is kumite?
Look, guys,
I know there's a secret full-contact event...
...being held in Hong Kong
in the next few days.
Yes. Hong Kong is an exciting city.
I also happen to know a little bit
about some of your competition.
Okay.
Would you just tell me
how you got invited?
Thanks, guys.
What? Think you can
give me some competition?
Sure. I'll try.
That's what I like to hear,
a kid who isn't afraid to lose.
No, I got it.
I don't want to take your money.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
- You like this kind of fighting?
If you want to see some real fighting,
you can see me fight at the kumite.
I'm here, too, for the kumite.
Aren't you a little young for full-contact?
Aren’t you a little old for video games?
- You want to go at it again, huh?
- Yeah.
Not bad, kid. Name's Ray Jackson.
I'm Frank Dux.
Mrs. Tanaka...
Mrs. Tanaka?
Yes?
It's very important
to the government of the United States...
...that we find Frank Dux.
We understand that
he might have visited Mr. Tanaka recently.
Mr. Tanaka is very ill.
We're sorry to hear that.
Was Frank here recently?
Frank came here to pay his respects.
- When was that?
- Two days ago.
Did he say, or do you know
if he was going to Hong Kong?
I don't know.
Of course you know. We're not trying to...
Mrs. Tanaka,
we're very sorry to have disturbed you.
Thank you very much for your time.
- May I help you?
- Yeah, how you doing?
My name's Jackson. This is Mr. Frank Dux.
Are our rooms ready?
Mr. Lin in Room 310 wants to see you
after you check in.
Who the hell's Mr. Lin?
I'm Lin. You Jackson?
You look like a Jackson.
That would make you Frank Ducks.
No, no. It's Dux.
Gotcha. Like "Put up your dukes," right?
Okay, so here's the deal.
This is the biggest kumite ever.
We got fighters from all over.
I've been assigned by the IFAA...
...to help you
and the other North American fighters...
...to find your way around.
I'm gonna make sure
you guys give it your best.
And don't disqualify by fighting
outside the arena.
The Triad, they are like the Mafia...
...is allowing us
to hold kumite here this time.
Here it comes, man, the Walled City.
Not a place for outsiders.
You are in Hong Kong.
But you are about to cross
an invisible border into mainland China.
No joke, man.
It's a run-down piece of no-mars-land...
...in the middle of a tourist paradise.
It goes back to the old lease agreement
between Great Britain and China.
Once you step out of the sunlight
into the narrow corridors...
...it's time to protect your nuts, guys.
Okay, USA!
"Okay, USA!"
Okay, guys.
First, you'll show the Black Dragon boys
your invitation.
Then you got to qualify
and prove to them...
...you can step onto the runway
and not get killed.
Got it?
You got it?
It says he represents the Tanaka clan.
You don't look like Tanaka.
Shidoshi Tanaka trained me.
What's the hold up?
He says Senzo Tanaka is his Shidoshi.
What's the difference
if Bruce Springsteen is his Shidoshi?
If Senzo Tanaka is his Shidoshi...
...then show us the dim mak.
What the hell is a dim mak?
Death touch.
Thanks.
Vic, choose a brick.
Okay, Frank.
What about this one?
No!
Bottom one.
Son of a bitch!
Is that good enough, guys?
We honor your invitation.
No shit, you honor his invitation!
That was great.
Very good, but brick not hit back.
Here's a picture
of the man we're looking for.
His name is Frank Dux.
We have reason to believe
Frank is here in Hong Kong.
His name was on a list...
...on a flight from San Francisco
two days ago.
Two days ago?
Maybe he already left,
went somewhere else.
Asia's a very big place, you know.
We were hoping
you'd hold onto this for reference.
We're here because Frank is
fighting in the kumite...
...and we're here to stop him.
The kumite?
Yes.
Inspector Chen...
...we all know the kumite
is happening here in Hong Kong.
And we all know it's going on
over the next three days.
All we want you to do is
pass this picture out to your men.
If they spot Dux,
they give us a call at our hotel. Simple.
My men already overworked.
- If it's too much trouble, forget it...
- Inspector...
We're all overworked,
but we need your help.
I'll see what can be done.
You know where to reach us.
You'll come upstairs with me
for an interview.
Like hell! Let go of me.
You want Hussein, no?
No. Hussein is an asshole.
What did you call me?
You want me to spell it out for you?
Leave the girl alone.
He is the American shithead
who makes tricks with bricks.
Guess the kumite starts
one day earlier this year, huh?
- Look, guys, let's all calm down, okay?
- No.
She is coming with me upstairs.
No, I'm not.
If we have to fight for her...
...then both of us will
be thrown out of the kumite.
Just for her?
We could arrange this another way.
- Do you gamble?
- What is bet?
You hold this.
If I can grab it before you close your hand...
...I get the girl.
If I cannot...
...she's yours.
Very good.
What? You can't do this!
Just relax.
Take it.
Geez, Frankie,
I hope you know what you're doing.
Ready?
Go.
You lose, American asshole.
Looks like she's mine.
Now leave the lady alone.
You understand that?
Why were you with Hussein?
I've been trying
to get a story on the kumite.
I'm a reporter.
He tell you anything?
He told me I had nice legs.
He's right about that.
Why is it that no one
will talk about the kumite?
What is this air of mystery?
I'm just trying to find out
what it's all about.
Why are you fighting in it?
It's personal.
You want to prove
your manhood to the world?
The kumite is for the fighters,
not for the people who read newspapers.
I've heard that it's unnecessarily brutal...
...like a cockfight, except it's with people.
You have the wrong picture.
Well, you tell me about it then.
I want to have the right picture.
Okay, I'll talk to you, but one condition.
What's that?
You agree to have dinner with me
tomorrow night.
Well, actually, I was hoping
Hussein would be free.
That hurts me, just looking at it.
Yo, Frankie!
Earth to Frankie.
This is ground control. Do you copy?
It's time to get ready.
You'd better stop doing that stuff.
You might want to have kids
one of these days.
Victor's downstairs.
Kumite Express leaves in five minutes.
Are you ready?
I am ready.
You can almost smell the adrenaline
in this place, can't you?
Yeah.
They are gonna love me over here.
You can really love Asians
because we're good-looking.
Welcome, warriors of the world.
Today you become part of a tradition...
...that began hundreds of years ago.
The kumite was first used
by the Kokuryukai...
...the Black Dragon Society...
...to measure the fighting skills and spirit...
...of its members.
Every five years,
the best fighters in its ranks...
...would face each other in full-contact...
...with one winner emerging
as the superior warrior...
...the champion.
The Kokuryukai has been joined...
...by the International
Fighting Arts Association...
...as co-sponsor for this event...
...and as the guardians
of a rich and powerful heritage.
After three days...
...one fighter will prove himself
to be the best.
May the mightiest warrior prevail!
Now, remember, it's full-contact.
There are three ways to win.
One, you knock the guy out.
Two, your opponent quits
and shouts, "matte."
It's like saying uncle.
Three, you throw the fucker
right off the runway.
Piece of cake.
Haji!
Hajime!
That's why they call
this thing "bloodsport," kid.
Watch this, Frankie.
I'll show you how it's done, buddy.
Haji!
Asshole.
Hajime!
Come on, get up! Come on!
I'm going to kill you, man!
You got it!
Frankie!
Look at him, buddy. Yeah!
You check that out?
- Good stuff, Jackson.
- Thanks.
But what took you so long?
Funny. Real funny.
Chong Li! Chong Li! Chong Li!
What's going on?
That's Chong Li, the current champ.
He's never been defeated.
Holds all the records,
including the fastest KO.
He killed a guy during the last kumite.
Yeah, kicked the poor bastard
right in the throat.
Guy died right there on the platform.
Chong Li stood there and watched him die.
Junbi!
Haji!
Hajime!
Chong Li! Chong Li! Chong Li!
Now I show you some trick or two.
Junbi!
Haji!
Hajime!
Fastest I ever saw!
His first fight in the kumite,
he broke the fucking world record!
My buddy!
Junbi!
Haji!
Hajime!
Go home!
This is real good stuff.
How's your eel, as good as mine?
I don't know, I haven't tasted it yet.
You gotta tell them to kill it first.
You should ask for forks.
Inspector Chen.
What a pleasant surprise. Please join us.
No. I never eat here.
I found some information for you.
What is it, Inspector?
Frank Dux is at the East Lake Hotel
in Kowloon.
Thank you.
Hey, have some eel.
Okay, Dux, you know why we're here.
We're taking you back, Frank. Let's go.
Only when the kumite is over.
Who the hell are these two scumbags?
Just stay out of it, pal.
It's not your business, okay?
I ain't your pal, dickface.
Look, Frank...
...the government has invested
a lot of time and money in you.
Uncle Sam can't afford to let you get hurt.
I won't get hurt.
That's why we're here,
to make sure of that.
Don't make it tough on us.
I'll be in the airport in two days.
That's not good enough.
Frank, read my lips.
We are taking you back now.
Don't make us use 50,000 volts on you.
Excuse me.
You want to shit sparks?
You just stay put, okay?
Stay put.
All those different fighters in one event.
- It sounds wild.
- You'd have to see it to believe it.
Come on, Frank.
Couldn't you just get me in?
I really want this story.
It would mean so much to me.
They have strict rules. No press.
I bet we could think of something.
I doubt it.
You telling me you never break rules?
What do you mean?
Who are Helmer and Rawlins?
Just friends. Why?
They must be very close friends.
They've been inquiring about you
all over Hong Kong.
What do you want from me?
I'd really like you to help me
get into the kumite.
But more than that...
...I'd really like to get to know you.
After all, we have all night.
I have to go.
I know.
Good luck today.
Thanks.
Meet me for dinner again tonight?
Sure.
About the kumite, I'm sorry.
I cannot help you.
It's okay.
I'll get over it.
See you.
Where the hell have you been?
You can't just disappear
in the middle of kumite like that!
I got a rep to uphold, you know.
You and Jackson don't tell me nothing.
You guys are driving me crazy!
Right now, hurry up and change.
Pick a brick, any brick.
I know. The bottom one, right?
See? Not a scratch on it.
Neither is this.
For you.
Yo, Frankie.
I hope we don't bump heads.
Come on, let's do it, buddy.
Feel strong today?
I feel fine.
Good. You're a good fighter.
- Good.
- Thanks.
This isn't the first time
I've had to go undercover to get a story.
Chong Li! Chong Li!
Junbi!
Haji!
Hajime!
All right, Frankie! Yeah!
Dux! Dux!
Time to separate the men from the boys.
Just be careful Chong Li doesn't separate
your head from your body.
Go for the gut. He's soft there.
What are you talking about?
Chong Li's weak in the gut.
That's how Parades surprised him.
You listening to me?
Go for the stomach
and stay away from his right leg.
Will you stop worrying, Frankie?
I've got it under control.
You sound like my mother. Man alive.
Junbi!
Haji!
Hajime!
I got him!
What are you doing? Keep going!
Jackson! Jackson!
I put him down!
He's dead! I got him! Yeah!
No! Stop!
Chong Li! Chong Li!
Come back, Frank!
Ray, I'm here.
The doctor says you're going to be okay.
You are lucky you have a head like a rock.
Yeah, you'll be out of here in a week.
I'll get back at Chong Li.
That's a promise.
You think that's what he wants,
someone to share a room with?
Janice, stay out of this.
Frank, I don't want to see you get hurt.
Then don't watch.
If you want to argue, go elsewhere, please.
Sorry.
You're not even trying to understand
what this means to us, are you?
What's to understand about
a bunch of guys...
...who have to prove themselves
by beating each other up?
- Why are you a reporter?
- What does that have to do with it?
Just answer the question.
My father was a reporter.
I was a good writer.
It seemed the right thing to do.
And you want to be the best reporter
you can be, for him and yourself, right?
Yes, that's right.
I'm just trying to be the best I can be.
Not just for me,
for Tanaka, my Shidoshi, too.
Great, Frank, that's just great!
Go right ahead!
I just hope you don't end up like Jackson,
or worse!
But I'm not going to stand around
and watch it.
You're blowing it, Frank.
Forget about the girl.
Forget about getting back
at Chong Li for Ray.
You have a chance to take it all tomorrow.
Do you understand?
You can be the first Westerner
to win this thing.
But you got to have a clear head.
You hear me?
Why are you so interested
in stopping the kumite?
Someone almost got killed there today.
I have a friend fighting in it.
I don't want him to get hurt.
Who is your friend?
His name is...
...Frank Dux.
You guys here for the finals?
There aren't going to be any finals, Dux,
at least not for you.
Don't try to stop me.
We're not. He will.
I didn't come this far to stop now.
You shouldn't have come in the first place.
Take him.
You're really being a hard-ass about this.
Careful.
- Put these on and I won't have to use it.
- It's your last warning.
Inspector, no. We've got to take him back.
Just give us a break.
We've chased you all over Hong Kong.
- Can we stop this?
- Okay, Frank, you win.
But it's wrong what you're doing.
It's a mistake.
I'll meet you at the airport tomorrow.
Now what?
How are we going to stop him?
Follow me.
Time's up. We can't wait any longer.
Give me one more minute.
I give you my word. He'll be here.
We must follow the rules.
Where's Mr. Dux?
I wish everyone would calm down.
I said, he'll be here.
- Too late.
- Too late?
No such thing as too late.
Finally.
- It's about fucking time!
- Sorry.
How do you feel today, Dux?
I feel good.
I am ready.
Dux, my man!
Junbi!
Haji!
Hajime!
Come on!
Well done.
Junbi!
Haji!
Hajime!
You are next.
Prepare the platform for the final match.
This is it, Frank.
You can make history here today.
You okay?
Yeah.
Junbi!
Haji!
You break my record, now I break you.
Like I break your friend.
Hajime!
Get him! Come on!
Get up!
Right on!
Come on!
More!
Up!
Get up, Frankie!
All right!
Say it!
Matte!
All right!
Mr. Dux, you fought with inspiration.
We of the Kokuryukai salute you.
This is for you, Shidoshi.
So you stomped him real good?
Worse.
What do you mean?
He made him say matte.
All right, Frankie!
Don't you get too cocky.
Because you might have to
go up against me next time.
I promise.
You guys are out of your minds!
I'll drink to that!
By the way, next time you fight...
...try to keep your clothes on.
Anytime, anyplace, anywhere...
...if you ever need me, I'll be there.
I love you, my friend.
Me, too.
Take care.
He's not going to show.
Looks like he did it to us again, huh?
Hey, guys!
You coming or what?
You son of a bitch.
You're always late!
You're really a pain in the ass,
you know that?
I'm just glad you're on our side, kid.