Why has your breathing changed papa?
Why? I don't understand.
Mama, where is Rehan?
Why aren't we waiting for him?
Mama why are you crying?
Mama? Papa?
Why are you crying mama?
Papa where are we?
Please let me go from here.
- Is it necessary to do this now?
- Yes Ma'am.
What do we have to do?
Why can't we wait for Rehan? Papa,
where are we? Papa?
I'm getting suffocated here papa.
Please let's go. Mama let's go. Please.
The bomb blast at the President's Palace.
What do we have to do with that?
We don't know anything.
You're still crying mama, please don't.
Please papa get me out. Doctor?
I was going to identify him,
but his state was such that I could not.
So you have to identify him, Zooni.
Is this Rehan?
No! It can't be Rehan. It can't!
Please, don't make my daughter
go through this. Please.
It's compulsory.
Zooni my darling, even this is life.
If only I was a roll of wool
wrapped around her fingers...
That fragrance on your breath is me.
How ever will you stop, not breathe?
How can you love me so much?
How can anyone love another so much?
Don't come close to me,
this storm will destroy you.
Think about it, if I go today
I won't come back tomorrow.
At this time we are at the
Bureau of Military Intelligence.
There is not much information
forthcoming on the blast...
...but here is the head of the
Anti-Terrorist Unit.
Mr. Susheel Rawat. Mr. Rawat.
What can you tell us about the blast?
When we know more.
We'll tell you more.
But something to go on,
who is responsible.
These media people.
They start 24 hour channels
and then get after us to fill the time.
Everything is under control.
Sir, Tyagi has been called from
intelligence agency RAW
Tyagi? Now things will be out of control.
So Tyagi, case solved yet?
So what does your psychology
mumbo-jumbo say?
This is his work.
Who? Who are you talking about?
These two are telling the truth.
They haven't seen him.
They were simply given instructions.
The master planner is someone else.
Do you need an invitation
to tell me his name? Who is it?
This man has changed the face of the IKF.
He has taken a rag-tag group
and made it a professional organization.
A group on par with the most
deadly in the world.
On par with the best
intelligence agencies in the world.
It's because of this man that 8 ships and...
...a large part of the Bombay port
are under water.
It's because of this man
that Islamabad airport's...
...new wing was destroyed even
before it could be completed.
He has changed the face of terrorism
in India and Pakistan
Those blood shot eyes and...
...fanatical terrorists are a thing of the past.
This man is a thinker. A planner.
No one knows his name.
No one knows his past,
or where he comes from.
He can be anyone.
The man sitting next to you on the train...
...or a bank teller, or even the
cigarette seller outside.
He is intelligent and he's dangerous,
and he can be anyone.
We have to find him.
For if we don't, he can take
terrorism to a level beyond...
...our imagination because our
imagination is be nothing like his.
I'm sorry Grandfather, the mission
was not entirely successful.
I had set everything.
Those fools just didn't follow instructions.
Not everyone can be like my grandson.
A perfect soldier.
But even he slipped this once.
That too for some woman.
It's very unusual that
you were carried away like this.
And the woman what about her?
She is with God.
Now listen to me.
You don't have to worry about this soldier sir.
My concentration was, is...
...and will always remain
on our independence.
I am a soldier and nothing else.
That's all I wanted to hear my son.
Now I'll meet you after the Bangkok operation.
May God keep you.
You had taken me to my goal, Zooni.
Should never have taken you off that train.
But I became weak.
And I fell in love with you.
I hope you can forgive me.
I should never have brought you
into my life. Never.
God be with you, Zooni.
You are the Defence Secretary.
Do something.
Get that Tyagi off my back!
Last year the Al-Qaeda's attempt
on Delhi airport...
...was foiled by Tyagi.
She got lucky, once.
And now she thinks she's a
big shot intelligence officer.
I can't do anything now.
The Defence Minister himself
has asked hereto be on this case.
Sir, it's nothing less than the Armageddon.
The press shouldn't even get a whiff of this.
This IKF has made our life hell.
First the President Palace bombing...
...then Karachi Oil refinery
and last year it was the...
...plane hijacking. And now we hear
they've stolen parts from us,
Pakistan and Russia and are ready
with a nuclear missile!
Sir, This is their way of forcing India
out of Kashmir.
When Kashmir's ruler, Hari Singh,
decided to join India...
...in 1947, then why this talk of
independence now?
But the Kashmiri's had also been
promised a vote,
a referendum to decide
whether they wanted to stay a...
...part of India, join Pakistan
or then be independent.
All these years later they are
still to get that referendum.
What referendum are you talking about?
When half of Kashmir is occupied
by Pakistan, how is it possible?
A referendum needs
to include all of Kashmir,
why should it include only half?
This is not an India-Pakistan
issue any more.
IKF wants both India and Pakistan
to leave Kashmir.
They want a separate country.
An independent Kashmir.
Please, I know the history
of India and Pakistan.
Tell me about this bomb.
How powerful is this bomb,
Mrs. Tyagi, and what are the dangers?
In the last few years over 15,000 people
have been killed in Mumbai,
Oklahoma City, New York, Bali,
Madrid and London.
And losses have run into millions.
But if they use this bomb
5 million people can die.
An entire city can be destroyed.
That city can also be our capital, New Delhi.
We must stop this bomb.
Whatever it takes.
But Sir, this bomb is useless for them.
What do you mean?
The missile needs a special,
Indian made trigger.
If they don't have that,
they can't use the bomb
Only until they get the trigger.
Only until then.
Sir, there's nothing to worry about.
Outside of Delhi,
We have 6 triggers at various
military bases around the country.
In Rajasthan, Kutch, Darjeeling,
Amritsar, Leh and Kashmir.
They are safe there.
I want all the triggers brought to Delhi.
In the next 12 hours they will all be here, Sir.
Get me the Defence Minister of Pakistan,
...I want to share this information with him.
We can be sure. Just as we are
taking steps to secure the triggers,
IKF's mastermind will be
taking steps to steal them.
Rate on missions, Sir.
And I will bring this trigger to you myself.
Be alert. IKF will be after you at every step.
If the weather holds up,
the trigger will be...
...with you in 3 hours, Sir.
Glory to India!
This is the day every soldier lives for.
For a chance to serve his country.
The last time you saved me from the IKF.
Today we both must save the
country from the IKF.
This soldier is ready to take
lives or to give his own life.
Anything for his motherland, Sir.
Good news. The trigger will be
with us soon. God keep Rehan!
God is great!
Mummy is fine. How are you?
Mummy will save the country
I know you wanted custard.
But Grandma has made rice...
...pudding with so much love, so please eat it.
What have you brought?
Rice pudding or custard?
We've checked the list of officers
coming from Kashmir.
How can it not be ok?
I have hand-picked these officers.
They are the army's very best, elite forces.
Ok, so that's where he is.
Who?
An ace officer from the Jat Regiment Sir,
Captain Ranjeev.
His wife reported he hadn't called her
for a couple of months.
She wanted to know if he was
on some secret mission.
That's wives for you. Am sure she was
after him with some pudding or such.
Poor man must have needed a break from...
...all that so he didn't call, understandable.
He didn't call his wife for two months?
Just find out,
was his last mission to do with the IKF?
Yes Ma'am. Major Suraj's regiment
was surrounded by the IKF.
At the last moment Captain Ranjeev's
regiment got there and saved them.
Everyone from Captain Ranjeev's regiment
was killed. Only he survived.
That's him! We have to stop him!
Sounds like the base is trying to contact us.
The signal is too weak.
It's amazing isn't it? Such a small thing
can take so many lives.
- Our lives too, in it's defence
- So?
I'm not afraid of dying Sir,
But it's better to kill for your country
than be killed
You want to kill people?
Make them eat your wife's cooking!
You are dying the death of a brave soldier.
He who dies on the battlefield goes to heaven.
God keep you.
Grandfather. I am not empty handed.
Praise be to God! You don't have
just a trigger there with you.
It is our decades long dream.
We have sacrificed so much for.
You must get that trigger to us now
at any cost. Kill, or be killed.
Yes, grandfather. I will meet you in 3 hours...
...At Shikara 1 pick up point. Goodbye.
I was right. That was no accident.
He was in the helicopter.
Jam all the phone lines in the area...
...mobiles, satellite, internet, everything.
I want a communications blackout.
We can't jam radio signals,
we have military operations in that area
If you can't jam them, you can at least
monitor them, can't you?
Search the entire area.
How far is the road unit?
No! He's still alive.
I don't care how many bodies you saw.
I know Rehan will reach the pick up point.
I have not given him permission to die.
He cannot die.
Quickly, call Grandpa.
Go. Fast. Papa!
Hand me the scissors please.
Who is this, mom?
Rehan, I don't know.
Go, please sit over there.
Is he also dead like Grandma?
Quiet! Little monkey
His pulse is quite weak.
Try the phone. Is it working now?
No papa. It's still dead.
We've done the best we could.
I'm no doctor.
What can we do?
You can't go and get a doctor in this weather.
Not 50 kilometres in this storm.
No way.
Mom! Please leave Rehan.
Nothing darling. Nothing
Now it's up to you young man.
We can only pray you have
some reason to live.
It can be two days?
It can be two weeks?
How can you not know when
the storm will pass?
I want an update every hour, you hear?
Can't you do anything right?
Till I don't see a body
I can't believe he's dead.
Don't do that Rehan.
What are you up to?
I can't hear his heartbeat.
There is no heartbeat.
Rehan wants to hear his heartbeat,
like he hears Grandpa's.
The heart is not here, it's there.
Forgive me Zooni. I have no choice.
Do you know the cricketer Rahul Dravid?
Rahul Dravid is Rehan's father.
Because Rehan's father is dead you see,
...so mom said Rehan could choose any father.
So Rehan chose Rahul Dravid.
Are you Mr. Dependiddle like Rahul Dravid?
Can you also be completely
trusted like Rahul Dravid?
That outhouse of yours is falling apart.
Look, look the dead man is awake.
Don't talk like that.
When the weather is better
we'll get it fixed. It's freezing.
Before you thank me.
Come and eat something.
Don't drink so much
you'll become a hittototomas.
Not hittototomas, kid. Hippopotamus.
And where did you learn this word?
From Colonel uncle.
Hitto. Hittototomas.
Would you like something?
I'm sorry I didn't get your name.
I didn't know there were military
operations here.
There are such few of us here.
What will the militants do here?
They can hide.
The dead man stinks so Rehan thought...
Strange, when Zooni couldn't see
she didn't bang into a thing.
And now that she can see,
she's constantly walking into things.
Thank you for saving me.
You were lucky, so you survived.
What did I do?
Is it just the 3 of you here?
Zooni's mother died a couple of years ago.
And left me all alone.
And before that her husband
died in a bomb blast.
I don't know why, but Zooni
blames herself for his death.
When will this storm end?
I must leave from here.
It's hard to say. It might stop
tomorrow or maybe a week.
Don't think of leaving in this
weather though.
Certainly not in your state.
Rest a while. You are our guest.
Dispenser of India's destiny.
You keep teaching me things.
Tell Rehan a story.
...Dispenser of India's destiny
You're not a good mother.
You never tell Rehan stories.
I don't know any stories.
Not me. You. You're a bad boy.
Go. I'm not talking to you.
Rehan loves you more than
you love Rehan.
But mom Rehan already knows
the national anthem.
Let's hear it.
Thou art the ruler of the minds of
all the people... Dravid,
...Orissa and Bengal. Dravid, Orissa and Bengal.
You and your Dravid fixation.
Dravid, Orissa and Bengal.
Do you know the national anthem?
No.
See even the dead man doesn't know
the national anthem.
Please tell mom, not to teach Rehan.
The phone's dead. Tell her not to teach Rehan.
What's this?
Which soldier doesn't know
the national anthem?
Why are you lying to the child?
I am not here to teach him
the national anthem,
...and I'm not here to play with him.
I don't care if I lied to him...
...I'm a soldier on a mission not his father!
Come here immediately!
If you don't eat vegetables
how will you slay the dragon?
Captain Ranjeev, come and join us.
Tell us about your life.
I've heard soldiers have
fascinating stories to tell.
I'm not hungry thank you.
I'll just go to bed.
Your bed has been made upstairs.
The room on the left.
Dead man made mom cry.
Eat your food.
What's this?
Mom has sent it for you.
So you'll get better faster...
...so you can leave faster.
But what is it?
Poison.
Milk with turmeric.
And don't try and throw it in the WC,
it stinks it up and mom finds out.
Don't throw it out either,
the snow gets yellow.
And in the wash basin the colour stains it,
you'll get caught.
And yes! If you find some other way.
Please tell Rehan.
Next time Rehan will do the same.
It really is poison.
"Come closer now,
I will not come back again and again"
"Put your arms around me,
so I can cry again and again"
If only I was a roll of wool...
...wrapped around her fingers...
"Think we will never meet again, just suppose,
not till this lifetime is forever closed"
"Come into my arms, hold me close,
we may never again have the night's repose."
"Think we'll never meet again, just suppose,
not till this lifetime is forever closed."
Thank you.
Yesterday I was very rude.
Actually, I'm not very good with children.
Am not very good with words either.
But I am good with a hammer.
Not everything can be done alone.
Rehan doesn't have a father...
...so he sometimes...
he won't trouble you again.
He's a good kid.
So have you forgiven me then?
Thing is, I spend so much time alone...
...that I don't know how to behave
in company any more.
Like this one time I went to my friend
Mihir Wohra's house for a party.
I asked his wife how she likes
being wife number 2.
Turns out she was wife number 1 and
had no idea there was a wife number 2.
After this I decided I would stick to
safe topics.
So I asked my Colonel how his son
was doing at school?
Now that's safe? Right?
Wrong. Just that day his son
had been thrown...
...out of school, for biting his teacher's bum.
And not just that.
He was sent back to apologise the...
...following day and he ended up
biting her other bum.
Close your eyes.
Rehan doesn't want to wash his hair.
Rehan will not wash his hair.
You have to wash your hair or you’ll get
such big, big insects in it.
Let them come Rehan will take the
insects for a walk every day.
May I help?
Give it a try.
I'm not talking to you I'm talking to him.
He's such a sweet kid.
Why are you bothering him.
But he has to wash his hair.
He'll wash it when he feels like it.
Rehan! Look up.
You were right.
Everything can't be done alone.
Dead man is funny.
Don't call him dead man, son.
Rehan likes the dead man.
Can I help you?
I'm fine. Thanks.
Everything can't be done alone.
You told us some good stories today.
Why have you stopped telling stories?
Your father talks a lot after a
couple of drinks.
Earlier I couldn't see. Now I've seen
too much to believe in stories.
Your family must be worried.
You've been missing for a few days.
I have no family, I never met my parents.
They died when I was 3.
I'm sorry you're so Lonely.
Not at all. Why do you say that?
Your smile doesn't reach your eyes.
A soldier's life is like that.
There must be someone else
hidden behind that soldier
Perhaps. But, I don't think
I really understand him.
Sometimes to understand yourself, you need to
see yourself from someone else's eyes.
I could never get that close to anyone.
Why? You couldn't trust anyone?
I don't trust myself.
And then every time, a new mission, a new city.
I couldn't be in any one place for too long
Sometimes you seem very familiar.
The moon booms, blooms, balloons,
of fright freaks the thieving thief
The silly ant sucks sugar,
silly sugar sucking ant for sure.
The moon booms, blooms, balloons,
of fright freaks the thieving thief.
The silly ant sucks sugar,
silly sugar sucking ant for sure.
A difficult song this is, can you sing it for me pure.
Moon blooms sugar sucking
creams the thieving thief.
The moon booms, blooms, balloons,
of fright freaks the thieving thief.
The silly ant sucks sugar,
silly sugar sucking ant for sure.
Surly Khadak Singh simmers
and stutter sputter go the shutters.
Stutter sputter go the shutters making
surly Khadak Singh simmer.
Surely Khadak Singh simmers
and stutter sputter go the shutters.
Stutter sputter go the shutters making
surly Khadak Singh simmer.
A difficult song this is,
can you sing it for me pure.
Stutter sputter go the shutters.
Surely Khadak Singh simmers more.
The moon booms, blooms, balloons,
of fright freaks the thieving thief.
The silly ant sucks sugar,
silly sugar sucking ant for sure.
The moon booms, blooms, balloons,
of fright freaks the thieving thief.
The silly ant sucks sugar,
illy sugar sucking ant for sure.
Ripe Papaya upon the ripe tree.
Tree ripe or ripe Papaya?
The ripe tree Pinkoo picks.
Pinkoo picks the ripe Papaya.
Say it.
Ripe Papaya upon the ripe tree
picks 'Pinkoo ripe kapda'.
Kapda? Cloth?
Ripe Papaya upon the ripe tree,
pick on tree or Papaya ripe?
Pinkoo picks the ripe tree,
pinkoo picks the Papaya ripe.
A difficult song this is,
can you sing it for me pure.
Pinkoo picks the ripe tree...
Pinkoo picks the Papaya ripe.
The moon booms, blooms, balloons,
of fright freaks the thieving thief.
The silly ant sucks sugar,
silly sugar sucking ant for sure.
The moon booms, blooms, balloons,
if fright freaks the thieving thief.
The silly ant sucks sugar,
silly sugar sucking ant for sure.
A difficult song this is,
can you sing it for me pure.
The moon booms blooms, balloons...
...of fright freaks the thieving thief.
The moon booms, blooms, balloons,
of fright freaks the thieving thief.
The silly ant sucks sugar,
silly sugar sucking ant for sure.
Rehan will not call him dead man any more.
You're my good son.
Can Rehan call dead man, papa? Please?
Close your eyes.
So tell me Captain Ranjeev,
have you ever loved...
...a woman so deeply that
her smile made you breathless?
I...
I loved my Nafisa like that. She was...
Heavenly!
Papa, you've started again. I've told you...
...not to drink in front of mama's photograph.
"Let me sit and drink on the Mosque ground...
...or show me a place where God is not found"
Fantastic! Superb!
"In this life without you I have no...
Complaint."
No complaint, I have no complaint.
Enough papa, enough.
What are you doing?
We're having such a nice time.
Let's go, papa.
Let me finish this drink. "In this life
without you I have no complaint.
But this life without you is no life anyway..."
"I wish I could bury my head in
your veil and cry, just cry..."
"Are you sure your eyes themselves
don't lack in tears, are dry, just dry?"
The letter 'H'
"How do you do, dear one?
How do you think, dear one?
I'm just happy oh ho ho.
So, you've slipped then aa ha ha."
"What if I let my heart live in your eyes?
What if I close my eyes,
and punish your heart?"
"What can I say in praise of
the one who made you?"
"These nights, this clime,
this river side, this playful breeze"
"Time has given us such beautiful pain.
...I am not me anymore and
you are not the same.
Our hearts tremble now as they meet.
Like they were never apart for even a beat.
But you got lost and so did I.
After our travel together..."
Now you're scared.
Who are you? How do you know all this?
You can't know. What's happening to me?
I hear him in your voice,
your breath, it's all the same.
It's me. Rehan.
Your Rehan.
What I did to you.
I've never forgiven myself for it.
I promised myself I'd stay away from you.
I didn't want to cause you more pain.
Perhaps it was God's justice that
I had to die at your doorstep.
But you kept me alive.
And now I want to live.
I want to live for you, for our son.
Rehan... You are Rehan?
My real name is Rehan Qadri.
Kashmiri?
Yes.
Go on.
When I met Zooni I was on a mission.
And that's why you fell in love
with my daughter?
Promised her marriage?
Was that all a part of your mission?
That was my weakness.
I was not free to love.
I am deeply sorry and ashamed
about my selfish love.
And you've come back to
repeat that mistake?
My mission is not complete yet.
After this storm, it will be.
Then I will stay with Zooni
for the rest of my life.
Mission! Mission!
What is this great mission...
Because of which you're
playing with all our lives?
I can't say.
What?
I know my silence can go against me.
But I do not want to lie and
I cannot tell you the truth.
All I can say in my defence
is that my love is true.
I have given you a lot of pain,
still I am asking you to fill my wounds.
I know I'm not worthy of your forgiveness...
...but I stand before you with the hope
that you will forgive me.
I would not have left my Nafisa for anything.
God came in the way otherwise
I would've still been with her.
There is no reason to believe him,
but there is also no reason not to.
It was your decision then Zooni
and it's your decision now.
7 years! 7 years I have lived with the guilt
that I sent you to your death.
Every day I curse my self for
sending you there.
Do you know what it's like to live with that?
Look at this!
When you were off being a great soldier...
...on your missions this is what I was doing.
I was taking parts of all these faces,
trying to make one face. Your face.
So I could have something to cry in front of,
something to show my son.
To tell him this is your father.
And now you say all those tears,
all that pain was for nothing? No!
Why should I open myself to pain again Rehan?
Why should I take you back?
Give me one good reason
why I shouldn't believe you are still dead.
Give me one good reason.
I don't have a single good reason.
They are all bad. Each and every one.
I was taking parts of all these faces,
trying to make one face.
Why are you going?
Because I can't play cricket like Rahul Dravid.
Don't worry. Rehan will teach you.
I am not dependiddle either.
I can't be trusted.
No you are dependable for Rehan.
See Rehan has learned how to say dependable.
Rehan will never trouble you again.
He won't call you dead man.
He will have a bath himself.
He will not give you milk and turmeric,
but please don't go.
Rehan loves you more than you love Rehan.
Sit properly!
Eat!
Why are you venting your anger on him?
The one who deserves it has left
without saying a word.
He must be in his room.
Go tell him breakfast is ready.
I'm not going to stand around
in the kitchen all day for him.
He's gone. He said goodbye to Rehan.
Not to you.
No, he can't go. He can't go.
How dare you leave me again.
How dare you?
Your life is mine now, do you hear?
You can never leave me and go. Never!
Papa!
When I have your hands in mine.
I have with me the heavens divine.
When you're close, this world is naught.
Destroyed in your love, a triumph sought.
When I have your hands in mine.
I have with me the heavens divine.
When you're close this world is naught.
Destroyed in your love, a triumph sought.
When I have your hands in mine.
I have with me the heavens divine.
May my life's-breath find refuge in your heart.
Destroyed in your love may my life depart.
As close as fragrances are to breath.
As close as songs are to lips.
As close as sleepless nights to memories.
As close as arms are to embraces.
As close, as close as dreams to eyes.
Be that close to me, oh love of mine.
When you're close this world is naught.
Destroyed in your love, a triumph sought.
When I have your hands in mine.
I have with me the heavens divine.
Let my eyes swell with tears, let me cry today.
Take me in your arms, get drenched today.
The sea of pain trapped in my heart will explode.
I have so much pain your veil will be drenched.
As close as secrets are to heartbeats.
As close as raindrops are to clouds.
As close as the moon is to night.
As close as kohl is to eyes.
As close, as close as waves to the ocean.
Be that close to me, oh love of mine.
When you're close this world is naught.
Destroyed in your love, a triumph sought.
When I have your hands in mine.
I have with me the heavens divine.
My breath was incomplete, heartbeat incomplete,
incomplete was I.
But now the moon is full, complete in the sky,
and now with you complete am I...
Give us some good news Aakash.
Can we go any further?
Sorry ma'am, we'll have to wait
another 2 or 3 days.
But we have to do something Aakash.
We can't just stand around.
No. Not the press. We can't talk to the
media about the bomb yet.
The order's come directly from Delhi.
We can't talk about the bomb
but we can talk about him.
Aakash! Inform the press.
Newspaper, Radio, TV.
The search is on for a terrorist
hiding in the outskirts of Srinagar.
This terrorist is badly wounded
and is wearing an army uniform.
He is also carrying an electronic part.
If you have any information
on this man please...
...contact your nearest police station immediately.
Come on Rehan, drink your milk.
Rehan loves you more than you love Rehan.
No, I love Rehan much more than that
and he has to drink this milk.
And what about this Rehan?
At this time?
Colonel? At this time?
What's the matter?
I have risked life and come here
for a very important reason.
I've run out of rum!
The games destiny plays with us.
And if one is in the army their...
...destiny is not in their hands anyway. Cheers!
Rehan, if you like you can come
to my house and radio your unit.
You have a radio transmitter?
Meet the man who lives
in the middle of nowhere...
...and keeps a radio to keep in touch with people.
Always wonder why he lives out here.
It's late today. It'll be dark
by the time you return.
It's dark already.
Ok, so it's night already.
Come tomorrow. The weather...
...should be clearer as well.
Come and radio your unit then.
There's no need for that.
Why not?
He has just returned after 7 years.
I don't want...
...him to disappear for another 7.
You are trying to guard a soldier is it?
Rehan, do you want me to radio them?
No, I'll have to do it myself.
Of course, of course.
Let him give his status report then you...
...can keep him imprisoned here
forever, right Rehan?
Fine, now no more discussion.
What do they say in Punjabi?
Let's have a whopper of a drink.
Where's your father?
He was to take me to colonels' house.
Do you really have to go?
Just this last bit of work.
Papa takes a while to get ready.
He'll be down soon. Papa!
Once upon a time there was a prince,
and a princess who was blind.
Mom, you are telling a story?
One day the princess
met an ordinary man who...
...followed different monuments
in different cities.
But the princess saw the prince
hidden in that ordinary man.
What was the prince's name?
Rehan.
The prince saved the princess
from a huge, scary dragon.
The dragon had a big, red face.
Every time he opened his mouth...
...gigantic balls of fire would come out of it.
What was the dragon's name?
Grandpa!
Come on Rehan, let's go to the
Colonel's and radio your unit.
The search is on for a terrorist hiding
in the outskirts of Srinagar.
This terrorist is wearing an army uniform.
He is also carrying an electronic part.
Grandpa, Rehan loves you very much.
I will have to go for a couple of days
to hand in my resignation.
Whether or not you're on this mission,
the IKF will definitely loose.
Terrorists can never win.
That's the thing. These people are not terrorists.
They are fighting for their independence.
And who will run this country of theirs?
The IKF?
No. Whoever the people of Kashmir elect.
In fair elections.
It seems you're not against the IKF,
you're for of them.
You are a traitor.
You may be my daughter's husband,
...but I'll gladly kill you.
I was doubtful when I saw the news on the TV,
but by then it was too late.
I had my doubts. But today I was certain...
...when I found this trigger in your pocket.
You can't do anything now.
I am going to radio the...
...military and hand you over.
Colonel! Colonel!
Please sir, give me that trigger.
All this will be over in a couple of days.
Then I can stay with Zooni
and Rehan forever.
I'd rather they be dead.
I'll never give you this. Never.
Don't you dare, Rehan!
No!!
My son. Rehan!
God be praised a million times.
You're alive! Do you have what I want?
Yes, I have it with me.
What's the matter?
I'm tired that's all.
I just want all this to end.
Look here...
I know what I have to do.
Come here and take what it is you want.
The coordinates here are loc rep 34,74...
...mount 2730, 500 house.
That was him. Thank God
he hasn't reached his people yet.
There is very heavy fog right now. We'll try and be...
...there tomorrow morning.
God be with you.
Sorry ma'am he gave his location in code.
We'll need some time to break it.
Give Ranade the code to break.
Keep the ground search going.
And continue monitoring the
frequency he called from.
We only have till tomorrow morning.
Contact the base camp.
Are they ready with the sketch of the
impostor of Captain Ranjeev?
Papa!!
Papa! Someone help us please!
Mom, what's happened?
Papa! Papa!
Mom! What happened?
Nothing, go watch some TV.
Rehan. Papa...
I've just left him at Colonel uncle's.
They're both drinking rum.
He said he'll stay there tonight.
The search is on for a terrorist
hiding in the outskirts of Srinagar.
This terrorist is badly wounded
and is wearing an army uniform.
He went missing 8 days ago.
He has an electronic part with him.
This is a sketch of him provided by the army.
If you see this man anywhere
please don't try and catch him your self.
He is armed and dangerous.
Please contact your nearest police...
...station immediately.
Or call this number.
Hello! Hello! Can someone hear me?
Ma'am someone is sending an
SOS from the same frequency.
Hello. Hello. Yes we read you.
Hello, can someone hear me?
Hello, yes, we can hear you.
I am Malini Tyagi from the
anti terrorist special forces. Who is this?
I am Zooni Ali Beg. My husband.
I thought he was dead.
But he came back 9 days ago.
I think he's the one you are looking for.
He may have killed my father
and my uncle. Or not.
I don't know. Just please help us.
I am alone. It's just me and my son.
Zooni, Zooni don't panic.
And listen to me carefully.
Does your husband have
some sort of an electronic part?
Yes, I saw it on TV. It's with me.
It's him. Your husband is the one
we are looking for. He is the terrorist.
Listen to me carefully Zooni.
I am going to tell you the most...
...important thing you will ever hear.
If he leaves with that trigger,
...if he joins his comrades they will...
...use a nuclear bomb over our country.
Millions of Indians will die.
One of them can be my daughter.
Another can be your son.
There will be complete destruction...
...and the only one who can
stop it Zooni, is you!
But, he is my husband.
Tell me you will help us Zooni.
Tell me you will stop him.
Whatever it takes.
Yes.
We have your location now Zooni.
We know where you are...
...we'll be there tomorrow morning.
Ok.
Who are you running away from?
From me? From your Rehan?
I have only one Rehan. My son.
Papa? What happened?
Nothing son. Everything is fine.
What's the point?
You'll kill him as well.
I'd rather die first.
You killed Papa quite easily.
I didn't kill him.
It was an accident.
And Colonel Uncle?
Give me the trigger Zooni.
No.
Give me that trigger!
What will you do?
Kill me as well? Kill me.
I've already died once because of you,
why not once again.
Zooni, despite all my lies.
Despite all the pain I have given you.
Do you believe that I love you?
Then for the sake of that love.
You have to do what I say.
If you don't give me that trigger...
...then they will torture and
kill Rehan right in front of us.
Then they'll kill you in front of me.
Then if they have any mercy,
then they will kill me too
And the person to do all this
will be no stranger.
My own grandfather will destroy
his family with his own hands.
I don't care about myself Zooni,
but I am not willing to
sacrifice Rehan or you.
This is the only way we'll be able to
live our lives in peace again.
And what about the lives of those millions
that will die from the bomb?
No one will use the bomb. It's just a threat.
The governments...
...of India and Pakistan will have
no other choice, but to give in.
After all your lies, how can I believe you now?
Grandfather
Or the Indian army whom I called.
No. Grandfather.
You can't leave.
Take care of Rehan and yourself.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Rehan! Please for our son's sake. Stop!
Why Rehan? Why?
Rehan loves you more than you love Rehan.
Don't say that. Please don't.
Now I'm not scared.
When I have your hands in mine
I have with me heavens divine
When you're close this world is naught
Destroyed in your love, a triumph sought
It's easy to choose
between right and wrong.
But to choose the greater of two goods...
...or the lesser of two evils.
Those are the choices of our life.
Rehan loves you very much
And Zooni loves Rehan very much.