Come on, Kelly, let's go.
Let's get the hot food
out to the customers.
Who the hell
eats hot dog food, anyway?
What the--you stupid moron!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Why don't you watch
what you're doing?
What do you need--
a red light and a green light?
Come on.
Get this stuff cleared up.
Jeez, how many times...
Vicky! l don't believe it!
What are you doing here?
How have you been?
God, you look great.
Look at you.
Thanks. You know, the one good
thing about dancing in Vegas...
is it does keep you in shape.
-lt's been a while.
-Yeah, it has been a long time.
But l see you haven't
lost any of your moves.
l'm keeping in shape.
l figure l still have
a few good months left in me.
l am pushing 20, you know.
Have you thought
about a second career?
Never. l'll die on my toes.
Dancing or...working here?
Look, all l know is
you're slaving away...
in this grease trap,
and you're not dancing.
You know, l still have
Franco's classes...
and they're so important to me.
Are you still with Franco?
Yeah. He's the best.
At dancing, maybe. You forget
who you're talking to.
l know the routine.
lt's the same thing
with all the girls.
l don't want to get
heavy-handed...
but you be careful of him.
-Kelly!
-l have to go.
Listen, there's a friend
of mine--James Wilcox.
He's an agent here in L.A.
Give him a call.
He might be able to help.
Kelly!
Down here.
That's it. Now!
Down here. Come on, Kelly.
Come on. You're leading them.
Now, reach back. You're late.
That's it. Come on.
That's it. Turn. Reach.
Use the whole body.
Come on. Move across now.
Cross the floor. Back. Come on.
Up. Now, that's it.
Up, down. Hit the floor.
Back...and down.
Reach. That's it.
Pull back. Come on.
Come on, now.
Reach across. And hup 3, hup 5,
hup down, hup 2...
hup back!
That's it. Thank you.
-l'm serious.
-Just get out of here.
Come on. You promised.
l know.
You're looking better.
You still got to learn
to relax, though.
-l'll work at it.
-Loosen up.
Let the music caress you
when you move.
Look, l got a couple of minutes.
You want to stay and work?
-l'm sorry. l've got to go.
-Kelly...
l'm a very good teacher.
lf there's anybody who knows
what you need, it's me.
Nothing but the best
for the best, huh, baby?
l know someone
who'd argue that point.
Did mommy forget
to pick you up again?
Cute, Kelly. Some people
love you for your body.
Me, it's your charming wit.
So what did Our Almightiness
want this time?
lt wasn't my charming wit,
Cupcakes.
Do you want to go for a bite?
No. actually,
l was supposed to meet...
some dear,
close friends of mine...
but it's way out in Venice...
and l'd hate to take you
out of your way.
l'll ride the bus.
Well, at least let me drop
you off at the bus stop.
Really, Kelly, l think
you'd love to meet these guys.
They're terrific.
l guarantee you they won't want
you for your body or your wit.
That's a relief.
But l'd definitely keep
an eye on your purse.
Nice, Cupcakes. Nice.
You promised me
you wouldn't call me that.
l can't help it.
You're just so cute.
Would you stop?
There they are over there.
l tell you, Kelly,
you're really gonna love this.
Hurry up. l don't want
you to miss anything.
-Should l wear my coat?
-No. You don't need it.
Come on.
Come on. Up here.
-Ozone!
-Hey, Adam!
Hey, man, Adam!
What's happenin'?
Nothing much, man.
This is Kelly.
Hi.
Come on. Let's do some of
the stuff we do in class.
-Oh, no. You kidding?
-Come on. lt'll be fun.
-Not here.
-Come on!
Five, six, seven, eight.
Come on.
Watch him.
-l can't do that.
-Try. OK. All right!
Come on, Kelly. Get down.
Show us what you got.
-All right, Miss Bennett!
-Good!
Go turn 'em out, man.
Kelly.
Get 'em!
Come on.
-Let's go.
-Let's get out of here.
-Let's go get something to eat.
-OK.
Ozone, wait up.
What's up, dude?
Who was that guy?
That was nothing.
Hey, wasn't she hot?
Oh, God. l feel so silly.
No, you were good.
Hey, wasn't she hot, Turbo?
You guys weren't
so bad yourselves.
Oh, allow me. Kelly...
the mean machine right there--
that's Turbo.
Hi. What kind of names
are Ozone and Turbo?
The kind of names
that only a few people...
are allowed to call us by.
-They're our street names.
-All the dancers have them.
Really? Well, then why
do you get so upset...
when l call you Cupcakes?
Cupcakes!
All right, enough already.
Well, l've got to run.
l've got a lot of things to do.
Thanks for the dance.
Sure. Anytime.
Maybe we'll see you again, huh?
-Maybe.
-And who knows?
With a little work,
you'll be poppin' and lockin'...
and breakin' in no time.
You owe me one, Miss Bennett.
l'll see you later.
Special K!
What?
Special K. Any good dancer
has a street name.
Man, l should have got
her number. Look at her.
What are we doing here?
We're gonna see Adam tonight.
Do you think l'm here
to see Adam?
What, are you falling
in love again?
No, man. l just like the way
she dances, all right?
Girls!
Don't you worry. l got
the finest dancers available.
ln fact, l suspect it's not even
going to be a contest.
No, l...
l think that l can guarantee you
that we're going to win.
Well, this is a surprise.
Hi, Ozone. Hi, Turbo.
The name's Tony.
OK, Tony. l had
a great time yesterday.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. lt was different.
Listen, l got
to get back to work.
You guys probably
ought to leave...
'cause if Franco comes
in here and sees you...
l'll get in a lot of trouble.
Hey, that dancing's fresh.
-lt's what?
-lt's bad!
Wait a minute, now.
Hey, Turbo!
Hey! What's up?
You want to waste your time,
do it someplace else...
but don't mess with mine.
-Who are you?
-The name's Tony.
Well, as long as
you're standing there...
you're wasting my time,
and my time ain't cheap...
so l suggest you clear out now.
lf you want to take my class...
your name goes
on a waiting list.
lf you want to talk to him,
you talk to me.
And who might you be?
Orlando--
choreographer...dancer.
So this bit
of amateur dancing...
that my class was
so privileged to witness...
was your conception.
Come on, man.
Let's get out of here.
Since we're all here...
why don't you show us
what you've got?
-You owe me $7.00, man.
-Yeah? What for?
For teaching you
how to dance, sucker.
Class dismissed.
Don't worry about it.
They ain't nothin'.
Do you know, if we put them
on the streets, we'd burn 'em.
l'm sorry about what happened.
l tried to get them to leave.
Why were they here?
l guess they came to see me.
-You know those guys?
-l just met them once.
Well, l'd keep it that way.
Forget it.
You want to hear the music for
the show l'm choreographing?
-You got it!
-Yeah.
All right! Congratulations.
That's great.
You know, l may seem
tough sometimes...
but there's always a reason.
You know that, don't you?
Yeah, l know.
You know, those street kids
haven't got what it takes.
They're very talented. You
really should see them dance.
lt takes more than talent.
You got to be tough.
Now, you...
You've got the talent.
Head up.
Caress me. More passion.
Take the floor. Dance.
Dance...across the floor.
That's it. Now, jump.
Come on, fly.
Feel it! Up.
That's it. Now you got it.
All right, over here.
More emotion. To the mirror.
Feel it. All right,
now turn around.
That's it.
What are you doing?!
Franco, stop!
-Kelly, l just...
-Just get away from me!
Go to hell!
Goddamn it!
l'd like to thank you
for this award.
lt's the recognition
of my peers...
that makes all those agonizing
days of teaching Ozone...
everything l know that--
l don't want to stay here
all night. Do you?
Award winners don't push brooms.
Oh, yeah? Why don't you
go out and sweep, man?
Who do you think you are,
anyway--Fred Astaire?
Who?
Just go on and sweep,
knucklehead.
Hey, Turbo, did you
finish sweeping up?
-Yeah.
-You sure?
Yeah. You want to come
see for yourself?
All right, man.
Man, look at this stuff.
Look at that cup
right there, man.
Uh-oh. We've got company.
You guys are dirt, man.
We'll put you under.
Yeah. You're looking
at the piranha.
We're gonna eat you and...
spit out the pieces
we don't like.
Oh, yeah? Show me, man.
Come on, sucker, right now.
You want some?
Then come and get it.
Why don't you punks just split?
l think l hear
your mama calling you.
You don't like what you see?
Yeah, we're the dudes
gonna put you under.
Yeah. You're looking
at death, man.
You'll have to put a bag over
that face to hide the shame.
Anytime, man!
Friday night.
Be there...
unless you're chicken.
Hey, face, who are
you callin' chicken?
l won't blame you
if you don't show up...
'cause it's gonna be
real messy.
Oh, yeah...
and bring your girlfriend
the dancer...
'cause you're gonna need
a shoulder to cry on.
Come on.
Let's show those heifers.
Man, those dudes are whacked.
They don't deserve
the right to go against us.
But you heard them.
They called us chicken.
Well, those dudes will just
have to wait their turn...
now, won't they?
What about Friday?
We're not gonna back down.
Yeah, well, if those dudes
come Friday...
and they cross that line,
we're gonna cut 'em.
We're wasting our time, man,
on a bunch of nobodies.
You heard them.
They think they're so bad.
They're punks.
We don't got nothin' to prove.
Look, they put us down.
We can't go back on that.
Why not?
Man, everybody will bag
on us if we back down.
What are you worried about?
You're the best, right?
All right. Let's turn
these fools out, man.
Come on! Let's hit it.
Hi, Kelly.
Hi. Hope you didn't
come here to eat.
Oh, no way. l respect my body.
l've missed you in class lately.
Been busy. Has me working
double shifts now.
Franco's been acting a little
weird the last few days.
So what's so unusual about that?
-Well?
-Well, what?
Well, did anything
happen between you two?
No! l'm just ready for a change.
l feel my life getting stale.
Stale? Like that hamburger
if the customer doesn't get it.
Hey, Earring.
You gonna order something?
Yeah. l guess l'll have
the...Health Department.
My father just happens
to work for them.
This is the kind of place
that would make his mouth drool.
lf you want anything,
it's on the house.
Thanks.
God damn. The earring prince
here thinks he...
-Adam! l do have some good news.
-And what's that?
l'm going to see an agent
about some work.
Kelly, that's great!
Maybe some of these years of
training will start to pay off.
Well, Kelly,
these pictures are very good.
You're very photogenic.
You want to get serious
about your dancing?
-Have you danced professionally?
-Well, once.
Did you ever see the ''Dancing
Doggie'' dog food commercial?
Let's just say you have
no professional experience.
l think we should pursue...
the dance possibilities
here in town.
Allow me to set up
a few auditions.
You can make the rounds,
get your feet wet.
-What do you think?
-Sounds great to me.
OK, so l'll set up a few
appointments this week.
We'll see you later, OK?
Thank you, Miss Bennett.
You were excellent.
Unfortunately, the part
calls for a tall blonde.
Thank you. You were excellent.
Unfortunately,
we're looking for--
A short brunette.
This isn't worth it.
Blonde, brunette--
if they're looking for hair...
why don't they look at gorillas?
Don't let it get to you, Kelly.
There will be more auditions.
Not for this girl.
l just don't know if this is
what l really want to do.
You know what you need?
You need to live a little.
Relax.
l need longer legs, shorter
legs, punk hair, no hair...
l just need a whole new life.
Well, if you need a whole new
life, l know just the place.
-Where's that?
-The Radiotron.
lt's a place where street
dancers go to show their stuff.
Turbo and Ozone are
meeting me there tonight.
Ozone would love to see you.
After what happened
at Franco's class...
l'm the last person
he wants to see.
Now, that's not true.
-He asks about you all the time.
-Sure.
Hey! l could have used that.
Kelly, it was only
the first day.
There's nothing to be
discouraged about.
ln fact, there are plenty
of auditions coming up.
As a matter of fact, there's
something big developing...
in the dance community
right now...
and l'm trying to get the facts.
Sounds great.
Kelly, are you OK? l mean,
you sound really down to me.
No, l'm all right.
Well, are you eating? Let me
treat you to dinner tonight.
l already have plans.
l promised some friends
l'd go watch them dance.
Well, if you need
anything at all...
you just give me a call, OK?
l mean, that's what
l'm here for.
Thanks, James.
l really appreciate your help.
lt was my pleasure.
Have a good night, OK?
OK. Bye-bye.
Man!
You guys want us?
Then come and get us.
We wore them punks out!
We showed 'em.
We burned them dudes.
You're whacked, man. Fool!
What's the matter with you, man?
You know, there was something...
about the Radiotron
that was really different.
l mean, the people there
were real.
lt was alive, you know?
lt had an energy
that felt really good.
l was really surprised.
See? l told you
that's what you needed.
You were right...just this time.
Man, shut that thing off.
-What?
-Turn it off.
What's bugging you?
They beat us, man.
Don't you understand?
They just caught us off guard.
-So where am l going?
-Right over here.
What's she doing here?
Hey, man, help me
clean up this mess.
What's the big deal?
lt's only a girl.
Just do it.
Fine!
Hi!
We just thought we'd come by
to see how you guys were doing.
That's cool. We're just
working on some new moves.
You guys were really
great last night.
They were just watching
the girl, not the dancing.
lt was just a cheap shot.
l'd burn any girl that put
her face in front of me.
-She was good.
-l'm better.
Boy, do l have an idea!
We'll put together our own act.
What a team--the 3 of you,
and me as manager.
She ain't no street dancer.
She knows nothin'
about what we do.
She can learn.
Yeah? How?
You can teach me.
We're asking for trouble.
Man, now l know
we're in trouble.
Hey, let's go celebrate.
Lunch is on me.
No, l'll treat.
No, l want to treat.
No, l'll treat, OK?
All right. There you go.
Thank you.
l'd like to make a toast.
To the best.
To our friendship.
Are you a dancer?
Yeah. l'm one of
those guys that--
Dancer, my ass.
You look more like freaks to me.
Looks like their mama
never taught them how to dress.
Hey, don't listen to him.
Come on.
Yeah. Now, that's what
l call dancin' music.
Hey, why don't you come
over here and dance with us?
Yeah. Here's a quarter.
Oh, yeah?
You laughin' at me?
-Shut up, you little runt.
-Yo, man! What's up?
Are you lookin' for a fight?
l'm right behind you.
What about the check?
This is fun!
Let's go wreck another place.
Well, l can't say it was dull.
Well, l'll walk you
to your door.
Who is this from?
Hold onto it a minute.
-How sweet of him!
-Him?
Your boyfriend?
No, my agent--James.
He can do a lot for us,
you know?
Well, l was thinking...
that maybe...
See you tomorrow, OK?
Sure.
-Good night.
-Good night, Kelly.
-Street dancing?!
-James, you don't understand.
Kelly, l'm aware of what it is.
lt's just that l'm working
on getting you...
into one of the biggest
dance competitions...
which can lead
to incredible exposure...
and you're telling me
you want to be a street dancer.
Would you just let me
explain to you--
Kelly, you're wasting your time.
You've got to think
about your future.
We're building a career.
You can't make a living
dancing in the street.
l never thought you would
be so narrow-minded.
Kelly, l'm not.
lt's just that
you've got to be serious.
Street dancing belongs
on the street.
lt won't get you to Broadway.
Well, we won't know that
until we give it a shot.
Kelly, l hate
to tell you this...
Why not?
You know why everybody's afraid?
lt's because
they don't understand it.
lt's not just kids dancing
on a street corner for a nickel.
They put more heart
and soul into their work...
than any dancer l know.
James, it's real. lt's fresh.
All l'm saying is--
James, just get us
into the contest...
and l guarantee you we'll win.
All right, now, let me
get this straight. Humor me.
You want me to put
you and your...
street-dancing friends
on the same stage...
as trained,
professional dancers?
Well, come see
for yourself, then.
We're going against
Electro Rock tonight.
Electro...what?
Electro Rock.
We got a score to settle.
This time,
we're gonna cut 'em bad.
You're...really talking
like a street person.
-You packing a blade?
-Yeah.
OK. l'll go.
Where the hell is she?
Don't worry about it, man.
She'll be here.
Hey, punk.
Hey, are you back
for more, fool?
Yeah, and wearing
rags like that...
l hope you'll be able
to back it up.
Yeah, and you know it.
Kelly, l...
Maybe you're
a little overdressed.
Don't worry about it. Come on.
James, l'd like you
to meet my friends.
-This is Adam.
-Hello, Adam.
-Hi.
-And Turbo.
Turbo.
-And this is Ozone.
-Hi, Ozone.
James came to watch us dance.
l don't dance for
anybody but myself.
Oh, yeah, punk?
Yeah, l know
what you're thinkin'.
You feel lucky?
Now.
Be cool, all right?
You bad? You want some of this?
You know, you do what you want,
man, but don't touch me.
You must be feeling
lucky tonight.
Now.
Don't worry about it. Just go
over there and watch us dance.
Kelly...
Go, girl! Go! Do it!
Why don't you go
keep James company?
All right. Go work 'em, Kelly!
Right on.
Oh, wow! What is this?
That's the girl from the beach.
That's good.
Kelly!
Man, you were great.
l couldn't believe it.
Unbelievable. You guys,
l want to tell you...
Amazing. Just fantastic.
Turbo.
Yeah, you got to teach me
that sometime.
Ozone, the way you dance is...
it's incredible.
Thanks, man.
lt was great meeting you all.
All right? Thank you.
Kelly...you were...
you were right.
lt was just phenomenal.
-Well, l'm glad you liked it.
-l did.
Hey, listen, if you want
to spend time with them...
then l totally understand.
No, it's OK.
l just need to talk to them.
All right.
Hey, let's go celebrate.
Listen, l would really love to,
but l really got to go.
-You're not gonna stay with us?
-Well, l came with James, so...
We did really great tonight,
you guys! That was fun!
See you tomorrow.
-Yeah?
-lt's me.
The door is open.
How you doing?
l'm all right.
We sure tore the place up
last night, didn't we?
We did OK.
James thinks we really
have something.
He says that we have one of
the hottest acts around.
-Oh, did he, now?
-Yeah. That's why l dropped by.
He told me about
this big dance contest...
and there's gonna be judges
from all over the country there.
lt's really big!
Are you kidding?
Those dudes don't want...
to have nothin'
to do with our kind.
What do you mean? We're good.
That's all that counts.
Oh, yeah?
Well, you know what l think?
l think we'll be
wasting our time.
Those dudes don't want
to give us the chance.
Actually, he's working
on it right now.
He's got some really
great connections...
and he can get us the chance.
He's really a nice guy,
and he's trying to help us out.
l've never needed anybody,
and l don't need them now.
lf those dudes want to see us
dance, have them come down here.
Or maybe they're afraid
of getting raped or mugged.
l really don't understand you.
l mean, this could be
a really big break for us.
Who knows what it could lead to?
l don't care!
l have everything
l want right here.
But if that's what you want,
Kelly, then you do it.
Nobody's stopping you.
Yeah, but...
Well, James has invited
everybody over.
He's gonna have
this little party...
and you guys are
supposed to be there.
Well, here's his address.
You guys are welcome
to come if you want to.
-Are you ready?
-Yeah.
Hello, Max. Good to see you.
Thanks for coming.
And then you brought...
Susan, right?
Nice to see you.
Will you excuse me?
Hello. How are you?
Kelly! You made it.
-Hi, James.
-Hello.
-You look fantastic.
-Thank you.
This is really nice.
Where's Ozone and Turbo?
Are they coming?
They had some
other commitments...
but they're going
to try and make it later.
Good. Good, because l've got so
many people l want you to meet.
l've been talking you up
like crazy here.
So come this way.
-You got to meet these people.
-OK. Great.
-Sofie!
-James.
Hi. This is the dancer
l was telling you about.
Kelly Bennett,
this is Sofie Cunningham...
a very gifted choreographer.
-Happy to meet you, Kelly.
-Nice meeting you.
Kelly is a client
and a very close friend.
Look at these fancy cars.
You sure we're invited?
Oh, there they are.
l'm really glad you came.
You're here! Great.
Welcome. The place is yours.
Enjoy yourself.
And there are some
very important people...
l want you to meet.
Come on. l'll take you there.
Come on.
-What's this?
-Fromage de tete du porc.
-Who?
-Hog's head cheese.
Sick, man! Sick!
Are you an entertainer?
Ah, yes. l'm one of
those guys that...
He's one of those young men
that spins around on his head.
Would you like
some of this pig cheese?
No, thank you.
Excuse us, Sofie.
There's someone else
l want you to meet.
Could be our major
competition in the contest.
-Excuse us.
-See you later.
l'd like to see you dance
professionally sometime.
l'm sure.
-Steven, how are you?
-Fine.
Good to see you.
Kelly.
You two know each other?
We've met.
Yeah. She used to take my class.
Well, this is
a pleasant surprise.
Ozone, this is Franco. Ozone.
Now, wait.
-Did he take your class, too?
-No.
l don't teach amateurs.
Well, these amateurs
will be competing with you.
-On the same stage with me?
-That's right.
James, l thought
you were a smart man.
Now, don't jump to conclusions.
l've seen them dance.
Yeah, in the ghetto, maybe.
But in the real dance world...
against a disciplined
art form...
they're going to make
fools of themselves.
You callin' me a fool, man?
Look around you.
lt's pretty obvious, isn't it?
-Hey, come on.
-Get him off!
l told you he belonged
on the streets!
What is the matter with you?
Happy now?
Come on, man. Let's go.
What do you mean, go?
That lady and l were working
on a 3-picture deal.
Come on, man!
-Remember...
-Lunch!
-Excuse me!
-Ozone, wait. Stop.
Please don't go.
Franco--he's just sick.
Well, l think you have
everything you want...
right here, baby.
Let's go.
Ozone!
lt's all her fault.
Told you she'd be trouble.
You had no right
to talk to him that way.
Just telling it like it is.
Face it, Kelly.
They're a different class
of people. They don't fit.
You know, Franco,
you're a really poor excuse...
for a human being.
You say they're
in a different class?
Well, you're right. They are.
They're in a class
all by themselves.
They're the best
at what they do...
and not you or anybody
is gonna take that away.
You know it's really sad?
With me, you had a chance.
But now l can see you ain't
gonna amount to nothin'.
And what makes you so special?
Well, unfortunately, Kelly...
you missed your chance
to find that out.
Thank god.
Yeah. Well...
l think you better leave.
l didn't have any intentions
of hanging around.
All right. We're gonna lock.
Now, when we lock,
roll our wrists...point. OK?
Go.
Now, we're gonna roll
our wrists, point, lock...
kick out, jump up...
Baby Legs, come on.
Do the wave. Let's see it.
All right!
Break, hot tot.
He's sharp.
Soda Pop.
Footwork.
Let's see you spin.
There it is.
Come on, Ram.
You guys are doing good--
real good.
She has a fast spin.
Pose.
Hi, Turbo.
You better be careful.
They might beat you someday.
l hope they do.
ls Ozone inside?
No.
Do you know where he is?
l haven't seen him
for a couple days.
Well...you better not
let him catch you.
where could he be?
Venice, maybe. l don't know.
-Kelly.
-Yeah, Turbo?
Can't you see what's going on?
Hi.
-What do you want?
-l want to talk to you.
l don't think we have
anything to talk about.
-What's wrong?
-l don't want to talk about it.
lf it's what happened at
James' party, Franco's a moron.
l know how you feel.
You don't know how l feel.
You don't know nothin' about me.
And your friends are
all phonies, man.
They're just like you--
up there in your tights,
being told what to do.
We don't care if we don't
step on our right foot.
We do what feels good.
And we don't do it
in the classrooms, either.
We do it on the streets.
So you're just gonna
throw the whole contest...
out the window, huh?
You're not even gonna
give yourself a chance?
We don't need it like you do.
They'll put us on the stage
and laugh at us...
because we don't
fit into your world...
because we don't have
the right credentials.
You know what your problem is?
Your problem is you.
You're a quitter!
You think you know it all,
Miss Perfect.
Well, you don't know
how l feel...
or why l do what l do.
Would you just stop
holding back?
l mean, you're always
putting up fronts.
''Nothing bothers Ozone.
''Everybody always
looks up to Ozone.
He knows everything.''
God forbid he has
no doubts or fears.
What are you afraid of?
Well, maybe l don't know
everything...
like your boyfriend James.
Would you get off it?
James is not my boyfriend.
He's my agent, and he's
just trying to help us.
James is just a friend.
l mean, he really
believes in us.
That's why he got us
the studio to rehearse in.
Come on. l want
to show you something.
l want you to see what
real dancing's all about.
Look at him.
You see his face?
That's dancing, Kelly.
Well, this is it.
What do you think?
lt's wonderful.
Thanks.
God, it's so nice to be
in a real studio again.
l'm really glad you like it.
You know l'd do
anything for you.
For us, you mean.
Well, yes, of course.
For everybody.
Am l missing something?
Yes. Music. Let's get to work.
You guys can't let me down now.
l'm going to call all
my friends in the business...
and get you in that audition.
And you better be good.
Believe me, Kelly, l've called
every S.O.B. in the business...
and it's always the same answer.
''Forget it, James.''
This audition is for the biggest
dance production in years...
and there's no way
they'll even consider you guys.
lt just seems that Franco has
a lot more pull than l thought.
But we can't give up now. We
can't let Franco off that easy.
l don't know what else l can do.
Ozone and Turbo will go nuts
if they find out.
We can't tell them about this.
Kelly, we have to be
reasonable about this.
l don't want to be reasonable.
l've been reasonable
all my life...
and it's gotten me nowhere.
l am finally happy
and l have some real friends.
l'm not going to let them down.
Those phony, narrow-minded
stuffed shirts...
won't consider it dance
because it's not traditional.
What do they want?
l'll tell you what
they don't want.
They don't want kids
in T-shirts that are torn...
and bandanas
and spiked bracelets.
Unless...
What?
No. Ozone will never go for it.
He's got too much pride.
Kelly, it's the only way
it will work.
Yes, this is my group--
the Allegro Vivace Dance Trio.
Good luck.
Gracie. Avanti.
All right. This is it.
We're on after the next group.
You guys ready?
As ready as we're
ever going to be.
Well done.
What the hell
are you doing here?
You surprised to see the fools?
We're here.
-We seem to have a problem here.
-l'll take care of it.
l'm the manager of this group.
What seems to be the problem?
l'm very much afraid they won't
be able to dance for us.
And why not?
Because l don't
think they'll fit in...
to our particular production.
What? How can you say that?
You haven't even
seen them perform.
Look, l'm sorry,
but we're looking...
for some very good
jazz dancers...
and it's been made
very clear to me...
that those people don't fit in
to that particular category.
Look, they're here.
Just let them dance.
Look, l'm sorry. l'm going
to have to ask you to leave.
Well, it's your loss.
l don't know what to do
with these people.
l'm sorry. lt's not going to
work out. This is Franco's show.
They're not going
to stop us now.
Who's next?
Ozone.
Street dancer!
Look, l'm not going
to stand for this!
You must stop immediately!
Now, listen here, young man.
Did you hear me?
You must leave now!
Look, l'm not going to stand
for this. You must stop.
Stop right this minute!
We are auditioning
jazz dancers only.
Stop this nonsense! Jim!
Oh...God. There's more of them.
Jim!
Jim, get them out of here
this instant.
Wait.
Maybe...
-All right, stop this nonsense.
-Go away.
Look, l'll pull my dancers out
if this doesn't stop...
and l mean it.
Let's talk about it later.
l can't see.
All right.
All right, that's it.
We had a deal, Mary. Remember?