I know a girl who
took a picture of her ...
and sent to the Queen of Denmark
and each won $ 10,000.
- It looked like what? She?
- There was shaped like a heart.
She pooped a heart and the queen
Denmark bought a photo?
- She merdou a heart.
- Do not say merdou, they say shit.
If merdou says.
- If you say shit.
- If merdou says.
- If you say shit. Shit, she pooped.
Shit goes to shit.
- If merdou says.
- There merdou.
It's like dying and dead.
- Shit, shit, shit ...
- Merdou, merdou, merdou ...
Sorry.
Are you well?
Seem ... stars seem ...
inside my head.
- John.
- Yes?
You merdou in your pants?
- The Queen of Denmark!
- My God!
- Get out.
She was a slut!
The Queen of Denmark!
- She loved fucking!
- My God, bye!
She wanted so much!
- Vie!
- You should go up.
- Mia!
- Vie!
- Vie, come on.
Tell him soar!
I have a lot of things
to do today.
Like what?
You're so stupid!
Violet, coming soon.
Stupid!
WITHOUT DESTINATION
Do you think John tasty?
He needs to wake up.
You should have sex with him.
Let the two have sex with him.
Let's call him and say that
transaremos with it at the same time.
Come on!
It's gonna be crazy!
No!
What?
I lost my phone!
In my purse.
Holy shit!
Want some water?
For anyone who is smiling?
- For you.
- Why?
Because you make me smile.
Why are you always so sweet?
Why are you always so beautiful.
Today, Prashant, I'm just tired.
So I said:
I look like the kind of girl
who will buy bras ...
00:08:36,375 -> 00:08:37,877
take home Ios, Ios prove ...
and then try to return it?
I tasted one, did not fit.
Woke up.
I will ... win.
BORROWING MONEY
BUY GOLD
I just said "do not mess with me."
Shit ...
Minele!
Super Cat. Super Cat.
You're my little
Black and Super Cat.
With the great hump of the rear.
Attention ...
here comes the Super cat.
There, Super Cat.
Come, let's have lunch.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
SON
ARE YOU A CAT cool!
LOVE, MOM
75 DOLLARS
And then cat?
Hey!
- It is now?
- No, that was you.
It ...
This bid networking
is crazy!
It's like that guy.
With fish, you know?
It ...
No.
You know that guy?
He is hungry,
fish but does not know?
And then the other guy was there ...
The older guy, helping him ...
- Teach a man to fish.
- Yeah, man! Yes!
This, man. Type Chicken of the sea.
Do you know?
But hey, I'm working on it, ok?
So do not worry.
Great.
And then, man, it'll be like ...
like, "what do you want on Hanukah?"
Ricky, okay guy.
I'm not your parents.
They would kill me if they knew
I'm staying here.
Oops, birthday?
Yeah, something like that.
Secret.
I like to save
these things to me.
How old are you really?
Wow, dude.
You celebrated last night?
No.
ACE OF 16H 04H
EVERY DAY
No!
I shove it in my ass
and look out for a week.
Perhaps, if you do,
pink skirt.
No, just go out in hell!
I want this torture
in my large intestine.
I hate it!
Maybe vibrate from time to time.
I do not care to vibrate,
I just want to destroy him.
I wonder how long it would
to decompose inside your body.
No, this is not possible.
Our bodies are not
capable of decomposing it.
Hey ...
want another round?
Is laughing at what?
Are you shy?
Yes, I'm shy.
So ...
Can I borrow.
Drinks!
Think about how her life
would be wonderful ...
if she had a cell phone
he liked.
You're not funny.
And you're a terrible driver.
We go to the bathroom.
Stop.
Jesus, why do you always have to ...
Behave.
Right.
God!
- Got a light?
- That was fast.
No fast. Efficient.
Got a light?
I'm pretty sure
can not smoke here.
I can do whatever I want.
You got a light?
You know the rules
about not smoking here.
I can do whatever I want!
No you can not.
Not when smoking.
Watch, Violet.
Just get me a fucking!
Just went to a bar with some friends.
You're so serious, man.
I love it!
Man, when are you going to invite me
in one of your nights ...
secret agent in the bar?
Type introduce me to your guys?
You really are retarded, are not you?
It's family, cousin.
I wish the rent
were family.
You know, maybe you should
meet the girls.
You and Violet get along.
Nifty! I'd love ...
The TVpequena was broken, right?
Shit ... Man, I clean today.
A little before four ...
pm.
People, this is not the last
helicopter out of Vietnam.
There will be another train.
- Just the way you like.
- Thank you.
More ketchup?
Sure.
More coffee?
Yes.
Ok
Ok?
Thank you.
- What!
- Eyes in the back, man!
Man, I tell you. You have to connect.
The world will fuck you if you lose.
The world has screwed me.
- You're an idiot.
- Yes, I am, John.
That's how I keep on top.
Oh, yeah ...
I arranged alphabetically
for you.
You know, it's funny, Jonathan.
Should annotate and send
somewhere.
It ...
Wow ... Busy week.
I'm just the delivery boy.
Do not shoot the messenger, right?
Good humor, good.
I'm happy for you.
Obama, baby, "yes we can".
Anything is possible.
Then turned the knob ...
Right ...
I opened the door and down the stairs ...
turning to the left.
You turn left repeatedly
to descend and exit the building.
But when you come home ...
you climb the stairs
and turns right.
So when you turn left,
you're leaving ...
but when you turn right,
is coming home.
And that's good.
But the handle is a trick.
It's almost like ...
if I had to go home
to leave.
Because you turn right.
Absolutely, man.
You are fully
getting somewhere.
It is as if their standards
be repeated many times ...
you do not know more
that the standards are.
Right.
Still talking about, man?
Or maybe ...
you only get a point ...
that his disappointment with yourself
becomes so much bigger ...
the disappointment of his parents
with you, you ...
I do not know.
But somehow you read
with it that allows you to ...
reward yourself
once in a while, but ...
Only a way that
seem a compromise.
I want to commit
with it.
It ...
she is also good with ketchup.
Your mother left you fall head
or something like that, John?
Brother, you have to get
that beauty where you can ...
before another idiot
take you. Right?
Now tell me the plan, Batman.
It's all just funny
in its irony.
And worse when you get older.
That shit inescapable.
Brother, you know, it's just life.
Love it or leave it.
Cool.
He took it to some porn site
for ex-military freaks?
It's about clarity, man.
Clarity.
Shit does not mean shit.
Unless you mean shit.
And only mean shit if you ...
need to mean shit.
So you can do shit, right?
What?
Hold the thought.
Yeah, baby, what's up?
Yes, yes, all quiet.
Except it ...
Yeah Right. Much in the head.
Do you know how beautiful it is?
Sure, sure ...
Lizzy wants to know if I would go
to a party tonight, John.
- Okay
- Vai bring their girlfriends along?
Jesus, Charles, by you
always have to say ...
Yes.
Right.
Yeah, baby, he stumbled.
Yes, he calls you later on
what, where, when ...
Sure, the itinerary.
Ok, calm.
Talk to you later. Ciao.
So where is the clarity?
Are you all ready?
- What's going on?
- Only in New York.
Everybody swingin '!
Stop!
And shoot!
Open the door!
Stop!
Not every day can be
a day at the fair ...
otherwise you would
tired of smiling.
Something like that. My grandmother
used to tell me that.
It ... That Charles is a part.
Oh, dear, do not listen to Charles.
He's like a fish sucking
the side of the tank ...
when trying to make sense.
Hit the glass and get going.
You got a pen?
I want to give you the address of the party ...
- And I have two people in line.
- Wait.
Yes.
- Hi, Lizzy.
- How you doing, baby?
How is your day?
Paris that help me.
MOM
I. ..
Hey.
If you found work?
Tonight ...
some of us will take some drinks
at the bar down the street.
You should ...
come if you want.
Later.
What is your name again?
Next!
It's your birthday
It's your birthday today
- My baby was born ...
- Hi, honey, it's your mother.
My beautiful boy!
Honey, call me.
I'm a little
worried about you.
No need to talk,
if you do not want ...
call me but I know
you're right.
Ricky is with you?
Aunt Jackie ...
I. ..
that not that guy ...
with the fish.
What are you doing?
It's a camera?
Violet!
Lower the shit that song!
It's probably a good idea.
I can not hear!
- Begin?
- Yes
Welcome to my life.
Ok ..
Disconnect.
Help me move ...
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait!
Need to prepare ...
Hey, need fire?
Yes, that would help.
What the fuck?
- What the fuck are you doing? Turn!
- No!
- Turn!
I just do not want to talk
about those things.
It's gonna be crazy ...
show the kind of Paris Hilton
or something.
I do not want to be an actress.
I cleaned the whole apartment.
Get that camera out of my face.
Do not yell at me,
his voice is so annoying!
My God, and his is not?
Just do not yell at me, ok?
It's a great idea.
Not pire. It's about you ...
It's about both of us, ok?
Me too.
Ok?
Yes, yes, I did.
Mia, move. Hide yourself.
I'm hiding.
Welcome to my show.
Oh, and put the cigarette
back in the mouth.
Hey.
Need a light?
Yes, that would help.
Okay, maybe try telling
something interesting.
BE KIND OR GO AWAY
THANKS
My God.
Ok, this one ...
- No, no! Seriously.
- Seriously what?
Seriously!
Wait a second.
What? Right.
There is nothing funny
about this situation.
The guys are not strangers?
I think people in general are.
Exactly.
Tell me about your philosophy
men, women, and people.
I think it's very easy
generalization on my part.
Men are ...
seeking power.
Women are looking for ...
love.
And children are seeking ...
independence.
- Where are you?
- Ok!
Hang in there.
How old were you?
I do not know, I was five.
And what happened?
Tonight?
Do you remember?
You know, just describe, tell how it went.
I sat at the kitchen table,
eating my potatoes and peas.
Hey, how many months
was his mother?
She was about 8 and a half months ...
- This is very pregnant.
- It is.
Very close to giving birth.
And all I remember is
look inside the room ...
after hearing my mother scream.
I got up, went to the door
and looked inside ...
and my father was kicking
my mother's belly.
And she walked away to the wall.
And then she fell near the crib
he had built ...
for when the baby arrived.
Then I remember being in hospital
with my mother screaming in pain.
And she just give birth,
but the baby was dead.
E. .. was a girl.
And she was dead.
The beating killed her belly.
- Do not laugh at me.
- No, I'm not laughing at you.
I'm not laughing, I just do not know ...
I do not know how it all went through.
Do not even know.
Well ..
I do not know. I know this
vai sound horrible, but ...
When I was growing up,
I even felt that ...
I did not feel that I was human.
- What?
- You know.
- What is?
- What happened?
What prompted this?
I do not know ... Something like ...
I was looking out the window and she
told me not to look out the window.
And she was ironing and ...
She was ironing and ...
she came to me and said:
"Do not look out the window.
I told you not to look out the window. "
Then I remember
this great iron ...
coming towards me.
How ...
in slow motion ...
I do not remember the pain,
just remember this ...
big and loud cry ...
A. ..
blood-curdling scream?
It is.
- You can not park here.
- Okay.
What are you doing?
- Just digging.
- Yeah, whatever. Come.
What Mia said is really true?
Do not be an idiot.
On?
Yes.
Ok, well ... In the know
at a party a few months ago.
And this other girl had
simply disappeared.
Then she moved here and
we are best friends ever since.
Whatever.
I think Mia has me
as an example, you know?
Why do you think ...
I mean ...
What are "friends"?
"Friends" is the worst type shit
show on TV.
"Hmm .. Why do you think ...
I mean ... "
Like, your questions
are so stupid.
It's scary when
a girl of 6 years ...
sees a lot and knows your heart ...
and you do not care for her.
For me, it was just this
disturbed person and ...
I could not hate her.
Do you know? All I know ...
All I could think was
I had to pity her.
Because I know how my father
she was and how she suffered ...
So I could not hate her,
because that was the only way ...
Her vent your pain ...
their frustrations, so ...
I could handle the shit and
everything else and tried to be strong.
And say, "Hey, all right" ...
And just hold on.
There were times when I really
I hated my mother.
And I had thoughts of ...
You know ...
I do not mean "kill her"
but just, you know ...
push her and say:
"Fuck you."
Do you ever think, like ...
perhaps at this point in your life ...
say it, tell her how
feel about all this?
It's too late.
It's too late for that, she ...
She became, she is
a different person now.
- I do not even know her more.
- But, Mia ...
honestly ...
It's like she erased everything and
written in ink on top of Jesus.
I mean, do not you think
would make a difference if you said:
"Look, this is what I think
you did to me ... "
- Know what I mean?
- She would just ignore.
Alright! Lets ignore it.
- Let her ignore.
- She would just ignore.
I'm just saying ...
I'm just saying that I
would want her to know.
I would want to say
I feel for her.
She would ignore ...
Only coffee.
01:03:38,908 -> 01:03:40,000
Thank you.
This part will not be seen by
nobody but us three, right?
Sure.
Lie. Lie.
Lie ...
BE KIND OR GO AWAY
THANKS
NEVER NEVER NEVER
GIVE UP
It's strange that you're so unemotional
when he talks about things like that.
Well ..
It is because I went through this ...
over and over in my head and ...
just ... Do you know?
This has disturbed you?
It's like a movie, you know?
Yes, I cried.
I cried all the tears.
I stayed up all night ...
unable to sleep.
I cried until no more tears are left.
From what you cried?
Mostly, for my father.
Because he was the one who
really understood me.
He was the only ...
who knows ...
who loved me.
And it does not hurt me.
E. ..
Do you know?
Although he made
these terrible things ...
he was a person
very curious to me.
A very interesting person.
He was very intelligent
and very artistic.
And I knew it was
so like him.
Nothing like my mother ...
When you're a guy, you ...
You see his father in him?
No.
Sorry ...
Ok, but, I mean,
it's just that ...
I will not talk about it.
Ok
It's just ...
I do not know who will see it.
If someone is going.
About what you want
talk then?
I do not know.
What do you want to talk?
Let's talk about ...
All I knew was ...
it hurt.
And the second time he penetrated me,
and I was crying, it hurt so much.
And I thought: "My God,
it should be pleasurable. "
And that brochou me immediately.
And I looked down and saw
this pool of blood ...
out of the way of my legs.
And I just thought:
"Oh, my God."
And his name was Jim and he was ...
And I just ...
"Oh, my God ...
looks like you killed someone
these sheets ".
And he said: "It is ...".
Apparently he really loved me
and asked me to marry.
So of course, I let
immediately by another guy.
How old were you?
I was nineteen.
You were a virgin with nineteen?
Yes.
They say that if you are a virgin
and lose his virginity ...
to his first love,
that after experiencing ...
the loss of her virginity,
you just hate that guy ...
because you want him back and not
realizes how much he wanted ...
how was precious,
until vai.
It did not hurt?
I do not know.
Well ..
Well, I think that is quite different
for men.
Do not you think?
I mean, I think the same.
I think that guy
not feeling your pain.
- No.
- The guy who I was ...
- I did not feel my pain.
- They just think they're earning.
Exactly! He was just
thinking about having sex.
I'll only date women
going forward.
What do you think
attracts the guys who ...
they just want to eat you and you leave?
Pardon?
I mean ...
it is a quality
attractive in a guy?
You search it?
Type someone ...
You look at someone and think:
"He just wants to earn"?
No, I do not think it's attractive.
I find disgusting.
I look for personality in a guy.
- He must have a sense of humor.
- You know, I'd say that ...
I could not care less
on the appearance of a face.
I do not have a type.
Do not care about height.
I do not ... As long as they are
taller than me.
I know many guys
they have giant egos.
And you know what? I think there
great art in humility.
Do not you think, Mia?
I mean ...
There is a great art to be humble.
Even if it's beautiful, even if
be smart, whatever.
Just receive a compliment and say ...
"Yeah ...", instead of:
"Yeah, I am too."
I could not do that.
Know what I mean?
You understand me?
No, I'm not understanding.
You're being totally confused.
No, I'm not.
Mia knows what I'm saying.
Ok Maybe it's a
subtle feminine language.
What we are saying is that
know a lot of guys ...
ok, I'm saying. Ok
Wait a minute.
- Here's what I'm saying.
- What?
I know many guys who
think they are so delicious ...
they are the best thing ...
Whatever. Whatever.
Perhaps they are beautiful and intelligent,
or maybe smart and beautiful ...
Whatever!
I'm just saying ...
I agree.
When ...
a person is humble,
a man or a woman ...
so this is a very quality
greater than having a huge ego.
Now I make sense?
Ok ..
Let me ask you a question.
- Right?
- Yes
Ok, so ...
Ask the question.
Ok So ...
If it were to confer
all people ...
- With whom he had intimate ...
- Yes
- In the last five or ten years ...
How were their ideals?
How dovetailed
humble in that category?
Well, no, obviously.
Because if there was an ideal
I would be with that person.
I do not know how many
people I slept.
I'd say something close
two hundred faces.
- Two hundred?
- It is. It is.
Do not worry;
I was safe with them.
You know, condoms and everything else.
- Rubber gloves.
- Rubber gloves can say.
Nonoxynol-9. Whatever.
It is at this point two hundred guys
and about three girls.
- Three girls?
- It is.
You know everyone's name?
Man, if they expand, a line
all these chicks together ...
could reach the moon
God is dead and no one cares.
I did not mean anything by it.
Just shut up once, ok?
Ok
I do not believe
I'm crying ...
I can not even remember
the last time i ...
How do you feel?
I feel ...
well.
Not so good, but you know ...
Honestly.
It is not good ...
you know ...
just ...
just be myself for a change.
Who are you generally?
Happy Birthday.
- Yes?
- John, I love that cat, man.
Yeah, the cat is good.
Still to drink?
Should bring
your girls, man.
It really was thinking
to invite them to eat.
In order to cook?
I had this ...
amazing story
that should tell tonight ...
- And that should be a part ...
- Mia, think we should go soon?
Just give us the short version.
My mother locked me in the basement.
I regained consciousness.
I escaped.
I said to everyone: "Get out."
I ran away.
I began my own life.
I made many mistakes,
but learned from them.
And now I am a strong
and independent woman.
Mia! We gotta go!
Just do not hate me because I'm beautiful.
I do not hate ...
you just confuses me.
Mia!
Exciting.
- We gotta go.
- Exciting.
Animal!
Like me.
What is exciting?
Come on!
Come on.
That is immortalized
on tape forever.
We are terrible actresses.
No, we are brilliant actresses!
Ok Good is good enough.
As I give the zoom it, John?
Here ...
So much effort and so little
recognition.
That dress is so tight.
- You are getting fatter, Violet?
- It is. My butt is increasing.
My body thinks is
pregnant.
But it is not, then my
Ass is increasing.
You are pregnant in your ass?
- Where the hell are we?
- Suite 623.
Hey, who's the boss
tonight?
That's it. Anything else is extra.
In cash.
Who is the groom?
Congratulations, sit there.
- No touching.
- Sorry.
I want to put on your tail.
This costs an extra.
- Are you ready?
- Where are you? We're waiting.
- The security kicked me out again.
- Hurry up!
Right.
I think in a strange way
he's jealous of me.
Drive.
- This is for you.
- Thank you.
Hi, Lizzy.
Yeah, all right.
Yes, I'm here tomorrow.
Legal.
You too.
Goodbye.
I hate the suburbs.
You want to eat?
If the path of a bar.
That dinner of pasta.
- Not good? Not good?
- Spectacular.
- Incredible.
- It's my specialty.
- Now let's turn the lens.
- I have a question.
- Yes
- We have some questions, baby.
Right.
- What are friends?
- That are friends.
This is good. I like that.
Why do not you talk more?
Good question.
And it was a great answer.
You outweigh me.
There are just a number
it works.
This is the potential John.
What is this shit?
My God!
It's like, it's like ...
I mean, sleep on it.
- She found her place.
- No, I thought not.
See it. See it.
The notes of John ...
All ten!
All ten, look at that guy!
I knew he was smart.
Why do you guard that?
- Why do I keep it?
- It is.
To remember?
This is my zenith.
That's where I ...
We take a close
photo of before and after?
My God.
After a haircut.
- Begins as a progression ...
- Can you catch?
See it. See it!
This guy just took off in December
Can you see it?
- What? What?
- How are you?
- You went through my things?
- No, it did not move!
I'm glad that John and I are
finally coming together ...
because he is my friend
and my cousin ...
- How's the job search going?
- He's cool.
- What do you do?
- The job search?
Yeah, how's it going?
- How do I do?
- I'm sure you know.
- Oh, I know.
- Do not just take.
Just get! Do nothing more.
She is bossy.
- Who is your favorite?
- You are.
See, that's why I forgot.
Lost our first kiss ...
and I felt bad.
And I know what happened, but I forgot.
- He's the luckiest guy
He's the luckiest guy
- In the Lower East Side
Because it has wheels
And we want to take a ride
- I screwed. I'm so bad.
- You spoiled.
- Come here, baby.
- Go on, buddy.
- I will prepare for you.
- Best seat in the house.
You deserved it.
- He's the luckiest guy
- In the Lower East Side
Because it has wheels
And we want to take a ride
- He's the luckiest guy
- In the Lower East Side
Because it has wheels
And we want to take a ride
- Where's the cat?