"$500 for the death of Charlie Wei."
Executive Producer
NG SEE YUEN
Hey, friend!
Your style's not bad.
But take it easy.
You look done in.
You must be the Four Door
Fist Champion - Charlie Wei?
I'm Charlie Wei.
Your name, if you have one?
Sure, it's Thunderfoot.
I've heard of his devil's kick,
it's famous in the kung fu world.
It's never been defeated.
And won't be.
I suppose I should warn you.
I've been given good money -
to kill you!
Someone's paid you to kill me?
I'll pay twice as much to kill him!
You could,
only my honour comes first.
You must realise,
the contract's sealed.
So you must die.
Don't be so sure,
for I, Champion of the Four Door
Fists, have never yet been defeated.
I'll break every bone
in your body and send you to hell!
Producer
ZHANG QUAN
Starring
JACKIE CHAN,
HWANG JANG LEE,
and
YUEN SIU TIEN
Cast
WANG HAN CHEN, SHI FI ZI,
HSU HSIA, WANG JIANG,
LIN YING, CHI TIAN,
CAI HUI, YUEN SUN YI,
JIANG JIN, LIU RONG
Martial Arts Directors
HSU HSIA, YUEN WOO PING
Assistant Martial Arts Directors
YUEN ZHEN WEI, YUEN SUN YI
Assistant Producers
WU SI YUEN, XI HUA AN
Assistant Directors
XIAO LONG, LUO WEN,
HE TIAN CHENG
Camera Operator ZHANG HAI
Lighting Technician LIN WEI
Production Assistant DENG LIN
Set Design DING ZHUO LUN
Property Master YANG SHI ZHENG
Runners DENG RU, TAN XI
Cinematography HUANG TIE HONG
Wardrobe LU RUI LIAN
BA0 GUO LAN
Make-up Artist GAO SHAO PING
Editor PAN XIONG
Music Editor ZHUO FU LIANG
Art Director DING YUEN DA
Sound Editor JI HONG YUEN
DRUNKEN MASTER
School of
Martial Arts.
Director
YUEN WOO PING
Scarface.
What is it, master?
Finish the lesson.
I must go.
Yes sir, I will, sir.
Stop!
I'm now going to demonstrate.
The first lesson
is the Five Animal Styles.
- He's bonkers. - Three-legged cat.
- Four-eyed rat.
Let's get started.
Dragon Sees Tiger.
Tiger Rears.
Snake's Tongue Darts Out.
Panther Sees Fire.
White Crane Spreads Wings.
No. Hold it, hold it.
There isn't any power in your wrist.
How do expect to make any progress?
Straighten it up.
I suppose you think that was funny,
playing tricks on your teacher.
Take that! And that!
- It wasn't me!
- Who was it? Tell me.
Freddy did it.
So, Freddy Wong.
Just because
your father is Master Wong,
gives you no damn right
to cause trouble here.
Oh, balls! You think
kung fu is just a performance.
You mean my kung fu is lousy?
It's not that bad,
but it's not the best.
Suppose you show me
exactly what's wrong with it?
Right. Just look at
your panther Sees Fire.
Well, what's wrong?
That spread between your paws
is an open invite.
And that Horse Stance
is bow-legged.
I bet with one sweep that I...
There, you've been thrown, see?
Just wait!
Shut up! Shut up you turkeys!
So, you'd like to test
your teacher's kung fu?
We can all learn
from each other.
I can take almost anything, you bum!
But I've taken enough bullshit!
Right! Come on!
You're wide open.
Do you know that, teacher?
See how good his Horse Stance is?
Pork belly, shut up!
Look! Right foot! Chicken Stance.
Bastard!
Freddy, you're the cat's ass, making
old crow-face dance like that.
He's so full of bullshit.
He thinks he's God's gift
to kung fu.
You sure made him dance!
And that face!
You did all of us a favour,
that's for sure.
- Gee, that's not bad!
- Go have some more then.
Damn that! I was talking
about that chick there.
Wow! That perfect frame she's got.
Yeah, sexy.
- How much?
- 76.
That one in the red?
Imagine being kissed by that chick.
Kissing is for children.
I could get her to hug me.
You're kidding. She wouldn't.
You want to bet on it?
I'll bet you a whole dinner.
She's hot,
she wouldn't look at you twice!
All right! A whole dinner, then.
Watch.
He's looking for trouble.
- What is it?
- It's agony, my eye.
My eye. Blow on it, please.
Can't you help me? Huh, can you?
One more, huh?
Did you see that?
Thanks a lot.
Hey, a snake! There!
Don't be scared,
I'll kill him, it's all right.
That's how it's done.
I must try that on your sister.
On my sister?
Thought you could take
advantage of my daughter, did you?
Me touch her!
She was asking for it, dumb bitch.
You wanted to lay
your filthy hands on her.
On her? That's a laugh.
She's much too ugly.
Think you're real smart, huh?
Well, I'll teach you a lesson, boy.
So you want to play it kung fu?
Try this.
The old bitch is tough.
Hey guys,
you're gonna help me, right?
Some friends they make.
OK, you're nothing but a skinny
old woman, so I'll let you win!
Fresh greens!
What's your game? Stumbling
about like some drunken stooge.
Don't answer back.
Hey! Master!
Antique jade!
Look, sir, antique jade.
Is it real??
But of course. It's an heirloom.
It's valuable, sir.
- How much is it?
- Ten bucks.
- So expensive?
- It's worth it.
Here.
Just ten cents.
Hey! Hey, sir!
You can't give me this,
it wouldn't buy an old plate.
I couldn't sell
such a valuable piece for this.
No sale, no money.
But my jade!
That was all I had in the world!
Well, take this.
Daddy, Daddy, are you all right?
- At least give me something!
- Sure!
Daddy!
What's wrong, old man?
He smashed my jade and he won't pay.
Shithead! Piss off!
Talking to your mother?
Rot in hell.
Hand over this man's money.
Pay? Not before I put you
in the ground.
It's too bad you feel that way,
because I'm in a bad mood.
Now I'm gonna teach you a lesson!
You're mad!
You almost killed me!
Wow, my knuckles just escaped.
This is for you, now get going!
That's enough, I'm dying.
Don't worry, you're safe,
it's only the blunt side.
I've no intention of killing you.
Not yet.
Please, Please!
That one came pretty close.
Watch what you're doing.
Drop dead.
You're lucky I missed, this time,
but it's quite by accident.
I chop, chop, chop...
Then, I slice, slice, slice...
And then I beat, beat, beat...
and mix it all together.
You sure have brightened my day.
You know, it must be at least ten
years, brother, since we last met.
You hardly look a day older.
I wouldn't have recognised my niece.
She isn't a bad girl,
just a bit na'i've.
And where is Freddy?
That young rascal,
he's always getting into trouble.
He's grown up now,
you won't recognise him.
So, you'll stay for a few days?
Freddy!
Freddy, come and meet your aunt!
- Come on, lad.
- Coming.
Say hello.
Hello, Auntie, cousin.
- Hello.
- Hello, Freddy.
What on earth's the matter?
I've pulled a muscle.
I'll soon put that right.
Here, let your aunt...
No, I'm all right.
Relax, just for a second. That's it.
Oh, dear.
Oh, mother!
Well, you feel better?
Thank you, yes.
He'll be all right now. Your son's
grown into a smart-looking fellow.
He's quite clever,
and his kung fu's not bad.
Oh? I would like
to see his kung fu sometime.
OK, you'd enjoy a match.
People say you're strict with him
and that he's a good boy.
Tell me what else they say.
They say he's courteous and polite,
setting other boys a good example,
and that he's well-mannered
and obliging.
That makes me really proud to be
his father. Freddy, come here, son.
I'm glad he isn't like the other
boys here. They're real sex maniacs.
Only today my own daughter
was attacked by one of them.
What's more, when I went
to rescue her, he attacked me!
What? You mean to tell me both
of you were attacked in my own town!
- Would you recognise him?
- As if I could forget! Yes.
Good! When I find him, I'll flay
him alive! Freddy, come on!
- Uncle, there's really no need.
- But, why?
Because he's in this very room.
But where?
Over there,
your precious son, Freddy.
What? It can't...
Down on your knees!
Please!
You'll pay for this,
you scum, you criminal!
Ah! Oh, my God!
- Mr Wong.
- Yes, Mr Li. What has happened?
I'll tell you, that bastard
son of yours beat him up.
Why would he do that?
Because he's nothing
but a wild animal.
He attacked my son,
breaking all the bones in his body!
He really beat him up.
He's all wrapped up like a dumpling!
Wong, what are you going to do?
Vermin from hell,
I'll beat you to death!
No, no!
Brother,
you mustn't kill your own son.
I've got to kill this devil,
he's a disgrace.
Sounds bad for a teacher
of your standing
to flog his own son to death.
If he must be punished, I suggest
that Mr Li here, is quite capable.
Stop him!
I beat your son,
so let him punish me.
There, you hit me,
I promise I won't fight back.
So, you think you're funny, huh? OK,
Mr Wong, what are you going to do?
I disown him! This slime is mine no
longer. Do what you like with him.
So, my suggestion -
you pick your man,
he'll fight Freddy who'll be
strictly forbidden to fight back.
Ten blows should be enough.
Now, Mr Li, do you approve?
Ten blows won't be needed.
I'll do it in three!
Master, listen,
I'm going to fix that squirt.
Be sure you leave him
looking just like I am now.
The Divine Eight, that palm-style
of yours is really something.
Ha! I'm only starting.
I'm not dead yet.
Enough!
That's your ten blows, Mr Chao.
And you said
you'd put me down in three.
Snake and crane together.
Strike the viper points.
Let's try your Divine Eight again.
I told you I've got style.
Hey, my jacket's getting dirty,
take it!
You regret not paying
for that jade now!
You've got the wrong guy.
Are you all right, master?
Idiot!
Master, now I look just like you.
OK, you win with your smart tricks.
I'll get you back. Let's go!
You haven't heard the last of us.
Come on, let's get out of here.
I'll get you yet!
Careful, careful!
He came in with one cripple
and left with two.
You fight well, I give you credit,
but I'll still kill you!
You mustn't kill
a child of your blood.
Break his wicked ways
through practice.
I've tried with that bastard.
Right! From now on
you stay in this house.
We'll start with five hours
Horse Stance!
Now, don't move.
Have some more boiling water!
There!
Are you comfortable?
Are your legs shaking,
are they aching?
You know, I feel really sorry
for you. Poor little chicken!
I bet you this will tickle.
Stop! Don't do that.
- What are you trying to do?
- Carrying out orders!
It's your father's idea.
He says for every bowl you break,
you stay another hour. You bastard!
Darned idiot!
Master!
Master.
Yes, his stance
appears to be pretty steady.
Sure he hasn't had a rest?
I've been watching him
like a hawk, absolutely not.
You're certain?
Well, any problems?
Yes, I feel very tired.
- Tired? You don't seem to be.
- I am, sir.
Even though you're sitting
on a chair?
What? Sitting on a chair?
Let me see. Oh my God, he is!
You young criminal,
I've tried to teach you, but no.
Well, it leaves me
no alternative, then.
I'll have to ask Uncle
to discipline you.
- Who's that?
- Beggar Su.
Ow! My foot again!
Hurry up pinhead,
it's choking me!
Won't be a second.
Practising your kung fu
upside down, huh?
I'm dying.
Here, something to eat.
Here! Wait till I get some water.
Take this thing off my neck.
It's killing me.
Hurry!
Hey, come on, get up!
Why did you get down so fast?
Here, eat this.
Is it true Beggar Su
is going to train you?
That's bad news for you.
You've heard about that bastard?
I know he's a bit hard.
Worse than that.
You'll be crippled for life.
I'm telling you, honest.
I'm not kidding.
I knew one young guy who was
his student, wow, was he a mess!
He lost all his teeth,
his hair was torn out.
You should have seen his busted
nose! His father didn't know him.
He's a real sadist, a torturer.
Then, what can I do?
You'd better do something.
I've got to think fast.
Think, damn you, think!
Let's see, you might, ah...
- Yeah, we run like hell!
That's not running, come on!
Hurry! Follow me.
Yue He Restaurant
Dumplings, dumplings!
Take a seat over there.
Excuse me,
do you mind if I sit here?
No, sit down.
You're by yourself, good,
I don't like eating on my own.
Sit down, sit down.
This restaurant's not bad.
Look at the food,
so wonderful, so juicy.
Real good smell, really fantastic.
What can I get you, sir?
- This is such a surprise!
- What's that?
No, no, go ahead, eat!
I'll start with
a bowl of shark's fin.
Sorry, no shark's fin.
Too bad. Soya pork, roast goose -
plenty of fat, steamed grouper...
Sorry sir, no grouper.
Then any fish will do.
Steamed abalone and shrimp noodles.
- Yes, sir.
- A pint of wine, right away.
Can you really eat all that?
Easy, I'm still growing,
I've got to keep strong and fit.
That's great, oh boy!
Now we eat. Thank you.
Have a little wine, be my guest,
drink up, this looks good.
Oh, boy, I'm starving.
Here, taste that. Eat up!
Go on, don't be shy! Help yourself.
I insist! Drink, drink, drink.
- Cheers
Wow, this is such good grub!
Go on!
I say, boy...
He really gets that food down!
Ah, feels great.
Well, friend,
that was really special.
Delicious! Now listen, friend.
I've got to go now.
This meal's on me, I insist!
I'll pay as I'm leaving.
We'll meet tomorrow.
Finish your dinner.
See you tomorrow! Bye, now.
Sorry.
See you tomorrow, bye.
That will be exactly $1.05.
I'm not paying.
You're not? Well, who is?
The old guy over there.
He's a good friend?
I'm his son, you idiot!
Is that so, now?
Just how many fathers do you have?
That guy owns this place
and you're talking to his son.
That makes you a bastard.
Thought the meals were free here,
did you? We don't give credit.
Pay or die!
I've forgotten my money, that's all.
I'll fetch it right now,
and I'll pay the bill.
Oh, yeah?
Pay or die!
Gorilla, get him!
Oh, no.
Hold it, let's talk!
Pig, you were so greedy
for all that food, now spit it out!
One roast leg!
One soya pork!
That's enough.
And one pint of wine yet.
Now you've emptied my belly,
I'm hungry again.
Hey, that's enough,
or do you want to kill the boy?
For your information,
he's going to clean the toilets.
You want something to clean, huh?
Thanks, old man.
You dare to interfere
in our business?
I'm the gorilla, watch how I jump!
Jump, then!
Now he's jumping all right!
It hurts!
This is how to wash your face.
You thief!
Let's be friends.
You've got arms of iron,
but you've brains of straw.
Stop that.
This way.
I can't help wondering
how old you are, old man.
For your age, you sure are tough.
I've had to be tough
to survive to this age.
I'm not like the young men today.
None of you can fight.
Always getting thrashed.
Today was a bad day.
Usually with one blow
I'd have done the lot!
You haven't seen my real style.
That sounds like an excuse.
I forgot to ask why
you couldn't pay for your meal.
That's a long story.
And what's your name?
I'm Mr Su.
Hey, there's a fellow with the same
name screwing up my life!
That's why I'm on the run.
He's this creep, named Beggar Su,
my father asked to train me.
- So you're afraid then?
- What? I'm not afraid.
Though I've heard he's very cunning,
violent and mean. But I'll show him!
That old fart. Wait till I see him,
I'll tear him apart.
You'll show the fart, huh?
Yeah, sure. Where do you come from?
The sky is my roof
and I sleep wherever I may.
You're a bum, that it?
Everyone knows me as Beggar Su.
Your name is Beggar Su as well??
- Beggar Su?
- That's the name, young fellow.
Lucky I'm fast on my feet.
That was close.
Not fast enough.
You can run as fast as you like,
but you can't get away.
Now, listen.
Your father's paid me well to train
you and I'm going to do it.
It hurts!
How long will this take?
- A day?
- One year exactly.
I'll never make it.
You already have your cash,
so you can relax.
But I'm going to enjoy this!
I'll see you in hell!
Damn you!
Let me go, you're breaking my neck.
You're just an old beggar.
Like to pretend you're a real tiger?
I'll show you what a tiger's about.
I see your tiger's
got a bad paw, huh?
It's still there.
All that kung fu looks like dancing.
The Crane attacks!
Angry Crane. Crane eats The Shrimp!
The Crane flies.
Your fingers are stronger
than my teeth!
I'm coming to get you!
You scared me!
Climbing trees to get away now.
Monkey kung fu.
You're choking me.
Ready to learn?
- Answer!
- My head!
- Are you?
- I guess I've got no choice.
But I don't like
your style of recruitment.
Let me down!
I don't want to die yet!
You're supposed to be a teacher,
you'd break a gorilla in half.
All students with style
must learn how to fall.
That was only your first lesson.
Where are you going?
To take a piss.
- Over there!
- All right, teacher.
From the right jar
to the left jar.
The back jar to the right jar.
The back jar to the front jar.
Left jar to the right jar.
Right jar to the front jar.
Stupid old man,
playing games with jars.
Break my back is all this will do.
Come on, hurry!
He's so mean.
Freddy! Freddy! Freddy!
Have a good wash,
you old crank!
Hey you, get out of here.
Asshole, piss off. Are you deaf?
Are you blind?
Can't you see I'm busy?
No hanging around, you bum.
Move your ass.
Who says? Is this your place?
Suppose I don't move it?
A big mouth and a wet ass.
It should be taught some manners.
How's it feel?? Nice and dry?
Right, you twerp! I'll give you dry.
I'll shove you in head first.
Come on.
What's that supposed to be, kung fu?
Who taught you that load of shit?
No-one calls my dad's kung fu shit!
Judging by that,
your old man's kung fu stinks.
I wouldn't ask him
to clean my shoes.
Perhaps it's better
you call me Father.
Go to hell!
Sit down! Stand up!
Sit down!
All my sons must obey.
I don't even need to use my hands.
You better use them, I'm not scared.
Had enough?
I'll fight to the end!
Your hand! Your stomach!
Your leg! Your head! Get lost!
- Get back!
- Why?
So, you're hiding in
your turtle shell now.
Your skull's like butter.
It's not worth it.
You could study kung fu for the rest
of your life, but you won't beat me.
I won't kill a nobody like you.
It could ruin my good reputation.
Bend down and crawl between my legs.
Then go home to your pig-stys.
Crawl!
Go on!
Wait!
Aren't these your pants?
What's that supposed to be, kung fu?
Who taught you that load of shit?
Your skull is like butter.
You could study for the rest
of your life, but you won't beat me.
I won't kill a nobody like you.
It could ruin my good reputation.
Bend down and crawl.
Go back home and clean pig-stys.
Crawl between my legs, crawl!
Careful with that wine.
It's very expensive.
It smells good.
Let me dry your cloak.
Hey, sexy, where are your trousers?
My God! It's burning!
You burnt my cloak!
That's my best cloak!
My wrists!
Your wrists seem to be very weak.
More rabbit food.
Tea's weak and it's cold again.
Teacher, you're giving me
a headache.
Eat!
Weak wrists?
Can't pick up your food? Here.
Teacher, I'm finished.
- That was quick.
- Yeah.
Use these smaller cups
and pour it back again.
Go on.
I wish I'd known
about this part first.
Oh, this is killing me.
- Hey, Freddy.
- What?
Crack this walnut for me.
No, you've got to do it this way.
Now you try.
Please, teacher!
Haven't I cracked enough?
To hell with this.
Why don't we take a walk?
All right.
- I did it!
- You won again!
Look at this!
- You're very quick!
- Of course!
Place your bets.
My money on the right.
Hey, get going now.
What, go now?
I haven't made my wine money yet.
I've still got more money to win.
- There! Who's betting?
- Back your winner now.
Come on, lift up the cup!
Enough noise!
Lift it up!
You win! Ha, ha!
We won again! This is great!
I knew you would.
We've got enough for a good meal
and wine. We're rich!
You there, old man.
I'll play a game with you.
Right! This is my lucky day.
Go ahead, choose.
Let's see.
- See? It's not there.
- Hold it.
Watch it!
Think you're quick, huh?
Well, my eyes are quicker.
Lay off!
So, you're trying to cheat, huh?
Police! Police!
Everybody move!
Teacher!
Trying to escape, huh?
Hey! Hold it!
You're a dirty thief.
Give me back my money!
I don't have your money.
Meathead, don't you know who I am?
Who cares!
I'll tell you who I am,
I'm Iron Head.
Oh, that's really hard!
Scared?
Hey, baldy!
Get this straight, pay the money.
I don't care if you're a tiger!
I warn you shitface,
I choose who I bury next!
Say your prayers, because
you're about to feel my iron head!
- His head's too hard!
- Don't give up now!
Let's see you stop Iron Head.
Good, very good!
You sure can jump.
Bet you never guessed you'd end up
jumping into someone's pants!
Why, you!
Here, boy.
Great, it works.
Here, hard nut, try this!
Are you still Iron Head?
That's enough, please!
Sure!
Teacher, my wrists are breaking!
One, two, three, four, five, six...
Oh, my hands!
No more exercises.
Go fetch some more wine.
OK, teacher.
Ru Yi's Restaurant.
Waiter!
- Some wine.
- Shall I fill it up?
No three cups will be enough.
- Is that all??
- Come on, be quick!
Here you are.
Damn it! Where's that stupid boy
with my wine?
The bastard!
That's him!
Old man, what school are you from?
And you?
Old man, have you heard
of the King of Sticks?
Yes, of course. I've no doubt
Beggar Su rings a bell.
- Beggar Su?
- The same.
Let's get out of here.
Wait! You don't believe that liar?
- Why not?
- See his hands?
Beggar Su wouldn't be shaking
like that. You can see he's a fake!
So you think you're being funny.
I'm not fooled so easy.
But I'm not lying, I am Beggar Su!
Well, let's see.
- Teacher!
- The wine!
It's water!
Idiot! Now see what you've done.
Teacher!
Take that!
They were damn lucky. Next time
I'll take them apart! Let's go.
Cheer up, eat something.
Teacher,
it's my fault you were beaten.
It seems
bad luck follows you around.
I've seen a lot of things,
but till today,
I've never been beaten in a fight.
He wasn't better, but you've
no strength without your wine.
You sure can talk.
True, but if I was taught better,
I could've beaten that jerk.
You mean to say I'm not
teaching you right?
You're just pushing me around.
You're teaching me how to be beaten.
Your father is without question
an excellent martial arts master.
His methods
are amongst the best,
so why would he ask me
to teach you my style?
So you could torture me.
He asked me because he knows
I've got a secret style.
Tell me then!
The secret of my Eight Drunken Gods!
I suppose you'll teach me
The Crawl of the Drunken Cat!
That shows your damned ignorance.
Dozens have begged me to show them,
I've always refused, so there!
Don't be fooled by my staggering,
there's power inside to kill,
It looks real enough, yet it isn't,
the pretence lets you win.
Clever, isn't it?
Why haven't you shown me yet?
You must know the basics,
or all your work is wasted.
Why do you think
I've been pushing you?
So you can master the techniques
of the Eight Drunken Gods.
- I think you're ready.
- Really?
To study my style, you'll find it
easier if you have a drink first.
Drink up.
Have another cup.
Freddy, did you go to school??
Yes, for a while.
Drink up the wine.
- Cup shall not rest.
- I'll recite a poem.
It'll put your ears to the test.
Power and wealth are to no avail
when only our drinking prevails.
Boy, enough, enough.
Sober men and sages
are both lost through the ages.
All our brave drinkers
shall never die.
Shing Fung produces
the finest of wines.
The best soldiers
of Shien Yang are always young.
Even the King
couldn't stop my drinking.
Let's drink a toast
to our ship that's sinking.
With uplifted cup,
I say to the moon:
Why does my shadow appear to swoon?
Wine in a radiant cup you see.
Put down that cup,
the horses await thee.
Fallen in the field of battle, the
soldier says who will remember me?
Who will remember me?
The God Lu, the drunkard
with inner strength.
The God Li, the drunken cripple
with the powerful right leg
The God Jun, the drunkard
holding a pot in his arms.
The God Lan, the drunkard
with the sudden deadly waist attack.
The God Chan, the drunkard
with the swift double-kicks.
The God Tso, the drunkard
with the powerful throatlock.
The God Han, the drunken
flute player of the powerful wrists.
The God Miss Ho, the drunken woman
flaunting her body.
Ouch!
Come on, boy, this is serious.
That's meant for women.
Miss Ho is a woman, yes,
but she is strong. Watch and learn.
- Can you do it?
- I've got it.
- Put some energy in.
- Yeah, OK.
This is sissy. I won't do it.
Mr Wong, why did you persuade
the people of Bull Hill
not to sell me their property? Well??
Was it because of
that business with your son?
That will be settled in good time.
I'm not responsible.
What's your game?
What is yours?
I'm most interested
to know why you want to buy.
The graveyard
on that hill is cursed.
It's disturbing family spirits.
It's destroying my feng shui,
so I must buy it.
They'll get more than $20 per lot,
it's good money for that land.
Your concern isn't wanted.
I don't think it's that simple.
There's a curse on the name of Li
and it must be exorcised.
I've got three childless mistresses.
They can't even produce
a chicken egg!
Perhaps you have a little problem?
You can't hide anything
from me, Mr Li.
And what's that supposed to mean?
This - you want Bull Hill
to get what's under the ground.
You're mad!
- The coal!
- The coal??
You know well about
the rich coal seam down river
and you have a large interest
in the coal company.
You can fool the farmers,
but you can't fool me!
There's a big deposit there.
Let's discuss a share.
If you don't interfere,
there's 20% in it for you.
Is that so? I'm highly flattered.
So kind. But I refuse.
In the first instance,
it's not yours to give.
That land
belongs to the village. Now go!
Robert Wong, don't try to stop me,
there are ways and means!
$1,000 for the death of Robert Wong.
Robert Wong is dead.
Martial Arts Masters Feast day.
- Everything ready for the ceremony?
- Yes.
See that there's plenty of wine
on table one.
Well, it's you again.
Big funeral??
Are you a masochist, coming here
looking for more punishment?
Are you still itching?
Yeah, I'm itching all right.
My hands are restless.
Good, I'll bake another dish.
- What's that, sir?
- Filleted boy on stick.
Get my stick.
So you cook?
I'll try this.
Good, real tasty.
Master.
Cheers.
I'll have the skin off your...
Here, bite this.
Wow, your teeth are sharp!
They bit right through the bowl.
Now what?
Be careful now, toothy,
take it easy.
I did warn you.
Sit still!
Push off!
That's called a Fart
for the King of Sticks.
That's called Dog Eat Shit!
Not quite!
No sooner said.
He's pissed.
The old man will like this.
Teacher, I got some wine for you,
some real good stuff.
A present from the King of Sticks!
Teacher!
Teacher?
"Freddy, one year has passed, the
time has come to go our own paths."
"I've taught you all the techniques,
the magic of kung fu."
"Practise well and remember,"
"The Eight Drunken Gods
is the ultimate kung fu."
"My home is the world, try not to
miss me. Go home and be a good son."
"Remember, if you ever need me,
I'll come. Beggar Su."
Teacher! Teacher!
Teacher!
Straighter.
Master Wong!
Master Wong, Li and his men
are digging up on Bull Hill.
- Really?
- Yes, sir.
You boy, tell my men
I'm up on Bull Hill. Be quick!
This way.
Your skill in kung fu is renowned.
I'd like to compliment you, Mr Wong.
Who are you?
I've never seen you before.
Why do you want to kill me?
I'm Thunderfoot, I kill for money.
Today I have a worthy opponent,
I'd like to pay you my respects.
I've heard of you, a cold-blooded
assassin who'd sell his own brother.
That's me.
But killing me,
you won't find that so easy.
Then I suppose you'll wish me luck.
Hands are for door knobs
and legs break down doors.
See? 30% hands, 70% legs.
Robert Wong,
are you ready to meet your death?
Father, are you all right?
Don't worry, I'm here now.
You're back, you bastard.
I'm a master now. Whoever
insults you pays with his life.
That I swear!
It's you again.
Good. You can help
bury your old man, shitface.
We'll see.
Hey, Master Wong, the day you
fathered that asshole was a sad day.
Careful, or I'll rip you apart!
Dumb-ass, go and clean pig-stys
or I'll have to bury you too.
Not me, you bastard,
but the worms will grow fat on you.
Today's my lucky day,
two for the price of one.
Up yours!
Hey, hold it, hold it, wait for me!
- Wait!
- Teacher, how did you get here?
Now for some fun.
I must see this fight.
Beggar Su, get lost,
this is not your business.
That's where you're wrong.
It's my business all right.
Don't be afraid, I won't lift
a finger, that won't be necessary.
He can do it alone,
he'll outwit you every time.
Drink, boy!
Teacher, it's very strong,
what is it?
100% proof, the way I like it.
I'm drunk.
I'm the God Lu,
the drunk with inner strength.
The cripple Li!
The drunk with a strong right leg.
The God Lan.
A sudden attack to the waist,
the God Jun!
Holding a big pot in his arms,
Han's gone mad!
Well done, The Eight Drunken Gods.
Patience, you've
not seen it all yet.
The God Han.
He's the flute player
with the powerful wrists.
Tough man!
Your flute is bent.
Now, the God Tso!
The drunkard with the...
Powerful throatlock.
I lock!
Go ahead, then!
Now your lock is broken.
The Devil's Shadowless Hand.
Very clever.
The God Chan!
The God Chan won't reach old age!
Where's the drunken Miss Ho?
Ho, ho, ho...
Wait! I forgot to practice.
What?
I didn't bother.
Oh!
Teach me now.
It's too late!
Freddy!
She'll appear without a shadow,
just perform the actions.
Watch close and you'll see one.
Try and combine all seven gods and
try and see her as your own Miss Ho.
Ho? You want Miss Ho? Sure.
Go away! Get lost!
This is called
Widow Seeing Lover Off.
That's called
Woman Sitting on Toilet Seat.
You missed.
Putting on Make-up.
Pretty girl looks in the mirror.
These are the famous
Eight Drunken Gods?
You think you're
the only master here.
Well, my drunken gods don't mess
around. Nobody can fight like them.
I must be getting addicted.
Here's to Miss Ho.
He did it!