Hey, don't vomit. If you do, I'll make
you eat every bit of it.
Now for a loop-the-loop, so get ready!
What the hell's Brooklyn doing at the controls?
He throws up every time he grabs the joystick!
He's a mechanic, not a pilot!
I've heard it before, Bebe.
But it's time he and Mary-Ann got acquainted.
I told you to take your hands off your weapon.
I'm not on a suicide mission with Brooklyn.
We land in five minutes.
That's government bullshit.
Hope you're right, man.
Looks like a real hullabaloo.
What's this, another war?
Bad things happen when you tool with a gun.
Hey, listen to this!
I bet we'll be buried in money
by this time tomorrow!
What's Kyron 5's level?
What's this line for?
We go in, we get the chips.
And that's it.
We go in, we get the chips,
and we get out.
That's what Bancho said.
Hear that? Just now? A strange sound?
Look, it's burning!
What worries me is what took 'em down.
Let's go to Borneo.
It's still hot.
What's wrong?
Listen, let's go to Borneo.
Enough of that, Bombay.
Take it off.
Robocola, Pepsi type.
Made on Island 8JO, 2023.
How nostalgic.
You know, I was thinking.
We can move it better than
some lousy chips.
What?
A Gunhed.
Too heavy.
I told you we only came to
get the Kyron chips,
and I told you to stop playing
with that, didn't I?
Bad things do happen when
you tool with a gun.
All right!
Brooklyn, let's go!
Your routine, Brooklyn.
Rangers.
We're treasure hunters.
Maybe we want to know why you're here.
I only wish you were right about that.
Electric barrier?
We can't go back?!
And you buzz all the way out here?
Kind of a long hop.
This isn't Texas anymore.
We want this Biodroid as badly as you!
It's not very wise to make a ranger angry.
We're gonna get the chips with Bombay.
You cover us while we go ahead.
What if she wakes up?
I'm picking up something.
Moving right for you.
I know.
A sound activated mine's drifting in the air.
Cut all voice communication.
All sensors on mute.
It really is. A series nine R two, 2010.
It's ancient. It won't explode.
Where's Bombay?
This can't be happening.
We gotta save Bombay!
She's right.
Like you said, we're bandits.
Bebe!
Is that all you care about?
My partners died for this.
I won't give it up for anything!
What're you doing?
My leg!
It hurts!
All of a sudden, the Biodroids launched
an attack against human beings.
One of them stole the vial and returned
here, as if programmed to do so.
Bad break for us treasure hunters.
Bancho, if he was alive, would've said,
"Forget the chips, go get the vial."
Where the hell is Nim?
Who are you?
I'm the one who saved you.
Then why were you hiding?
You looked weird. Screaming and weeping...
I was with someone else.
Where is she?
You two wanna get off this island?
It's no use.
What about the ocean?
Just try.
That's Eleven. I'm Seven.
Eleven lost her voice.
Who are they? What kind of place is this?
A plan might help.
Use these kids?
No, don't.
Eleven will take you to Kyron.
This is dangerous. This isn't child's play.
Where did you get this?
It's garbage from the Robot War.
Show me where!
Run!
Because you saved their asses,
this place is too dangerous now!
My seat.
I'm a mechanic.
I don't drive.
Saving my butt?!
You... saved my butt?!
Adults... Always trouble.
The only way back to Mary-Ann
is through Kyron Dome.
Nim's plan is to take this truck first,
then walk, climb and crawl.
According to Eleven, it's at least
twenty hours to Kyron.
Brooklyn! Brooklyn!
It's a nickname.
I don't know what it means.
Bancho called me that.
Where are we?
Gunhed parts.
Everywhere.
It started yesterday. You brought that
strange, eerie sound with you.
We need a Gunhed in order to
get that monster robot.
Manipulate a finger a certain way, and
it will activate the energy matrix.
The processor’s dog meat.
But the core's in good shape.
I can convert it to a manned machine.
What we need is a pilot.
Gimme the vial, Nim.
A chemical accident.
Don't you wanna find out
what Kyron's up to?
Seven, show the via! to the camera eye.
The new and ultimate energy form.
I graduated from Beverly Hills High School.
The countdown?
At the Kyron Dome?
Brooklyn! Brooklyn!
Nim! Nim!
If we get to work on this Gunhed here,
we can get to Kyron again.
We need this Gunhed.
And a pilot.
Me? You must be kidding.
I'm a mechanic.
I get carsick in a cockpit.
That's how I lost everything.
Air Force... My job...
If Bancho hadn't picked me up...
Not a chance.
What'd you expect to find?
Ah, a Balkan gun.
What else?
A weapon rack. With a six-barreled
missile launcher...
Why did you come back? Nim told you to?
You'd get your butt blown off without me.
First, the vial. Then the keyword.
And Kyron 5 will have total
control of the planet.
As long as we have the vial,
Kyron 5 won't wake up.
But I don't like the way the
Biodroid died in the pool.
What were the shining worms
that pierced Bebe?
Found them?
Bebe?
Bebe!
Nim! Can you hear me?
Answer me, Nim. Nim!
Nim! Nim, can you hear me? Nim!
Nim, can you hear me? Nim!
Shut up and listen.
The Biodroid has regenerated.
It's after the vial.
The Gunhed got hit too.
The energy matrix is dead.
What's this? For God's sake, what is this?
Anyway, I'll see you at Kyron Dome
in twenty hours.
The Gunhed will be there too.
Fuel tank, fuel tank, fuel tank
for air-conditioning.
Seven, put this in the fuel tank, would you?
Seven?
Hey, be careful with it, Seven.
Where's Nim? What happened to
the two of them?
That's enough.
Let's party, Gunhed...
We'll fill you up on the road.
Who's the boss here, anyway?
FonNard...
We've got the weapon rack on.
Your time's up, Seven.
Explode the sidewalls.
Give me thirty seconds after the explosion.
Let's go, Gunhed.
Seven, you promised.
Get back to the truck.
Activate the environmental sensor.
Optical scope "On".
Number 1, check. Number 2, check.
Radiation sensor check!
Infrared sensor check!
Rear weapon rack in number one position.
Gather up your courage.
Slow and easy. FonNard.
What is this?
Get down! Down! Down! Down!
Don't embarrass me!
All right, fonNard...
Warm up the chain gun.
We'll see if it works.
Ready to fire!
Do something about the noise!
Activate the grappling gun.
What's that sound?
I don't like surprises!
Check the cooling system!
Please, Gunhed. Move your butt, will you?
Good.
Don't fall, don't fall.
Huh? Optical? What's that?
Can't you make it simpler?
No sweat, buddy.
Seven?
Sorry!
Where the hell are you?!
By the booster.
Get up here, on the double!
I can't.
Help him, Gunhed.
Can't you turn your leg or something?
You're a man, Seven. Try it!
Even a woman couldn't do it!
In forty seconds I have to fire the booster.
Go ahead, I'm prepared to die.
Stop the sequence.
Fifty-five tons doesn't sound so bad.
Fire the booster!
The "NOSE" is coming down. I got it!
Hurry up and fire!
Fire!
Don't play with the bomb, Seven.
I connected the cable, Gunhed.
Any reaction?
Yeah, I'm counting on you.
Enemy sensors think Gunhed's
getting the data down there.
If we could only fool the
vibration sensitive one...
I know. I'll confuse them
with these bombs.
Ten minutes will be enough. After that...
I'll do what I like.
We'll get off this island together.
Maybe I don't want to leave.
Maybe I like it here.
Bad things can happen when
you fool with a gun.
Brooklyn, we've hidden some food and water.
If it's marked "Seven," it's safe.
"Eleven" is dangerous.
I have to cut the voice communication.
Anything else?
Don't die.
Yeah, I won't die.
Got the data?
Any info about Nim and Eleven?
Such a sensitive answer!
Show me level 260.
Seven's gonna save ten minutes for us.
Be aggressive.
Blow up A-S.
What's this?
So, we take a ride.
If they detect us, right?
How far can we get in ten minutes?
Well, then, Gunhed, my dear...
Let's try tank mode, shall we?
This is a bad joke. In fact,
this is a moving coffin.
Oil canal? You didn't say you could swim.
You could've asked for my opinion
about this. We're not waterproof.
I'm talking about discipline, numb-nuts.
We'll get off at 385 and get the coolant.
So, now what?
Then let's get off at 381.
So... then... what?
Brooklyn! Brooklyn!
How long have I got?
We're trapped inside the reactor.
Thanks for letting me know.
I'm going out!
Do it quickly, Gunhed! I'm coming out.
Hurry up, Gunhed! Quicker! Faster!
Can't you make it move faster?
Tell me exactly what's gonna happen.
What'll happen if they find us?
Cheer up, everybody.
You too, "NOSE".
You're surrounded.
Come out with your hands up.
Can't make it! We're out of fuel.
This is the last gas station.
The upper floors are death valley.
I'm not playing.
Just getting ready to go it alone from here.
In those vessels? Those whiskey barrels?
Robots and whiskey, huh?
So long.
I gotta go it alone.
What're you talking about?
You serious? About the whiskey?
What's the ammo situation?
Doesn't give us much time.
And your armor's in lousy shape.
She scared me to death. That's why...
What if we draw the Aerobot's attention?
The Biodroid?
Can Nim handle it alone?
You related to somebody named
Bancho, by any chance?
Just checking.
Show them just how good we really are.
You got it, buddy.
Gunhed, standing mode!
I knew you'd say that.
Don't booze up, Gunhed.
Who's sending this?
Come on, straight ahead. I'm here.
Come over here. That's right.
What the hell is that code?
C'mon, tell me, Gunhed.
Yeah, big boy, come on!
Geronimo!
Bebe!
Where's Seven? Seven!
I kept my promise.
Where's Gunhed? He died?
What'll happen to Gunhed?
Look! A message from Gunhed!
He's alive!