Do you enjoy it?
Yes, but you have to take me to the
Ocean Park next time
Okay, if only you are a good boy
I'll bring you to go
Got it
Where is mom?
When will she come back?
Your mom went somewhere else
She thinks that I'm not good enough
for her, she left me
Next time, I will take you
to your mother, okay?
Okay
But, are you going to leave me
Iike mom?
Of course not, I love you very much
I will always stay with you, okay?
You're quite a caring step-father
I knew it
You guys have no other better place
to go
Tony, come here
Mom
Tony
Are they all your boyfriends?
She is not that good
Oh, they are your boyfriends
Bullshit
I came to take back my son
You dumped him before he was born
and now you want to take him back?
You didn't eat breakfast?
How come out have such good appetite?
Charles, the world is changing everyday
In the past, a kid means nothing to him
But today, he means the world to him
I changed my mind
I want to be a good father
You have been a step-father for years
It is my turn now
Tell his lawyer to come talk to me
The court will decided
who can keep him
Laws stand on the rich side
If we check the DNA, you'll definitely
lose
You ex-marine from the British force
try to mess with me?
Go back to England for begging
What does it have to do with England?
You are nonsense
I am a Chinese, I live in the SAR
of China
I am happy
I didn't marry you
The son belongs to me and Mr. Chiu
He has nothing to do with you
If you go to court, you will lose for sure
Besides, we just got married
We will take Tony to see his grandfather
in America soon
Don't be stiff-necked all the time, okay?
Stop, I don't want to be involved in
your family business
I think you have come to the wrong
place
You should go to the Social Welfare
Department right now
Tony, let's go
Dad
Get lost
Why making so many troubles?
I just want to take my son back
Go
Move
Damn you
Give me back my son, now...
Don't be this, come on
It's okay, hurry up
Damn you British dog
Don't blame me of bullying you
This sum of money is more than your
pension
Go get yourself some medicine
Go
Dad...
Attention, that guy has arrived
Everybody standby
You see? It is nothing special
Who are you looking for?
I am looking for your boss, Mr. Dick
Mr. Dick is not here
you better leave now
Stop...
Don't under-estimate him
Everybody, go get him
Stop...
Stop. You'll have no way out
Game over
We will do whatever it takes to get him
Don't let him go up to the roof
It's the 69th floor, he's almost reached
the roof
Go get him
Stop! Stop!
Mr. Charles Cheuk
Mr. Dick
you said this building is best guarded
in Shenzhen
But all your security guards are thieves
They aren't even qualified to be a
security guard
When I came here earlier
they paid no notice
But started to chase after me like
I am a murderer
They use useless weapons
If I was just a rude visitor
I think I would have been dead
I am very sorry
I think you need to rehire some useful
guards
A good guard is to solve problems
Not some fools who only know abusing
violence
If not, they will only cause more troubles
Mr. Charles, I need your help
to train and reorder them
Go back
Okay, bye
Today Mr.Cheuk gave us a valuable
lesson
Mr. Cheuk is our country's security
specialist
He is a martial art coach, too
He is very good at martial art
and self-defense techniques
You guys should learn from Mr.Cheuk
Yes
Everyone
violence is not a solution
Chinese people are not barbarians
If you want to do a good job
you have to control everyone's temper
Remember to control your temper too
okay?
Got it
Happy birthday
What are you doing? Are you okay?
We wish you happy birthday
Today is your birthday, congratulations
But,
I am showering
I showered you when you were little
Right
I am a grown up now
Are you shy?
We did this because you are an adult
now
Get out...
You guys should have waited until
finish showering
Uncle, happy birthday
Good Come on
Make a wish
I picked this cake
You've already applied to stay in HK
What other wishes do you have?
You guys can spend a lot of time
with me in Hong Kong
But I've got lots of chances here
You see, lots of HK people always
come here to eat and shop
They come everyday
That is not the same
Make a wish for a girlfriend, hurry up
Right, find a girlfriend
Come on
You are not young anymore
The girls in Hong Kong look modern
and smart
You will sure find someone you like
I will introduce girls to you, okay?
The daughter of Aunt Yee is very pretty
Right, she's got a great body too
No, please
When you get your travel document
to Hong Kong next week
you can stay in HK for 2 months
Uncle will help you get the citizenship
in Hong Kong
It will be easier to travel back and forth
I will think about it
Why?
You don't have to think anymore
Listen to me, come next week
Enough
Dad, can you still punch like before?
Of course, look
Really? That's great
Why don't we go up to the roof
to practice, okay?
Don't you regret?
Why would l?
I will beat you down
We will see
Okay
Dad, you've got some skills
You thought that I didn't practice
anymore
I practice everyday when I wake up
in the morning
Really? Come again
Okay
Watch me
Son, do you want a good lesson?
You want me to hold your leg?
Sorry...
Dad, I will go get you some tea
Damn, you improved a lot
Our car broke down
What happened?
How is it? Can't you fix it?
No, I can't
I thought you can help me save some
money
Now I need to find some way to get
to the train station
Don't talk like that
Forget it, we better think of something
Is your car broken down?
Do you need some help?
Hey man, are you going to Hong Kong?
Yes
Can you give me a ride?
Sir, you are so strong
If you are a thief, won't I be in a lot of
troubles?
No way, I look so nice
I don't look like a thief
I will pay you
Forget it, get in the car
Thanks
What?
It's okay, I've found a ride
Bye Bye
My name is Cheuk, Brian Cheuk
I am a security officer
Hello, just call me Charles
Mr. Charles, what kind of business
are you in?
I am not a business man
I am a driver
I was a soldier before
Soldier? ln China?
No, in Hong Kong
I was a Chinese soldier under the
British Army before 1997
a freak left by the reunification
Don't say that, you are smart
the best candidate to become a security
officer
The HK economy is so poor now
thieves are everywhere
What good laws and rights in HK
There are laws and right in HK
Laws? Laws are written to protect
the rich people
Fair justice never exists
Looks like you are unhappy with
the society now
Yes, I've decided to bomb those
people I hate to death
Good! Blow them away with what?
Plastic bomb
Do you know how to make a bomb?
Of course not, how would I know
how to make a bomb?
End of your ride
You can find a taxi over there
Thank you
Brother in law, sister said
that she is taking Tony to America
I won't bother you anymore, see you
Okay
Bye
My name is Horn, other than working
in a garage
I am also an insurance agent
health food salesman
If you want to be a film extra
I can help you
No need, I come from China
Do you want money exchange?
My exchange rate is 2 to 1
Don't bother him
What did your sister say?
She told me not to be so nosy
Because if Chiu takes Tony to America
to see Chiu's father
he will get 2/3 of his inheritance
It is worth about US 1 billion
That's great, your sister is going to be
rich
But the three sons in Chiu's family
don't have any children
I don't know how that asshole
could give birth to Tony
I was beaten up by them couple
days ago
It hurts really bad
But, I am a nice person
I kept it to myself and didn't tell anyone
Also...
They took my money too
Brother in law, you are very handsome
Did he mention where to put the ransom
It's not like this...
I raised him up, but he is Tony's dad
I only hope to get his custody
It's that simple
What the hell? This is family problems
You should go to the Social Welfare
Department
Here is the Organized Crime Bureau
I can charge you with wasting
an officer's effort
Officer...
Honey
Officer, listen to me
Take your son home, I am very bush
right now
Okay...
This is it
Leave?
Do I have to get you the number of the
Social Welfare Dept?
Crazy
Don't make me mad, otherwise
I will bomb you guys to death
This is not a bad idea
Don't joke around, think carefully?
Are you trying to fool me?
Brother Charles, you can do it
We can ask Fatty to come back from
China
Are you crazy? We will never get away
with it
Don't worry. I will call Fatty to prepare
the tools
I will go make a phone call
Okay...
Brother Charles, it will be fine
But... it'll be shit
Should we make such big trouble?
Guess who this is?
Uncle
Why is it taking you so long to change?
No too long, where are they?
They are in the VIP room
let me tell you a bad news
They want to make a match for you
Are you kidding me?
They're going to introduce Aunt Yee's
daughter to you
I'll show you
Uncle
Tea Thanks
Tea...
Where are you going?
I want to go get some ice-cream
will you go with me?
Okay
Hung, why are you so late?
They are waiting for you
Waiting for me? For what?
Go in there first, come on
Mother, you called me to come here
just for a dinner?
I still have lots of things to do
Your aunt Cheuk's son in Shenzhen
has come
Aunt Cheuk, hello
I want to introduce her son to you
You want to do a matchmaking?
Where is he?
He is not here yet, sit down, cousin
Have some tea
The editor is calling me
I have to call him back
Excuse me, I have to go make a phone
call
Luckily I left quickly
Are you kidding?
Is this the one?
Aren't we going back?
If you want to go back, go ahead
I am not going back
I hate this kind of situation
Uncle, tomorrow you have to take me
to school and pick me up from it
What? You are so greedy
If you don't promise
I will tell them you are here
How dare you
You know? I will hang you up
and whip you
Uncle, I know you won't
What do you think?
I can't believe my mom wanted
a matchmaking for me
And he is dummy from China
Yeah
I am a famous reporter
If this spread out, how can I face my
friends from now on?
Y2K is approaching, but she is still
doing this corny thing
What are you looking at?
Guess is that the girl they want to
introduce to me?
I don't know
That's right
I will call you late, bye
I want to ask you what are you looking
at?
You don't have to be this mean, do you?
I don't have to be nice to a person
who isn't polite
Who doesn't have manner?
You
Me?
You guys are really here
Sister, how come you know I am here?
My informer told me that you brought
my son here
You are here too?
Okay, we're waiting for you
That's him?
Right, that's him
Sister, stop wasting your energy
I don't need you to introduce girl to me
Sorry, I have never thought of being
your girlfriend
Stop dreaming
There are lots of girls like you
in Shenzhen
Right
I think you're quite a special kind of
man in HK
You are corny
Please show a little respect
Stop arguing
We only want to introduce a friend
to you
So you guys know each other?
Hung, this is my brother Brian
Nice to meet you
Bye
I have a meeting to attend to
I'm leaving now
Bye
You don't want to go in?
What is she?
She is a reporter, Papa rezzi
To explore other people's privacy?
No, only to satisfy the curiosity of
readers
Sister, listen...
If you introduce girls to me again
I will not apple to stay in Hong Kong
No, please don't. No problem
anything you say
Let's go up
Come on, let's go
Come on
Hurry
Uncle, hold it
It will take a long time if we go this way
Let's take the short cut
Okay
This short cut is much more faster
I am late, hurry
You have to pick me up from school
I know
Let's shake on it
You have to listen to the teachers
Thanks for helping me
But if you go in there
you will have no way out
We're expected it already
Do we look like four dogs which just
got abandoned?
Thanks
Shut up
Sit properly
In this mission, everybody has to be
very careful
Because we believe the criminals are
heavily armed
That is why I want to combine the force
of two districts
Boss, your call
What?
He said that he is holding the teachers
and students as hostage
of the Ching yee primary school
He wants a negotiation
Who are you?
Once I was here to report a case
The social Welfare Department didn't
accept my complaint
That is why I came here
My wife is going to take my son to
America this afternoon
You better get my son back
If you don't do it before the school is off
The students will have to stay after
school
including your son
This is a serious crime
you'll be put behind bars for a decade
I have no other choice
You guys don't have any choices either
You better take a look at the trash can
on the street
I have set bombs in each classrooms
If you try anything, I will press the
button
What is the situation?
We will report live at the scene
It's messy here
Don't bother us
Move, the police is working right now
Please co-operate
Go away, No pictures
Get lost
Alpha, ready
Beta, ready
Charlie, ready
This car is quite new, how many
kilometers has it gone?
About 10,000km
This is spacious, I don't know if the
stereo is as good as it looks?
You try it. Try the front and the back
Listen
4 criminals stormed into the Ching Yee
Primary School
and took the teachers and students
as hostage
They demand police to stop one of the
suspect's son from leaving HK today
Miss, please get out of the car
The police is at the scene
What? I haven't finished testing it
I am not going to sell it to you
please get out of the car
Get out of the car
What kind of salesman are you?
Move
Boss, this is a dramatic incident
it is full of excitement and it is touching
The sales of newspaper will go up
tomorrow
Yes
but if we don't have any information on
it
your chance of getting fired will be
higher
What should I do?
Go get some news, go
Find whatever you can on it, go
Stop pushing
It's you?
You?
Do you know what is going on in there?
Everybody knows it except you
Looks like it is very serious
Tell me what happened
A nutcase is holding a group of student
hostages
Nutcase?
Shit, my nephew is in there
I have to go inside
Don't go...
What are you doing?
Stop him...
No
The whole place has been sealed
on one is allowed to go in
If you do that you are going to get
those children killed
I know you guys have lots of snipers
hiding somewhere
It will be useless if you guys kill me
If I die
my three friends here will blow
this place up
I know him
I only have one request
that is to have my son back
If I don't see my son before 3 o'clock
I will blow this place up
We don't have enough time
Please calm down. Give me more time
okay?
All you have to do is go pick him up
at the airport
If I see my son, I will surrender
Here is my son's information
I have faxed it to the Organized Crime
Bureau
Charles
It's you?
My nephew is in there
Please don't hurt him
I only want to see my son
No one is supposed to get hurt
Give me more time
I need some time to get to the airport
Okay, 7 o'clock
7 o'clock, if I don't see my son
I know you are not sincere
Wait for me
Go
Shit, hurry up, it's almost one p.m.
Charles, 100%
Stay calm, don't stir him up
The hostages are still in there
Sir, it's him
You know the suspect?
Yes, he drove me to Hong Kong
I am from Shenzhen
I came here to pick up my nephew
This simple?
You don't believe me?
Detain him
Sir...
What are you doing?
I am his girlfriend, no his fiancee
He is a retired British soldier
He might really have set bombs here
Come kidnap me
What are you doing?
Don't come here
He has a knife, you better don't come
over
He is pointing a knife at my ass
don't come
Don't come over
Stop or I will shoot
Go after them
Yes, sir
The suspects are heading for Wanchai
They've brushed us off
All units, pay attention...
The suspect's car is heading
for Wanchai
Eu car one and two, go after them
Set road blocks
Looks very familiar?
Really? Fasten your seatbelt
I'm not ready yet
You don't have to be that cool
What is your name?
Call me Simna
Simna?
Isn't he dead?
Stop the car...
Stop...
Stop
Here comes Simna
The suspect is heading for Western
District
The license plate number is Hotel
Charlie7010
All units, pay attention...
Simna, can we make it?
What do you think?
My brother in law always keeps his
promise
We must get Tony for him
If not he is going to blow up the school
The worst thing is that we can't get
hold of Tony's information
I don't know what Tony looks like?
Don't worry, I am Tony's uncle
Just count on me
Who is she?
She is...
His girlfriend
What are you talking about?
You don't have to mind what I just said
Without my help, do you think
you could get away?
I don't care, I want to get the exclusive
this time
If not, my boss is going to fire me
So you are a reporter?
Super Entertainment Weekly
I am the famous reporter Hung
Check the car up there is it on the
wanted list?
I will get you this time
Shit, they are here
What should we do?
Do you know what is the quickest way
to the airport?
The Airport express
Wrong, it's the car driven by me
Are you crazy?
What the hell? Why does it take so
long to print the ticket?
Sorry, Mr. Chiu. They are working on it
Radio, we've discovered the suspect's
car on Ching Ma Bridge
Follow him
When you discover the kid
inform me immediately
Tony, are you okay?
How come you don't look happy?
I miss my dad
What? Am I not your dad?
You are not my dad
Asshole, do you really think that
I want to be your dad?
IF it's not because of my dad
I don't want you
Mom, do we really have to go to
America?
Good boy, listen to me
If we go to America, we can have
everything
That is awesome
Stupid
I don't want to go to America
I want to go to school
Stupid
Don't call me that
my name is Tony Wong
Your name is Tony Chiu
Tony
Mr. Chiu, here is your ticket
Go get him
Don't scare him
How can you be so rude to your son?
If it's not for the DNA report
I won't call him my son
Uncle, how come you are here?
I will take you to your dad, okay?
Okay
Let check if those bad guys have gone
yet?
They've gone
Do you think we are blind?
Run
I'm done
Please
Done, let's go
So fast
Let's go
Tony, uncle Charles will take you
to your dad
Tony...
Sister, do you know that your husband
is in trouble?
He is keeping the school teachers
and students as hostage
He is surrounded by police
What the hell?
Damn
Brother-in-law
What are you doing here?
Let me help you
Do you think we are idiots?
Fix him
Hey, someone stole my son
Yes, he is good at Kung-fu
Go get help then, no matter how much
it'll take
I have to take my son to America
Take him away
Yes
Please, follow me
Say "thank you"
Thanks
You have it over there too
I know
Let's take a picture
Attention to all passengers
Come
The New Airport Express is
experiencing technical difficulty
reparation will take 30 minutes
Sorry for any inconvenience caused.
Come on, let's go
I can't believe that they fled away this
easily
No problem, they won't get away
There is another flight to America
tonight
I have to take Tony away
Bobby
Yes, boss, we'll fix it
Okay, let's go to plan 1
It'll be useless for them to take the kid
away
Yes
Uncle Cheuk, I want some water
Hello, let me use your phone please
Charles, this is Cheuk, I've found Tony
Where is he right now?
He is with me, I will bring him back
right now
Hey, I'm Hung from the Super
Entertainment Weekly
I've found your son
you have to let me interview you
Save your nonsense
Iet me hear my son's voice
It's your dad
Dad
Tony
I'm with uncle Cheuk right now
We'll go look for you, be careful
Okay, be good and listen to uncle