And tell Chi Hon to get me
a bowl of pigbone congee.
Tell him to knock before he comes in.
Thief.
I am a thief, come catch me.
Crazy!
Tell the police to catch me...
What are you doing?
I want your purse.
Look, no one arrests me
even I robbed over ten purses.
What should I do?
Help! Rape!
Go to hell...
What are you looking at?
Sir, do you know where my master is?
Who is your master?
The King of Swindlers, Master Wong.
- Master Wong?
- Yes!
He just got released.
Master Wong.
I am leaving now,
take your time in there.
Come look for me again
when you are released. Take care.
No! Come save me.
Master Wong, come back.
Don't come any closer...
Master Wong... Help...
- Twenty thousands.
- I want it!
Aunt Six, what's the matter? Watch out!
One circle.
It should be fine.
I win. It's a big slam...
160 fold! Grandpa Sam.
Grandpa Sam...
Can you pay before you faint?
I need to use the bathroom.
Grandpa Sam...
So, ready?
- We are waiting for you.
- Let's go!
Three Kings, straight flush
in the middle and on the last row.
Three of a kind, full house
in the middle, four aces on the last row.
Three of a kind, full house of 4,
four sevens at the end.
One pair... Two pairs... Straight?
One pair, two pair and straight?
Yeah! You are dead!
Wait.
All straight.
All are straight. Pay up, 3 points each.
I am going to the bathroom.
Hurry. No one wants to be a dealer,
I will do it.
Hurry...
What should I deal first?
Wait. Pass.
Eleven.
What're you doing?
I need to use the bathroom.
Super Twins!
Come on...
- Come on...
- Come on.
You lose!
You don't have to win too much!
Sir, I just got out of jail.
- Let me win some money, OK.
- Honey.
I need to piss.
Honey, help Leung, he is very sad.
Stop wasting my time, OK?
Brother-in-law,
Leung suffered badly in jail.
How badly?
They are not human beings.
On my body,
they tattooed a nasty mark!
Did they rape you?
Five men held me down.
Six, seven people raped me.
Look.
Don't look, let's go.
Don't be like this.
Don't look, it's nasty.
Be strong. Let him see it.
Everybody come take a look.
Aunt Six, come on!
B boy, come take a look,
aunt will give you money.
Do you want to seek revenge?
Turn around!
"I love Ken Choi"
You like Ken Choi? What the hell?
So what? What's wrong with Ken Choi?
Nothing, he is quite handsome.
Yes, what is wrong with Ken Choi?
Nothing...
My god!
Honey.
Asshole! You hate Ferrari so much,
then train a student to kick his ass.
Save your breath. If I teach him,
it will at least take 20 to 30 years.
By then, Ferrari will be dead.
Then why don't you go challenge him?
Yes...
I'll come out from seclusion
but I need $10,000,000 as deposit.
I don't have that much.
You should have told me earlier.
Don't come any closer.
I do have some money.
I do have a little.
Show me.
Only a little.
You only have couple of dollars.
You lied to me, you have what it takes
to become a true swindler.
Really?
Am I handsome?
- Of course.
- What about you?
I am more handsome than you.
You lied to yourself.
You have to do that
to become a true swindler.
That's great.
Master Wong,
can you show me some of your skills?
Lick my shoe clean first.
Again?
I think I will teach you
a little bit then.
Thanks, Master Wong.
Yes, that kid has been in that house
for couple of days.
Who is he visiting?
I don't know! I heard that he's asking
a man to help him seek revenge.
There is a Master Wong
who is rather famous.
But I haven't seen him before.
What should I do, boss?
I don't want to see him.
Help me put him away.
You three, how can you
be representatives of Japan?
I'm predestinated to be an orphan,
that I will be alone for my whole life.
As a swindler, you now have
a strong force around you.
Faster.
This will do.
Ferrari will be scared
when he sees you like this.
Master,
this only can be used in the movies.
Can you teach me some practical tricks?
This is fast and powerful.
Don't get mad.
Master, please come out
from seclusion and help.
OK! $10,000,000 as deposit,
three month's prepayment.
Stop saying $10,000,000,
I only have a little money.
I don't think you have any money left.
I do before.
But on the way back,
you bought a pack of cigarette.
How do you know that?
You can't trick me.
So if I can trick you,
then I can ask you to do whatever I want?
Whatever you want!
- Will you come out from seclusion?
- OK!
You swear.
If you can trick me,
I will come out from seclusion.
OK.
Please don't...
Ma'am, haven't seen you for ages,
I don't know you've got big breasts.
Of course.
Kiss my nipple.
You kiss me too.
How come there is no reactions?
I think he is going to the kitchen
to get a knife to kill me.
Bastard, how dare you don't break in?
How come you are so calm?
Don't be silly,
you don't have big breasts.
- I do.
- You have little breast.
You scam!
I am clipped between,
please come and help.
You are so stupid!
Use your brain!
Leave, go home
and think of something better.
What? You think that you hire
couple of hitmen and it will do?
You only carry a hammer? Man,
put more money into your budget.
Right! At least get a toy gun!
It's real!
Get out.
Honey, are you OK? Honey, how are you?
I am OK!
Stop it, let's go.
Where?
Go back to Hong Kong. I'll go visit
Ferrari and seek revenge myself.
Yeah! It's great!
Honey, when we get to Hong Kong...
I will buy you a diamond ring
for your birthday.
Don't try to scare me.
You never buy me anything
which is worth more than $200.
Let's go.
I don't want it... Help.
Brother-in-law is right.
I want a diamond too.
Don't be so greedy, or you'll get crazy!
Don't get mad! It's just a joke.
Special news. Mr. Cheng Yat-tone,
a billionaire of Hong Kong,
and the famous merchant Mr. Ho Lin.
Both of them
have been missing for a week.
People suspect that
they might be kidnapped...
Your brother-in-law
recorded this part of the news.
He has watched it over a hundred times.
He wants me to watch it a hundred times
until he comes back.
And he wants me to tell him
what I think about this.
I can tell something mysterious.
Is there any lead to this case?
Confidential.
Did the police arrest any suspect?
I said, he is trying to play me.
Be patient.
May be in a couple of days,
he will teach you couple of his tricks.
Honey.
Pizza, have you seen your brother-in-law?
No! Isn't he with you?
Pizza, your brother-in-law
is acting stranger recently.
I think that he has damaged his brain
on that night.
What's wrong with him?
He bought me over ten diamond rings.
You...
So what, I am true to you.
While we were shopping,
he suddenly disappeared.
I thought he came back already.
Come to Ferrari's house at eight tonight.
It's Master Wong.
Mr. Lee, First Love is here.
Let her in.
Hello!
Sorry to let you wait!
Sit...
How come you have so many bodyguards?
Recently,
all my friends have been missing.
So I hired more bodyguards to protect me.
- Get out...
- Yes! Mr. Lee.
Have something to eat.
I am scared.
Don't worry!
After we finish singing,
we will go to my yacht.
Then we will go to the Lamma Island
and eat seafood, OK?
- I don't like seafood.
- Why?
I am allergic to it, look.
Allergy?
Take him back.
Boss.
So, have you finished Lee's job?
Done! But I met a person.
I wonder he's the one
Lon wasn't able to kill.
What does he look like?
Tall and thin, full of secret.
He looks nasty!
Miss, are you talking about me?
It's him, bring him back!
OK.
I don't think I know you.
Let me introduce myself.
I am Master Wong...
who has broken many girls' hearts.
Are you a bad guy or a good guy?
Bad guy!
If a man is not bad, girl won't like him.
You are right!
What do you want?
I want... to break your heart.
OK, get in the car then.
Your car is no good?
Why don't you get mine?
OK, whatever.
This is Master Wong, right?
Just by looking at you,
are you the Fat Dragon?
Thanks for flatting me.
Nice to meet you...
- My pleasure...
- The pleasure is all mine.
No, it's all mine.
Master Wong,
so what brings you to Hong Kong?
I came to learn from you.
You must be joking.
I am not joking.
I heard that you're great in gambling.
If you can teach me, I will be pleased.
So what do you want to learn?
Let's just play mahjong.
How do you want to play, Fat Dragon?
Taiwan style.
OK! $1,000,000 as ante,
$200,000 per fold.
Do you have that much money?
A bank draft of $10,000,000.
I trust you.
How many rounds are we going to play? 32?
Well...
4 rounds?
One hand!
We only need one hand to get the winner,
OK, Fat Dragon?
Good, King of Swindlers, I'm amazed.
Go keep Master Wong company.
Tenth thousand.
Five bamboos.
Red Dragon.
Four of a kind.
Four of a kind again.
Three bamboos.
It'll be a grand slam!
Don't do anything stupid.
Yes, I need to use the rest room,
excuse me.
He's a professional swindler and he'll
know that we've peeped at his dominos.
What is it?
Ghost!
Bitch! Did you peep at my domino?
So? Did you peep at my domino?
No.
Come...
You want this domino for sure.
Don't discard it if you are afraid.
I am afraid that
you will have no money to pay.
I win.
Thank you, it's a grand slam.
200 folds,
everybody pays $41,000,000 please.
You are the dealer,
you have to pay $200,000 more.
But forget it! Give it to your maids.
No wonder you are called
the King of Swindler.
Fat Dragon is really fat.
You want to mess with me?
Don't worry honey, I am here to save you.
You've got great skill...
How come they look like
they are very good friends?
Call me if you want to play again.
Don't worry, have my invitation now.
Let's just play poker this Saturday.
Really? What is the bet?
You won $120,000,000 today.
Then we have to go at least
$500,000,000 on Saturday.
OK.
Your brother-in-law
is hard to understand.
Sign this contract, if you don't come
you've to lose $500,000,000 too.
OK! Leung.
Coming.
- Sign it.
- OK.
Honey. I just won $120,000,000 tonight.
I will buy you couple more diamond rings.
I don't want it, what are you doing?
I am going to buy it.
Help... I don't want it.
I will never forget
what we have done tonight.
Ma'am, we didn't do anything.
Nothing? How dare you?
I am going to commit suicide.
I am going to jump.
You are having an affair with that woman!
Sister, don't be like this.
Brother-in-law,
will you say something please?
She wants to jump,
she really wants to jump.
Even a fool knows that
she is trying to mess up.
If she wants to believe it
then let her die.
After I won that $500,000,000,
I will go find some other girls.
No way, I am not going to jump.
Go get me some dessert.
Don't you dare have another woman.
You really think that
Ferrari will bet with me again?
I signed the contract already.
You signed it for me.
He let me do that
which means that is not real.
I also found out that
all the company under his name...
he sold 20,000 pieces
of dealings in future.
Three of the richest men in Hong Kong
have disappeared.
I think he must have kidnapped them,
to force the stock market to drop.
And use this advantage
to make tons of money.
He is a real good swindler.
He asked me to play on Saturday
because he wants a delay.
I will be trying to gather enough money
and thus leave him alone.
Then he will be making tons of money
in the stock market.
Should we call the police?
If we do,
those rich men will be in danger.
- What should we do?
- Yes!
Bill, after I put on this black suit,
pants and tie,
do I look like a gangster!
You are a gangster!
No way! I graduated
from Fukien University.
I can't find any work
so I came here to work.
Do you know how to read?
Yes! But if I dress like this,
will I get beaten up?
This... You can't avoid it.
No way?
"There is nobody behind the tree."
U graduate student, what does it say?
There is nobody behind the tree.
Idiot!
Boss, I just want to use your restroom.
You don't have to point
so many lazar guns at me.
Stupid! My boss told us
to burn down your house.
We know that you will be homeless.
So we have prepared
the presidential suite for you.
Take him there.
Uncle Lin, hello!
Brother Tone, nice to meet you.
Mr. Lee, long time no see.
How is the real estate business
doing recently?
Who are you?
I am like you guys,
I have been kidnapped.
We are not like you.
Each of us possesses
at least couple hundreds billions.
Do you have it?
After tomorrow night, you won't.
Today the stock market
dropped 3,000 points.
I'll sell everything
the day after tomorrow,
then I will gain couple hundred billions.
If I can get out.
I will talk so much shit about you
on my television station.
No one watches your station.
Give them their late night snacks.
No, we don't want it, help...
Why are you screaming?
You don't like late night snacks?
No! They gave us Viagra every meal.
We haven't eaten anything
for a long time.
What an evil man!
There're no cockroaches found in
these few days. We're starving to death.
I am very smart.
I caught a small crocodile
outside earlier.
I hide it inside my shirt.
It's a house lizard.
No, a crocodile is nutritious.
Give it to me...
No.
- I'll give you a million, give it to me.
- Really?
I will give you ten million.
Quiet! I will give you ten flats,
let me have it.
I'll give you ten better flats!
- Really?
- Yes.
Keep your words then.
I will give you my TV station.
I know you are very kind, right?
Right. Uncle Lin, you can have it.
Here comes the late night snacks.
How come it is not Viagra tonight?
Boss is worried about your health.
Very good!
It is better than abalone.
Forget it, you wanted it yourself.
You still owe me a TV station!
How dare you!
You will lose all your money.
Brother-in-law hasn't come home
for two days already,
should we go save him?
We have to play poker
with Ferrari tonight.
If we don't go,
we will lose $500,000,000 dollars too.
You signed the contract.
We are running out of time,
he must be captured.
I have to go save him.
How?
Gamble for your master.
No way!
Get up straight.
Brother Tone, don't cover it, come on.
OK, smile a little, ready.
Thanks,
you guys can put on your clothes now.
Mr. Lee, you lost 20 flats to me.
Mr. Tone, you lost 10 flats to me.
You are well known, don't try to run.
Uncle Lin, you lost in the contest of
who can pee farther.
No, you lost.
Sorry! I remember it wrong.
We will pay you,
you don't have to take pictures.
Are you trying to blackmail us?
How can you think of me that way?
It is faith that brought us together.
I just want to treasure this moment.
Please don't get me wrong.
Boss,
the stock market will be opened
at 3 or 4 thousand points,
you'll gain a fortune.
Why are you still going to bet with him?
Even if we don't have Master Wong
in our hands,
just by using our secret weapon,
I will win his $500,000,000 for sure.
Why should I worry?
Boss, what is your secret weapon?
It's that DV machine and my glasses.
Fat Pig, use the DV machine
to look at my card.
Will it work from this far?
Wear this glasses and sit opposite to me.
Yes, boss!
Boss, you have a king.
It's awesome, boss!
Wearing this pair of glasses.
I can see any of his cards.
Why should I worry?
We have to play with him then.
Go get ready,
our guesses are almost here.
Yes! Boss!
Where is Master Wong?
Who?
You don't know? I come alone tonight.
Your hair is very pretty.
Stop sweet talking.
It's 7 o'clock right now.
We will play for three hours.
At 10 o'clock,
even if you lose one dollar,
you will lose all of your $500,000,000.
Where is the money?
Not your necklace. It's money, silly!
So much money...
I will talk to you later.
Master Wong's wife
and his sister-in-law is missing.
There must be a conspiracy,
go check it out.
Got you.
Can we begin?
I need to use the restroom.
What if I need to stool?
I think I will wait.
Deal it!
Damn! This house is so big,
how are we going to find him?
- You are right!
- Damn!
Somebody is over there.
Tonight Ferrari is gambling inside,
no one will stay in the garden.
Who said that?
Where are the rich men?
They are in the basement.
Why did you hit me?
You look like a gangster,
that's why I hit you.
Go the hell!
It'll be safe to get changed.
Let's bet small, $1,000.
Sorry! The rule state that
you must bet at least $100,000.
I heard that
you don't know how to gamble.
Don't try to show hand on every hand!
This won't work on me.
Don't worry,
I don't like to show hand this easily.
Up to you, let's go smaller. One million.
Quit.
What the hell? Too big for you?
Stop it!
Sister,
I heard the voice of brother-in-law!
Honey.
- Who are you?
- A thief.
Honey.
Honey?
What a coincidence?
Go find the key.
They are...
This is my wife,
this is my sister-in-law.
Interested?
My sister-in-law is worth ten flats of
"High Class" estates.
What about your wife?
Mr. Lee, because of you.
How about two flats?
One?
Just give me the down payment.
It's at his back.
Found it.
I've got the key.
You bitch!
Let's take care of her, sister.
Pick it up...
Bitches these days do know how to fight.
Woman, where are you from?
Shanghai.
Good, my dear sister!
Let's try to use the handkerchief.
Hurry.
Your Jack is bigger, go ahead.
- Pass.
- $500,000.
Quit.
Are you going to go?
No.
Are you going?
No...
You are not going to go?
No.
"No."
You didn't play every hand,
what the hell is wrong with you?
Do I have to play every hand?
I have to lose money too!
You know it is $100,000 a hand.
Boss, looks like
he is trying to waste time.
He's plenty to lose.
First Love has gone for too long,
go check on her.
If anything happens, then...
Does it hurt?
You two can't take the key from me.
You two can't beat me.
Just did a hole and die, OK?
Sister, hit her.
Let me show you my power.
Almost there...
You bitch, how dare you swallow the key?
Spit it out.
Or I will cut your stomach.
What do you want?
How did you escape?
I can open this kind of lock
with a clipper.
You should have told me earlier!
So I don't have to fight so hard.
Who told you to fight?
Leung is gambling for you.
India Garden, one flat, deal?
Two flats?
You pay the down payment,
I will pay the rest.
Smart-ass, keep fooling around.
I've had couple millions more than you.
At 10 o'clock
I will start to count your money.
Even you lose one dollar,
you will lose all your $500,000,000.
Don't mind me!
I have to go take a shower later.
It's still early.
It's 9:40 now.
The clock stopped by itself.
In 20 minutes you will lose
all of your $500,000,000.
Who are you? I haven't seen you before.
Every time I am in a hurry
you just have to be in my way.
Where are the old fools?
They left by taking a taxi.
You will be going home in a funeral car.
I have changed into woman's clothes,
no one will hit me.
I never seen woman this ugly before.
$10,000,000.
Mr. Leung, are you going to go?
Are you going to go?
Not big enough!
How big do you want?
At least $50,000,000.
OK, $50,000,000.
$50,000,000 then...
He will go!
- Master, sit down.
- Of course.
I will go with your $50,000,000. Card.
Master Wong, you can't play this hand.
It's him who is gambling.
Who said so?
I did!
Mr. Leung should go on with this game.
You're...
I'm the Chairman of the
International Gambling Association.
And...
- I've been the honored director...
- Enough!
Let's stop right now,
we'll gamble tomorrow.
OK.
If you leave now,
you will lose $500,000,000.
What the hell?
I have to play this hand?
Whose money is this?
Yours! I sold all your property.
Honey.
Master.
What should we do?
Play it, or I will lose my money.
Stop acting. Are you going or not?
Go! You can make it.
OK, I will go and I will show hand too.
It is only one hand.
Just a game, win or die.
His covered card is a King.
What is it?
My hand is bigger that yours. Card!
If you want to win,
unless you have all hearts.
Does he have a straight?
You can't make it, right?
I've got yours.
He doesn't have a straight.
You don't have a straight.
Kid, you learned from
the King of Swindlers for so long,
what have you got?
I have a pair of Ace,
let's see how you can beat me.
I have a pair of Ace too,
but my pair goes with a pair of queen.
Your pair goes with a pair of 10.
Mine is bigger than yours, fat boy.
Very good...
No way, you cheated.
Your card is...
How come it is not a king?
That fat boy's eyes are very tired
after a whole night of work.
What he saw was not my card.
But my fingers.
Why should I go
if I don't have a pair of Ace?
You must be crazy!
I quit using
your technology two years ago.
You are out-dated.
Master, your trick worked.
Of course, he thought that
he would bet you for sure.
If not, why would he sit there...
and lose $500,000,000 to me?
What an idiot!
So what, I will give you $500,000,000.
But I will have 50 billion
early tomorrow morning.
I don't think so!
I tell you the truth! Within 25 minutes,
the HK stocks in London
raised 10,000 points...
because the billionaires...
and the government allied to push it up.
The reading is 16,000 points now.
You are lying.
Your fellows betrayed you
to buy in stocks too.
I think you'll lose 10 billions instead.
You assholes!
"Kick his butt!"
Move!
What is he doing?
This is the long lost kung fu,
Fat Mantis?
Isn't this move most powerful?
- It kills without blood.
- Yes!
Leung, you are good!
I wish my boss the Masked-man
will see this scene.
I won't disappoint you.
Leung, you can continue
to be an undercover.
No way!
I have $500,000,000 dollars now,
I will buy Pizza a big diamond and... OK?
You finally want to
buy me a diamond ring?
Of course!
No matter how deep my love is to you,
only a diamond can prove.
Honey, you give
all the $500,000,000 to Leung.
Don't worry.
I have to naked pictures of
the three richest men in Hong Kong,
I think it is worth more than 5 billion.
Really? What do you mean?
It's all exposed.
Don't we still have 5 billion?
Honey...
You told me that you will buy
a huge diamond hill to me.
We have been to Diamond Hill earlier.
We went to Wong Tai Sin too.
Do you want to go to Lok Fu?
Leung, you are mean!
Why are you so mad?
Look at my hand.
Where did you get your nails done?
It's very pretty.
You promised me to buy me a diamond ring.
How can I forget.
Turn around.
What?
This diamond shop belongs to you.
Everything here belongs to you.
Made in London of the opera to the sky
from the boys to men.
Whatever.
Go pick it!