Here! You take this!
You can have this ticket
and keep it!
I'm not paying that ticket!
Jesus! Watch where you're going!
Go down to the cellar and check
the water line to the boiler.
- Do that today, all right?
- Frank, would you give me a hand?
I ain't the doorman, Miss Barrett.
- I'm the building superintendent.
- You're also a human being.
What the hell,
I'll do you a favor.
I asked you last week to fix
the radiator in the baby's room.
Didn't I do that?
It's getting cold in there,
and l--
Okay, it's no problem.
- Stop that carriage!
- Whoa! Get it!
That's my baby!
Watch out!
- Jesus!
- Oscar, watch out!
My God!
Stop that carriage!
- How many are there?
- Fourteen. In here.
I hope you can handle it.
It's been like a nightmare.
How big are they?
Four feet.
Kids, listen up!
Look who's here!
- I thought it was gonna be He-Man.
- Yeah!
I know. Let's all sit down,
and we'll have fun!
Yeah!
My dad says you guys
are full of crap.
Some don't believe
in the paranormal.
He says you went out of business
because you're full of crap.
Song.
Come on, everybody!
He-Man!
- Let's go get a beer, all right?
- Yeah.
- Thank you. Call anytime.
- Bye.
- That's it, Ray. No more parties.
- Here's your share.
I won't take abuse
from overprivileged nine-year-olds.
I know, Z,
but we can't quit now.
The holidays are coming up.
That's our best season.
Man, face it.
Ghostbusters doesn't exist.
In a year, those kids
won't remember who we are.
Ungrateful Yuppie larvae.
- After all we did for this city.
- Yeah.
We conjured up
a 100-foot marshmallow man...
blew the top three floors off
an uptown high-rise...
and got sued by every state, county
and city agency in New York.
Yeah, but what a ride.
If went out into traffic.
I started really running after it.
Then it just suddenly stopped
in the middle of the street.
Did anyone else see this happen?
Sure. Hundreds of people.
- Egon, I didn't imagine this.
- I'm not saying you did.
In science, we look
for the simplest explanation.
- We're ready, Dr. Spengler.
- Start with the negative calibration.
What are you working on?
Trying to determine if human emotions
affect the physical environment.
- It's a theory Ray and I had.
- Can they see us?
No. They think they're here
for marriage counseling.
They've been waiting over two hours, and
we've increased the room temperature.
It's up to 95 degrees now.
My assistant is asking them
to wait another half-hour.
Good. Very good.
Very, very nice.
What do you think?
Excellent.
Do the happiness index next.
- I mean about the carriage.
- I'd like to bring Ray in on this.
Sure. Whatever you think.
But not Venkman.
- Do you ever see him?
- Occasionally.
- How is he these days?
- Peter was borderline for a while.
Then he crossed the border.
Does he ever mention me?
We didn't part
on very good terms.
Then we lost track of each other
after I got married.
- We're ready for the affection test.
- Good. Send in the puppy.
I thought of contacting him
after my marriage ended, but--
Isn't that sweet?
I appreciate your doing this.
Try not to worry.
Here's my phone number.
You'll call me?
Yes.
Don't mention any of this to Peter,
if you don't mind.
No, I won't.
Thanks.
Let's see what happens
when we take away the puppy.
Hi. Welcome back to "World
of the Psychic." I'm Peter Venkman.
I'm chatting with my guest
author, lecturer and psychic...
Milton Angland.
Your new book is called
"The End of the World."
Can you tell us when it will be
or do we have to buy the book?
I predict the world will end
at midnight on New Year's Eve.
- This year?
- Mm-hmm.
That's cutting it a little close,
isn't it?
Just from a sales point of view,
your book just came out.
You won't see any paperback sales
for a year.
It will be another year before
you have the mini-series possibility.
Just devil's advocate,
shouldn't you have said...
- "The world will end in 1992."
- Wait a minute.
Better yet, 1994.
This is not just
some moneymaking scheme.
I have a strong
psychic belief...
that the world will end
on New Year's Eve.
- For your sake, I hope you're right.
- Thank you.
But I think my other guest
may disagree with you.
Elaine, now you had
another date in mind.
According to my source...
the end of the world
will be on February 14...
in the year 2016.
Valentine's Day.
Bummer.
Where did you get your date?
I received this information
from an alien.
As I told my husband...
it was in the Paramus Holiday Inn.
I was having a drink at the bar,
alone...
and this alien approached me.
He started talking to me.
He bought me a drink.
And then I think he used
some kind of a ray...
or a mind control device.
He forced me
to follow him to his room.
That's where...
he told me
about the end of the world.
Your alien had a room
at the Holiday Inn in Paramus?
It might have been a room
on the spacecraft...
made up to look like
a room at the Holiday Inn.
I can't be sure about that.
Of course not.
That is the whole problem with aliens.
You just can't trust them.
Occasionally, you meet a nice one--
Starman, ET--
but usually they turn out
to be some big lizard!
That's all the time
we've got this week.
Next week, though--
Give me Ira.
Hairless pets.
Weird.
Until then,
this is Peter Venkman saying--
See you then.
Norman, we were supposed to have
the telekinetic guy who bends spoons.
He cancelled.
This is the best we could do.
The respected psychics
all think you're a fraud.
I am a fraud.
Mr. Mayor. Lenny.
Pete Venkman.
- Can I help you?
- Yeah, get your hand off me.
Thank you.
I'm an old friend of the mayor's.
I'm Jack Hardemeyer,
the mayor's assistant.
I know who you are. I just don't see
any ghosts anywhere.
That's why I wanted
to talk to His Highness.
We did a job for the city
a while back...
and got stiffed on the bill by some
bureaucratic bookworm like yourself.
You stay away from the mayor.
He's running for governor next fall.
We don't need him associating
with two-bit frauds...
like you and your friends.
I'm a voter. Aren't you supposed
to lie to me and kiss my butt?
Yes, I want you to put the Vigo
in the arch.
Under the arch there.
Everything you are doing is bad.
I want you to know this.
You be careful there, all right?
No one listens to me.
Dana, how are you doing?
How's this Bonington coming?
Fine. This mixture you gave me
works really well.
I make pretty good cocktails,
don't I?
- You're doing quite good work.
- Thank you.
It won't be long
before you can assist me...
in the more important
restorations.
Just a white thing.
- Thank you, Dr. Poha.
- Janosz.
I've enjoyed working here,
but my baby's older now...
so I'm going to try to go back
to the orchestra.
I'm sorry to hear
that you will not be not here.
Could I say good-bye,
maybe bring you to a brunch today?
I have an appointment today.
In fact, I must go.
I don't understand. Every day I say,
"Can you do something?"
You say,
"No, I can't do something."
Do I have bad breath?
- Of course not.
- All right.
I'll give you a rain check.
I think she likes me.
I do. I truly do.
This one's interesting.
Berlin, 1939.
A flower cart took off by itself,
rolled half a kilometer.
Three hundred eyewitnesses.
My best to the coven.
Berlin?
Check Duke University studies
on controlled psychokinesis.
- I pulled it.
- Could you help me?
I need a love potion aerosol...
that I could spray
on a certain Penthouse Pet...
to obtain her total submission.
- Hello, Venkman.
- How's it going, Pete?
Very well. Hi, Egon.
How's school?
I bet those science chicks
dig your large cranium.
They're more interested
in my epididymis.
Let's close up
so you can buy me a calzone.
I can't.
I'm working on something.
But your book came in.
"Magical Paths
to Fortune and Power."
Thank you.
Good luck with that, Venkman.
- Put this on my account, please.
- Sure.
- Look at this.
- Yeah.
What are you working on?
We're just kind of...
checking on something
for a friend.
Neat. Who?
Ray's Occult.
7:00 on weekdays, midnight on Saturday.
Thank you.
- Who?
- Just someone we know.
- I can't!
- Yes, you can.
- Who?
- Nobody!
Can you tell me now?
- Now?
- Dana Barrett!
My Dana Barrett?
I'll get it.
Hi, Ray. How good to see you.
Thanks for coming.
Always glad to help and hug.
- Hello.
- Nice place.
I know I'm asking for the big hurt,
but I'll give us one more chance.
He tortured me, pulled my ears.
- What would you like to do first?
- Examine the baby.
Yeah, and anything associated
with the baby, especially toys.
- Then the buggy.
- Can I put him over here?
- Wherever he sleeps.
- Yes.
- This would be fine.
- This okay?
Lay him down flat.
Sweetheart,
they're going to look at you.
We'll do a cursory medical exam.
Gammel and Pross
Infant Acuity Test?
We'll finish
with an APGAR score.
It won't hurt him, right?
No, I don't think so.
He'll be fine.
- Done this before?
- On a chimp.
I heard Mr. Right ditched you
and ran off to Europe.
He didn't ditch me.
We had some problems...
and he took a good job offer
from a London orchestra.
He ditched you.
Subject is a male Caucasian
of approximately...
24 inches in length.
Subject weighs approximately 18 pounds
and is eight months old.
Okay. Ocular?
Pupillary response normal.
- Auditory.
- Normal.
Axillary reflex.
- Appears to be ticklish.
- Yup, baby ticklish.
You should have married me.
You never asked me.
Whenever I brought it up,
you'd get drowsy and fall asleep.
You never got it, Dana.
I'm a man. I'm sensitive.
I need to feel loved.
I need to be desired.
When you introduced me as "the old ball
and chain," that's when I left.
I may have a lot of personal problems,
but I'm a total professional at my job.
- Egon.
- What?
What are we doing?
He's fine, Dana.
- He's very healthy.
- He's okay.
Where does he sleep?
Here, I'll show you.
Get a stool specimen, please.
Business or personal?
It's a little messy.
We don't want to play,
just sweep for valances.
Very cheerful.
My parents didn't believe in toys.
You want to play
with a big kid?
I should have been your father.
I could have been.
I understand.
Help!
He's gone completely berserk!
You never even had a Slinky?
We had part of one,
but I straightened it.
He had some sort of clear liquid
coming out of his mouth.
Yeah, that happens.
- What do you think?
- He's ugly.
He's not "Elephant Man" ugly,
but...
he's not attractive.
- Was his father ugly?
- Don't listen.
And he stinks.
You are ripe, senor.
Did his father stink?
Yeah? Your daddy was smelly?
- What's your name?
- His name is Oscar.
Named after a hot dog.
You poor, poor man!
But seriously,
is there anything...
unusual about him?
I don't have a lot of experience
with babies.
But you're excited now because
Mama's here to get your stool sample.
- Right?
- Stool sample?
Nothing.
So, what, Brainiac?
I'd like to run some gynecological
tests on the mother.
Who wouldn't?
Let's check the street.
It stopped right there,
in the middle of the crosswalk.
I can get us out there.
Hold on.
We're scientists.
Get out of the way!
Thanks a lot.
We have to do an inquiry.
Thanks. Appreciate it.
- Get out of there!
- Relax, you're on the meter.
I think we hit the honey pot.
Something is brewing under the street.
I've got 1118 on the PKE.
2.5 GEV's on the giga-meter.
What does that mean?
How you doing?
- Me?
- Yeah.
- Fine. It's cutting fine now.
- Great.
- Why are you cutting?
- Why am I cutting?
- Yeah.
- Boss!
Who told you to stop cutting?
Somebody tell you to stop?
- What are you guys doing here?
- Did you tell him to stop?
- Yes. What are you doing?
- What's it look like?
Why don't you let us work?
We let you work.
Relax. He's been working overtime.
Some diaper bag downtown is making us
work on a Friday night. Right?
Of course you're right, Raymond.
Right, Ziggy?
- You guys take it easy.
- Come on.
What have you been doing?
While you were getting coffee
for an hour, I've been digging a hole.
You uncovered an old air shaft.
It just goes on and on.
This is very intense.
We should get a deeper reading.
Yeah, we'll need a deeper reading.
Somebody has to go down there.
I'm stinging!
Listen to me.
What? Who?
l, Vigo, the scourge....
of Carpathia...
the sorrow of Moldavia...
command you.
Command me, lord.
On a mountain of skulls,
in the castle of pain...
I sat on a throne of blood.
What was, will be.
What is, will be no more.
Now is the season of evil.
Evil?
Find me a child...
that I might live again.
Yes. A child.
A child?
A child.
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm good.
The speed is good, boys.
Keep it coming.
We're breaking through.
I see some light.
I'm in some kind of chamber.
There's tile work.
Slime!
It's a river of slime!
There must be 25, 000 gallons!
It's flowing like a river!
Van Horne. Pneumatic transit.
It's the old Pneumatic
Transit System.
Whoa! That's good.
Hold me up.
What do you see?
I'll get a sample.
What's going on here?
- What's the story?
- Hang on.
You boneheads are going
to roust me out again?
I got 3,000 phones out
in Greenwich Village.
I got to check eight million miles
of cable, and you're hassling me?
What do you mean?
The phone lines are over there.
I told you.
The phone lines are over there!
What did I say?
How many times--
You're not with Con Ed
or the phone company. We checked.
So tell me another one.
I've got a major gas leak!
Where do you think this is coming from,
the sky?
Okay, boys. Boys?
Pull me up now.
There's some kind of activity
going on with this stuff.
- Hey, take me up!
- Start it!
What's going on up there?
Come on!
Get me out of this hole!
Sweetheart, hello.
Go back to sleep.
- Who is it?
- It's Janosz.
Hello, Janosz.
This is a surprise.
Hello. Yes?
I happened to be here
in this neighborhood...
and I thought I'd stop by
and see how it is with you...
because of all this blackness.
We're fine. Thank you.
Then you're okay?
How's the baby?
He's okay.
He's sleeping.
- But I wooed.
- That's okay.
You don't need anything?
You want me to come in?
- No, thank you.
- All right.
I just thought that
I would check. You know.
Well, don't let the bedbugs bite.
Good night, Janosz.
Before we begin this trial,
I want to make one thing clear.
The law does not recognize
the existence of ghosts, nor do I.
I won't listen to malarkey
about goblins, spooks and demons.
Stick to the facts
in this case.
Leave the ghost stories to the kiddies.
Understood?
Sounds like an open-minded guy.
He's called "The Hammer."
It's in the hands
of our lawyer now.
You guys are making a big mistake.
I do mostly tax law
and some occasional probate stuff.
I got my law degree
at night school.
That's fine, Louis.
We got arrested at night.
Put these guys away fast...
and make sure
it's for a long, long time.
I don't think it will be hard
with this list of charges.
Good. Very good.
Violating a restraining order...
willful destruction of public property,
fraud, malicious mischief.
See you in a couple years
at your parole hearing.
You won't take us alive.
All right, let's get on with it.
Your Honor, ladies and gentlemen
of the audience.
It's not fair
to call my clients frauds.
The blackout was a big problem
for everybody.
I was stuck in an elevator for two hours
and had to make the whole time.
But I don't blame them.
'Cause one time I turned into a dog
and they helped me. Thank you.
Very good, Louis.
Short but pointless.
Mr. Fianella,
please look at Exhibits A through F...
on the table over here.
Do you recognize this equipment?
The cops took that
from their truck.
Do you know what this equipment
is used for?
I don't know.
Catching ghosts?
I remind the court that the defendants
are under a restraining order...
that strictly forbids them
from performing services...
as paranormal investigators
or eliminators.
So noted.
Now, Mr. Fianella...
can you identify the substance
in this jar marked Exhibit F?
Yeah, that's the stuff.
I've worked underground for 27 years.
I never saw anything like this.
Whatever's there,
they must have put there.
- No, we didn't!
- Shut up!
So you were just trying
to help out a friend.
Who was scared of what was happening
to her, and when you're scared--
- What?
- There was no evil intended.
- I live here.
- You live here.
When you live in a place, you don't
want nothing bad to happen. What?
It will never happen again.
It's a one-shot deal.
- Objection, Your Honor.
- What?
- He's leading the witness.
- Sustained.
- Give me a break. We're both lawyers.
- Mr. Tully...
do you have any questions
for this witness...
that might have some bearing
on this case?
- Do I?
- No, we've helped them enough.
No, Your Honor.
Your witness.
Please tell the court why you
and your co-defendants...
dug a very big hole
in the middle of First Avenue.
With so many holes there,
we thought no one would notice.
Keep that up,
and I'll find you in contempt.
I'm truly sorry.
I'll ask you again.
Why were you digging the hole?
Please remember you're under oath.
There are some things
in this world...
that go way beyond
human understanding.
Things that cannot be explained and
most people don't want to know about.
That is where we come in.
Are you saying the world of the
supernatural is your exclusive province?
Kitten, what I'm saying is...
when shit happens,
someone has to deal with it.
And who are you gonna call?
Shut up!
Stand up! Get up!
You too, Mr. Tully.
You're guilty on all charges.
I order you to pay fines
of $25,000 each.
I sentence you to 18 months
at Ryker's Island.
- Egie, she's twitching.
- I'm not finished!
On a more personal note...
let me go on record as saying
there's no place for fakes--
- Your Honor?
- Shut up!
Or tricksters like you
in decent society.
This is important.
You play on innocent people's
gullibility.
- Yes, sir.
- Be quiet!
- But--
- If my hands weren't tied...
by the fetters of the law...
I would invoke the tradition
of our illustrious forefathers...
reach back to a purer,
sterner justice...
and have you burned
at the stake!
My God! The Scoleri Brothers!
- The Scoleri Brothers!
- Friends of yours?
I tried them for murder!
Gave them the chair!
Do something!
Tell them you don't believe
in ghosts.
Do something! Help me!
Don't talk to me,
talk to my attorney.
That's me! My guys are still under
a judicial "mis-strangement" order.
That blue thing I got from her!
They could be exposing themselves.
You don't want us
exposing ourselves.
You're next.
All right! I rescind the order!
Case dismissed!
- We won the case!
- Now do something!
I always hated this part.
We haven't used this stuff
in a couple years.
- I hope it still works.
- It should.
The power cells are good
for 5,000 years.
There's no time for a bench test.
Heat them up.
Do.
Re.
Egon.
Come on, fat boy!
I'm taking you home
to my private zoo!
You got him!
- Bring the trap.
- Okay.
Behind you!
Hold it, Ray!
Venkman, start bringing him back!
Come on, meanie.
Let's go, chubby.
Keep pulling to the right!
Okay, the trap's going in!
No, Spengie!
- Hold it, Ray!
- Hit it!
- Two in the box!
- Ready to go!
We be fast,
and they be slow!
We're the best!
We're the beautiful!
- We're the only Ghostbusters!
- We're back!
Ghostbusters.
Yes, we're back.
Something strange going on
Something's wrong
Ghoul in the room
Outside is the storm
All alone and afraid
- Certified check, cash or money order!
- What can you do
Oh, is that what I think
Did I see something move
Chills down your spine
Your heart fills with frighf
Not thrilled by the things
that go bump in the night
Walk through the wall
With no time to stall
You call the Ghostbusters
Well, that's who you call
- Stop, Hit it
- Bye-bye.
- What is it, honey?
- It's that darn ghost again!
He won't leave us alone.
We'll have to move.
No, wait !
Don't worry.
We're not moving. He is.
Who are you going to call?
Ghostbusters!
I remember the time
I visited the grave
My life on the line
Only my life to save
All by myself
with no one around
Did not understand
a hand comin' out the ground
I knew it wasn't mine
- It was somebody else
- Now.
Before it could get me
I just screamed for help
- Then
- Ghostbusters
Packs strapped to their back
screaming
Ghostbusters attack
Janine, lunch!
- It smells like somebody took a big--
- We are the busters of any
G-h-o-s-t
...with our special
half-price service plan.
What? Hold on! Half-price?
Have we all gone mad?
I guess so.
That's not all.
Tell them, Egon.
You mean the Ghostbusters'
hot beverage thermal mug...
and free balloons for the kids?
I've been experimenting with the plasm
we found in the subway tunnel.
Careful.
- Should I get spoons?
- Don't bother. Watch this.
Go ahead, Ray.
You worthless piece of slime!
You ignorant disgusting blob!
You're just a short-chain molecule!
You foul, obnoxious muck!
You have a weak
electrochemical bond!
I have seen some disgusting crud
in my time...
but you take the cake!
This is what you do
with your spare time?
This is
an incredible breakthrough.
What a discovery:
a psycho-reactive substance.
Whatever this stuff is,
it responds to human emotional states.
Mood slime.
Oh, baby.
You mean this actually feeds
on bad vibes?
Like a cop in a donut factory.
We ran tests to look
for a strong positive reaction.
- What kind of tests?
- We sing to it and talk to it...
and say supportive,
nurturing things to it.
Are you sleeping with it?
Oh, you.
- It's always the quiet ones.
- You hound.
How about the kinetic tests?
Ordinary household toaster.
We'll take your word for that.
It responds to music, so we've been
playing middle-of-the-road stuff.
- Paul Young works okay.
- Works for me.
- Dig this.
- Loves Jackie Wilson.
You guys do this at night
when I'm not here?
I get it. It sings.
It sounds exactly like Jackie.
- That's fantastic.
- Just watch.
Does it do Emmy Lou Harris?
- Your love is lifting me higher
- It dances too.
Than I've ever been lifted before
- Whoa! Shake it up!
- Yeah! Happy thoughts.
And I'll be at your side
Oh, baby!
You're my number-one
Christmas boutique gift item.
The first time somebody gets mad,
the toaster eats their hand.
We put a warning label on it,
we have no liability.
Did you ever go for it!
The old man-eating toaster bit.
Get him!
Hello.
I'm looking for Dana Barrett.
- Room 304, Restoration.
- Thank you.
Hey, Dr. Venkman!
"World of the Psychic."
That's right. How you doing?
- I'm a big fan of yours.
- Thank you very much.
- It's one of my two favorite shows.
- You're kidding. What's the other one?
"Bass Masters."
It's a fishing show.
Yeah, I know "Bass Masters."
You're good, pretty eyes.
I didn't paint it.
I'm just cleaning it.
- It's a Gauguin.
- I've heard of him.
Aren't you going to introduce me
to your friend?
Sure. Peter Venkman...
this is Dr. Janosz Poha,
the head of our department.
I have seen you on the television.
I quite enjoy.
You're not here on business,
I hope.
It's top-secret.
Say, Johnny,
you have a Gauguin too.
Actually, I'm preparing this portrait
for the new romantic exhibition.
This is Prince Vigo,
the ruler of Carpathia and Moldavia.
- He's a bit of a sissy.
- He was a very powerful magician.
And a genius in many ways.
He was also a lunatic
and a genocidal madman.
I hate this painting.
I've felt uncomfortable
ever since it came up from storage.
You're probably feeling
what Vigo is feeling.
Carpathian kitten lost.
He's missed his kitten.
- We'll just put one in here.
- No altering valuable artwork!
- Go! The joyfulness is over!
- He's kidding.
You won't get a green card
with that attitude, pal.
I don't know what to do.
Oh, of course.
You're sweet
on this hunky stud.
Every now and then, I get the feeling
that painting is watching me...
even smiling at me.
I think we got more food
on your shirt...
than in your mouth.
You're gonna take a bath.
Yeah, do your favorite thing.
You know what you get to do?
You know what's more fun
than anything?
Splash Mommy.
I get to splash Mommy. Yes.
I'll be ready for you this time.
Mommy's taking her shirt off too.
Peter, it's me!
Please, let us in!
What the hell is this?
Let us in, please!
I didn't know where else to go.
The most awful thing happened.
The bathtub was trying
to eat Oscar!
I was giving him a bath.
There was all this pink ooze
reaching for him!
- You're all right.
- I won't let them get you.
You're all safe now, okay?
I was so terrified.
- You guys just sit down, relax.
- I'm sorry.
I'll get you guys a shirt
or something.
Ray, Dana's just come over
to my place.
Her tub tried to eat her.
What? Are you serious?
That's great!
I mean, that's terrible.
But it's great for what we--
Yeah, I will.
Sure, we'll get right on it.
A major slime-related
psychokinetic event.
- What happened?
- Something came out of Dana's bathtub.
- It tried to grab her and the baby.
- Are they all right?
Yeah, she went to Venkman's.
This is interesting.
Remember the painting Venkman mentioned?
I ran Vigo the Carpathian
through the occult reference net.
Look what came up.
Nice ugly history.
You think there's a connection
between Vigo and the...
slime?
Is the atomic weight
of cobalt 58.9?
Let's go to Dana's.
I'd like to check out that bathtub.
It would be a good idea to go
to the museum in the morning...
get a look at that painting.
- Ray's checking out your place.
- He is?
I have held onto this
for a long time, Oscar.
I got this from a girl...
who got this
from Joe "Willie" Namath.
We don't want to know how.
So please don't hose this down...
or give it your personal rinse.
It's time for you
to start practicing...
what we big guys call self-control.
Get out of here.
Look at him.
Look at his gut.
He's a coconut.
You'll stay at Uncle Pete's
till this blows over.
This is your place now.
Hi. Come on in.
This is my place.
How are we going to handle
the sleeping arrangements?
It's best for me if I lie on my side
and you spoon up beside me...
your arm draped over me.
The other way, I get your hair
caught in my throat...
and I choke in the night.
How about you on the sofa
and me and the baby in the bed?
It's a way to go.
It's so late.
I really should put him down.
May I?
Yeah, if you want to.
You're short...
your belly button
sticks out too far...
and you're a terrible burden
on your poor mother.
- Did you find anything at Dana's?
- Just some mood slime residue.
But I got something
on that Vigo character.
I found it in Leon Zundinger's
"Magicians, Martyrs and Madmen."
- Dig that.
- Vigo the Carpathian...
born 1505, died 1610.
105 years old.
He hung in there.
He didn't die of old age.
He was poisoned, stabbed, shot, hung,
disemboweled, drawn and quartered.
- Ouch.
- He wasn't too popular.
Not exactly a man of the people.
Also known as Vigo the Cruel,
Vigo the Torturer...
Vigo the Despised
and Vigo the Unholy.
- Wasn't he also Vigo the Butch?
- Dig this. There was also a prophecy.
Just before his head died...
his last words were,
"Death is but a door.
Time is but a window.
I'll be back."
Let's suck in the guts.
We're the Ghostbusters.
- Please go!
- Who's this wiggler?
He's yours. Sic him.
How are you?
Ray Stantz from the Ghostbusters.
Beautiful lab here. We're just
doing a routine spook check.
- Dr. Venkman, Dana is not here.
- Yeah, we know that.
- So why are you came?
- We heard there's a major creep here.
We checked our list,
and you were there.
Johnny, where in the hell
are you from?
The Upper West Side.
The whole room's extremely hot.
- That's one ugly dude.
- Hot?
That's Mr. Vigo.
- Vigs, look this way, please.
- Don't.
- No.
- Show me something.
No photographs, please!
Slides are available
in the gift shop.
Thank you, Winston.
You know what?
Give me angry, will you?
You've had a bad day.
You're cranky.
Yeah. Thank you. Good.
Angrier.
You're scaring me.
Stop it. Yeah.
Good!
Walk for me, talk for me. Yeah!
Give me hot and sexy.
Can you do it?
You can.
Oh, boy.
Show me some teeth.
I bet the girls like you.
Do the girls? Do the guys?
I bet they both do.
Do the animals like you?
That's it! More!
Yeah, you're big!
All right, destroy me!
Yeah!
Give it! Yeah!
We need to talk.
I've worked with better,
but not many. Thank you.
John, thanks.
You finished?
Yeah, I'm finished here.
- Are you all right?
- What?
- Are you coming down with something?
- Me?
Your prince.
She cleaned.
He's asleep.
Come here.
What happened
with my apartment?
The guys spent
the whole night there.
They went through
all your personal stuff.
They tried on some
of your clothes...
made some long-distance phone calls,
cleaned out the fridge--
Did they find anything?
They found a little
of that pink slime.
What should I do now?
You are supposed to get dressed
and get crazy with me.
- Peter, I don't think--
- This is exactly what you need.
I have got you a baby-sitter.
The whole thing's wired.
I don't think we should
go out on a date.
I can't leave Oscar
in a strange place...
with a strange person.
"Strange person"?
Janine Melnitz from my staff.
- Janine has experience baby-sitting?
- Here.
- Thank you.
- Here's some things from your apartment.
Some wardrobe choices.
A couple provocative ensembles.
I'll leave it up to you.
But after dinner, don't put any
of those cheap moves on me.
- It's different.
- I have all new cheap moves.
Hey, you!
It looks like you're awake.
You're awake.
Yes, you'll have the whole place
to yourself tonight, pal.
It will be pretty neat.
I got some Laura Antonelli tapes
you can watch.
Did you see some shirts here
in the floor /bed area?
- I put them in the hamper.
- I have a hamper?
- Yes, in the bathroom.
- Neat.
- Tell me next time you do that.
- I thought they were dirty.
I have more than
two grades of laundry.
There's not just clean and dirty.
There are many subtle levels.
You hang this outside the window
for 20 minutes, it's perfectly fine.
Interesting role model for you.
They couldn't get to you
until after the New Year.
Just don't go in there.
I'm closing up.
Should I take the subway
or the surf ace roads? It's busy out.
I'm walking.
Good night.
Well, now hang on now.
Do you maybe want to--
No.
Do you want to have
something to eat with me?
Yeah, I'd love that...
but I told Dr. Venkman
I'd baby-sit for him.
- Do you want to baby-sit with me?
- Okay, I would.
- Great. His place at 8:00. Bye.
- All right.
- I can get his address from the W2--
- Buddy, move!
We were right.
Multi-planar Kirlian emanations.
Here's your next month's
cover of "GQ."
Check out the aura on this sucker.
There's definitely
a living presence there.
We should get a deeper look.
I'll run this shot
through the spectral analyzer.
Good. I'll try turning up
the Roentgens.
What do you think?
Chinese?
- How about Thai?
- No, too spicy.
- Greek?
- Mexican?
- Pizza?
- Thin or thick?
Chicago.
What the hell is that?
I know what it is.
- I've seen it before.
- Where?
When you had me dangling like a worm
on a hook 100 feet below First Avenue.
That's the river of slime.
What in--
- We need a blanket or a hose.
- Let's get out.
Why is this closed?
Fire! What are we gonna do,
put our heads in the toilet?
Taxi!
It's great that you're here.
We've got incredible news.
Can I have one try?
All-you-can-eat barbecue rib night
at the Sizzler.
We analyzed the photos of Vigo.
The spectrogram shows a river of slime
flowing behind him.
We're going into the subway and sewer
system to trace the source of the flow.
Change your clothes.
We'll wait.
Egon thinks it might be a breeding
surge in the cockroach population.
Hi, boys.
What's up?
The guys are going into the sewer
to check for slime.
Egon thinks there may be a huge surge
in cockroach breeding.
Want to blow off dinner
and go with them?
Taxi!
Women. Huh?
Will you watch your step?
I hate this.
According to this old transit map,
there should be an entrance near here.
I'm not getting anything yet.
At least it's too dark
to see the cockroaches.
It's the subway rats
you have to worry about.
Big as beavers.
Some of them
are four or five kilos.
Enough, all right?
Listen. You can hear them
behind the walls scratching.
There must be thousands.
- Just shut up about the rats.
- Okay.
Hello!
I'm out of here.
They're gone.
What the--
Before we go further,
we should get our proton packs.
Good idea.
- What's that?
- What's what?
Sounds like a train.
Uh-uh. These lines have been
abandoned for 50 years.
Probably in a tunnel above us.
I don't know.
It sounds awfully close to me.
That was the old New York Central
"City of Albany."
Derailed in 1920,
killed hundreds of people.
Did you catch the number
on the locomotive?
Sorry, I missed it.
Something's trying to stop us.
We must be close.
Where's Ray?
Guys!
- Sorry. I found it.
- What?
- Right here there's a hole.
- Let's go.
What about the packs?
Unbelievable.
Did I tell you?
I wasn't lying, was I?
It takes a lot of negative energy
to generate a flow this size.
New York. What a town.
Let's see how deep it is.
Get a sounding.
All right, six feet.
Twelve feet.
Maybe something's pulling it.
- Hold on.
- I'm trying. Give me a hand!
Something's got him!
Get his belt off !
- We can't hold it!
- Wait! Hold on!
A toast to...
the most charming, kindest--
- It's me.
- It's you.
And most unusual man...
I've ever broken up with.
Speaking of breaking up with neat guys,
why did you dump me?
I didn't dump you.
I was protecting myself.
You weren't very good for me.
You know that, don't you?
I'm not even good for me.
You're much better
than you realize.
You don't give yourself
enough credit.
I need to hear that.
If I had this kind of support
24 hours a day...
I could have myself whipped into shape
by the end of this century.
Why don't you give me a jingle
in the year 2000?
Why don't I give you a jingle
right now?
So the seven dwarves had a limited
partnership in a mining operation.
One day a beautiful princess
came to live with them.
They bartered housekeeping services
for room and board...
which was a good deal.
They didn't have to withhold
Social Security or taxes.
You're not supposed to do that, but for
the purposes of this story it's okay.
It really is a great place.
It needs a woman's touch.
But it looks really good.
- You know--
- Bedtime.
- You're very good with children.
- Thanks. I practiced on my hamster.
You live alone?
I used to have a roommate,
but my mom moved to Florida.
- Come over here and sit with me.
- Okay.
You want to play Boggle
or Super Mario Brothers?
I think motherhood
is a very natural instinct.
I'd like a child myself.
Would you?
Tonight?
Nice going, Ray.
Were you trying to drown me?
Like it was my fault...
that you were too stupid
not to drop that plumb line!
Watch your mouth
or I'll punch your lights out!
- Yeah? Well, anytime! Come on!
- Right now!
It's go time! I want you bad!
- Grab me! Come on!
- Wait! Stop!
Get your clothes off quick.
Ray, what were we doing?
I was ready to kill you.
It's the stuff.
It's like pure, concentrated evil.
And it's all flowing
right to this spot.
- Are you sure this is it?
- Yeah, he said Armand's.
- Excuse me--
- It's all right. We'll look in back.
Please get out of my restaurant.
- Absolutely incredible!
- You cannot come in here!
The greatest tangible evidence
of psychic energy in years!
- You're disturbing my guests!
- Just a second.
Boys, you're scaring the straights.
Can we do this tomorrow?
This won't wait.
It's hot, and it's ready to pop.
- It's all over the city.
- Under it, actually.
- Rivers of the stuff.
- It's all flowing to the museum.
Look what he got all over me.
- What is this stuff?
- Sorry.
Oh, God.
You mean my museum?
I was going to tell you between
the dessert and the cheese course.
- There they are.
- You can never go back there.
- You'll have to find a new job.
- It's psychomagnotheric plasm.
It affects behavior.
We were fighting!
- We were in a fight!
- Had him by the throat.
We have to see the mayor.
- Ghostbusters.
- How you doing?
Come right this way.
You got another proton pack?
My kid brother wants one.
- The proton pack is not a toy.
- He's right.
Dana, we were just baby-sitting.
We watched TV and ate something.
- Then one thing led to another.
- I know what you were doing.
I didn't know anything would happen.
Hi. How was your date?
It wasn't a date.
It was just dinner.
- Where's Peter?
- He was arrested.
Typical.
- Did he call?
- Nobody called.
Is Oscar all right?
He's fine.
Such a good baby.
He was fussy at first,
then we gave him French bread pizza.
Passed right out.
Good.
I'll just give him a look-see.
You think we should go?
I don't know. I don't think
we should leave her alone.
You're right.
Let's stay.
Lenny! Big man!
- Ghostbusters.
- Mr. Mayor.
What is this?
A slumber party?
- That's what we're here to talk about.
- I don't want to hear about it.
You've got two minutes.
Make it good.
First of all, Mr. Mayor,
it's a pleasure to see you again.
Almost 50 percent of us voted for you
in the last election.
I appreciate that.
Sorry we have to meet
under these circumstances.
We're here tonight because
a psychomagnotheric slime flow...
is building up beneath the city.
Psycho what?
- Psychomagnotheric.
- Big word.
Negative human emotions
are materializing in the form...
of a viscous plasm
with explosive supernormal potential.
- Does anybody speak English here?
- Yeah.
We're trying to tell you
all the bad feelings...
all the hate and anger of this city
is turning into this sludge.
I didn't believe it either...
but we went for a swim in it
and almost killed each other.
This is insane.
Do we have to listen to this?
Can't you stop your lips from flapping
for two little minutes?
Lenny, have you been out
on the street lately?
Do you know how weird it is out there?
We've taken a head count.
There seem to be three million...
completely miserable assholes
living in the tristate area.
Please.
I beg your pardon.
Three million and one.
Budgy-brain here doesn't realize
if we don't do something fast...
this whole place will blow
like a frog on a hot plate.
- Yeah, right.
- What am I supposed to do?
Go on television
and tell ten million people...
they have to be nice
to each other?
Being miserable
and treating other people like dirt...
is every New Yorker's
God-given right.
Your two minutes are up.
Good night, gentlemen.
- Wait!
- You're making a big mistake!
You're making
a very newsworthy mistake.
The "Times" will be interested,
and you know the "Post"--
Whoa!
- "Mayor Hides Slime."
- "Time Square Slime."
"Slime Square."
Fine.
Before you go running off
to the newspapers with this...
would you consider telling this slime
business to our people downtown?
It must be done right away.
You know the expression, "It all
comes back"? It's gonna come back!
This city's in danger!
The whole state! The whole world!
- All we want to do is help!
- I'm warning you. Come on, let's go.
The mayor wants them kept under strict
observation for the next few days.
We think they're seriously disturbed
and potentially dangerous.
- We'll do whatever is necessary.
- Thank you, Doctor.
I await the words of Vigo.
l, Vigo, the scourge of Carpathia...
You've told me this.
the sorrow of Moldavia...
Sorrow.
I've heard all of this.
command you.
Command me, lord.
The season of evil begins
with the birth of the new year.
Good.
Bring me the child,
that I might live again.
Yes.
Lord Vigo...
I was wondering.
This woman, Dana,
is fine and strong.
Now, if I...
was to bring that baby...
could I have that woman?
So be it.
On this day of darkness,
she will be ours:
wife to you...
and mother to me.
Yes!
Thank you, lord!
- Is she the killer or what?
- No, that's Rita Hayworth.
She was married to Citizen Kane
while they were doing this thing.
Right after they finished,
she dumped him for some polo player.
I don't know why beautiful women
love horses so much. Do you love horses?
You don't have to stay.
Peter will be back soon.
We don't mind.
- Can you see okay?
- Yep.
Oh, God!
- What?
- It's Oscar!
Call 911 right now!
- God, it was a ghost!
- No, that was Janosz.
- He took him.
- What's happening?
- What should we do?
- Where's the baby?
The museum!
- Where are you going?
- To get my baby!
We have to find the guys.
As I explained before...
we think the spirit
of a 17th-century Moldavian tyrant...
is alive and well in a painting
in the Manhattan Museum of Art.
Are there any other paintings
in the museum with bad spirits in them?
You're wasting valuable time.
He's drawing strength from a slime flow
collecting under the city.
- Yes, tell me about the slime.
- It's very potent.
We made a toaster dance with it.
And a bathtub tried
to eat his friend's baby.
A bathtub?
Don't look at me.
I think they're nuts.
Sweetheart.
I thought I'd lost you,
that I'd never see you again.
- Oh, baby.
- Hello, Dana.
I thought you might come.
You stay away from us.
I mean it.
Don't worry.
He will not be harmed.
He has been chosen...
to be the vessel
of the spirit of Vigo.
You will be the mother
of the ruler of the world.
- Doesn't that sound nice?
- No, it sounds ludicrous.
You stay away from him.
I mean it.
I don't think we have a choice here.
Take a look.
It's not Gainsborough's Blue Boy.
He is Vigo.
I don't care who he is.
You can't take my baby.
You bastard!
Is this a big dinosaur
or a little dinosaur?
It's just a skeleton.
Which way was it heading?
What was chasing you in the park?
The park bench? I see.
What? Wait a second.
Lieutenant, I think
you better talk to this guy.
I'm busy here.
It's some dock supervisor
at Pier 34.
What's the problem?
He says the "Titanic"
just arrived.
Well, better late than never.
We're swamped. We've had more than
3,000 calls since midnight last night.
We've got every officer on the streets,
and I'm still shorthanded.
Meter maids are chasing ghosts
all over midtown.
There's this shell thing
over the Manhattan Museum of Art.
We can't make a dent.
- Have you tried dynamite?
- We've tried everything.
What's going on?
It's pandemonium out there.
Yes, I know.
We're working on it.
While you're "working on it,"
I'm going down in history...
as the mayor who let New York
get sucked into the tenth level of hell!
We've got no choice.
Call the Ghostbusters.
Wait!
I'm sure there's another way.
Jack, I spent an hour last night
talking to Fiorello La Guardia...
and he's been dead for 40 years.
Where are the Ghostbusters?
- They're not available.
- What do you mean?
I had them committed to the psychiatric
ward at Parkview Hospital.
You what?
They threatened to go to the press.
I was protecting your interests.
Yeah?
Stop protecting my interests.
You have exactly three minutes
to clear out. You're fired!
- But the election--
- Harry, remove this man.
- You're making a mistake.
- Get me the Ghostbusters!
Mr. Mayor, look at this.
What is it?
Have you ever seen anything like that?
Somebody get me the Ghostbusters.
He put the baby in a carriage,
then they levitated away.
- Where did Dana go?
- She went to the museum to get the baby.
Then there was an eclipse. The whole
town went dark, and everybody's nuts.
It all fits.
Vigo wants in on the 21st century.
He needs a human body to inhabit.
Oscar must be it.
- And we're the only ones who can help.
- You bet we are.
It looks like a giant Jell-O mold.
I hate Jell-O.
There's always room for Jell-O.
Soon it will be midnight.
The city will be mine and Vigo's.
Mainly Vigo's.
We have a terrific opportunity
to make the best of this relationship.
We don't have a relationship.
I know. Marry me. Together,
we will raise Vigo as our son.
Let me tell you something here.
There are many perks in being
the mother of a living god.
I'm sure we could get
a magnificent apartment...
a car, free parking.
Many marriages begin
with a certain amount of distance.
Yet I think that...
you and I could learn
to love each other.
Yes.
I could learn.
Pull them.
Full neutronas.
Let's cook!
Save them.
That slime wall
is pulsing with evil.
It would take a tremendous amount
of positive energy to crack that shell.
I doubt there's enough goodwill
in this town...
to do it.
Are things so bad in this city
that there's no way back?
Sure, it's dirty, crowded,
polluted, noisy...
and there's people who would rather
step on your face as look at you...
but come on!
There must be a few sparks
of humanity left in this burg.
- We just have to mobilize it.
- He's right.
We need something that everybody
can get behind. We need...
a symbol.
Something that appeals
to the best in each of us.
- Something good.
- Something decent.
Something pure.
- Makes you wonder, doesn't it?
- Wonder what?
Whether she's naked
under that toga.
She's French.
You know that.
Got it.
Ready with the speakers.
Slime blowers ready?
Internal audio set.
Internal electric set.
Slime blower primed and set.
Good slime.
Is our slime in a good mood tonight?
I hope so.
She's a lot bigger than a toaster.
- All yours. Let's go.
- Thank you.
Testing, one, two. How many of you
are a national monument?
Raise your hand, please.
Hello, miss.
- Let's frost it.
- It's slime time.
Beautiful.
Pilot controls are ready.
It's getting late.
It's almost midnight. Let's go.
Here's something off the request line
from Liberty Island!
We're gonna squeeze some
New Year's juice from you, Big Apple.
You know your love
Your love keeps liftin' me
- Keeps on liftin' me
- Love keeps liftin' me
- Higher
- Liftin' me
Higher and higher
Imagine people's faces
when we come on shore.
This should get the city's
positive energy flowing.
Keep kicking, Libby.
Make this work, we'll pop for a weekend
in Vegas with the Jolly Green Giant.
You look fantastic in this.
I was born to wear this stuff.
This equipment is heavy.
I'm so glad
I finally found you
You're that one in a million girl
And now with
my lovin' arms around you
It's a lovefest, New York!
- Sing it out!
- Come on!
Your love
- Is lifting me higher
- You sing!
- We're running out of time.
- Can't you go faster?
The vibrations
will shake her to pieces.
- We should have padded her feet.
- They don't make Nikes in her size.
Don't worry. She's tough.
She's a harbor chick!
Sorry! My fault!
Happy New Year.
Stay fit. Keep sharp.
Make good decisions.
Oh, good.
It's you.
Okay, but I didn't know
you had your license.
Four minutes to go...
and then party time.
It's happening.
It's really happening.
Go away from here!
- I love you when you roughhouse!
- Hit it, Mama!
- Drop the hammer on her!
- Go! Do it now!
- Oscar, look.
- Go away!
- Don't you know who this is?
- Happy New Year.
He's Vigo! You are like
the buzzing of flies to him!
Johnny, you backed the wrong horse.
Hose him, please.
- One down.
- On the ground.
Boy, am I glad to see you.
- Is he dead?
- No, this slime is positively charged.
He'll wake up feeling
like a million bucks.
This gentleman is a little ripe.
That's all right, my friend.
I think I had an accident too.
Get him away!
Get a knife
to cut her out of this!
Listen. You need to stay right here.
Don't move.
Uncle Pete has to help your mom.
Stay here and don't say anything.
Hold it, deadhead!
You want a baby?
Go knock up some willing hellhound!
Otherwise,
get back in that painting...
where you belong!
- One!
- Two.
Three!
You got him!
Oh, that was really stupid.
- Ray, can you move?
- No. Are you okay?
- Venkman, how are you?
- I'm fine.
Please, do something!
Not so fast, Vigo!
You, the bimbo with the baby.
The big shoulder look is out.
You know, I have met
some dumb blondes in my life...
but you take the taco, pal.
Only a Carpathian
would come back to life now...
and choose New York.
Tasty pick, bonehead!
If you had brain one...
in that huge melon
on top of your neck...
you would be living
the sweet life...
out in Southern California's...
beautiful San Fernando Valley.
Oh, darn it.
Now we become one.
- Where's that singing coming from?
- The people outside.
Excuse me. Ghostbusters.
I'm here with you, guys.
He's weakening! The singing
is neutralizing the slime!
I can move!
Sweetie!
He's back in the painting!
Go find a shady spot.
Vigie, you have been
a bad monkey.
We'd like to shoot the monster.
Move, please.
l, Ray, am Vigo,
and rule the Earth!
- Be gone, you pitiful half-men!
- Now!
- I did it!
- That was great!
- I'm a Ghostbuster!
- I loved it!
- You all right?
- Come on, get up. Let's get this off.
Here. Here we go.
- How do you feel?
- Groovy.
- Are you all right?
- Yes. Thank you.
Spread out, shorty.
I love you guys.
- I love all you guys.
- Great.
- And I love Venkman.
- Let's go.
- Wow.
- We have to live with this?
- Real friendship.
- Yeah.
Are you all right?
Why am I dripping with goo?
You had a violent, prolonged,
transformative psychic episode.
Sorry we had to hose you,
but you were out of control.
Hey, man...
let me tell you something.
I love you.
- Yes?
- Yeah.
I love you too.
Fellas.
Take a look at this.
Early Renaissance, I think.
Raphael or Piero della Francesca.
No, I believe it's one
of the Fettucine's.
Ghostbusters