There are 666 portals that connect
this world to the other side.
These are concealed from
all human beings.
Somewhere in Japan exists
the 444th portal.
The Forest of Resurrection.
This way.
Better be right.
Just follow me.
Where are they?
Don't worry, they are coming.
I'm not worried. I just don't trust you.
Do as you please then.
It's a quite a big deal
for a pick up, isn't it.
Where's the other car?
We gotta wait for him.
Are you serious?
It's not safe here.
We have specific orders from him.
Look, the roads could be
blocked by now.
We gotta go!
What's the matter? You afraid?
Shut up.
What the hell we doing here anyway?
You shut up.
An order is an order.
Stop whining.
Orders?
Do you know what we had to
go through for this?
Besides, this place gives me the creeps.
Don't bother.
These assholes will only follow orders.
What?
Is there any party?
Or you trying to promote hoodlums?
You... Better watch your mouth.
After all this running around,
all we get is a useless
bunch of punks. Forget it.
I see. So shall I give you a rest?
Forever.
Stop!
We gotta keep him alive.
It's an order.
Shut up!
I do not get the point
why he is so special.
But you have to follow orders, too, right?
Calm down! Both of you.
Back off.
Don't be so choosy.
We gonna let you get out of here
when he comes, all right?
I hate waiting.
Stop it for now.
Okay,
we'll wait for him.
We better hurry up.
I hate this place.
A forest to the southwest is
an ominous feng shui sign.
Oh, really?
To meet with you guys is
an ominous enough.
Stop it. Don't start again!
Bring the girl.
What's with this girl?
Just following orders.
One girl and one asshole.
What good are they?
What the hell is he doing?
Come on, he should have some plan.
Hey wait.
I'm taking no part in kidnapping.
What?
5 men on one girl,
you must be proud of yourself.
Hey, let her go and take off your wig.
Shut the fuck up!
Do you know who you're talking to?
We are the ones set you free
from the jail where you belonged.
I'm a feminist.
So, what you gonna do?
I said let her go.
Watch it.
Just let her go.
Are you crazy or what?
Don't let me tell you again.
This would be your last chance.
What now, tough guy?
Where did they go?
This place is wrong.
I'll kill him.
Better not.
He'll become a monster, too.
I don't get it...
Oh Yes. I can kill him twice.
Nonsense.
Let's get out of here.
No, we'll go after them!
You don't understand.
Look, this is your fault...
It's not just that. Think about it.
Thinking isn't going to do a bit of good.
Nonsense. They were not dead.
Let's get them before he gets here.
Yeah,
you're right.
You didn't have to kill him!
What's your problem?
You're no different from those men.
They're bastards, I'm not.
I'm sorry...
Thanks for helping me.
I didn't mean to help you.
They just piss me off.
What are we gonna do?
Didn't you have any plans?
Plans are always changed.
Great. They're going to kill us.
They were...
Surely dead.
Hey.
Why were you in jail...?
Shut up.
Something's not right with this place.
About what?
People are everywhere...
but it's too quiet.
Nobody's here.
I feel them.
What makes you feel that?
I have a strong sixth sense...
Hey,
wait.
What's wrong with you?
Where the fuck you think
you are going?
Stay back.
This man...
What are you doing?
Stop!
Let him rest in peace!
I don't believe this...
You're crazy.
Let's go. We'll take their car.
Stop it! Let's get out of here.
They must be around here.
Something's wrong here.
Again?
I can feel it!
They were...
Something is wrong!
Hey...
What?
They were dead...
and they came back to life.
So what?
The dead could be back to life here.
We've been here over and over...
We always buried the ones we killed...
Dead bodies are everywhere...
Where the fuck are they?
No, I didn't mean to...
Come!
Let go of me!
Game is over.
What are those monsters?
Who knows, they are your playmates.
Then you die, and play with me!
Remember your orders!
Don't kill him!
Hey, you got wrong man.
Just let him go.
Don't be a fool, punk.
Wow.
This is complicated.
Hey, she's been taken away.
What?
That runt shot my arm
and took the girl.
Jesus, the both of you!
You're both crazy!
You turning back?
Well, I'll play with you later.
OK?
Good job shithead, now he's gone.
Don't you get it?
I let him find the girl for us.
Huh?
We'll get them both after he finds her.
Pretty smart...
Orders are to get both of them alive.
Oh... too bad.
It doesn't matter anymore.
You...
I'll be in charge from now on and
he will die.
What?
It's all been planned.
He comes here to be killed.
Don't fool with me!
What the fuck?
Die slowly.
We don't want you back alive.
Are you okay?
Yeah... But this place is fucked up.
Nothing can stop me...
Not even those monsters.
Don't worry.
Hurry up!
Bastards...
Ouch!
You okay?
Shit...
Your hand!
He took it... That bastard!
Damn it! We'll make them pay for this.
Shouldn't we report back?
No...
We'll search for them...
and destroy them!
Yeah... But where are they?
I know what they're thinking.
They took the mountain paths.
I was trained at FBI HQ at Langley.
I'm an expert in profiling.
An expert?...
Expert, so where in the mountains?
Don't worry. I'll track them down.
I grew up in
Yellow Stone National park,
a natural born hunter!
A hunter?
Which way?
No!
Shut the fuck up!
What's wrong here...
He'll come after us.
Let me go!
This is so insane.
You... You did all this?
It's all your fault!
Stop... You're crazy...
Hey.
No!
What?
You don't have to kill him.
Shut up. Don't preach at me.
You can't hurt people for no reason.
A lot of people are better dead.
That's not for you to judge.
What are you? A preacher?
Let's go.
Look, no more killing, okay!
We've been waiting.
Finally... This is going to end soon.
My gun.
Who are you?
How did you get here?
I was kidnapped...
um...
What?
I can't remember.
Huh?
I can't remember anything what
happened before I got here.
Yeah, right.
How about you?
What got you in prison?
I was...
What? You don't remember either?
I forget things easily.
So... You too.
When did you get here?
Now.
What's going on? What are those
monsters... those two weirdos?
What are you up to?
Something bad.
Where are others?
Where? They're all dead.
Oh,
and why are you alive?
Gotta problem?
Yeah. You.
A scumbag like you should be dead.
Oooh, who are these scary people?
You're dead.
No, let's get away from here.
That was pretty good.
But not good enough...
Hey, babe.
What are you?
You'll need an army to kill me.
You.
I'll give you power...
in death.
Him!
No, we have to go!
No, not him! Let's go! Now!
Hurts?
Human life is only an instant.
Your body will eventually rot.
Do you wanna be dead?
or wanna have eternal life?
Eternal...
Any trouble?
Yes, a little accident.
Are you okay officer?
Don't call me officer.
Did you do it again?
You better behave yourself,
officer...
You want to fight me, the master of
all martial arts? The Fighter!
Okay, Fighter.
Fighter?
We don't have time.
Let's kill them!
Right, Fighter.
Your heart!
Here. Help yourself.
What?
Mother fucker!!!
I'll show you the world beyond death...
Come on.
Let's go.
Why?
We have to hurry.
No. I never turn my back.
We don't have time for this.
That man is dangerous...
Who is he? You know him.
He's...
That's enough.
Who is he?