Antwone. He's here.
That's Antwone.
Antwone?
Ohh!
"First call,
first call to colors."
Damn. Berkley!
What?
You've been in there
10 minutes, man.
Shut up.
Yeah, okay. You know...
one day, Chief s
gonna come in here...
and catch you taking
them Hollywood showers.
I should snitch on you.
Come on, move, man.
Get out of
my way, snitch.
Oh, come on.
Yeah, yeah. Ruff!
I got you, man.
Ooh!
Arf!
You better quit playing, man.
What's cracking, Fisher?
Your head,
if you don't get away from me.
Heh.
What is that on your face?
Keep the fuck out my face, huh?
Say something!
Say something, huh?
You're always talking!
I'm cool, man, I'm cool.
I'm cool. I'm cool, man.
Petty Officer Fisher, you've been accused...
of violating Article 128...
Assault on a superior
non-commissioned officer.
How do you plead?
Guilty, sir.
Well, in your statement,
you say your attack...
on Petty Officer Berkley
was provoked by a...
a racial slur.
Is that correct?
Yes, sir.
Petty Officer Berkley,
did you make...
any racial remarks
to Petty Officer Fisher?
No, sir.
Punk, you...
- Stand at attention!
- Stand at attention.
This is
the United States Navy, son.
I find you guilty.
They'll be a forfeiture
of $200 for 2 months.
You'll be restricted to
the boundaries of the ship...
for 45 days, and you'll
perform 45 days extra duty.
I'm reducing you from
ship's serviceman...
petty officer third class...
to ship's serviceman seaman.
And I'm recommending
that you be evaluated...
at the psychiatric clinic...
before our next underway period.
You're dismissed.
So, what happened?
How'd it go?
Same old, same old.
I got busted...
but now I gotta go
to the psych clinic.
You gotta go
to the nut house?
Farmer, shut up, man.
Give it up
to the shrink? Damn.
See you next week.
Seaman Fisher.
Right this way.
I understand it's not
your first time here.
You saw Dr. Williams?
Nah, he saw me.
Heh.
That's your wife?
Yes.
Have a seat.
I understand
you like to fight.
It's the only way
some people learn.
Hmm. But you pay the price
for teaching them.
You want to talk about it?
About what?
Whatever's bothering you.
Why does something
gotta be bothering me?
What,
because I jumped on a white boy?
Something must be wrong with me?
"Send him to the psychiatrist.
Nigger try to kill his master."
Hmph.
"He must be crazy."
You looking for a discharge, Fisher?
I ain't looking for nothing.
That's where you're headed.
If I want out of the navy...
I'll just leave.
Unauthorized absence?
Yeah,
if that's what the navy calls it.
Hmm. Running away
how you handle your problems?
I don't have no problems.
Hmm. Where you from, Fisher?
Where'd you spend your childhood?
Cleveland.
Parents still live there?
I never had any parents.
They deceased?
I never ha...
I never had parents.
That would make you...
a medical miracle, Seaman Fisher.
Where you from?
I'm from under a rock.
Okay.
Okay, all right.
I want to see you next week.
I ain't coming back.
Why not?
'Cause there's nothing wrong with me.
I agree with you there.
See you next week.
See the receptionist on your way out.
Next Wednesday, 1400.
Whoa!
Walker. Phillip Walker.
That was the name of
the last guy who stalked me.
Oh, man, I'm busted.
Yeah, you're busted.
What's up? Where you been?
I'm on restriction.
- Again?
- Yeah.
How did you get off the ship?
Um, well, I just
came from the medic.
Why?
Uh, well...
I'm working on this
high priority paper...
for this commander.
Oh. What kind of paper?
Well, I'm...
I'm not at liberty...
to talk about it right now.
Oh. Well, I was gonna
invite you to a party.
Me?
Yeah, you.
Well, I'm on restriction.
Yeah, you told me.
Hmm. I gotta...
you know, get back to the ship.
They probably looking for me...
right about now,
so... you know...
Talk to you.
Damn.
See you when you're off restriction.
Yes?
Yeah, send him in.
Get your monkey hands off me, man!
I thought you may have forgotten...
your way here last week,
so I took the liberty...
of sending an escort team for you.
You may be able to make me come here...
but you can't make me talk.
Thank you.
You're dismissed.
You don't want to talk to me?
Let me lay this out for you, son.
This is how many cases I have, okay?
I don't have time to waste.
Now, I get 3 sessions only...
to make an eval...
and a recommendation to
your commanding officer.
You know he wants to throw you...
out of the navy, don't you?
Now, you can sit here,
and you can not talk...
to me if you want to...
but our sessions don't begin...
until you begin talking to me.
I got nothing to say.
Okay.
Then we'll sit until you do.
I got a whole lot of
work to catch up on.
We can sit here every day...
until the day I retire.
Doesn't matter to me.
It doesn't matter to me, either.
- All righty.
- What about the brig?
What about it?
Send me to the brig.
There's the brig right there.
Lock yourself up.
What do you know?
Time's up.
See you next week, 1400.
Want some chips?
Hmph.
What?
I didn't say anything.
I thought you said something.
I was just clearing my throat.
Okay.
Maybe you're coming
down with something.
I'm all right.
It's just sort of...
Just what?
Just...
It's just a waste of time sitting here...
week after week...
wasting time.
I don't want you...
to waste your time, Antwone.
So, what you want me to say?
It's not what I want you to say.
It's what you want to tell me.
Maybe you can start
by asking me a question.
I don't know.
Get things going.
I can do that.
You said you come from under a rock.
What did you mean by that?
I don't know, I...
It was the first thing
to come to my mind.
What do you think it means?
Well, it could mean...
that, uh...
that you feel under pressure...
uh, you feel a weight...
pressing down on you.
That you're in the dark,
that you're alone.
You said you had no parents.
I had parents.
Okay.
Only 3 sessions, right?
Only 3.
My father's name was Edward.
So you knew him?
No.
I didn't even know his last name.
You know where he is?
Yeah, I know where he is.
Joey...
He went to his ex-girlfriend's house.
They got into an argument.
She killed my father.
Where was your mother
when this happened?
Behind bars.
I see.
I was born in prison...
2 months after my
father was murdered.
Why was she confined,
your mother?
I don't know.
All I know is what I told you.
So you were turned over to the state?
Yeah. The state placed
me in this orphanage.
It was supposed to be until...
my mother got out to claim me, but...
She got out, but she never claimed me.
Hmm. How long were you there?
2 years.
How does that make you feel, Antwone?
I don't know.
Come on, you must have
some feelings about it.
You know, you...
What did it feel like?
Rainy days.
Rainy days? Okay.
Why is that?
You know, in Cleveland...
it rains.
Not all the time...
but, uh, to a kid...
who wants to go out and play...
it seems like it rains every day.
But, uh...
kids expect it to rain sometimes...
but... for one kid...
it rained too much.
Hmm.
Okay.
You want me to come back next week?
Yes, I do.
You ever try to find her, your mother?
No, sir.
Okay. Next week.
Busy day?
Uh, no more than usual.
Hmm.
The tomatoes are from our garden.
Yeah?
Mmm. They're so much
better than last year.
Heh heh.
I mean, I'm no green thumb or anything...
but... heh heh.
Who knows?
Maybe I'm learning.
These tomatoes really are good.
When I was 2...
I was placed in the Tate foster home.
Reverend Tate, he was
a fire-breathing preacher.
He had his own storefront church.
There was only a few members.
There was Ms. Tate,
cousin Nadine...
my foster brothers Keith...
Keith was half white...
Dwight, and me.
It was church 3 times on Sunday...
Bible study on Tuesday...
Y.P.W.W. Meetings on Thursday...
choir rehearsal on Friday.
We found out if we caught the Holy Ghost...
in front of Ms. Tate...
she'd give us vanilla wafers after church.
So we'd catch it every Sunday.
Reverend Tate...
he didn't like Dwight at all.
He said he had too much pride.
So he tried to beat it out of him.
Sometimes, he would even
try to beat him to death.
Did he beat you?
No, sir.
I think he pitied me.
And I liked him for it...
but I was ashamed of him.
What about Mrs. Tate?
What about her?
I don't know which one
of you no-good rotten...
hardheaded niggers put your
dirty hands on my walls...
but I bet I'll get the right one.
I took you in...
when your no-account mammies
threw you away...
and this is the thanks I get?
Tsk.
You ungrateful niggers.
Hmph.
Now I know I got the right one.
She used to brag about...
beating me unconscious.
Hmph.
She'd threaten to do it again.
But she never did.
Why do you think she never did?
Uh... maybe she was scared.
She found a new way to get me, though.
So you like fire, huh?
No, Muh-deah,
no, Muh-deah...
I don't like fire.
You...
stay...
away from things
that don't belong to you.
You hear me?
You hear me?!
Yes, yes, Muh-deah!
- You hear me?!
- Yes!
Dumb nigger.
I tried everything I could...
to get her to like me...
and nothing ever worked.
Were you the youngest
of the foster children?
No,
Dwight was the youngest.
I was in the middle,
and Keith was the oldest.
Ms. Tate, she used to
put us against each other...
so much,
we started hating each other.
But I think deep down inside...
we really hated ourselves.
What do you mean?
Keith was half white.
She would try to compare Keith...
to me and Dwight.
You know,
he had the good hair...
and we had the bad hair.
She used to say how
Keith was better than us...
because his father was white.
I wished I was Keith.
Mmhh.
But not even Keith could escape...
from being called a nigger.
She hardly used our names.
She said the word nigger so often...
called us niggers so often...
that we could tell...
who she was talking to by...
the way she said the word nigger.
What happened to Dwight and Keith?
Dwight is in Lucasville State Penitentiary.
Keith got taken back by his mother.
He was raped by one of her boyfriends.
Mmhh.
Did what happen to Keith happen to you?
Hell, no.
Okay.
Was Mrs. Tate ever...
Was she ever nice to you?
Yeah, there were times.
Sometimes she would
tell her friends that...
we were good kids and that
she was proud of us.
Chummy times.
Chummy times?
Yeah. I got to where I could tell...
what kind of day it was gonna be...
by the scent in the air when I awoke.
How could you tell?
Well, if I awoke
and there was the smell...
of grits and eggs...
or water steaming off the pavement...
as she hosed it down...
I had to look out all day.
But... if I smelled pancakes...
everything was okay.
She make pancakes very often?
No, sir.
I can delay my next appointment...
if you want to talk some more.
No, sir.
Hey, Slim.
What?
You going home next leave?
Hell, yeah. I gotta tend to the flock.
Hey, when I get leave...
I'm gonna be like a... a vampire...
coming to town with his coffin.
Just a place to lay down,
before I get down.
What's that mean?
Man, shut up.
People trying to sleep.
Aw, shut your grouchy ass up. Jesus!
Hey, when you going home, Pork Chop?
When your mama quit tripping...
and send me my money.
What about you, Fish?
When you going home?
Fish?
Fish!
Last night...
I had a dream about Jesse.
Who's Jesse?
He was my best friend.
When I wasn't at home...
I was probably wherever
Jesse was for 3 reasons.
One was, being his friend...
he wouldn't beat me up.
Hey, Jesse, look!
I got 5!
And the other reasons were...
so he wouldn't beat me up.
I only got 3.
I liked him a whole lot.
Give me yours.
We used to drive
our friend Kenny crazy.
Let's get Kenny.
Kenny hung around me...
for the same reasons
I hung around Jesse.
Hey, Kenny, let me see.
Where's Jesse?
Ugh!
Aah! Stop, stop!
Get 'em off, get 'em off!
Hey, Kenny, what's wrong?
Hey, Kenny,
don't forget to write!
Ms. Tate, she hated Jesse.
She hated seeing us together even more.
But for years, she couldn't keep us apart.
I was so happy when she kicked me out.
Twonny.
That hoodlum nigger Jesse
call up here askin' for you.
Said something about y'all
going to the picture show.
Now, that's the devil's work...
and who told you you could go...
to the picture show, anyhow?
I mean, where you get
the money, nigger?
Did you steal it?
I already told you.
I've been raking lawns.
Well, you woulda stole it.
Give me the money.
I said gimme the money.
You don't know what to do
with no money nohow.
That's why I never
let you have none.
Why you always got
to make things...
difficult for me?
Difficult?
Difficult.
Where you learnin'
such fancy words at?
Fancy?
Ain't no fancy word.
Don't sassy me, boy.
No one's sassing you.
Don't sassy me!
Ain't no one sassing you!
Don't you...
I ain't gonna let you beat me no more!
No more!
Lord Jesus.
I want you out of my house.
Hmm?
And who you think
gonna take you in, huh?
Retarded nigger,
don't nobody want you.
Your damn mammy
didn't even want you.
Gimme my shoe. Hmpf!
Must've felt pretty good...
when you took that shoe from her.
Yeah,
I felt like I was gonna go...
right upside her head...
but I just chilled.
Why'd you chill?
I don't know.
Well, I'm glad you did.
How'd you feel?
I felt like I won a prize...
but it scared me.
Why?
It was the first time I ever felt...
more powerful than her.
It was like a surprise.
Whatever happened to Jesse?
We lost touch.
You know how it is.
Yeah.
It might be helpful
to understand the mentality...
of people like the Tates.
Here.
It's called
The Slave Community.
Why I gotta understand
somebody beatin' on me?
What you went through...
was in part the result
of the treatment...
that slaves received
from their masters...
and then passed on
to their own children...
generation to generation to generation...
right on down to the Tates.
Sir, that sounds like an excuse.
I mean, I was a kid.
I understand.
You sound like you takin' up for 'em.
I'm not saying what they did was right.
What they did was wrong.
We all have choices.
They made the wrong choices.
But this is not about them.
This is about you.
You were sent to me...
because you have an anger problem.
Well, you got the right to be angry.
But you also have to learn
to channel that anger...
to use it constructively.
Instead of gettin' into fights...
go to the gym.
Hit the bag,
lift the weights.
You have to use that energy
to better yourself.
You say you're taking
Japanese classes, right?
Yeah.
Okay, you're already
on the right track.
Can we talk about this next week?
3 sessions, son.
Unfortunately...
that's all I'm given
to make a recommendation...
and I'm gonna recommend...
that you be given a second chance.
That is what you want, isn't it?
To stay in the navy?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Okay, stay out of trouble.
Antwone!
What's up?
How you doing?
I'm cool.
Oh.
You don't seem cool.
I'm all right.
What are you doin' in there?
You still workin' on that paper?
No, I'm finished.
I just went through there
for a short cut.
Oh. Where you goin'?
Nowhere.
I... I gotta go.
Cheryl, I'll talk to you later.
Why you always talkin'
about somebody's momma?
Man, we ain't talkin'
about somebody's momma.
We talkin' about your momma!
Hey, Fish!
Yeah, I bet you won't be fightin'
no more honkies on this boat.
Man, this ain't no boat.
Dis a ship.
"Dis a ship!"
Country-ass Negro,
who let you in the navy?
Fish!
What's that book you readin'?
Let me see the cover.
The Slave Community.
Whatcha readin' that shit for?
Because I want to.
This ain't no slave ship.
And these ain't no slavery days.
I can't tell.
You the only buck-dancin'
Uncle Tom on the ship.
You a part-time brother.
Yo, Grayson, man,
what...
Why you always talkin' shit, man?
What I do ain't got nothing
to do with you.
You better get
out of my face, bro.
Either you tryin'
to hang out with the brothers...
or you tryin' to hang
with the white boys, man.
You better sit your ass back...
You better make up your mind.
What you gonna do?
Whatcha gonna do?
Come on!
Stop it!
Let me go!
Get your hands...
Thank you, sir.
Who's next?
So, um, Dr. Davenport...
you sent him to the gym?
Hit the punchin' bags?
Ain't that what you prescribin'?
So, why are you here?
You feelin' under pressure?
You feel like, uh,
a rock is on top of you?
Come on now.
Speak the hell up.
You better make it snappy.
You only got 3 sessions comin'!
What are y'all lookin' at?
What you lookin' at?!
You feelin' sick?
You need a healin'?
Do you need a healin', huh?
Do you need a healin'?!
Some of y'all sick-ass sailors...
need to come back after working hours!
See, that's when
the good Dr. Davenport...
he'll be layin' his hands on you!
Or he may have a book in there...
that may have the answers
to all your problems...
and all your questions!
Ain't that right?!
Ain't that right?
Would you like to step into my office?
Are you finished?
I thought I was
just gettin' started.
Let me tell you something, son.
It may have slipped your mind...
but you are addressing a superior officer.
You understand me?
Do you understand me?!
Yes, sir.
I slipped up.
You better believe you did.
No, sir,
I mean I slipped up...
when I talked to you.
What?
3 sessions, right?
That's correct.
Can't be floutin' regulations.
Well, what do I do, Commander?
'Cause I don't know what to do.
I don't know what to do.
Tired?
How was your day?
Long.
Not complaining, though.
Well, don't wait up.
I got a lot of work to do.
I know.
- Good night.
Well, it's nice
to finally be off...
restriction for a change.
Yeah, I'm gonna be
squared away from now on.
Hey!
Y'all need somethin' from the exchange?
Man, what's up with you
and the exchange?
You spend more time there
than you do on restriction.
I'm just tryin' to be
a good shipmate, man.
I'm only kiddin' with you.
But bring me back some Skittles.
And a Snickers.
And some pork skins.
And a sandwich.
Thank you.
What are you doin' here, sir?
I was in the area and saw your ship.
So you just saw this big ol' ship...
moored alongside the pier?
I want to see you back in my office...
next Wednesday, after knockoff.
That is, if you want to continue.
I think I need to check
my calender first...
sir.
Okay.
Well, you let me know, okay?
Yes, sir.
Hey, Cheryl.
- Hey.
What's going on?
Nothing.
You just gettin' off work?
Yeah.
Oh.
You, uh...
You mad?
Why would I be mad?
I'm sorry.
That's cool.
So, you finally off restriction?
Yeah.
So you can hang out now?
So what about now?
I'm off.
Nah, I gotta...
I gotta meet somebody.
Well, I promised I'd meet somebody...
in a few minutes,
so... you know.
What's her name?
- Look, it ain't like that.
- Ok.
It ain't like that.
What about tomorrow?
Um, what about the day after tomorrow?
Say, Wednesday, after knockoff?
That'd be better.
Okay. Um...
meet me in the lobby
of the female barracks...
at 1700.
Okay. All right.
I'll meet you at 1700.
- All right.
- Yeah.
It's a date.
Are we done?
Yes, we are.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
Um...
do you think it's...
Do you think it's possible...
for somebody that had
problems all their life...
you know,
not to stay that way?
You know,
you think it's possible...
they can change?
Absolutely.
Why do you ask?
No reason.
Do you want something to drink?
- No, I'm good, sir.
- Okay.
Uh, you know, you...
You know, when you
kinda meet somebody...
you know, if you have problems...
it wouldn't...
Who is she?
What's her name?
Cheryl.
She works at the exchange.
That's a good thing.
Keep it navy.
Right?
So?
Um... so, um...
Have you spoken to her yet?
Yeah, I spoke to her,
but, um...
I get caught up...
tongue-tied.
Everybody's awkward at first.
Okay.
No, not like me.
No, everybody is, Antwone.
Trust me.
Even you?
Even me. Everybody.
So...
Well, we're going out tonight.
Good.
We supposed to go out
a couple of days ago...
but, uh, you know...
I just wanted to clear my head.
Take some time.
You know, talk to you first.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
So, what should I do?
Well, she's a nice girl?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, obviously you like her.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, I think you should
just go out with her.
I mean...
I tell you what.
You know, sometimes it helps...
just to take the anxiety
out of a future meeting...
to role play.
What's that?
Like, you play yourself
and I'll play Cheryl...
and I'll ask you some questions...
and we'll have a conversation...
and you'll see that
you'll have a good time, okay?
Yeah,
you play Cheryl.
Okay, now.
That's right.
I'm man enough to play Cheryl.
Okay.
Uh, you go first.
Nah.
I'll go first.
So...
how you doing?
Fine.
Good, good.
So, where we gonna go?
Out.
See?
Uh...
I'm hungry. You?
I could eat.
See? That's good.
You got it.
- You think so?
- Absolutely.
I don't think you have
anything to worry about.
I'm gonna give you
my phone number.
If you have any problems...
any questions at all,
you can call me.
Any time of day or night.
Have fun.
Give me a call, okay?
We're gonna be fine.
Okay.
You never know, son.
These things,
sometimes they can escalate.
Escalate into what?
My wife and I went out.
It escalated into marriage.
No, we not escalatin' into marriage.
All right, well good.
You get outta here.
And have fun.
Hey...
have fun.
- Okay?
- I will.
Okay, see you later.
No escalating.
Okay.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
What is this?
Frappuccino.
Frappuccino?
Yeah.
You like it?
For $6.00?
What do you care how much it cost?
All the money we're makin'.
That's why I joined
the navy, you know?
To see the world,
build a fortune.
I don't know what to do...
with all the money I got.
Okay, now tell me...
why you really joined the navy.
For real?
Yeah, for real.
All right, well...
my father's a navy man,
Vietnam vet...
and, uh, his boys were
gonna grow up one day...
and join and serve just like he did.
Only one little problem.
He didn't have any boys.
- So you...
- Mm-hmm.
So I, yep.
It's worth it, you know?
I mean,
even if I hated the navy...
which I don't...
it's worth it just to...
just to see his eyes
and the way they shine...
when I put on that uniform.
So you and him are close?
Yeah.
We're close.
Mm.
Can't wait to go home for Thanksgiving.
You going home?
I'm gonna go home.
Mm.
I'm kinda hungry.
How about you?
I could eat.
What?
Nah...
Nothing.
What?
- What?
- You sure?
- No.
- Okay.
You shoulda ordered something.
I like what I ordered.
These are good.
You know, vegetables
are good for you.
Want to try some?
Come on.
Try it.
It's good.
It's got, uh,
white cabbage...
purple cabbage, yellow cabbage.
Nasty cabbage.
Man!
It's not that bad.
Mm-hmm.
So...
what do you like to do?
Or what do you want to do?
What would you like to do?
What would I like to do?
Mm-hmm.
Um...
like, um...
I want to teach.
Yeah?
My mother was a teacher.
- For real?
- Mm-hmm.
Mm.
A teacher's, um...
I think that's a powerful position,
you know?
You get to give to kids and all that.
I think you'll make
an excellent teacher.
Really?
Thank you.
I think, um...
I think you're beautiful.
Thank you.
What?
Well, it's just funny.
I mean, nice,
what happens to your...
To your mouth when you smile.
One side curls up higher than the other.
Did you ever know that?
No.
It's cute.
Oh, thank you.
You shouldn't hide it, you know?
You should smile more often.
It's good for you.
Yeah.
Oh.
Here we are.
You had a good time?
Yeah.
I had a great time.
Thank you.
Well... good night.
Good night.
What is that?
Japanese.
That meant,
"It gave me great pleasure...
to spend this evening with you."
Cool.
That was beautiful.
Thank you.
So, how do they say...
"Maybe we can do this again sometime?"
Uh...
I don't know.
Nah.
Let me know.
I will.
Good night.
Oh, yeah,
I kissed her, man!
Shoot.
But I ain't...
I ain't gettin'
into all the intimate details with you.
For real.
That's just how it is.
That's my girl,
I respect her and...
Mind yours.
God, that made me look like a pizza.
Hey.
Hi.
Ohh.
Whatcha doing?
Organizing.
These pile up.
Well...
you could start off
by gettin' rid of that one.
Make the pile a little smaller.
No, you're gonna have to get in line.
Yeah?
I remember that one.
You can get rid of that one, too.
Look it.
Huh.
Ohh...
a lifetime ago.
Not to me.
Let's see this.
What?
How long are we gonna do this?
Are you gonna just keep ignoring me?
Come on, baby.
Come on, now.
What are you talkin' about?
I mean...
we're just having a good time.
Why don't we...
You're just gonna continue to act...
like you don't know
what I'm talking about?
Look, I don't know
what you're talking about.
You don't know...
I'm hungry, you know?
I mean, I walk in...
Talk to me.
Jerome?
She kissed me.
What?
I didn't even push her.
The only thing I did was
I walked her to her door...
I threw some Japanese on her...
and then she kissed me.
Listen, Seaman Fisher...
Oh, sir,
I'm sorry for knockin' on your door...
but I had to.
I had to talk to you.
Hello.
I'm sorry for bustin' in
on you like this.
You know,
this is highly irregular.
Yes, sir, I know.
But what am I gonna do?
I mean, we get underway
to Mexico next week...
and I'm startin' to get
serious with this girl.
Okay, okay.
Well, she'll be here
when you get back.
How do you know?
Maybe she won't.
Because if she has a fraction
of the bounce that you have...
she'll be here,
I guarantee you.
So you think I should just chill?
That would be a good suggestion.
- Chill. Yes.
- Okay.
I won't be doing this again.
Thank you very much.
Good night.
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
Who was that?
A patient of mine.
He was, uh...
on his first date.
He was so excited.
He couldn't wait to tell me about it.
Well, don't cure him.
Yeah!
Show me what you're working with!
Show me what you're
working with, whoo!
Hey!
All right, man! Fish!
I don't know about you,
but if my math is right...
we a lady short at this table.
Oh, you ain't know?
My man Fish says
he got himself a girlfriend.
She's in the navy.
Right, Fish?
Yeah, be writin' to her
every minute he can find.
Just so romantic.
Quieres bailar?
I don't understand.
Oh, you understand.
Quieres bailar?
Si. Si, bailar.
I don't know...
She wants to mate.
Do the dance.
You understand.
Come, come!
Venga, venga.
No, I'm fine.
Let her oil the old slave down.
What your girlfriend don't know...
won't hurt you.
Hey, come on, man.
Get up, get up, get up.
No, I don't want to.
You don't what?
You should leave him alone, Grayson.
I'm not botherin' him.
But he didn't answer my question.
What question?
You don't what?
How come I never seen you
with a girl, huh?
I mean, man says he's got
a girlfriend, right?
Well, anybody ever met her?
Huh?
Anybody?
Don't worry about it, sweetheart.
You see,
he's a cherry boy.
Never been to the sugar shack.
Too scared to go.
Fuck you, Grayson.
Huh?
What did you say?
You heard me.
Fuck me?
With all these women in here?
You want me?
See what I mean, brothers?
Hell, I'm worried about you, Fish.
I mean, all this action up in here.
Why you don't want no woman?
Yeah. Faggot.
Here we go again.
Davenport.
What time does his plane get in?
Okay.
No, no, I understand.
I understand.
Okay, just let me talk to him first.
All right, thank you.
I thought we were
all done fightin', Antwone.
Let me in.
The X.O. Wired the statements
of your shipmates.
Now, do you wanna start
at the beginning?
Look, you're gonna
have to talk to me, son.
You better tell me something...
'cause I'm all you got right now.
Now,
I'm tryin' to work things out...
with your commanding officer...
but you gotta give me something.
I don't know what to say.
So tell me what happened.
They were frontin' me.
What do you mean,
frontin' you?
Some of the guys
were baggin' on me.
I couldn't take it.
How so?
I don't know.
Just, uh...
just makin'... makin' jokes.
What kind of jokes?
Jokes about me with...
With women.
I wasn't takin' it.
What kind of jokes about
you bein' with women, Antwone?
Jokes like me bein' a virgin.
Are you?
I don't know.
I might be.
Okay.
Why do you think you
haven't been with a woman?
Think about it, son.
Must be a reason.
I mean, you're a...
good-lookin' young man.
Must've had many opportunities.
Maybe you don't like women.
Maybe you like men.
I like women.
Maybe you don't care about sex.
I care about sex.
I think about it all the time.
All right. We're right
back where we started.
How come you've never
been with a woman?
I have.
Okay.
When?
When I was young.
There was...
There was a kiss.
Okay.
How was it?
I hated it.
It was t...
It was terrible.
Why?
I threw up.
Because...
because she put her tongue in my mouth.
She... she always did.
That's my mama.
That ain't your mama!
You said the other lady was yours!
I changed!
What?
You can't change!
That's my mama!
Nigger?
Nigger, you hear me callin' you?
I said nigger.
Comin', Muh-deah!
Dwight! Keith!
Yes, Muh-deah.
Here... here I come.
Get your behinds down here.
And I told y'all not
to mess up your clothes!
- Nadine?
- Yes?
We're gonna be downtown...
at the social service office.
All right.
Twonny? You stay with Nadine.
Yes, Muh-deah.
Twonny.
What you lookin' at out there?
Hmm?
What you lookin' at?
That's it.
Gimme some sugar.
Now get on downstairs.
What did I say?
Get on downstairs.
In that basement and drop 'em.
Hurry up.
Now, unbutton 'em all.
Come on.
I said, come on!
Now, pull 'em down.
You heard me, pull 'em down.
Pull 'em right over my feet.
Now get over here closer.
Closer.
You don't have to be afraid.
Now touch me.
You know you wanna.
Yeah, that's it. Kiss me.
Come on, now. I said kiss me.
Baby, gimme some sugar.
Antwone!
Ooh! I'm gonna tell on you!
What's up, man?
You all right?
Come on in.
She did it again.
She hit you, too?
It's okay, Antwone.
You could stay here.
I'll look after you.
Come on. Let's get you a shirt.
She made me...
She made me do these things.
And I was only a little boy.
If there was something
that I wouldn't do...
she would beat me.
And Jesse was the only one
you ever told?
Yes, sir.
She's the only woman
I ever seen naked.
I'm almost 25 years old.
I never done it.
That's embarrassing.
I hate it.
Yes,
can I help you with something?
Hello, Ms. Davenport.
I'm Seaman Fisher.
Antwone Fisher, ma'am.
Well, what can I do for you?
I'm here to see the commander.
I'm one of his patients.
He told me to meet him here.
Well, he's not home yet.
But...
um...
Well, come on inside.
You can wait.
Would you like some cider?
Sure. Thank you.
Seems you gettin' all ready
for Thanksgiving, ma'am.
Don't call me ma'am.
You're gonna make me feel old.
Call me Berta.
So, are you going home
for the holidays?
No,
but the chief cook on the ship...
he's plannin' a big meal.
So I'll be there for that.
That sounds nice.
Here you go.
Thank you. Very much.
Um...
first thing I saw...
first time I was in his office...
it was you.
Yeah. It was your picture.
I thought you
had a nice face...
a good face, and...
maybe he's all right...
if he married a woman like you.
You ready to get started?
Yes, sir.
Nice meetin' you.
It was very nice to meet you, too.
Okay.
I was just tryin' to be nice.
Why don't you try bein'
nice on that ship?
Hmm?
Have a seat.
I like your house.
Thank you.
Tell me about your house.
Your house the day
you left your family.
Sir?
The Tates.
When they threw you out.
Tell me about that.
Oh.
It was back to the orphanage.
Um...
they, uh... they told me I needed...
to develop my social skills.
Nobody was into adoptin' teenage boys.
Uh...
they sent me to a reform school...
in Pennsylvania.
That's where I got
my excellent skills I have now.
Hmm...
What then?
Um... I was on my own.
The social worker,
she took me to a...
A men's shelter.
She gave me $67...
and, uh...
she said good-bye.
How long were you at the shelter?
Just till the next mornin'.
And?
I slept on a few park benches...
and I came here.
To my house?
No, sir.
I joined the navy.
That's it.
I mean,
that's the Antwone Fisher story.
Okay.
That is it.
You're done for today.
Okay, sir.
Don't talk to my wife anymore either.
You hear me?
Yes, sir.
All right.
Seaman Fisher.
Sir?
Get up here.
What I do?
Cut the jaw jackin'.
Up here right now.
I don't know what
you think you're up to...
but you better be careful.
I didn't do anything.
You didn't do anything?
My wife is inviting
you to Thanksgiving.
She thinks you're very charming.
Do you have any idea...
where she might've
gotten that impression?
Huh?
Look at me when I'm talkin' to you.
No, sir.
Maybe she responds to nice people.
Okay, nice people.
Next Thursday.
Thanksgiving,
my house...
my family, my dinner table. 1400.
Don't be late.
Yes, sir.
Get outta here.
It's nice out here.
How'd you find this place?
It's a lighthouse.
I'm a sailor.
It found me.
You knucklehead.
You come out here a lot?
Sometimes I come out here to think.
Or to work out some problems.
Mmm.
I know what you mean.
Well, um...
Can I be honest with you?
Yeah.
Remember when I, uh...
I told you that I was...
I was workin' on
that important paper?
Yeah.
Well, I lied.
I know.
You know?
Yeah.
You're seein' a psychiatrist, aren't you?
Ohh...
you knew.
Yeah, I knew.
It wasn't that hard to figure out.
Mmm...
Are you tryin' to tell me I'm crazy?
No.
So?
So I'll understand if you...
If you don't wanna
be bothered no more.
You're not the only person...
that's seen a shrink before.
Oh, you seen one?
No...
but I told you
my dad's a Vietnam vet.
He has.
I guess he made it, huh?
So, why...
why are you seein' a psychiatrist?
My life before the navy
was kind of complicated.
I was feelin' ashamed.
Of what?
Of bein' unwanted.
And, uh...
I had no parents.
Mmm...
You know, I was...
I was afraid to even approach you.
Would you believe...
that...
I was too shy to approach you?
- No.
- Yeah.
Um, until I realized
you were stalking me.
I wasn't stalking you.
Well, if there's anything
I could do to help...
I'm here.
You're doin' it already.
What am I doin'?
Just bein' you.
Happy Thanksgiving.
Um...
happy Thanksgiving.
Happy holidays, sir.
Happy holidays, ma'am.
I know.
It's... Berta.
Yeah.
Come on... come on in.
Hello.
I'm Antwone.
I, um...
Yeah, I'm hungry.
I could eat.
1400, huh?
What took you so long?
Oh, I stopped by
to get some cider, sir.
- Okay. Good.
- Happy holidays.
Thank you. Come on in.
Everybody's here waitin' for you.
We're about to say grace.
All right, everybody.
This is Antwone.
- Antwone, this is my family.
- Hello
- That's my mother Johnny Mae.
That's my wife's brother Uncle Duke.
- How you doin'?
- Hello, sir.
This is my dad Howard.
- That's my sister Gwen...
- How you doin'?
And her full-grown daughter.
Hi, Antwone.
Oh, you wanna come and sit next to her?
Gwen, Gwen. Uh...
Come on, baby.
You come on over here and sit.
Okay.
All right.
Duke, why don't you lead us in prayer?
Okay.
Everybody join hands.
Let's bow our heads.
Heavenly Father...
we come to you on bent knee...
and body bowed...
as humble as we know how.
We are grateful for this opportunity...
to share another Thanksgiving Day...
as a family.
We thank you for our health...
O Lord, and for our friends...
who honor us with their presence.
We also pray for peace in the world...
and in our lives. Amen.
Amen.
All right.
This looks good.
Yeah!
Here's a little piece.
Thank you. Mmm.
Honey,
you want some more turkey?
Oh, no,
thank you, ma'am.
Ohh, don't be actin'
all bashful around me.
Especially at the dinner table.
Dad, leave that boy alone.
Shoot!
- Huh?
- I'm okay.
All right, then,
let me see you dig in.
I mean, the food is free.
Howard...
You know, when I was in the service...
back in the war... that was
before you were born...
Howard!
Anyway, I spent the holidays...
in Europe on guard duty,
and I... ohh!
I sure did miss my mama's
holiday cookin'. Whoo-oo!
Howard, would you leave the boy alone?
Oh, I ain't botherin' him none, Johnny Mae.
No, you leave me alone, huh?
Baby, he wants to eat!
Oh, no, look, I'm just talkin' to the boy.
I'm sure he wants to be
home with his family, okay?
Hey, listen,
let me ask you something.
Where you from?
Cleveland.
Cleveland. Yeah?
Yeah.
Cleveland...
I bet you miss your mama's
holiday cookin'...
don't you? Huh?
Excuse me.
Where he goin'?
I don't know.
See?
That's what happens every holiday season.
Why do you want to do that to the boy?
Y'all ran the boy outta here!
That's what happens every holiday!
I didn't run the boy out.
I was tryin'
to talk to the boy.
You okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
I just never had
a real Thanksgiving...
at the Tates' before.
You didn't have a real one...
over here either, I guess.
You have a real nice family.
Thank you.
I got this for you...
for having me over today.
Oh, you got a gift for me.
Is it money?
No.
Oh, it's a poem.
I can't see without my glasses.
Why don't you read it for me?
Um, I'd rather you read it.
Please.
"Who will cry for the little boy?
"Lost and all alone.
"Abandoned without his own.
Who will cry for the little boy?"
"He cried himself to sleep.
"Who will cry for the little boy?
Who never had for keeps."
"Who walked the burning sand.
"Who will cry for the little boy?
"The boy inside the man.
"Who knew well hurt and pain.
"Who will cry for the little boy?
"Who died and died again.
"A good boy he tried to be.
"Who will cry for the little boy?
Who cries inside of me?"
Who will cry for the little boy, Antwone?
I will.
I always do.
It's beautiful, Antwone.
I know. I told you I was good.
Yes, you are.
You are good...
because you're honest.
You're more honest than most people...
even in your anger.
The only thing you're
not honest with yourself...
about is your need
to find your own family.
Your natural family.
I don't feel like
I need to look for them.
Mmm. It would answer
a lot of questions for you.
I don't have any questions.
You're upset with them...
because you feel they
didn't come to your rescue.
Maybe they didn't know.
How could they not have known?
That's a question you need to ask them.
"Regard without ill will...
despite an offense."
That's Webster's definition of forgiveness.
Why do I have to forgive?
To free yourself...
so that you can get on with your life.
Why I gotta go look for my family?
I got you, Doc.
Ohh...
I think that he had a good time tonight.
Hmm?
Antwone.
I think that, uh...
he had a good time, don't you?
Yeah, seemed like it.
He did the sweetest thing at the door...
when he was saying good-bye.
He invited me to come to his ceremony.
You know he's graduating
from his Japanese class.
Yeah, I know.
Well, he wants me to come.
To be with you.
What did you tell him?
I told him that I would
be honored, Jerome.
Okay...
Okay.
Congratulations.
Petty Officer Fisher.
Good job.
Thank you, Commander.
I was waiting.
Cheryl, right?
How you doin', Cheryl?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Heard nothin' but
good things about you.
Where's your wife?
She couldn't make it.
She sends along her congratulations.
A small gift for you.
Okay.
The Philosophy and Opinions of Marcus Garvey.
Thank you, sir.
You're welcome.
Is there somewhere
we can talk in private?
Do you mind?
That's fine.
I don't mind.
Okay.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, sir.
Hello?
What's up, Doc?
How are you?
I'm good.
Yes, you are, Antwone.
You're good.
I hear nothin' but good things...
from your C.O.
Hear that you're
gettin' along very well...
with your shipmates.
I'm proud of you.
Thank you, sir.
Have you thought anymore
about finding your family?
I don't know.
For what?
Well, I just think
that there's really nothing...
more important than that, Antwone.
What are you tryin' to say, sir?
That I'm proud of you...
that I think you've come a long way.
Okay.
You said that.
What's wrong?
There's nothin' wrong.
You understand,
this is very difficult for me.
Our sessions have ended.
Now, listen.
Just listen to me, all right?
I've taken the liberty of...
What do you mean, they ended?
They... They ended, son,
and it's time for you...
to move on.
You can't stall here.
But you and me are
workin' out my problems.
You and me can't work out...
You told me that we need...
to figure out my problems.
- Listen to me...
- Get off me!
Hey, get out!
- Get out!
- Nobody ever stays!
Everybody's always leavin' me!
People grow.
People move on.
You've grown.
It's time for you to move on.
Hey, my mother left me!
- My father!
- I understand...
Jesse and you!
Jesse? What do you mean?
We shoulda never gone,
that's what. Jesse!
Jesse?
Tell me something...
Cow bells ringin' in my fuckin' head!
Cow bells?
Tell me about the cow bells...
But I keep trustin' people!
Trustin'...
What happened to Jesse, Antwone?
Stay away from me.
Nobody's takin' anything else away...
from me no more.
Who is it?
Man, I just asked who was it.
Fish! Oh!
Hey, what's up, dog?
What's up with you, man?
What's goin' on with you, man?
Hey, man, stop playin'.
Stop playin'?
All right...
don't make me kick your ass now.
You know you can't fight worth shit.
Man...
What's up with you, man?
What's up with you?
Where you been at?
Where you stayin'?
What's up?
Huh?
I'm at the men's shelter.
On Prospect.
Where you stayin' at, man?
For real.
I'm on the street.
What you doin' on the streets, man?
I got nowhere else to go, man.
You ain't got nowhere to go.
You couldn't come to my house?
No, man. Your mom ain't
gonna let me stay up in here.
You trippin', man.
She ain't gotta know.
I mean,
she work all day...
sleep all night.
Besides...
there's so many people stayin' up...
in this house,
She wouldn't even know
you're here no way, dog.
You can stay here,
for real.
Y'all got something in the refrigerator?
Yeah, we got something...
You hungry?
- I'm hungry.
- You hungry?
- Yeah, man.
- "Yeah, man."
- Stop playin'.
- Come in here.
I mean, you smell like you been...
on the streets, too, man.
Dang, slow down, man.
Ain't nobody gonna take your food.
Hey...
Hey, you remember that time...
Mrs. Tate wouldn't let you use her lotion?
She made you oil up
with old cooking grease instead.
You walking around all day...
smelling like a fried chicken dinner.
You like,
"I sho' is hungry!"
Man, that was so funny.
That had me rolling for real.
But not as funny as your mother...
chasing you down the street with that brick.
Oh, okay, okay.
You remember that?
Yeah, I remember that.
That was funny.
Dude,
that wasn't funny, man.
I still got the knot
in the back of my head.
Fish, you know you're
my best friend, right?
What you want?
What, I can't be happy
my dude back on the block?
Huh? I can't be happy
you back here at home, man?
I want you to do something for me, though.
What?
Just look out for me.
Somebody after you?
Why somebody got to be after me, man?
Huh?
I just want you to look out for me, dude.
All right.
You my best friend, right?
Yeah, man.
Stop trippin', man.
Man, come on.
Let's get you cleaned up...
and hit the streets.
Yeah, I don't know.
You know Brenda.
I used to like her.
Psh.
The Brenda you used to like, dog...
got about, like, 3 kids now.
Gettin' all swole.
She big for real, dog.
Ain't no little bootie Brenda no more.
Hey, how's your mother?
Aw, tsh, man,
she got knocked up.
For real?
Yeah.
It's bad.
Go ahead, man.
Get you something.
I got you.
Break it off, old man!
Jess, what you doing?
This ain't no riddle.
This ain't nothing
you got to figure out.
- Jess...
- Hey, hold off, Fish.
Hey,
you better break off my loot!
- Hey, Jess, man...
- Look out for me, Fish.
And by the end of the next day...
I was in boot camp.
I always felt like
Jesse was the lucky one...
and I envied him for it.
Well, how could he
be the lucky one? He's dead.
Yeah, well, he left me...
and he knew he was the only one I had.
So, you're angry at him...
because you felt he abandoned you.
Yes.
A little bit.
How is he the lucky one?
'Cause he don't have to fight no more.
Neither do you.
So, you think I'll make it?
I think you already have.
What do you think?
I think, uh...
maybe in another life or time...
I would have been king.
When you locate your family...
I want you to contact me.
All right?
I want to hear all about it.
Yes, sir.
I love you, son.
I love you, too.
Who's this?
Guess who.
Antwone.
No, this is Phillip Walker...
the late-night stalker.
Aw.
So...
I, um,
I'm going on leave.
When?
As soon as you
put your request in...
and come with me.
You serious?
Yes.
I just came back.
They're not gonna let me
leave again this year.
Can you ask for emergency leave?
Tell them somebody close to you...
is in desperate need.
Cheryl, I...
I really want you to come with me.
I got these, uh...
2 open tickets.
To Cleveland.
You're gonna try and find them.
Yeah.
I need to find them.
But not without your help.
All right.
Let me see what I can do.
First the light-skinned girls.
They got adopted the quickest.
Then the light-skinned boys...
and then the dark-skinned girls...
and then,
last but not least...
the dark-skinned boys.
I'm really sorry.
All birth records since 1980...
have been moved to social services.
Last contact with your mother?
I was 2 months old.
And with father?
Never.
Place of birth.
Ohio State Correctional Facility for Women.
I'll be right back.
I need you to sign for me.
Best of luck, Mr. Fisher.
Thank you.
There's nothing in here.
Why don't you go see your foster mother?
- Who, Mrs. Tate?
- Yeah.
I'm not... I'm...
I'm not going back.
Well, why not?
I mean, she might know
something about your family.
No.
I haven't done this before.
Take a ride with me.
If you selling shit,
just keep on walking.
Oh, my God.
Is that you, Antwone?
Come here, baby.
Don't touch me.
Yeah, it's me...
and I'm all grown up.
I'd like to speak to Ms. Tate.
Well, you want to come in?
No.
Would you like to get her?
'Twon's here.
Lord have mercy.
Where's the child?
Oh, nigger!
Hug my neck.
Oh, nigger.
I...
Don't you know how to come home?
Where you been?
I came for one thing:
Whatever you can tell me
about my real family.
I don't know nothing
about your real peoples.
A name, number, anything?
I said I don't know.
Now, come along.
Come on.
I remember everything.
Everything.
You could have helped me...
but instead, you beat me
to dust, and you...
Boy, I don't know
what you're talking about...
Yes, you do.
I was 6 years old!
Now, you just listen...
No, you listen to me!
No, I think you done forgotten...
I think you forgotten.
I said listen to me.
This is my time.
You understand me?
It don't matter...
what you tried to do.
You couldn't destroy me.
I'm still standing.
I'm still strong.
And I always will be.
Antwone.
Elkins.
Your father's name was Edward Elkins.
You take Shaker Heights and East Cleveland...
and I'm gonna take Akron and Cleveland.
Yeah. 1976.
Hello. Hi, um...
I'm looking for the family of Edward Elkins.
Edward Elkins.
Hello.
Hi, I'm looking for the family...
no... Ed-ward.
E-D-W-A-R-D.
What? I'm speaking clearly.
You can't...
Okay.
Well, thank...
thank you.
I'm looking for the family...
of an Edward Elkins.
You should have said
that in the first place.
Wha... why you...
Forget it, man.
Yeah, well,
we're from California.
Yes, it's very nice here.
Okay, well, thank you
for your help, ma'am.
Thank you. Bye.
Any luck?
What you got?
Chinese.
Hello?
Hello, ma'am.
Yes?
I'm looking for the family...
of an Edward Elkins.
Hmm?
Wh-who is this calling about Edward?
My name is Antwone Fisher.
I didn't mean to disturb you.
I'm just trying to locate my family.
Honey, Edward Elkins been dead...
a long time.
Yes, ma'am, I know...
a long time, but he was my father.
Wait, wait, wait.
Who is this...
calling me up out of nowhere?
How'd you get this number?
I got your number
out of the phone book.
I been calling Elkins all day.
Got no reason to lie to you, ma'am.
Well, honey,
Edward never mentioned no...
What's your name again?
Antwone.
I don't think he knew
my mother was pregnant.
She was away in prison.
You know how he died?
Yes, ma'am.
He was murdered by
one of his girlfriends.
My God.
Wait.
What made you decide to show up...
20-some-odd years later
in the middle of the night?
Mmm, that's a long story.
But I'm in the navy...
and, uh, I'm stationed on the west coast.
I gotta get back in a few days.
Well, I... I want you to come
by my house before you go.
Okay.
Okay, look.
Y-Y-You have a pencil?
Take down my address.
Yeah.
It's 1089 Drexel.
1089 Drexel.
You know where that is?
Yes, ma'am.
All right, well, come by
my house tomorrow, hear?
- Okay. Um, ma'am...
- Yes?
You mind if I bring
my girlfriend with me?
Yes, fine. I'm... I'm looking
forward to meeting her.
I'm sure she's looking
forward to meeting you, too.
You... listen.
You know, if...
If Edward was your father...
then you talking to your auntie, son.
You are talking to your Auntie Annette...
your daddy's baby sister.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Good night.
Bye.
I found them.
Hmm?
I found my family.
You did?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, baby.
Mmm.
I don't know.
What do you think?
Well, he does look like Eddie.
I do?
Yeah, you look just like him.
Mm-hmm.
I brought my birth certificate.
Born in '76.
That's the year Edward died.
Yeah, he...
He died in June...
and I was born in August.
And your mother's name is...
- Eva Mae Fisher.
Eva?
I know Eva.
That's Jess's sister.
Who?
Jess.
You mean Fish?
Yeah, Fish.
Jess Fisher.
The boy's name is Antwone Fisher.
That's Jess Fisher's sister, Eva Mae.
You know, Mae-Mae.
She live over there on Hodge Street.
No, I don't remember no Mae-Mae.
Y-You know where she lives?
You don't know her, do you?
No. I... I...
No, no.
You want to meet her?
Uh...
yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
You sure?
'Cause we can take care
of this right here and now.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Let me get my hat.
Want me to go with you?
No, why don't you just stay
here with us, baby?
Okay, let's ride.
Bye.
You're not gonna let nothing
happen to me, are you?
No, Antwone.
I won't let nothing happen to you.
Who is it?
Eva, it's James.
James Elkins.
Edward's brother.
Did you hear me, Eva?
This is James.
What you want?
Can we come in?
Hey, Eva.
Hey.
It's all right, son.
Come on.
Who's that, Eva?
That's Johnny.
No.
That's Antwone Quenton Fisher.
Who's Antwone Quenton Fisher, Eva?
That's my first-born son.
Oh, God.
Ohh!
There's nothing going on around here.
You wanna stay?
I'm gonna stay.
I'll be in the car.
You want something to eat?
No.
Why'd you never come for me?
Didn't you wonder where I was...
or what I was doing...
or what I'd become...
or even if I was still alive?
Didn't you?
I've taken care of myself.
I have.
I've never been in trouble with the law.
I've read hundreds of books...
written poems...
painted pictures.
I've traveled the world.
I serve my country.
I speak 2 languages...
and I'm working on a third.
I never fathered any children.
I've never done drugs...
or even smoked a cigarette.
I used to dream about you.
My mother.
You know,
what you'd be like.
How you look.
Your voice and your smile.
Even your scent.
For all these years
I wondered about you.
I dreamed about you.
Didn't you miss me?
On the way to school
each day...
I imagined you were just
around the next corner...
and when I'd get there,
you'd be there.
And in my mind,
you was always there.
You just couldn't find me.
So I'd race to the next corner...
and you'd be there.
I'd know you would.
Then you would
buy me ice cream.
And then you would take me home.
I'm a good person.
I'm a good man.
Hey, boy, how you doin'?
I'm your Uncle Horace.
Get out of the way, Horace.
Come on, baby. Here he is!
Oh, look at you!
Look at you!
I'm your Aunt Eda, baby.
Ooh, I'm your cousin Jeanette.
Welcome home!
And I'm your Aunt Anna.
How you doin', baby?
This is my wife, "T."
How you doin', good-lookin'?
I'm your cousin Eddie.
My dad named me after your father.
And this is my brother Ray.
Whassup, dog?
What's crackin', man?
Hey, I'm your cousin Jason, man.
What's happenin'?
All right, boys, open up.
Welcome.
All right.
Come on, let's eat!
You want some pancakes? Ooh.
Sure, sure.
Here we go.
How about some sausages?
I'm not a virgin anymore.
I'm glad to hear that.
How you doin', son?
I'm great, sir.
All right. Good.
Good, good.
Very good to see you.
So?
I took your advice.
I found my family
and I found my mother.
Good.
Yeah.
So?
Well, in my heart I forgive her...
but if I never saw her again...
I understand.
It's funny to feel that way
about your mother...
but I did it...
and I owe it to you to tell you
that you were right.
You owe it to me?
Yes, sir.
I needed to find her.
Yeah. Well...
if I was right, it was
for all the wrong reasons.
Sir?
This stays between you and me, okay?
Yes, sir.
My wife and I, we were gonna
have a bunch of kids...
when we found out
we couldn't have any.
And it rocked her to the core.
I knew what to do for her, though.
She needed help, treatment.
I made sure she had it.
The best psychiatrist,
the one that trained me.
But I...
the well one, the strong one...
At the same time I went about
the business of shutting down.
Very subtle, very quiet.
It was my little secret.
Until one day, a young man came
into my office and into my life...
and he blew up that little
secret, right in my face.
And he put me to shame in a way
I never thought possible.
Because of you, Antwone,
I'm a better doctor...
and I'm learning
to be a better husband.
You don't owe me anything.
I owe you.
You're the champ, son.
You've beaten everybody
who was beating you.
I salute you.
You hungry, sailor?
I could eat, sir.
Let's go.