Hello!
Hello, is it Ha-tau?
I'm Auntie!
What's the matter?
Are you still sleeping?
I'll call you later
OK!
Hello!
It's you again, Auntie!
You still didn't get up!
Then I call you later
Oh, no need! Just go on!
The problem is that your
cousin is not feeling well
and will go to see doctor!
To avoid wasting time in travelling
I'll let her live with you for
several day! OK?
Didn't I have a cousin really?
She's your second uncle's
daughter, Ah-ngor!
Who is it?
I just thought that you were out!
I'm Ah-ngor!
You are my cousin, aren't you?
Just treat yourself at home!
There are kitchen and washroom
Hello! Someone's calling me!
Tell him to call me later!
Hello!
Hello! Can I speak to Brother Wah?
He's sleeping. Who is calling?
You don't even know me
You must be his new friend
I'm Fly! Who are you?
I am his cousin!
Cousin?! Never mind!
Tell him that I'm waiting for
bargaining with Fat-karl
Tell him to contact me
when he get up
OK!
Hello!
Hello, Cousin!
Didn't Brother Wah get up?
Didn't still! Is it urgent?
Didn't you want me to wake him up?
No, thanks! If he get up,
tell him that I'm still
waiting for Fat-karl
and tell him to call me!
OK!
Go to sleep if you are tired!
I could sleep in the living room tonight!
Why do you wear a gauze-mask?
To avoid infecting other!
What kind of disease?
The doctor said that my lung
is malfunctioning
and tell me to see a specialist
You won't die!
Just eat more oranges and
you'll be alright!
So strange!
A guy called Fly had phoned you
several time a while ago!
Really? What did he say?
Hello!
Hello, little cousin!
Haven't Brother Wah get up?
Hello!
I'm still staying with Fat-karl
for collecting debt
Damn it! You still haven't
get the money till now?
He's just making fun of you!
you stay there and I come at once!
I cannot go for dinner
with you tonight!
Here's one hundred dollars
for your dinner!
The key is under the carpet!
Take it off, would you?
It isn't looking good
Have a cup of tea first!
Fat-karl, I tell you...
I'm doing you favour
to talk with you
for such a long time
I, Fly, am not famous
because I'm not qualified
also my Big Brother always
tell me to be subtle
Did you know Mr. Aeroplane
of Agah-chee Wan?!
He had made a debt of $1600
and just paid it late for two days,
now he cannot fly,
and have to sit on a wheel chair
I did that with my own hands
Are you trying to frighten me?
He, Aeroplane, is a nobody
and cannot be compared to me
I tell you...
I, Fat-karl,
never before have the habit
of paying debt
Let's say that Big-Circle
who were more powerful...
and now Big-Circle
becomes Small-Circle!
Do you know why?
It was because he forced me
to pay his debt,
so I hit him nearly into death
He now get only one eye left!
Just having two years experience
don't you have the guts to collect my debt?
I got knife-scars more than
the number of your leg's hair!
Scar? My Big Brother has one!
I'll cut myself if you have!
Cut yourself then!
Haven't you finish talking?
We're in the beginning still!
Still in the beginning for so many hours!
Don't you want to die?
Don't move! Everybody don't move!
Would you pay the debt?
Yes, yes! Why wouldn't I?
It's unbelievable! So easy!
I know, just by his face,
that he is a sheep wearing tiger's skin
With so many companions,
they will strike you in the very
beginning if they have guts
You are right!
This is for you!
Thank you, Brother!
Where are you going Big Brother?
Brother Wah!
Visiting Mabel?
Yeah!
She hasn't go for work yet!
I'll wait for her downstairs
OK!
That boutique has a lot of
new arrival!
Really?
I'll go to the boutique with
you some other day!
OK!
Mabel!
Come here!
I didn't have my dinner!
Would you go eating with me!
That's OK if you don't like to!
Why did you go to work so lately?
I just left from the hospital
Just from the hospital? Why?
Stomach-washing again?
Not stomach-washing!
It's abortion!
Are you kidding?
You can treat it as kidding
if you like to!
No it won't! Why didn't you tell me
that you were pregnant?
Had you gave me a chance
to tell me?
I had waited for three day!
But didn't you call me?
You could call me if I didn't!
Call you! What could I tell you?
Tell you I'm going for abortion
or tell you to marry me?
We'd been together for six years!
What did I get finally?
I felt like not knowing you
and didn't even get any money
I'm so poor that I had to borrow
my mother's money for abortion!
Speak up! What did I do for?
Shut up!
Stop saying!
Since the day we'd met,
you knew already what kind
of person I am
Don't stay with me if you want
to marry and want money
Don't think that because you had
abortion so secretly
that I would feel sorry for
all the rest of my life
I won't!
Your mouth said you won't
but your heart said you will
Because you didn't bother me,
didn't care about me
I spoiled your baby
And I am going to tell everybody
that I had your baby aborted,
so that you'll feel guilty for
the rest of your life
You've got the guts!
Cousin!
Are you alright?
What's the matter, cousin?
Are you lovelorned?
What did you say?
I tell you! Never talk
about lovelorn again
Or else, I'll throw you out!
Did you see the doctor?
I just returned from the hospital
What have the doctor said?
I will get the report tomorrow!
Haven't you have your meal?
Go eating with me!
I have make the meal!
Fly had phoned you again
this morning
What had the dirty guy said?
Nothing special!
Just some casual talk!
Didn't he ask anything about me?
What kind of thing?
The thing happened last night!
Fly had asked only once!
What? What did he ask?
I'm afraid to tell you!
Just tell me what you heard!
Do you insist me to tell you?
He asked me if
you were lovelorned
You have been here for all day!
What didn't you go out?
No place to go!
I have no friend in Kowloon
Eat quickly!
We'll go out together tonight
Cousin, are you studying or working?
I'm working already!
What kind of job?
I'm working in a friend's restaurant
Boy friend?
Well! Not quite!
Everybody call him Uncle Tang
Let us go to the cinema a while later!
We'll go if you are free!
You have no need to stay with me
Calling rescue?
Ah-site, how much have you lose?
Five hundreds!
I won't play for so little money!
One thousand for one game,
agree for not?
One thousand? What's your opinion,
King of snooker?
What? To see my quality
just by one thousand dollar?
I play with single-hand
in this game,
for two thousands
Single hand!
Let's sign contract at once!
Ah-site!
Single-head!
Another ball into pocket!
What's your opinion?
Right, King of snooker is really great!
Ah-site, how many scores have I lost?
No need to calculate!
He has thirty scores more than you
Still has five scores more than you
even if you win all the ball rested
How do you look?
That means we need
a targeting stick!
Ah-site, bring me my private cue
Start, start!
Stunt Follow
Get away!
Get out of my way!
Now, set the targeting stick!
Not stable! Make it more stable!
Beware! You will lost 7 scores!
Save that balls! Save it!
Are you taking me as a dead!
Fuck off!
Big Brother!
What's the matter, Big Brother?
Get away!
Go away, bastard!
Don't go!
Bastard, don't block the way!
Damn you!
Damn it! Damn it!
Fuck off
Big Brother!
Could we leave now?
It's OK!
Be quiet, would you?
Are you alright?
I'm alright!
Why don't you go to sleep?
It's so late
Cousin, my report said that
my health is alright
I want to celebrate with you at first,
but, Auntie said the weather is fine
and the restaurant is busy these days
Uncle Tang want me to go back earlier
I have called you twice,
but you have no response
You must be very tired, I think
Summer is coming
and many people will spend
their holiday in Lantau Island
Do you have holiday working
in such career?
I've made a meal for you
in the kitchen
Besides, I've bought several glasses
I know, they will be all broken
sooner or later
So I've hid one of them
One day when you need this glass,
give me a phone, and...
I'll tell you where it was hidden
Goodbye, Ah-ngor!
Everybody!
Be quiet! Be quiet!
All my relatives and all my guests,
today is the wedding of
my brother, Ah-site
We've prepared some simple
food to serve you
Would we all raise our glasses
I drink first
Cheer!
I've already said that two hundred
dollars were too much
How would I know he would
hold the ceremony on the roof!
Please eat!
Use your meal, please!
Don't behave this way! Eat!
Look at this way!
Take one more photograph!
OK! OK!
Thank you!
Go bring your mother-in-law and
father-in-law to take a photograph!
Hurry up!
Father, would you take a photograph!
No!
Take it, father!
Don't be like that,
go take a photograph!
No! What for?
It's really a shame!
Eat quickly if you want to!
We must leave soon
or else I'll faint
Don't be like that, father!
Don't hold any celebration
if you don't have money
Celebrating on the roof
is extremely unbelievable
I just don't know how to teach you
You have never done
a good work in the past
It's your brother's wedding!
Why did you made it so shabby?
Don't you think that I didn't
want to make it luxurious?
But I have no money!
What can I do?
Damn it! So noisy!
Gay fellow!
What did you say?
What did I say?
I said you are gay!
I did serve you shark's fin
or abalone, didn't you?
It has no air-conditioning!
Why are you so talkative?
You only deserved vegetal abalone
If your son-in-law didn't
say you love eating abalone,
I won't let you have it!
If I know you are so troublesome,
I'll give you shit, not abalone!
Are you looking for death?
Don't you dare throwing things to me?
Don't block my way!
Let me kill him
Don't you want to fight?
Don't do that, Big Brother!
Want to fight, don't you?
Hey, now what do you want?
Get away!
I tell you, don't make any noise!
What can't I speak?
Sit down!
Get lost!
Good boy!
Sit, sit down!
Hey! Is it right?
He's really bastard
Do you really want to fight
before Big Brother?
Don't you?
Speak up! Speak once more!
Anyway, he is Ah-site's father-in-law
If you make trouble,
your young brother will be embarrassed
Do you agree?
OK! It's my fault!
I'm wrong!
My young brother,
I make you suffered today
I'll pay for it when I have
money some days
I knew that It's our turn
But it happens so soon
The cops arrested us last night.
They're just small fry, It's not a big deal
Big-mouth kay controls the money
They said that
The cops are making a deal with him.
They wont him to be turncoat witness
This case is quite serious!
So that Godfather sent me
to inform you that,
don't make any trouble if
it is not necessarily these days
Hey, the police has a great
action outside!
All of you bastards
who have drugs and weapons,
go hide them away quickly!
Ah-wah, someone visiting
you outside!
Thank you!
What are you coming for?
I visit you with special reason
Your brother, Fly,
owe us a sum of money
He hasn't pay the debt for several period
and didn't reply our call
My big brother sent me
to inform you that...
If he don't show up tomorrow,
we won't give him any chance
Tell Tony that I know how
to teach my own man,
and, about the debt,
I will ask Fly
If It's true,
I will bring him to see
Tony tomorrow
Do you want to see me?
You need money don't you?
I always need money
I'm used to it. I have big prospects
The fortune teller told me
I'll be freat at the age of 30
Every thing is fine then
No need to stay here
Did he told you that you can't live to 30
No!
I heard that you borrowed money from Tony
Who is Tony?
I don't know him.
What did you say?
English
You knew that I don't know English
I ask you. Did you borrow money from Tony?
No!
No? Why are they looking for you?
They are eating around the corner
Do you want me to tell them you're here?
Yes!
Who are you winking to?
How much did you borrow?
Just a small sum. Take it easy
Small sum is also money
How much?
Hundreds bucks. It's not a big deal,
leave him alone
But they come to me
Tell me
4 meals and a pair of gold bracelets
Here are eight thousands!
What? Eight thousands?
Are you using one dollar as two?
It's so if he said it is!
The principal is eight thousands!
What about the rest?
He haven't paid for
four installments
Omitting the odd, he still owe us
thirteen thousand and five
We are giving you benefit
because we know you
Why don't you go robbing?
Who do you think you are?
Speak to me?
So fond of talking
Ah-kwong, talk to him for
several hours at there!
Yes!
Fuck off, you son of bitch!
Shut up! Get out!
Get out!
Your brother is lucky in
working under you
If he is working for other,
he have already died!
Don't talk anymore
I don't want to talk about that
I return you the principal first
But he really didn't have money
to paid the interest
So we have to delay for
two installments more
Two installments delay?
Why not return to me after my death?
You must trust me even
if you don't trust him!
I'll responsible for this debt
But I have no money now
I'll give you after two days
How can you be a Big Brother
if you don't have any money at hand
I think you better go farming!
I thought that you had money
so I dared to talk with you
You are such a poor Big Brother...
Did you really want it?
What's the matter?
What? You are crazy!
I have the gut to take it
if you have it now
OK! I dial a phone first
Why are you standing here still?
Your boss told you to talk with me,
why didn't you speak?
What's your father name?
What's your mother called?
Stop joking, Fly!
Why didn't you speak?
You don't have parents?
Aren't you the boss?
Don't come near to me
I have some problem now,
can you lend me some money?
Could you?
Yes, I could!
Really?
Really! No problem!
Fly!
Now I borrow these money
from your boss
It's up to you, take it or not!
But, there's no debt between us
from now on
I tell you, if I become rich
in the future
I will paid back to you
Today, you are wrong
in helping outsider
to beat your own people
Is it right?
What are you waiting for?
Take the money to Tony!
Cancel each other!
This is given you as bonus!
You are really something!
Playing trick in my place
You are also great!
You've make fun of me!
Wait a moment
Get away!
Tony, I'm employing you
to guard this place,
instead of inviting robber to rob me
What do you mean by that?
Boss, he is just losing temper!
The situation is bad now,
but you two still fighting each other
Are you treating me as a dead?
It's him who done wrong first
Borrowed my money
causing trouble in my place,
and robbing my boss
He was wrong in the
whole situation, Godfather!
You know he is crazy already,
so don't bother him
And you are doing too much,
taking advantage from him
You must know that he was
guarding that place!
Godfather, I'm giving back!
He want the money back,
so I paid the debt
We've made an equal exchange!
Equal?
What are you doing?
I'm the one who make decision till I die
So troublesome!
Now I tell you two,
you paid the installments every month
And the event is settled in this way
Make a vow!
What are you two doing?
I told you two to make agreement!
Have a hand-shake? Shake
Ah-kay, the traitor,
is a witness for the police
We cannot let this guy survived
Kill him before he go to court
What's your opinion?
The task is difficult!
Which one should we send?
I don't want outsider to take this case
Let's make it this way
You two, find some smart boys
to draw dead lots two days later
He's the one, brave, and haughty
Send your younger brother
if he wish to do it
I'll let him go!
I'll let him not paying my debt
His family can have subsidize
if he fail
Do you have the guts?
What? What did you say?
Frightening me?
Shut up!
Don't making fun of the followers
You and me are the bravest
It's either you or me to take this case
I'll do it if you don't,
say it and I'll take it!
You'll do if you don't speak up
Say you don't and admit that
you are a coward. And I'll take the case
Wake up!
Now you two are pushing me together?
OK! I kill you two first
and then I'll kill him
Not again! Stop quarrelling!
I have my plan in handling this case
All of you go out first
I leave now, Godfather!
Ah-wah, come back!
I know that you and your brother
are good friends
But he is too crazy. Teach him...
or he will like a time-bomb beside you
and some day he will
cause you deadly trouble
I know, I have think of it
I want to find him a job
It's good to do it!
Fishballs...
That's all for today
Brother fly, brother wah is here
Hey, you deal with him
Fishballs...
Fly Big brother
Give me one
What?
Do you mean I can't do small business?
Do you know who I am?
You'll develop into big business
Yeah, I sell fishballs here today
Someday I'll sell bounbs in Middle East
Bull shit Police is coming
Wait a minute...
Police is coming
What the hell!
Does this cart belong to you. Fishball man
What's your name? Fishball man
What?
If you don't sell fishballs
You stand here with scissors?
How come so you're Fishball man
I'm just cutting my vibrissae
So It's not your cart. Take it away
Take it
Hey! What are you doing?
The cart and the fishballs
are bought by money
Money doesn't matter. But pride matters
I'm not famous. But people know me
I don't want to sell fishballs
I want to hang around
Get lost, get away
I want you to have a job
I don't like selling fishballs
What do you like to sell?
You can't do anything
Just hang around
You are not anything
Yeah, I'm not anything
I can only sell fishballs
You ask me to do that
If I can't stand anymore
I'll put poison on the fishballs
It's good for you. Do you understand?
Hi, what a coincident!
Right! Really a coincident!
How are you?
Fine!... I have married!
Good! Are your husband
treating you good?
Quite good!
So heavy is the rain!
Who knows how long will I have to wait!
I'm waiting for my husband!
Have a cigarette?
I didn't smoke anymore!
It's not yours
I leave now!
Goodbye!
Is Ah-ngor here?
She is not here. Who are you?
It's alright. Thanks
Lady!
What's the matter?
Is Ah-ngor here?
I'm not sure! She had went to Kowloon
and still haven't returned
To Kowloon?
Yes!
Thank you
You're welcome
When did you arrive?
I just arrived
You look a bit fatter than before
A little bit
So are you
It's all because of him
He's my doctor
Would you stay up here tonight?
No... I'm going home now
Ah-ngor!
I just wanted to you tell that
I've found that glass
Miss Cheung called you just now
She said that she was going to
the pier of Silver-mine Bay
and told you to wait for her anyway
You may go to sleep
and I`ll check in for you tomorrow
OK!
When do you go to work next morning?
Very early! I'll make breakfast for you
Good!
How long will you live in here?
It depends!
I leave now
I see you off
That's OK! It's near
Would you not go home tonight?
Why do you not visit me until now?
Because, I know myself clearly
I cannot promise you anything
If I'm not missing you,
I won't visit you today
If you don't visit me in these days
I will probably marry that doctor
Fish-ball guy, give me one dollar
of fish-ball with more dressing
Take it, why don't you take it?
You've said you want more dressing!
Take it or I'll get mad
Fish-ball guy? Damn you!
It won't, Mr. Fly!
Why are you so poor?
You don't have to sell fish-ball,
do you?
Poor guy
It must be your Big Brother
who told you to do so
You should leave your Big Brother
Look at my followers,
all dressed up!
Taking wireless telephone,
do you need that?
You bastard! Your Big Brother
sent you
selling fish-ball in the street
Working for me is better!
Escape
Escape for what?
You are a gangster!
We have so crowd of gangsters here!
It's no need to afraid!
Beat him!
Don't be afraid!
You'll be alright even if you're in jail
Fight back at one
if someone beat you
Don't make us lose faces
You bastard, you...
Take it easy! It's OK!
You are not selling drugs,
just fish-ball
Something good to be seen
Beat him!
Hey, don't go you bastard
Don't go!
Go to hell, bastard!
Take him here
Finished drinking
Right! How many chicken wings
are there in two boxes
About two or three hundreds!
Two or three hundreds?
Hey, go back and tell your boss...
not to send you to take thing
so heavy alone
Or else, I'll give him one fist
for one wing in return
You are crazy
I am crazy?
Do you want me to help you?
It's OK! Anyway, I will quit!
Quit! Why?
I want to find a job in Kowloon
Good! It's doing me favour!
You can live in my house!
Don't say the second time
You can't deny it if
you say it twice
I'm not kidding!
I go out and
will never come back
Hey, what do you want to eat?
Tell him that I'll go to
find him on time
If Fly has anything wrong,
he'll pay for it
It's finished!
What's the matter?
Nothing special! Fly has some problem
and I'm going out now
Would it be dangerous?
No, it'll be alright,
I'll be back tonight
Uncle Kwan, so many people here?
Ah-wah, It's Fly doing wrong
in this case
But, I don't want to make it big
since we all know each other
Say something good to Tony
and the case will be settled
Tony, no matter what did Fly do,
I'll punish him according to my rules
So please give me back my brother
Brother? What kind of brother?
Is this a brother?
You like to protect your brother
now you are protecting him!
Making fun of me?
You should protect him if he is good
Now you are just protecting a lump of shit
How can you be a Big Brother?
Tony, stop when you
have some advantage
Don't go too far
Uncle Kwan, save it for yourself!
I'm teaching him to grow up
His gangster can treat me
like this
Where can we stand
in the future then?
I'll release him surely!
But I must be satisfied
My requirement is low
Just say one sentence I like
I'll release him
Do you like to hear these words
Do you want your brother?
Ah-wah!
Big Brother
Are you alright?
Can you walk?
Yes, I can
Tell your follower to help him stand
Help him stand
No, I can stand by myself
I can walk by myself
Don't get near to me
Big Brother! Big Brother!
I tell you two,
this case can't be settled even
if you bring the highest King
Fly, this case certainly
won't end up this way
You take this money
And go back to Til-gang Lin
and wait for the case to fade out
I won't go!
I've made a vow
I won't go back to see my mother
if I do not succeed
OK, I go to Lantau Island with you
Why do you drive me away
so insistly?
Why? I don't want you to be
killed tomorrow
when you go out
You know he is just a mad dog
Why don't you listen to me
not to provoke him?
It's him who provoked me,
I didn't provoke him
Don't you think I should just about it!
I have the power to play, haven't I?
Don't you have the power
to play with him?
If you have, you won't be beaten
so heavily and have face swollen up
Yes, I was beaten to
have face swollen
You are blaming me on losing you face,
you can leave me alone
No one force you to speak this
Don't speak it for fun
I leave you alone now
If you are safe when
you go out tomorrow
I'll do anything for you
We all don't know what
will happen tomorrow
Do you agree?
Let's go eating out!
Come along!
Beat him!
Fly, I twist your face
I twist you to death
I can plot against you
this time, can't I?
Don't beat my Big Brother
Leave him alone. Just beat me up
Not enough?
Let me beat your brother up.
That makes you two pairs
I want you to see
how I fool around your brother
Shit
fight back
I, Tony, is very justified
An eye for an eye,
and a tooth for a tooth
Don't move!
It's the most sensitive place of you
I don't know where will you
eject if you move
Great! I'm lucky this time
Will I still be so lucky next time?
You are so excited
Do you want to join our party?
OK! Come join us! Come on!
You cannot move a little
You will eject on this brother
or that if you move
Don't let them look down on you?
If I cannot escape today
You must go back to Til-gang Lin
and never go out again
Tough guy
But whether you are tougher
than this thing
It's very hard... very hard...
Very, hard, isn't it.... very hard isn't it...
Look at you, bitch!
Another one collapsed
Damn you! You are pissing!
You should wear him a napkin
before taking him out
What kind of Big Brother are you?
Right! Let your head down
so that you can see your face by the urine
And see why you are such a failure
Then, go back to your motherland
and farm with your Big Brother
Urban road is not suitable for you?
Do you understand?
It's alright, alright!
Where... are you going?
I'm letting you lose face
Just treat that you've never know me
From now on I have no business
to do with you
Just leave me alone
Cousin
Open the door! Open up!
Open the door!
Hurry up! Open the door!
What's the matter?
My cousin felt to the ground
and hurt himself
He's alright. Let him take a rest first
Where have you been last night?
I was staying with cousin
Lock the door when you leave!
Give me a phone if anything happens
She's coming
Hey, receive guests
I'm sorry
You talk to each other first
Shooting in a police station
won't cause death penalty
Go to jail for several years
and become a man when you come out!
Now people call you boy,
and they'll call you "sir" tomorrow
It's a chance to be famous!
Understanding?
Godfather. I'm afraid!
What? Afraid! You've drew the lots
and now you said you afraid
Every colleague will kill you
even if I let you go
Don't say so much! Keep going!
Godfather, I'm really afraid
Chicken-hearted
Godfather, I've got something to talk to you
$23.5 with tin. Here is $30.
No change. Thanks
Ah-site
Brother
You're a different person after you
become a father
I have no choice.
I have a young wife and baby
I'll do anything for living
Take the money
What are you doing?
I promised you
I'm sorry for last time
Please find a luxurious restaurant this time
And the lest of the money is for the
celebration of your son's first month
Remember,
don't let your wife's family look down on you
Do you understand?
How can you get the money?
It's none of your business
I'll not around.
Call brother wah if you get in trouble
We didn't do any big thing
I feel ashamed
Don't say that, brother
Listen to me
You may despise me in the past
Yes, I deserve that
But 2 days later,
when you read paper and watch TV
You'll realize that I'm not an idiot
I can be your big brother
Remember to tell everyone you
Remember
Do these clothes suit you?
You didn't sleep the whole night!
Take a rest!
I can't sleep!
Don't worry! Just slight injury!
It's alright!
You're lucky this time,
but what about the next time?
I've never thought about next time
in doing anything
Just one thing
I want to be with you next time
when I go touring
I've said this twice
I won't take it back
What are your opinion?
Come on! Come to me!
Brother Wah! My Big Brother
have given me a lot of money last night
and told me to hold banquet again
And he said I would know
he was not coward when I read
newspaper two days later,
Brother Wah, would you
come out at once
Nobody will care about him
if you don't
I'm coming now
Going out again?
Nothing! Some kind of friend
called me out to talk a while
Right! I'll go to buy some medicine
in Silver Mine Bay
Do you want me to buy anything for you?
I'll be back soon
Double eight
Miss Cheung called you
to tell you that medicine
was not important
But took care of yourself
and came back earlier
I win again
Give me money
Count it later
Why not tell me
you're changed your address, Tony?
Get up...
Do you know the game rules here?
You don't welcome me?
Give me money
I don't want to be screwed up
You're been screwed up
Even you feel sorry,
your son will have no ass
What are you talking?
What? What?
Let him be the boss 2 days
He never be the boss.
He risks his life for that
Just 2 days
Come on
seven tile of circles
Do you know the rules? Get another tile
Eight
I'm sorry
Come on
Don't fool me
Leave him alone
Let him be a two days hero
You're very patient. Goddam you!
You think I don't dare to beat you?
Come and beat me
If you beat me
I'll lie down
And you'll get into
big-mouth kay's trouble
Come on
Goddam you!
Shit
I'll shoot him if you move
Shoot him if you dare
Are you threatening me?
Pull the trigger and shoot me
Don't shoot
No...
Are you scared, Asshole?
Let me blow off your head
No..., don't shoot him
I wanted to shoot him
But you're not worth to be shot
These are the money that I owe you.
Take it
You must take it.
Or you'll lose your chance
Take it. Or I'll shoot you
Say thank you
Thank you
You're nothing even you wear suits
with call phone
Be the man of such brother
And you'll go to hell
We just want to make money
You mean I shouldn't take the money
even he pay me back?
Take it and go dancing
You treat your brother like that
I'm in grocery, mom. Do you come up?
What is going on?
Nothing. I know you don't like feeling hot
So I buy you a air conditioner
We're installed it down there.
This one just leave in to you
I don't come up. Your father is here
He's your husband, not my father
When will you calm down
and stop escaping?
Why did you come out to see me?
Why don't you leave me alone?
Who will care for you if I don't?
Don't think that you'll be
famous after this task
Right, everybody will say
you are brave this time when you do that
But no one will remember you next week
But what become of you then?
No one will know you later
I've done many things
for godfather also
I had received money for death
when I was fourteen
I was greater than a lot of people, right?
But look at me!
I'm just an ordinary man now
Anyway, you were famous
for sometime!
But what about me?
No one notice me and
you are happy about that
People look down upon
everything of me
They even said that
I was a dog beneath you ass
Do you know that?
I would rather be three-minute hero
I don't want to be a fly for all my life
Let me finish a great task on my own,
would you?
Just for this time
OK! Did you decide to go?
I'll go with you if you want to
I'll take revenge for you
if you are shoot down
Don't treat me so good,
would you?
I can't pay you back
I don't want to talk
so much with you
Just say it, and I'll go with you
We'll go to Lantau Island
if you say no
I'll settle anything following
OK! OK! OK!
I go back with you
Ah-choi, Ah-choi
Don't look down upon other
He used to be great and famous
but now he was finished
Don't be so stingily!
Give something to Ah-cho