BETTY BLUE
I had known Betty for a week.
We made love every night.
The forecast was for storms.
Saved!
Now for a nice little shower!
First time we've met in daylight.
You're much too early!
So what? How do I look?
What do you think?
Do I please you?
Eating all that chilli by yourself?
In this heat? You're mad.
I'll eat chilli no matter how hot it is, Betty.
Me too, I'm starving!
Glad to see me?
They're all bastards!
Who?
Forget it, Kiss me!
All bastards!
No wonder a girl ends up splitting!
Wait, explain, I don't get you.
Why don't you ever listen to me?
I do listen! I'm listening!
I expect more from a guy than sex!
To think I spent a year in that dump
wiping tables and dodging drunks
just to get felt up one morning by the boss!
I've got to start all over again now!
I split. Anyway, I was fired.
Can't even buy a train ticket.
She was a flower with psychic antennae and a tinsel heart.
Not many girls could dress as casually as she did.
I can't get up! We drank too much.
I need to take a piss.
Don't press on my bladder.
I'm happy being with you.
I'd like to stay with you if I can.
Well, I think you can.
I've got no wife, no kids.
We've got a nice pad.
I have an OK job. I do repairs.
I'm confident...
We're still young.
I didn't want explanations.
I only wanted to kiss her
and caress her ass
as long as her bladder held out.
Who is that guy? Wake up!
Who is he?
Make yourself at home!
Wait, I'll be right back.
How are you? Excuse me,
you're sitting on my trousers.
I don't wear underwear either.
It's uncomfortable.
I'll get you some coffee.
I have to make it first.
I'll do it, You get dressed.
Is it because of that girl
that you're still in
the sack at 10 a.m.?
10 o'clock already?
You're fantastic. It's 11!
Always moisten the grounds first.
All I have to do is to run an ad
to get loads of guys for your job,
but I want to be fair.
I've had you a long time
and you're OK.
But I don't think you can
keep that girl here
and do your job right
Know what I mean?
See how it swells up?
George told you about her?
You let everyone see!
He could've told you
how much she does here.
The housework, shopping,
everything! That counts a lot!
Saves me lots of time!
What's more,
she does it for free.
So you want me
to just forget it,
I did oversleep today,
but I'll make up for it!
Especially after coffee!
Tell me when.
Slap some paint
on all these shacks!
They look like hell!
They sure would look better.
There may be a way...
Can you and your girl do it?
That'd take
a whole crew of painters!
We'd still be at it
in the year 2000!
When you're in love, what's time?
And don't you two form a crew?
OK, but how will you pay her?
You're crazy! You just asked me
to forget I saw her!
How can I make ends meet
if I pay her?
Just do it at your own pace!
Get to work! I'll order
the paint from old George.
Don't worry, just plug away!
And don't forget
to moisten the grounds!
Who was that fat slob?
The owner.
What did he want?
Nothing, he just wants us
to do a little paint job.
Terrific! I love to paint!
500 bungalows. 500 fronts.
1500 sides.
Thousands of shutters!
Just a little paint job!
Are you two going to repaint
all these shacks?
Should repaint the people too!
Now shut your big mouth,
George!
Hell, are you mad at me?
How did you guess?
Don't talk about it in front of Betty! Go play your sax!
I just told those nice folks
we'd paint their house.
What shall I paint?
The shutters.
And I'll do the rest.
- What's bugging you?
- Nothing.
The winner helps the other.
Ready!
I hope she doesn't fall!
She won't. She's young!
I win!
I'll help you now!
OK, go ahead!
What a drag!
Shit, you goofed!
What's wrong?
My fault. I forgot to tell you
not to go past the corner!
The brush is too big.
Now it looks as if
that side is started!
But who cares?
"Who cares?"
You're not going to paint
just one side, are you?
You want to do
the whole shack for them!
You really are
a champion house painter!
What do you expect?
Go on, I'll hold the bucket.
Ready?
Smile! Hold the roller higher!
It's terrific!
- I look awful!
- What are you mad about?
We're fed up with painting.
Just one more!
Stop, we've already got 50, Betty.
Let's have a beer.
That fat slob again!
You sure are working hard!
What do you expect?
You're fantastic! We'll see
if you can keep up the pace!
What did he just say?
He didn't say anything!
What do you mean, "the pace"?
Don't worry, my dear young lady,
I'm not asking you to do it
non-stop, I'm not a monster!
Just keep fanning yourself.
Suits you nicely!
To do what non-stop?
All the bungalows.
He's kidding!
Do I act like it?
I'll think it over!
Betty! Stop!
You're insane!
I don't mind painting your crate!
Makes it look more sporty!
But I won't paint your shacks!
She's insane!
One wipe and it'll be like now!
Got to forgive her,
she's having her period!
I'm sure she's sorry!
I'll even paint
the light poles for you!
No, the light company
does that, you jerk!
Hi! It's me!
What did you tell that asshole?
Look, he wouldn't let you stay
unless you worked!
It's murder
to paint all those shacks!
In a way, yes.
"In a way"!
Shit, they're all bastards!
We should cut
all their throats!
- How would that help?
- Have you no pride?
I'll paint the whole town pink
just to stay with you, kitten!
You're nuts! Look what shit
we're in with that asshole!
You let him screw you
and for what? Tell me!
We're all in the same boat!
Stop talking bullshit!
How can I love you
if I can't admire you?
We're only learning
how to die here!
See the wind outside,
blowing bits of newspapers by?
Papers from the North one day,
from the South the next,
all full of the same bullshit
and we're in between!
Now look, we've got
a nice pad to screw in,
so it's you who's nuts!
You nerd! Something's always
wrong with you guys! Shit!
You're a dumb bitch!
Always something wrong
with a guy!
It's dark in here,
it stinks, it's ugly!
I'm fed up!
Can't breathe in here!
I'm going to fix your house up
good so I can breathe!
Look at all this shit!
Not that one, Betty!
Why is it so special?
Sentimental attachment.
What's all that?
Hitler's memoirs.
Give me that box. Please!
Did you write this?
Yeah. Ages ago.
You wrote that many pages?
Yeah, but it's nothing,
just crap!
About what?
Just stuff...
I'd almost forgotten.
No one forgets stuff like that!
Won't you come to bed now?
You can't start
reading that now!
You'll see if I can't!
Betty was the first one
to read it... quiet at last.
At 30, you begin to know
what life's about,
and you enjoy a break.
Want some coffee?
One lump or two?
Two lumps then.
I'm going to work now.
Do you like it?
Oh it's you!
What'll you be painting next?
The Sistine Chapel!
Actually working! Will you do
the insides afterwards?
Yeah, cover up your furniture!
I'll start now.
Come and see my girls afterwards.
What's this? Is it my birthday?
No, baby, just dinner for two.
What is it?
Mussels. I'll pour your wine.
Some spread!
I'm dreaming!
Taste it!
Like it?
I know that smell.
Turkey with chestnuts!
Do you like that?
Love it, Ideal in this season!
What's the occasion?
Wait, let me look at you.
When I think you wrote that!
I've never read
anything like it!
You don't realise.
Now I see why you came
to this hole. To write that.
To think you paint shacks
drives me crazy!
This world wasn't
exactly made for me.
We'll see about that.
Kiss me.
I hadn't come to that hole
to write.
It was later
that I started writing.
So I could feel alive.
Mornings you start at 11
and now afternoons at 4!
It's too hot! But I work
till dark, lots of hours!
By the way, I'm out of paint!
That's the end of that!
Who are you to talk
to him like that?
I'm not talking to you!
Guess who you are talking to?
The greatest writer alive, fat ass!
Doesn't show on his face!
And she hasn't even got panties on!
Take a good look, schmuck!
Shut up, you!
Now get your eyes full!
She's a real hellcat!
Not hurt, are you?
You asshole!
Now get rid of that girl!
I don't ever want
to see her again!
I think I'll go to work now.
Hey, Betty,
I'm going to work.
She's in a real frenzy!
She loves housework!
There goes the casserole!
The ironing board!
The record player!
My Gershwin record!
Frankly,
I wouldn't want
a housekeeper like her!
I don't blame you.
She's almost through.
Your pad will look very Zen now!
OK, are you coming?
You're insane!
What? I can't hear!
I love you! I love you!
Once more!
I love him!
We could've taken the train!
This is adventure!
Who is she?
My best friend. We can stay
with her. She's a widow.
What if she's not home?
We'll visit Montmartre!
You do trust me, don't you?
And the rent?
Could you do odd jobs there
in exchange for rent?
You bet! I'm a plumber!
A plumber? Great!
My toilet's broken!
I'll buy the stuff!
No, I'll swipe it
from a building site!
What are you doing?
Not even a masterpiece
gets read unless it's typed.
Can you type?
You plan to type all that?
Good luck, sweetie!
- How far are you?
- On page 1.
Go away, you confuse me!
Lisa's out again tonight
Still like it as much?
Don't you worry.
I may never get published, Betty.
Are you kidding?
It's a strange world, baby.
Won't you eat now?
I've boiled some eggs for you!
I don't have time!
Why stare at me so?
I think you're beautiful.
Then come and kiss me.
What are you doing?
Repairing the tap. It leaks.
Aren't you cold?
I'm not very warm.
How's Betty doing?
She's progressing.
And you?
Your eyes are shining.
Oh, Zorg. I just got laid!
Really laid!
Don't laugh!
Who is he?
You'll meet him!
Time for bed.
For me too.
Smell anything burning?
No, why?
Rusty, come on!
Zorg, come here!
Guess what I'm typing?
"TH E EN D"
You've got me all wrong.
You're a writer, not a plumber
What did I type? A novel!
Don't be so dumb!
Play the races if you like,
I don't care, but
stop being a plumber, OK?
See this list? All the publishers
in this dumb town!
All of them!
I think I'll go buy a racing mag.
What'll it be?
- Tequila
- We don't have that.
Pernod then.
Is this a turbo?
No, it's a UFO.
- Is it yours?
- No.
Costs a lot!
It's got ABS...
Great brakes!
And it can do 150 mph!
My dad has one!
Your dad has an old crate,
and it's green!
There's Zorg!
- And the racing mag?
- Sold out.
Lovejoy, Baby Shark
and Eat-Your-Soup in the lead!
Lovejoy out!
You're Zorg?
Eddy Sayolle.
Is he your wonder boy?
Is that your UFO outside?
You bet! Beautiful, isn't she?
Some kids are taking her apart.
Better just give 'em the keys!
You're kidding!
How about a ride
on the motorway! 150!
No, we have to mail
the manuscripts!
The ass she's got!
Be careful!
I've got a better idea.
Tequila rapido!
You take a towel and a glass,
and tequila and Schweppes.
Say a prayer!
They'll print it, Betty!
Off it goes!
So you write books!
Do you make any bread
doing that?
Sometimes!
You've got it made!
A soft job behind a desk.
You write, then go get the cash!
And what is your... branch?
Historical novels!
Is that joint yours?
Yes, Pizza Stromboli!
Eddy's Pizza Parlour!
I forget what kind
of books you write!
Science fiction!
Betty, come and see!
What's going on?
We're sinking into debauchery!
Fantastic!
Don't mess up my stuff!
He's moving in, OK?
Don't touch!
Do they make 'em for men too?
Try one on!
It's the only thing
I feel good in.
100% silk!
There's a red one too!
Feels sexy!
Open the bottles!
No mail on Sunday.
Have some coffee
and a croissant.
I've got a job for you two.
Like what?
"Like what"! A job!
Where's my Milanese?
Don't forget those aperitifs
on the terrace!
Did you get N 3?
This... is yours!
Is it always like this?
- And 9?
- Where is 9?
Between 8 and 10 usually.
Good night!
Those drinks!
Doing OK?
- Did you get 9?
- Where is 9?
The fat lady!
May we order? Really!
Where are the toilets?
Come on, smile!
I've had it!
That bitch at N 5!
I'll hit her pretty soon!
I'll handle her!
Is there some problem?
Is that girl an idiot or what?
I said pizza with anchovies,
not ham!
Try some pimento sauce on it,
No, now give me what I ordered!
I'll see what I can do.
Mine is great! No problem!
What do you need?
Do you know nouvelle cuisine?
That's just crap!
Wait till you see my repel cuisine!
Watch!
You pick out the worst
garbage you can find,
stinky junk,
bits of sweaty sausage,
a little tomato, nice,
fresh spaghetti,
an old cheese rind,
lettuce that's good and rotten,
one olive,
and there you are!
Now add a little sunshine!
I fofgot the best part!
- Oh shit!
- You said it!
How's your pizza?
Hot!
It's you that's hot!
You're turning me on!
Look out for your blouse!
Doesn't matter.
- What's wrong?
- I'm tired.
I 'm OK, just tired.
Good-bye and thank you!
A madhouse.
What kind of books do you write?
Detective novels.
Any answer yet?
Not yet.
Are you insane?
Shut up!
You're insane! Call the manager!
What's wrong?
The service was rotten
all evening!
And now this little fool
won't get my coat!
I'll pay their bill!
Keep out of this!
Go back to your dishes!
Beat it!
You're crazy!
Insane!
Shut up!
Throw them out, Eddy!
What's the matter?
Nothing, she'll be OK.
Shit, tell me what happened!
Leave me alone with her!
Put water on her face.
I'll get some.
Beat it, Eddy! Shit!
What was it? Is she sick?
Look, don't you ever get mad?
Mad, yes, but that scared me!
Now don't say it was nothing!
She almost killed that woman!
Bullshit!
With your royalties...
Shit, stop bugging me
about "my books"!
I've only written one
in all my life!
And I doubt I could write
another one! "Royalties"!
I thought...
You thought what?
She told you that?
She found a manuscript
and thinks I'm a genius.
Keeps waiting
for publishers to reply.
That drives her nuts.
She may be right
About what?
That you're a genius.
You bet! Read this, toots!
"United Books.
"Sorry no. Amusing, but
your style is unbearable.
"You deliberately
wrote a non-book..."
Who is this queer?
Hide that quick!
How are you today?
What's wrong with him?
Something he can't swallow.
I see. Well, I feel great!
Any mail yet?
I didn't look.
Betty was a wild horse
that had cut her hamstrings
jumping over a wall
and was trying to get up.
What she thought was a meadow
was a gloomy pen.
She couldn't bear immobility.
She was not made for that.
"I've read everything, but nothing
"like what you had
the poor taste to send us.
"Your writing shows
all the signs of AIDS.
"I return this nauseating flower
you call a novel.
"Rely on me for publicity.
"leave that thing
where it belongs
"in the quagmire of your brain.
"Sincerely yours, Thomas Colas."
That's just part of the game.
We're bound to rum into morons.
It won't kill us.
It's not important, my love.
OK, it's not important.
I'm going to a doctor.
Anything wrong?
No, just to see if my IUD is OK.
Coming with me?
I'll put some makeup on first.
I love to look at old magazines,
it's reassuring.
I look silly, give me my jacket!
But I look good in it!
Is this it? There's no plaque!
Stop it, he's not deaf!
Yes? What can I do for you?
My wife has an appointment.
Did you write this?
- That?
You recognise this, don't you?
Who signed this?
Shitty asshole publisher!
Yes, I'm mad as hell!
I'll clean it all up.
You shithead!
Tell him what you think!
I don't give a damn
about his letter!
In your writing
as well as your speech,
you show no notion
of good taste!
And you think you do!
Get out! This is my home!
Stop making a scene!
You're mad!
She's insane!
Go on, dance!
Come here, I'm all alone!
I'm coming, baby!
It's dy ... it's na... It's mite...
it's dynamite!
The sauce!
I would've loved to be a rocker!
Shit, he's a real rocker!
Come and help me!
I'm not making it
with cheap wine but...
with champagne!
Pizza Stromboli!
What's wrong, Eddy?
My mother's dead.
Shit, my mother's dead!
I feel awful!
Is this your only black tie?
I have to be there.
For the funeral.
You should get
a little rest now, darling.
I have to dress.
Give me my jacket.
No, sleep, and
I'll call you a cab later.
560 miles.
If I leave now, I'll make it,
You're nuts, you'll never
make it in one piece!
We won't let you go alone!
You don't realise!
My mother's dead!
Help him.
It's not funny.
Cut it out, it's not funny!
What's all that noise?
That's not a Christian way to be!
It's OK. Forget it,
Your poor mother's upstairs!
It's Christian enough.
They're my friends.
I didn't know you could play.
I can't. Just 2 or 3 things.
You're a funny girl.
I waited ages
for a meaning in life.
You're the best thing
that ever happened to me.
You're only saying that
because you're tired.
If I'd written that book,
I'd have a meaning in life.
It's only bringing us trouble.
It's not because you wrote it.
You are a writer!
Then why can't I write
anymore now?
Because you're a prize dumbbell.
Thank you.
You look tired.
I'm OK.
Did you see
all those stars?
A life isn't much.
Just 4 photos.
Like it here?
It's different!
I want to make you and Betty
an offer.
Stay here and rum the piano store.
See? I'm psychic!
Shall I go ask Betty?
Tell me, do you like the idea?
Yes I do.
Fantastic!
Just one thing...
Take her flowers now and then.
- Who?
- My mother.
He sure gave us a nice present!
No, I just can't do it!
Sleep in a dead woman's bed!
I know it's no fun,
but just don't think about it!
No, I refuse!
Shit, I don't believe it,
Do you know how late it is?
We'll just use this foldaway.
Let me, it's a man's job!
Stupid thing!
You said it was a man's job!
What is this?
Can't you do it, man?
Shitty thing!
Calm down. Use the pedal!
The pedal is stuck, Betty!
I'll go get the tools then!
Hell, not at this time of night!
I didn't do it on purpose!
Let's stop, it'll only get worse.
It's safer.
"Sleep Away the Foldaway Way!"
What are you up to?
It gives off bad vibes.
You don't feel 'em of course!
The bad vibes are gone now!
I liked that place.
Sunny weather, sunny people.
As if they'd all
had their motors tuned.
Guys freak out
over a full tank of gas.
Big cars are the last flash
of our civilization.
I thought we were broke.
We are now.
I lay this gift at your feet!
You're crazy!
I'll tan your hide, damnmit!
I'm really fed up!
He locked himself
in the bathroom.
And that window is so high!
Why do we ever have children?
What's wrong?
I'm dizzy, I can't do it!
Let me do it!
Be careful!
Bob! Hurry, come on!
Come on, yourself!
Makes me dizzy!
Archie! Why do you do this?
Your dad's going to wallop you!
He's OK, Bob.
I'll leave you here till you dry!
That's for Pearl Harbor!
Yesterday,
he shut himself in the fridge.
Fancied himself an arctic explorer!
You little moron!
Let me offer you a drink.
I insist!
You did me a favour!
Darling, what did he do to you?
Ever hear about
the 3 supermarket witches?
A great story! I'll tell you.
Sit down!
Real hungry.
They're so hard they almost hurt.
Touch and you'll see.
Go on, touch.
Feel that?
Awfully hard.
They hurt.
You've got goldfish!
Real goldfish!
How about some Pineau?
Got anything to munch with it?
Help yourself in the shop!
Bananas, coconuts, apricots.
No, that's all sweet.
I want almonds or peanuts.
Eat my pussy! Eat it!
Hurry!
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
I don't turn you on!
It's not that.
Sometimes I resist my desires
in order to feel I'm free.
I'm fed up!
Forget it, Let's go have a drink.
Bob hasn't touched me
for a month!
Not since I left the clinic.
Is it normal
to have to wait so long?
It'll all work out.
I'm sure it will!
Sometime when we're in bed,
he'll...
slip it in from behind
without caring if
I'm asleep or...
Let's have those drinks.
The goldfish love that tune!
I've bored you long enough now.
You're not boring me.
Wait, Betty wants...
I almost forgot...
Betty wants
to knock out two walls.
Eddy? Can you hear me?
It's nothing,
just two thin little walls.
What do you mean "nothing"?
You're both nutty.
Wait, imagine that wall
as a barrier between us
and a sunny meadow.
Isn't it an insult
to let a silly
little barrier bug us?
OK, but go #easy now.
Don't worry, we're not crazy.
All right, bye!
Do I look like Stallone
in Rocky IV, baby?
No, like you writing your book.
I don't see what demolition
has to do with writing.
I'm not surprised.
Want to go shopping with me?
Do you want to?
I'll go alone then!
You're acting like shit today!
You're out of your mind!
Calm down!
Stop!
Shit, Betty, stop!
Enough!
Betty, please!
It's over, okay?
What's going on here?
Nothing, she didn't feel well,
so I slapped her.
I was afraid.
she'd have a fit.
I know that's hard to believe!
Why is that hard to believe?
We'd just been jogging!
Does jogging help?
A lot, yeah.
And how is the little lady now?
I told you
not to point that at me!
I'm aiming at him, not you!
Put it down!
Look at his shoes!
We saw a guy with green hair
one day too.
The world's like that.
Don't go by details.
It's only an accident!
If we goof some day,
it'll be your fault!
Did you search him? No!
You just like to carry a pistol!
Don't get mad! Look at them!
I'd clobber him in a sec!
I've had 40 years' experience!
Then work it out alone,
count me out!
Always blowing your top!
Open cup! Cut it out!
I'll give you 2 seconds!
OK, I'll stop!
Next time, you've had it!
Our recruits get good training,
but it wrecks their nerves!
I'm sorry, it's my fault.
Are you just passing through?
No, we rum the piano store.
Friends of Eddy's?
You should've said so!
We'll drive you back!
Come on, Betty.
Good and ripe.
What else?
Ham.
Round or square?
Did you hear about
the butcher's wife
and the postman?
No shame at all. Two slices?
Four.
Bob, I'm in a jam!
And I'm in a ham.
I have a piano and my
delivery men didn't show up!
It has to be delivered! Your brother-
in-law's got a truck, hasn't he?
It's too big,
it's a logging truck!
I'll manage! I can slue around
with the biggest ones!
So no problem!
Annie, come here!
I'll phone him.
Tell him I'll come back later.
OK, I'll do that.
Hi, Annie.
Have things improved with Bob?
A little, why?
What's on your mind?
Nothing, and that takes
all my strength!
You sure are a funny guy.
I doubt that.
27 tons! Think it'll do?
Hey, this must be worth plenty!
Must be worth a lot of bread!
Spare me your comments!
Know how to work this?
Just press, it's easy!
Shall I press?
Oh, shit! Asshole!
That's the oil release!
Try the other one!
Now watch!
Got a manual?
Yeah, there's a manual.
What're you up to?
What are you up to?
I can't hear!
Come on down!
What are you up to?
You jerk!
Know what that piano's worth?
You wouldn't tell me!
I'm coming!
Did you tie it down?
The lady's waiting!
Let me go.
I have to tell you!
I'm selling a piano!
I'm an hour late!
She'll be hopping mad!
I'm coming!
What's that?
Dust from Atlantis?
It's a pregnancy test.
And what does it say?
It says yes!
But how, with your IUD?
Happens sometimes.
It can't be true!
Sit down. I'll be right back
to look after you!
It's great, eh?
What's wrong?
You look like a ghost?
We're late as hell!
Never saw so many
baby carriages!
We almost made one less!
Not so fast!
The truck's brand new!
I'm not going fast!
Anyway, it's a turbo!
What? Are you kidding?
I'm only going 25 mph!
25? You're going 50!
50? That's not fast!
Got your licence?
I doubt it,
Hi there! Remember me?
Doing 60 with a truck
limited to 45 mph
on a road limited
to 15-ton vehicles
and to 30 mph. Not bad, not bad.
Your papers... full inspection...
the whole bit,
Sorry, I was dreaming!
If you flunk the alcohol test,
you'll wake up fast.
I just found out
I'm to be a father!
What?
A father!
Got a cigarette?
Sure.
Fathers!
Bravest daredevils of all!
You'll see... there's joy...
but sorrow too,
sorrow.
Take a child by the hand.
Lead him into futureland.
Give him a confident stride.
Treat a child
like a king.
Hold him with pride
Close to your side.
What does it feel like?
I don't know.
I want another test to be sure.
Do you like the idea?
I don't know.
But I'd say it's not so bad.
As a present to you.
We made love.
I had a dizzy sensation:
while we screwed,
her IUD was like
a broken door
banging in the wind.
Now you strangle me
and rape me?
Yeah.
Better rape me first.
All right
Look.
See the little wall?
The Little Wall of China?
The one that starts at the lake.
And that big rock, see?
- That big thing?
- Yeah.
Beautiful.
And isn't that
little house nice?
But what are you driving at?
I love this place!
You're right, it's perfect.
Everything in its place
Fantastic.
It's all for you.
All of it!
It starts at the wall
and goes beyond the rock.
And the house
is in the middle.
And that's not all!
Happy birthday, my love!
20 years old!
Have to eat it now!
I dreamed
your book was published.
Why don't you think
of something else?
Give me a cigarette.
What's this medicine?
Nothing. Just so I can sleep.
Hey, what do you mean?
I don't take them often.
- Who's that kid?
- What kid?
Downstairs.
That's Nicolas!
A young genius,
but he hasn't got a piano.
What's this?
Champagne! One bottle apiece.
And ice-cream
with passion fruit in it,
That's for you!
We never know
And they never shrink!
I love you.
S'funny.
Champagne usually wakes me up.
Don't do that to me now!
Not tonight!
Thirsty?
Want something to drink?
You're no fun.
No fun at all.
Let's play Scrabble! You love that!
I'll let you win, OK?
You're no fun
to leave me all alone!
Your bag is ugly.
PREGNANCY DIAGNOSIS:
NEGATIVE.
Aren't you glad to see
Eddy and Lisa? And Rusty?
Even bald I'd love you!
Life is against me.
If I want anything,
it's denied me.
I can't even manage
to have a baby.
Answer me!
What's wrong?
Your hair looks fine!
You should swim a bit,
The water's just right!
You're insane!
What're you doing?
My Betty... Come back.
It's me.
I hear voices.
No, that's the wind.
Some nut always
has a radio on at 3 a.m.,
waiting for World War III.
I hear the voices in my head!
I'm going insane!
It's all over now.
Mine's got hot pants
and yours is going bananas.
Don't ever say that!
I'm sorry.
Don't panic!
- What happened?
- Please sit down.
Where's Betty?
Stay here!
Can't be true!
Don't stay here.
Bob, what happened?
She poked an eye out.
That's not possible!
This look awful, but she'll live.
Yes, speaking.
What? You've read it?
No, I believe you.
I'm just surprised.
It hasn't come yet.
OK, I'll sign every page...
I want 15%.
OK, 10%.
I don't give a shit.
No, I can't travel now.
Yes, I'm doing another one,
but I can't explain. Just stuff
that pops into mind.
Betty, we did it! The book's
going to be published!
What have they done to you?
The dirty bastards!
We're going to make it, my love.
I'm writing another book.
For you.
For you? Betty!
Dedicated to you.
What are you doing here?
What did you do to her?
You're crazy! Get out!
What is all this shit?
I want to see her doctor!
What is this shit?
Tell me!
Sit down!
I need to talk to you.
She's in a state of shock!
Know what that means?
- Serious?
- We can't predict the outcome.
I can't guarantee that
she'll ever recover.
Be brave, my boy!
Chemistry
has made great strides.
Electrotherapy gets results.
Ignore all those dumb lies!
There's no danger!
I'm taking her home!
You're joking!
That girl is totally insane!
Shut up, shut up!
It's your medicine
that drove her mad!
Your shit's wrecking her mind!
You're making her sick!
I said beat it! Get lost!
I'll slug you!
Forget it!
I keep hearing your voice
in the house, Betty.
Worst of all, the silence,
and words that just pop up:
"Can't find the damn sugar!"
"You're kidding."
"That shitty vacuum cleaner!"
"Zorg, are you asleep?"
We're going away together.
Make one last effort.
We were meant for each other.
No one can ever separate us,
no one, ever.
Are you writing?
Just thinking.