Mr. Gong
do you remember this?
What is it?
It was a present from you.
Take a closer look
This was
your graduation present
Amazing
you still have this key ring?
Of course I do!
Do you know
how important this is to me?
C'mon, let's go!
OK!
You were right!
It looks like a mussel
These mussels have hair
This is where you put it in
The holes are all wet
Hey, this woman
got two men on her
I got two women doing it
I've never seen tits
this big before
What are you doing?
I can't take it anymore.
I'm gonna do it with this
Hey, Seok Gu
you are a genius.
I never knew I would ever
enjoy noodles this way
The wrapping keeps
getting in the way
Well, we're here
Mr. Gong
since the dinner was a bit oily
why don't you come over to my place
and have something like kimchee?
It's late.
Good night
Yes
I like getting wet
in the rain
Mr. Gong!
You look sexier
when you smile.
Young Je
can I borrow this first?
No, can I read it first?
Let's read together
They are huge
Give it here
Wait!
If we keep passing it around
we'll lose track whose is whose
So we'll put
our names on it
What if we get caught
because of the names?
- Then just write our nicknames.
- Yeah!
What?
The P.E teacher is here.
You're stallion?
I am crazy train
Are you stallion?
I'm the big unit
Damn it!
You read this kind of stuff
and all of you will
commit sex crimes
Get down!
You make noise according to your
nickname on each hit, understand?
Yes, sir
What were you again?
I am the big unit
Then...
It's squirt-squirt
What the!
Hurry up and get down now!
What's going on here?
I am having
a sexual education class
If they need to be punished
I'll do it!
Look after them Mr. Gong
Your class came
last for the third straight month
It's a first ever
in this school's 75 years history
Three straight months!?
I have a favorite to ask
If we come in first
on the Sports Carnival
I think Mr. Gong will feel better
We can do it, right?
Yes, Miss
I have a question
My grades went up 10 spots
then do you
carry me for 10 rounds?
DongHyun will carry me first
since you fell by 32 spots
Miss...
I heard you did it on purpose
because you wanted to carry me
So hurry up
I'm worried Dong Hyun will
win the bet again
Is it possible to
root in that position?
Didn't you see
the couple at the motel?
Dong Hyun on her back
makes it possible
Anything is possible.
Better watch out
That hurts...
Anything good today?
Check this out
High school kids...
Good evening
this is DJ Bea
It rained hard tonight
On a night like this
the pain of love deepens
Loving an older woman is
much more painful
This is the story of Dong Hyun
from Yong Chun Dong
19 days ago I fell in love
She is 7 years
older than me
I wanted to
keep her for eternity
But the thought of not being able to
own her forever rips my heart in two
Did you really write
a love letter to him?
Yes, and I am going to put it
in her lunch box
I think
you should reconsider
I thought about it enough
It's a pity that I can't
see this tomorrow
I am sorry, I can't go to
your engagement party
Tell your fiance Min Su
that I am really sorry
Love has no limits.
Go for it Dong Hyun
Buy a bunch of roses
then go to her
house and confess your love
Confess your love
Where are you going
at this hour?
Going to buy roses
Roses?
- Does he smoke?
- What?
"ROSES"
Come look at this
My... he's all grown up.
There is something
I must say to her
but I could not meet her
Hey, hold it tight.
You're making it spill all over
Can't you see
it's all foaming up?
Do you know what happens when
you mix soda and this powder?
You can get woman high.
I used it on my girl
last night and
she got so high
we rooted twice
What's a squeeze?
The Candy
I told you about before
This trainee's
nickname is Candy too
so she's as good
as my squeeze anyway
You are going to
give this to her?
Give this to her first
then wait for my chance
Ms Kim!
You must be thirsty.
Why don't you have some of this
I just opened it
Thanks
Don't drink it
There is a bug in it.
Really?
- What the...
- You prick
Mr. Gong
I made this lunch
Really? Thanks
I'll enjoy it
There is a caf called "Lovers"
only about 5 minutes walk from here
Would you like to go later?
Well, I don't know. All the teachers
may have dinner together
I'll tell you later, okay?
Didn't I beat you up
enough yet?
I'm not gonna
let you hurt her.
Dong Hyun, you saying you're gonna
go one on one with him?
You're dead meat
Hey, you're gonna get high
if you drink that
You can't fight them
clear-headed
- What the?
- You're all dead!
Hey, isn't that a letter in
Mr. Gong's lunch?
- Try this rice cake!
- You do!
Wait!
This is between Chun Soo and me.
Leave us alone!
Wait!
All right, all right.
You can have Ms. Kim
Okay?
- Are you okay?
- Doesn't it hurt?
It hurts like hell
Dong Hyun. Miss Kim is
your squeeze forever
Looks like no more
rooting bets anymore
Don't stray and
go straight home
Don't go anyway!
- Understood?
- Yes, sir!
Are you really
going to confess today?
Yes!
I even prepared the roses
Mr Gong!
Can we go to
"Lovers" later?
I think I have to attend
the teacher's dinner
I see!
I hope you
meet somebody nice
Can't you give it to her now?
Why is your squeeze
drinking alone?
Stop calling her my squeeze
Okay!
go tell her
straight up like you
stood up against Chun Soo.
It's been three hours already
Okay!
Hey
it's you Dong Hyun
Miss, I have something
I must say
- When I first...
- You!
Do you know
who my first love was?
No!
But, I am willing to
accept your past
Before I met you
Miss, miss
I think
she completely passed out
Won't she wake up
if we touch her?
Let's touch her
and see what happens
Don't start imagining
stupid things
We have to protect her
until she wakes up
Okay!
I'll go watch
if my mom's coming back
I'll turned out the light, so my mom
won't know we are here
I'll go with you
- Follow me!
- Me too?
Do you think
Dong Hyun will do it with Miss Kim?
I don't know.
Shall we make Dong Hyun drink
the love potion
and see what happens?
I didn't feel anything
when I drank it
Me too, nothing
Will Miss Kim want to do it
with Dong Hyun?
Remember last time
when we were peeping?
Woman was screaming
when they're enjoying sex.
I still get a hard-on
whenever I think about them
Have you got cup noodles here?
No, let's go buy some
at supermarket
Sure, then let's do it here
I was going to explode
If I reached out,
I could have touch her breasts
The thought of me being inside her
made me shiver all over
Hello... hello?
Teacher Yoon
this is Dong Hyun
Yoo Ri
we're almost there
- Thank you!
- Please, be careful
Mr, Gong!
Five years ago the start of
a new semester. Do you remember?
A sudden burst of rain
left me stuck at the bus stop
Then you appeared and said:
"Are you a Gwang Chun high student?"
"Then lets share
this umbrella" and we left.
When your hand
touched mine, I knew
you were the prince
I had been waiting for
Then beyond
my wildest dreams
the prince became
my teacher
Since that day all the time we spent
together has been like a dream
You'll never know how much effort
I put in trying to meet you again
I was so afraid you would
think my emotions were childish
My feeling got stronger as
we spent more time together.
I must confess to you
as I cannot hide
my feelings anymore
Mr. Gong
I love you
Seok Gu
lets do the rooting bet again
See who is first to hump
Miss Kim
Dong Hyun!
Mom.
You know that your mother
has always trusted you?
First class
Second class
Write one wish on
that piece of paper
What do we do with this?
This is this school tradition?
One person from the class
that wins the Sports carnival will be
picked to read wish
Last year
one trainee teacher wished
for a women's bathroom
Is that why boy's school
has women's bathroom?
Yes!
This tradition has
been going on for 30 years
Please write a good one
Mr. Gong, please find someone
wonderful to marry
Your class isn't too bad
But we are going to win, though
You never know
what will happen
Have some.
You know, if we win this final,
that we win everything?
Didn't you see?
Because of Gu Tae Shik
Because of Gu Tae Shik from Class 1
we are half a lap behind
He's the captain of
the track team.
Don't worry!
I am going to run in the finals
And when we win
Mr. Gong will be overjoyed
We will now
have the 1000 meter relay as the final
event of this year's Sports carnival
The runner and teachers
please proceed to the starting line
I will escort Mr. Gong
Are you trying to win
you piece of shit
We still did a good job
coming on the second
We must win
Hey, isn't that the wish memo
the trainee teachers wrote?
Something things are more
important than rooting.
Let's win this one
- Okay, this one is for Dong Hyun
- Lets go!
You piece of shit, are you
gonna stand in our way?
Go, go class 6!
Lets give it all we have!
Why aren't you saying
anything Miss Kim?
Whether we win or lose, I'll never forget
the time we spent together
Lets try our best
Let's go class 6.
Go Go Go
Class 6 is the best
Ready!
Seok Gu!
This is our final day
So it is
Will we see
each other again?
Of course.
It's not like we are going abroad
According to school tradition
Dong Hyun
from class 6 will pick a wish
Go ahead
Mr. Gong
Tell Miss Kim
how you really feel
Once a student
always a student
Yoo Ri
will you marry me?
At the age of 15
my wet dreams ended like that
Did you watch
'Entertainment Weekly' last night?
Yeah, I was shocked
How is it possible that Namil and
Hyo Jin are going out?
It's Namil this time?
It was Jong Kook last time
What a whore!
That bitch! Doesn't she have
a scandal with Hiddink yet?
Anybody got any pads?
Why the hell does
it have to start now?
- Got one?
- Kyoung Lim, will this do?
You use that?
Looks creepy.
I was chatting
on the net last night
and one dude asked me
out saying he was a full-on stud
He wanted to meet
at Dae Huk Lor.
So did you meet him?
So I bolted out because he said
he was drop dead good looking
And Uni students are
full of cash these days
So what was he like?
What a friggin let down!
He looks were so insulting
I kicked him in the balls right there
in the middle of the street
Hey, here comes
the trainee teacher
Settle down
and let's greet our guest
- Attention, Greetings!
- Good morning
This is Mr. Ji SeokGu our new
trainee teacher for our class
No, I mean trainee teacher
Mr. Ji Seok Gu
- Please give him your utmost attention.
- Yes, ma'am!
It's so nice to meet you all.
I want to say
Is that everybody should
study hard...
That's it.
Thank you.
- Mr. Ji
- Yes?
What do you call
'that' in English?
An English teacher
should know basic words.
It's THAT. THAT
Any way, I hope we can have
a pleasant time
for the next couple of weeks
Can I drink this?
Sure
We squeezed some for you
It tastes good
Okay, enough of that.
Let's start class
We'll study harder
if you sing us a song.
Sing them a song.
I am sure they'll study harder
You promise
you'll study harder
if I sing you a song?
Yes!
Who are you?
I suppose you are
the new trainee teacher?
Why?
What's wrong?
I suppose
you danced too hard?