Flying Monkey, you want to get Charmy?
Did you get my permission?
Incredible! I'm exhausted.
I can't believe she gave me
such a valuable gift.
Too bad, she smelled like
stinky tofu tonight.
Anyway, it's still very special.
This old shoe is yours in exchange
for your token of love.
The shoe is for me.
You can't just take it.
Why is he here?
I've received the symbol of our love.
You're too late!
Another one?
I don't want a used woman!
I've taught Flying Monkey a lesson.
Here's a towel.
Thank you.
Bitch, come out!
Come out, bitch!
What's the matter?
You two!
Adulterous couple, come out here!
How dare you treat me like this?
What have I done?
You were just with
Scholar Wong and then him.
Now you've asked me to come here,
you whore!
He's talking to you.
I was not with him.
Don't deny it.
I saw him taking off your clothes.
He didn't take off my clothes.
Don't lie to me.
I saw you naked.
You can't stop me
from revealing the truth.
Yim Wing Chun,
ever since you left Fook Chow
I've been thinking about you.
I've traveled so far to see you.
I'm so stupid!
You are stupid.
I didn't take off my clothes,
she did.
Shame!!!
Leung Pok To,
you're as dumb as a pig.
You've misunderstood, she is...
Don't say it.
I know, she's a woman.
I'm sorry...
Sorry...
Are you alright?
Did that silly guy hurt you?
I'm talking about her heart,
not her body.
Why didn't you tell him
that you are Yim Wing Chun?
What's the use?
He does not love the real
Yim Wing Chun.
You are all useless fools. Can't you
even protect the 2nd Fortress Lord?
What happened to your pecker?
I guess you can't fool around anymore.
From now on,
you can concentrate on kung-fu.
Am I right?
Of course, you're right.
Who did this to you?
It's a woman called Yim Wing Chun.
I'll take revenge for you.
Useless fools.
Can't even defeat a woman.
The bandits are coming!
Calm down,
we're not here to rob you
but to buy wedding gifts.
It's on the left.
It's on the right.
Left.
Right.
2nd Fortress Lord,
which way is the tofu store?
How would I know?
I only come here at night.
Now who's leading the way.
Go straight!
What's going on?
A party?
Bandits...
Slow down people!
Are you nuts?
How dare you come in broad daylight?
I'm preparing for my wedding.
Stay away!
Wing Chun, please stay away.
He's given us a lot of money.
Yes, he's doing business with us.
We're making big bucks here.
Don't ruin our businesses!
Your wedding?
Whose daughter have you kidnapped?
I've come to get Charmy.
How dare you!
He's messing with your wooden dummy.
Stop.
Stay away!
Not bad. My Cotton Belly
could have killed someone else.
What do you think?
Good kicks, quick and fierce
but my hands are faster
I blocked them all.
So you are Yim Wing Chun.
Who are you?
I'm Flying Chimpanzee.
Another beast!
I was the one who wounded the Monkey.
Come and get me.
Go ahead.
You are really gorgeous.
I must have you.
Are you married?
Cut the bull!
You're right,
not everyone can tame a wild horse.
How about a kiss?
Let me go!
Help me, Wing Chun.
If you get any closer,
I'll kill her.
We'll fight again tomorrow.
If you win, I'll let her go.
But if you lose,
you'll be my wife. Let's go.
Wing Chun, help me!
How dare they take
Charmy from Wing Chun.
Look, she's fuming.
Please come again!
Help!
Wing Chun.
Wing Chun...
Leung Pok To, help me.
Stop him.
Whirling kick!
See you tomorrow at the fortress.
Mr. Leung, Mr. Leung!
Pok To, Pok To!
Pok To, help me catch a cricket.
No problem.
Wing Chun, hurry up.
Wing Chun...
Hey, he's calling you.
Wing Chun!
Can't you hear him calling you?
He's not calling.
He's just talking in his sleep.
Are you crazy?
Why did you give the
Nine Magic Pill to Leung Pok To?
Our master gave it to both of us.
Half of it should be mine.
That pill is worth at least 200 taels.
He belongs to someone else.
Why did you save him?
You're out of your mind!
I've got to save Charmy.
But she's your enemy now.
Charmy and I are still friends.
It's not her fault.
It's a misunderstanding.
Maybe that's fate.
Even if I am single all my life,
I still have my pride.
Besides you'll still be here
to keep me company.
I've finally found my love.
Didn't you say that
all men are disgusting?
But it's more disgusting
and miserable to be alone.
I'm sorry.
Congratulations.
Wing Chun. Please don't go.
Wing Chun.
You...
Why did you get up so early?
Did you know
you've just eaten 200 taels?
I know...
Where are the bandits?
10 miles from the
west of the Tai Sin Peak.
Hey, be careful!
There is no more magic pill.
Go back. You haven't recovered.
I will go to the fortress
to rescue Wing Chun.
I'll tell her that
you wanted to come.
No, let's go together.
Sorry for embarrassing you
the other day.
Let's not talk about it anymore, okay?
Okay.
She seems a little different.
She is not the Wing Chun I remember.
Since you two are good friends,
you must have known
about the forced marriage.
When Wing Chun was 17,
the villagers called her
the Tofu Beauty.
However, a villain laid eyes on her
and forced her to marry him.
She didn't want to marry him,
so she asked
a top kung-fu master to help her.
The Master said she could avoid
the marriage by learning kung-fu,
but that would scare
other men away as well.
Finally, she learned kung-fu
and drove the villain away.
Life can be changed by
just one decision,
but Wing Chun has no regrets.
Something wrong?
You seem to be telling your own story.
Wing Chun is my best friend,
she tells me everything.
Did she tell you about the crickets that
we caught together when we were kids?
She is not Wing Chun, you...
Don't worry about who she is.
She is beautiful and very fond of you.
You seem to like her too,
so why don't you accept her?
Do you know? You are my Wing Chun.
I'm not.
You're Wing Chun.
You are.
I'm not.
I'm not!!!
You're Wing Chun!!!
Okay, I am. Are you alright?
I am just over joyed.
I've finally found you.
It was worth the pain.
The newlyweds are here.
Thanks.
Congratulations...
Hurry up.
Congratulations.
All the best.
Come, my wife.
May we ask how
the bride and groom met?
Everyone knows I kidnapped her.
The bride and groom should kiss.
Why did you hit me?
I can't stand it.
I didn't do anything.
Let's go on with the wedding ceremony.
Let's kowtow.
Alright, go to bed.
Stop.
The bananas are crushed.
This means you will have many children.
My pecker is missing.
How can I have children?
It's alright,
at least your wish is granted.
Brother, let me help you do it.
My pecker is willing to help.
Come on,
I haven't touched
woman for two years.
Listen...
This woman is the bait
to trap Yim Wing Chun.
I'm the only man
who can control this wild woman.
Don't you want to see
your big brother get laid?
Big brother, what about me?
Shut up, go drink
with the rest of your brothers...
Dinner time.
He's sleeping with his eyes open.
Look at you.
Who hit my wife?
Go back to sleep.
I'm so drunk.
I can see the scarecrows moving.
Cheers.
Wake up.
Yim Wing Chun,
I'm the only one in the fortress
who can't drink or sleep.
It's all your fault. Get her.
Let's go.
Go rescue Charmy.
Okay.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
Go
You're early.
Wing Chun.
Pok To.
You damn Chimpanzee, let her go.
Charmy, don't be afraid.
I don't want her even
if you give her to me.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
And yourself.
Okay.
You can leave first.
Wait.
Bring me the Champion Spear.
If you can get the spear out with
three moves, then I'll release her.
If you can't get it out,
then you'll have to stay with me.
Okay. You got a deal.
The spear is under my feet,
come and get it.
I'll be very gentle.
Shut up.
You are a bit slow.
But if you surrender now,
I'll let them go.
I haven't even started.
Just wait till I beat you.
I like it.
Come and stop me.
I'll push it into the wall,
let's see how you can pull it out.
Thank you very much.
Bravo!
Shut up, are you happy that I lost?
Great, this is getting more
and more interesting.
I enjoy fighting with you.
We'll fight again in three days!
Let them go!
Yes!
Wing Chun, thank you.
Wing Chun.
Wing Chun, are you okay?
Not quite.
Where are you going?
To see my Master.
Will she be okay?
You've eaten my Nine Magic Pill,
you should be alright.
Master.
Teeth is stronger than the tongue,
but gentler than steel.
Not strong enough, not gentle enough,
how can I defeat the Chimpanzee?
Even a tall tree has to
return to its origin.
Wing Chun, go and get married.
The owner is on some
personal business.
Closed for the day.
Has Wing Chun become Mrs. Fortress?
We can't have sweet tofu anymore.
You'll be cross-eyed
if you continue to stare like that.
Charmy...
Charmy!
Relax, you're out of breath.
Go to hell.
Charmy, why didn't you tell me
you were back? Who do you think I am?
Have you lost your...?
She lost her virginity long time ago.
It doesn't make any difference.
The bandits just used me
to bait Wing Chun into their trap.
I believe you,
but the villagers don't.
We should get married secretly.
Why don't you move in
with me first.
We will have our wedding
after the rumors are gone.
Charmy is going to marry
Wong Hok Chow!!
Marriage can't be forced.
You've seen what happened
the other night.
Charmy and I have became
husband and wife.
Here's your token of love to me.
I don't have such precious stuff.
Look.
My old shoe!
I've waited for your proposal
for a long time.
It's you?
Give me back my chastity!!
I'll kill myself.
What's done cannot be undone.
Don't worry,
I'll take good care of you.
Is he alright?
He's adding up my wealth.
I didn't know you are so wealthy.
What's done cannot be undone.
I'll marry you.
Then I'll marry you, too.
Do you know how much he has?
Of course I do.
Congratulations.
Thank you...
Leung Pok To!
Who is Leung Pok To?
I am.
I have a message from Wing Chun.
I'm very thirsty.
Can I get some sweet tofu.
No problem. Please sit down.
Wing Chun, you're so cruel.
Why are you reading my letter?
Give it back.
This is mine.
How can you leave me?
I thought you have a letter for me?
Yeah, but it's a message.
Look at him I am glad I have you.
How is that? Isn't the message
sweeter than the soy bean milk?
Yes.
I've packed your clothes.
I've also packed for Wing Chun.
Thank you.
I've made this for you.
Thank you. It's pretty.
Clothes are better when new,
but relationships are better when old.
I wish you and Wing Chun happiness.
He has probably chosen
to be with Charmy.
He's not coming, I should leave.
Oh, you're here already?
Why did you hide in the tree?
I was afraid I'd be late,
so I got here last night.
I just woke up and here you are.
You are always so silly.
Let's go.
Not feeling well?
Let me help you.
May we borrow your place
to rest for awhile?
Certainly, I am going to pick
some tea leaves.
Make yourselves comfortable.
Thank you.
Are you alright?
Let's rest for awhile.
I'm still a bit jittery
after taking the magic pill.
Or is it because of me?
Don't tease me?
No, no.
Mosquitoes.
Ouch.
Let's see how far you can fly.
Now I understand what my master said.
Use Wing Chun to redirect the force
of the Chimpanzee's cotton belly.
Let's fight the Chimpanzee again.
No, it'll be my loss if you lose.
How can that be? I...
Unless we get married first.
Your knees are hurting me.
It really hurts.
You deserve it.
It's a natural reflex.
Pull it out if you can.
I also have a good one.
No... don't tickle me.
You tricked me.
Don't worry. I'll be back soon.
Shout if you need me,
I'll rush right in.
Wing Chun.
Kick his ass!
No one can ever escape from me.
If you want a lesson,
I'll grant you one.
What if you lose?
I'll call you mom.
Great. My good son.
How dare you?
Choose your weapon.
Eight Chop Swords.
Your short swords
can't compare with my spear.
You'll definitely be my wife.
I don't think so.
But, you can be my son.
The longer the stronger.
The shorter the riskier.
It's no use
to have a long weapon.
Stop. Move aside.
It's between me and her.
Wing Chun Fist.
I'll give you a ride.
One more.
Your kung-fu has improved a lot
in the past few days.
You haven't seen anything yet.
Cotton Belly!!!
Kick you belly open.
Redirect Force.
I have destroyed your Cotton Belly.
I guess you should call me mom.
More Wing Chun Fist.
Call me mom.
One more kick.
Again.
Not bad, you're really persistent.
I'm not fighting anymore,
my hands are numb.
Fortress Lord, are you okay?
How are you feeling?
You asshole!
How can you attack from behind?
Say sorry to your mom.
Big brother, you...
Say it.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Mom, am I right?
Yes, good son.
Farewell, mother of thieves.
Farewell, be good.
Yes, mother of thieves.
Wing Chun...
I'm thrilled. I'm very happy.
Get up. Let's go.
I am so happy.
Do you know how worried I was?
But I knew you would win.
When can we get married?
Let's celebrate with the others.
Thank you...
Never thought that we could
sell all our leftover goods.
Yes, the buyers gave us a good deal.
Thank you...
Charmy, you should settle down, too.
Don't worry, I won't work
at your tofu shop for life.
You're a lady, remember?
Thank you...
Congratulations...
The two of you are made for
each other.
I wish you both a peaceful life.
Thank you.
Wing Chun I wish you
both the very best.
When have you become
such a smooth talker?
I am nice because
I have a happy marriage.
It's almost the lucky hour,
you should get going.
Yes, if we miss the lucky hour...
Yes, hurry up.
Let's go.
Thank you.