Seung-jae
come in
That's ok
Come in
2x1=2,
2x2=4,
2x3=6,
2x4=8,
2x5=10
2x6=12
2x7=14
2x8=16
2x9=18
I didn't
steal that money
Half of it
belongs to my dad
He gave it
to my aunt to raise me
But now, she says
she has no money for my tuition
She has money
for her daughter's private tutor
but not for me
Does that make sense?
I...
I'll never forget today
I'll show everyone that
I can do it on my own
Then
I can laugh about
what happened today
Seung-jae,
Are you asleep?
No
Come here. It's warmer
Your heart is so pure
When I'm with you,
You make me feel so innocent
You're very kind...
Always...
Thank you for staying with me
- Where are you going, sir?
- Excuse me?
21st floor is cafeteria
I don't think a VP would be
eating there
No. I eat at the cafeteria
So-hee!
Sir, is the VP also a member
of the 'Royal Family'?
No. He's a self-made man
He was sent to America for an
adoption when he was only 6
He received MBA all by himself
He's pretty impressive
Here are marketing plans
from our new recruits
Thank you
May I ask why you've
requested for them?
Just to see if there are
any fresh ideas
Take yours back
Sir, nothing was chosen?
I stayed up a week straight working it
You thought it'd be that easy?
Read over
VP's note
on each one
It feels like a report card
'Would you give me a chance?'
I hope you're well
I haven't heard from you
in last 2 months
It snowed here
As I watch my neighbors
get busy with clearing
snow off their doorsteps
I felt my heart rush a bit
I'm getting ready for the winter
as well
There isn't much,
a small town mailman needs to do
But, if there's something
that I must do, then I should do it now
In any case, I hope this winter
will soon be over
I hope to see you before this
winter passes
I really would like to see you
Dad. You're making a mistake
Get... out... bastard
Ho-gul!
I know you don't want to hear me
say it but the village will sink
We're gonna get kicked out anyway
So, what difference does it make?
Can't you see I'm doing this for us?
For Dad and his illness?
He doesn't even know
Let's talk about...
Forget it.
Why don't you go
and kiss ass to grandma
Hey, Deuk-sam!
Yeah... Yes
Hey
Hi. Have you eaten?
Seung-jae!
Don't worry about it
Just let it be
But,
about So-hee's grandma...
What about her?
So-hee's aunt
sold her land here
A realtor came by
with paperwork and asked me
to mail it to Seoul
Does she know about this?
Probably not
You'd better tell her, then
Let her not plant
on government property
And a day after tomorrow, deliver
this paperwork to Seoul personally
To Seoul?
Your paperwork is in there too
The postmaster at Dobong post
office wants to see you
He's a friend of mine
Just introduce yourself
It's time to start thinking
about a new job
When I was in America,
I had many older brothers
with all different backgrounds
One of them taught me this
But, now, I can't remember
who it was
When I was 7
for the first time
in my life, I got a gift from my dad
And I was so happy
But, 2 days later
he passed away
And, now
I'm so afraid of
this feeling of happiness
Please promise me
that you won't die without me
Her name is Yoon So-hee
I don't know who that is
If you see her,
you can't
forget her
She's about this tall and
has beautiful eyes
with long straight hair...
She's beautiful!
Anyone who shows up here
with just a name
is always a sales person
So, what are you?
I'm a mail man!
Boy... You're persistent
I have to see her
Excuse me!
He's my client
So-hee!
Your aunt told me you work here
Wow, pretty impressive company!
It's been awhile since I moved out
Then the letters
I've sent you...
I never got them
Oh. That's what happened
So, what brings you here?
Well...
I had some business with...
Post office in Seoul... Uhm...
I came to see you
You're still sweet
But, I'm really busy
right now
I'm sorry but you should go
You heard about
big corporate like this
We have very tight schedule and
it's not very flexible
That's ok. I'll wait
No. I mean...
Words get around here so fast and I can't really say
you're my family member and...
You know what I mean?
Then I'll wait for you at some
other place. Take your time
No. Really
You should go
So-hee
Are you angry that
you never got my letters?
I didn't mean for that to happen
I really did send them
If you tell me your new address
I'll send them again
No
You don't have to
I just want to leave the childhood
memories as they are
But,
That day...
Seung-jae, we're both adults
We were adults at that time
We had good feelings for each other
and things happened
But that's that
I'm happy with my life right now
And...
I'm in love with someone
And he proposed to me last night.
We're thinking about
getting married this spring
He's a really good person
Just think of it as a gift from a friend
Grab something to eat
on your way back home
Right. I mean,
I'm pretty hungry...
I was waiting for you
and...
I forgot to eat...
Well...
Seung-jae!
Where will you move to?
I don't know, yet
We're moving to Jinan
It has cheap real estate
and also has a hospital
and a big post office
If you want
I can look into a place for you there
Sun-mi, when will you get married?
What?
Married? Well...
I have to find a man first
What kind of a man do you like?
I don't know
I guess...
I like men who have
clear eyes
and soft lips...
I'm so embarrassed
Sun-mi, let's get married
You like me, right?
I mean, you don't have to like me,
but you're interested in me.
So, can't we get married?
If you don't want to, then forget it
Bastard!
How can you say that so easy?
You know
I've always liked you...
I tried to forget you so many times,
But I couldn't
I ordered all those magazines
just to see you everyday
You know I don't read any of them.
You didn't even get a bell
for your bike...
And now, you ask me
to marry you and...
Just like that... Bastard
You're such a bastard...
So-hee,
what happened?
- What?
- About VP
What is he gonna do now?
What are you talking about?
The bankruptcy
I heard his loss adds up to
a few 1 million wons
I'll call you later
2x3=6... 2x4=8...
2x6=12... 2x7=14...
2x8=16... 2x9=... 18...
The reason for our gathering here
today is...
Lately we became awkward
with each other
due to the dam construction matter
But, we used to be so close
Like one big family
So before we all leave, we should
take this time to mend our friendships
Please enjoy
Should I clear the table?
You're acting strange today
Open the door, will you?
Aren't you cold?
The wind is quite chilly
He snores so loud
Grandma, where are you going?
I'm going to see my son
It's late
Wait till morning and I'll go with you
That's ok
Don't go
If I go, then So-hee will come
So-hee's coming?
You go back to sleep
I'll be alright
Wait, don't you want to take this?
I got no use for that
You can have it if you want
How are you?
Grandma...
Did you see her go?
Were you with her?
Grandma... Did she go to Mars?
Daddy is there...
Did she go there?
She doesn't know how to write...
How will she send me letters?
She was in peace
Good. That's good
Seung-jae...
Remember that brook
where we used to go play?
And catch fish?
A bit down from it,
there was a stream...
That's Noruet stream...
And further down, there was a river...
Songnae River. It's a wide river
That must be it, then
I saw you in my dream and...
You were there... By that river
You were fishing there
The sun was warm
and the wind was cool
Sitting there by the riverside
you looked so happy
Sometimes. When I was down
I thought about going there
I thought I could see you
if I went there
and sit next to you
lean on you... and just rest for a little
there...
You can come anytime.
I'm always there
You're late! Come on
Let's go
Seung-jae, were you cold?
Seung-jae!
Sorry
Is this the residence of
Yoon So-hee?
Yes. That's me
You got a mail and a package
From who...
We only have
kimchi soup or miso soup
I'll have miso soup.
Do you have a room for a night?
I have one, but it's a bit damp
You want it?
Yes. I'll take it
I'll give you a good price for it
Thank you. And ma'am...
Do you know where I can find post
office workers who worked here?
Post office?
Mr. Kim!
It's me. So-hee
This is Songnae River, right?
Nothing has changed
Do you know where Seung-jae is?
He sent me a package
but I can't make out the postmark
He sent it to me on my birthday.
I didn't think he'd still do this
But I guess he was thinking back to
when we were kids
This postmark is not from Korea
I've never seen it before
Happy birthday
Much time have passed
since we saw each other
I came here because
I missed you so much
Now, I can see you
Whenever I close my eyes
and say my wish
This is Mars. This is what
we've been chasing after
What we didn't know was
that the whole time
it's been right here right in our hearts
So we can meet anytime
And get back whenever we want to
Here, where I thought I would come
when I am dead
Was just here in our heart
When you have anything
you wish not to forget
When you find your most cherished
moment in your heart...
then, we'll see each other there
Until then, take care of yourself
Seung-jae, from Mars
Today...
I realized the planet in his story
is the place that I already knew
And for the first time in a long time,
I sent a letter to Mars