HERO
Two thousand years ago..
during the Warring States period,
China was divided into seven Kingdoms.
For years they battled for supremacy
while the people suffered.
The King of Qin was the most ruthless
in his efforts to conquer the land
and unify all under heaven.
He was regarded as a common threat
by the other six Kingdoms.
The annals of Chinese history
are abound with tales of the assassins
sent to kill the great King.
This is one of the legends...
I was orphaned at an early age
I had no name,
so people called me Nameless
Being a nobody,
I studied swordsmanship
After 10 years of practice
I acquired a unique skill
The King of Qin has summoned me
My deeds have astonished the Kingdom
By order of His MaJesty
we have brought the mighty warrior
Sky, Flying Snow and Broken Sword
the three assassins from Zhao
have sought His MaJesty's life
for 10 years
His MaJesty has known no peace
To the astonishment of all
a mighty warrior of Qin
has smashed them
His MaJesty can finally sleep at night!
We reJoice for our King!
This warrior sent from Heaven
has exterminated the assassins
Summon the warrior!
Remain 100 paces from His MaJesty
Or you will be executed.
Never forget that
No one is allowed
within 100 paces of me
Do you know why?
To guard against assassins
Yes. That's why I am confined
in this armor
You have removed a great peril for me
How should I reward you?
My service was for Qin, not for a reward
Achievements must be rewarded
Sky's silver spear...
wounded many of my brave warriors
Announce my edict!
By order of His MaJesty
he who kills Sky
will receive gold and land
and be allowed to drink
within 20 paces of His MaJesty
I am informed you're a citizen of Qin
I am a Prefect from Leng Meng County
A County Prefect over 10 square miles!
Surely the lowest-ranking official in Qin
How did you defeat such opponents?
I took them on one by one
Tell me the details
Does Your MaJesty know
Flying Snow and Broken Sword were lovers?
Yes, I do
And that they hadn't spoken
for three years?
For three years? Why?
Flying Snow had an affair with Sky
Broken Sword never forgave her
Why haven't I heard this before?
I went to great lengths to uncover it
To divide Flying Snow and Broken Sword
I first needed to eliminate Sky
I have an idea of what you planned
Your MaJesty is wise
What did you use to defeat Sky?
The sword
I must arrest criminals in my county
On the fifth day of the sixth month
Sky attended a chess house
I had learnt he enJoyed playing chess
and listening to music there
So, the seven masters of Qin Palace
We are here to arrest you!
Identify yourself by showing your spear
Halt!
What can a minor official do?
This is my territory
So?
You are on the King's most wanted list
I am placing you under arrest
Old man, please play one more tune
Martial arts and music are different
but they share the same principle
Both stress attaining a supreme state
Sky and I faced each other
for a long time
Neither of us moved
We fought the battle in our minds
How swift thy sword!
I thought I knew everything
about my Kingdom
I didn't know that Leng Meng County
held a talent like yours
Broken Sword
Flying Snow
By order of His MaJesty!
Flying Snow and Broken Sword
have teamed up for assassination
He who kills either of them
will receive gold and land
and be allowed to drink
within 10 paces of His MaJesty
Three years ago, Flying Snow
stormed the palace with Broken Sword
3000 elite troops couldn't stop them
I've since emptied the palace
so assassins cannot hide
Was your sword swifter
than theirs combined?
No
How did you do it, then?
Disguised as a citizen of Zhao
I sought them in the Kingdom of Zhao
I learned they were hiding
in a calligraphy school
under the names Highcliff and Springbrook
Rumor had it
the Qin army would attack that day
Most of the townspeople had fled
Only the school's students remained
Why have you come at such a time?
Who are you?
I'm from Yi County
in the Kingdom of Zhao
My father's dying wish
was for one of your scrolls
I fear this may be our school's last day
Which calligrapher do you seek?
I respectfully request Master Highcliff
Highcliff was Broken Sword
Legend said his skill as a swordsman
was rooted in his calligraphy
So I had my concerns
I needed to find out if it was true
What do you want written?
"Sword."
You are fond of the sword?
It was my father's dying wish
What size scroll?
Eight feet
For that size I will need red ink
My master has asked me
to borrow some red ink
My master wants to borrow some red ink
Did you hear me, Master Springbrook?
Master Highcliff wants to borrow red ink
Tell him to come himself
Could I have some red ink?
The character "sword"
was still being written
when Your MaJesty's troops
arrived at the city gates
Draw!
Your MaJesty's army is invincible
not only because it is brave
but also because of its archery
with a greater range than any other army
The Qin archers are like artillery
intimidating the enemy
Hail! Hail! Hail!
Please remember
their arrows might destroy our town
and topple our Kingdom
but they can never
obliterate our culture
Today
you will learn the essence of our culture
Hail! Hail! Hail!
Those Zhao people didn't flee?
They drew strength from their calligraphy
What was so difficult about "sword"?
There are 19 different ways to write it
I asked Broken Sword
for a 20th way
Both calligraphy and swordplay
rely on one's strength and spirit
The 20th style would reveal
the essence of his swordsmanship
How odd to write it in 19 ways
It makes the written language
impossible to comprehend
Once I've conquered the six Kingdoms
and all the northern tribes
I will eradicate this problem
by mandating one style of writing
Wouldn't that be ideal?
Your MaJesty won't stop
at the six Kingdoms?
The six Kingdoms are nothing!
I will lead my army to conquer vast lands
and establish a great empire
Hail! Hail! Hail!
Master Springbrook
Why are you going outside?
To fend off the arrows
You aren't needed. Stay inside
The Qin archers are powerful
You alone may not stop them
Hail! Hail! Hail!
You are good
You are even better
You didn't come here for calligraphy
Who are you?
I've travelled here to deliver an item
Please meet me in the library at midnight
Great calligraphy
Great swordplay
You didn't even see my swordplay
I couldn't have written without it
At midnight
meet me in the library
Several hundred thousand Qin troops
were readying for the next onslaught
I studied the character all night
trying to unlock the secret of his skills
It would reveal his swordsmanship?
But it's Just an ordinary word
Calligraphy and swordplay are similar
One must comprehend their true essence
Did you discover it?
It eluded me
So how did you challenge them?
Although they hadn't spoken in three
years They spied on each other
At midnight
Broken Sword would peek into
Flying Snow's room
At 2 o'clock in the morning
she would spy on Broken Sword
What strange behaviour
I was surprised too
So I used Sky's silver
spear to get to them
Sky died by your sword?
Yes
Who are you? Why are you here?
I'm from the Kingdom of Qin
I have a message from Sky
Go on
He said he had lived a life
without responsibilities or commitments
He cared for only one person
Who?
Flying Snow
Sky was certain she'd avenge his death
To fight, meet me at the Qin camp
You can leave now
Go!
I know you saw us!
Let me tell you
we've been together for three years
I let you see us on purpose!
I no longer care about you at all!
We were both very foolish
I just wanted you to care about me
I'm not going to fight you
Go away!
I will kill you in honor of my master!
You ask to die. I will help you.
Why do you laugh?
What you did last night was stupid
My plan proved successful
When Flying Snow was fighting me
she was disturbed and disoriented
I defeated her easily
I never imagined supreme warriors
Iike Broken Sword and Flying Snow
allowing their emotions
to be a liability
It sounds as if you did divide them
Yes
In that case, they must have been
petty and narrow-minded
True
Your story sounds logical
But
you have underestimated one person.
Who?
Me
Would you like my impression of them?
Three years ago they stormed the palace
I was impressed
by their valor and dignity
Their character could not be petty
So Flying Snow's affair with Sky is a lie
Their betrayal of one another is a lie
The story you Just told is a lie!
Except for one thing
Sky did know one of you
Who?
You
I surmise you two were old friends
And Sky's defeat has only one explanation
What's that?
He permitted it
To kill me, the two of you formed a pact
using my men as witnesses
That was not hard to arrange
The hardest part was to persuade Sky
to put his life in your hands
You were not fast enough to defeat Sky
He died willingly under your sword
Such devotion deserves true respect
He was the first to sacrifice himself
for your mission
Sky was proud
He saw himself as an unrivalled fighter
What convinced him you could succeed
where he had failed?
You have trained, perhaps for 10 years
with one goal, my assassination
You have a great skill
that few can counter
Killing Sky got you within 20 paces of me
So why seek out
Broken Sword and Flying Snow?
I surmise that your skill
requires you to come within 10 paces