O
On
Onc
Once
Once U
Once Up
Once Upo
Once Upon
Once Upon A
Once Upon A T
Once Upon A Ti
Once Upon A Tim
Once Upon A Time
Once Upon A Time I
Once Upon A Time In
Once Upon A Time In C
Once Upon A Time In Ch
Once Upon A Time In Chi
Once Upon A Time In Chin
Once Upon A Time In China
Once Upon A Time In China IV
Congratulations...
Is Master Wong Fei Hung there?
Fei Hung is out,
thank you for coming
Give them the red packets for their presents
I am going to fetch it at once
Thank you Master Tam,
your present is too precious!
Please go in and have some tea
After you...
Red packets...
Come on, it's yours
Master Chiu has arrived
Your son won in the Lion King Competition,
he is so famous now
Give a red packet as a present
Master Wong,
today is a big day.
I want to have a drink with your son.
Where is Fei Hung?
He has gone to the train station
Is this the lion head used by Wong Fei Hung
for the competition?
I've heard that this defeated
thousand of lions
for the gold medal
Someone said Master Wong joined
the competition so as to save a person
That's why he returned the medal to
the government after receiving it
What a hero!
Isn't it fantastic!
A true hero!
The Lion King Competition started...
My master,
Wong Fei Hung, appeared
He is the head of the 10 Tigers of Canton,
and he is the coach of the Local Militia
He stood on the tower,
he called, "Leung Fu,
Leung Fu..."
Who is Leung Fu?
Why did Wong Fei Hung
shout for his help at such at critical moment?
Leung Fu, never heard of him!
Never heard of him?
He is so famous
What a shame!
About Leung Fu,
his eyes are sharp and big
Look at me!
Remind you of anybody?
Leung Fu is great,
he is a famous Kung-fu master
from Mei Province to Fu-Shan
He is famous from Fu-Shan
to Macao and to Hong Kong too
Inform me when you see Master
I haven't seen Master yet,
let Fu keep on bluffing
Leung Fu is the number one
student of Master Wong,
but...
He is as famous as
Wong Fei Hung
I know him so well!
Guess who am I!
I don't know
Don't you know?
Let me tell you
I am Leung Fu
It's him, it's him
Wrong guy
Foolish people,
they are too ignorant
Master...
Master!
- What's the matter?
Some officials are coming,
they look nasty
Officials?
- Yes
What are they coming for?
Maybe they are coming to arrest someone?
Impossible, let's go and have a look
Sire
The Deputy Governor is coming
with his golden dragon
with a congratulation card
from the General's Office,
for Master Wong
Please arrange for the reception
A congratulation from the General's Office?
Quick!
Ask them to prepare the firecrackers,
to welcome the golden dragon
Hurry up!
Brother Fu,
a golden dragon is coming from the East Gate
A dragon?
Yes, a big dragon
Coming for a challenge?
You are stepping on my foot
Brother Fu, what'll we do?
Inform Master now
There's no time!
Now, listen to me
Ah Yan,
bring me the lion head
Club Foot, the flag of our Association
Don't forget the drum
I see them,
they are outside the East Gate
Give way please
Here comes the Lion King
Sire
What's the matter?
A lion from the Cantonese Association
has come to block our way
Block our way?
Have they come to welcome us?
It doesn't seem so
The lion keeps kicking our dragon's head
Master
Have the people from the
General's Office arrived yet?
No, they've stopped in front of the East Gate
Why?
A lion is challenging them
Brother Fu, balance yourself,
don't fall down
Brother Fu, you are heavy
No Shadow Kick from Fu-Shan
The dragon head can't touch
the ground
I haven't lost face, have I?
Dragon in the sky!
Lion head
Think you can catch the lion head again?
Club Foot
Master!
You are back?!
Why are you standing there?
Hold the tail
Yes, Master
He must be Wong Fei Hung
Dragon in the sky
Master, watch the dragon
Club Foot, "Rolling tiger"
Club Foot,
"Tiger look up to the moon"
All right
They are higher,
let me test you
Clubfoot, the lion head must face the
dragon head, that's the rule, got it?
That's no problem at all
Club Foot, keep your balance,
don't make any mistakes
I am speedy
Excellent, so stable
Dragon ball
Dragon ball from the golden
dragon, it represents good luck
Catch the ball
Master Wong, good luck to you
Thank you very much
Ever successful
Club Foot, let me send you there
Once again
Master, I can't make it
Let me do it
Catch the tail
Yes
My respects!
I am the Deputy Governor,
Guan Shingtao
Your Excellency,
I am Wong Fei Hung from Fu-Shan
I've heard your name for a long time,
you're really a great master in Kung-fu
We've seen the best today
You really are the Lion King
Thank you
You're welcome
If it hadn't been for this,
we would never have seen
your fantastic lion dance
Master Wong rejected the gold medal of Lion King
Thus, his Excellency Li Hung-Chang asked me
to return the medal to you
Please
don't make me lose face
Come on, please take it
Your Excellency...
Please take it
Thank you, Your Excellency
Please be seated
Thank you
Fu!
Tell me,
how should I punish you?
I know what to do
I have packed up,
I will leave for Fu-Shan by tomorrow morning
How about the ticket?
I have asked Uncle Kau to buy it for me
I will go to the train station
by tomorrow morning
When you reach Fu-Shan,
write me a letter to tell me you're all right.
It's written
No, I mean
I will write a letter
right after reaching Fu-Shan
You are always disobedient
Brother Fu
What's the matter?
Let me come back to Fu-Shan with you.
I'll live in seclusion with you
Live in seclusion,
you are that great?
I won't stop you from living
in seclusion alone
You've a night to think over,
are you going to live in seclusion or not?
Your Excellency
Master Wong
Everybody, please
Master Wong, please take a look
An invitation?
Yes
Why is there another Lion King competition?
This Lion Competition is between 8 countries
Another competition
what a pity you're going back to Fu-Shan soon
Why do the foreigners want to
organize another lion competition?
This lion competition organized
by 8 foreign countries,
mirrors the present situation,
The relationships between China
and the other countries are quite tense
Our country is getting weaker and weaker
The challenge of the 8 countries
Is designed to suppress our spirit
there may be other tricks as well
To compete with the lions of the foreigners...
It's quite a challenge
I won't leave no matter what!
I guessed so
Master Wong
this competition is similar to a war
Our office has sent someone
to investigate their force
These are the plans designed by the foreigners
Golden Eagle, Giant Clam
Long Dragon, Double Horses
Flying Phoenix,
Golden Unicorn
I have heard that these lions
are much bigger than normal
They are specially equipped
But I don't know how powerful they are
I hope you can participate
in the competition with me
To fight together for our beloved country
Master Wong, it's different
from the previous competition
I hope you'll come with us
Fu, guess what Master's answer will be
He must say,
"I'm afraid we may be trapped if we
participate in this competition"
I am afraid we may be
trapped if we participate in this competition
"But, if we don't participate,
our country will lose face"
"I think, we should have a detailed plan"
But, if we don't participate,
our country will lose face
I think, we should have a detailed plan
Master Wong, are you going to participate or not?
"In our present situation,
it's pointless participating in this competition"
Although we know this a trap
we should take the risk anyway
I have to participate in this competition
Master Wong
We're going to participate in the competition,
bravo!
Shit
I can't stay for the competition
Oh yes
Go and seek help from Aunt May
Good idea
Aunt May!
How can she help?
She has a news agency in Peking
Go and help her to deliver
the newspapers, beg her to let you stay
And ask her not to tell Master, that's it
Good idea, but...
Your ideas are usually terrible
Is this Man Hing News?
It seems to be
Aunt May...
Have you got the wrong address?
Aunt May
Coming...
Who's it?
It's me, Leung Fu
Aunt May
Have you had Cantonese tea yet?
There is no Cantonese restaurant in Peking!
Why did you bring so much luggage with you?
You know, Master is so mean!
So we didn't tell Master we came to help,
but told him we were going to Fu-Shan
Don't tell...
Don't tell your Master you are hiding here,
right?
Right...
So you...
Only Brother Fu was kicked out by Master
You bastard
What's happened?
Brother Fu, I don't mean to tell the truth
You always betray me
I didn't...
Not another word!
Follow me
Stupid
You deserved that!
Let's have a look...
So spacious!
Will they publish the news about your arrival?
Don't say anything without my consent
Siu Mo, come here
What's the matter?
Look. This word is wrong,
you should write it this way
And this paragraph,
why not move it down here.
So, it won't be that messy
That's the way to print a newspaper
Try it
The words are not clear enough
Don't be big mouth
it's printed on the dress
You assaulted Aunt May
Brother Fu, I was about to tell you,
but you didn't...
You always betray me,
and now you want to frame me too?
You bastard!
How dare you set me up?
Set up? What set up?
What was set up?
Fu, you must be insane!
Someone is coming
Siu King, open the door
Let me help her to open the door
Miss Siu King, let me open the door for you
No, thanks
Who is it?
Wong Fei Hung
Why did Fu react so strangely?
Master is coming,
hide up now, be quick
Master Wong
Don't tell him that I am here
What was the noise about?
Someone wanted to open the door for me
When he heard your name,
he was got scared
and ran away
Does the man have big eyes?
Right, that's him
And a guy like this
He is here too
And the other one, like this
Let's get out of here!
Brother Fu, your luggage!
What's wrong with you?
Why shout at me?
Club Foot, hurry up
Why shout at me again?!
Brother-in-law,
have you seen sister to the train station?
Where are they?
Stop searching,
they left when they saw me
Your sister asked me to take care of you
Sister asked me to take care of you too
Are you hoping sister would come back sooner?
I may write to her
What kind of important news is it?
Why is it printed on a cloth?
Nothing, look at it yourself
It's an article
about the status of woman in China
What kind of status do women have?
So, you only ever think about men?
This news agency of sister's is in real trouble
Look at the newspapers,
they are all piled up here
They never sell,
no one wants to look at them
No matter what we print,
it's useless
Someone will take a look at it
Who?
They'll give me face if I ask them to take a look
Of course! It's too generous of Master Wong
It's a gift from Master Wong, one for everyone
Stop fighting over them!
Everyone gets one
Be careful!
Don't break the things inside
What's in the wrapping?
Other than a paper, nothing else!
It is a newspaper
The more newspapers you read,
the more you will know about the world
The more you know,
the more you can achieve
Is this sheet of paper that powerful?
To be frank, my students and I
come from poor families
We want to learn Kung-fu
to earn a living
We haven't studied, so we are illiterate
How can we read the newspaper?
What a pity,
they can't show you the respect they want to
The paper is so dirty,
don't use it for wrapping anymore
OK, just once
I think, we should start teaching people to read
before operating a newspaper
Or, these papers will just be used as wrapping
I wish there were more people
like you in the world
Your sister never praised me like this
Am I nicer, or is my sister nicer?
You are both nice
The Ladies of the Red Lantern are coming.
Come and take a look
The Red Lanterns?
Let's go and take a look
"We come from the four seas"
"Our lantern is hung on the
mast to recruit heroes"
"Our God sends us the swords"
The angels change the clouds
with their handkerchiefs
"The world, receives our order"
"Our words will be spread forever"
"We fear not foreign guns"
"For we use wind, fire,
thunder and lightning as weapons"
"We are powerful"
Dressed in red, with little lanterns
The ladies from the Red Lantern Sect
Juggle!
Expel the foreigners
and strengthen our beloved country
Red Lantern shines on the fairies,
expel the foreigners,
we are enriched with power
We use holy swords to go against foreign guns
A riot over there!
Don't go over there,
It's too dangerous
I will wait for you right here
All right!
We have strong will to protect our holy land
Throw the lanterns
Juggle!
Hear my order!
Return the holy land to us
Set the altar to hang the lanterns
Expel the foreigners
Mister, please lend me the whip
Give way please
This is the foreigner’s drugs store
Don't kill innocent people
What's the situation?
The leased territory is ahead,
the foreign troops will be coming soon
Don't go there
You'll lose your life if they catch you
Have you seen Wong Fei Hung?
Master Wong?
He must have left
Left?
Did you see him leaving?
Go!
You are Ladies...
What drives you to kill people and set fires?
Don't kill us, we're innocent
I've come to save you
They are coming, kill them!
Yes!
Let them go
Don't listen to him, attack!
Don't come over here again
You may go now
Go, run for your lives!
Who is he?
He must be Wong Fei Hung
Wong Fei Hung?
Go!
Come here
Juggle!
Red Ropes!
Attack
The foreigners are coming,
run!
They're over there, fire!
Go!
Your ladies have all left, why haven't you?
Don't move
The lease troops
Take them away, go!
Go!
The Red Lantern is showing it's power
Holy Mother
Watch out, be careful
Yes
Have you seen a Chinese
fellow passing by the way you came?
No
I think the patient needs more medication
Let me help you
You'll go home soon. Don't cry
Miss...
We have come to a conclusion,
you should leave this place immediately
All right,
if that will make you feel better
I leave now, but...
Maybe you need some more help later
I don't think so. Go
Child, let me help you to open the door
Thank you
I saw everything
Our Father won't forsake
those who devote their lives to others
Father, I hope there is a real God
So as to solve the hatred between our nations
Otherwise, we can't escape
from the coming disaster
Don't worry,
God has arranged everything
May God bless you
Thank you Father
Take care
Welcome to our army
Your ancestors sacrificed
themselves in the
Anti-Ching movement
This is the 8-colour flag of the Ching army
Lui...
You'll have chance to take revenge
for your ancestors now
Wong
Bravo,
I'm General Henlintak
Lui, Wong,
tell the descendants of the Anti-Ching warriors
You have my full support
To go against the Ching soldiers
who invaded your land
Kill him, kill him
You pig
Put him in the cell
Put him in the shithole
Wong Fei Hung
Did they torture you?
Are you the lady of the Red Lantern?
I thought you were allied with them
I'm sorry!
We must punish the Chinese rebels
to maintain our interests in China
This may also be a warning
to the Chinese government
Moreover the Manchurian government
uses such local organizations
as a protest against us to frighten us
By punishing these people
we can prevent any further disturbances
But this is China
punishing these people will cost us our heads.
The armies of the 8 nations
made a pact in Tientsin
everything is set for a war
against the Manchurians
Then let us execute the China man tonight
Then tomorrow,
display his corpse in the street as an example
Yes, General
You won't get the chance to compete
with Wong Fei Hung
Because they will execute him tonight
Aim...
Fire!
Kill him!
There's the prisoner
Thank you
On your feet!
Are you Wong Fei Hung?
I am Father Thomas
I am sorry to have to bring you some bad news
You will be executed by the Germans
in an hour's time
Wong Fei Hung
Executed?
You devil,
you will be punished by Heaven
My child...
There is only one God who can save you
It's the God, who gave me this holy clothing
So they won't suspect me
Father, you should leave now
Open the door
Get up
Father, stay back
Catch him
Catch!
My child.. Wait
I want you to help me
You must knock me unconscious too
Sorry to have to hurt you
Let me do it
Why did you punch so heavily?
Not to make them suspect him
Don't hit him anymore
It's enough already
Go!
Hurry up
Thank you for reporting
Your Excellency, please
Your Excellency
Master Wong, please get up
What?
Wong Fei Hung is missing?
Yes, Your Excellency,
we saw the parade of the Red Lanterns
Then I was separated from my brother,
he hasn't come back yet
The capital is in such a mess
The foreigners are going against the boxers
It's not wise to get any side angry
On one hand,
the foreigners want us to protect them,
on the other hand,
The Empress Dowager wants us
to overlook the matter
Ah Fu
What?
Do you think Master is doing this
to draw you out of hiding?
Master knows I am clever,
so he's using this method
to force me out
This method is quite new
No, brother Fu, Master needn't use
so many people to look for you
Just Club Foot and I were enough
You can shut up!
If you hadn't let Aunt May know,
how would Master have suspected me
of staying in the capital?
Fu, behave yourself
Don't worry too much
I will try my best to find Fei Hung for you
Thank you, Your Excellency
Your Excellency,
Fei Hung might be in the hands
of the Red Lanterns
Ho Lan
Your Excellency
Get some information on the Red Lanterns
Yes!
Are there many ladies from the Red Lanterns
Maybe
I think, Wong Fei Hung
may have been caught by the German Army
I have to check it out myself
Your Excellency, let me go with you
On this matter, it's better for the officials
to discuss among themselves
Please don't worry
My office carries some weight in the capital
It's bad luck staying with you two
One is as dumb as a stone
The other betrays me
Don't you think the street is
quieter than usual
You are just more aware
Really?
What's happened?
Have we come to the wrong place,
it's all red
The Red Lanterns shine,
here come the ladies
My dear fellows,
kneel down for worshipping
They're the Red Lantern ladies,
what beauties
I am going to kneel, kneel
Brother Fu, are you insane?
Not that simple! Should we kneel down too?
I failed in courting Aunt Yee
Now, I've got so many choices!
You'd better let me choose first
I'm Leung Fu,
I'm strong and considerate
and I know how to make a lady happy
if you get my meaning
How dare you!
I want to know where Wong Fei Hung is
Haven't you caught Wong Fei Hung?
How can this guy claim to be
the greatest Kung-fu master?
He conspired with the foreigners
and locked our senior up
Fei Hung is not that kind of person
Don't you dare accuse him!
Do you think I'll believe what you say?
Don't you want me to believe he's not involved
because he's in hiding?
Follow me to our main hall
Let's see how long will stay hidden
Lady, don't be so stubborn
We don't know what happened either
How dare you!
It's you who refuses to listen to the truth
Burn the house
Burn the house?
Be careful of the lanterns
They won't have a chance to use them!
Let's get the leader first
I don't think so
Watch out!
My feet!
Escape from him
The Red Lantern Shines
Brother Fu,
let me handle this
She is too tall for you
Go and fetch a shorter one next time
No need to make it look good,
they can't see us
You act like you mean it!
Lady, why do you always attack my feet?
Burn your crude mouth!
Like that is it?
Let's see how you like it
Are you excited?
But you're trying not to show it!
Come on...
Is this dirty stance taught
by Wong Fei Hung?
Wong Fei Hung is not as smart as me
Some more
Red ropes
Let me catch them
It hurts!
Amazing Lantern
Catch it
Master, let me help you
Blow the powder off!
Why are you lying down?
That was a stupid idea
Come on
What...
So many people
Yan!
Master!
Club Foot!
Club Foot is missing too
Master, only you can save me
Your Excellency
What can I do for you?
I'd like to see Ambassador Henlintak
concerning Wong Fei Hung
Your Excellency,
I've never heard of Wong Fei Hung
In the German Territory,
no one is allowed to interfere
with our judiciary system
You imprisoned him without reason
It's my duty to protect him
Don't you know the leasing terms?
It's an agreement between China and Germany
Change it if you want to
Otherwise, settle it with another war
Damn it!
What barbarians!
Now, even you should follow our judiciary system
I don't think war between us
can be avoided anymore
Indeed, the war will start tomorrow
Our lions are well prepared
to fight with your dragons in the Square!
You will find out whose system is the best
Fine,
I will come for the race!
You will be the losers, for sure
Your Excellency,
What about Wong Fei Hung?
I don't think they'll dare harm him
Let's go back
What the hell happened?
Holy Light shines
It must be a trial of the Cantonese Association!
Why would we be on trial?
The main hall of the Red Lanterns!
Isn't this your main hall?
Yes
We are divided into
Red Lanterns, Blue Lanterns and Green Lanterns
This is our head quarters
And this is where we
execute the foreigners too
I won't care what it is,
I have to go in
Wong Fei Hung
Return my country and my power
I fear no fire or knives
The Heaven's troops come
to expel the foreigners
We will sacrifice our lives
for our beloved country!
Lady Miu San is taking
Wong Fei Hung to greet our Holy Mother
I am Wong Fei Hung,
I come to look for my family and students
If you know where they are, please let me know
Burn the incense for our Holy Mother
Lady Miu San is leading
Wong Fei Hung to greet the Holy Mother
To enter our main hall,
you must go through the
Green Lantern Position first
You will pass the 1st test
only if your feet don't touch the ground
Please!
All right, thank you
Go down
I've kicked them all over
Can you still stand?
Return to normal position
Thank you
Blue Lantern Position, please try
How do I pass it?
This is the Whirl Position
designed by the Blue Lanterns
Cross this big revolving lantern
But you can't tear any of the paper
If you can go through it safely,
then you've passed
Thank you
Watch out
Take it
Ether powder?!
Lady Miu, why are you here to fight with me?
If you want to go out, fight with me
Senior
Give me the sword
Lady Miu
We work for our own master, go now
Thank you
Senior
I am fine, don't worry
Fei Hung
Master
Dad, Club Foot,
are you all right?
We are fine
Master, save us
Fu
Haven't you gone back to Fu-Shan?
You're so mean
The candles are red
The heroes come from the
local organizations
Flying phoenix
from the poles
The dragon is kept in the cabin
The Holy Mother is right here
Poor fellows,
kneel down to worship the Holy Mother
Are you Goddess Lotus?
My family has not offended you.
Why did you kidnap them?
Please let them go
Stepping on the Heaven's ladder
Master, what kind of Kung-fu is it?
She can fly!
It's just some tricks!
Our country is in trouble,
everyone is responsible for her safety
You should carry the duty
to expel the foreign devils
I think you should join us and be the boxers
Join the boxers?
I've no relationship with any God or ghosts.
I think, you'd better seek help from others
Wong Fei Hung,
why are you so stubborn?
I have to punish you on behalf of our God
The paper troops,
listen to my order
Juggle
Do you think such tricks can save our country?
Do you want me to set them free? It's simple
If you can pass through my
holy tower and holy bridge.
I will let your men go
If not...
You must follow me
Well,
I have to offend you then
Walk on the holy ladder
Catch!
Take it back
Ah, it's just wires
Ok, let me come up and play with you
Right ladies, let's test your balancing skills
Now, only the Holy Mother is left
You will be my student!
Double Dragon's stance
Master's feet are tied
Go down
Not that easy
Come here
All right!
Cut!
Take it back
Come up
Cross the bridge
Your bridge is ruined,
why don't you release us now?
Retreat!
Master, my money was on you!
No... I mean.
I was sure you'd defeat them
Burn the bridge
Fei Hung
How are you?
I am fine
Fei Hung,
I was worried about you
It's a mess, a mess
If Aunt Yee sees Master holding Aunt May,
there'll be trouble
Fei Hung, it's fine, let's write to Aunt Yee
to tell her we're safe
Aunt Yee is enough, how can he court Aunt May?
Aunt Ching will come
next month... Oh my God!
What is it?
Who's there?
I want to comfort that lady
But you don't know her
So how can you comfort her?
If I don't comfort her,
how can I get to know her?
They are back! Come out!
Master, master
Are you all right?
I am fine
Of course, they can't
compete with master at all
How are you, sir!
I'm glad you're back
Old Master Wong, Master Wong
We were thinking of ways to save you all night
Then we discovered
the Red Lantern Sect had visited
We've just sent someone to rescue you,
but you are back now
Sorry for worrying you
Time
Shit, it's started
Master Wong
Your Excellency
General Guan has instructed us
that if we see you
we should ask you to go
to Tun Chau Square at once
The Dragons and the Lions are fighting now
What?
The Lion King Competition is being held today?
Right, The Lion King Competition organized by
the 8 countries is being held today
Right, Master, it's today
Why are you so excited?
I thought you'd forgot
Think again!
Your Excellency,
please show me they way
Fine
Fei Hung
Aunt May
Brother-in-law,
let me go with you
If anything happened,
how could I explain it to your sister?
Club Foot, follow me
Yes Master!
Ah Fu
Why are you standing there?
Come on now!
So childish
Childish
Bastard! What a copy cat
Our nine golden dragons
must stay alert
Under the bait,
there are machine guns
Nine Dragons set out
They are blocking our way,
we've to find a way out
Dragons in the sky
Dragons in the sky...
The Yellow and the
Red Dragon are destroyed
There are many enemies,
you'd better be more careful
Got you!
Halt!
We are the competitors
The competition had started,
leave now
What did he say?
He said the competition has started
We are not allowed to go in
How come!
Master, let me talk to him
Consider it carefully Fei Hung
Fu, Club Foot, let's go
Forget about them,
let's rush in
Fine
Don't let them leave
They have gone that way
Don't let them get away
Ride on it's back
Be careful of it changing position
Catch the dragon head
Let me ride that horse
The dragon of the Blue Clan is in trouble
Take the wounded away
Yes Sir!
The great eagle is coming
White dragon, watch out!
Yellow dragon, be careful!
Sir, the red dragon is trapped
Close the gate, hurry up
Prepare to fire weapons,
close the gate now
Close the gate
Fei Hung, they are trying to close the gate
They won't!
Hurry up, they are chasing us
Don't be afraid, I am here
Club Foot, you have no horse,
you can't catch up with us
Open it, quick
Yes!
Let's see who's faster
Damn you Clubfoot, how dare you
step on my shoulders?
They are shooting...
Get down!
Fei Hung, we've made it
Watch out, it's coming
Just our dragon is left
His Excellency is in the middle
It's oil, let's escape
Hurry up
Sir
Fei Hung
- Sir
Wong Fei Hung
You must take revenge... for me
Your Excellency...
We were too late
What a pity
Your Excellency...
Your Excellency!
The officers from Tai Lei Temple
send their condolences
The Officers from Shun Tin Office
Sirs, thank you for your condolences
His Excellency Li Hung Chang
sends his condolences
His Excellency send his condolences
Wong Fei Hung sends his condolences
A blood letter from Wong Fei Hung
I am the Lion King of Ching Dynasty
I was too late to participate
in the competition last time
Now I am challenging
the lion kings of the 8 countries
If you accept the challenge,
I'll meet you in two days time
in the same square
Let destiny determine who will win or lose
Wong Fei Hung
Does Wong Fei Hung want to take
revenge for Guan Shing-tao?
Fine, tell him that I will give him a chance...
To meet an even worse fate!
Brother Fu, how do I look?
Fine, just look at Clubfoot
so lady like
To be honest, I don't think so
But I am afraid we'll be discovered by others
Don't worry!
If we are discovered,
I'll handle it. Let's go
Sister Fu, what does your lady look like?
She is like me, so lovely
We're so well matched!
Sister Yan, don't run off
It doesn't matter,
we will go for our own targets later
What for?
To look for our own ladies
That's big trouble
This seems to be the road
leading to the rented territory
Who cares if it is or not?
Let's concentrate on the ladies!
Let's go
Master Chiu, why are you looking for me?
I have heard that you are going to challenge
the lions of the 8 countries
Our ancestors have left us something
to combat the "Powerful Fists"
I asked the smith to repair it overnight
I don't know whether it's useful to you or not
The copper lion
Yes
It's made from 90 catties of copper
Look at the craftsmanship in this lion head
It is a work of art
But our students can hardly handle it
If it is useful to you in the competition,
Please take this as a present from our school
Master Chiu
Please rise
Fei Hung, this lion head is much heavier
than normal lion heads
It's not easy to handle
Yes, but there are merits too
The lions of the 8 countries
are strong and powerful
It's useless to rely on our Kung fu against them
We should destroy them by tactics
I agree with you
I would like to accompany you Master Wong
Master Chiu
Father...
Father
The Red Lanterns are here
Red Lanterns?
Listen, keep calm, keep calm
It is not safe here, we'd better leave
Where are you going?
You devils!
Sister, let's chase the devils separately
The rest of you...
Burn the church. Go
Go, chase after the devils
Yes!
It's on fire
What? On fire?
Where is on fire?
It should be the East Alley
The church of Father Thomas is over there
I have to take a look
Fu
What's the matter?
The Red Lantern ladies are burning and killing,
what'll we do?
Don't disclose our identities
Leave at once
Freeze
I know you are men posing as women
So, you've seen through our disguise
Ladies, castrate them
We are in danger!
Let's run for our lives!
Where are you going?
Club Foot, let's go separately
So, whom should I go with?
Kill them right here
Wong Fei Hung?!
Go
Why don't you go now?
Go now
Oh... He asked us to go
This way is safe
This way
May, you'd better stop searching
for Fei Hung with us
Well, I will wait for you right here
Master Chiu, let's search for
Fei Hung separately
Fine
Go over there
Sister, the foreigners are over there
Let's attack them from both sides
OK, follow me
Yes!
Father Thomas, are you all right?
Heaven have mercy
My child, the Red Lanterns are after us,
run for your life!
Go that way
It's you?!
Yes, it's me
What bad luck!
Father, you are here!
It's you
Go over there.
Let me fight with them
Go!
Yes, Senior
Ladies, no massacre please,
they're innocent!
If you want to kill, kill me first
Get lost,
you have no say here
Catch them and kill them right here
Yes
Let's run for our lives
I'll kill the woman,
you take the foreigners!
Sister, stop!
Father
You!
Kill the devils!
Sister
He saved me once
You liar!
You are the betrayer!
When Wong Fei Hung came to our hall,
I started to suspect you
Now, I'm proved right!
You are not qualified to hold
this Anti-foreigner's Flag
Shoot!
Senior!
She deserved it,
God will punish her
Miss
Let's go
Get lost, forget about me
Don't leave me alone!
I didn't betray you
Die bitch!
Let's see your magic now!
Miss
Stop!
Help!
Fei Hung?!
Take her away
Prepare to fire!
You are hurt, why do you still want to fight?
Don't go!
Move her over there
She's been hurt.
She must be cold
Use this to cover her
It's dark! I can't see anything
What a fate!
Where is Wong Fei Hung?
Fei Hung...
Where is he?
He is here
You're not him!
I'd never have believed
I'd die saving the devils!
It's my punishment!
I may die in peace now
Wong Fei Hung, at last, you've come
Brother Fu, let's go
Brother Fu, the Holy Mother is coming
Brother Club Foot,
come and save us!
Go to hell
Stay where you are!
I want to punish you
Club Foot, are you all right?
I'm fine
Take aim!
The symbol of heresy!
Should we save her?
How?
We are wearing the uniforms
If we go out like this,
we will be shot at
I'm Goddess Lotus,
the spirit resides in me
I'm invincible!
How dare you offend me!
I've to punish you on behalf of God
I'll send you to hell!
To tear your skin off!
To break your bones!
You bastards!
Let's go
Master
The three of you, stay where you are
Club Foot? Ah Fu? Ah Yan?
Why are you dressed like this?
Are you going to be opera actors?
You had it coming!
Holy Mother...
Don't cry, tears can't help
Right, Holy Mother hasn't passed away,
she is living in our hearts
Let's take an oath, we should
carry on the mission
of killing the foreigners!
Kill the foreigners,
save our beloved country!
This bait could hurt us anytime
If the opposite side use fire.
Getting the bait is less important
than beating their lions
Let's attack them remember
Yes, Master
Music!
The lions roar!
Each lion attack a monster
Yes!
"One step to the sky"!
Stop turning!
We can't turn
"Magic Turn"!
I want you to "turn round and round"
Old Master Wong, I can't
identify the flag in the front
It's so messy,
I can't identify either
Forget the flags,
let's recognise their face
Should we beat this one?
No, not this...
Club Foot, hold this for me
I feel better having no lion head
But, how am I going to handle
two lion heads?
You are abnormal anyway
The may be scared of you
holding two lion heads!
That's it
It's our turn!
All right!
"Swinging lion tail"!
Come on...
Fu, what are you doing?
You should be careful!
"Tiger jump"!
Come on...
Why has it gone dark?
Where am I?
Who are you?
Big head Buddha,
don't you recognise me?
Let me show you
Some more!
You want to fire?
Not that easy!
Here comes a cookie!
This one is even better,
I'll leave it with you
Let's help old Master
Attack!
Master Chiu, watch out!
Catch the lion tail
So you are scared away?
Brother Fu, look out behind!
How dare you scare me?!
The sun will soon go down
behind The Forbidden City
History will be re-written
We'll see who is going to be the winner
Throw the burning lion heads up here
Yes!
The bait?!
Ah Yan
Ah Yan!
Take cover!
My ass is shot! Take me out!
Go!
Club Foot, come over here, be quick!
Master, let me send you up there
General, leave here quickly
We won
General Henlintak
Good news
Long live Germany!
Long live America!
What has happened?
Why are they so cheerful?
Bull shit, they are celebrating for us
It's bull shit indeed!
Let's go and take a look
I can't see them, move forward
Move forward
Yes
Fei Hung
Sir, why are you dressed like that?
The allied troops of the 8 foreign countries have
marched into the Forbidden City
The Empress Dowager has surrendered
Master Wong, let's go
Let's go!
Although we won this competition,
we lost our country!
Henlintak
General, go to the celebration now,
let us handle Wong Fei Hung
Wait for me
Fei Hong
Henlintak!
Get lost, don't block my way
Wong Fei Hung
I am here
Hurry up
Don't go. Protect the General
What's happening?
Henlintak, get down!
Lui, protect the general
Henlintak!
Wong Fei Hung!
Master!
Let me handle this
Go down
Club Foot!
Try my kick!
Watch out!
General
Do you wanna escape
Do you want to cuff me?
Watch my kick
Club Foot,
I'm going to kill you
Not that easy
Try my "Scissors kick"!
Henlintak!
Strike!
You had it coming!
Lui
Master
Club Foot, let me handle it!
Master, let me handle it!
Strike!
Eat dirt!
I wanna break your leg!
Go and protect the general
Go
Wanna escape?
Club Foot they have guns!
Fire
Let's go!
Master,
shall we let them escape?
We can't change anything
by killing him
Let's go
Master!
Master
Are you seriously hurt?
No!
Fei Hung
Brother
It's dangerous here, we'd better leave
Dad, let's go back to the South
Yes. Our capital is occupied.
We should go back and prepare to retaliate
OK, let's go back to the South, now
Get in
I can't sit down!
My ass hurts!
Lie down then
Subtitles adapted by Peacht
acfmovies.com