Get down! Get down!
We've a man down, PC 1667 call an ambulance!
Sam...
I took that bag of money...
to pay the loan sharks...
but they found me...
I told them your plans...
I'm responsible... for the death of the team
I'm so sorry...
Wing...
I'm sorry...
Stay calm! Get down!
Stay where you are! Don't move!
Frank!
You're the man!
Inspector Tai!
I bow to you...
as soon as you return you cause problems
I have 72 complaints...
from other...
governmental departments...
and citizens
You tell me...
what to say to them
Sorry, sir
We found the gang that robbed the Bank of Asia
Wait, when did you come back?
You had me brought back
I did?
You told PC 1667...
Do you make noodles for everyone?
No
Noodles are comforting
When I need comforting, I think of you
It's that simple?
What more do you want?
Inspector Chan?
We were just talking about you
I'm busy
Why are you impersonating a policeman?
More than 10 years ago,
a man stole food for his son
When he came out of the store,
he was run over by a truck
A kind policeman...
I gave you a chance to explain.
Why are you still lying?
I'm telling the truth
You are not Kwong's younger brother
Who are you?
I've always wanted to be a policeman,
but I couldn't
To me, be a good policeman...
Why did you get into my business?
True, I'm not a policeman
but did I ever harm you?
No, neither did I
Nor will he
I've told Sasa's friends...
they must win the game
Then we'll know their next move
Believe me
Do you regret being with me?
We have composites of the suspects
Sasa
Sue Chow, daughter of a shipping magnate
She's disappeared
Fire, son of a jewelry tycoon
Ex-US Marine
This Ferrari is owned by Tin Tin Law
His father is president of Kam Fuk Securities
Max Leung, genius game creator
Father is Wing Yu International's K. H. Leung
Mother is Japanese
Joe Kwan works for his mother
He studied in America
An under-achiever
Most importantly...
his father is a policeman
Chief superintendent of Northern District
All from rich families
They have no purpose in life
Track him
Chan Kwok Wing, senior inspector
He was suspended one year after our incident
His girlfriend won't marry him
If you want to be a policeman,
why don't you join the academy?
Because my dad was a thief
Don't you dare lie to me again
He's toying with you
That's your girlfriend's home
I'm best of the best at games
Play with me, and you'll lose
Leave her alone
Sorry, whatever I say goes
Game start, at police headquarters
Bye!
Ho Yee, what brings you here?
I got a call, they said Inspector Chan's in
trouble
And told me to come see him
Nothing happened here
Wait in the briefing room, I'll go get him
Okay
Okay, bye Okay
Ho Yee?
Yes
I called you
What happened to him?
He's coming; I'm his good friend
Please give this to him
This bomb must be kept stable
if the balls are not centered...
the bomb will explode so don't move
You have 10 minutes
I wanted to give it to him myself
I'm sure you can do that for me
Thanks so much
Ho Yee's waiting for you in the briefing room
Thanks
Get everyone out!
It's a bomb, run!
Call the bomb squad!
Don't be afraid
What do we do?
Help me carry her to the safe room
Remember the balls must remain centered
Got it
Just go
1...
2...
My foot's numb
It's okay
Let her sit
Wait
It's usually the red wire...
or blue, or yellow...
Get out of here!
Inspector Chan!
Ho Yee!
Don't be afraid!
I'm not
As long as you're here,
I'm not afraid of anything
Sorry
Like you, my brother was also a policeman
I knew something might happen to him
If I must blame someone, I'd blame his killers
I never blamed you for his death
You know how much it hurts me...
to see you like this, this past year?
Put the safe room on screen!
I'm Inspector Chik from the bomb squad
What's the situation?
I think I've stabilized it
There are circuit boards in different layers
It could be any wire
Don't cut any of them
each circuit has a feedback
Any wire may trigger the bomb
I couldn't save Hong
But I must save you
You may think I'm stupid but...
Do you love me?
In this life and the next...
I will love you
Last option, freeze it chemically
Be right back
She's cutting the wires!
Ho Yee!
It could be a fake
Get out of there!
Wait
Don't move What?
Run!
Ho Yee!
Ho Yee...
Stay with me...
Wake up...
Please!
You've been accused of helping
someone to impersonate an officer...
and bombing the police department
They're all aroused by your matters private
You're under arrest!
Give me a cigarette, sir
Quit, you'll get cancer
Don't worry, they'll let you go
You did it to yourself
What are you doing?
Our lawyer Come here
What's going on?
We fear police harassment
We're here to I.D. hi m
The SP okayed this
Inspector Chan
How's your girlfriend?
We'd like to visit her
Go near the hospital and I'll kill you
What are you trying to do?
Should we also charge him with...
threatening us?
Of course
To be honest, we hate you stinking cops!
We're robbing another bank tonight
The game continues
Joe Kwan, I'll personally get you
Anytime
After you get out
The bank is on the top floor
with $100 million cash
It's show time
Let me make a call
I want to make bail
Sorry, can't help you
I want to get them too
Sasa
What's up?
Well?
I couldn't
Heartless!
Try to get me out...
or many will die tonight
How?
I'll have to kill him
if I want to break you out
Tell me how!
Think of something!
Dad told me to join the police...
because they are righteous
Tomorrow I quit
I don't want to see my Dad again
I'm going to the toilet
Dad, you go so often
Are you sick?
Come with me Okay
They can't see me
Bring it back when you're done
Thank you
Oh, my god! I've died and gone to heaven!
In a game, new directions
are given at each level
They are crazy
If we win the game...
we'll find the next target
Mission complete, Terrorists neutralized
I did it! Yeah!
Bank of Hong Kong?
It's in the Convention Center
Whatever you do...
keep our men away
Call the police
Don't be afraid. Just call the police
Big guy
What?
Hong Kong police; we need...
your telescope
There they are!
Do you have a phone?
Let me use it, thanks
999 emergency
Sasa, make some calls for me
Hurry, I can't hold them off
They will trace my line
Just make those calls
Inspector Chan!
Stop them!
We'll raise the stakes
Double points for hitting each cop
Joe, there are so many people down there
Do we still shoot?
Don't panic the crowd.
Get them out, one by one
Please come, miss
Miss...
Please come here
Something's wrong, Joe
We'd better go
Shut up!
Fire, over there
Mom and Dad?
Why are they here?
So many cops? Where's your son?
What's going on? Do you see them?
Where is my son?
Up there, robbing the bank
Robbing? Impossible!
My son is a robber?
I'll give you $1 million to kill my dad
$2 million to kill mine
Here is Convention Centre
One by one, come in
There he is!
Max, come back!
Come back, Max!
Max!
Max, come back!
Max, where are you going?
Stay calm!
Son!
Are you okay?
Go!
Chan!
Don't go there, call the SDU
Inspector Chan?
Joe, I've been shot! Help!
I don't want mom and dad to see me
Go...
Last time we tied; let's go again
Okay
Run!
Come on!
Come!
You lose
Police! Drop your weapons!
Damn it!
Hands on your head!
Get down!
I'm a cop!
Who are you?
I'm Senior Inspector Chan
Someone's been shot! Call an ambulance!
Who is he?
He's bleeding badly, save him!
He's dying
Hurry!
It's really Chan!
Call an ambulance!
Freeze!
Okay
Drop your gun
Joe, give up, you're surrounded by cops
Really?
I'm not afraid
I'll take you both with me
But I'm not a cop!
If you kill me, you'll still lose
Joe, you don't hate the police
You hate your dad and yourself
Shut up!
Your friends are dead
No one else should die
It's game over
I don't lose, I've never lost
I want to play one last game
You're on!
The rules?
Same game, for his life!
I accept
You're my man
Call it
Go
Joe!
What are you doing?
Control yourself!
You've totally embarrassed me
Joe!
Give up
How can I live this down!
Drop your gun!
Son of a bitch!
Trash!
You're killing me!
You will ruin me!
Son of a bitch!
Give up!
Drop your gun!
No!
His gun is empty!
Son...
Hold on!
You're letting me go!
I know!
Hold on tighter!
I won't let... you...
drop
You said you'd hold tighter!
You try it!
I suffer more than you!
Thanks, everyone
Inspector Chan...
At least untie me!
Ho Yee, you're recovered
You're discharged now
Bye
Be happy
Rest well
Goodbye
Salute!
Don't hide your face, no matter what,
I want to marry you
Marry Inspector Chan!
Marry him!
How touching!
Let's go
Where to?
Take my statement
At my proposal...
I want even more police
How about phony ones?
That'll do
What's up, Tsuen?
I've been here over a month
My wife is waiting for news from me
I'm broke; I need a loan
You promised...
Dad
I'm hungry
Wait here Frankie
Stop!
Run!
Call the police! Thief!
Quick!
Freeze!
Run!
Dad...
You rotten thief
Inspector Chan
Thieves have dignity too; get an ambulance
Yes, sir
Kid
This is the way of the world,
it's full of injustice
Many things can make you sad
Forget the past, when you
grow up be a good man
Okay?
What's your name?
I'm Frank Cheng