Look, look! They're shooting at us.
Fire!
It's just a dragon dance!
Return to your posts!
Start drumming!
Yes!
Master Wong,
watch out for the gunfire!
- Can you make it?
- Yes!
Give me the tail!
Monumental Bravery
Limitless Trust
Look over there, Wong Fei-Hung...
more and more foreign ships
are anchoring in our docks.
Britain was given Hong Kong,
Portugal was given Macao,
Russia occupies Hak Lung Gong.
Our country is divided
and I'm being sent to Vietnam
to fight the French.
How will the Vietnamese
react to this plaque here
that says "Our land, our people"?
Step forward!
Yes, Your Excellency!
Take it down! Quick!
Wait a minute!
Excellency, the Government
changes its policies so often
you could be called back soon.
The Government is factionalised,
and has reduced my army.
I fear that, while I'm gone,
the men that remain here
will be dismissed.
You're the chief trainer
of my Black Flag Army.
I hope you'll organise them
into a local militia.
So that if China comes under foreign attack,
they can defend it.
Master Wong...
Get up!
Excellency, don't worry!
I hope you'll return soon.
Wong Fei-Hung,
the unjust treaties forced upon us
are written on this fan.
When you see it, think of me.
When I return, I hope the treaties
will have been erased.
Pork buns!
God Loves the World
Here they come.
What are you talking about?
The town's full of foreigners.
You're very smart
to do business with them.
I couldn't make it in China,
so I went to England.
Let's take a photo
with Chu's pet bird.
What an honour
for our feathered friend!
Don't mention it.
Let's take your picture, too!
Thank you very much.
Master Wong...
How is everyone?
Fei-Hung!
Great Uncle, it's been a while.
You're looking good.
Thank you!
Fei-Hung, see who I brought with me?
Master Wong! Had tea yet?
Everyone's waiting for you.
- 13th Aunt.
- Fei-Hung!
She wants to shake your hand.
It's a foreign custom.
Let me introduce you.
This is Joanna.
How do you do?
Do?
She's asking how do you do?
Say, "Thank you".
Oh, "kill you".
Fei-Hung, let's take a photo
with the bird. OK?
OK.
Sit down...
Fei-Hung, taking photos is simple.
How does it work?
Look there.
Don't move or the photo
won't look good. Sit up.
Ready! One, two, three!
What happened?
That's boiling water!
Are you OK? Are you hurt?
I'm all right!
This foreign game is too dangerous.
Too much powder
You told me not to move!
Are you all right?
Yes.
Grand Uncle,
I'm glad you asked me here
or you could've ended up like the bird.
Do you think so?
Chu!
I'll go back to England in a few days.
Yee was in England,
but she insisted on coming back.
At least this way, she won't mix
with those foreigners any more.
Take care of her for me.
Take care of her?
Chu, say something.
You're scaring me!
Anyone here?
I'm looking for Master Wong.
Is anyone here?
Who is it?
What's up?
I'm from May County.
M... ay... May... May.
I'm Leung Foon.
I want Master Wong to teach me.
- He...
- He's not here?
- I...
- You?
- Wong... Master Wong...
- You're Master Wong?
- No... yes!
- Ah, so you're Master Wong?!
I was practising kung fu on my cows,
when one kicked my arm.
Please take a look.
Good!
Not that one, this one.
Master Wong,
why are you plastering my leg?
I only hurt my arm.
Too... late... now!
It's stiff, Master.
Why is it stiff?
Are you... all right?
Oh, I get it!
You want to teach me kung fu?
Roll? You want me to Roll?
I said no, not roll.
I'm good. Even in plaster.
I can move like lightening.
Not a bad stance.
Stupid.
Still not good enough?
I'll keep trying!
I'll show you a few more rolls.
What's all this noise?
Who's he?
Master is teaching me kung fu!
Buck Teeth So
is teaching you kung fu?
- Who are you?
- Buck Teeth So!
- You're not Master Wong?
- Stupid
Buck Teeth So? Who are you?
He is Master Wong's student.
And who are you?
I'm also Master Wong's student, Kai.
What happened to you?
Don't ask. I have to get back
to the theatre.
I'm off.
I'm off before he plasters
my other side.
Foon, have you finished mending
that hole in the roof?
The show will start soon!
I'm here to act,
and you make me fix the roof.
It's not fair! I'm scared of heights.
If you can't play this role,
how do I know you can act?
When I'm famous,
I'll send you up here to mend the roof.
What are you doing? Summersaults?
What are you playing at?
I thought it was the ship's cannon.
You wish! It's only thunder.
Cannonfire is good luck.
Maybe we'll all go
and mine gold in America.
Then we wouldn't have to suffer here.
Country bumpkins... so stupid!
Don't move or you'll spoil it!
Are you ready?
A foreign woman speaking Chinese?
China will be taken over
by foreigners soon.
Wait for me!
- One, two...
- Wait for me!
Wait for you?
It's stuck!
Foon, where the hell are you?
I'm changing!
Hurry up! Don't be so lazy!
Foon, you brag about your kung fu.
You can't even climb the roof
to fix something.
You broke the stage
with a somersault.
You show me how to do it
if you're so good.
Miss, I had your dirty clothes
washed and ironed.
Thank you!
Do you need fresh water?
No, I'm almost done.
Who is it?
You're naked!
I'll invite you to our new show.
Thank you, Boss!
- Take care, the path is slippery!
- Bye bye
A Chinese
pretending to be a foreigner!
Miss...
...your umbrella!
Sir, what's your hurry?
Come up,
there are lots of girls here!
It takes so long.
Don't move!
A gunshot! What's the matter?
Who is it?
Master!
- Master!
- It's Wing. Open the door.
Master!
You opened the door just in time.
I nearly broke it down!
Have lunch with me sometime.
Excuse me!
Kai, who's been shot?
The greengrocer.
Who shot him?
I don't know. Ask Master.
Buck Teeth So, if I wasn't here,
you'd have broken that!
Por... ky... Porky...
My name's Wing. Call me Porky
again and I'll get mad.
Back so long and you still
can't speak Chinese.
- Por... ky...
- Bu... ck... Tee... th.
So, bring the medicine.
You can't handle the medicine!
What are you arguing about?
Master, I'm teaching him
how to be Chinese.
- Give me The Magic Healer.
- The Magic Healer.
3, they're all 3 characters.
Master, you know I can't read!
And you laugh at those
who can't speak Chinese?
Come on, So.
Powder for Seven Cuts.
Blood-Clotting Powder.
So is from America.
He studied medicine there
and learns bone setting here.
Then he must be smart.
Master, here's the water.
Finally.
Take a rest, you'll be fine.
Master, this bullet is from a shotgun.
Let's bandage him.
There are many ships, he can't tell
American and British flags apart.
He boarded the wrong ship
and got shot.
The country's being sold off
piece by piece.
When they argue, it's we who suffer.
We can't accept this kind of
treatment any more!
The Manchurians have taken our land.
Now they join the foreigners
and sell out our country!
Brothers of the Local Militia,
let's fight!
- Ca... ca... calm down!
- You're lecturing me?
Por... ky...
Watch your mouth! I'm your senior!
- Wing!
- Master!
You're too rash. Keep out of this.
This is a matter of life or death.
I must meet with the authorities
and the Westerners.
Otherwise how are we to survive in Fatshan?
Excuse me sir,
you would like something?
So, you explain to the captain.
Yes!
Excuse me,
we have an appointment in this restaurant
with Mr. Jackson of the Sino Pacific Corporation
and General Wickens of the British Forces.
I presume they would have
reserved a table for us.
So we can begin to discuss
this matter more leisurely.
This is my master, Wong Fei Hung.
And I'd be grateful
if you'd show us the table.
How... come... your... English...
is... so... fluent?
This way please.
Why so many daggers?
Excuse me, sir.
Your menu, sir.
So, ask them to bring us
some dim sum.
Foon, your job
is to check tickets today.
I'm here to learn acting
not check tickets.
It doesn't suit me.
It can't be helped.
The others have gone
to America to mine gold.
America?! Gold mining?
Boss, is there really gold there?
Would I lie to you?
It's all in the newspaper.
I'd go too if I didn't have to
run this place.
Newspaper?! What newspaper?
They're here for protection money.
You haven't paid?
Yes I have,
but these thugs are from Shaho.
How dare they make trouble
so far from their turf?
If they mess with me, they've had it!
Yes...
What are you doing?
I know you know some kung fu.
Didn't you say you
wanted to show off your stuff?
Here's your chance.
Boss, I'm not that good.
They've come to pay their respects
especially to you.
I'm being set up. Stop!
Boss, open the gate!
Boss, open up. Quick!
Oh, there's no daytime show.
No tickets left.
- Thank you, Boss. I'll come another time.
- Hey kid, come on down!
I came all this way, and no show.
Next time I won't bother.
I know you're Foon.
You've got something to say?
I'm just the ticket collector.
We're the collectors here.
You must be quite a guy...
facing us all alone.
You've got guts!
Got guts...
You must be joking.
Let me buy you a gift.
No need.
No need for gifts,
just give me a hand.
Go on, chop it off.
Chop my hand off?
I'll chop your mother's head off!
Don't go!
Come on!
Me against all of you isn't fair!
Let's fight one on one another time!
Why not now?
Get him! Stop!
Someone's fighting in the theatre.
They're armed!
Stop! Stop! Get him!
Excuse me, excuse me!
What's happening?
A fight!
Fight outside,
we're doing business here. Out!
What is it, brother?
They want money,
and they want to fight me for it.
There are too many of them.
Kill that asshole!
Sounds like trouble.
Let's take a look.
That's Porky,
one of Wong's disciples.
Never met him.
Porky, out of respect for your master.
I'll let you off.
You're Master Wong's disciple?
I am!
I saw this young doctor
at Bo Chi Lam.
Buck Teeth So
That Chinese American.
- Foon!
- What?
I'm not kidding,
if you don't bring a hand to Shaho...
they'll be digging
your grave in Fatshan!
Let's go back to Shaho!
What? Turning chicken just
because Wong's disciple is here?
You want a hand?
This pig will donate one!
Big brother, what shall we do?
Do? Tear them apart!
Brother Wing, this one's for him!
He can have it for free.
You asshole!
Shaho's stupid, Shaho's dumb...
You want to mess with me?
I'll beat you to death.
Have some refreshments,
enjoy the show!
Take that! Hold it!
Add a little water,
make a perfect brew.
Who's throwing boiling water?
Find him! Go look up there!
Who threw the boiling water?
Out! Go!
You old bastard,
it must have been you!
No it wasn't. I'm just eating.
Really?
And that, Your Excellency, is the
position of Her Majesty's Government.
May I suggest that
we leave it at that?
Your Government is most generous.
Wong Fei-Hung,
Wickens of the British forces
and Mr. Jackson of
the Sino Pacific Corporation.
They've kindly agreed
not to press charges.
So stop seeking damages
for the greengrocer.
This is unfair.
The people are outraged.
Outraged?!
Wong, you have no authority.
You are a mere civilian.
Who are you to negotiate?
This is a new age
of international cooperation.
It's better to keep the peace.
These rolls are made from our flour.
So you appreciate western food?
The foreigners draw boundaries here
and set up forbidden areas.
If we fight amongst ourselves
and keep bowing to them,
we'll lose more than flour.
I know you are friends with Lau,
Commander of the Black Flag Army.
He doesn't follow orders
from the Central Government.
I've been sent here to watch you.
I intend to set an example
here in Fatshan.
Are you all right?
What is all this?
Master, it's our Local Militia.
Master Wong!
Stop them!
Stop!
Don't fight!
Kai, I told you
to tell them not to fight!
He told you not to fight!
Put down your weapons!
You still want to fight?
Don't move.
I expect you'd have an explanation
for this disgraceful intrusion.
Good day!
General Wickens.
- You're not bad!
- Of course!
Boss, that looks like Wong Fei-Hung.
Master Wong Fei-Hung.
He's outnumbered! Let's take him on!
Don't fight!
Did he hit you? Don't fight!
Don't fight, Kai!
I told you not to fight!
I said don't fight!
You're still fighting?!
Are you sure?
They're coming. Let me go!
Boss, are you all right?
- Who kicked me?
- I don't know!
- Have you taken them on?
- Yes, we have!
Carry on!
- Buck Teeth So!
- Stupid!
I'm so sorry!
So, tell them
it's all a misunderstanding.
No need to explain.
If China had no forbidden areas,
we'd all be in danger.
Master, this alien can speak Chinese.
You still want to fight?
Don't call me an alien, you devil!
Listen, we're here to do business.
Don't let this kind of crap
keep us from making big money
Otherwise you'll get yourself
in real trouble.
Goodbye, aliens!
Tiger let's go!
Shoot on sight. Run! Run!
The authorities are here!
Let's get out of here!
Stop! Stay where you are!
Drop your weapons.
Why are the Local Militia fighting?
Where's Porky? Gone?
Don't move or we'll shoot.
Wong, this area's administered
by the foreigners,
yet the Local Militia
dare make trouble here!
You're their leader.
Explain yourself!
Excellency, as trained soldiers,
these men wouldn't act
without a good reason.
Soldiers? They're trash
the government discarded.
They're under our command now.
Excellency...
Tell them report to City Hall,
or get arrested!
Excellency!
Master Wong will pay
for all the damages.
Yes, Your Excellency!
Beware of fire!
Beware of thieves!
Master, I've lost my appetite.
All this trouble was started
by a gang from Shaho.
Now we have to report to City Hall.
Are they going to arrest us?
Master!
Sit down! City Hall's authorised
to look into this.
If it's a set-up,
they'll find out.
So, let's eat. Until the verdict is known,
this'll be our last meal together.
Let's eat.
Attention, Militia men,
prepare to eat.
Pick up vegetables!
Eat rice!
Swallow!
Pick up vegetables!
Eat rice!
Swallow!
13th Aunt!
Don't worry,
your men will be fine.
It's late, why aren't you sleeping?
I want to take your measurements for a suit.
A suit?
Why would I want a western suit?
It's for when you go abroad.
13th Aunt,
is the West really so wonderful?
What do we have to learn from the foreigners?
They invented the steam engine
and many other things.
We must move with the times.
When we have time,
you must tell me more
about the world beyond China.
13th Aunt,
if the western world was so great,
why did you come back?
There are still some things here
they haven't got.
Such as?
People.
I missed some people very much.
I was abroad for two years,
but my heart was here.
You were always in my thoughts.
You are very kind.
- 13th Aunt!
- What's wrong?
I thought... No, it's nothing!
Fei-Hung, you and I
are relatives by name,
not by blood.
We were raised together,
don't call me 13th Aunt.
What else should I call you?
I'll do it.
What's this? It doesn't matter!
It doesn't matter?
Of course it does,
one must be precise.
Chinese shouldn't wear suits.
Chinese are Chinese,
Westerners Western.
There will be railways
and a telegraph company soon.
Everything will change.
China will change with the world.
You're right. Western guns
and ships are already here.
Everything is changing.
What will we change into? Who knows?
I appreciate your gift,
but you keep it.
When all Chinese wear suits,
I'll wear one.
Come greet the God of Fortune!
Here I am, the God of Fortune!
Get out of my way, you bloody priest!
Fortune?
Sir, we already bought
the God of Fortune.
Come greet the God of Fortune!
Sir, we already bought the God of Fortune!
Sir...
Did you buy protection from me,
or the other guy?
He's rotting in a ditch.
Want to see him?
Just buy a new one!
If I pay him, what happens
when the other guy comes?
Sir, do you need help?
You should join us!
- Life is tough right now!
- Give it all
so we can take care of you.
Sir, don't clean me out,
give me a break.
And who'll give me a break?
Hand it over!
Robbing your own people!
It's Master Wong!
You're from Shaho?
Come with me to City Hall.
Save me!
Stabbing your own people?
Get going! Run!
Quick! Run!
Where have you cowards run to?
Damn you!
It's too high!
Run
All right! That's amazing!
Did you see
the speed of that kick?
- Did you see it?
- No, it was too fast.
Listen to me. This man is a gangster.
I'm taking him to City Hall.
Please come and testify against him.
Incredible!
What a jump!
Boss,
he demanded protection money from you.
Come with me and be a witness.
Me?
And fear for my life,
like the theatre boss does?
You two were practising kung fu in there,
I didn't see any fighting.
In America,
people have to walk carefully.
Why?
Because they might trip on all the gold.
- Is that true?
- There's more!
If you wash your face in the river,
you'll find gold.
Is it really that wonderful?
Of course it is!
One visit to America is worth
a lifetime of work in China.
Come on, take a leaflet!
There's one for everyone.
People in America wear
dark glasses day and night.
It's so bright it hurts your eyes.
You can't pick up gold
if you're blind.
My poor lost sheep,
God's Kingdom belongs to you.
You're promoting America, too?
Material things are transient.
Only Jesus is the truth.
Come to Jesus. He forgives all sins.
I arrested a criminal today.
Will Jesus be my witness?
Beware of thieves.
Beware of fire.
Boss!
- Boss, Are you over there?
- I'm here!
Get ready!
- Master!
- How are you?
Are you crazy? Fans in this weather.
So, the Governor has locked up
the Local Militia?
He won't release them
till the suspects are caught.
Master!
I can't be a witness
because I'm a suspect.
They even let Hung of Shaho go.
When will our men be released?
When a witness comes forward.
Master, what about Foon?
- Foon? Do you know him?
- Yes.
You must be mixed up in this.
What are you hiding?
I...
Master, you don't always trust me.
So, I...
What? Speak!
Mas... Mas... Master... The... There...
Fire...
Calm down, So. Don't panic!
Master!
So!..
Master, what shall we do?
Those arrows came from the roof.
I'm coming!
Never mind me.
Gather... the valuables!
Kai, get your weapon.
We'll take them on.
Wing, put out the fire. I'm off.
Alone?
Damn!
So! Here!
Goddamn steps!
His Excellency's fan?! Here it is!
Wow, the roof's like a furnace!
It's like hell down here!
Someone's on the roof. Shoot him!
It's Master Wong. Run!
Bo Chi Lam is on fire!
Don't forget the camera, hurry up!
Bo Chi Lam will be lost forever.
What Are you doing?
Taking a photo of Bo Chi Lam.
You'll be burned alive!
You're blocking the sign!
A little more, I can't see you.
Should we wait for Master?
The... roof... is... is on fire!
So, look this way!
Kai, shift a little to the right.
I thought I had it with me.
But I was taking pictures
of the clinic. So, I...
You're just like the foreigners!
Don't ever bring this
into the clinic again...
or I'll throw it away!
His Excellency the Governor is here!
Wong Fei-Hung, you open kung-fu schools,
triad societies...
divide up the town
and run illegal businesses.
Now other triads take revenge...
The burning of Bo Chi Lam
is your own fault.
It's time to mend your ways!
Excellency,
mine is not a triad society.
If the authority
labels martial arts illegal,
then our grand tradition will be lost.
So when we are attacked,
how will we defend ourselves?
Is that what you call
preserving the peace?
You can't even save your clinic
and you dare lecture me!
It's your job
to investigate the fire.
You tell me, who did it?
I don't know.
You don't know?!
You're hiding something.
Wing!
Wing, what are you doing?
Master!
Can I come in?
Foreign devil!
- Wing!
- Master!
Go on like this,
and you can stop calling me Master.
Don't go.
You must have a complaint
against Fei-Hung.
You can tell me.
Wong Fei-Hung,
I know who set Bo Chi Lam on fire.
I can be your witness.
Check if anyone's from Shaho.
Yes.
- Hey, are you from Shaho.
- No!
Not the way you talk.
So many people!
Boss, looks like
the Governor's going to arrest you.
Goddamn!
That Jesuit must have squealed.
Shouldn't we go and hide back home?
Never! We're afraid of the Governor.
He's afraid of the foreigners.
So let's find some
influential foreigners!
Wait for me.
We want to speak to Mr. Jackson.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
What's going on down there?
Damn, we've no English. Try harder.
Please, please let us in
to see Mr. Jackson.
We all want to see Mr. Jackson.
Jackson...
I'd better have a cigar.
I don't like cigars.
If I keep a dog,
it'll guard my house.
You are wanted by the Governor.
What good are you to us?
I'm not afraid of being arrested.
But I am afraid that
without a leader,
my brothers' talents
will go to waste.
You came all this way
to make money,
by sending so many Chinese
to America.
Why don't I give you some women
to ship over?
No, we don't allow
the labourers to breed.
Don't allow them to have descendents.
Otherwise they'd stay for good.
Not as wives as hookers.
As many as you want.
It's Wong who's the problem.
Dare you kill him for me?
- Master Wong?!
- Yes...
I'll invite him to the show tomorrow.
He won't get out alive.
Or the authorities.
Do you hear noise?
Something just dropped
into the water.
Wing, the Governor is after
the Shaho Gang.
Foon, where have you been?
I have to go back to the theatre.
Come with me.
Wait. Let me lock up first.
OK!
- Hey, come out first.
- Oh, right!
This is Wing.
He'll solve all your problems.
Master Wong's students. Welcome!
Don't worry.
I'll check the tickets for you.
I like gate duty.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Tickets. Show me your tickets.
Stay in line.
Do you have tickets?
Tickets?
Do you know who I am?
Look at the poster.
He's Wonder Ho, I'm White Gent.
And I'm Wing! No ticket? Go!
The show's starting
and you dare tell us to leave?
OK, we'll go, you'll regret this!
We'll go! We'll go!
Tickets...
Brother Wing, let's go in.
No hurry, the actors aren't here.
Thank you so much.
Have you seen Wonder Ho
and White Gent?
They tried to barge in,
I told them to piss off.
What? They're the actors!
Who will act then?
Then we don't have a show.
You stay here,
I'll go and fetch them.
Tickets...
My Master's coming!
I'm out of here!
Excuse me!
Mr. Jackson, let me introduce you
to the Reverend Father.
Please to meet you, sir.
General Wickens, please take a seat.
So you accepted the invitation!
Please!
13th Aunt!
Master Wong!
Why so formal?
Relatives must respect
the rule of seniority.
OK, let's just watch the show!
Please...
Wing, we're in trouble.
Master's here. I don't want to stay.
The actors are gone.
You're going. What'll I do?
I can sing.
So what?
I can act a little. Let's go!
You dare sing on stage
in front of your Master?
Who's going to recognise us
with make up on?
OK, let's take a chance.
Come backstage.
Lucky you got us
or the show would be cancelled.
I'm amazed you recognised me!
Isn't that Wing?
Who's Wing? Let's go! Come on!
The White Snake is now a Fat Snake.
Porky! Porky!
Hey, Porky Wing's changed profession.
Where will we buy our pork
from now on?
Wing, again!
Nonsense!
I made him do it, don't blame him.
Don't blame him.
Pack up and never come back.
Never come back!
Brother Wing, I'll join you
in the pork business.
Watch out!
Get down!
Seal all exits!
Lead the foreigners out.
Yes, sir!
There's fighting outside.
Foon, it must be the Shaho Gang.
Go after them!
13th Aunt!
Stop it!
The Troops.
Yes, sir.
Get ready.
Don't shoot at the audience.
Don't shoot!
Son...
You fool.
Shoot him.
No!
Limestone powder.
Close your eyes.
Stay down!
It's not Wong?
Forget him!
Protect His Excellency!
Come on.
Gun!
Take cover.
13th Aunt, take the gun
and protect the reverend.
They're here for me. Keep away!
Reverend Father!
Master, take the pole!
Master, I'll help you!
The floor's too thin.
Oh, and who are you?
Protect 13th Aunt! I don't need help.
Leave her alone!
Tiger, use your gun.
You idiot, shoot him dead.
Shoot them.
No!
Reverend Father.
Run
Reverend Father!
Wing, come and protect 13th Aunt.
They've gone backstage!
Let's see you fight up here!
Damn it!
Why did you ambush me?
It's you who ambushed me!
Foon? He's Foon?
It's dangerous here.
There are killers inside.
Question him!
Foon, what're you doing?
How would I know?
He's been hitting me
ever since he came in!
Don't move!
You say don't move,
but you still hit me!
Let's all stop this fighting!
Let's go!
Master Wong, don't move!
Your Excellency.
Silence!
Excellency, they left something.
Glory to the Militia
Death to foreigners
Weren't all the
Local Militia arrested?
How many have you sheltered?
Your Excellency, I'm being framed!
Don't listen to him!
Arrest these Shaho thugs!
What Shaho thugs?
That's the second time you've hit me.
Find out the truth
before you lay blame.
The truth?
He's taking protection money!
What? My Master?
Yes! That's him!
Master Wong? Isn't he from Shaho?
Where's Shaho? Near the Yellow River?
You don't need to explain.
My men will soon arrest
your other members.
But I'm going to arrest you first
and close your clinic.
Then let's see you make trouble!
Many people have been injured.
Let me help them, then I'll go with you.
All right, go ahead.
You'll be guarded.
If anything happens,
I'll execute you on the spot.
Don't move. You're bleeding.
So, fetch the medicine.
OK!
Go away. Can't you see
the eviction notice?
That doesn't give you permission
to steal our stuff.
Give them back!
You dare to hit us?! Go away!
Don't you have anything better to do?
Master, they were stealing,
I stopped them.
So what? Do you want to fight?
I'll fight with you.
OK, let's go!
No! I mean I'll fight you!
Master, how can I fight you?
Where'd you like to be hit?
Is it here? Here?
You want me arrested right away?
If not, don't stop me from saving lives.
Master!
Stop acting up!
We'll arrest you,
if you get in our way.
Porky's smart,
escaping arrest this way.
Hit me! Such restraint!
Mr. Cheng!
Still bleeding.
Fetch me the coagulant!
Coagulant!
He's dead. Tell his family.
So...
Fei-Hung!
What's this tattoo?
It reads, "Jackson".
Is it his ship's name?
Don't be scared. I'm Wong Fei-Hung.
You're badly hurt.
If you move, you'll tear the wound.
You're Master Wong? Help me!
Get up. Where are you from?
America!
America?
We crossed seas and were
denied medicine when we were ill.
Many were thrown overboard.
In America,
we were branded like pigs.
We were cheated
by the Chinese dealers here.
We signed contracts,
paid for food and passage.
Paid for so many things.
Those who tried to escape were killed.
I came back to China.
I... l... Master Wong...
Don't worry, you're home now.
Let me see
if we can find your family.
Try not to think too much.
Kai! Keep his contract
with the foreigners secret.
Or the Governor will arrest him.
I understand.
Going to America's better
than staying here.
Don't miss out! ...Come on...
Take a look! You want one?
Go to America? How?
Take one. You want one, too?
The same America as in the newspaper?
If you want to go, pay an exit tax,
passage, rental, blanket and food.
You can get a 3 year contract.
It costs 2 years' salary?!
You haven't got any money?
No.
Then don't even think about it!
Shove off!
You want one?
It's a land full of gold!
A fight's about to start over there!
A fight?
Let's go and watch it. Come on!
Don't go!
You dare show off in front of
my house and hit my disciple.
What's your name?
Master Yim.
I warn you.
My swordplay is unmatched.
You're a guest,
so I'll let you strike three times.
On guard!
Second strike!
Just two strikes
and you already draw your sword?
You're not my match.
Let's forget it!
Don't go!
You dare strike me from behind?
'Iron Robe kung fu'!
I've let you thrust 3 times.
Admit defeat!
There must be a way to beat him.
Why are you following me?
My name is Foon. I'm from May County.
There are lots of gangs in this town.
My kung fu is poor.
I'm often bullied.
I can't even make a living.
Please take me as your student.
What's the point of
being a kung fu expert?
I can't make a living either.
Master, are you hungry?
You take shelter.
I'll think of something.
Give me a drumstick!
Good stuff, eh? We only eat the best!
Gentlemen, come inside!
The soup's salty. Don't drink it.
The soup's very salty today.
Hey, why'd you steal my bowl?
Gentlemen, welcome.
Come in and have a drink.
Welcome gentlemen.
Let me sing to you.
Master, have some soup.
2 men drinking from the same bowl.
Pathetic!
Madam, shall I have them thrown out?
If I made my name here,
no one would look down on me.
Right,
you have to become the top dog.
Who's the best in town?
Master Wong?
13th Aunt, you're right.
China must change.
Fists can't fight guns.
I'm under house arrest,
soon I'll have to fight.
Take care of yourself!
Fei-Hung, I'll wait for you.
You don't have to.
If you do,
I won't die in peace.
You won't die...
I'm just a man...
Go home.
Wing, he...
Wing, go inside, it's raining hard.
Master didn't tell me to come in yet.
Wing.
Come back to Bo Chi Lam.
Master!
Come on in!
I...
Master, let me!
So!
It's raining harder than ever.
It's closed! Push off!
I'm 'Iron Robe' Yim from Shandong...
I'm here to challenge Master Wong.
Please tell me
which of you is Master Wong?
Master, a challenger!
Wing, bring some tea!
Master!
Bring tea!
Please!
Kai, take the patients to one side.
Have a seat!
Fold the umbrella.
Have some tea!
Foon, what're you doing?
Foon?
Master Wong,
your techniques are famous,
especially your 'Shadowless Kick'
and 'Ten Forms Fist'.
I intend to open
up my own school here,
that's why I'm here to challenge you.
Soon the people will know
my martial arts is the best.
I'm under house arrest,
you could get in trouble.
I can't fight you today.
Are you a warrior or not?
Master Yim!
I've too many patients here!
It's not the right place to fight!
Wing, Kai!
Do you want to be thrown out again?!
What are you waiting for?
Take the patients to the back.
I'll take you inside.
They're going to fight.
How dare you touch our patients?
Move him or he'll get hurt
by my master.
Bullshit! If not for my Master,
I'd beat you up.
Let go!
No!
God damn it, Foon!
What?
You dare try again?
Yim, stop fighting.
If you don't stop, I'll fire!
Don't hurt my Master. Give it to me!
Master, are you all right?
I've mastered the Iron Robe.
I don't fear guns.
Wong Fei-Hung, I won so easily,
it doesn't count.
Let's fight again tomorrow!
If you don't come,
I'll assume victory! Foon!
You jerk!
You ungrateful shit!
Stupid.
Speak Chinese, you banana!
Are you OK?
Yes, I just slipped!
The guards were injured,
there'll be trouble.
The Governor's men will be here soon.
Wing, Kai, go inside,
take some money and go.
13th Aunt,
go and wake the man from America.
What are you waiting for? Go!
Take him with you.
So, you don't know kung fu.
Don't wait for them. Go!
Master...
Take care!
I'll see you off!
Don't act on impulse.
Master.
Be careful!
Don't worry, your word is my command.
Wing, tell 13th Aunt to leave.
I let them go in order
to get the whole gang. Search!
Yes, sir!
Wait! I have many patients here
and many invalids.
Please don't disturb them.
You're asking me not to go inside?
There must be something hidden there!
My plan was to catch you off guard
and see who might be hiding
among your patients. Search!
Yes, sir!
Someone's getting away! After them!
Go!
So, go quick!
Get them!
Right!
Wing, fight!
What? Master?
Wing, I told you to fight!
Manchurian Dog!
You insult me?
Samson's Lift!
Are We really allowed to fight?
Yes!
Where's my gun?
Where are you going? Come back.
Shadowless Kick.
After them!
Yes!
Don't bother.
The man you want is here.
Split up.
Right!
This way.
Hold the pole, the rest go under.
Wong Fei-Hung,
I arrest you on charges of treason!
Your Excellency, I'll go with you.
Kai!
Master!
Kai, fetch medicine for the wounded.
Medicine from Bo Chi Lam
is the best.
How many of you are there?
Are you all right, Your Excellency?
You good-for-nothings!
We're almost there. Hang on!
Now we've got guns, we've got power.
We have to find women
for the foreigners.
Sha... Shaho Gang!
Quick, go that way.
A woman!
Let go of So!
You get away!
Don't let her go!
Let go!
Sir, take care of yourself.
They are too many. Forget about me.
Go to hell!
Run
Let me go!
Go!
There's one over there.
Get him! Get him!
Damn you!
How dare you come to help?
Attacking the clinic?
Kicking Wong Fei-Hung?!
Challenging Master Wong!
We're not going home.
Let's wait here!
When do you think
Master Wong will get here?
Open your mouth wide.
Open the door!
Go away!
You dare shoot me?
You'll be shipped out tonight!
Do you hate me?
Will your skin need spicing up?
When you have to serve
those stinking labourers,
you're gonna wish it was me.
Take her to my room!
Yes...
Boss, the one who beat Wong is here.
Great!
Good, now Fatshan will be ours.
Master!
You know each other?
Foon is now your senior.
You can trust him.
He's our senior?
Call him Big Brother.
Big Brother!
OK...
Remember he's senior.
Master, I'm busy tonight.
Please excuse me!
We'll talk about
the new school tomorrow.
Get the presents
for the Master ready.
Master Yim!
This is to help you open a school.
The Yim's Fist Style
will soon dominate Fatshan.
Come... let's toast Master Yim!
Cheers, Master!
Don't move! What do you want?
Master Wong, we all admire you.
We know you've been set up.
Master Wong,
we've decided to free you...
and we'll take responsibility for it.
Master Wong, this way!
Great! Let's go, Master!
Master!
China is a land with laws.
I won't make a mockery of them.
Go! Master!
Go with them, Master!
No, Excellency.
I appreciate it, but I won't go.
Wong... Master Wong is over there.
Master!
Master, you're still here?
So!
Master... Mas... Mas...
Speak slowly.
Master, 13th Aunt and I took that man,
but we ran into the Shaho Gang.
They killed him
and captured 13th Aunt.
Think of a way to save her.
What?
Master Wong, let's go and save her.
Wing, I'll give you a few men.
Good!
Let them go!
Right!
Buck teeth So,
how come you spoke so fast?
I was... rehearsing all the way.
I'm sure you'll miss the
Chinese food when you return.
Isn't that Master Wong?
Aren't they the Local Militia?
Master, you're great.
You even beat Wong Fei-Hung.
Give us a little demonstration.
Just a little!
OK...
Bitch! The hell with you!
That's enough, master, enough!
Master, that's enough!
What's wrong?
This money is dirty.
Don't accept it.
What?
Is he insulting us?
What do you mean?
You're looking down on us?
Nothing in this world is perfect...
Virtue is often found among
the lowly...
Our priority is to make our name
in Fatshan.
When that's achieved,
we can talk about justice.
That's life. Foon, pick up the money!
Pick up the money!
You think you're a big boss?
I think you're a nobody!
Foon?
Pick up the money!
Make our name in Fatshan?!
That's life!
Boss!
Bastard!
Damn you!
13th Aunt, wake up!
Bastard, don't touch me!
Don't scream. I've come to help.
Foon, is it you?
So many people are coming!
Go!
Get that woman!
Foon, stop or I'll kill her!
Our boss? Go to hell!
Hit me? Damn you!
Master, they are inside.
Let's go in!
What happened?
Master, Foon wasted no time!
He tried to force himself on my wife!
No, it's not true...
Shut up!
Foon, how dare you!
Apologise to your comrade!
Yim, we met at Bo Chi Lam.
Shut up, you bitch! Go!
You want to rebel?
Stupid! She's not his wife.
Really?
She's related to Wong Fei-Hung.
Wong Fei-Hung?
Foon is trying to escape!
Escape?!
How dare you.
Come back!
Get him!
Stop right there.
I've brought some Chinese girls here
for Mr. Jackson.
We come to see him tonight.
Open the gate. Mr. Jackson is expecting us.
Come on...
Open the gate. Come on...
We're getting cold, please.
Mr. Jackson will be very happy.
Open the gate...
Thank you, come on.
Take it easy!
Yes, Big Brother!
It hurts.
Right!
Master, these people have turned on me.
They'll do the same to you.
Don't trust them.
You don't trust your comrades,
yet speak up for Wong?
How is it? Too tough for you?
Let him go.
I'll do anything you want.
What makes you want
to sacrifice yourself for him?
You dare try to bargain with me?
Are you really Master Wong's woman?
When I'm done with you,
your face will be so scarred,
even Master Wong won't recognise you.
Where's the woman
you took away today?
Big Brother! Wong Fei-Hung is here!
Master Wong?!
Fei-Hung?
Arm yourselves!
Get all the guns out.
Go, get all the women on the ship.
Master, Wong is here.
You have to protect us!
Don't worry!
Foon!
Go!
13th Aunt!
Go, get Wong Fei-Hung.
You're not needed here.
Go search for 13th Aunt.
Yes.
Master Wong!
Master Yim, win or lose,
it's just a game.
You've got no excuse not to fight.
As you wish.
Down there!
External Chi Kung?
Today only one
of us leaves here alive.
Hey, how do you fire a gun?
Don't worry, we have guns.
You said you're good, come on.
Master, I'll help you!
Porky?!
Any more?
Buck Teeth So!
It's you?
Come up and get me down. Quickly!
13th Aunt has been kidnapped by the Shaho Gang.
Go and save her.
What?
13th Aunt has been kidnapped
by the Shaho Gang.
Hey, get me down,
Buck Teeth So!
Sorry, I forgot.
Your Excellency.
Enemy is approaching.
General, please!
This is General Wickens of
Her Majesty's Royal Armed Forces.
I'm escorting this Chinese officer who
comes in search of escape prisoners.
On his behalf, I request permission
to search your premises.
This is the territory of
the United States of America.
Permission is not granted,
and any trespassing...
will be regarded as direct
violation of our Federal Laws.
Damn your Yankee laws!
Damn you Brits to hell!
Stop! Don't shoot... stop!..
Excellency, it's dangerous here.
You'd better leave.
Comrades, get inside!
Boss, what now?
Kai, I'll help Master,
you save 13th Aunt.
No, I'll stay!
You save 13th Aunt.
I'm Big Brother! You listen to me!
Neither of you have to stay.
Go save 13th Aunt.
Go!
Wong Fei-Hung,
All's fair on the field of battle!
You call this Yim's Martial Arts?
The world's full of surprises.
One must take precautions.
Be quick, the ship's leaving.
Take them aboard!
Go, bitch!
Fei-Hung... it's 13th Aunt. Fei-Hung...
Bring her to the ship, go.
Fei-Hung...
Troops, attention.
Mr. Jackson, Master Wong is here!
Master Wong, take him on!
The ship's over there!
Hung, take them to the cabin.
Yes, sir.
Line up the men, ready now.
Get down, quick!
Turn around.
There... there!
Leave him to me.
They're yours.
Wong Fei-Hung,
Master Yim, our match is over.
He's leaving.
Master Wong, watch out!
Master Wong, where are you?
We haven't finished yet.
Master!
I am a master of the Iron Vest...
Master Yim!
Master Yim...
Wong...
It's true. Our kung fu is
useless against the foreign guns.
You scum!
Master Wong, don't go!
Hold your fire!
Load the cannon.
This is Commander Man from the
Provincial Government of Guangdong.
12 o'clock 30 degrees.
No, 10 o'clock 40 degrees.
What?
10 o'clock 40 degrees.
Aim, fire!
Wait!
Fire!
Oh, God!
Damn you Yankees.
They've hit my ship.
You there, check the ship.
Who is this Wong Fei Hung?
Foon?
Kill him!
Watch out!
Master Wong, come on out
and fight man to man.
Fei-Hung,
he's got a gun in his knife.
Don't fall into his trap!
Shut up.
Bitch, you brought them here,
so I'll burn your face.
Let's see which is faster,
your fist or my gun.
Burn!
Let me go!
Mr. Jackson.
Sir.
Mr. Jackson and the Shaho Gang
sold women to America.
Your Excellency, save us.
The Shaho Gang
and Jackson stole guns.
By law, you can't kill me,
you must hand me to the Government.
You've violated international law.
Put down the gun!
Why won't it fire?
Did I forget to load it?
If you don't put it down,
I'll kill him!
Put down the gun!
You've offended a Chinese Official
in a forbidden area.
How will you explain that?
Don't let even one Chinese
leave alive.
Then I won't have to explain
anything to your Government!
You scum!
You don't have to explain!
Your Excellency...
You jumped from this height?
Child's play. No big deal.
Thank you, Your Excellency!
All credit to Master Wong.
Don't mention it!
Thanks, Master Wong!
China's changed so much.
How can I deal with it?
America?
Do they really have gold there?
If they really did have so much gold,
why would they come here?
Maybe we're standing on gold now.
After this ceremony,
you'll be my Master.
But 13th Aunt
and I are so close now...
We'll be together
from morning to night.
If one day she marries me,
then you'll have to call me Uncle.
I'll be your senior
so you'll have to serve me.
Foon, what are you thinking?
Have some tea, Master!