What's in your mind?
Your mission is to divert the girl
who's reading the comic book with a wild look.
That one, no way.
What about the one next to her?
I'll take care of her,
you take care of the wild one.
It is an order.
Miss, do you have it?
What are you talking?
Just a little is enough.
What do you want?
I mean time.
No.
Hey.
You bastard, you wanna get away?
Don't let me catch you.
Sis.
What a coincidence?
Yes.
What're you doing here?
Getting a sun tan.
Good.
Let's go.
Seems like we've known for a long time.
Yes, I have the same feeling.
Tell you the truth, I like you.
I know.
Tell you the truth, I'm not short-sighted.
Blocking...
Returning to the point.
Where did I leave off?
Yes, do you know
a guy named Mike Chan?
Do you know Mike Chan?
- No.
- What?
- Mike Chan?
I don't know him.
Mike... Chan.
There's Mike Chu, and Peter Chan,
but not Mike Chan.
Have you forgotten?
Please think carefully.
It's very important to me.
I think my sister may know.
Then let's go and find her.
See how long can you stand.
Play? Let's play together.
No, thank you.
Get up, are you okay?
Yes.
Sis, do you know
a guy called Mike Chan?
Mike Chan?
Tell him.
Which Mike Chan?
This Mike Chan.
Oh, it's Coward Chan.
Coward Chan?
Yes, it's him.
Four days absent in a week.
Sleeping in the class.
Is that right?
Yes.
Do you know what are his activities?
He doesn't have any.
He's a coward.
Play ball.
I have to try it this time.
I don't think it's a good idea.
This isn't our game.
Sis isn't afraid, why you?
You haven't tried it before?
Yes, I haven't.
Me too.
Is it right?
Let's try it.
We're no longer kids afterwards.
Come, try once.
I don't think so.
Come on, there's no one here.
- No.
- Once!
- Okay...
- Hurry!
Can you take it?
- Quick!
- Coming...
- You won't regret?
- No!
- Close your eyes then.
Then I'm coming.
- Come.
- Coming...
What are you doing?
You've got asthma?
No, just breathing.
Breathing?
Where's my glasses?
What glasses?
- Glasses...
- Glasses?
Okay.
How do you feel?
Alright, you?
Very good.
But little girl shouldn't try this.
If you wanna try, count me in.
You aren't afraid of asthma?
Yes, but for you, it's okay.
- Chow Sing-Sing
- Run!
I wanna ask you something.
- It's you.
- Don't be afraid...
What?
I think you're the only one
who can teach me.
How to get a girlfriend?
Why ask me?
I've seen you two just now,
very skillful.
It's only basics, any target?
Yes... but... I'm afraid.
No problem, let's discuss it.
Of course, you should have
the guts to do it.
But, I think you should
take care of your hair first.
Yes... yes...
Wasting my time.
All those stuffs are irrelevant.
How are you, Turtle?
Turtle...
So powerful! How can a kiss
be that powerful?
It must be the power of love.
When do you marry her then?
She said when she'd get enough saving.
Fine... Then I must be the most miserable?!
I'm in love with a little girl.
How can I end that up?
Sing, you've got a girlfriend.
Can you manage?
I can manage that for you.
Okay... go ahead.
You must be kidding.
Look at me... my appearance... by how?
Good that you know.
After all, it's a big trouble.
Big brother... I've got information.
What?
Mike's been out with
the two girls over there.
Those two...
You two... go and handle them first.
Sing, you always ask us to do so.
Are we like gigolo?
- Then do you go for it?
- Of course.
Such young men
can't hold themselves on.
How can they handle big cases?!
Hello.
Hi...
Go and buy a drink with me!
Drink only?
How about... lunch together?
Still playing?!
Does Sing
really have a girlfriend?
Yes, very pretty?
Prettier than you.
Yes, tell Sandy to consider me.
I'm not bad, right?
Just the haircut is a bit outdated.
Bad boy.
Do you have another girlfriend? Tell me.
No.
Why your ears turned red?
Don't know.
What a shame to know your friends.
Let me tell you.
Don't let me see Chow Sing-Sing again.
If I see him.
I'll beat him up. Did you hear?
You don't wanna go out with me?
Not really. It depends.
Tell me if you don't want.
If you like me, you should hold my hand.
But not holding the school bag.
That's what I mean.
Get something to eat.
What did you say earlier?
I ask you again, am I pretty?
- Say it
- Pretty...
Let's go somewhere else.
What?
I wanna pee.
I wait for you.
Let's go together.
No, don't talk in the washroom,
talk it here.
Do you wanna pee?
I wanna hold it for a while.
Can you?
Nothing's hard in the world
if you're sincere.
Go and get something to eat.
- You hold it a while then.
- Okay!
To be an undercover, I'm ready for this.
How come you're like this?
Let's go.
No... There's someone I know.
Uncle, auntie.
What a coincidence?!
Yes, it is. This is Miss Ho.
She's my previous previous tutor.
Miss Ho, ever since you
stopped tutoring me.
My school result drops.
Come to my place if you have time.
But I'm going to move.
Are you?
I'm getting married.
Marry? Congratulations.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
I'm dating now.
Your boyfriend?
Hello, how are you?
But he's naughty.
How interesting.
Let's go.
Haven't eat yet?!
I'm not feeling well.
Excuse me, I have to go.
Okay, bye...
Bye...
Bye, I'm safe now.
- Sing...
- Who is it?
- It's me.
- You've got the wrong person, man.
Not wrong.
If it's not your voice,
I couldn't recognize you.
Sit...
It's you?!
Yes... Sit...
Let me fix the situation for you.
Miss Ho, don't you get mad.
The reason why Sing is with Sandy lately.
It's all because of work.
There may be some personal
feeling between them.
It's hard to say,
but don't think it's real.
You too.
In fact, Sing is aggressive.
Even though he got fired
by the police force.
He still comes back as undercover.
Also, because of it,
he even spent
$100,000 of your wedding money.
What a guy!
He's very miserable now.
Look at him, right?
So, let's think of a way to help him.
Let's think.
That means the wedding is off.
Good idea, what a good solution it is.
No wedding.
You damn fool. I'm in big trouble now.
Why insult me?
I helped you.
Lucky that we don't
have your kind in our team.
Damn Old Fool.
You insult me?
What? "Damn Old Fool".
Say it once more.
Damn Old... Fool.
Why did you hit him?
He insulted me.
Me too, why didn't you beat me?
I'm not as big as you.
You know it better.
Have a cup of tea.
Don't be angry, those guys are just...
jealous of you.
Don't you worry. I'm here.
But this case depends on you.
The problem isn't you,
it's Chow Sing-Sing.
This guy's gone too far.
He'll get in trouble soon.
You have to be careful.
Here, go have some fun.
Here's my supplementary visa card to you.
Are you teaching me?
No.
Don't ever say bad things
about my friend before me.
I admire your loyalty.
You know?
Everyone respect you in the station.
They say you're honest,
capable, kind and generous.
If the world has more people like you,
it'll be good.
So, what you gonna do?
- Expel Sing.
- Good!
Don't follow me, I'm getting married.
I like to.
You've got no future.
I don't want future.
Give it to someone else
if you don't want it.
Don't bug me.
What about me?
Ask your mother, don't ask me.
Have you ever liked me?
You know it's only a game.
What? Am I contagious?
Jacky said you're no good,
asked me not to be with you.
Fellow classmates.
We're here to have a test,
how about it?
Get out.
Damn you.
Throwing dusters in front of me?
When I throw dusters,
you're still nowhere.
Tell them to get back to class.
You tell.
I tell?
You're the teacher.
Where's your dignity? How do you teach?
Say it.
Class begins.
Louder.
Say in complete sentence.
Class begins, today... has a test.
Class begins, today has a test.
Is it okay?
Test, test.
Chow Sing-Sing, you come out.
I'm not in a good mood today,
what do you want?
I can't control myself.
Let me go then.
Mr. Principal.
Hello, Mr. Principal.
Hello, Sing, long time no see.
Yes, I haven't seen you at school.
How's business?
It all depends on the students.
Where are you getting rich?
Rich? Most important is to
have you to look after me.
I've taken over a food stall
at Temple Street. Interested?
A food stall? Yes.
Okay, count you in.
Well thanks.
Why are your parents looking for me?
What parents?
Your mother.
She's here, Auntie.
Yes!
You bad boy, I'm here to
withdraw you from school.
Mr. Principal? I'm here to withdraw my son.
Welcome...
It's sad to see kids school less.
Who said so?
Hold it, who said withdrawal.
I said it.
Hello, Madam?
What Madam, call me mother.
What? You did it with my dad?
Of course, or else how would I have you?
You don't acknowledge me, is it?
You did it with my dad?
I've done it too.
Look, I've brought his birth certificate.
His mother, Yu Su-Chiu, that's me.
What, you're Yu Su-Chiu?
Yes, I can prove she's Yu Su-Chiu.
Be quiet please.
Give me time to think what has happened.
Okay.
Right, kids must go to school.
What? What are you talking about?
Look, what do you think I look like?
What? Yes, you've got it, I'm a hooker.
I'm at the whorehouse at Portland Street,
called the Big Breasts girl.
And I've been worked
as a hooker for 25 years.
Come when you have time.
How much do you charge?
You?
Just wanna know.
$100, buy one get one free.
10 men a night, only get $500.
If I work hard for the whole month,
I can only survive, hold this for me.
I have to scold the bad boy.
You bad boy.
You said you'll attend English school
to get foreigners for me.
But you come here for fun.
Poor me.
How come hooker wears a gun?
Yes...
I even buy you a toy gun.
He likes to play toy gun.
Thank you, mom.
You give it back to me.
Didn't you say that you bought it for me?
You... give...
You bought it for me.
Yes.
Then it's mine.
I wanna play it now, I wanna try it.
Look up.
Let me play.
You love me, you bought me the gun.
Play.
You play, but don't aim at me.
Don't.
Don't aim at anybody.
Sing, playing gun in school
is a serious crime.
I want school.
No, put down the gun.
I'll play gun if no school.
Are you alright?
Alright...
The gun is loud.
Don't.
The gun is here.
The gun is so real.
Don't play gun... very serious...
What? I'm in charge here.
The sound is so real.
Wow! The gun is really powerful.
Mrs. Chow,
where did you get such a toy gun?
Damn you.
Mrs. Chow, I'll teach a lesson to your son.
Let's go!
Hey, you really wanna mess things up?
You mess things up, not me.
What do you mean to withdraw me?
What can you do here?
I'm in charge here.
Don't be so mean.
I just wanna help you.
Help? You just wanna help yourself.
You're selfish.
Let me try once, okay?
Whether lose or win,
I'll take the consequences.
My career, romance and future
are all in your hand.
Leave now if you wanna help me.
Silence means you promise.
It's only a toy gun, don't get excited.
It's for kids.
It's not for adults.
Fire all my bullets, how do I report it?
- Mrs. Chow.
- Yes.
You can leave with your son.
Good.
Why are you in such a hurry?
I'm leaving, bye.
I'm just playing, no need to scold me.
Then why you didn't respect her.
You deserve it.
Go back to your business.
Big brother.
You're leaving?
This is my phone number, call me.
What is it?
School map, good for escape.
Did you draw it?
No, just pick it.
Who would draw something like this?
Beat the shit out of me.
Here.
Where did you get this map?
Sing gave it to me.
Where did Sing get it?
I don't know.
Madam Wong, do you believe in Sing?
I believe in Tat.
I believe in Sing.
How can I trust you guys?
I believe you...
You believe in Sing, he said so.
Madam, I've talked
to the Secretary of Security.
You guys from RCU are no
longer needed in this case.
We'll take care of it ourselves.
You can continue believing in Sing.
Sorry, Lydia.
Tat, I trust you...
Where's Sandy?
Don't know, I'm busy now.
I told you to keep an eye on her.
Seems she went downstairs.
Why didn't you say earlier.
Hey, still some more, finish it.
Come on, mark the time.
No watch.
Let's go.
Mr. Lee, we're on position.
Over.
Hey, have a drink first.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Make sure you know where they are.
Got it.
These guys are really amateurs.
Yesterday Prime Minister John Major
told reporters that.
British government has no intention of
yielding to any terrorist demands.
He denied.
Any negotiations have taken place between
the terrorist group and Government.
Let's see how tough
they play when I've got
300 school kids in my hand.
Roll the ball.
See you later.
The machine isn't working.
Let me check it.
Let me tell you a secret.
What?
There's terrorists in Hong Kong.
Crazy...
Merry Christmas.
Don't move. I don't want to hurt anybody.
Everything's ready.
Hurry...
Hello.
Sing.
Louder.
Where's those guys from Special Branch?
Where's Tat?
Go to call the police at once,
I'll be there immediately.
Special Branch.
Hello, I'm Chow Sing-Sing.
Damn you!
Hello...
What's the telephone no.
Of calling police?
999. Quick!
We've got a mantle of frequency
in here from around here.
With intention to jam the signal.
I can't exact the signal
path is moving too fast.
Johnathan, check it out.
Damn you.
Follow me.
Wait... I'll do this one.
What's the problem?
Someone's going?
Shit... get them to the basement.
Get up, move...
Moving...
Sir.
Sing, why are you back?
There's a heavy armed group of terrorists.
Currently kidnapped a group of hostages.
I want you to dispatch
a team of SDU to save them.
I haven't received the order from above.
There won't be any
because there's only me
who know at this time.
You're the captain here before.
We can't go without the order from above.
I know, but there're lives involved.
It's emergency.
There's no more time.
Sorry, can't help you.
Then can you lent me your warrant card.
Well...
Sing, you wanna go to jail?
Yes, Sir.
Team No. 3, unit A, B, C move out.
There're hundred of lives waiting
for you to rescue.
I'll take every responsibility. Believe me?
Yes, Sir.
Move out.
Move it...
Hold it.
Under the pool, there's an air-raid shelter.
Follow me.
That way.
Hurry.
Get away... Let me do it.
Go.
Why is it so bright suddenly?
Where's my glasses?
Feels uncomfortable without my glasses.
It's here.
Damn it, the entrance is exploded.
Kill you bastards.
How come it's hot dogs?
Watch out, hurry...
- Be careful...
- Hurry...
Police, freeze.
Don't shoot, we're on the same side.
- Mr. Chow, I met them in the tunnel.
- Lower down.
Sing, very scary, the terrorists.
Shut up!
How did you get out?
We came from the underground tunnel.
But it was exploded.
Can't go in again.
Any injuries?
No, we're all safe, except me.
You're the best.
Yes, he's very good...
Any more students inside?
I don't know but Tat is in there.
Tat?
He saved us.
He saved you?
Like an exterminator.
Exterminator?
But don't know if he's dead or not?
Go in at once.
Yes, Sir.
Damn it.
Hold on...
Surrender! It's unfair
that you have two against me.
You'll learn a lesson
when my partner comes.
Fire.
There's a lot of police here.
Got to make some help now.
Shit.
Move in.
Pay attention.
There must be more students.
Lead them out.
Remember, we're going to save is
a Chinese man with moustache.
Any discovery?
No, Sir.
Sir, does he have any characteristic marks?
Marks?!
Indecency.
What about personality?
What personality?
Who asked this stupid question?
Found anybody?
No, we've searched all classrooms.
There's a whole fucking army out there.
Oh, dear.
Move.
Stand there...
You're Chow Sing-Sing?
- Sir.
Have you seen Terminator?
Which Terminator?
- James Bond.
- Which James Bond?
Head of discipline.
What head of dispensary?
- Take him out.
- Yes, Sir.
Take him out.
Don't.
Light-grenade.
Sir, who to do next?
Get him out for first aids.
What about you?
Hurry, save life first.
Sir.
I cover you, ready, go.
Kill all of you guys.
Anybody still alive?
Answer me if there is any.
I've reached the last machine room, over.
Read me? Over...
Hello...
Freeze.
Sing, relay...
No weapons please.
And hand gun.
Easy.
Very nice, turn around...
Why?
Because I want you to turn around.
What?
You fool.
Bye...
Are you alright?
Yes... where's the bullet?
Where did you hide it?
In my back.
Is it?
All inside.
You've been shot?
You're pretending just now.
Young man, be realistic.
Don't cheat around.
Don't bullshit, I'm in pain.
Let me get an ambulance.
- Hold it.
- What?
Everybody is coming.
Let me be rewarded first.
You're greedy again?
What? You are.
He's not police, I have to arrest him.
Chow Sing-Sing's action
is planned by our RCU's
Don't misbehave.
Tsao Tat-Wah.
I'll be responsible for everything.
You've done a good job, no student is hurt.
Thank you, Sir.
Sir, you've promised
that RCU isn't involved.
No.
Yes, there's an order, here,
see for yourself.
You're hated by me more.
Wow... hand grenade.
Bastard, interrupt me while I'm talking.
Don't think that there's
no arrest after death.
Lock him up.
Who pushed me to the front?
I'll settle with you latter.
Thank you.
This time, you got me in trouble.
Sir.
Have I misbehaved this time?
You've learned from me at last.
Thank you.
Chow Sing-Sing.
Yes, Madam.
You have done very well,
we welcome you back to the police force.
But, I'm not interested
in the traffic unit.
Don't worry.
This time you'll be either
Chief Superintendent or Chief Inspector.
Thank you, Madam.
I've heard that you've been shot.
Yes, but to me, it is only a scratch.
It's really nothing.
Very good, any request?
I want an ambulance.
Call an ambulance.
Ambulance?
Someone's dating me.
See if you can beat him first.
Okay? I'm not a coward anymore.
Did I say I wanna date you?
I came here to learn flower
arrangement only.
You bastard snatch my girl,
I'll beat you up.
Beat you.
Ripped by:
SkyFury