The Nuclear Explosion
has ruined the city.
Also, changed our destiny.
Radiation has contaminated the water.
This unprecedented catastrophe.
It gives birth to an ambitious genius.
Who invented
the Water Purification System.
The basic need of mankind is in his hand.
He vows to rule the world.
I haven't seen my two good friends
for a long time.
We'd accomplished
many great tasks together.
The Nuclear Explosion dispersed us.
The whole city is
in the state of ferment...
robbery, riots, bloodshed...
People are killing each other,
for survival.
For all my effort.
I just manage to ensure the donation...
the medicine is safely sent to the needy.
What a huge tank of water? Where to go?
I wasn't told.
"Clear Water Corporation."
Water bandit again!
Stay away.
Hired to kill me?
He's too poor to hire.
We're told to explode all the tanks,
if we're being mugged.
Thanks for giving a hand.
Or I'll return with bare hands.
So, how about a 50/50 share.
I knew you're mean.
I didn't call for your help.
Ungrateful chick.
There's no free lunch.
Bye!
I work hard for money, what you for?
50/50.
30/70.
A deal! 50/50.
I changed my mind.
60/40 mine 60. Yours 40.
It's unacceptable.
Not to someone apathetic.
Scoundrel!
You'll take the small one.
Water!
Come. It's from Clear Water Corporation.
About the water bandit incident today.
Spokesman of
the Clear Water Corporation alleged,
the government is incompetent
to protect them.
So they consider a price raising.
If they succeed.
It'll the fourth times this fall.
Here is the special news.
Damn! Price raised again.
Mom, is it?
What is it?
A fish.
Fish has no legs.
Then, how can a fish walk?
Let mom show you.
Once upon a time, fish swam in the water.
It's cute.
Mom, I've a tooth loosen out today.
Can I hide it for a wish?
Where do you like?
Are you serious?
Please.
This is the last time.
Is it fun?
Yes. One more time.
Please, no.
One more. Please.
Ching.
Dong Dong.
Auntie San.
Cindy, a peach for you.
Have this.
Taste it.
How a woman uses Ku Fung to please kid!
Auntie, have you ever met Wonder Woman?
How about you?
Mom said Wonder Woman had a Wonder Baby.
She's too busy,
no time to show up anymore.
Really?
Are you hungry? I'll get some bread.
Let's wait for Chat.
See what I've got.
Water.
Hurry up. Let's bath.
Move, have a good bath together.
Kiddie, come.
Terrific.
I knew you did it in the afternoon.
So what?
You may spare some for the needy.
Mom, it's fun.
Come.
Tomorrow is Christmas Eve.
Let's celebrate.
You're hopeless.
It's damn good.
Don't talk indecent in front of kids.
It's your fault.
Kids reminds us of our age.
Let me see.
You're still in good shape.
Sure!
I keep fit.
Really.
No! It hurts!
Stop.
The Spiritual leader of
White Solar Society.
Daddy's on TV.
Denouncing the water scheme is inhumane.
He aims to provoke the crowd.
If there's clean water, there's way.
I've enough of the news.
Kiddie. Turn it off.
Not seeing doesn't mean not happening.
Though the country is
in a state of ferment,
chances of grasping money is abundant.
If three of us cooperate,
we'll make a lot of money.
No way.
Go to Auntie Chat.
Come here.
30,000 people will come
for Chong Hon tonight.
We must have them under surveillance.
Last the gathering convert into riot.
All of us must alert.
My fiancee gave it to me.
I haven't slept for three days.
I'm dying.
You aren't the only one.
Stay.
Are you deaf, stay.
Get her.
Why they want us to die?
In fact, there's no any clean water.
Why keep sending us out?
Chong Hon said
territory is all contaminated.
Your Water Scheme is deceptive.
Put down your gun first.
Stay.
No!
I pleaded my husband not to go.
It's wise to stay here.
At least, there's no radiation.
We may live longer.
Let me talk to Daddy.
She wants to talk to you.
The crowd will revolt
in the Square tonight.
Don't wait for me. I'll be on duty.
But give my girl a kiss, please.
Merry Christmas...
Let me talk to Daddy.
Liar! He said he'd come home for Xmas.
Daddy told me to give you a kiss.
And Merry Xmas too.
Dad's kiss is different, he'd beard.
- Too bad.
- What's the matter?
- Dad can't have the roasted chicken.
- That's right.
Objection!
Chief, all units are ready.
Roger.
Report to me when Chong Hon arrives.
Which fairy fanned.
To cover the earth with snow.
Help! Give me back.
It's my water.
Scum! Give me back.
Mom, you're wonderful.
Marvellous!
Don't let Daddy know.
Thank you.
No problem.
- All units, standby.
- Yes.
Calling Team One.
Lot of people died of radiation
for waters.
We like to confer with the Government.
Stay calm unless I give my order.
Yes.
Where is Daddy?
Let's go there.
Good.
They said out there are clean headwaters.
But, the expedition members died
one after one.
Why did they die of radiation?
Why?
Blasphemous! Show me the headwaters then.
Mrs. Lau, why so late?
Where's the Commissioner?
- There.
- Thank you.
You said your guns.
It's used for protecting us.
Why do you point them to us now?
Compel us to
look for nonexistent headwater?
Whose order to fire?
Chong Hon, run!
Why? Why fired? Why?
Cindy!
Don't panic.
Send more assistance from Headquarter.
They killed our people.
Release tear gas!
Cindy!
All squads cease firing.
Husband!
Why are you here?
Cindy is lost among the crowd.
Why do you bring her along?
What a mother you are?
Mom!
Don't cry! Let me take you to your mom.
Cindy...
Mom.
"The for seasons compose a saga."
"With ups and downs."
"They interchange like a windmill."
"And make your heart tremble."
Where's the roast chicken, mom?
Dumped.
Remember our promise?
Go.
Bye. Dad.
"Which fairy fanned..."
"To cover the earth with snow."
"An ant has its cave.
A house has a door,"
"from where one hears the wind blow."
He hasn't any record
in the military file.
Will that be Chong Hon's conspiracy only?
An anti-government emotion
by firing someone.
Anyway.
Spread out his photos immediately.
Can I talk to you alone?
- Please leave the room.
- Yes, Colonel.
Lately I've been thinking.
Who will sacrifice his life
for the country.
You're the one.
What can I do?
Assassinate Chong Hon.
He's getting influential,
our Government will be overthrown soon.
Casualties will be enormous then.
If Chong Hon dies.
Chaos will not last long.
And the society will soon back to normal.
I'll give you time to think it over.
But reply me before New Year Eve.
Because Chong Hon
has gathered some crowds.
It's a mourning ceremony on New Year Eve.
I'm afraid, he'll make use of the crowds.
Send five cartons of medicine
to the South.
Are you going?
I'll join you later.
You should know me.
The President's deputy.
I'm ashamed of the title.
Even though I'm so close to him.
I can't give him any advice.
It's hard to control famine people.
I've got the right person.
What do you want from me?
To form an expedition team,
to look for clean headwaters.
You still believe it
after so many deaths?
Yes.
I'll prove to you later.
Some officers conspire to kill Chong Hon.
But they should consider the consequences.
I need someone trustworthy
to convince him,
his goals can be achieved by
co-operating with the government.
Goals?
People talk dull in places like this.
Nothing but money can amuse you.
What's that?
The blood stains on the stole,
remind us of our path of glory.
What do you want to tell?
To search the clean headwaters.
I strive for nothing but money.
Sorry, I took a pledge to my husband.
Then the stole means nothing to us.
No!
Don't!
If you really want us to die with you,
I'll.
If an oath becomes a burden,
it's inept.
How long
do the Nuclear Catastrophes last?
It's inept for a Wonder Woman now.
But the baby needs a mother completely,
to help her to go through hurdles.
I pledge to you.
I'll be a good wife and a good mother.
Never ever a Wonder Woman.
I prefer gold not cash.
You can refuse.
You'd better be smart.
Be good in jail.
Take him away.
You aren't allowed.
The Chief is my good friend.
Let me in.
Shift. Come on.
Chief.
Go to hell.
You'd seen something confidential.
Did he agitate the riot in the Square?
I'll find him for you.
You are the head-hunter, Chat.
Sure I am, the best.
$300,000. Enough?
It deserves $400,000 at least.
If you catch him alive,
I'll pay $800,000.
Gold.
Attractive!
So what?
Let her take it.
Look forward to my good news.
You aren't allowed unless I call you.
May I know who starts shooting.
Who did it in the Square?
How dare you disparage me.
I raise you
up to represent righteousness.
For justice I fight with the government,
until the right at the Square.
I begin to wonder...
I'm inducing the bloodshed.
You're powerful enough,
to compel the government
to make concessions.
What a holy man you are!
Delighted in being a spiritual leader?
Are you feeling like a Savior?
- I don't.
- You do.
Never try to supersede me.
Your hands are trembling.
I chose you,
because the mobs like handsome looking.
What should I do now?
As you think you're brainy,
do whatever you like to.
You may go now.
- Mr. Kim.
- Out.
I really want to see
what's inside his brain.
It's over. He's deviated.
I hope our next generation.
They're able to live in genial planet.
For this operation.
You're responsible solely.
As usual, I'll accuse you.
This is a secret even to your family.
When times comes, you'll be retaliated.
Don't kill him.
Why do you want to kill me?
Assassination is not a solution.
You're wrong.
What're you looking?
Why he's being tailed so easy?
Isn't it strange?
He's mine.
I've been following him whole day.
A dummy indeed.
Stay.
Give me.
For what?
Bitch.
You can't take him away.
Piss off!
A bomb?
My treat!
A bomb!
Disperse.
No back door?
Still some thugs?
Pain in the ass!
I've been tracing the gunman.
But stupid Chat
has caught him last night.
What coincidence of the Press Conference.
The Chief, Chong Hon all take place here,
the gunman set up as being caught.
Somebody uses Chat.
They're connected each other somehow.
I'm sure.
Wash your hands after drawing.
Yes, mom.
"Out of order."
I knew you can't refraining
from hearing this,
because you're incorrigibly nosy.
You deserve it.
I know I've been hot-tempered lately,
and given too little care
to you and Cindy.
Sorry.
Often, and old couple finds
talking candidly difficult.
I just want to confess to you,
having you and Cindy,
is the greatest accomplishment
in my life.
I love you!
Thanks for your effort of expediting.
Our liaison with Chong Hon.
We may have a drink after the conference.
This the permit.
As Chat brings along the gunman,
stay close to her.
Forestall any intruders.
Welcome, Mr. Chong Hon.
- Thank you.
- Please come in.
Husband.
You may escort the President out here.
Not until it's completely safe.
Chong Hon's here.
Chat is coming soon.
Get off!
Damn you!
Give me your hand.
A permit from the Deputy.
I'll take him with me.
Yes.
Go.
Hand him over to me.
You may have the money.
For the safety of Chong Hon.
He'll show up only
when the meeting begins.
Husband.
What brings you here?
I've heard the tape. I'm sorry.
Hello... yes...
Ok, Chat's here.
Stop feigning.
Is the trip alright?
Don't pretend you know everything.
- You caught him in vain.
- You're poisoned.
Who care? I got my money.
You're immutable!
The Chief likes to see you.
Wait here.
From now on,
he's not allowed to leave the room.
Yes, Chief.
If I get into trouble, you too!
I hope you may
cancel the press conference.
Because the Press Conference
and the gunman,
they're plotted insidiously.
Chong Hon's rarely willing to make peace.
We can't cancel it, no way.
If anything happens,
I'll take the responsibility.
No one can take that.
What will happen?
I, Chat, will bear sole responsibility.
Commissioner, press are all here.
Let's go.
Husband.
Take care.
I'll be fine. You go home.
Don't worry.
Where's Colonel? I need my money.
We're pleased to
have Mr. Chong Hon today,
to present for the peace talk.
The gunman in the Square
has been arrested.
Sorry, you shouldn't disrupt the meeting.
A present from Mr. Kim.
Stop the President from leaving.
Run.
You arranged the peace talk.
People will blame you
for Chong Hon's death.
- Run...
- Run before it is too late.
This's Colonel.
Kill the Chief, the Commissioner.
Where's my husband?
The Colonel took him away.
You said I'll be alright.
The Congress House is out of control.
According to the report,
the missing Commissioner
Mr. Lau,
is responsible for Chong Hon's death.
Chong Hon
has embarrassed the Commissioner.
Because of his discontent
with the Government.
Daddy.
- Cindy, where's Mom?
- She's out.
Where's she gone?
You are betrayed.
The Colonel has ordered to perish you.
Run at once.
Tell my wife to meet us at the station.
Aren't we waiting for Mom?
I'll tell her.
Thanks.
Colonel, we lost the target.
Please leave the station.
Mom, a few tickets left.
It rumors people congregated
are to be arrested.
The government is insane
for killing Chong openly.
There's curfew after midnight.
This is the last train.
Tickets all sold out.
The Government is keeping the tickets.
Where's Mom?
Let me get in.
Go.
I ain't going without Mom!
I'll come back later for her.
No!
Stop that!
Cindy.
Mom...
Cindy, don't go.
Attention.
Mom.
Where have you gone? You'll kill us.
Daddy.
"All mortal pursue loves with loves."
"Finally find a flame passion
lurks pathos."
"Blessed are the impersonate,
yet lacks fullness."
"Love mellows
without grudge of fretfulness."
"My loved one
once shared his reminisce,"
"all loves had resemblance."
"The day I was stricken by the feel."
"I saw a magnetic field."
Imprison those alive as rioters.
Burn the corpses.
"Be incredulous to a vow of fidelity."
"The reign of love has no fairy tale."
Thank you.
Things happened as your calculation.
People're terrified,
they deeply recanted the government.
It's time for next step.
But they begin to be dubious about us.
Action must be imminent.
Leave it to me. Don't worry.
Ok.
Wait, I had a dream last night.
Dreadful!
Really.
The president's dead in my dream.
You're in charge
and practiced militarism.
Still I were a faceless man
who hid in shadow.
You and I are inseparable.
Your money and intelligence,
will my military power,
it makes us the best rulers.
The world is belonged to us soon.
You and me?
Me and you?
Me and me!
I hope to expedite the burial,
but we don't have enough hands.
Chances of finding your friend here
is lower.
Mom...
It's late when I got to the station.
I could only find Cindy.
He makes use of Chong Hon's death,
as an excuse for military dictatorship.
He planned it all.
Shit! I took his money!
Give my parents back.
Cindy, be quiet!
Stop the bullshit.
You're the President's man.
Find Dong Dong for us.
I'll pay whatever it costs.
I'm sorry.
If I clash with the military now.
It's just worsen the situation.
You're a big shot!
It's just a piece of cake.
Chat.
I'll look for her secretly.
Time is running out.
We must get clean water at once.
Or the people will stir up.
Give me three days.
If we don't hear Dong Dong, we'll go.
I'm out of your plan.
I go nowhere without Dong Dong.
Dong Dong...
Are you Dong Dong?
The prisoners are very hostile to us.
And no intention to
cooperate with the government.
Besides,
we don't have record of your friend.
Let me find her.
Stop meddling.
The place is under the military.
Being agitated, your friend
will be endangered.
Also, Dong Dong may riot be here.
Mom...
I won't give up.
Don't go.
Stay calm.
Damn! I'm an asshole!
Dong Dong will be fine.
I can't believe that the Colonel,
hands in glove with Mr. Kim.
We have disappointed many people.
I'll call a meeting to dismiss Colonel.
It's too risky.
Most of the military force is his men.
You think he'll organize a coup d'etat?
This's the Congress House area.
All vehicles must stop for inspection.
Stop.
Colonel, we've occupied the lobby.
Only some are defending.
- Seize the place.
- Yes.
Cover me,
I'll safeguard the President to leave.
Good.
Mr. President, we must evacuate.
The Colonel has seized our building.
Inform all units,
the President's receding.
Calling all units,
Mr. President is receding.
Go.
Back off. Cover President.
- Call Doctor!
- Yes.
How's the President?
The stake is handsome for this battle.
I think I'll modify our plan.
You distract them
with the President's double.
Until you find the headwater.
Be careful.
Go.
Get him.
Get on.
Kau, get on!
Kau!
Kau.
- Send President away.
- Yes.
I need to keep it secret.
Sorry, everyone.
I don't like you. Let me go.
I'm in a bad mood.
- I'll punch you.
- Let me go.
What's up?
She hates me. Why I bring her along?
She...
Come here.
There're two points on the map.
You'll meet your guard at Point 1.
Point 2 shows where the water is.
Going with her?
Yes! Bring her.
She's much safer with you.
All people died during the course.
You want me to bring her along?
Take a look.
Fish?
That's right.
Is there really having water?
They were found
at the last expedition team.
We still have hope.
You're more competent
for this mission than me.
They want me to stay.
I only care about finding Dong Dong.
Dong Dong, can you face her?
Cindy, be good.
If you find the water,
Mom will be very happy.
Ok! I'll go.
Walk fast!
Watch out.
Shit! Are you the guard?
Exactly.
Damn! Kiddie, let's go.
Do you know the route?
Of course, I never fail.
Don't be obstinate!
You've a girl with you.
I won't be merciful,
even though you're San's friend.
I don't give a damn.
I just do what I think.
To hell with your arrogance.
If you're as mighty as you think.
Why you need me?
- I'm Tak.
- I'm Cindy.
- Cindy.
- Uncle Tak.
Nice to meet you.
We've things to do.
It's not a party.
You can't find the water without me.
Don't think I'll be nice to you.
Kiddie, let's go.
Make no haste.
Let's wait here for a while.
- Why?
- It's hot!
You may go on your own way.
- Cindy.
- Kiddie. Come over to me.
Cindy,
can you tell me why you're so beautiful?
Don't look at him.
I found some water.
Drink.
Thanks.
Let's go.
Stop.
The President?
I'll report to the Colonel.
Mr. President, please alight.
Don't move.
Gun's down.
Walk.
- Fill the tank.
- Yes.
Tak, what are we waiting for?
Some friends.
Are they with us?
What?
You're telling people where we are.
Tak, see.
Who are they?
Same as us looking for water.
Let's go.
Why?
Wait!
Let's go, Cindy.
Go.
Ok.
You use their death to feign ours.
What a scumbag!
They volunteer to protect us.
So they think the expedition team's dead.
Be careful until we find the water.
- Cindy, let me help you.
- Thank you.
What're you waiting?
Want me to hold you?
Relax, Mr. President,
this is a secret cellar.
The Colonel should never know
we're hiding here.
President's double
had out the West already.
Hope they can make it.
Chat has set off.
If she loses,
we'll never able to leave here.
Radiation is high here.
Stay.
Put them on.
Tak, what's up?
No gas. We have to walk.
Tak, look!
Damn! Watch out the thorns.
It's gamma rays.
Don't get pierced.
Watch out!
Keep off. It's fatal!
These traps mean something.
It seems
we're getting close to the water.
That's right.
Watch out!
The President!
Get off!
I'm exhausted.
I don't want to die.
Don't worry. I won't let you die.
Stop using me as a bait, ok?
If not,
the President will be jeopardized.
How brave!
Aren't you afraid?
Damn! It's a long time.
Smell it.
Yes! Fragrant!
You...
Look there.
The headwater is there.
Is this the headwater?
The grass tells the water is unpolluted.
The headwater is underneath.
Go ahead! Jump!
You go first.
Why not you first?
I can't swim.
You can't! Why are you here?
If I know I need to swim.
I'd have learnt when I was a baby.
Cindy, you stay here.
Until I come back.
Before I jump I must let you know,
you like me, I can tell.
Say yes before I jump.
Not now.
You want to die?
Of course.
Like this?
Why not?
Let me tell you.
Row like me in the water?
Hold your breath!
What are you doing?
You have to wait here.
No, I'll go too.
Like mother, like daughter.
Grapple my hand when we jump.
Go.
The gate must lead to the water source.
How's your foot?
Don't breathe deep.
The air is not enough.
Three of us need more.
Can we go on?
But you broke your leg.
It's too far to swim back.
If we go on we may find an exit.
Bet or not?
I do.
Honestly, I love you.
So do I.
Say it again.
You jerk!
Uncle Tak?
He can't make it.
Damn! Useless!
You almost made it.
I want Uncle.
Uncle's dead.
We can't leave him here.
Cindy, Uncle died for us.
He wants us to find the water.
Now I only have you.
Let Uncle's will come true.
Be good!
Why did she show up again?
People want to be hero in time of chaos.
She's just a woman.
A woman? Masked like me?
Don't neglect
the strength of a faceless person.
Maybe we can make friends. Just kidding.
I didn't mean to kill him so soon.
But he made me mad.
When will you give me her head?
It won't take long.
What's in it?
Maybe her head!
Maybe anyone's who betrays me!
Maybe mine!
Only if I kill the President,
and put your face on mine,
and explore more clean water.
I'll be a Savior.
Your face and my wisdom.
It's a perfect president!
Tell me. Why do you kill Lau, the Chief?
He killed Chong Hon. He deserves it.
Stop insulting him.
Wonder Woman!
How dare you assassinate an officer?
I do it for revenge.
Why did you kill him?
For the country.
Everyone has to sacrifice.
Great!
"Modest sun and light breeze
send up sprouts."
"Larks sing for Spring is coming."
"The dreamer wakes up to find..."
"The butterfly has flown away."
"Gleefully rowing a gondola
beneath the bridge,"
"not knowing snow
has covered the bridge."
"Sing a folklore..."
"When the lotus blossom unknowingly."
"The four seasons compose a saga,"
"with ups and downs."
"They interchange like a windmill,"
"and make your heart tremble."
Cindy.
Auntie Chat, I'm tired.
Come on.
Damn! A brick wall!
What does it mean?
Auntie Chat, what's it?
Moss?
There is hope. We made it.
Damn! This wall killed many people.
Clean water.
Shit! Let's run, Cindy.
It's Chat,
she found the water.
Mr. President.
You may go now.
Thank you.
I know you could make it.
Why did you kidnap the President?
It must implicate
with my husband's death.
Chat will tell you later.
No way.
San,
give us the President.
He's mine.
Bitch!
For the President's safety.
Trust me if we're still friends.
Our Excellence!
Mr. Kim, San is being tailed.
We'll soon find out
where the President is.
- Get lost.
- Yes.
Perfect timing.
The bomb that hit me didn't ignite.
Perhaps it's God's will.
Let me wait till Chat returns.
What's happening? How is your friend?
I saw them.
But people chased after us.
We hardly can talk.
Dong Dong, no!
Why don't you tell me you're hurt?
I'm afraid you won't let me go.
Mr. President.
He's President's double.
The real President is safe.
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't want too many people knowing.
Chat is out for the water.
Chat?
Does she worth your protection?
If it was me, you'd do the same thing.
Besides, she's with Cindy.
San, what's really going on?
Go to your mother.
Mom.
Cindy.
The death of Mr. Lau and Chong Hon,
is plotted by the Colonel
and Clear Water Corp.
San tried to distract other attention.
She used the double
to protect the President.
She also gave me a chance to reciprocate.
I'm an idiot, I'm so sorry for it.
But I found the clean water.
Is it still an oath?
We're friends forever.
You're all here.
Faceless monster! Go to hell!
Jibber!
Asshole!
Run!
Auntie San.
Come over.
San.
Stay away.
No.
Ching.
You jerk! So persistent!
A special announcement.
The missing President wishes to tell.
As the legitimate ruler of the nation.
Listen! The President.
I solemnly reveal the truth to you.
We're deceived by Mr. Kim,
the Clear Water Corp.
Our water hasn't polluted by radiation.
It's Mr. Kim who contaminated the water.
But, nightmare is over.
Try to turn on your tap.
You may have the clean water back.
Long live the President!
Who's calling President?
Who's calling me?
My name? I'm the President.
It's mine. Give it to me.
You'll never be a president.
You dream is over?
Run.
- Your Mom.
- Mom.
Cindy.
Mom.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Thank you.
We didn't do it for you.
We did it for friends.
Let's go.
How is Auntie Chat?
Some mistakes... have no remedy.
But, it may depend on us.
The sincerity of our friendship.
So?
Except any daughter.
I only have you.
You're not coming?
We're leaving.
You kiddie! Always giving me hard times?