Come on, Susan.
Think about Daniel.
He wants you to be happy.
Come on, Susan.
Give her a hand.
Mrs. Tsui, be brave.
Mrs. Tsui.
Come on, Mrs. Tsui.
You got the wrong person.
My daughter-in-law is over there.
Cathy, Daniel's Caribbean trip
turned out to be a tragedy.
You met him there and got married.
Then he died unexpectedly.
You're a strong girl, Cathy.
I didn't expect you to hold up.
Grandma, my real name is May.
Daniel said your name was Cathy.
Who knew if he was for real?
I made it up.
Why isn't your father here?
Busy in meetings?
He could've come. But his sentence
just got extended.
Sentence? Your father's in jail?
Yes. For smuggling pigs.
Isn't he a diamond tycoon?
I lied to Daniel.
Why?
Because he made up stories.
What did he say?
He bragged about himself.
Said he represented top
fashion labels,
went to Stanford,
came from a good family,
started his own business,
and won many honors.
They're all true.
I didn't know, so I made up stories.
Did Daniel know before he died?
Yes and no.
I didn't tell everything.
Susan.
Can I look around my house?
Come on, Susan.
I dated Daniel for 7 years.
Took him 7 days to marry this woman.
Whisky.
3 years. You broke up 4 years ago.
They don't count.
We have this in different colors.
Miss.
Please look around.
Are you crazy?
Stealing our own product?
At least it's ours.
Don't defend her!
Daniel and I spent 7 years
to build this company.
Took Daniel 7 days to marry me.
I just lost it on the spot.
This can't go on.
You have to find something to do.
Tell me, what's your ambition?
It's done: To marry a rich man.
And he passed away.
Call me next time if you lose it.
I'll get you any bag you like.
Why help me?
You're my sister-in-law.
Daniel loved you. So do I.
Where's my purse?
Did you see it?
No.
It was just here.
Strange.
I had it on me.
Still don't recognized me
after 3 years?
Sorry, Whisky is too old.
The master is dead, Whisky is dead,
you are no good!
Go take a look.
I smell gasoline!
There's a girl. Call the police.
This is Saigon...
What street?
I'm not sure.
The road is under construction.
Miss, wake up.
Am I dead?
Miss...
Call ambulance.
Am I dead?
Not yet! Go back now.
But it's going to hurt.
What if I'm disfigured or crippled?
You'll be fine!
Hurry!
I'm dead. Leave me alone!
You better listen to me.
Who are you?
Why should I listen to you?
Left arm and left leg are broken.
3 broken ribs on the left.
Left lob is punctured.
A clot is compressing
on the left optic nerve.
Everything okay on the right?
Yes.
Let's all move to the left.
Your left or my left?
The patient's left!
Why is it taking so long?
Long enough to butcher a pig.
May, you better be all right.
Daddy's too old for this!
I left the triad for you.
Now I go to bed at 10, wake up at 6.
How I can go back to that life?
Who'll pay for the bills?
Or the mortgage?
If May dies, her money will be ours.
Shut up!
Be nice to your stepsister!
May's money came from Daniel.
If she dies, it'll go back
to Grandma.
Shut up!
Be nice to your stepsister!
We're her immediate family.
The money is ours!
Grandma
It's okay.
Sit.
Move!
No, you sit.
No, sit.
You were here first.
No. I'm a gentleman.
Come on.
Fine. Thanks.
It's hot.
Hot? Let me.
It's ready, please.
Thanks.
How's May?
Don't know, we've been waiting
for hours.
I'm sure she'll be fine.
Thanks for your kind words.
What now?
My shoe.
We'll stand.
- Sit.
- No.
Sorry.
Please sit.
No!
We will not sit. Okay?
Room 3, bed 19. It's this one!
A young beauty. What a shame.
Nobody escapes death.
Officer, what are you doing?
We're told she'll die in 5 minutes.
We came to pick her up.
Who are you? What's it to you?
I know her.
So? This is not your business.
No, officer, why her?
She just barely escaped death.
So she'll die again.
Don't interfere with us.
Leave. Our order says it's her.
Is it possible you made a mistake?
We never make mistakes.
This is odd.
Doctors said
she'll make quick recovery.
It's not her time yet.
Anything can happen in 5 minutes.
How?
She's energetic
and is eating a banana.
Eating a banana doesn't mean
she's energetic or she won't die.
Ever heard of "sudden death"?
But she doesn't have the look of it.
There's a look of it?
There is! I'm an example.
I looked different right
before I died.
See?
Then we'll wait and see how she dies.
Why not double-check your order?
Right, we don't want any mistakes.
Hurry, check your PDA!
I don't need you to teach me.
Then hurry! So?
No looking!
So?
We'll look ourselves.
Correct! She's choked to death.
It says she'll choke on banana.
No, it says she'll choke on plantain!
But she's eating a banana.
They're the same thing.
Banana and plantain are different.
They are?
I think so.
But look at the size of that.
It's a plantain!
Size doesn't matter!
It's still a banana.
It also says your subject is a man.
The name doesn't match.
Really?
May Ho!
It's true.
But we have the right room number.
Isn't this Kowloon Hospital?
This is Hong Kong Hospital.
Told you you were wrong!
You just wouldn't admit it.
Calm down.
You could've took her away
by mistake.
I wonder if this is how I died.
We'll be on our way.
Kamen Rider again protects
mankind from the Shocker.
Go! Go! Let's go!
To protect the peace of the world!
You can see me.
My left eye sees ghosts!
May, are you allowed to smoke?
Doctors said it's fine.
What's wrong with Daniel's plants?
May is no good
May, are you allowed to drink?
Doctors said it's fine.
What's wrong with Daniel's Whisky?
May is no good.
Susan, we came to visit May.
You shouldn't scream every time.
Whisky's dead!
Grandma, I'm still a patient.
What do you usually do in the house?
Smoking, drinking, sleeping,
eating, watching TV!
If you can drink and smoke,
it means you can work.
Come to the office on Monday.
Be on time.
May is very devoted.
Daniel's car is a wreck
but she's keeping it.
Forget it...
I give up.
Do whatever you want.
If it's death then so be it.
Just don't make it painful.
I took sleeping pills. I'm tired...
What happened to you, puppy?
Relax.
You forgot to hit the brake
and shut the door.
Hurry! It's dying.
Hurry!
Drive carefully!
We'll do everything we can.
Wait outside.
It's the medicine.
I'll go wash my face.
Sorry, I'm really scared.
I'm serious.
I'm awake... I won't sleep...
What do you want?
Ask me if I'm a ghost.
Ask me...
May Ho!
Are you a ghost?
Yes, I'm a ghost.
Ask me...
If we went to school together.
Did we go to school together?
Yes, NTK elementary school.
I was your classmate.
Guess who I am.
Class President.
No.
Vice President. Wrong again.
Treasurer. No.
Secretary.
I got it.
Why don't you ask me if I'm Ken?
Are you Ken?
That's right!
People knew me as
"Ken The Class Clown"!
Ask me how I died.
How did you die?
I pulled a great stunt!
When I was 13, it was incredible...
May Ho!
The puppy's fine, Mrs. Tsui.
Left without a word.
The puppy stays here tonight.
We'll call her tomorrow.
Mrs. Tsui is so irresponsible.
Look at the mess.
Morning, Mrs. Tsui.
Sorry, I saw a ghost last night.
It led me to a sick puppy,
which I brought to a vet.
I fell asleep there.
The vet didn't see me
and locked the door.
Fine, it was the traffic.
Fine, I over-slept.
Please excuse us.
Where's the ashtray?
No one smokes here.
What is that?
A great knock-off from Shenzhen.
We don't even carry this style.
Handy compartments.
Good for cell phone and cigarettes.
We represent this brand!
I can't deal with this!
You don't want to work?
What's there for me to do?
I don't care.
You can daydream
or play computer games.
But you'll come here everyday
for 8 hours.
Then I'll play computer games.
Fine by me.
May.
I got you an ashtray.
How's the game?
Pretty low score.
Surfing the web?
Want to fix Daniel's car?
That'd be wonderful!
Dad bought Daniel the car
when he was born.
They are the same age.
The license number is his birthday.
Daniel loved driving it around.
Come with me.
Are you afraid of ghost?
Did you really see something?
Then...
Have you seen Daniel?
Has he come back to see you?
He's a ghost too, right?
I made it up. There's no ghost.
It doesn't exist.
That's a relief.
I'd hate to see Daniel as a ghost.
If he were a ghost,
he wouldn't want us
to see him anyway.
It was really a ghost you saw!
The kid died when he was 13.
March 4th 1979...
Let's see.
"Boy suffered nasty fall
using umbrella as parachute"
He fell to death.
Wrong!
He was in the fourth grade that year.
I saw him on TV 3 days later.
May 16h 1980...
"Boy strangled himself using curtain
as Tarzan rope"
He was strangled to death.
Wrong!
He repeated fourth grade that year.
I saw him on TV 3 days later again.
1981...
Wait dad, there's this much more?
Yes, a lot more.
"He was stung by bee,"
burned by candle, electrocuted
by wall socket,
bitten by dogs...
Enough... I remember...
That year he repeated
fourth grade again.
Skip to the last accident.
The one that killed him.
September 10th 1982...
Right, he was expelled that year.
I never saw him again.
"Naughty boy lost in ocean
during typhoon"
"Most likely have drowned"
That's all.
No more articles.
The body was never found.
So he was drowned.
Who else was drowned?
Your brother-in-law!
That's the person who left you
with all the money.
He was trapped in algae
while scuba-diving in the Caribbean
and drowned!
Don't you forget that!
Ken, are you here?
This is May Ho.
Is there anything I can help?
Are you May Ho?
You're Sam Wong?
No, I'm his father.
He just left. He's an airline pilot.
Sorry, we've only talked
through e-mail.
You want to fix this wreck?
It belonged to my late husband.
I see.
I didn't want to trouble Sam,
but no one else can help.
I found him on the web.
No trouble.
Sam is crazy about
fixing classic cars.
It's good to keep him busy anyway.
It's a good distraction.
He's still upset over
his girlfriend's death.
You should cheer up too.
The deceased would want to
see us happy.
Did I take the pills?
One more.
May.
What?
I have a friend coming.
He's a doctor. A nice guy.
His family is in
the shipping business.
I think he suits you.
May.
Come on, May.
I'm tired. I should go.
You should date again.
Miss.
Your friend?
No.
I'm from the other table.
I've been watching you.
Can we be friends?
I mean it.
I meant what I said.
Don't just stand there.
Go wash your eyes before
you go blind!
May, Daniel's been dead for 3 years.
Tina.
Your friend?
May, this is Ben.
Hi.
Give me.
I'll go get drinks.
I asked Tina to introduce us.
I've noticed you for 3 years.
Can we be friends?
I mean it.
I meant what I said.
I really want to help you.
You're ill. I'm a psychologist...
I'm not after you.
I like Tina.
I just wanted to please her!
Should've said so.
Have a good time, he's not bad.
I know.
The letter is for you.
Sorry... Ms. Ghost.
I'm going to be reincarnated.
Congratulations...
But I can't let go of my boyfriend.
Put him behind you.
Look at me and my husband.
He leaves me alone,
and I don't miss him.
I can do anything I want,
go anywhere I want.
It's so free!
Promise me, take care of Sam for me.
No... There's nothing between us.
I've never met him.
We only used e-mails.
Relax, I want you two
to be together.
I know you're destined to.
Impossible. Do tease me.
Good thing don't come by easy.
Hang on to the letter.
Don't open it until June 17th.
It'll help you.
Okay.
Ms. Ghost?
Ms. Ghost.
Sorry. I won't open it.
"The life of the dead is placed
in the memory of the living."
It's me!
You scared me!
I'm in big trouble.
We are facing a great disaster!
Are you getting married?
I don't know what happened.
I woke up like this.
Then Biggie said she was marrying me.
It's "After Death Wedding"!
She followed me all day.
May...
It's done. I got Ken a wife.
Why?
I found a priest.
She said Ken likes you.
So I did this to keep him away.
"It cost me $38,000!"
Don't hurt my dad!
No... Ken?
No, Ken!
It... It's here?
Leave, dad!
I'm going.
Go!
Remember... $38,000...
Don't...
Calm down. I'll handle this.
She won't listen to you.
She will.
Ms. Biggie.
No one likes me.
It's just a misunderstanding.
See? She won't listen.
No one likes me.
Why? You're cute.
She's cute?
Look at her ugly face,
her flabby arms,
and her big butt!
Quiet. Want me to help you?
Ms. Biggie, he can't marry you.
What else can we help you with?
I want to be thin.
- Impossible!
- Shut up!
- I want to be pretty.
- Impossible!
Shut up!
I want to be like you.
I want guys to stare at me.
Can I possess you?
Impossible. Marry her, Ken.
Impossible.
Just once.
Let me be pretty for 1 minute.
I'll get Ken to marry you.
But I want to possess you.
30 seconds?
My lucky break.
I won't let her possess me.
20 seconds? 10 seconds? 1 second?
Guys would stare at me in 1 second?
I'm not THAT pretty.
That's true. How about 1 minute?
30 seconds? 20 seconds? 10 seconds?
She's just going in circles.
1 minute? 30 seconds? 10 seconds?
Enough. Will you leave?
I'll get a priest to put you away.
My father knows many
with great powers.
I've never been thin.
I've never been pretty.
It's my final wish...
It'll really just be a minute?
It's been more than an hour.
You should come out.
I want men to yearn for my affection.
Darling.
Honey.
I want men to go crazy for me.
To fight each other...
FOR ME!
Have you had enough? Come out!
No, I want to flirt with men
and party with them!
Go for it, darling.
What monster dares to come here!
It's powerful!
Please take care of him, Buddha.
I'm possessed...
Stop running!
I'm possessed!
Stop screaming!
Ken...
Help!
Somebody help...
I'll be back!
Ken...
Ken, are you all right?
Take me home.
He wants to go home.
Then take him.
I can't reach him.
Umbrella...
He wants an umbrella.
Yes, he'll use it as a medium.
This is all I have.
Ken, we're home.
Ken...
Answer me, Ken!
Help!
Any ghosts here?
"Kowloon Funeral Parlour"
My friend is hurt. He's a ghost too.
He went into a temple to save me.
I don't know what to do.
Can you help?
Too late. They got away...
He'll dehydrate.
Please think of something.
Experience tells us it's too late.
He needs to go back to water
if he was drowned.
You're too young to know.
How long did you live?
How long have you been a ghost?
3 years.
4 years.
90 years!
Why didn't you grow?
Want to see my aged look?
You want to?
No...
Put him into water!
He's still unconscious.
It'll have to depend on his will.
A priest is here.
She's powerful. Let's go!
May...
Don't worry,
I brought the priest here.
May...
Too late. They got away.
There's one more.
No...
You're a liar just like your dad.
May...
I paid, come over.
Cost me $58,000...
Don't get in the priest's way. Come.
Bring me salt.
Understood!
He died in the ocean, he needs
to be soaked in salt water.
You won't take him in?
- How are you two related?
- Classmates.
There's more.
I think you two are lovers.
He didn't reincarnate
so he can protect you.
But we're really just classmates.
Did he date you after you grew up?
How? He died at 13.
He's been dead this long?
How did I miss that?
The beef I ate earlier must've reduced
my power.
Salt's here.
Done!
It's done?
It's a symbolic ritual. Let's go!
The salt is expensive.
May, the total is... $96,000.
$96,000!
Don't give up
Madam...
It's okay... I know him.
Wait... I'll break it!
1, 2...
Kamen Rider comes back to life.
He defeated the evil Pot Monster.
Rice will be available to all people.
Yes!
So how do I contact you?
"Easy, like this."
Ken!
I'll appear right away. Try it.
Try it.
Ken...
No, it's cheesy.
Cheesy? It's cool!
Ken!
- I'll snap my finger.
- No.
Ken.
A finger snap.
No. Ken.
- A finger snap.
- Ken.
A finger snap!
Fine... Have it your way.
Why?
Don't know.
Why aren't you reincarnated?
"It's my treat tonight."
"Have a good time with Mao Tai Wine."
Something you can't let go?
"Sorry, my athlete foot itches."
"Then use Tinaction!"
Are you in love with me?
I know, you saved me
from the accident.
What accident?
It was suicide!
Believe it or not,
I love my husband deeply.
I don't bother telling people that.
Who would believe it?
They'll just say:
"7 days is not love."
"She only loved his money!"
Even if they don't say it,
that's what they'll think:
"7 days is not love."
"She only loved his money!"
Sometimes even I ask myself:
"7 days is not love."
"I only loved his money!"
"So why get so upset?"
But who knew
I would miss him this much?
I really... really miss Daniel.
I've seen many ghosts
with my left eye,
but I never saw my husband.
Maybe he's thinking the same thing:
"7 days is not love."
"She only loved my money..."
Ken...
Where are you? Come on.
Cheer up...
Ken...
What?
Well anyway,
thanks for the puppy.
I like it very much.
Wake up... Get up...
It's blind... Poor thing.
It's blind.
It's mad... Poor Thing.
It's mad.
Don't bring me more puppies.
I thought you like them.
I like flowers now.
Like them?
Yes!
How can you pee here?
You'll drown the plants!
Let's give them names...
Okay.
President, Vice President,
Treasurer, Secretary...
How about the last one?
We'll call it May Ho.
- Ken!
- May!
It's a male!
How did I miss that?
You blinked!
Not fair.
A fly got into my eye. Again!
You scared me!
Let's play hide and seek...
I want to watch TV.
I hate you!
I know you forwarded
Sam's message to me.
Don't deny it, I saw Daniel's car.
"But anyway, thank you."
It's not right playing
video games everyday.
Give me something to do.
I'll think about it.
Anyway, thank you.
Here you are!
We're worried about Tina!
What's wrong?
Tina has changed into another person.
She has lousy taste in clothes,
and would beat me up
when she loses temper.
Her appetite also grew.
She wouldn't stop eating!
What do you think is wrong, Susan?
Grandma, I think Tina's got...
Bulimia!
How come? There weren't any signs.
Grandma, Tina doesn't have Bulimia.
Then why can't she stop eating?
She's possessed.
That increases your appetite?
It's Biggie!
Tina, you'll eat yourself to death.
Tina, what's wrong? Don't scare me!
I'm not Tina.
Why are they here?
You won't stop me from eating.
Stay there!
What are you holding?
Let's be friends.
Is it the red chopsticks?
It's nothing. She's just possessed.
Drop the chopsticks!
Drop the fork!
Okay, calm down.
Break it! Toss it over!
Here comes Ken! Where's the monster?
I'll protect the peace of the world!
Yes!
Biggie Monster?
Ken.
Leave me alone. I'm afraid of Biggie.
You'll protect the peace of the world
for me.
Ken!
Jerk!
She's full. She never eats much.
You'll stuff her to death!
I mean no harm. I just want to eat.
It's the only thing
I want to do right now...
For 10 years I starved myself trying
to look pretty.
I regret doing that...
Every woman does the same thing.
I'll be reincarnated to Ethiopia.
There'll be no more food.
I just want to eat a big meal,
rub my tummy,
and let out a burp.
A satisfying burp.
If that's all you want, possess me.
Hurry before I change my mind.
Tina...
What happened?
A fat ghost possessed you.
You ate a lot.
Will I be fat?
These pills will help.
What's May doing?
She's helping you.
Go for it...
I burped!
That's two...
That's three.
Congratulations!
It's time to go.
To Ethiopia. The baby's due.
Did she burp?
Yes. Three in a row!
Thank you.
Thank you, May.
How much did I eat?
Everything on the table.
How many calories is that?
Spaghetti is 500, Chicken is 700.
Spaghetti is 900.
Chicken is 1200. It's fried.
And the soda.
It's okay, exercise will help.
You bailed out on me!
Lucky I took care of it.
What? Why staring at me?
A staring contest? Let's go!
I'm so happy today.
Grandma and Tina thanked me.
We went to Karaoke together.
I and Tina played drinking games.
Tina even accompanied me
to the bathroom.
Where did you learn that?
You're over-reacting.
I didn't touch you. I just slipped.
But it isn't right!
I have a husband.
How can you kiss me?
We are friends!
Elementary school friends!
I thought you knew that!
I'm going to be reincarnated.
So you really can see ghosts?
Ever since the car accident.
What are they like?
They wonder about...
There are many things they can't do.
I have cancer. I have 3 months left.
The company is up to you and Tina.
I'm not good enough.
You just have to. There's no choice.
I had my doubts about you.
But after what happened to Tina,
I think you have what it takes.
You can do it.
Does Tina know?
I told her last night.
She cried all night.
And hasn't stopped.
Come on... Baby...
Hand...
May Ho, I'm leaving. Good-bye!
Ken...
I said good-bye already. What now?
You always come and go so suddenly.
I bid you farewell.
Are you in a rush? Grandma is dying.
I'm a ghost. What can I do?
It's fate.
I want to see Daniel.
He's a ghost too.
There's nothing he can do.
I want to see Daniel!
Why didn't you ask me until now?
Fine.
Daniel drowned in ocean,
so talk to the ocean.
Go ahead.
What do I say?
Tell him the exact opposite of
what you're thinking.
Why?
How would I know?
That's the tradition.
It's okay. Go ahead.
Daniel!
I don't miss you! Don't come back!
Will it work?
Whisky?
What's this?
It's Daniel's dog!
It's really working!
Daniel, I've lived happily
in the last few years.
Don't worry about me.
I'll take care of Grandma, Tina,
and the company.
Daniel, I don't want
to see you anymore.
Not one more look. Not one more hug.
Can you hear me?
Can you hear me? I don't love you!
I don't love you!
I just want to see you and hold you.
Why won't you come?
He probably crossed
the Twilight Junction.
His memory is erased.
It's too late to turn back.
Does this mean I'll never see him?
What you said to him was great.
It's probably
what Daniel would've wanted.
Take good care of yourself from now on.
Because very soon...
I'll cross the Twilight
Junction too...
You'll forget me too?
I don't want to just leave.
But I worry...
the longer I stay...
the harder it is to let go.
Before I go...
Can you give me a hug?
How? I can't even touch you.
Just pretend I'm Daniel.
How?
Close your eyes, and think I'm him.
Close your eyes.
Didn't you always want to see me?
You said you missed me.
I feel the same way too.
I never left you, I was always here.
I know you love me.
People may say:
"She only loved him for his money!"
I know that's not true.
I really do.
"Twilight Junction"
I have to go.
Don't be a naughty boy
in your next life!
Don't play with window curtain
or umbrella!
And stay home during typhoon!
You hear me?
What?
Good-bye, Ken!
It's beautiful!
Your boyfriend is something!
It's too soon...
It's beautiful...
Your son is something!
It's not done yet...
He's back.
Son, May Ho is here.
May Ho!
You haven't changed, just got bigger.
I'm Sam Wong!
People knew me
as "Ken the class clown"!
Remember? We went to the same school
I repeated the fourth grade
for 3 years.
After that I was expelled.
Didn't you drown when you were 13?
Almost! But I hung onto
a piece of wood.
I swam as hard as I could.
I had the will to live.
I wanted to take care of dad!
Liar! He lost his tuition
playing Mahjong,
Had his friend calling me
to say he was drowned.
I was so scared.
So I called the police.
Why didn't I know?
Something's wrong...
Sam has had on crush on May
since childhood.
Stop screaming.
Sam never said he liked you.
Damn it!
I think you two are lovers.
He didn't reincarnate
so he can protect you.
People may say:
"She only loved him for his money!"
I know that's not true.
I really do.
Good-bye, May.
Daniel!
Who are you?
I'll call the police!
Be my guest.
Daniel!
Daniel...
You see the old man
in the white jacket?
Yes.
He's not a ghost.
You see the longhaired girl
in white robe?
It's her pajama. She's buying supper.
I lost my vision.
What more can we ask for?
We have someone who loved us,
and protected us after death.
We should do something for them.
Let him go, May.
Mrs. Tsui died peacefully.
I'm sorry for your loss.
May...
There's only you left...
No!
Please...
Don't be stubborn, May!
I want to open up my third eye
to see Daniel!
You saw him! For an entire year!
I didn't know it was him.
He chose a different appearance
so you won't miss him more.
He chose Sam because
he is destined for you.
Open yourself up!
I want to open up my third eye!
Told you it's not possible.
Listen to her.
Why can't you understand?
I'll pay any price
I'll give all my fortune!
Fifty, Fifty!
She's your daughter!
I really can't help.
Think I don't want your money?
Your husband wanted you see him
crossing the Twilight Junction,
because he wants you to forget him.
It's good-bye forever!
Do you understand?
Let him go?
Keep on living
Thank you, Daniel.
May Ho!
It's beautiful!
Sure! I replaced the gearbox, the engine,
even the hood.
Is this still Daniel's car?
My girlfriend had liver, kidney
and lung transplants,
but she's still my girlfriend.
You believed that? I was kidding.
Your girlfriend gave me a letter.
Before or after her death?
After... What's the date today?
June 17th.
Just in time... It's today!
What?
You were at the Caribbean
4 years ago?
I met Daniel that day.
What were you doing?
Sand got into my eyes. He helped me.
Which eye?
My left eye.
What does it mean?
Was everything pre-destined?
Sorry.
It's okay.
It's too soon for me too.
I'm going. Bye.
Bye.
What are you doing here, President?
How do you know its name?
It's mine. It was missing.
Yours?
Yes. It's a little crazy.
I'm also missing a blind
and a cripple.
They're all here!
Vice President, Treasurer,
Secretary...
Your husband was a thief!
Where's the other one?
May!
Here you are, May.
It's called Ken.
May.
Ken.
- May
- Ken
It's called May!
It's a male!
We can still call her May.
See? It's responding to the name.
May...
It's not listening to you. Ken...
Put it down...
See who it'll follow.