[Church bells chiming]
BOTH: Bonjour, monsieur.
Bonjour.
Bonjour, monsieur.
Say bonjour.
Bonjour.
Ahem.
STORYTELLER:
Once upon a time...
there was
a quiet little village...
in the French countryside...
whose people believed
in tranquilite.
[Doors bang shut]
Tranquility.
[Organ playing]
CONGREGATION SINGING:
Come Holy Ghost
Creator come
From Thy bright
heavenly throne
Come take possession
of our souls
And make them all Thine own
Far from us drive our...
STORYTELLER:
If you lived in this village...
you understood
what was expected of you.
CONGREGATION SINGING:
...unto us bring
And through all...
STORYTELLER: You knew your
place in the scheme of things.
And if you happened to forget,
someone would help remind you.
[Snorts]
The season of Lent is upon us.
This is, of course,
a time of abstinence.
Hopefully,
also a time of reflection.
Above all,
let this be for us a time...
PERE:
a time of sincere penitence.
[Dog whimpers]
PERE: It is a time
to stand up and be counted.
STORYTELLER: In this village...
if you saw something
you weren't supposed to see...
you learned
to look the other way.
PERE:
This is a time for Christ.
When you reflect,
he knows what you reflect on.
STORYTELLER: If by chance...
your hopes
had been disappointed...
you learned
never to ask for more.
PERE: He knows for what
you must be forgiven.
[Wind whistling]
So in this Year of Our Lord,
1959, things...
STORYTELLER: So,
through good times and bad...
famine and feast...
the villagers held fast
to their traditions.
Until...
one winter day...
a sly wind
blew in from the north.
PERE: Where will we find truth?
[Wind blowing]
Where do we start looking?
[Wind whistling]
PERE: Where will we find truth?
We will find it...
[Door closes]
Who the hell are you?
Oh, uh...
We're here about the patisserie.
We'd like to rent it...
VIANNE:
and the apartment above.
Where are you from?
Well, we lived in Andalucia
for a while.
Let me see.
Before that, Vienna...
and before that...
- Athens.
- Pavia.
ANOUK:
Pantoufle hated it there.
Pantoufle is her kangaroo.
But he can't hop.
Bad leg. War injury, huh?
I'll expect you to keep it
in good condition.
[Door slams]
[Vianne chuckles]
[Humming]
ANOUK:
What a nice town this is.
Don't you think so, Mama?
It's a lovely town.
Mama, Pantoufle wants to know
how long we can stay.
VIANNE: Oh, tell Pantoufle
not to worry.
[Whispering]
Time for bed.
What story tonight?
Pantoufle wants to hear
about grandmere and grandpere.
Not tonight, Anouska.
ANOUK: You always say that.
Tell about
grandmere and grandpere.
Not tonight.
How about the princess
and the pirates?
ANOUK: OK.
ANOUK: Prepare to fire!
All hands on deck!
ANOUK: Ready, aim...
fire!
REYNAUD: Forgive the intrusion.
VIANNE: It's a pleasure.
ANOUK: Sorry, monsieur.
- Pirate attack.
- Of course.
What is your name?
Anouk. What's yours?
I am the Comte de Reynaud
at your service.
ANOUK: A real one?
Like the Comte de Monte Cristo?
Ah-ah!
He was not a real one.
VIANNE: To what do we owe
the honor of your visit?
Well, as mayor of Lansquenet...
I want to welcome you
to the community...
and to invite you to worship
with us at mass on Sunday.
That's very kind of you,
but actually we don't attend.
VIANNE: We're glad to be
so near the church, though.
We'll enjoy
singing with the bells.
The bells are not intended
as an entertainment, Madame.
They are a solemn call
to worship for...
VIANNE: Mademoiselle.
I beg your pardon?
Mademoiselle.
I've never been married...
but feel free to call me Vianne.
I hope you'll stop by when
I open for business next week.
Yes.
Yes, opening a patisserie
during the holy Lenten fast.
I could imagine better timing.
Oh, but it's not going
to be a patisserie.
Then what do you intend to...
It's a surprise.
It was sweet of you to drop by.
STORYTELLER:
The Comte de Reynaud...
was a student of history,
and therefore a patient man.
He trusted the wisdom
of generations past.
Like his ancestors, he watched
over the little village...
and led by his own example...
hard work, modesty...
self-discipline.
I have completed
the 18th Century.
[Sniffling]
Madame Clairmont.
Your letter to the editor,
Monsieur le Comte.
This paragraph about family
and tradition, it's...
it's beautiful.
Oh! Ha ha.
Well, thank you.
I value your opinion.
[Dog barking]
[Door closes]
VIANNE: Bonjour! Hello!
REYNAUD: May I ask...
have you been in contact
with your mother recently?
CAROLINE: Why?
She seems to have
rented out the patisserie.
CAROLINE: Oh.
I haven't talked to my mother
in quite a while.
I'm sorry.
I did not mean to pry.
Oh, don't be silly.
I have no secrets from you.
How is the comtesse
enjoying Venice?
The comtesse?
Oh, she's fine, thank you.
Yes,
she's enjoying it very much.
Venice.
[Sighs]
WOMAN: I heard she was
some kind of radical.
I heard she's an atheist.
What's that?
Don't know.
GUILLAUME: Come on, Charly.
[Whimpering]
Come on.
Oh!
Uhh! Oh!
You should be more careful!
- So sorry, Madame.
- I'm sorry.
VIANNE: Are you all right?
CAROLINE: I'm fine, I'm fine.
VIANNE: I'm sorry. Do you want
to come in and sit down?
CAROLINE: Please don't
trouble yourself. I'm fine.
VIANNE: No, it's no trouble.
I'm Vianne Rocher.
Caroline Clairmont.
I'm the daughter
of your landlady.
This is my son Luc.
VIANNE: Hello.
And this is my Anouk.
Come in, please,
where it's warm.
Try this.
I bet you've never
had hot chocolate...
made from
a 2,000-year-old recipe.
Thank you, but no. Luc.
CAROLINE: No.
WOMAN: What's this?
What do you see, Madame,
in this?
Sorry?
VIANNE:
What does it look like to you?
Just say the first thing
that comes into your mind.
WOMAN: Um...
A woman riding a wild horse?
Ha!
- Ooh!
- Oh, silly answer.
Oh, no.
There are no silly answers.
The pepper triangle,
that's for you.
A tiny hint of chili pepper...
VIANNE:
to play against the sweetness.
Tangy, adventurous.
What do you see?
I see teeth.
LUC: I see blood...
and a skull.
Very dark.
VIANNE: Bitter chocolate.
That's your favorite.
CAROLINE: Which will
have to wait five weeks more.
Lent. Thank you.
We must run along.
It's been nice to meet you.
My pleasure.
ANOUK: Pantoufle, come on!
Pirate attack!
WOMAN: How much are
those chili things, please?
VIANNE: 4.50 a box.
Could you put a ribbon on it?
Mm-hmm.
WOMAN: Then I can pretend
they are from my husband.
Of course.
[Woman laughing]
[Whispering]
WOMAN: Josephine Muscat.
She waltzes to her own tune.
And these are for your husband...
unrefined coco nips
from Guatemala...
to awaken the passions.
Ha!
You've obviously
never met my husband.
never tried these.
[Snoring]
[Music plays on radio]
Don't be pathetic.
[Kids shouting]
[Kids shouting and laughing]
[Door opens]
CAROLINE: Luc.
You've got a tiny error
in problem six... Oh!
Luc! Oh.
It's nothing.
It already stopped.
Mother, the new teacher...
wants us to correct
our own mistakes.
I didn't tell you
how to correct the mistake...
I just told you
that you made one.
[Knock on door]
[Moaning]
[Footsteps]
WOMAN:
Not hungry, Monsieur le Comte?
The Lenten fast, Madame Rivet.
Are you not supposed
to eat something?
It's all right. Leave it.
[Whispering]
VIANNE: Hello.
May I help you?
It's expensive.
I don't waste money.
I have a knack for
guessing people's favorites.
These are your favorites.
Am I right?
VIANNE: On the house.
I think I'd better...
[Mumbling]
WOMAN: Well...
SECOND WOMAN:
This certainly is different.
THIRD WOMAN:
Yes. Very different.
WOMAN: Look at that.
[Dog barks]
WOMAN: Oh!
Oh. I'm so sorry.
Bonjour, Monsieur Blerot.
Bonjour, Madame Audel.
[Dog barking]
GUILLAUME:
No. Not that way, Charly.
Come on.
Come in! Please.
Come on, boy.
I've got something for you.
VIANNE: What's your name?
GUILLAUME: Charly.
He's fourteen years old.
That's ninety-eight
in human years.
No, I meant your name.
Oh! Guillaume Blerot.
You're very kind.
He has so few pleasures left.
Would you care...
VIANNE:
Would you care to buy...
something special
for your lady friend?
Lady friend?
VIANNE: The lovely woman
your dog was so fond of.
Oh.
VIANNE: Her favorite
is chocolate seashells.
That's my guess.
Oh, no. I mustn't.
Madame Audel is in mourning
for her husband.
Oh, I'm sorry.
When did he pass away?
The war. German grenade.
Hmm.
Well, it's been fifteen years
since the war, so...
Not that war.
Monsieur Audel was killed
on January 12, 1917.
It was quite a blow
to Madame Audel.
Apparently so.
- Hmm.
Bonjour, Mesdames!
ALL: Bonjour, Monsieur le Comte.
I wish all my tenants...
were as reliable as you,
Madame Drou.
How is the comtesse
enjoying Italy?
Uh... She may be
extending her trip.
MADAME DROU: Ah, very nice.
Have either of you seen
the new shop across the square?
The chocolaterie? Yes.
Shameless, isn't it?
[Clicks off]
REYNAUD:
The sheer nerve of the woman...
opening a chocolaterie
just in time for Lent.
REYNAUD: The woman is brazen.
My heart
goes out to that poor...
illegitimate child of hers.
Mmm.
Bonjour.
[Singing] You ain't nothin'
but a hound dog
Cryin' all the time
PERE SINGING: You ain't nothin'
but a hound dog
Cryin' all the time
Well, you ain't never
caught no rabbit
You ain't no friend of mine
Ooh, yeah!
REYNAUD:
A new addition to the liturgy?
I have a weakness
for American music...
Monsieur le Comte.
How long have you been with us,
Pere Henri?
It will be five weeks.
Your predecessor, Pere Michel,
he was with us for five decades.
Yes, well...
I only pray I can live up
to Pere Michel's example.
Yes, that's my prayer also.
I looked at your sermon,
as you requested.
I've made one or two notes.
You're very kind.
Not at all.
Oh, one more thing.
If you haven't seen
the new chocolaterie...
perhaps you might
like to take a look.
It's important
to know one's enemy.
Don't you think?
VIANNE: Hey, where's my kiss?
Aah! Ugh!
Watch where you're going!
ANOUK: Excuse me!
Hello. Morning.
What's the decor,
Early Mexican Brothel?
No! If I need help,
I'll ask for it.
What do you see in it?
Not a damn thing.
Come on. It's a game.
VIANNE: What do you see?
I see a cranky old woman
too tired to play games.
VIANNE: Hmm. I've got
just the thing for you.
ARMANDE: That little girl
of yours, does she mind it?
Mind what?
The way you move her
from place to place.
Oh. She's doing fine.
I think it's good for her.
VIANNE: Seeing new places,
meeting new people.
Your cinnamon looks rancid.
Well, it's not cinnamon.
It's a special kind
of chili pepper.
Chili pepper in hot chocolate?
VIANNE: Mm-hmm.
It'll give you a lift.
There.
[Sniffing]
It tastes like...
I don't know.
[Chuckles]
BOY: Hop, hop, hop, hop!
SECOND BOY:
Where's your kangaroo?
ANOUK: Uhh!
BO Y: Hop, hop, hop!
I'm your kangaroo now!
[All yelling]
Stop it!
Stop it! Unh!
Anouk! In this school,
we are civilized.
We do not strike one another!
ANOUK:
But they insulted Pantoufle!
TEACHER: I don't care.
Didi, Dedou, come along!
[Slams door]
TEACHER: And be quiet.
Where's Pantoufle?
Shh!
My mother says
you don't have a father.
Sure I do.
We just don't know who he is.
I was out all night with him.
We swam naked in the Tannes.
At dawn, when I returned
to my house in my bed...
my mother poked her head
in and said...
"Wake up sleepyhead."
[Laughing]
She had no idea I'd been gone.
Sure you didn't
put booze in there?
Nah. Something better.
Perhaps you should
give it to my daughter.
ARMANDE: Melt that chilly
disposition of hers.
You and Caroline have a problem?
Do we have a problem?
She won't let me
see my grandson.
I'm cut off from him.
VIANNE: Why is that?
Armande, why is that?
Oh, I'm a bad influence.
'Cause I don't like her treating
him like a trained poodle.
I swear, that boy doesn't piss
without her permission.
ARMANDE:
Ever since her husband died...
she's been so...
The way she frets
and fusses over that boy.
If only she'd let him run,
let him breathe...
let him live.
But she worries
that he will overexert himself.
Not much danger of that.
She won't even let
the poor kid ride a bicycle.
Do you think
he'd like to see you?
Do you have more of
those bean thingies, please?
Oh, sure.
VIANNE: How many do you want?
How many have you got?
Jack of hearts is a better
hunter than you, eh?
Shoots the trump
from right out under your nose.
Are you Serge Muscat?
The one and only.
What's your pleasure?
- Is your wife here?
- Josephine?
Well, it depends what
you want with Josephine.
Oh, she left this at my shop.
Well, let me have it.
I'll give it to her.
Oh, no. I'll give it
to her myself, thanks.
MAN: Got to go.
I'm late for supper.
SECOND MAN:
But the game's not over yet.
Do you want to play?
You know Belote?
Of course I do.
Sit down.
[Footsteps]
VIANNE: Josephine.
[Clatter]
What do you want?
You forgot this.
To be your friend.
I don't have friends.
Does Serge know you're here?
Does it matter?
Do me a favor.
Try one of these rose creams.
Tell me if you think it's
a little heavy on the Cointreau.
SERGE: Josephine!
I'm coming!
JOSEPHINE: He talks about you.
He says you're indecent.
He says you're an influence.
You're a bad influence
for someone like me...
I don't have to listen to a word
your husband has to say.
JOSEPHINE: No, not Serge.
Not him.
Reynaud, the mayor.
He... he talks about you.
Time to go.
Look what I won.
That's good. Come on.
[Man laughs]
MAN: Bonsoir.
SECOND MAN: You see?
I said they'd be here.
[Birds chirping]
Luc, mind if I take a peek?
Oh, um...
It's not really...
Show me.
Oh.
Well, I exaggerated
the angle of the head.
You draw beautifully.
What's your going rate?
What?
To do a portrait.
How much would you charge?
Oh, I...
[Insect buzzing]
I couldn't.
I'm not really a...
Fifty francs?
Sound reasonable?
It'd be great.
[Vianne chuckles]
When could you come by my shop?
Oh.
I'm... I'm really sorry, but...
the comte forbids it.
He spoke to Mama this morning...
and a lot of others.
Whatever you say.
I wish I could. I really do.
Thanks for showing me
your drawing.
Wait.
[Door slams]
Am I breaking any laws?
Tell me?
Am I hurting anyone?
You're asking me my opinion?
What exactly have you been
telling people about me?
Only the truth, mademoiselle.
Well...
if you're expecting me...
to just shrivel up
and blow away...
you're going to be
highly disappointed.
Let me try and put this
into perspective for you.
REYNAUD:
The first Comte de Reynaud...
expelled all the radical
Huguenots from this village.
You and your truffles
present a far lesser challenge.
REYNAUD: You'll be
out of business by Easter.
I promise you that.
Aah!
Uhh!
Aah! Aah!
[Baby crying]
VIANNE: How long have you
been standing here?
I forgot to pay you
for something the other day.
I'm sorry.
No, it was a gift.
No. People talk.
No, people would lie about me.
I don't steal.
Not on purpose. I...
VIANNE: Yes, I know.
It's nice to see you.
Would you like to come in
for some chocolate?
This is for you.
How sweet of you.
VIANNE: Thank you.
Hmm, it's lovely.
I heard you don't go to church.
That's right.
You won't last long here.
JOSEPHINE: People talk.
Oh, sorry.
I'm behaving badly, aren't I?
VIANNE: No, it's OK.
JOSEPHINE:
You don't misbehave here.
It's just not done,
did you know that?
If you don't go to Confession...
or if you don't
dig your flower beds...
or if you don't pretend...
that you want nothing
more in your life...
than to serve your husband
three meals a day...
and give him children
and vacuum under his ass...
then... then you're crazy.
You must think I'm stupid
to stay with him.
No, I don't think you're stupid.
Well, I am. I'm weak.
I don't love my husband,
and I lie.
Things could be different
for you, Josephine.
Serge doesn't run the world.
He might as well.
VIANNE:
Is that what you believe?
I know it.
Oh.
Then it must be true.
My mistake.
You make the most
wonderful chocolate.
[Sips]
Pantoufle wants
to hear the story...
of grandmere and grandpere.
Ohh!
Don't say, "Not tonight."
You always say, "Not tonight."
All right, all right.
Oh.
Your grandfather...
George Rocher...
was the young apothecary
of the town of Aulus-les-Bains.
STORYTELLER:
It was Anouk's favorite story.
Always told in the same words.
George was honest,
prosperous...
and trusted by his customers.
But George was not content.
He felt there
should be more to life...
than dispensing liver oil.
In the spring of 1927...
the Societe Pharmeceutique...
formed an expedition
to Central America...
to study
the medicinal properties...
of certain natural compounds.
George was the expedition's
most eager volunteer.
But his adventure
took a turn he did not expect.
One night, he was invited
to drink unrefined cacao...
with a pinch of chili.
The very same drink
the ancient Maya...
used in their sacred
ceremonies.
The Maya believed
cacao held the power...
to unlock hidden yearnings...
and reveal destinies.
And so it was
that George first saw Chitza.
Now, George had been raised
a good Catholic...
but in his romance
with Chitza...
he was willing
to slightly bend the rules...
of Christian courtship.
The tribal elders
tried to warn George about her.
She was one of the wanderers.
Her people moved
with the North Wind...
from village to village...
dispensing ancient remedies...
never settling down.
Not a good choice for a bride.
George did not
heed their warning...
and for a while,
it seemed that he and Chitza...
might lead a happy life
together in France.
[Wind blowing]
Alas, the clever North Wind
had other plans.
[Banging]
One morning,
George awoke to discover...
that Chitza
and the little girl Vianne...
had gone away.
Mother and daughter...
were fated to wander
from village to village...
dispensing
ancient cacao remedies...
traveling with the wind.
Just as Chitza's people
had done...
for generations.
VIANNE:
Just as Chitza's people...
had done for generations.
Will it just go on forever?
Night, Mama.
I appreciate your coming in,
Armande.
What's so important
that I had to postpone my nap?
I've got some chocolate cake.
Grandmother.
Grandmother... bonjour.
May I...
Would you like a cup of...?
No, thank you.
I'm just here to do a portrait.
Mm-hmm.
Whose?
Yours, actually.
VIANNE: Is the light OK
where she's sitting?
I have something for you, boy.
I've been carrying it around
since your last birthday.
It's a book of poetry.
Oh.
Thank you.
You don't like poetry?
Oh, no. Of course I do.
Yes.
Neither do I.
It's not that kind of poetry.
And in a moment of weakness...
I prayed to the Virgin Mother...
to soothe Charly's soul
in his hour of suffering.
You understand an animal
has no immortal soul.
I understand, mon pere.
Yet you flout God's law.
GUILLAUME:
I'm weak and a sinner.
PERE: What else?
Impure thoughts.
GUILLAUME: The woman
who runs the chocolaterie.
Vianne Rocher?
She suggested
I buy chocolate seashells...
for the widow Audel.
And, well...
I guess that got me to thinking
about the widow Audel.
At her age? At your age?
Yes. And yes.
And just what were you doing
in a chocolaterie during Lent?
It was for Charly.
Again you flout God's law.
Well, but if Charly
has no soul...
then there's no harm
in him breaking Lent.
GUILLAUME:
Isn't that so, mon pere?
Ten Hail Marys,
twenty Our Fathers.
"Will she never have done,
then...
"that ghoul queen of
a million dead bodies?
"I see myself again...
"skin rotten
with mud and pest...
"worms in my armpits
and in my hair."
It's perfectly wretched,
isn't it?
Perfectly.
VIANNE:
Would you like some cake?
Ahem. I'm not supposed to.
Don't worry so much
about not supposed to.
ARMANDE: Hmm?
Live a little.
Oh, her hair appointment's
almost done.
I have to go.
- What about my picture?
- Next time.
LUC: Thank you for the cake.
Don't look so damn pleased
with yourself.
[Knock on door]
Stay here.
[Pounding on door]
[Pounding louder]
JOSEPHINE: I did it.
[Laughs]
I did it. He...
He was so drunk.
[Giggles]
He woke up.
He saw me packing, but...
So he tried to come after me...
but I had already tied his feet
with his belt, and...
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Boom! Right on his face.
[Laughing]
Right there
on his big, red face.
VIANNE: Mmm.
VIANNE: Oh.
Tsk. Ohh.
It is so stupid, isn't it?
I never blame him.
Sometimes I even forget
what really happened.
VIANNE: Now, now, now.
[Crying]
VIANNE: Shh.
I saved her!
You remember her father
collaborated with the Germans?
Nobody wanted to touch her.
Except for me.
And this is the way
she repays me?!
Your anger is understandable.
Anger?
Everybody's laughing at me!
REYNAUD:
That is not your concern.
Your concern is
the sacrament of marriage.
SERGE: Yeah, of course.
The sacrament.
VIANNE: Dip the ganshbe
into the white chocolate.
Like this?
Good.
Yes, shake it, a little.
Put it on the parchment sheet.
You're doing great.
[Door opens]
Oh. I'll be right back.
Oh. Good morning.
Can I interest you
in some Nipples of Venus?
Rumor has it that you are
harboring Madame Muscat.
REYNAUD: Is that true?
You make her sound
like a fugitive.
She is a fugitive,
from her marriage vows...
which have been
sanctified by God.
Josephine?
VIANNE:
Come out here a minute.
Let His Radiance
have a look at you, hmm?
VIANNE: Is that sanctified
enough for you?
It's not the first time.
I'm truly sorry.
REYNAUD:
You should have come to me.
Your husband will be made
to repent for this.
Tell him to repent
on someone else's head.
REYNAUD: Come on. In!
SERGE: Monsieur le Comte!
I'm going to make
an example of you.
In there. He's ready.
Well, but confession
must be made...
in the spirit of contrition.
Have you come
in the spirit of contrition?
Contrition, yes.
He's ready.
[Sighs]
BAPTISTE: Licentiousness,
idolatry, sorcery...
gluttony, and drunkenness.
Correct.
And what are the three
conditions for mortal sin?
Serge?
Mortal sin...
is sin whose object is...
committed by...
deliberate... consequence.
Incorrect. Didi?
Mortal sin is sin
whose object is grave matter...
which is committed
with full knowledge...
and deliberate consent.
PERE: Correct.
Gah!
VIANNE:
So, how do you know...
if the coverture
is properly tempered?
JOSEPHINE: You check to see
if it's at body temperature.
Then you dip
the palette knife...
to see that the coverture
hardens on it evenly.
Correct.
Closer.
Aah.
STORYTELLER:
In the village, time passed.
And the chocolaterie
did not go out of business.
[Drops package]
[Charly yelps]
STORYTELLER:
The Comte de Reynaud...
felt himself being drawn
into a strange crusade.
His struggle to transform Serge
into a gentleman...
became more
than an act of good will.
It became a test...
a holy war between chateau...
and chocolaterie.
[Charly howls]
LUC: Each time, I...
I tell myself
it's the last time.
But then I...
I get a whiff
of a hot chocolate.
Or those moon things.
AUDEL: Chocolate seashells.
So small, so plain, so innocent.
I thought,
just one little taste...
it can't do any harm.
But it turned out
that they were filled...
with rich, sinful...
YVETTE: Buttery filling...
and it melts,
God forgive me...
it melts ever-so-slowly
on your tongue...
and tortures you with pleasure.
PERE: Against You alone,
have I sinned...
and done what is evil
in Your sight.
[Plastic crinkling]
[Crinkling stops]
Indeed I was born guilty...
a sinner when my mother
conceived me.
You desire truth
in the inward being...
therefore teach me wisdom
in my secret heart.
[Swallows]
STORYTELLER:
Now, the comte was no fool.
Though he hoped
to redeem Serge...
he knew that
this redemption alone...
would not be enough...
to regain control
over the village.
He understood
that some larger lesson...
needed to be taught.
Some greater problem...
needed to be identified
and solved.
Little did the comte suspect
that his greater problem...
would arrive
one quiet afternoon...
in the dull green waters
of the river Tannes.
[Children playing]
You're it!
Hey, look!
BOY: I'm over here!
VIANNE: You've never really
told me what the problem is...
between you and Caroline.
'Cause it's none of
your damn business.
[Armande sighs]
ARMANDE:
I'm an embarrassment to her.
I swear, I read dirty books.
I eat and drink what I like.
And sin of sins...
I refuse to go to Les Mimosas.
JOSEPHINE: When I was a kid,
we called it Le Mortoir.
It's a nursing home for old...
It's in Toulouse.
Mmm.
ARMANDE: Caroline loves
the thought of a nurse...
with a clipboard
recording my bowel movements.
ANOUK:
Mama, Mama, come quick!
They're here!
They've come to Lansquenet!
- Slow down, Anouk. Who's here?
- Pirates!
Come on!
- Why can't we stay?
- Come on!
BOY: But why can't we stay?
OK, enough.
BO Y: But, Mama,
just a little bit.
MAMA: Come on.
VIANNE: Hello. How are you?
ANOUK:
Anybody got a sweet tooth?
[Guitar playing]
[Guitar continues playing]
I bet he's the captain.
VIANNE: Anouk, don't do that.
Anouk, don't do that, please.
- How do you do?
- Sorry.
ROUX: I'd like to apologize.
For all of us. Sincerely.
What for?
ROUX: For whatever it is
you're here to accuse us of.
Why would I do that?
Well, because we river rats
are the dregs of society.
With horrible diseases
and criminal impulses.
[Chuckles]
Sounds terrifying.
Is it true?
It's what you townspeople
always seem to think, isn't it?
This is not my town.
Sorry.
ROUX: Well, then,
what do you want?
Are you here to save us?
Are you
the Catholic Aid Society?
French Family League?
Communist Workers?
Which idea are you selling?
Chocolate.
I'm sorry, chocolate?
ANOUK: What's a river rat?
Is it like a pirate?
[Vianne chuckles]
Yeah, you could say that.
You could.
Have a look
at my treasure chest.
VIANNE: Oh.
Let me guess, they're for sale.
ROUX: As a matter of fact,
they are.
For a mere thirty francs apiece.
You laugh? I can get fifty
for them in Paris.
Then go to Paris.
We'll take two, please.
You'll take two?
Yes, please, absolutely.
ROUX: OK.
VIANNE: I don't know
if I have the right change.
Just a minute.
They're beautiful.
ROUX: Ireland's finest.
Thanks.
Thank you. Listen...
I should probably warn you.
You make friends with us,
you'll make enemies of others.
That a promise?
It's a guarantee.
[Laughing]
ALPHONSE: What's he up to?
JEAN-MARC:
Maybe he's joining the circus.
[Door rattles]
Sorry, we're closed!
Josephine, you look different.
So do you.
I just want to tell you
that I am so sorry.
SERGE: For everything.
But I've changed.
You see,
God has made me a new man.
I ask you, I beg you...
please accept my apology.
I accept.
I promise, from now on,
everything will be different.
Everything already
is different, Serge.
[Chuckles]
Well, I mean,
when you come home.
Home?
Thanks for the apology.
The flowers are lovely.
No, please don't, Josephine.
We are still married
in the eyes of God.
Then he must be blind.
[Locks door]
JEAN-MARC: The council
has no legal authority...
to force them to move.
The riverbank is public land.
[Grumbling]
The mayor wishes
to say a few words.
REYNAUD: If I may...
ladies and gentlemen
of the council.
These people are
rootless, godless drifters.
MAN: That's right!
REYNAUD: Theirs is the way
of slovenly pleasure.
MAN: Yes.
They would contaminate
the spirit of our quiet town.
REYNAUD:
The innocence of our children.
Now, the chairman of the council
is quite right.
We cannot force them to leave.
MAN: Why not?
But we can help them
to understand...
that they are not welcome.
[Muttering]
[Glass shatters]
Josephine?
Josephine, you think
you can just walk out on me?
SERGE: You stupid woman!
Worthless cow!
You're nothing without me.
You can't even use a skillet!
Can't even put
a goddamn meal on the table.
He's inside.
JOSEPHINE:
He's here. Oh, God.
SERGE:
I need to talk to you.
Please open the door.
I know...
- Mama!
- Come help me!
SERGE: Open the door.
Open the door.
I just want to talk to you.
VIANNE:
Go sleep it off, Serge!
SERGE: Ah, you shut up,
you bitch!
You've caused enough
trouble already!
You...
[Pounding on door]
Unh!
SERGE: Open this door!
Mama!
Aah! Aah!
JOSEPHINE: Oh, my God!
[Shouting]
Stay away from me.
Aah!
- Come here now!
- Aah!
SERGE: Aah!
Why, you meddling bitch!
You...
[Choking]
Ahh!
VIANNE: Aah! Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Who says I can't use a skillet?
[Drops skillet]
[Laughs]
[Bell tolling]
Bonjour, monsieur.
Bonjour.
Wonderful.
Come on.
Up. Come on. Up.
[Groans]
Come on.
[Laughter]
His skull can't be
as thick as we thought.
[All laugh]
VIANNE:
It was like swatting a fly.
Ohh. The worst is over.
He found out
what you're made of.
[Laughs] So did I.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Mmm!
How long have we got?
She's at the hairdresser
for an hour.
[Gasps]
Fuffi?
CAROLINE: Fuffi.
I'm so sorry, but I have
to break the appointment.
FRANCOISE: Is something wrong?
CAROLINE: No. I volunteered
to distribute these.
I promised the comte I'd have
them out by the end of the day.
FRANCOISE: Count me in.
Not that I expect any of them
to stop by for a hairstyle.
CAROLINE: It's not just that.
The comte feels
we must stand firm.
We cannot trust these people.
Before you know it,
they'll be doing jobs for food.
They'll be begging
at our doors.
FRANCOISE: Not at this door.
CAROLINE: Good, Fuffi, good.
[Exhales]