Miss, your dog is very pretty.
Yeah, it's like our dog Lucky!
Bring your dog to our home
if you've time, we live in 9/F.
What are you doing in my house?
I love cleaning my body before...
doing my job!
This is the 5th homicide case
in these 2 months.
It's such a cruel murdering,
but there is any clue left!
It must be done by
the professional killer.
Damn it! The murderer is cold-blooded!
The murderer even broke the man's dick!
Isn't it the music?
Yes.
How do you remember it?
He loved watching Japanese blue tapes
which made much noise.
Say, the women yelled loudly!
But on last night,
he changed to classical music.
So, I remembered very well about that!
How do you know
he loved watching blue tapes?
I saw once in my classmate's home,
the girls made the same noise.
What's on?
He is the 3rd witness
who heard classical music...
during the period the man was killed.
I guess, the murderer used to listen
Mozart's music when killing.
Are you the one who loved
listening Mozart's music only?
Officer Lee, we found 2 more corpses
at the staircase of the 9th floor.
They are believed to be an aged couple.
PC369, make a statement for that.
Yes Sir, kid, come with me.
The murderer might have seen them,
so they were killed.
Shave if you have time,
stop pretending to be great detective.
Officer Lee, I suspected that
there was only one single killer.
The murderer may be a woman.
I regret to ask you here!
How could a woman throw a man,
who was over 200 lbs from here to there?
From the way he was killed,
how can you say it's done by woman?
Say the last 2 cases,
legs and arms of the naked victims
were broken.
Even the reproductive organs
were teared off.
And this victim,
legs and arms were broken,
the skull was cracked.
The reproductive organ
was busted by bullet.
So, I suspected it was done by woman.
About the last 2 cases,
that was caused by sex dispute.
And this one,
must be a punishment by the triads.
Tinam, please! Forget the illusion.
Officer Lee, I suspected
the last 2 victims were killed in bed...
the murderer killed them
when making love with them.
Were they making love
with a female gorilla?
How can a woman have such force?
This must be done by couples of men.
Tinam, take more rest!
But now I am normal!
You killed your own brother 2 months ago
How can you become normal
in such a short time?
What are you talking about?
I wanna kill you if you don't shut up!
Officer Lee,
it's an accident, you know it!
Yes, for this case,
the ordinary people will never forget!
I make you resume duty soon,
is giving face to your passed brother.
Shit!
In fact, you should take
6 months more psychotherapy.
But I am normal now!
You claim yourself normal?
You don't even know how to hold a gun!
Are you normal?
Not any nuts will admit they are nuts!
You are transferred to
the Anti-vice Dept. from next week.
You should not follow this case!
Have you hair cut and shave,
you will look better.
Stay where you are! Don't go!
A colleague is hurt, call the ambulance!
Brother, how will you get hurt?
Brother!
Buy some napkins in times of period.
To shut his mouth and his ass.
This is my treat!
I won't give it to another.
What do you want to hint?
Do you want me to give you
something in return?
Don't you think I am that practical?
You are like a... wolf!
Wait!
This girl is so bitchy!
You can sleep with her this time!
I will be the next!
Lower your voice! Don't let her
hear that! Or we won't have chance!
Hold your scissors well!
Woman is made by fire,
you may easily get hurt, be careful!
Never mind, I have a big hose!
If you cut my ear, I will cut your hose!
You are fooling me!
What a shit this time!
Tommy!
Why don't you call me these days?
Don't you see me working hard?
I will call you later.
Do you want to brush me off
because I am pregnant?
What? You mean it's my baby?
How can you prove it?
You always fool around,
I wonder it's the baby of the rascal!
Are you framing me?
Girl, take the abortion in Shunzhen,
that's easy!
Why bothering us?
She is my girlfriend only.
How dare she frame me!
I have lived with you for half year!
You are the only man in my life!
He wants to brush you off!
He is fond of me, why don't you leave?
I am sorry!
Don't tell me of bearing my baby!
I am sponsoring you some money!
Take few hundred and leave now!
Damn you, how dare you frame me!
I will help you to get rid of your baby!
You are great!
Go to hell!
How dare you bully my friend!
Do you trust me now?
Stop crying!
He shampooed my hair twice,
then he dumped you!
You should forget this man!
Let me take the revenge for you.
I will cut his dick off!
Cop, stop!
- Help!
- Stop!
Let's go!
Call the ambulance!
It seems that one ball is missing.
You'd better leave first.
Don't move!
I warn you, I will shoot if you move!
Shoot then! Why don't you shoot?
Are you afraid of writing report?
Why did you hit him?
The scumbag deserves it!
Only Ah Si trusts that bastard!
He is called Tommy, not Scumbag!
You are too old, man!
Scumbag means bastard!
I will shout for help.
Rape! Indecent assault!
Don't move!
Do you mean it?
I am just playing with you!
Take the gun back!
You must be scared to throw up.
What's your name?
Tinam!
That's smart!
I will let you go now, because that...
Scumbag!
That Scumbag deserves it.
You shouldn't put it in that way.
It's me, Kitty, who let you go,
I won't sue you!
What are you doing? Why don't you leave?
I would have cut your dick
if you stayed a little bit longer.
Poor man! He forgets the pager!
Chinese pager?
Hello, Chinese pager!
Mr. Tinam, did you drop your pager?
Did you vomit again?
Did you pick my pager?
Yes, I did!
It's lucky for me to pick it up.
I was working there.
How can I take it back?
At least candle light dinner.
I won't waste any time on you.
I work in the Anti-triad Dept.
of Kowloon City,
you bring it back tomorrow.
Shit-head,
did anyone bring me the pager?
I don't think so, but a girl comes,
saying that she was raped
by one of our colleague.
A girl? Where is that girl?
She is inside, Officer Lee
is taking the statement for her.
What?
Fuck!
Tinam, come to see me later.
You look pale!
Bull shit!
Are you nervous?
I am not!
But you are drinking other's milk.
- Alright.
- Thank you.
Tinam, follow me!
The girl...
Come in right now!
You may go.
Do you want any coffee?
I have drunk milk!
The girl told me the story
which she was indecent assault.
You are great!
After you've resumed duty,
this is the 1st day you're praised.
She praised me? What is it about?
Brave in catching thief, strong enough.
You could stand such a long time!
She said you chased
after the wolf for 15 minutes.
He escaped after a long time running.
You are fit, I guess!
I run every morning.
You recognise the guy
who pretended to be cop?
Go with the girl and
picture out that rapist.
- You mean me?
- Yes.
The girl wrote a letter
to the radio station to praise you too.
She is flattering me!
Stop...
Stop!
Kitty...
Just pretend to be my boyfriend
if you are kind enough.
Kitty.
Dad!
What a coincidence?
He is...
He is my new friend.
I understand that...
He is called Tinam, a cop.
I have to go now,
I am hurrying to the flood stall.
Fine!
Take care of Kitty.
Sure! I will take good care of her.
- Don't worry...
- That's very kind of you.
- Bye bye.
Bye bye.
Take care.
You are skilled at using others.
Give me back the pager.
Why not accompany me
to the department store?
Catch the pager.
This is not mine.
Quite sexy.
What do you want? Want a peep?
Pay first.
Are you pretending to be cool?
I think we have some generation gap.
You think it's the common way
to court a boy like this?
What? Should I court you?
If you don't intend to court me,
you needn't fool me for 1 whole day.
You gave me trouble!
I just want to teach you how to behave.
Will you cut the line
in such impolite way in future?
If there is no body around,
won't you afraid I would rape you?
I have seen something of you.
What is it?
Your mole.
Should you point at me
with your hot gun?
It's not funny!
What are you doing?
I should have met you earlier.
You needn't knock so hard!
I didn't!
Hey boy, why not stop here?
We should move now.
They are laughing at you! You wolf!
I haven't had sex impulse for long!
Go and get him.
Kidding? If so, I will change you.
It's your word!
Hey, guy! Are you crazy?
Actually I should thank you.
To thank me?
I haven't agreed to give you advantage.
You will know it later.
I am leaving.
Let me send you home.
You know there is mini-bus
in this world?
What number is your pager?
Lucky number for you.
Lan, what are you doing?
You are bad tempered!
We buy the bowls with money.
I'd work all day!
Why don't you close it? I am tired!
I told you in Mainland
that I am working in a food stall.
But I didn't know I'd be so tired!
If I knew it,
I wouldn't have left Shunzhen!
OK...
It's my fault, OK?
Poor business tonight,
you'd better do it yourself!
I want to sleep!
Dad, what's the matter?
- Nothing...
- Did she bully you again?
Kitty! Forget it.
I don't understand!
What are you scare of?
She is your step-mother anyway.
We shouldn't quarrel for such nonsense.
Have you eaten?
Not yet.
Your boyfriend is so mean
to treat you any meal.
Poor business tonight.
Why not eat the remained wantons?
Let's eat together.
That's good!
Kitty, don't be that mean to the boys!
You should treat your boyfriend better.
I have got it, don't worry dad!
Dad, you'd better go up first,
I want to make a call.
Can you make a call at home?
I don't want that bitch to hear me.
Be good, go up first.
OK, I am going home.
Come back earlier.
OK.
You bastard! You bitch!
Since you come back,
let's settle it among ourselves now.
Your wife wants to live with me.
Just give me few thousand,
that's settled.
You son of a bitch!
I want to kill you...
Don't!
Don't stop me from killing
that son of a bitch!
Go!
I want to kill you...
Go to hell!
Dad! Dad!
- Bee, go now...
- Go.
Don't go!
I wanna kill you bastard!
How dare you kill my dad!
- Bee, leave now!
- Don't go!
Go to hell!
Don't go!
Can you get the girl of that old bag?
Not yet, we don't know
where she is hiding!
Kill her once you get her.
Got you!
Why don't you leave now?
Excuse me...
Where is Bee?
I don't know!
There.
Go to hell!
Do you still want to escape?
You killed my dad?
Don't get mad, stay calm first!
I didn't mean to kill your dad!
I want to kill you bastard! Go to hell!
I will break your head!
Damn it! Do you want to kill me?
Damn it!
Get lost!
Fight back?
Bitch!
Damn it!
You are useless, she is coming alone,
how can you let her hurt me?
Drag her in.
Do you want to kill me?
Rape her! One by one.
Go out first.
Bitch! Damn it!
Let me do it first.
Go to hell!
Let's die together.
What happened?
Don't come over.
Don't come over!
Where is the car?
Not here! It's in the next floor.
Go down!
Don't kill me!
OK, but you should help me.
Why don't you tell me earlier?
I think you are great!
Hold it!
Where are they?
Come on, check over there,
and the rest follow me.
Smile!
- Who are you?
- Smile!
I am Sister Cindy.
Have you waken up?
Why don't you sleep a bit longer?
What are you doing?
Eating noodle.
I will do your next finger after eating.
Are you crazy? You nuts!
You put me in deep shit!
Where are my fingers?
Where have you put them?
Why only 9 fingers are left?
I am so hungry...
I will finish your fingers right
after eating the noodle.
You want to chop this too?
I don't mean to chop it! I want to
change the finger prints for you.
What?
You are crazy!
But you are crazy!
Look at this.
A thief broke in a finance company
to rob and kill.
They lost a million cash
and some bank notes.
Now, the criminal is wanted
by the police with $100,000 award.
You are famous now!
How can you shoot in such a foolish way?
You left your finger prints
all over the scene!
You know, they have TV.
Now, other than changing your identity
and finger prints,
you still have a choice.
To be put behind bars.
And to be raped by the lesbians
once per day.
Bullied by those powerful women.
When you are released at 40.
Your look will be as old as
a 60 years' old granny.
Nothing else you can do.
But work in the nightclub.
Not to be club girl, or be the manger.
But to be the toilet maid.
Stop!
You recognise my face too.
We killers can't let any one
who recognise us to be alive!
Do you want to kill me?
I won't kill you!
Why do you help me?
It's your luck!
I have found that
you are born to be a killer.
What are you?
A killer!
Killer?
Professional killer.
Not common killer.
We clean the society too.
To clean away the rubbish of the world.
Like the scumbag Bee.
He deserved to be killed.
We killed those bad eggs only.
Do you want me to help you?
Not helping me, but help yourself.
You know, you are wanted.
Why to be killer?
To make big money.
After that,
you can control the things yourself.
You know, who is powerful,
who can give order.
Who is powerful, who can give order?
I don't think you will choose
to be put in prison.
This is your new information.
Shang Hill-qun?
Your job is air-hostess.
You are coming from Singapore,
23 years old.
You've no parents, but just one sister.
I am sleepy.
Come on!
What are you doing?
Who is he?
He is the wolf...
who raped many girls in Lamtin District.
I have watched him for a long time.
I just want to teach him a lesson.
Bitch, do you want me to rape you?
Let me do it!
Damn you bastard!
- Scumbag!
- Why did you beat me?
It's your bad luck to meet Miss Kitty!
Come on, why do you stop?
Where are you, Sister Cindy?
Are you taking weapon?
Give me the knife to cut his balls out!
I want you to try the taste of danger!
I won't open the door for you.
Open up! You bitch!
The key is put round the man's waist.
Either he rape you,
or you kill him!
Bitch! Open the door,
or I will break your tits!
I will count 3, One, two...
Go to hell!
You bitch, I want to burst your tits!
You bitch! I want to burst your tits.
3 minutes and 7 seconds.
That's too slow.
I have put 10 pieces of glasses,
4 screwdrivers, 2 bricks and a wire.
And I put a gun down below the wall.
You still needed 3 minutes to kill him!
You have poor judgement.
What if I was raped by that nuts?
Then, you should blame yourself
of being shit!
Remember,
when you have no choice but to kill.
You should find any weapon
which could kill.
But how about having no weapons?
Use your brain.
We women, our body is weapon too!
How about if we have no tits?
Can you let me touch a bit longer?
Men, just to please them.
No matter you have big tits
or small tits, it doesn't matter.
Just to make them happy.
Can you explain it?
I am a killer, but not a hooker.
It's just the same!
Big tits, small tits, even no tits...
No big deal!
Come on, beat me!
I have knife, I have advantage!
Help!
You are useless,
why do you still cry for help?
Just think how to defeat me!
You are twisting my leg!
How can I rebel?
OK, now twist my leg.
You would be in deep shit!
I am hurt! Stop...
The principle of killing,
anything you get in hand,
will become the killing weapon.
Besides knife or sword,
high heel shoes, socks,
and teeth brush...
Teeth brush?
I used a teeth brush
to stab into a man's nose.
It reached the brain, and he was killed.
But, the most powerful weapon is...
Our bodies.
No matter men or women.
Just to make them impulse,
that is his weakest time.
No one can resist from that!
At that time,
that's the most perfect moment to kill.
To kill with full confidence,
you should study
the target's information first.
So, you can pose him to be your enemy.
To make a file for him.
You should know his living habit,
the place he often goes.
His hobby, his merits
and his shortcomings,
and his temper too.
Even his sex habit.
Sex, is the wonder weapon of us.
No matter men or women,
they will be attracted by sex.
One of your senior, she is a lesbian.
Senior?
Stop mentioning about her.
Anyway, you should know pretty well
about your enemy.
Let me teach you how to make that file.
Isn't it so?
How do you have my file?
I searched your stuffs
when you went out.
Don't you afraid I would discover that?
You went to Mainland 4 years ago.
I think you have forgot that thing.
You are named Shaw Bing.
You are 35 years old, Scorpio.
You wear 36D bra.
You have the habit of drinking red wine.
You don't have sex life
for quite a long time.
How do you know that?
You masturbated twice in these 5 nights.
How dare you peep me!
I peep you every night.
Don't shout so loud next time.
Our neighbors can hear it.
You are bad enough!
Remember? We are killers!
But I tell you.
Those I killed were all bad eggs
who deserved being killed.
Only your senior,
She loves money only.
She will kill her own dad too.
You don't want to mention her!
She is the most famous killer
in our circle.
You will meet her sooner or later,
but be careful.
I know she is powerful!
How do you know that?
If not so, you won't make her file!
You are really smart!
But we should be careful!
Have you asked your fellow
to buy you breakfast?
They are buying.
What are you wondering?
Are you still thinking of the girl?
She killed many people,
it's troublesome for you
to meet her again!
The buddies of Bee
are searching for her.
Don't you think Kitty is poor?
You should show mercy to yourself first.
It's too cruel for you
to take my only cigarette.
The murderer is more cruel than that!
This case is more horrible.
The victim lost the penis!
What?
Our buddy is questioning
the Philippine maid.
I don't know.
Sir, your breakfast, sausage with eggs.
What did you hear last night?
I don't know.
Did your master sleep with you?
Who touched your ass?
You wolf!
What's happened?
Sir, they can not find...
They can't find the...
What?
The stick?
What's stick?
Bird, bird!
Bird? What's bird?
You don't know bird?
I don't know bird.
I don't know what are you talking about.
What's the matter?
I don't know how to tell him
that his penis was missing.
Just tell me penis!
You shit-head!
Bastard!
Why don't they heat the sausage first?
It's cold.
There is some flesh up there.
What is it?
- It seems to be the balls.
- What?
Scrotum!
The color is smiliar to the one
which you are holding.
Don't you want me to lose my appetite?
Never!
Are there a girl bathing?
What are you staring?
There is a woman standing
and watching here for a long time.
What does that mean?
There is a precedent in the study
of criminal psychology.
The murderer loves to
come back to the scene.
You mean the girl is the murderer?
I suspected that it is related to
a female killer group.
Like the last case,
and the case of Kitty.
She was staying with a woman.
I suspected that
it's related to the last case.
The head won't trust you.
I do.
I have listened your opinion.
I think there are more than
one female killers who worked nearby.
They use different ways of killing,
some are brutal and some are not.
I will inform your boss to send you
join the investigation.
Thank you Sir.
OK!
You will have chance now.
If you let me choose,
I prefer seeing Kitty again.
Look at you,
it seems you have eaten the penis.
Have you eaten the lost penis?
What?
Don't you think I have eaten the penis?
Kitty...
Sister Cindy,
I have put the key on their bodies.
And I have removed all the weapons.
The wolves will burst your tits
this time!
Come on!
I admire you so much!
Kitty, you will carry
your first mission tomorrow.
I will take you to kill a Japanese.
He is called Taki.
To kill someone in Japan?
Should I wait you at the entrance?
Are you nuts?
Sure!
If someone tricks me,
I will sell you to be gigolo
for one year.
I... I...I...
I was born in Beijing!
You sing very well!
Damn you! It's the password!
Where is my aphrodisiac?
Boss, here it is!
Why did you spray it to your mouth?
To make the tongue harder, I guess!
What is your name?
My name is Baby.
Baby?
Do you dare
playing some exciting sex game?
I won't mind exciting sex game!
OK!
After this job,
should we go to Hawaii for vacation?
No.
We have a big deal left.
What is it?
I am ordered by the Japs
to kill one person.
A person who is difficult to be killed.
Who is it?
It is...
Sister Cindy.
Isn't she your master?
My master is difficult to deal with.
I have heard that she has a new student.
I wonder... are we sufficient
to kill them together?
We should kill them one by one.
First,
we should kill her genius student!
Do you agree?
Sure!
You have tried every means
to join my dept.
I can't reject anymore since
you have applied for so many times.
Thank you Sir.
About the chained homicide cases
happened recently,
the way of murdering is like
those happened half year's before.
Our head considered your presumption
of a killer's group,
and a branch leader of a triad society
died last night,
the way he died
was similar to those cases.
His limbs,
including his penis were all broken.
It's like to be teared off
at the same time.
Are there any clue?
Yes, few hours before
the murderer was killed.
Someone saw that he was staying
with an air-hostess.
Is she the suspect?
I do want you to tell me.
An air-hostess lives in
such a big house!
She must be a mistress of a rich man!
The house may belong to her dad!
I think it's the house
of her sugar daddy.
Who are you looking for?
We are cops.
We'd like to meet Miss Shang Hill-qun.
Miss, there are 2 cops looking for you!
Are you cops?
Kitty?
Kitty!
I haven't raised any kitty.
I am Tinam, Kitty!
I am sorry, I am called Shang Hill-qun.
I think you have mistaken me.
By the way, you can call me Vivian.
Sorry,
I mistake you as one of my old friends.
May I know what you are looking me for?
I want you to assist us
to investigate a homicide case.
It's related to Mr. Kan Tin San.
I don't know this guy.
At 10 p.m., October 2,
someone saw you staying with the victim.
I met him in the cocktail party.
He just wanted to send me home.
So you are the last one
who saw him before his death.
Hope you can give me a statement.
No problem, I have to get changed first.
Shit head!
What is it?
Don't you think she is like Kitty?
Who is Kitty?
Kitty is the girl who came to look for
Officer Lee some times ago.
You have so many girlfriends,
how can I remember all?
I am sure Officer Lee
will recognise her!
It's a serious case,
tell the buddies not to spread
any news to press.
What's the matter?
There is an accident of Officer Lee.
Detective Ti!
Why did Officer Lee suicide?
I don't know,
5 minutes ago, I heard a gun shot.
I rushed in, and saw him in the blood!
Few hours before he died,
Someone saw him staying
with an air-hostess.
Shit-head, take a statement.
Are there anything happened?
When did you reach the cocktail party?
8:30 p.m.
What kind of cocktail party?
A film's premier gala.
I was invited by my girlfriend,
but she didn't come.
What is the victim called?
Isn't it Mr. Kan?
Yes, it's him.
He came and chatted with me.
The cocktail party was so boring,
so was the film!
He promised to send me home,
so I went with him.
Where do you live?
No. 99, Old Peak Road.
Are you used to look at the man
like this?
Am I handsome?
Among the men in Hongkong,
you are quite handsome.
Forget this line.
Are you free for dinner tonight?
Let's eat beef set?
Isn't it delicious?
Are you alright, sir?
I am fine.
You do want to prove me
to be your ex-girlfriend.
Yes, you are my ex-girlfriend.
I have told you many times, I am not!
But,
I am glad to be a substitute of love.
- David.
- Tinam.
I don't think you can't recognise her.
She is Kitty
who taught Tommy a great lesson!
I am sure I can recognise Kitty.
I have witness, Kitty.
Detective Ti,
where is Kitty whom you mentioned?
Are you crazy? She is sitting here.
Do you mean it?
She doesn't seem to be Kitty.
Don't fool me!
I dare not!
If you want me to say yes,
I will return you the money.
Detective Ti, I think you miss
your ex-girlfriend very much.
If not, you won't mistake me as her.
You are right, I am fond of that girl.
Not long ago,
she got involved in a homicide case,
I wanted to find her out and help her.
But I could never get in touch with her.
She seems to be disappeared
in this world!
If the girl knows that,
I think she will be touched.
Really?
Detective Ti, I want to leave now.
OK
David...
Fuck!
Call the ambulance!
David...
I am Tinam!
I am Shit-head,
the air-hostess has been shot.
She is now in the hospital,
she wants to see you.
Oh shit!
Kitty...
Tinam!
This is for you!
The flowers are pretty!
Are you Kitty?
Do you know you are in great danger?
Are you still thinking of that girl?
She must be Kitty.
Her eyes!
I can tell she is Kitty from her eyes!
She doesn't admit,
you can't prove she is.
But, the witness died one after one.
The girl is dangerous,
it's not wise of you to go with her.
That's why I want to find the truth.
Do you think you are superman?
You are a cop only.
We have a gun more.
My instinct tells me that,
something you can't do it by force.
Just do what you're instructed,
or you would be in deep shit.
I just want to tell you a secret.
After killing my brother.
I have become impotent.
What? That's shit!
I have never impulse.
After seeing Kitty, on the next day,
I woke up...
I had erected.
Congratulations.
Until seeing her by the pool side,
I have the sense of impulse.
Don't you want to tell me
only she can cure your impotence?
Kitty!
Who are you looking for?
I am sorry, I am looking for Miss Shang.
She hasn't returned yet.
Well, I'd better leave first.
Wait!
Just come in to take a seat.
Take it.
Thank you.
How do you know I love drinking Vodka?
For men,
it's of no reason for them
to reject Vodka.
I am the sister of Hill-qun.
They called me Sister Cindy.
Is she called Shang Hill-qun?
From my lawyer,
I know that my sister is no relation
with the case.
It mustn't be business for you
to come to her again.
My sister, she has many boyfriends.
Do you have confidence?
Sure I do!
I love this kind of man!
I am sorry, I want to add some ice.
I have heard that...
You mistaken my sister as another person.
I am sure she is one of my friends!
Sorry, I am leaving.
Who do you think she is?
A person whom I would never forget.
Sister Cindy.
Kitty!
What are you doing?
Do you want to court me?
Just give him a chance!
Have dinner here tonight, OK?
He is busy.
Sorry, I want to get changed first.
My boyfriend will
come to pick me up later.
I know you are not Kitty.
But in case you are Kitty,
I do want to help you.
May I be excused.
See you!
Why do you stop me from killing him?
He is a cop,
it'd be troublesome for him to die here.
I can make his corpse disappear!
But someone would know
he has visited here.
Say the one inside the police station,
I could kill them
without any clues left.
No one will suspect us.
I think, you don't want him to die.
He is not worth dying!
He knows to much!
And he is suspecting you too.
If I don't kill him,
you will be killed one day.
Remember our principle.
Don't be controlled by your emotion.
I can do it myself.
Can you?
Are you that hard-hearted?
There is always the first time.
This house is exposed,
I want to sell it.
I will arrange you to some place else.
Enjoy your first time.
Don't disappoint me.
Are you searching for your pager?
When did you come in?
I have come in for a long time.
But I don't want to bother you.
Lower your voice next time.
Don't bother our neighbors.
Give me back the pager.
He does love you!
No wonder you miss him that much!
Why do you change the battery so often?
I haven't thought of him.
I want to tell you.
The Japs want to take revenge,
they hired Princess to kill us.
Princess?
She is your senior.
You should be careful!
Don't let her see you.
May be, she will kill after raping you.
The men are all heartless.
Don't fall in love with men.
Otherwise, you will be the loser.
Shit.
Have you waited long?
Do you miss me?
I miss you so much!
Kitty!
I am Hill-qun, don't come to me again.
What are you going?
You are totally different!
Yes, I was forced to do so.
I don't even know you.
Kitty.
I am Shang Hill-qun,
I come from Singapore.
All the documents can prove my identity.
Take it back.
You are lying.
You are Kitty, don't deny it.
No!
Are you Kitty?
Princess,
you didn't seem to make love with me.
You enjoyed so much,
how can you say that?
Although you are holding me,
you are thinking of her.
What are you doing?
When did you start jealousing?
If you don't, why didn't you kill her?
You are not listening to me.
You know the result of not obeying me?
I want her by all means.
Why didn't you admit yourself
to be Kitty?
Because I am a professional killer now.
We have conflicts in our jobs.
My master afraid my identity
would be disclosed by you.
She would kill you.
Sister Cindy is your master, isn't she?
If not were me to save you
in the carpark,
you would have been killed.
About those homicide cases
which left no clues behind,
are they all done by you?
We killed those who deserved dying.
Only my senior,
she kills with no reason.
What do you have in mind?
Either you give up your job,
or I give up mine.
Or, forget each other.
Does your master want to kill me?
I will talk to her.
It's not the good timing
to talk such thing.
I will talk to Sister Cindy later.
If anything happens,
you'd better leave first.
She is a woman only.
How can you help me?
Show me how you hold a gun!
Sister Cindy.
You haven't visited me for a long time!
You are heartless!
Is she my junior?
She is pretty.
She is the one whom I always mention,
Princess!
Princess.
She is Baby!
Greet them!
Baby.
He is Tinam!
I have met him before!
When did you see me?
I have seen you completely!
Sister Cindy said,
you are even better than me!
She is just kidding!
Having 2 wonderful students,
I think I have to retire!
You can't put it that way.
Can you retire?
You should appreciate that...
I visit you once
I come back to Hong Kong.
But, after I leave your house,
we may be enemies.
I know!
My lovely junior,
I think,
you and I will be the best partners.
Only we kill, but not to be killed.
But I am not interested.
You'd better try!
What man can do,
I can do better than them.
Are you alright?
I'm fine, she is a killer.
You have small one,
how can you compare with me?
Sister Cindy, we are leaving!
But before leaving,
may I give you a kiss?
Sister Cindy
Sure!
Let's go, Baby!
Stop searching!
She is taught by me.
I know what she wants.
From now on, she will be back any time.
You'd better leave.
Sister Cindy, Tinam and I...
I can't even protect myself,
why should I kill him?
I want to stay and help you.
Look at yourself in the mirror!
Your eyes are no longer fierce looking!
You are no longer a good killer.
- I...
- Shut up!
Killer can't fall in love!
Once she has love,
she won't kill with barbarity!
Otherwise,
you will be easily killed by your enemy.
Go now.
Why don't find the cops?
Cops?
I killed many people!
Should the cops arrest me,
or arrest her?
I put your dowry inside the pillar.
Come and take it back when it's safe.
Sister Cindy!
OK, let's go!
Why are you driving that fast?
I want to drop you in a safe place.
Now, it's safe!
I am sorry!
Come out!
I am long waiting for you.
Sister Cindy, you are really great!
I can't stop keeping fit once
you are alive.
Do you feel painful?
Why?
It's you who taught me.
A killer should never fall in love,
and should not let others know
about his living habit.
It's no reason,
this wine is newly opened.
There is no problem with the wine.
But, do you remember?
I kissed you before I left.
My lip-stick, plus your wine,
has become severe poison!
So, you are poisoned, but I am not.
You are heartless!
You can't even shoot the cripple!
Go and eat shit, men!
Sister Cindy, I have found that...
Your legs are more and more pretty.
I don't want to leave it!
What do you want? You want to suicide?
Not that easy!
I have found that...
You are a perfect wonderful killer!
Don't you know that...
You can live for 10 more minutes,
Have you tried the greatest killer
in the world?
Not yet!
You shit-heads! Go to hell!
If you are fast,
you can have her for 5 to 6 times.
Sister Cindy, enjoy yourself!
Baby, let's go!
Sister Cindy...
What happened?
Tell me, who did that?
Sister Cindy...
What's the matter?
Don't! Sister Cindy!
Kitty, when you see this tape,
I would no longer be in this world.
Don't feel sad for me.
It's the fate of all killers!
I am glad to see you getting your love.
Forget the revenge,
you can't defeat Princess.
Because you have love in your heart,
but Princess haven't!
Here are some pictures for your memory,
leave as fast as you can.
Sister Cindy!
Princess?
You haven't locked the door.
It doesn't matter.
Can you wake up?
The girl is mysterious!
She appears and vanishs any time.
She killed many lives too.
If you keep on like this, you will die!
Don't you think I am happy now?
You look poor! Shit-head!
I prefer to be killed by her.
At least, I would be happier!
Stop it! You nuts!
Take some food first,
I have bought you some chicken.
Shit-head, are you my friend?
You should help me!
Your gun is collected by the gun room,
you are on vacation!
It would be dangerous
if you get involved!
I don't mind the guns,
I can't even hold it.
Where are you going to?
I want to get an informant for Kitty.
Come here.
Boss, what's the matter?
Boss, I am making money!
You will lose, shit-head!
Have you seen this girl?
This girl?
Why are there so many people
looking for her?
Who else?
A lesbian is looking for her,
she pays much!
How can we find her?
I know she always goes to gymnasium.
Useless!
Man, go and eat shit!
Yes, I eat shit...
What's the matter?
Somebody wants to see Princess.
Baby, check who wants to see me.
Who is it?
Kitty wants to see Princess.
Bring her up.
Yes, Princess.
You are coming eventually!
Find me?
Stop pretending!
Don't you think you can escape from me?
Don't you want me?
Look, you are dressing like a hooker.
Poor taste!
Don't you like it?
I love it!
I love the way you look bitchy!
Princess...
Be obedient!
Otherwise, I will dig your eyeballs out.
Wait me downstairs.
I will wait for you.
This is for you.
How do you know I will come today.
I ask them to buy a bunch of
fresh flowers in every 12 hours.
I know you will come sooner or later.
Love it or not?
It's pretty! It costs much!
So many people in this world,
and there is so much money too.
Money's no big deal!
If anything looks pretty in your body,
I will buy it to you by all means.
I just come to be your partner.
I haven't promised anything, and...
What?
You have a close girlfriend.
How can she compete with you.
Don't you afraid
I am coming to kill you?
I have searched you!
Besides the lip-stick, nothing else.
Don't move, who are you looking for?
Go now!
Let her go!
Do you need to throw up
when holding the gun?
Are you feeling painful?
Don't push me to shoot!
Come on, throw up!
You will feel comfortable!
Tinam!
Baby!
Follow me.
Princess can find us no matter
where we are going.
What'll we do then?
Back to Sister Cindy's home.
OK!
Tinam, we have no chance,
you'd better leave me.
I tried so hard to find you,
I won't give up.
Let's die together.
Princess will come soon,
wait me here.
Be careful!
Have you ever dreamt
the ring was a bomb?
You are too junior!
You should learn more from me of
how to be cruel and cunning!
I remember! You are like Sister Cindy.
You want to die in the same place
as she did.
But, I won't let you die...
before I making love with you!
Isn't it delicious?
It is learnt from you.
My lip-stick is poisoned!
Can't you guess it? Let me tell you!
I am poisoned too, but I can stand it!
Because my stomach is filled with milk.
It will take 3 hours for the poison
to enter my blood.
But you are poisoned at once!
I still have time
to take gastric lavage.
But you, will die soon!
Kitty!
Let me send you to the hospital!
I am handicapped and poisoned,
don't waste any effort to save me.
Kitty, surrender yourself!
You want a cripple go to jail?
Listen, you are all surrounded.
Surrender now!
Sir, Tinam is inside.
Here is filled with gas,
once they shoot, it will explode.
Leave as quick as you can.
It's hard for me to find you,
I'd never let you leave me.