"Kazari and Yooko"
If my mom...
...tries to kill me...
Without fail...
I'll think of a clever way to fake my own suicide.
Kazari and Yooko
- Wel...
- Welcome home mom, right?
Welcome home mom.
Welcome home mom, right?!
Hey mom?
Can I have this?
No you can't, Kazari.
I like that CD.
OK...
You're in my way.
Good morning Yooko.
Want to eat this?
- Mom...
- Easy now...
- I'm leaving now.
- Take care.
Kazari's an angel,
a kind younger sister.
I really love her.
Missing: Male white terrier
by the name of Asou.
Mitsuko Suzuki.
Asou?
Ouch...
Yooko-chan.
- Good morning.
- Time to get up!
Hey, take your clothes off and show us
the marks on your body.
Don't struggle!
It's OK, just a little!
- Cigarette burns.
- I knew it.
You stink!
Do you ever bath?!
We'll get in trouble.
Let's get outta here.
Yooko?
Mom's...
How cute!!
Turn around!
So cute!
Mom's admiring me...
admiring Kazari.
Mom always says...
She gave birth to me...
so she's free to revive me
or to kill me as she pleases.
Asou?
Asou! It's Asou!
Come here, come here!
Are you alright?
- Are you Mitsuko Suzuki?
- You've been safe!
Hey, hey!
Sit over here, OK?
This is handmade, but I wonder if it suits
a young person's taste.
Here you are.
Don't hesitate to eat.
You can have this too, if you like.
Here you are.
Listen, this time let's do it this way.
It's delicious!
It's been so long since anyone
told me something like that.
Asou!
We haven't thanked Yooko-san, have we?
I'll give you a nice present.
I know!
Please have supper here tonight!
Supper?
That's something kind people
like to eat, isn't it?
Yooko-san, you're so cute!
- Want some?
- Thanks!
- Thanks.
Tomato... here!
- Here!
- Stop it!
Here!
I said stop it!
Here.
No more, I'm gonna be sick!
Amazing.
You'll eat anything, won't you, Yooko?
God...
this is secret from mom.
Like this...
You managed?
Alright.
- Thanks for the food.
It's delicious.
I'm glad.
I'm happy!
Hey. What is your twin sister like?
Our faces are exactly the same...
but our personalities are completely opposite.
How interesting!
In what way are you different?
Gloomy... disturbed...
You hate that sort of child, don't you?
I wonder in what way you've been
scolded to think that.
There's must be a reason why you're gloomy.
People can change.
It's in our nature.
Change.
Yooko-san.
Let me flatter you.
It's embarassing.
Nonsense.
Look at your smile.
You're very beautiful.
I'm ugly.
I look like a clown!
Not at all.
You need to learn to love yourself more.
We get along well, don't you think?
Why don't we take a trip together someday?
Get on a boat, go wherever you please.
Start all over.
As best friends.
I won't have to come back?
No, you won't.
We'll live somewhere we like.
Mitsuko-san!
How do I follow that dream,
I wonder...
Practise for our journey?
I like that.
The present I was talking about earlier,
is this actually.
This house already belongs to the two of us.
You can come here whenever you want.
That's right!
This too.
I'll treasure them.
Mitsuko-san.
You stole this, didn't you?
It's just a one-off thing,
forgive her.
Kazari, go to your room.
Listen, want me to tell you something?
How I felt when had you?
When I learned I was carrying twins...
When I think back on that,
it makes me sick, it's so disgusting!
You were excessive,
but still I gave birth to you.
Hey! Hey!
Do you understand?!
Mom... thank you.
I'm confiscating this...
If you enter my room...
this time I'll definetely kill you, OK?
Mom... I'm sorry.
But...
That key...
is a treasured, treasured present so...
Mom'll be furious!
Found it!
Sorry.
Mom will kill me.
"Mourning"
When I brought the kairanban over last night,
she wasn't even cold yet.
They say she had a stroke.
It was too quick, wasn't it.
This...
What should we do with this dog?
It's too much.
Suzuki-san...
People change...
Right, Suzuki-san?
People change.
Change.
Kazari?
Listen...
You broke mom's computer earlier, didn't you?
Mom... already knows.
Oh really. Well then,
let's make it your fault.
You're used to getting her angry, aren't you?
What?
Look, mom already knows.
She said you did it.
She yelled that her CD's were arranged
in the wrong order too.
No way!
I'd just drop dead.
Look...
Then why don't we do this...
Just for tonight...
I become you...
and you become me?
I'll change into you and apologise to her.
What do you think?
Hey Yooko, this outfit looks
really weird on me.
You are... Yooko.
I am... Kazari.
Just for tonight, OK!
So which one of us should go home first?
Rock, scissors, paper~
I won, OK?
Kazari, you go inside first.
Suzuki-san.
Mom, I'm sorry.
I couldn't respond to your love.
I'm going to kill myself.
Goodbye mom.
I really loved you.
Yooko.
Well written, Kazari.
Yooko suddenly ran to the balcony...
I didn't have time to stop her.
You tried to stab Yooko, didn't you?
Kazari, you can't be serious?
Don't say such sad things.
Yooko really loved you, mom.
"Mom and I resemble each other",
she always used to say.
Yooko.
Mom, I was a truly pitiful person,
wasn't I?
If it's scraps of carrots,
I'll eat them!
Whatever I did,
I'm going to live!
I've got Asou.
And I'm as strong as iron inside.
Ouch.
Satoshi.
Satoshi!
Ouch.
What is this place?
Huh?
I think someone beat you up, sis.
And after that, someone beat me up too.
Hey! Anyone there?!
Open up!
Cut it out!
You crying?
But, someone's trying to hurt us, right?
Eat!
I don't need it.
But it might be poisoned...
I want to go to the bathroom!
Go in that. It's there instead of
a toilet, I'm sure.
It's disgusting, sis!
Hang on.
Go over there.
If it leads to the outside,
go notify the police.
Don't let the bad guys discover you.
It itches.
What the hell!
Let me see the cool kid in you!
- From the day you were born...
- I get it, I get it!
Why'd you come back, you idiot?!
- I couldn't get outside!
- You stink!
You stink, don't come any closer!
There are other rooms here.
Save me. Save me. Save me!
There were three more rooms over there.
All the same as this one, no windows,
and the doors are closed there too.
Women are waiting alone in them.
Who locked us up in here?
Don't know.
It seems they all were kidnapped.
So you couldn't get into the
room beyond that one?
Well then, this time try going this way.
You go, sis!
I can't go in there,
that's why I'm asking you!
You're not asking me to,
you're ordering me to!
I'm not evil!
A college student?
Yeah.
She said she was caught yesterday.
They kidnap a woman every day?
That's insane.
There was no one in the next room.
A vacant room?
Was there anyone in the room after that one?
What is it?
There was someone
who seemed kinda bad.
In what way?
Kinda... like she'd gone nuts.
That kind of person.
You saw him too, didn't you?!
Right?!
You saw him, didn't you?!
You too...
your sister too...
you're gonna be killed!!
We're all going to die.
He's gonna kill me tomorrow!
Chop me up into little pieces.
Throw me in there!!
She said that at 6 o'clock every night...
a body comes flowing through there.
What's that?
A body can't flow through there can it?
Nobody else said anything about it.
I'm sure it's not true!
Go ahead and eat.
I told you I don't need it, didn't I?
You wanna die?!
It's not poisoned.
They're delivered to the other rooms too.
So what about my share?
You said you didn't need it, didn't you.
- Sis, I want some too.
- You ate it all yourself yesterday, didn't you.
You came back.
You must be having a hard time too.
Say... my older sister asked me to collect
everyone's personal belongings.
By themselves they might be useless,
but if we put them together they might be of use.
And it wouldn't just be for your own gain?
If we can save ourselves,
we'll save everyone, won't we!
I wonder...
Can something like this be of use?
Too early for you yet, huh?
What is this?
How long have have you been here?
Three days today.
I've been here for six days.
Do you have a watch or something?
Aren't you hungry?
My sister ate all the bread herself.
Did you really go ask everyone?
This is it?!
I told you that's all!
It's true. Yesterday I met someone
in the vacant room.
She said they got her
while she was out jogging last night.
Then... it's one day for her today.
It's been three days for you and me.
For the college student, it's been two days.
The girl in this room said
she's been here for six days already.
The girl in that room...
...has gone.
Gone?
Mhm. Wonder if she's gone outside...
This is the girl in the room furthest from ours!
Why's this happening?!
Why?!
Every day,
he comes to attack the next one in line.
The one who was locked up six days ago.
At 6 o'clock, he chops them up.
I'm sure he never takes a day off.
Like toothbrushing,
it has to be done everyday.
He won't kill you will he?
You'll probably escape, and live a long life.
I'm jealous.
If it was your turn today,
would you want to know about it?
What if it were you, sis?
Would you want to know?
Great, you came!
Your sister can use this if she likes.
Are you sure?
I won't be needing it anymore.
But...
Why are we being killed?
I don't know!
Warm, aren't you...
Someone's coming.
He'll find me!
He's coming to kill me!
I don't want to die alone!
No, no, no...
Satoshi!
Shit!!
I thought he'd killed you too.
What kind of person was it?
I couldn't see his face.
But it was a huge guy.
If we attack him together,
don't you think we could win?
He has a chainsaw.
The door, it seems it has a pole lock.
It sounded that way when he opened it!
So that means doesn't lock with a key?
Don't come any closer!
I won't let you hurt my little brother!
Satochi!
After he comes here,
he'll try to kill us right away.
But, he won't know you'll leave the room.
You'll go and let everyone out.
If you enter that way,
I'm sure everyone will understand.
But what about you, sis?
This way!
Let's go!
Hurry up!
I want to go home real soon.
When we get home, please take a bath.
You seriously stink.
What did you think when I was born?
What's this? Honestly, I didn't feel
there was any connection between us.
Sis...
Let's go call the police.
"3 people were seriously injured..."
"...traffic accident..."
When did you get back?
Want me to give you a hand with that?
I'm OK.
I see.
Keep at it.
You're just drinking juice again?
No homework?
Yeah. But dad told me to
keep working on my puzzle.
Your dad isn't here, is he?
Huh?
So for my sake,
please do your homework.
Alright.
If you do your homework over there,
you'll ruin your eyes.
Now, let's go get something sweet to eat.
Hey... what about mom?
From that day on,
dad wasn't able to see mom.
And mom wasn't able to see dad.
Ah!
It's dad.
I know it's painful but...
your dad is gone.
From now on, it's just the two of us.
Let's do our best, OK?
Hey! Which boxed dinner would you like?
Do you remember that day your dad
and I went out in the car?
Your dad was driving,
when an accident happened.
In the end...
only I was saved.
Your mom and I went over to your uncle's house.
And after that, we were in a car accident.
I was safe...
but your mother...
Hey... where have the scissors gone?
Want me to ask dad?
Hey dad, where are the scissors?
In a kitchen drawer, aren't they?
He said they're in a kitchen drawer.
I can see dad!
Mom is right here!
So it's not just you and me, dad.
If there's anything you want her to know,
I'll tell her for you, OK?
You can, can't you?
It really seems that way.
I don't know what she's talking about.
Ask her when that happened.
He wants to know when that happened.
All the time.
He doesn't say it, but he's always thinking it.
All the time, she says.
Mom looks sad.
I'm more sad than she is.
Face reality a bit more, will you.
Boring, isn't it?
Mom went into the bedroom.
Is that OK?
Leave me alone.
Well... go tell your mom
"I'm really glad you're not around anymore".
What did your dad say?
He said he's glad you're not around anymore.
Well then...
Tell him this:
I really...
Something burst...
...inside me.
I'm sorry about before.
Want some black tea?
Juice.
Wait here, OK?
No matter how much she might have yelled earlier,
she was no match for me.
Will you go ask your mom
about tomorrow?
What? Is something wrong?
Dad's world and mom's world were starting
to become separate from eachother.
What's wrong?
I've become unable to see you together.
You and mom...
Why can't I see the both of you?
What do you mean?
I'm not able to see both you and mom.
Come over here.
That's not how it is.
I'm sorry.
Listen... mom...
Do you remember what you always used to say?
What's that?
"From now on, it's just the two of us,
so let's do our best".
I remember.
I...
I want to live in your world, mom.
After that, I became unable to see dad.
You say your father passed away in a car accident?
Well then, who's that standing
right behind you?
There is nobody there.
It seems he's become unable to see his father.
He can hear my wife's voice, but it
seems he can't hear mine.
If he takes his hand, it seems he simply can't feel it,
even if his mind's used to it.
When I try to hug him, he just becomes like a doll.
So basically...
The two of you were quarreling.
And you both created a world in
which your partner had died.
Living with you lead your child
into believing in that world.
And he became like this.
That's about right, isn't it?
Mom and dad weren't in an accident.
It's sad that I became unable to see dad but...
I definetely think it was for the best.
Because I really wanted mom and dad
to be together again.
"Poem of collected sunlight"
Good morning.
- Who are you?
- I'm the human who created you.
- Stand up.
- Yes.
- Follow me, please.
Happy birthday.
Is that the sun?
Exposure to sunlight, even a small
amount has made my temperature rise.
Let's go.
The house in that forest down there...
That's where you'll keep me company.
Come inside.
First, I'd like you to make coffee.
I know what coffee is,
but I don't know how it's made.
That's right, isn't it.
Now, let's drink.
I've memorized how it's made,
so from now on I'll make it.
How was it?
I hate this flavor.
That's good. I made you that way.
Now drink it.
The sweet taste made it easier to drink.
It allows the coffee to be
normally absorbed inside my body.
The people in that picture,
where are they now?
Thery're not anywhere anymore.
What are you going to do with that?
I want you to learn gardening.
- Thanks for the food.
- It's delicious, but maybe a bit too salty.
- I understand.
Do you know what this is?
A rabbit did it.
Then that's what I saw this morning.
But knowing it's been at our food
gives me an unpleasant feeling.
In 47300032000~ seconds...
I will become inactive.
In time, every living thing will,
without fail, become inactive.
That's a beautiful sound. The wind makes it.
It's coincidental music, isn't it.
I like this kind of sound.
3.
2.
1.
It's been exactly one month since I was born.
After one more week,
I will die.
After I die, I want to
be buried on the hill.
I made you for that reason.
I understand.
Not again...
Where did you break?
You're still warm.
Thats right!
That man will fix you!
What's wrong?
What on earth happened?
Please fix it.
Please fix this child.
It's already dead.
You're in bad shape.
Let's hurry back to safety.
I... loved this child.
That... is death.
I'm sorry.
I resent you.
Why did you create me?
I...
...I don't want to have to bury
you after you're dead. It's painful!
There are birds' nests in the trees here,
so it won't be lonely.
I will die tomorrow afternoon.
How much time do you have left?
1729 seconds.
I also know exactly how much
time I have left to breathe.
And... you too...
When I fell off the cliff...
I saw the forest's true shape.
There haven't been any humans
here for a long, long time, have there?
For how long have you been alone?
I was made 150 years ago.
The girl who made me, was created by
someone before those 150 years.
By someone who also
had been created by someone.
Then human beings were no more again
for a long time.
But to make you was my dying wish.
Because I thought you'd be very
happy to be born into this world.
Thank you!