To those who loved this world once before
and spent time with its friends,
Gather again and devote your time...
Translated by Jasconius
Shion-san!
Look at this!
Found it.
...kinda gross, isn't it?
Just hurry it up, yo.
I'm counting on you, Reno.
Alright, yo.
Hey, hey, hey!
Senpai, hurry up!
Senpai!
Who is that?!
Ugh...
Elena!
G-go!
Lifestream...
The flow which governs the life of worlds.
It is the source of all worlds
and all of the life on those planets.
The Shinra Company found a way...
to take the lifestream and use it as a resource.
Because of that, we were able...
to live rich and plentiful lives.
But that wore away at the life of the planet...
There were a lot of people who thought that.
Shinra tried to use force...
against those who stood in opposition.
Shinra had a special force
who were called Soldier.
They were the ones who long ago...
took the one falling from the sky
to destroy the world,
Jenova's cell, and buried her.
There was one among them named Sephiroth...
who was an excellent Soldier.
But when he found out
that he had been born in a horrifying experiment...
he came to hate Shinra.
And then finally came to hate everything.
Shinra and those who stood against them.
Sephiroth, whose hate was so great
that he tried to destroy the world...
Those people who tried to stop Sephiroth...
There were many battles.
There was sadness in the sheer number of battles.
One who I loved
also became part of the Lifestream.
And then one day...
A fated day...
The world's power itself stopped all of the battles.
The world used the Lifestream as a weapon.
The Lifestream, gushing out over the world...
took battles, ambition, and sadness...
It took everything and swallowed it up.
In exchange for that sadness, everything stopped.
These things all happened two years ago.
Let's go.
OK.
But... the world...
seems to have been much, much angrier than anyone believed.
The Star-Scar Syndrome. (Geostigma)
Hey, Marlene?
What's going on?
Please, I ask of you.
Please don't take Denzel away.
He's not here anymore~
Cloud...
Where are you...?
Hello, Strife Delivery Service!
We'll deliver anyth...
...who is this?
I remember you, yo.
I got a phone call from Reno and them in Healin.
They said it's a commission.
Cloud... have you been doing OK?
No more messages.
Hey, Kadaj...
Is that big brother's city?
Yeah.
You think they'll give us a big welcome?
No way.
Don't cry, Yazoo.
Mother must be with him too, right?
I dunno about that.
Don't cry, Loz.
Look, it's big brother.
Where's Mother?
Big brother's hiding her, isn't he?
Did he trick us?!
Mother's really -there-, isn't she?
Don't yell about it.
I don't wanna talk to you!
Give me the boss.
Hey, it's me, Barret! I did it!
A new oil field!
O-IL-FIELD!
A huge one, too!
And we're sticking to plan, so soon
I'll be able to come visit Marlene!
Tell her for me!
See ya!
There was another phone call from Reno.
Anyway, just hurry, he says.
He seemed a little weird, though...
Be careful.
Uoryaaaa~~
Just as I expected, yo!
Rude, you're so cool!
Just as expected, would-be ex-Soldier.
Your skills are as impressive as ever.
Is that you, Rufus?
You've got no luck either...
That day, I...
What do you want with me?
Just before the buildings crumbled...
Who were those people who attacked me?
Say something.
I'm leaving.
...lend us your power.
Not interested.
We at Shinra have a big debt to repay to the world.
The responsibility of putting the world
in its current, pathetic state...
There's no helping people saying
that it falls to us.
Consequently,
we must somehow repay this debt of ours.
Let me in!
As our first step...
We began an investigation
into the influences that Sephiroth left.
The Northern Crater, yo.
What do you think was there?
Nothing.
There was nothing.
You don't have to worry about it.
But something unexpected happened.
Someone tried to get in our way.
Those people who attacked you...
They're Kadaj's gang.
Kadaj...
It seems that they meant to interfere with our plans.
Really... I can't figure why.
Why did they attack me?
You're with us, right?
Kadaj's gang is young and brutal.
They're extremely dangerous.
So, we decided to try and hire a skilled bodyguard.
I'm a delivery man.
You're the only one.
Please, ex-Soldier Cloud.
Would-be...
What is this "Mother" they were talking about?
Kadaj said something, huh?
Well, don't worry about that.
There are children all over the world
who yearn for their mothers.
You're living with the orphans, I hear.
You don't want to bring smiles back to their faces?
Our ultimate goal
is the rebuilding of this world, Cloud.
I...
Please, Cloud!
We're rebuilding the Shinra Company, yo!
Not interested.
Reno!
Cloud's living here?
Looks like it.
What?
Just like Denzel's!
Is Cloud sick too?
He could just tell us...
Did he leave because he's sick?
He thinks he's going to fight them by himself.
Fight?
No...
He doesn't have the will to fight...
Tifa?
Let's go home, Marlene.
No!
I want to see Cloud!
...I guess you're right.
It'd be nice to see him, huh?
Yeah!
Hey, what should we do when he gets here?
Go home together!
Before that, we'll lecture him!
Agreed!
I hate lies, you know.
I'm sorry!
This time I'll be honest with you.
While we were running away from you...
It seems that it fell from the helicopter.
What a ridiculous story...
Truly?
I swear it.
Then swear it on these.
What are you after?
We need Mother's power.
We have to have it, for Reunion.
Reunion...
We're going to collect everyone
with Mother's cells into one place.
And then we're going to get revenge on the world.
Preparations are coming along pretty well...
but you see,
someone had to go and hide Mother...
Preparations?
Geostigma.
You know all about it, right Boss?
In the Lifestream...
All because Mother's cells are working hard...
And yet we...
We don't even know where Mother is.
It's sad but there's no helping it.
We're spirits, after all.
Until we find Mother and divide up here cells...
We can't be normal!
Spirits and Geostigma aren't enough!
Not for the real Reunion, you see.
...what are you talking about?
Boss... you've figured it out, haven't you?
I'll live for you as well...
That's what I decided...
You wanna be a Soldier?
Work hard!
Hey, how do you feel?
Hey,
what are you gonna do when we get to Midgard?
We're friends, right?
Cloud, run!
Wanna play?
I see, you don't want to.
Where's mother?
It stinks!
Hey, where's Mother?
There's no one here!
Then let's play.
This should be fun!
Tifa!
It's not here.
I'm not crying.
Got it.
I'll bring it.
Time to finish this.
Cloud...
Run!
You've got Geostigma too, don't you?
He says he's gonna cure us.
Tifa?
Tifa!
You're late...
Who did this?
Someone I didn't know.
Marlene?!
Dammit!
You were heavy, yo.
...you were living with some kids, right?
It's empty.
That OK?
I...
You're so annoying, yo.
Brother was hiding it, huh?
The power born from the Lifestream.
These Materia will give us a new power...
Reno and them are searching...
It's Geostigma... isn't it?
It's alright if I die.
...is that what you're thinking?
As I thought.
There's no cure.
But Denzel was trying his best, wasn't he?
Why don't you fight it with us instead of running away?
We could all help each other and try our best!
Can't do it since we're not a real family, huh?
I can't...
I can't save anyone, I don't think.
Neither family nor friends...
No one.
Drifting, drifting...
Drifting, drifting!
How long are you gonna drag along like that, yo?
You couldn't find them?!
There was a witness who saw them being taken away, yo.
Where did they go?
The Forgotten Capital...
Ajit.
I've received a special power from Mother.
A power to fight against this planet...
which hurts the people living on it.
Actually, you all have this power.
That's right.
We're all siblings.
Chosen siblings...
who inherited Mother's cells
that were absorbed in the Lifestream.
But...
The planet is trying to interfere.
It's trying to stunt our growth!
That's why our bodies hurt
and our hearts seem to give up.
I'll cure you.
And we'll all go to Mother together.
We'll bring our family's power together
and get back at the planet!
Follow my lead.
Denzel!
Denzel!!
So you showed up.
Even though you're falling apart...
I'm sure this will be a good thing.
Question!
Why exactly did you come here?
I... wish to be forgiven.
Yes, I want to be forgiven.
By who~?
So he did show up.
I came for the children.
This guy is our Brother.
But you know, it's a shame...
He's a traitor.
Cloud!
You really can't save anyone, can you?
Vincent...
What's happening?
I come here a lot.
So I saw Kadaj and them here.
The Geostigma...
It seems that the cause is an overloading of the system
to remove parasites in the body.
There's a flow through the body like the Lifestream...
It fights against the invasion of harmful substances.
Harmful substances...
The Sephiroth element... Jenova's cells...
Call it what you want.
You know a lot about it.
Shion and Elena...
They were carried here on the edge of death.
It seemed
that they had been put through some hideous torture.
I managed to save them, but...
Well, I'm not sure how well...
Torture?
You reap what you sow.
It seems that they came into possession of Jenova's head.
And the Mother that Kadaj's gang is searching for is...
That abominable thing which heaven sent.
Jenova.
If they wanted to,
they could even remake Sephiroth.
Kadaj...
What is he?
Hmph, I don't want to think about it.
Marlene!
Cloud!
Denzel and Tifa, they...!
Tifa is all right.
I want to talk to Tifa!
Do you have it?
I can't believe it!
Vincent, can you take Marlene back to the store?
I'm going to go talk to Shinra about this.
I can't approve.
But...
I don't care about you anymore, Cloud!
Why won't you listen to what we're saying?!
Marlene...
Just wait a little longer...
The fight is going to begin now.
But we can't just fight!
You understand, right?
I don't understand!
Cloud, is this really about the fight?
Where did they go?
The Forgotten Capital.
Ajit.
Take care of it.
I'm going to go talk to Rufus.
Don't run!
I know you are!
Even if you find the children,
you might not be able to do anything.
They might be somewhere that we can't get them back.
You're scared of that, aren't you?
But you have to react to now, to more of this!
A burden?
Well there's no helping that, it's a heavy burden!
Unless you want to live all alone,
you have to deal with that!
You don't want to be alone, do you?
Even though you never answer,
you always have your phone with you.
You go to Ajit, yo.
Have we lost to our memories?
But... we just let her die.
Really, always drifting...
Hey...
Why don't you forgive yourself?
Can sin be forgiven?
...I've never tried it.
Tried it?
Tried it...
Marlene, we're going home!
I'll try it.
I'll let you know how it turns out.
It's me, Reeve.
How's work going?
I just saw you pass by,
but can you really make a living doing that?
It is like you, though, Cloud-san.
If it's OK, I'd like to help,
so I'll contact you again.
I got a phone call from Reno in Healin,
he says it's a commission.
Long time no see! It's Yuffie!
Hey, all the kids from Wutai disappeared...
Do you know anything?
Give me some info! Please!
He seemed a little weird, though...
Be careful.
I've never thought badly of you.
You came for me, didn't you?
That's plenty right there.
Hey! Are you listening?
Why are you doing this?!
Denzel!
What are you doing?
Mother's in there, right?
Why do you say that?
This... what is it? Memorial statue?
Shinra's the one that made it.
Wow, you used your head, didn't you?
But you're off-base.
We don't know either, yo.
What's this?
You don't have any faith in us, huh?
Uorya~~
Hey, Kadaj.
Tell me one thing.
Just one thing.
You said that you would become normal
once you got Jenova's cells, but...
What did you mean by that?
He... will return.
...Sephiroth.
A nightmare, huh?
So I hear.
So you hear?
I don't know Sephiroth.
Yeah, I just feel him!
It irritates me!
Me or Sephiroth, which does Mother...
Poor spirit...
Whichever it ends up as,
you all will meet the same end!
Mother made a long journey to come to this planet.
To erase a bunch of fools from space, you see.
But... you know, don't you?
Nothing has changed here
since the time when Mother came.
That's why I'm going to make Mother happy.
I'll do anything if Mother commands it.
Hmph, the nightmare comes again, huh?
As long as you guys are here,
the same thing will keep happening.
The Lifestream, which governs the flow of worlds...
It comes and goes in the space between life and death...
If that repetition is proof of life...
It is inevitable that history will repeat itself.
I don't know about Jenova or Sephiroth, but...
The same things should keep happening...
We will obey the fate of life.
And while doing so, we will stop you.
Chief, is that your excuse for seizing Mother?
Are you sure you're not regretting it?
Regretting?
I'm... beside myself in anticipation.
Good.
Then, shall we go ahead and end this?
Denzel, you have to run!
Uoryaa~~
This is...
It's no use...
Is it coming?!
I don't want to look.
Isn't this fun?
Not at all, yo!
You guys are really stubborn, yo.
I told you, if you just give Mother back,
that will be the end of this.
You guys...
What are you planning to do with Jenova's head?
This Reunion or whatever, are you serious?
We just want so see Mother.
She's our Mother,
but she's going to decide everything now.
So, where's Mother?
You know, you keep calling it Mother,
but it's just Jenova's head.
Hey!
Don't call Mother that!
I can't forgive that.
...sorry.
That's right...
Wait, why are we apologizing?!
Tifa?
You bastard!
Protect your mom here!
Barret!
Marlene's safe, right?!
Huh?
I can't match this!
Ugh.
Who's using my materia?!
The bad guys, of course.
Damn them!
Who's that?
The new version of Sierra!
I'll let you ride it later!
Where's the phone shop...?
Who's that person?
They're all friends.
Marlene is safe.
I dropped her off at the store.