See the crows?
They never tasted prince before.
Is this what you left me for?!
Fight!
Fight me!
You coward!
We have a pact! Fight!
Fight him, son. Fight him.
- Fight me!
- The Trojans have violated the agreement!
Prepare for battle!
This is not honor!
This is not worthy of royalty!
If he doesn't fight, Troy is doomed.
The fight is over.
The fight is not over.
Stand back, Prince Hector.
I'll kill him at your feet. I don't care.
He is my brother.
Paris!
Go!
Get inside, Paris!
Archers!
- Our men are too close to the walls.
- Pull back, you fool!
For Troy!
- Now!
- Loose!
Get them in line!
Get the men back into lines!
Front line, push!
Forward.
Forward!
Apollonians! Now!
Prince Hector!
We need to retreat!
My army's never lost a battle yet!
You won't have an army
if you don't fall back!
Back to the ships!
- Back to the ships!
- Retreat!
- Back!
Go back!
Back. Back to the ships!
Fall back!
- Men, fall back!
- Halt!
Halt!
But we have them on the run!
We're in range of their archers.
Have our men gather our fallen.
Send an emissary to the greeks.
Tell them, they can collect their dead.
Would they have done the same for us?
Go! Back!
Fall back into line!
You think I'm a coward.
I am a coward.
I knew he would kill me.
You were watching.
My father.
My brother.
All of Troy. Shame didn't matter.
I gave up my pride...
...my honor...
...just to live.
For love.
You challenged a great warrior.
That took courage.
I betrayed you.
Menelaus was a brave man.
He lived for fighting.
And every day I was with him, I wanted
to walk into the sea and drown.
I don't want a hero, my love.
I want a man I can grow old with.
They're laughing at me in Troy.
Drunk with victory!
They think I'll sail home at first light.
Maybe we should.
Flee? Like a whipped dog?
The men believe we came here
for Menelaus' wife.
Won't be needing her anymore.
My brother's blood still wets the sand,
and you insult him!
It's no insult to say a dead man is dead.
If we leave now, we lose all credibility.
The Trojans can beat us so easily.
How long before the Hittites invade?
If we stay, we stay here
for the right reasons.
To protect Greece, not your pride.
Your private battle with Achilles
is destroying us.
Achilles is one man.
Hector is one man.
Look what he did to us today.
Hector fights for his country!
Achilles fights only for himself!
I don't care about the man's allegiance.
I care about his ability to win battles.
He's right.
The men's morale is weak.
Even if I could make peace with Achilles,
the man won't listen to me!
He's as likely to spear me
as to speak to me!
I'll talk to him.
He'll want the girl back.
He can have that damn girl.
I haven't touched her.
Where is she?
I gave her to the men.
They need some amusement after today.
Come on, give the bitch to me!
Who's first?
Trojan whore!
What's this? A virgin's robe?
- You won't be needing that much longer!
- Hold her.
Better to be a Spartan slave
than a Trojan...
Achilles!
Are you hurt?
I watched you fight them.
You have courage.
To fight back when people attack me?
Dog has that kind of courage.
Eat.
I've known men like you my whole life.
No, you haven't.
You think you're so different
from 1000 others?
Soldiers understand nothing but war.
Peace confuses them.
- And you hate these soldiers.
- I pity them.
Trojan soldiers died trying to protect you.
Perhaps they deserve
more than your pity.
Why did you choose this life?
- What life?
- To be a great warrior.
I chose nothing.
I was born, and this is what I am.
And you?
Why did you choose to love a god?
I think you'll find the romance one-sided.
Do you enjoy provoking me?
You've dedicated your life to the gods.
Zeus, god of thunder. Athena, goddess of wisdom.
You serve them.
- Yes, of course.
- And Ares, god of war?
Who blankets his bed with the skin
of men he's killed?
All the gods are to be feared
and respected.
I'll tell you a secret...
...something they don't teach you
in your temple.
The gods envy us.
They envy us because we're mortal.
Because any moment might be our last.
Everything's more beautiful
because we're doomed.
You will never be lovelier
than you are now.
We will never be here again.
I thought you were a dumb brute.
I could have forgiven a dumb brute.
Do it.
Nothing is easier.
Aren't you afraid?
Everyone dies. Today or 50 years
from now. What does it matter?
Do it.
You'll kill more men if I don't kill you.
Many.
My lord, there's...
Tell the men to start loading the ship.
We're going home.
Gather the stores.
Agamemnon is a proud man.
But he knows
when he's made a mistake.
The man sends you
to make his apologies?
What are you doing enthralled
to that pig of a king?
The world seems simple to you,
my friend...
...but when you're a king,
very few choices are simple.
Ithaca cannot afford an enemy
like Agamemnon.
Are we supposed to fear him?
You don't fear anyone.
That's your problem. Fear is useful.
We need you back.
Greece needs you.
Greece got along fine before I was born.
Greece will be Greece
long after I'm dead.
I'm not talking about the land.
The men need you.
Stay, Achilles.
You were born for this war.
Things are less simple today.
Women have a way
of complicating things.
Of all the kings of Greece,
I respect you the most.
But in this war, you're a servant.
Sometimes you have to serve
in order to lead.
I hope you understand that one day.
We're going home?
We sail in the morning.
Greeks are being slaughtered.
We can't just sail away.
If it's fighting you still long for, there will
always be another war. That I promise you.
These are our countrymen.
You betray all of Greece
just to see Agamemnon fall.
Someone has to lose.
The gods favor our cause.
Now is the time to destroy
the Greek army.
Their morale is battered.
Hit them now. Hit them hard.
And they will run.
The Myrmidons didn't fight yesterday.
There must be dissension
among the Greeks.
But if we attack their ships,
we will unify them.
If they decide to attack us, let them.
Our walls can't be breached.
We'll beat them back again.
Yesterday, the Greeks
underestimated us.
We should not return the favor.
You're confident about the meaning
of these omens?
The desecration of his temple
angers Apollo.
The gods have cursed the Greeks.
Prepare the army.
We attack at daybreak.
Am I still your captive?
You're my guest.
In Troy, guests can leave
whenever they want.
You should leave then.
Would you leave this all behind?
Would you leave Troy?
Hold those barricades!
Archers to the rear.
Achilles.
Now!
Forward!
Enough for one day.
Yes.
Back to the ships!
It was his cousin.
To Troy!
- Back to the city!
We were going to sail home today.
I don't think anyone's sailing home now.
Achilles.
You violated my command.
No, my lord. There was a mistake.
I ordered the Myrmidons to stand down.
You led them into combat.
I didn't lead them, my lord.
We thought you did.
Where's Patroclus?
Patroclus!
We thought he was you, my lord.
He wore your armor, your shield,
your greaves, your helmet.
He even moved like you.
Where is he?
- Where?
- He's dead, my lord.
Hector cut his throat.
Don't!
Where are you taking me?
Do you remember how to get here?
Yes.
The next time you come here,
follow the tunnel.
There are no turns, so you can't get lost.
Just keep walking.
When you get to the end,
you'll be by the river.
Follow the river until you get
to Mount Ida.
Why are you telling me this?
- If I die...
- No.
...I don't know how long
the city will stand.
If the Greeks get inside the walls,
it's over.
They'll kill all the men,
throw the babies from the city walls.
- Please.
- And the women, they'll take as slaves.
- That, for you, will be worse than dying.
- Why are you saying such things?
Because I want you to be ready.
I want you to get our boy,
and I want you to bring him here.
You save as many people as you can,
but you get here. And you run.
I killed a boy today.
And he was young.
He was much too young.
That boy has just saved this war for us.
- Eudorus.
- My lord.
I need my armor.
No.
Don't go!
Rope!
Hector's my cousin. He's a good man.
Don't fight him. Please don't fight him.
Please.
No.
Hector!
Father...
...forgive me for any offenses.
I've served you as best as I could.
Hector!
May the gods be with you.
Hector.
No father ever had a better son.
Hector!
Apollo guard you, my prince.
You're the best man I know.
You're a prince of Troy.
I know you'll make me proud.
Hector!
Remember what I told you.
You don't have to go. You don't.
You remember what I told you.
Hector!
I've seen this moment in my dreams.
I'll make a pact with you.
With the gods as our witnesses...
...let us pledge that the winner will allow
the loser all the proper funeral rituals.
There are no pacts
between lions and men.
Now you know who you're fighting.
I thought it was you
I was fighting yesterday.
And I wish it had been you. But I gave
the dead boy the honor he deserved.
You gave him the honor of your sword.
You won't have eyes tonight.
You won't have ears or a tongue.
You'll wander the underworld, blind, deaf,
and dumb, and all the dead will know.
This is Hector, the fool who thought
he killed Achilles.
Get up, prince of Troy.
Get up. I won't let
a stone take my glory.
You lost your cousin.
Now you've taken mine.
When does it end?
It never ends.
Who are you?
I have endured what no one
on earth has endured before.
I kissed the hands of the man
who killed my son.
Priam?
How did you get in here?
I know my own country better
than the Greeks, I think.
You're a brave man.
I could have your head on a spit
in the blink of an eye.
Do you really think death
frightens me now?
I watched my eldest son die...
...watched you drag his body
behind your chariot.
Give him back to me.
He deserves the honor of a proper burial.
You know that.
Give him to me.
He killed my cousin.
He thought it was you.
How many cousins have you killed?
How many sons and fathers
and brothers and husbands?
How many, brave Achilles?
I knew your father.
He died before his time.
But he was lucky not to live long enough
to see his son fall.
You have taken everything from me.
My eldest son...
...heir to my throne...
...defender of my kingdom.
I cannot change what happened.
It is the will of the gods.
But give me this small mercy.
I loved my boy from the moment
he opened his eyes...
...till the moment you closed them.
Let me wash his body.
Let me say the prayers.
Let me place two coins on his eyes
for the boatman.
If I let you walk out of here...
...if I let you take him...
...it doesn't change anything.
You're still my enemy in the morning.
You're still my enemy tonight.
But even enemies can show respect.
I admire your courage.
Meet me outside in a moment.
We'll meet again soon, my brother.
Your son was the best I've fought.
In my country, the funeral games
last for 12 days.
It is the same in my country.
Then the prince will have that honor.
No Greek will attack Troy for 12 days.
Briseis?
I thought you were dead.
You are free.
If I hurt you...
...it's not what I wanted.
Go.
No one will stop you.
You have my word.
Come, my girl.
You're a far better king than the one
leading this army.
Achilles makes a secret pact, and I
have to honor it? What treason is this?
Consorting with the enemy king.
Giving him 12 days of peace.
Peace!
Their prince is dead.
Their army is leaderless.
This is the time to attack!
Even with Hector gone, we have
no way to breach their walls.
I will smash their walls to the ground...
...if it costs me 40,000 Greeks.
Hear me, Zeus!
I will smash their walls to the ground.
That's good.
For my son back home.
Well, Odysseus.
You found a way to make the sheep
invite the wolves to dinner.
Forgive me, Eudorus.
I should never have struck you.
You've been a loyal friend all your life.
I hope I never disappoint you again.
It's I who have been the disappointment.
Rouse the men.
You're taking them home.
Aren't you coming with us?
I have my own battle to fight.
Let me march beside you.
No. I don't want our men
to be a part of this.
It's a beautiful night.
Go, Eudorus.
This is the last order I give you.
Fighting for you has been
my life's honor, my lord.
Open the gates!
Here.
Plague.
Don't go too close, my king.
This is the will of the gods.
They desecrated the temple of Apollo...
...and Apollo desecrated their flesh.
They thought they could come here
and sack our city in a day.
Now look at them,
fleeing across the Aegean.
What is this?
An offering to Poseidon. The Greeks
are praying for a safe return home.
This is a gift. We should take it
to the temple of Poseidon.
- I think we should burn it.
- Burn it?
My prince, it's a gift to the gods.
Father, burn it.
Look at them.
You'd think their prince had never died.
You are the prince now.
Make your brother proud.
Briseis. Where is she?
- Where?
- I don't know.
Please. I have a son.
Then get him out of Troy.
Briseis!
Paris! Andromache!
Helen. We must go.
- Where?
- I'll show you. Now. Hurry.
Paris. Paris.
It's a long way. Quick.
We must go now.
Briseis!
Paris!
Let it burn!
Let Troy burn!
Burn it! Burn it all!
Burn Troy!
It's a long way. Quick.
- Come.
- I stay.
- No.
- My father will never abandon the city.
I can't leave him.
The city is dead.
They're burning it to the ground.
- What's your name?
- Aeneas.
- Do you know how to use a sword?
- Yes.
The sword of Troy.
As long as it remains in the hands of a Trojan,
our people have a future.
Protect them, Aeneas.
Find them a new home.
- I will.
- Hurry.
Paris, Briseis wasn't in her room.
I'll find her.
Go.
- I'll stay with you.
- Go.
Please don't leave me.
How could you love me if I ran now?
We will be together again, in this world
or the next. We will be together.
Go.
To the gate!
Soldiers of Troy...
...you men are warriors!
To lead you has been my honor!
My prince!
The boatman waits for us.
I say we make him wait a little longer!
Paris!
Have you no honor?
Too late for prayer, priestess.
I almost lost this war
because of your little romance.
You'll be my slave in Mycenae.
A Trojan priestess scrubbing my floors.
And at night...
Get up!
Hold her.
Come with me.
No!
Paris!
Stop! Please!
Paris! Don't!
It's all right.
You gave me peace...
...in a lifetime of war.
Briseis, come.
Go.
You must.
No.
Troy is falling.
Go.
We must go. I know a way out.
It's all right.
Go.
Briseis, come.
Find peace...
...my brother.
If they ever tell my story, let them say...
...I walked with giants.
Men rise and fall like the winter wheat...
...but these names will never die.
Let them say I lived
in the time of Hector...
...tamer of horses.
Let them say...
...I lived in the time of Achilles.