Nanny, what's with the young miss?
Such innovative style?
Just spicing up the routine
We've been here at least 100 times
this month
It gets boring
she needs stimulation
Make way... make way!
Make way!
Oh no! It's her again!
You can't see me...
None of these fortunetellers
are any good and it stinks
Foo, right?!
Yes, ma'am
Let's just go home
Hey, Chan
Still trying to set me up?
You're just too picky
Sit...
These beauties are all
from out of town
Have a nice chat
Miss, what's your profession?
I'm an escort,
But I don't worry, I don't do sex
So what do you do?
Drinking games!
Sir, what do you do?
A question for me?
I'm a poet
How does a poet make a living?
By publishing
How many books have you published?
None... yet
So, you're really a bum?
Remember to invite me to your funeral!
I'll definitely be there!
You're too picky
How will you get a wife?
Let me do the introduction!
No, we kids can take care of ourselves
Bro, even you're better looking
than he is
Not by much, it's just the hair
Who are you?
I'm her brother,
Also known as Beijing's Best Dressed
Super Double Blades...
Brave heart...
Stop!
Can't possibly remember all that
Good! Straightforward!
I dig your style!
Cheers
What's your name?
Flying Cloud
Any alias?
Spiderman!
I like you!
Cheers!
Why Spiderman?
Cause it sounds cool
Good! Fair enough!
I like you, too!
Bottoms-up!
Miss Liu, am I suitable?
You're strong, talented...
funny and macho...
a natural leader...
Overall, a pretty good catch
Keen observations. Well said
But this entourage...
to bring all these bodyguards...
it feels like an invasion
not a courtship
My boys are my best advisers
You need advise in picking a wife?
For reference
You're suspicious, paranoid
and indecisive
Bad-tempered
probably have sleeping disorders
You're brave but indecisive
You've got a lot of bodyguards...
which shows that you're really a coward
I'll marry you right now
Look, who's indecisive now?!
Marry me?
What do you love about me?
Eh.... can't find the words...
I just want to get close to you
Not close enough for you?
How close do you want to get?
Skin to skin, if you know what I mean
Over tea? You outta of mind?
Check please
Ms. Moth Liu
Thank you, six dollars
She's paying. She asked for the check
Bottoms up!
Good luck...
finding a man who'll have you...
BITCH!
You sonofagun!
Fat spider! I'll squash you
I'll never marry you. Fat Spider!
Fat Spider!
Sir, your sister is in trouble...
Help her!
Let's wait and see
Her temper will get her killed
one day
Maybe he's the man to subdue her
Damn!
Mister, lend me your washboard
Stop!
Looks like blood will be shed today
Hey, stop messing around
I can squash you with a finger...
but if you hold me hostage...
maybe we can force my sister
to marry you
Take my blade and gently slash me...
she'll have to say yes to save me
See, I'm really on your side
Ms. Moth Liu!
If you don't marry me
I'll kill your brother
Sis, he risks his life for you
He really loves you!
I'll slaughter him now!
Hey! That's a deep cut!
Sorry, I got too excited
Sis, listen! These may be my last words
True love is hard to find
When love comes knocking, you can't...
Sir, let's stop the bleeding first
I'm OK!
Sis, calm down!
There'll always be someone better but...
it's really time you settle down...
and marry someone like Spiderman here
What are you talking about?
He's an ass. I'll never marry him!
Even if you're not ready to settle down
at least set him down
Dear Ms. Hercules...
don't mind me
The scenery up here is fantastic
In fact, I'm enjoying the cool breeze
I'm not in a hurry, take your time
It's getting a bit stuffy
Excuse me... it... sounds like
I may fall soon!
Are you marrying me or not!
The country is at war...
and you able-body warriors...
are killing each other...
Personal vendettas
when your country is at war
Have you no shame?
The heavens is...
weeping at your folly!
What are you mumbling about?
Put simply, what l'm saying...
We're being invaded and
instead of fighting the enemies...
you're here killing each other instead
Say, if your mom asks you to study...
would you go play football instead!
Where's your priority!
Defeating the true enemy...
that's real courage
I understand now
How dare you drag my mom into this...
want to die?
You're so dumb!
You ignorant pig
He's trying to explain
Mr. Cloud! Stop...
First: It's obvious
you're not her man
Second: This scholar
is sabotaging our plan
I wonder what his motives are...
Third...
I'm bleeding to death! It's over
I'm fainting...
The country needs me. I'm going!
Sir, thanks for your advise!
See you!
Hope not!
When will there be peace again?
What happened to brotherly love?
What's your name?
Last name's Chan
Parents liked the seasons
Spring Chan?
Seasonal Chan!
And you?
Last name's Liu. My mother liked...
moths to flames
Flaming Liu?
Moth Liu!
Pleased to meet you!
Pleasure's all mine
Obviously
Your words...
are more convincing than my fists
I'm impressed
I'm more than a man of words
I'm a philosopher, too
I'm off, see you again soon
Come see for yourself!
The latest autographed
Poet Soo poster
They're authentic signatures
Who else has a beard like that?
Ake your time, calm down...
Let go of my hand
Soo, I love you!
Come see for yourself!
Calm down, take your time...
Look at you, your mascara is running
Miss, do I look terrible?
No, no, you've got style
Soo'll be impressed
But Soo doesn't even know me
I'd be impressed if he does
Your idol must be an incredible man
Wow, even the Emperor's here
Cousin!
Cousin Long, what're you doing here?
Soo's a pal and I'm the event sponsor
Ladies and gentlemen!
The Valentino of poetry!
Sponsored by Long Far Pharmaceuticals
Let the Love Forever Reading...
begin!
Soo Tung Bo!
How're you doing!
Good!
And you!
And you! Great!
Friends in the back!
Sipping wine and
Waiting for the moon
don't know when...
I dream of...
riding on the wind...
lonely is the night...
dancing in the dark...
with shadows around me...
feels like heaven...
sleepless is the night
no hate...
just regrets howling at moon...
Soo, I love you!
If only your love is forever...
that love will conquer all...
the future is unpredictable...
Wow, what a group
Even the Emperor is here!
A round of applause for my friend
The special guest of the evening
Seasonal Chan!
A feast in the palace to honor me
Your majesty, I love you!
Seasonal Chan
Good evening
You were fantastic!
That was a disaster
perhaps, maybe...
Maybe my style is too post-modernist
to understand
Did you understand my performance?
Sure
Your words were from your heart
I feel it
Your style is creative and alternative
One day, they'll learn
to appreciate your talent!
You flatter me!
I found something unique in your work
There's innocence, depth...
and meaning
If you work harder
One day, they'll love it, too!
The perfect match...
go get married!
Sure, a good match!
You howling your crazy songs
And she waving her crazy glowing stick
my head's still spinning from it
The perfect odd couple
Perfectly odd!
I order you to get married!
Your names?
Seasonal Chan!
And you?
Moth Liu CHAN!
I'm so lucky...
Miss is back!
Where were you last night?
We're all worried sick!
Got married last night!
To him?
Brother-in-law?
Cousin only
Brother!
What's your name?
Chan
Chan what?
Seasonal
Got it!
Got what?
Thank you for marrying my sister
May the heavens bless you
with good health
Sister sold-- no refund, no exchange
Thank you lord!
Hey, what's this! Talk to me!
Savior...
My cousin married you already
you'll protect her
Sure!
You've got to take care of her health
Here are some medicines for her!
This will improve her chi!
Guaranteed to work
Make her eat more!
This is for you
1000-year-old ginseng
You'll need it to survive her beatings!
Swallow it and it'll save your life
But...
it's too big to swallow!
Ground it, just suck, don't swallow
Come
This is my house
Stop, let's get off here
Honey, help me down, thanks
My wife!
Seasonal, Seasonal!
Come here!
You're finally a star
The Emperor blessed your marriage
Can I have your autograph?
I love your work, you're great...
Master, welcome home
A woman just landed in our front yard...
Master, who's that?
The mistress!
Madame!
Hurry!
Good day, madam
I'm your butler Wong Choy!
Good!
Long live your majesty!
Impressively trained!
Please rise...
Thank you!
Miss, where should we put Baby?
Ma'am, here's all the household
accounts...
All the accounts
all yours
Very good
Thank you, ma'am!
Stop calling me ma'am
It makes me sound old
Call me something else!
Master!
No, my husband is the master
of the house
You're She-master and
he'll be He-master
Tell me, does he...
have a girlfriend?
He-master says
we're not to speak of his affairs
We cannot divulge his secrets
Loyalty, I like that!
Here's your reward!
Thank you, She-master!
I'll leave you, He-master
What's wrong?
Will you hit me?
Not unless you did something wrong!
If I do, you must have done
something wrong
What are your definitions of wrong?
From now on
you'll love no one but me
You'll spoil me; never lie to me
Fulfill all your promises
Always tell me the truth
Never argue with me, have faith in me
Protect me, stand up for me
Share my laughter
Wipe away my tears
Promise that I'll always be only one
in your eyes
The only one in your dream
The only one in your heart!
Simple enough
Can you do this?
Sure!
Look, a beauty
Snow White from a distance...
Wicked Stepmother up close
Chan, the Club is hosting
a Persian Night soon!
You're teasing me?
Don't you have errands to run?
You're pushing it
This is male bonding time
women should go home
Let's drink, brother Soo!
Go home and make dinner!
Don't worry
We've got a really good cook
A sharp tongue
Tame her now or it'll be too late
Tong, get the 9th concubine
to come here right away!
9th concubine!
Coming! Coming...
What took you so long?
I was taking a bath
Go home now...
Not bad, come and go as you please
Impressive
You can do it, too.
Try
Honey
Please go home
Are you deaf
We'll trick her
Are you a man? Where's your dignity!
You can't even stand up to your woman
We despise you!
Got it...
Even I despise myself!
I'm not a man
Can you slap me again?
Sure, despicable!
We despise you!
Honey, I'll run along now...
I'll be the perfect wife...
and always give you face
I'll go home now and run really
really fast
You have fun
Persian night promotion, 20% off
Free fruit plates, too
Do they take cards?
What kind of cards?
Birthday cards!
They'll give you free wine for cards!
Cheers!
What a treat...
Persian pussy cats!
You're Soo's family?
I'll show you and beat you up!
Seasonal Chan!...
Master Soo!
Where's Seasonal Chan!
Brother Soo? What's wrong?
Seasonal, look for yourself
my entire household...
Over twenty of them were beaten up
by your wife
Look what she did!
How do you propose to settle this?
You see for yourself!
Good God...
If I slapped you, hit me!
Not my wives,
My children, my family!
Sammi...
How can you hit a helpless puppy!
Does she have a heart?
Brother Soo...
Your wife, your call
If you still consider me a friend
Give me justice, show me you're a man
Punish her and make her pay!
Why! Why did you do this!
Why...
Say you're sorry!
If you want me to stop beating you
say...
Tell me you're sorry!
Ouch! You're hurting me!
They are innocent
Why did you beat up his family?
Only I can hit you, no one else!
What gives you the right
to beat up others?
Why are you so self-righteous...
And I can't punish you?
You're just a bully!
Help! Help...
Help!
Who do you think you are!
Help! Mom, help!
Moth Liu, I'll make you pay
for hurting...
every concubine, every child
and the dog. What do you have to say?
Nothing, I didn't do this!
I only kicked down your front door
Are you kidding
I didn't come all the way
in the middle of the night...
to weave a tale for your entertainment
You don't frighten me...
nor am I the least bit amused
Do you think
I can be so easily bullied?
Don't push me!
She beat me up! She beat me up!
Now, I'll really give you
a good lashing!
She beat me up...
Honey, calm down!
How?!
I'm burning like the torches!
Torches don't fuel tempers
I'm fuming!
I've something to say!
Mister and ma'am, I'm sorry!
Me, mister? How old are you?
Abnormal growth hormones...
I'm only 14!
What do you want to say?
Ma'am didn't hit me!
So what caused your injuries?
Auntie...
Hit me when she crashed into the wall!
You're Soo's family!
Creditors!
Wrong person!
Uncle went mad and
pushed me to the ground!
Cousin slammed the stool on my head!
We came all the way
in the middle of the night
To frame you
Good boy, honesty is the best policy
Next time, remember to shave
before you go out!
Got it?
Soo
I beat up my wife for nothing
You owe me one
Your wife started all this
Unless she apologizes
our friendship is over!
So drastic!
My family's looking to me
for justice
Give me face?
OK?
OK! Let the ceremony begin!
You alright?
Silly girl, that's a dangerous spot!
Seasonal Chan! You're a sissy!
Will you promise
You'll never beat up anyone again
especially me?
No!
Hand me your favorite thrashing rod!
No, please
The rod!
Honey, the rod
So your friends are more important
Give me your hand!
One Two
Don't move
One
Two Three
Let's go inside!
Thank you. Honey!
You'll not to leave the house
without my permission!
That's tough!
I hold you responsible
for the He-master!
I swear I'll hit you, too!
Help! Help!
Close the door first! He-master!
Honey, let's go walk the dog!
Honey,
You should read more
Knowledge will give you wings!
Your daddy's so cool!
Go sleep in the bed
you'll catch a cold
Honey
Come on...
He-master
Where do you think you are going?
Wong, let me go out
I need to have some fun!
What do you think I am?
I'm only loyal to you!
Wong! Master!
Are you setting me up?
Master, I'm on your side
I've to understand the enemy
Gain her trust
Then, I can save your ass
- Wong
- Yes, master
I can't leave you behind and
sneak out alone
Why don't you come and
have some fun too
Let's go
No, you need to stay behind and
watch her
OK, sir
Almost time...
For anesthesia smoke
Soo!
A hug?
Your wife may hit you for this
aren't you scared?
Yes, but you'll protect me
It's no fun without you!
Let's go then
Told you he can't resist
the temptation!
Honey,
Wong!
Good morning! She-master!
He-master went to the Club!
There are tons of She-Masters
there tonight!
Hey, bottoms-up!
Let's make them drink!
- They're so boring; make them drink
- Sure...
We're cool naturally!
We can just sip!
OK!
Moth Liu is coming!
Moth Liu loves beating everyone up!
Where's she?
Gottcha!
It's not funny!
You're scared away all the girls!
If it weren't for you
where'd we get all these chicks!
You're a pal!
Chan...
Where's your girl?
Why are you all alone!
I want to go home
I miss my wife
But you're humping!
Yeah, so what?
I'll find you a check!
Too kind of you
You look like a beauty!
Sit here...
Closer
Stop humping!
Nice to knead you
Knead me?
What's with you?
Let's belly-dance!
Moth Liu's here!
Moth Liu?
You're ruining the party...
wait, stop!
Sir, are you alright?
I'm fine.... you run along now
Moth Liu is coming
No one is coming
Are you sure?!
Not again?
Who's Moth Liu?
Why are you so scared?
Drink
I'm spinning
Hurry. I wanna...
You bastard! Belly-dance!
Honey, I'm home... sweet dreams
Honey...
You screw around and
you miss your wife?
You're getting a good deal!
Sure...
I fell in love the first time
I saw you
I knew I would spend the rest of
my life with you
Only you can...
Make me a better person
Only...
Only if you'd not hit me
or anyone else again...
I'm scared, honey...
Honey...
My head's hurting. I'm in pain...
Honey
Are you really drunk?
Of course I'm drunk
Why else would I confess to you?
Really trashed...
Honey, where are you?
Right here, right next to you
Tired, sleepy...
Sleep now, sleep!
Wong, how did I get home last night?
Good morning!
Your outfit --- cleaned and ironed!
Burn it, burn it...
Wong, come here
What's up with you?
She-master has ordered me to dance
For the rest of the month
Where's the nearest cliff?
Why?
I want to jump off it
Just run for your life!
You think I can escape?
Honey!
So healthy... morning exercises!
Yes, good for your health!
No, no, honey
Shut up!
Honey
You like to watch belly-dance?
Not really
It's OK, if you like it...
Wong will perform you during the day
I'd personally perform for you
every night
No, it's OK...
Promise me
You'd not mess around again
OK...
I have faith in you
Finally, one big happy family
Can I make a request, honey?
I'll kill him now!
He-master, stop...
His majesty needs your service
Long live his majesty!
Who'll volunteer to test the new drug?
I will!
You, come here
Go with the imperial doctor
The tests are finished!
Let's have the report
This is Lucky
This is Lucky's puppy lover
and now is his wife
They've sworn that
They'll always love each other
Lucky's favorite food is his wife's
tea-flavored eggs!
Come, Mrs. Lucky
Lucky cannot recognize his wife
After drinking the Love Eraser
Lucky...
Lucky!
Majesty, with this magic drug
Our army will be invincible!
Love unites men
Without love
What's there to fight for?
I order this drug be banned forever!
Majesty, what wisdom!
- Watch it, it hurts...
- It's good for you
Bro, what's with you?
I walked into a bank robbery
I'm fine, I'm fine
Really?
But, don't you have
to make a delivery today?
Yeah
Honey
You're another's wife and
you still have to work for me
I feel bad
Honey, I'll be back soon
Three days, I promise
Hurry!
Honey!
The sun is setting
Honey, while you're gone
I'll write a book
When you come back
you'll be the first to read it
What's your theme?
A secret
You've seen my family jade charm
Your mom gave it to you?
You want to give it to me?
Don't, the charm is to protect you
Why don't we split it in half...
And we'll both be protected
Mom!
It's OK, it seals our love
I'll be back soon!
OK
Ghost story,
Bunny!
Where?
A meek little thing!
Chop, chop, chop. You chop, I chop...
I only invited you to snack
Why did you bring...
this scary Taoist monk!
He's an old friend
He came for my famous dish
you've a problem?
Bring the rabbit!
OK!
Gentle sir
Bunny demon?
The fire's cackling
Bunny demon!
Skin it before you season it
I said Demon!
Demon, I'll cook the demon!
Help!
Help...
Demon...
It's gone...
Stupid, get out of the way!
Help!
Wait for me...
Demon!
Help me!
Gentle sir, let me explain...
You and I were once deities
You were the God of Virgins
I was the Goddess of Innocence
We were tricked by the God of Peaches
And banished from heaven
Zeus took pity
And granted us seven lifetimes
as man and wife
This is the seventh lifetime
If we don't consummate our love,
I'll reincarnate as a dog
Can you not take pity on me?
Sir, it's only a one-night stand
But... you're a bunny
Inside and out, from top to bottom
I'm a beautiful young girl
Can't you see?
Be gentle to your servant girl
After tonight
When the sun rises
I'll vanish forever
Never bother you again
Servant girl, the sun's out
Hurry, get out of here
Before you vaporize
Shush!
Maids!
Maids?
What?
Good morning, princess!
OK, OK, rise!
It's all because I admire your talent
So I came up with this scheme
If only you're single
Then I didn't have to work
this hard to get you
You're really the princess?
So what about last night?
I'll explain
The breeze was my chi
The demon...
there were five of us
The princess included!
Bought the bunny at the market
I'd swear we didn't see anything
Life in the palace is boring
You artists lead such an exciting life
I really envy you
Safe journey, princess!
Savior!
Brother-in-law, so early?
Surprise!
Honey!
Honey, did you miss me?
Of course, honey
Missed you so much!
So did she, she really hurried back
She rode all day and all night
She hasn't even eaten or showered
Brother!
Skipping a meal may keep you slim
But skipping a shower, take a bath
Why don't I fix you a bubble bath
Do I stink? Not really
Let me see
Even your sweat is sweet
How sweet is it?
Sweet as roses
Honey, don't bathe again!
He-master!
Someone's looking for you!
I don't know her,
tell her to go away
Close the gate and let the dog out!
The dog's out!
Honey, let's go take a bath!
Who's she?
Looks exactly like a kept woman
You really shouldn't have
I've nothing to say
Talk to me
With regards to what happened
I have no comments at this time
Please accept my deepest regrets
but I believe...
this incident will not change our love
Over the long run
Tell me!
The princess pretended that
she was the bunny demon
And tricked me into saving her
from reincarnating as a dog
What a fantastic tale!
Did you sleep with her?
Yes or no?
Do you know
what makes marriage sacred?
Keeping your promises
Brother...
What crime did you commit?
None of your business, old man!
Even if I tell you, can you save me?
Neighbors confide in each other
I've done nothing wrong
Nine out of ten say
that they're innocent
Here's one for you:
Compromise and learn to forgive
It's the only way to be free
And live a happy life
So how long have you been here
Mr. Forgiveness?
Thirty odd years
Thirty odd years?
See how compromise has locked you up
It freed you?
Moth, the Emperor has punished
the princess
And he has planned some amends
I have one good and one bad news
The good news is the princess
will marry Chan as a concubine
You'll still retain your position
as the wife
Bad news is you have no say in this
Sister, forgive me, some tea
Say yes, you can't win every time
You can torture her
after the wedding
Once she's his, she's all yours, too
Moth Liu, the Emperor's own sister
pours you tea
And you refuse?
It's tradition
that a man can marry many
The princess is royalty
And she has agreed to be a concubine
And share your housework with you
What more can you ask?
Bend and compromise!
A woman must stay faithful and true
And a man can marry concubines?
Is one woman's love not enough?
When I go hunting
The lion is always accompanied
by a pack of lionesses
I've never seen it otherwise
It's natural for women to obey men
Not other way around it
You compare men with beasts?
Aren't you stretching it?
Miss Liu, look at your husband
He's handsome and talented
He's a woman magnate
Even if you keep the princess out
There'll be others, don't you see?
I will fight anyone and everyone
I must accept this fate
He's my husband and this is my duty
Even if I die fighting off other women
I will not complain one bit
Don't worry, your majesty
Moth Liu, I understand
Fearless as you are, fierce as you are
Are you not afraid of the emperor?
Sure, I'm afraid
I must fight for what's mine
Brave girl!
Aren't you afraid of me?
I'm afraid that
you overestimate yourself!
- You....
- Your majesty
I'm afraid that you'll force
your will on me!
- Your majesty...
- How dare you!
The emperor's furious
Emperor, cool your fury!
Your majesty
Your majesty, calm down...
Brother
Rise
OK, get up, get up
Shit! The lioness roars!
Insult the emperor and
you'll drink the poison wine!
Your majesty!
It's really my fault
I'll drink the wine for her!
Emperor is a man of his words
My husband is the emperor
I'll not let her get away with this?
Bring the poison wine!
Your majesty
may I have a pen and paper
This woman knows no shame
I'll write the divorce paper myself!
What did I do...
why are you divorcing me?
Your worst crime is...
Loving me!
The Emperor...
Why turn a wedding
Into a disaster?
If you'll leave Seasonal now
The Emperor will give you
the Love Eraser
Drink it and you'll forget
the one you love
After you drink it
you'll forget all about him
Drink it
Drink it and
your pains will go away!
It's better to forget
than to be heartbroken!
Sister!
Don't you forget me!
We just grew up in the same house
I'm not your true love
Remember me!
Seasonal Chan, when are you going
to marry the princess?
If you don't, you'll be beheaded
Straight to the guillotine
I can never marry the princess
It takes two to tango,
two to fall in love
Gentle sir, your servant girl
can only hope
That we'll meet again
in another lifetime
Thanks
Moth Liu has forgotten everything
Go to her, make her love you again
If you two fall in love again
She'll only remember the good times
Isn't that swell?
Thank you
What are you waiting for?
Good morning!
Foo, good morning!
Nanny, good morning!
Baby, good morning!
Why are you all so strange today?
Strange, no way...
Let's go out for breakfast
my treat
OK!
What shall we do after breakfast?
Start a fight or something!
Honey
Looking for you?
Moth
Honey
Bastard, who're you calling honey
Do I look like an easy victim?
No... no...
You OK? Are you stupid or what!
She drank the Love Eraser
Why call her honey?
And you had to give her a brick
to hit you with?
Not his honey, I'll hit you too!
Don't talk to these assholes! Go away!
You think this road's yours?
Yeah, you own this road or what?
I'll check the deeds right now
Are you OK?
Thanks
Careful now
Go!
We don't like you! Leave now!
Hate you!
I have a suggestion
Why don't we go to the Club instead!
Yeah!
Up yours!
Up where? Bring me a mat!
Art of War says:
stay still if your enemy's still!
We'll camp out here
Together, like fools
Just sitting here
is not a solution, Soo
But sitting and drinking is
Cheers!
Sit...
Sir, please come in
My brother told me everything
So we were married
Since your arrival
my family's been upset
They're split into two groups
One group hates you and
my brother leads that faction!
The other thinks you've got a heart
That's just Foo and Baby...
I want to put an end to this
I've decided to get marry ASAP
What?!
Mr. Tien!
I was afraid you wouldn't come
with the rain and all!
Get down! All of you!
Put your hands on your head!
Don't move! It's raining, go home!
I'd throw this lid at you!
Stop embarrassing yourself
Give it up!
I'll kill you!
Seasonal...
Brother, I'll marry him
Marry me
So when's the wedding?
Whatever you say!
Tomorrow's an auspicious day
I'm making soup, I need to go home
and watch the stove!
What kind of soup? Is it ready yet?
The antidote for the Love Eraser!
The Emperor's orders!
Long live his majesty!
Bride, let's go now
Master Soo, what's taking so long?
The order's coming! It's coming!
One order of steamed clams! Eat up!
Let's go...
Where's the antidote?
Here!
Soo, as a scholar like you
Reduced to such trickery
They'll make a mockery of you
do you know?
We poets will die for romance
Nothing can stop me
Honey!
Foo?!
What happened to her?
What happened?
Master Tien fell in love with me
And...
Where's my honey?
She's hosting a fight to decide
Who she is going to marry
Seasonal!
He-master!
The only antidote
Down the drain
- Moth!
- What do you want?
Honey!
Go...
You again?
Yes, it's me again
- Honey...
- What are you doing here?
Haven't you caused her enough pain?
What're doing?
How can you let her do this?
What if she gets hurt?
We thought about it
The men will fight each other, not her
Whoever wins will win her hand
The best fighter is not the best lover
She'll never be happy
with a violent man!
Agreed!
And you made her happy?
He-master
I want to enter the fight
How many?
All ten of us
We do everything together
We even share our wives...
eventually
You're not qualified!
Can't you bend the rules
I'm the famous poet Soo Tung Bo!
So what, I'm the infamous Nanny!
Beat up the nanny!
Infamous! We'll show you!
What are you doing...
All contestants proceed
to the boxing ring
Seasonal He-master
Don't do it!
Seasonal...
You'll die, don't go
He-master...
Seasonal, stop!
There're simply too many contestants
The organizers have decided
to turn the event
Into a group fight
There's no time limit
The last one standing...
And still standing after
I count to ten
Will marry my sister
Good!
What do you want?
He-master...
Seasonal, get up!
- Seasonal, forget it...
- He-master...
I'm a mango...
M-a-n-g-o...
We're supposed to fight or what?
Stop!
Illegal gathering
you can go to jail for this!
I order you to disperse now
Or face the guillotine!
I told the emperor
You kidnapped me and stole the antidote
No way?
Yup, I did
But the emperor came up with this ruse
to help Seasonal
Cousin, announce the winner now!
I still have to count to ten
One
Two
Three
There's innocence
And depth in your work
If you work harder
One day, they'll see it, too!
From now on...
I will love you and only you
I'll spoil you
Never argue with you
I will live up to...
Every promise
Never
Lie to you!
From now on, you will love only me
You'll spoil me. Never argue with me
You will always speak the truth
Never lie to me!
Never argue with me...
Honey?
I'll always protect you
Agree with you
Believe in you
I'll stand up for you...
No matter when or where
Laugh when
Your laugh
Wipe away...
All your tears
You'll be the only one in my eyes
The only one in my dreams
Only one...
In my heart
It's just that simple
Honey...
I'm sorry
Whether you remember me or not
You'll always be...
My beloved wife
Honey, don't leave me!
Honey...
Honey!
I've a confession
I've left the soup on the stove
all night
Let's go home and put out the fire?
Great!
Sure...
Does the Love Eraser really work?
By the orders of the emperor
of course it works...
Honey! Honey...
Honey... Honey!
Three months later
With my honey's encouragement
I finally published my first book
Come have a look
The Lion Roars is a real tear-jerker
Based on a true story,
You'll cry, I promise
The book...
became very popular...
Whether you're taking a stroll...
Having lunch...
In the toilet...
Giving birth
Hitching a ride
You can't put it down
Some say my husband's book
Lacks depth
And sophistication
But I truly believe that years from now
They'll still remember...
our love story!