Alright. We're giving you a cool
finishing stitches.
We can't stitch it up like this.
Relax, will you?
Relax!
What's that sound?
Did you get into a fight?
Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine. Teacher,
Il-mae is mine, right?
Everyone, bow to our teacher!
We welcome you, sir.
Teacher!
Tae-il!
Why are you crying
on this happy day?
- Then why are you crying?
- Because I'm so proud of you!
How much did you nosebleed
this time?
Not too much. Only about a bucket
this big... 2 of it...
You did well.
C'mon. Get up.
So, where is your bride?
My bride?
Yes, your bride!
Of course!
My bride just got off work.
So my bride should be here soon.
Oh, I see...
you're already getting excited
just thinking about her, huh?
Teacher! Please, don't touch it.
Don't be shy.
She's here!
Hello?
Tae-il... What are you doing?
Tae-il!
Congratulations!
Tae-il passed
level 1 bar exam
Did you really?
JOO Il-mae! How lonely you've been,
spending so many nights,
all by yourself! Open it.
This is my heart. From now on,
I'll breathe if you tell me to breathe,
And I'll stop if you tell me to stop.
Stupid! You're so stupid!
Stupid! Stupid!
Teacher!
Dad!
- For Tae-il!
Always wait for your return...
your apartment!
I call you because I miss you!
And I hear your lovely voice...
Stop!
This is the happiest day in my life
since the birth of
my daughter Il-mae!
Since we're in full swing of
celebration,
let's have the engagement
ceremony for SOHN Tae-il
and JOO Il-mae right now!
Dad!
Yes?
I wanna get married!
Sure! I'm so proud of Tae-il,
my SOHN in law!
It's not Tae-il!
It's not him
He's not the one I want to marry!
Teacher, you're just joking
with me, right?
You're worried that
I'm gonna mess up the 2nd exam,
And that's why you're doing this.
Shut up!
Please tell me this isn't real.
Tell me Il-mae wasn't serious.
What did you tell me before?
"Sir, I protect my woman!"
Well... you did really well.
I trusted you with my daughter...
Teacher.
You're worthless!
Even if this is the end of the world,
you can't do this to him.
You know he lived his whole life
just for you.
You're killing him.
But, dad, I slept with that man.
Many many times!
What?
I'm not a virgin anymore.
That's why I can't go back to Tae-il.
You worthless shit.
We did our best.
Okay, let's make a contract.
Thank you. I'll convey your message
to our president.
They want to contract
the agreement.
Il-mae! Il-mae! Get off me!
Let's go!
What are you doing?
It all started when we came to Seoul.
So let's go back to Pusan!
- Tae-il!
- Come on!
Let's go back to Pusan!
What am I? A joke?
You think you can just show up
like this and
cause all this ruckus and I'd
go with you?
Il-mae, I love you! I really do!
You don't know what love is!
- Il-mae!
- Excuse me, sir!
- Get off me!
- Sir!
Il-mae, don't do this. Think about it
one more time.
Do you know how I raised you?
Why are you acting like this?
- Let's go, ok?
- Get off me!!
Tae-il! Tae-il!
If you don't go with me, then
I'm gonna kill myself right here!
I already gave you my heart.
I can't live without you!
Don't be stupid. I'm not going.
Il-mae! Il-mae!
Tae-il!
Teacher, the sky looks
awfully blue today!
Tae-il!
I can't believe she's doing this!
Now what's gonna happen to him?
What am I supposed to do now?
You awake? You know how long
you've been passed out?
3 days!
You really scared me this time.
I prepared some seafood porridge.
Kang-chul left his gang and
opened up a sushi restaurant.
He made this for you using
only the freshest ingredients!
Too hot, huh?
Should I cool it down for you?
Give me a cigarette!
What? You got a problem?
No. I heard in Japan a father and
daughter in law smoke together.
I say, where are the morals
and ethics in that?
I mean, it's about liberation.
Cultural liberation!
We need to adopt that thinking
too, right?
- So what are you gonna do?
- About what?
About Il-mae!
We'll get her back. We will.
How the hell are you gonna get her back
when her heart has changed?
First, we gotta find out
who that guy is
Il-mae!
English, French, Japanese and now,
Chinese, too?
Wow, I'd better study harder
to be your husband
Who beat you?
I don't know. A woman came
into the bathroom and...
Il-mae!
How about a hot cup of coffee?
I'll get it.
Nonsense. I'll get it. Wait here.
Relax!
Come on, spill it out!
I'm sorry! Please stop.
I have hemorrhoid.
You should listen to your buddy
if he tells you to stop.
No, you're worse. If you're
his friend, you should've stopped him.
- Look! Look over there!
- Hold on. I should punish...
We got the wrong guy.
Shit!
- Why didn't you tell me earlier!!
- You didn't listen!
Would you like to order?
In a minute. Calm down!
Really?
Bastard! What?
You must know your enemy to win!
What's there to know? He's a rich boy
with tons of money! Fuck.
Fuck? Watch your language!
What am I? Your friend?
LEE Seung-no! Age, 30!
According to my investigation,
he emigrated to US at the age of 12,
received masters in psychology, then
graduated Harvard Law School,
received MBA at Wharton and
returned to Korea in 1999.
Impressive! Level 1 bar exam is
nothing compared to him.
Are you on my side or his?
Of course I'm on your side.
In 1999, he established
Phoenix Software, which
exports various games to
international markets.
In 2001, he was awarded for his
excellence in his industry.
Any weaknesses?
Neuschwanstein, or sometimes
it's known as New Swan Castle.
King Ludwig ll, a fan of Wagner,
built this castle for his lover.
But sadly, they never lived
together, right?
I'm different.
I won't spend my life only building
a castle for someone I love
Il-mae, I love you!
Cuckoo! Cuckoo! Hey, look at that
cuckoo flying over there!
You only know one side of a coin.
2002 Sisa English pg. 482.
King Ludwig ll and Wagner were
gay lovers.
Eventually, Ludwig destroyed
the castle, missing him
Why don't you go look for
a young boy?
Tae-il! You!!!
Take a good look at these!
A dog collar... At the office...
In the car... this one is outdoor...
Do you see now?
He has so many women,
besides you!
He's about quantity. Not quality!
He's not a man. He's a dog!
A dog!
Let's go.
Maybe you're too shocked to
fully understand the situation here.
No. It's you who's not
getting the situation.
I knew he had other women,
but I didn't care. Because I liked him
and that's all it mattered.
I'm sorry about this.
Let's go somewhere else.
Are you crazy?
What are you doing with
this playboy?
I'd rather be with a playboy who
knows how to love me,
than a kid like you who doesn't
even know what love is.
Nice photoshop work.
Pervert.
Fine! You can call me pervert or
whatever you want!
But what about me?
I lived my whole life just for you!
What about me then?
Who are you?
Me? An international referee.
Ready?
Hello?
Teacher, I forgot to tell you
one thing about LEE Seung-no.
He's a master in judo,
aikido and fencing!
Tae-il! Are you ok?
Teacher... he's pretty damn strong!
Tae-il! Tae-il!
Il-mae, I shouldn't say this
as your dad, but...
I think purity of heart is
more important than that of body.
I believe Tae-il loves you for
who you are in your heart.
Can't you just give him
one more chance?
Dad, give me a kiss!
You crazy?
You can't do it, right?
Neither can I. Tae-il is like that.
He's my childhood buddy.
Like a brother.
I can't even kiss him.
Really?
It's too late, dad.
I just want to be his friend.
I'm worried.
He'd never give you up.
There's only one solution.
I should marry Seung-no quickly
Tae-il! Are you out of your mind?
Why are you burning your books?
The reason for my existence was
to marry Il-mae.
Not becoming a judge
or a district attorney.
Tae-il! Tae-il!
Oh my god!
Fire! Fire!
JOO Il-mae, come back to me!
I love you forever.
Come back to me, JOO Il-mae!
JOO Il-mae, come back to me!
JOO... Il-mae!!
"Prepare yourself for death, and
you'll live and prepare yourself
for life and you'll die!"
said General LEE.
Chinese textbook pg.118, line 4!
Love is like a marathon!
I must eat to win!
Merciless bastard!
You can't take her away from me!
Maybe today is the D-day.
They dined at a fancy restaurant
and danced at a jazz bar, right?
Then, he probably gave her
Neuschwanstein and said,
he won't be a fool who
only builds a castle...
then a kiss.
They didn't kiss.
That's not the point!
With a little bit of alcohol and
sweet words, he melts her heart
Then with a seal of love,
the game is over
She becomes his woman.
You really like polar bears that much?
JOO Il-mae!
Tae-il! You're impossible.
Please let her go. Please.
You could have anything in the world.
But she's all I have.
Please let her go. I beg of you.
Il-mae! I never even got a chance
to show you how much I love you.
Just give me one chance!
He looks just like a weasel
Tonight is not the first night
we're sleeping together.
We've done it countless times.
So, don't bother me anymore.
You bitch! Bother you?
I've been bothering you?
How about me?
You think I enjoyed packing
your lunch for 4 years?
And reserving your seat at the library?
Do you think doing your
laundry was fun?
Really?
It's nice to know
how you really felt.
Can I go now?
Get out of my sight!
You make me want to puke!
No, I'll go.
I'm so shamed I wasted my life
chasing after a slut like you!
What? I ask you to go to Seoul
to look after Tae-il and
investigate Il-mae's affairs.
And, now you
return and cry like a girl.
Il-mae went to the hospital.
So, I thought she's gonna see
a gynecologist.
Hospital?
She has the myelodysplastic
syndromes,
the same illness that
took away your wife.
Oh, lord.
Teacher, you're so light.
You got no meat on your legs.
You've gotten so thin.
You need to eat more.
I'm not light.
You've become stronger.
Tae-il.
Yes, teacher.
Are you really ok?
Of course. I'm fine.
It's not a big deal to me
The funny thing is, the date for the
2nd exam is the same date
as Il-mae's wedding date.
Good. There is no reason why
you should attend her wedding.
Go on and do well on your exam
and pass it with flying colors.
Don't worry about me.
I'll pass the exam... get married...
have kids...
then I will come back to see you.
I'll never forget...
all you've done for me.
Alright.
Who is it? Dad?
Dad, Dad!
Tae-il... Tae-il...
Tae-il! SOHN Tae-il!
JOO Il-mae!
Yes?
Eat well and live well!
Eat well and...
don't get sick, ok?
If you do get sick,
don't get too sick. Ok?
You too! Don't get into
any more troubles!
And don't be so stubborn, ok?
Stop worrying about me.
I'll be fine.
Goodbye.
Tae-il! Do you know why
I'm marrying him?
Because he has other women.
He'll easily fall in love again.
Even without me,
he'll continue to live
a happy life!
But, you can't do that.
You'll only think of me
and love me!
Just like my dad!
I can't let you become
like my dad.
Dad, I'm not a bad person,
am I?
Of course not.
Like a flower... like a star...
you're the loveliest girl in the world...
Dad, let's practice the wedding march.
We have to be careful
not to step on my dress.
Alright, alright.
Il-mae!!!
- Tilt your head a bit to the left.
- Turn it just a little.
My love, do you know
what I did today?
I went to the photo studio with
Il-mae and took pictures.
She braided her hair and
wore this really pretty dress.
And we took a picture together.
She was trying to do what
you and I couldn't do.
Do you know what she said to me
as she took her portrait?
She smiled and said,
"Dad, I've a very happy life.
So please don't cry
when you look at this picture."
And she smiled.
My lovely child... my sweet child...
Teacher, you're killing yourself.
Please don't do this.
The 45th Level 2
bar exam center
Begin.
It would be much appreciated
if you'd participated in blood drive.
What the hell are you saying?
Of course it's our duty as his students
to do as much as we can.
- What's going on?
- Get off me!! You bastards!
SOHN Tae-il! You bastard!
How can you take a test right now?
Tae-il, come out here! You know
what Il-mae did for you?
Get off me! She... Tae-il, she's...
Tae-il doesn't understand why.
He's just trying to forget her
because she told him to.
Come on! Step on the accelerator!
He has no clue that she's doing
this for his own sake
For the only person she ever loved...
she wants him to be happy
even when she's not here anymore.
My love, what am I supposed to do?
What can I do?
I now pronounce you to be
husband and wife.
Nonsense!
- Nullify this marriage!
- Nullify! Nullify!
What the hell do you think
you're doing?
Ladies and gentlemen, this girl
right here, is a horrible person!
This stupid girl...
She's suffering from the same illness
which took her mom away...
So I can live happily by myself...
So I can pass the exam and
live happily by myself!
Il-mae, did you really think
I'd be fine?
I already gave you my heart.
How am I supposed to
live without you?
And our teacher...
he's a horrible person, too.
As her father...
this is how he shows his love.
Tae-il, why are you doing this to her?
What can she do now?
That's exactly why
I cannot allow this marriage.
If you'd known your wife's gonna die,
would you've not loved her?
Answer me!
Il-mae!
I never regret loving your mother.
Your mother was the best thing
that ever happened to me.
Even now, everyday of my life is
filled of joy because your mom!
Please, forgive her.
And please release her.
Allow me to be at her side
till her last day.
- Please release her.
- Please! Release her!
This marriage is... nullified!
Tae-il! I'm sick.
And I'll get sicker.
I'm afraid I won't be able to
be with you much longer
You can't die. I won't let you.
Forget the law school! I'll study
and go to a medical school
I'm gonna find out a cure
for your illness
I pretended I was asleep
and he's already snoring. Little fool...
Our first kiss was a long awaited one...
Thinking about our first kiss
still makes my heart flutter...
I love you, Tae-il!
Teacher, I can't say that!
Tae-il.
I can't... I can't do that here.
Let go of her, will you?
Let go of her.
Never! I'll never let her go!
I'm gonna cure her illness and
we're gonna live happily together
till our deaths do us apart
teeth fall out.