There´s always a price to pay
when you hire an assassin -
from ten to hundreds
of thousands of dollars.
Recently, a mysterious killer
has appeared in Hong Kong.
He asks for no payment
for his services.
He eliminates his targets - all evil
men - because they deserve to die.
In the world of professional killers,
this vigilante is considered
to be the king of killers.
Others who live in fear know him
as the ´´Angel of Death´´
Check Zone A.
You check Zone B.
Make sure everything´s in order.
Follow me.
- Good evening, sir.
- All levels have been secured, sir.
- Is the boss still in there?
- Yes, sir.
Stay alert.
Of all women, I find the Chinese
are the most exciting in bed.
How could they
be better than Japanese women?
Because their strong sense of moral
values makes them highly reserved.
I remember sleeping with them
during the war.
I´d hear their screams of pain,
begging me to stop,
but it just made me more excited.
Japanese women can do that too.
No, it´s not the same at all.
How I long for those days.
Find out what´s happening!
Sasaki?
- What´s going on?
- We´re checking, don´t worry, sir.
- Check for intruders.
- Sir!
Some sake?
Something´s wrong with the monitor.
Check it out.
Sir, he´s out cold.
Someone must´ve broken in.
Check the surrounding monitors.
Shut all elevator power immediately!
Do you read me?
Control, do you read me?
Sasaki?
Shut up!
So, who hired you to kill me?
I´ll make you an offer.
I´ll pay you three times what he did.
You have no idea
who you´re dealing with.
If you kill me,
you´ll also end up dead.
You´ll be hunted down by professional
hitmen from all over the world.
Yes, and whoever kills you
will receive a huge reward.
They´ll all be after your head.
So if I were you, I´d just go.
Leave while you still can.
You stupid idiot! You´ve just signed
your own death warrant!
Excuse me.
- Ma´am, I...
- One minute.
But you gave me the wrong change.
It says there that these are on sale
for half this price.
Let me see. Hey, Jerry, you forgot
to remove the old tags again.
Can I have my money back?
I already punched it in.
Do me a favour,
go and get something else!
But I´ve got everything I need.
Can´t you see the queue?
You´re delaying the other customers!
Then give me my change.
- There!
- Thanks.
Hey, you cheat, move on.
Hello there.
..I walked behind him,
and called out.
He turned around and I shot him!
Right in the forehead!
His head exploded like a watermelon!
I left him there,
his brains splattered everywhere!
Shooting through the heart
is much cleaner and quicker.
Joey, don´t you have
another assignment for us yet?
We could do with the cash.
There´s one coming up,
and you´re all in.
- Fred, have you called your mom yet?
- No.
She´s your only family, right?
In that case, why don´t you come? You
could get lots of money to send her.
Why don´t you buy
a new pair of pants?
These are very comfortable.
All right, you two,
you´ll be coming with me to Macao.
Joey, can I use this a while?
You´ve got some nerve
freeloading off me like this!
- Joey, I haven´t called my mother...
- I don´t give a damn!
I gave you that assignment
to kill Mrs Chu...
and you repair her drainpipes!
She needed my help -
besides she reminded me of my mom.
What about that knife I gave you
you used to cut your target´s steak?
But he couldn´t even chew properly.
And you call yourself
a soldier of the Golden Triangle.
Some tough guy! Maybe you should
leave and stop wasting my time.
All I really need is one big hit.
- Not for just a few thousand...
- Like a hundred million?
- Are you kidding?
- Do I look like I´m kidding?
- A hundred million US dollars!
- Let me do it, boss. Come on!
Get serious!
These guys want first-class killers.
- I could be a first-class killer.
- Really.
You look more like first-class jerks
to me. Hell, forget about Macao.
- Hey, come on, boss.
- Wait up, wait up.
Joey, could you tell me
where I can sign up for that?
Please, help me.
You really want that job?
OK, go to the Tsukamoto Centre
tomorrow morning.
Someone might just notice
your rags and toss you a few cents.
Eiji, the fund manager´s here.
You´d better come and meet him.
Eiji, what is your problem?
I was wondering how
a great man such as my grandfather
could end up with such
a worthless son, the likes of you.
You´ve no right
to talk to me like that.
It was your father who was killed
and you´re not doing anything
to avenge his death.
He´s taken care of that.
Only because
you don´t have the guts to do it.
Useless people like you
will be the downfall of Japan.
You´re not even capable of running
your own father´s business.
Well, I´m in charge now.
I´ve inherited everything.
You don´t even have
a sense of honour.
That´s what grandfather and I
had in common.
Eiji, your grandfather´s ashes
are in there!
No! No!
These are my grandfather´s ashes.
Eat them and he shall live
inside you. Go on!
You´re mad!
You´re nothing but an old coward.
You don´t deserve
his ashes inside you.
No! Stop!
You really are mad!
The board will hear about this.
Let´s go! Come on! Come on!
Sorry, Father. I´m afraid
they won´t listen to you any longer.
I have Grandfather´s soul, so they
have no choice but to follow me now.
You´re all mad!
Phew, he stinks!
´´A Day in the Life
of a Professsional Killer.´´
Grandpa, that man is really smelly.
Quiet, now.
The woman who just came in
is Anita May.
She´s 33 years old and runs
a prestigious modelling agency.
No criminal record,
but according to Interpol,
she´s involved in
some of the biggest crimes in Europe.
She recruits top European hitmen
to assassinate political figures.
She probably gets her clients
from her modelling agency.
- This is coffee?
- Well, it´s decaff, sir.
What´s the point in drinking coffee
if it´s decaff? Forget it.
This is Chris Crado,
42 years old, runs a liquor business,
no criminal record, sir.
Aside from selling vodka,
he acts as an agent for Russian gangs
operating all over Asia.
Therefore he could easily get
in touch with Russian assassins.
So why have all these agents appeared
at the Tsukamoto Centre?
Aren´t they afraid
of being caught together?
It´s because they all want the
one hundred million dollar reward.
If you were a hitman,
you´d be here too.
- Something´s up, Captain.
- Zoom in, please.
Look, if you don´t have
an invitation, you´d better leave.
Just give me a chance.
I´m the man for the job.
What the hell are you talking about?
- Please...
- Get out of here...
I really need the money and...
- Are you looking for trouble?
- Please, let me go, sir.
Are you deaf? I said leave.
Stop! Hold it right there! Do you
morons have any idea who this man is?
He may stink and look like hell,
but he´s also the top hitman
in Mainland China!
- So you´re an assassin?
- I served at the Golden Triangle.
Great! Just play it by ear.
What? Do you know me?
Do you have any idea who I am? Well?
You want to see my invitation?
Well, all you have to do is ask.
Now, you listen. I want to speak
to your superior right away.
- I am the superior.
- Then you understand the problem.
Jerk, here!
I´ll take you in,
but you do exactly what I say.
Can you repeat that in Chinese?
And in Japanese, if you like.
Have you prepared
the bank draft, sir?
Five million dollars in a Swiss bank.
Thank you.
- Five million?
- That´s just for deposit.
Attention, please. My name is Martin,
I´m Mr Tsukamoto´s fund manager.
If you need a translator,
use the earpiece in front of you
and tune in
to the desired language channel.
You´re all aware of Mr Tsukamoto´s
recent assassination.
His will states that a reward
will be offered to avenge his death.
Please turn on the computers
in front of you.
Each of you has an account at
a Swiss bank with a balance of $5.
Please enter your four-digit private
code - your ID for your account.
Whoever completes the mission
will automatically receive the reward
into his or her account.
And for everyone´s convenience,
I´ve filed all the details regarding
the death in your computers.
You´ve all received the same
information to ensure a fair deal.
I´ll repeat the terms again.
The killer and the mastermind
are worth 50 million dollars each.
If they are the same person,
then he is worth 100 million dollars.
If there´s official evidence
that either one doesn´t exist
or is already dead, the full reward
is for the remaining target.
Ah, the right target. The right
target will be identified by us.
We form a special committee
set up by Mr Tsukamoto.
Regarding our professional details,
all information can be accessed
on your computer.
Lastly, I want to make this clear -
we do not encourage lawbreakers.
We won´t be held responsible
should you become involved
in any illegal activities -
you´ll also be disqualified.
- Police!
- This is a search warrant.
Everyone please remain in your seats
and take out your identification.
You´re all suspected of being
involved in international crimes.
Please cooperate,
if you don´t want any trouble.
I´d be more careful, if I were you.
We have two lawyers here, Officer.
What´s happening here?
We´re in the middle
of a legitimate business deal.
I´ll have my secretary
send you a report.
Great!
Why do you have
so many discount coupons?
- I collect them.
- And why so many coins?
He collects them also, so?
- And this knife?
- What about it? It´s for cooking.
- Can´t he speak?
- I´m his manager.
Everyone with talent needs a manager.
So what´s your talent?
He´s a great gymnast.
He´s also good at running,
although he needs more training.
His record´s
9.9 seconds for 100 metres.
Let´s go, men.
Aren´t we going to arrest them?
If they want to play with fire...
- Isn´t that Tsukamoto´s grandson?
- Yes, he´s joining the hunt.
Are family allowed take part?
Mr Tsukamoto, sir.
I don´t like being interrupted
before my meal. What do you want?
Actually, I also
have an appointment - a bridge game.
And I promised my friends
I wouldn´t be late.
You Chinese talk a lot.
If I were you, I´d get to the point.
Your mere presence
is starting to irritate my men.
All right.
I´ve gathered some new information.
If it´s about my grandfather´s death,
I already know everything.
Of course,
but something new has come up.
Since your grandfather
didn´t want the police involved,
we had to use all our influence
to avoid an autopsy.
But we had someone examine him.
And he discovered something
very interesting.
- What do you want?
- You know what I want.
I´ll give you the information,
but I want something in return.
I scratch your back,
you scratch mine, right?
And the others?
You´ll be first to get any news,
so long as you pay $100 each time.
Aren´t you the least bit
scared of me?
I am, but I´m more afraid
of living miserably. Right?
You can cash this cheque
any time of day.
I just hope
your information is worth it.
What we found in your grandfather´s
body was a military banknote,
dating from the Second World War.
We still haven´t decoded it,
but our computers
will fix that in no time.
- When?
- After I´ve cashed this cheque.
Your meal is ready, Master Eiji.
Remove the extra setting, he´s not
eating, he might ruin my appetite.
No problem,
I don´t eat sashimi anyway.
In fact, I hate it.
On that night,
most of the security cameras were
destroyed by Tsukomoto´s murderer.
But we do have some videos, recorded
days before the murder occurred.
They also gave us a video
recorded the night of the murder.
But although the killer is visible,
he can´t be identified
as his back is to the camera.
Bill, you´ve seen the tape,
what do you think?
I think
he´s been in the centre before.
He knew his way around and where
all the cameras were located.
So there´s no doubt he´d given
the place a thorough going over.
Maybe he got hold of the blueprints.
But most of the cameras were
installed under a month ago, sir.
The blueprints wouldn´t tell him
where they were.
How do we trace the killer, then?
Well, we could run his image
through the computer,
together with anyone
who has been there.
All right, get video tapes dating
back a month and start with that.
Yes, sir.
And Bill, don´t let anyone
into the computer room.
They used to be bigger.
What a rip off!
What are you looking at?
You pervert!
Get lost!
Take it easy.
He was staring
right down my cleavage!
So, you like my watch?
It´s a Rolex, 24 karat gold-plated
and diamond studded.
It´s to commemorate the reunification
of Hong Kong with Mainland China.
- Have it!
- I´ve never had a watch before.
Now, I have a Rolex.
Don´t get too excited, it´s a fake.
You don´t expect the real thing,
do you?
Even so, in Tsim Sha Tsui,
this would cost about $800!
This is the most expensive gift
I´ve ever received!
- You´re a Chinaman, all right.
- What?
It´s just that Mainland hitmen
charge between 40 and 50 thousand.
You get 80 thousand
with 10 thousand down payment.
But the reward was 100 million!
I´m your agent, right? I have to pay
for everything, meals, transportation
and I have to pay my informers.
Don´t you think your share
is just a little excessive?
I invested 5 million dollars
without even knowing you.
No-one would do that!
Or would you rather forget it?
How about we split 60-40?
- Not a chance!
- What about 70-30?
All right, 80-20
and I´ll take the down payment.
First of all, I just
want to make sure you can fight.
And you must do everything
I tell you.
Then tell me what you want.
- You know what...
- Hey, you! Enough of your noise!
You´ve got 30 seconds.
I´ll give you something
to shout about! Get lost!
You son-of-a-bitch!
15 seconds, Norman.
Sorry, I didn´t mean to...
Sorry, lady, excuse me.
You wouldn´t dare hit a woman!
Come on! Run away then!
- What?
- But she´s a lady.
You don´t hit ladies?
I´d better look for someone else.
Wait, Norman!
What you need
is a whole new wardrobe,
if you want to be taken seriously
as a professional.
There´s nothing more impressive
than a stylish killer.
- What´s the matter?
- This costs $19,000!
Well, if you dress expensive,
you look expensive.
That´s how it works.
I was wondering if you could help us.
You see, my friend here, ah...
he wants to try a new style.
The ideal material is polyester.
It´s soft and tightly knit,
so you won´t leave fibres
on the crime scene.
Long coats are good
for carrying weapons.
Black suits look smarter and slicker.
And as for the hair...
always use mousse to avoid leaving
hair or dandruff on the scene.
- What are they for?
- To make you look smarter.
I´ll be in touch.
Take this pager.
Where´s my down payment?
What about all these new clothes!
Listen, don´t follow me, all right?
You will call?
These clothes cost me $19,000,
of course I´ll call.
His name is Norman Lu,
alias Crocodile Lu.
His file´s about an inch thick -
theft, selling of porno tapes,
swindling and illegal gambling.
I´m sure he´s up to another scam,
acting as an agent.
He did invest $5
just like the others.
Maybe he´s cheating
the other agents, sir.
He may be a swindler
but he´s not that smart.
So, what´s he doing here?
Are there any answers
in your computer?
- No, sir.
- Let´s go, then.
Is there something wrong
with what I´m wearing?
Course not, Fred, you look great.
By the way, what´s today´s date?
- The fourteenth.
- Ah, fourteen! One and four.
I better find you a job
since you need some cash.
Order whatever you want.
Yeah, you´re looking for
an exterminator?
What´s the salary?
That´s all?
No thanks, we´re not interested, bye.
But, aren´t we
going after the killer?
We still have to work in the
meantime. We have to earn a living.
Go ahead and eat.
Someone told me
he´s in a retirement home.
- I heard he died a long time ago.
- Why didn´t you say so?
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Have any of you seen Mr Leung lately?
Ah, yes, Mr Leung!
Yes, do you know where he is?
Well, you should ask Mrs Leung
about that. She knows everything.
I bet! Thanks.
Wait! We were just kidding.
You´re looking for old man Leung?
That´s right.
- He´s been missing for a while.
- He hasn´t come for tea in ages.
Excuse me, enjoy your tea.
Now there´s a hard worker.
Did you see all the pagers he had?
- You ate all that?
- No, I left this for you.
How could you eat so much?
I´ll deal with you later.
What an appetite!
Jim, what´s new, a new target? Good!
You gave the job to someone else?
But I´ve got this guy, he´s just
come from America, he´s really slick.
How did I get him? He wanted to spend
some time in South East Asia,
so he came to Hong Kong to see
his old friend. 50 thousand´s fine.
Of course not, he comes out in a rash
if he doesn´t kill regularly.
Whoever gets him first,
gets the money?
OK, OK, count us in then.
Who´s the target? Yeah... Right...
OK, get the money ready, thanks.
What a pig!
I eat three meals in one
to save time.
More like three months of meals.
I think we´d better leave.
- Wait, want take away?
- Take away?
The terms of our business agreement
are as follows:
Sometimes you may be required
to maim a target.
8,000 for the left hand, 10,000 for a
leg, and 20% discount for both legs.
- And the right hand?
- That´s free.
- Why?
- It always gets in the way.
So it ends up as a freebie.
Why don´t you look around
for a while?
What about you?
I don´t know the target,
so l´ve got to find my informer.
- But there´s so many kids around.
- Want me to chase them away first?
Wait here.
- I want some candy.
- Give me a pink one.
Just hit the tile and you win, go on!
Aw, you missed!
I can do it, watch.
- Need some help?
- No thanks.
OK, if I lose your dollar,
I´ll give you five back.
Deal!
Try number two tile, I want Big Bird!
That one?
Hooray! I won Big Bird!
Here you are mister,
toss another coin!
- What number?
- Try number one.
- Here mister, try it again!
- All right, one at a time, kids.
That´s great, mister!
There you go.
A bunny! I won a bunny!
No, kids. Sorry but we´re closed,
come back tomorrow, OK?
- Sorry, kids. Did you have fun?
- Yeah!
An assassin who loves children,
isn´t that sweet?
I shouldn´t have underestimated
a man of your calibre.
What do you mean?
Your target´s just over there.
Do the job, I´ll be nearby.
Wait! Who´s the target?
I thought you knew.
- Where´d you get the toys?
- From that man.
The Father of that kid. The kid likes
you, that should make it easier.
Just go over there
and cut his heart out. Piece of cake!
Go on, it´s getting late.
Just think of the cash. Go on.
That´s right. Don´t let me down.
Think of the reward.
Hey, Fred, have you called your mom?
- Not for ages.
- Me neither.
I just shot him!
Right in the forehead!
His head exploded like a watermelon.
Get down!
- Fred!
- Leave the kid alone.
You want him yourself.
- Help me! Help me!
- Sorry, I can´t!
Not me! That guy!
You! Drop the gun! Drop it!
Freeze! I said freeze!
- Hands up!
- I didn´t do anything.
- OK, Norman, let´s start again...
- Captain Kwan.
What were you doing at the carnival?
Having fun.
Having fun?
Children have fun at carnivals.
Well, times are changing -
these days, men are even selling
women´s lingerie and wearing it too!
We found your fingerprints
on the dead man´s gun. Explain.
Your fingerprints are on my wallet.
If my fingerprints are on this desk,
does that mean this desk is mine?
About the deceased, he´s from your
home town, so you know him, right?
I didn´t know him.
All right - explain your relationship
with Norman Lu.
Norman´s my friend.
Not just a friend, a close friend.
You´re lying,
that Mainlander is a criminal!
Oh, I see, a criminal, huh?
Look, whoever you are, you have
no right to accuse an innocent man.
This is what we get for saving lives.
Where were your people
when it happened?
Captain,
someone´s bailing out Norman Lu.
- Who?
- His daughter and a lawyer.
This is my daughter,
who just happens to be a lawyer.
- Hi, honey.
- What is it this time?
Nothing to do with me.
Don´t lie, someone´s just died
and I´m sure you know something.
Can you bail my friend out too?
Just what kind of friend?
Excuse me.
This is my friend.
You´re improving -
no scars, no tattoos.
Everything´s arranged.
No problems, you´re free to leave.
- And this man?
- He needs to be bailed out too.
- No problem. I´ll take care of it.
- Thanks a lot.
David, I´ll join you.
- That´s your daughter?
- That´s right. Why do you ask?
What? She takes after
her mother, all right?
I´m warning you...
don´t even think about it.
Got that?
´´Police Station´´
Wait for me here while I get the car.
David, wait.
I never expected your daughter
to be a budding lawyer.
Life´s full of surprises.
I couldn´t help noticing
some tension there.
What? She´s just cool
and reserved like me.
We treat each other
in a mature fashion -
since we´re living in modern times -
not that you´d know about that.
No, I guess not.
The boss is looking for you.
- Thanks for saving my life.
- You´re welcome.
Here´s $5,000. My card´s in there -
if you need anything, just call.
- Wow, $5,000.
- Is it real? Sure looks real.
You should´ve killed that guy,
then you´d have got $15,000.
Here´s your $1,500. You think small.
You should´ve had a bigger share.
Nice going.
Your pager.
- Drop him off at the corner.
- OK.
- You can go now.
- How will we keep in touch?
I´ll find you.
Go on, get out of here.
Give me a call.
- I´m sorry.
- It´s OK. After all, we are family.
I wasn´t talking to you. David bails
you out whenever you´re in trouble.
- So? He is dating you.
- You´re embarrassing.
No, it´s not OK.
You´re always doing this to me.
What?
You´ve been in and out of jail
since I was a child.
I always felt so embarrassed.
I decided to study law
just so I could bail you out.
One time our teacher asked us
to write about our fathers.
I couldn´t write a single word,
you know why?
Because I couldn´t think
of one nice thing to say.
Come on, Kelly,
don´t embarrass me in front of David.
It´s OK, we´re almost family, sir.
- Stop that!
- Look, just drop me off over there.
Thanks David.
- Yeah? What is it?
- I´m sorry for being nasty.
Just think about what I´ve said.
Sir? Stay out of trouble...
Sure.
To hell with that dumb Mainlander.
I can make it without him.
I´m a survivor.
Hi, Jack. Right...
do you know where Mr Lu might be?
No, no news, huh?
Can you lend me $20,000?
I´ll be... Jack?
Hey!
Your fridge is broken.
- How did you find me?
- I followed you home.
Aren´t you the sly one.
You should´ve told me
you were coming.
Would you have let me in?
Don´t be ridiculous!
I did sense someone was in here.
You picked the lock, right?
No, I came in through the window.
Right! I was just about to say that.
- Yours?
- I decided to move in with you.
That´s great! I would have suggested
it myself, only I didn´t know how.
- Where should I sleep then?
- Through there.
Kelly used to sleep here.
Now she stays in the hostel,
so I turned it into a spare room.
- Smells nice.
- What do you expect? Get some rest.
W-w-what if I slept with you instead?
- No, I talk in my sleep.
- How do you know that?
My girlfriends tell me.
Besides, I might end up telling you
all my secrets. Just stay here.
I´m so glad he´s staying.
What´s wrong?
Should I sleep on the bed
or on the floor?
It doesn´t really matter,
sleep anywhere you like.
- Is it good?
- Very.
When you´re through,
I want you to read these.
Tells you all about how
to be a first class killer.
But I can´t understand English.
So what? - Just look at the pictures,
like you´re reading a Playboy mag.
Here, take a look.
It says here, when you´re in
a restaurant, you should sit sideways
so you can get at your gun.
But everyone would know
I was a killer.
Exactly:
´´How to be a well known killer.´´
A real killer only carries his gun
on a mission.
That´s in here too, see?
You´ll get all the pointers
you need in here.
Forget it. I already know
what´s written in there.
So you think
you know everything already.
All right, then show me.
How do you hold a gun?
- Where is it?
- Here, use the banana.
- But this isn´t a gun.
- Use your imagination.
- Bang!
- Is that how you´ve been trained?
Some soldier you are.
You should stand erect,
facing straight ahead.
Support your right hand,
hold your breath,
and then you fire
at your intended target...
You´re eating your gun! I can´t
believe you´re eating your gun!
It´s a banana, all right? Not a gun.
Here´s a gun.
- It´s rusty.
- No, it isn´t, it´s an antique.
It´s the first real gun
I ever had. Here.
Watch where you point that thing.
- Have you ever shot someone?
- Have you?
Hell, I´ve shot lots of people.
I was known as the lean,
mean killing machine.
Anything I could get my hands on
I turned into a weapon.
I could use practically anything.
I killed three people every two days.
I remember a time...
How´s it going?
We´ve already ruled out 50%
of those who´ve been in the building.
That leaves us
200 more tapes to scan.
Let´s leave the computer running.
We´re wasting time.
We´d better keep an eye on Eiji.
Come on.
Your father isn´t back yet.
- I´ll watch the car.
- I´ll get my things.
Why are you here?
Your father invited me.
He said you wouldn´t mind.
- Did you touch anything?
- No.
What about my closet?
I´d nowhere else to hang my clothes.
There´ll be trouble
if there´s anything missing.
Did you touch her?
No, I slept on the floor.
I never touched her.
I hope not,
she´s never slept with a man before.
So she´s a girl then?
What are you doing here?
David, could you put these
in the car, please?
Did you meet my father in prison?
Could you help me
bring my things down?
All right.
- Are you leaving?
- Yeah.
David, watch your step.
Wait!
See you.
Could we talk?
David, I´ll call you later.
Let´s go.
- Where to?
- Somewhere we can talk.
That sly bastard!
Hello? Hey, Martin, what´s up?
- Is this your first time?
- Yeah.
- Want some ice cream?
- You don´t mind?
Of course not.
You can buy one over there.
- Never mind.
- Sure?
Isn´t she great?
I used to do that when I was a girl.
I used to love skating then,
so my father promised to bring me.
But I knew he wouldn´t.
Finally I came alone
and I skated the whole daylong.
I didn´t want to leave.
The attendants had to call my father
at closing time.
I can even remember the argument
we had by those stairs.
- You know why he got mad?
- Cos you ran away?
That wasn´t it.
He said he never
promised me anything.
I was heartbroken.
Once I realised he never kept
his promises anyway,
I went up to him and said:
´´I will never, ever trust you again.´´
Give him another chance.
Come on,
I´ll teach you to skate.
Well?
Easy, isn´t it?
Come on, I´ll lead you.
Here. There you go.
So, you´re from the Mainland?
Yeah, I was a soldier back there.
My mom lives there and I told her
that when I´ve made it,
I´ll come back and build
a lovely big house for her.
But I don´t even have enough money
to build a toilet.
What´s so funny?
For someone who´s shy,
you talk a lot.
Well, since you told me
so much about yourself,
I thought I´d do the same.
You didn´t meet my dad in prison,
did you?
So what´s my father up to now?
Don´t lie to me now, I can tell.
Do you really want to know?
Is that why you wanted us to talk?
To be honest I´ve no idea what
his plans are. But he´s using me.
Let´s make a deal.
- What?
- Give me you finger.
From now on,
promise that you´ll tell me
everything my father is doing.
And I´ll give you a reward.
Let´s see you try alone.
Careful!
Why do you have so many coins?
Well, they´re useful.
Can I have them?
Come on, Fred.
´´Children in Need´´
They´ll be of far more use
to those in need.
What´s wrong?
All that money!
Let´s go.
All right, you maniac!
Where did you bring my daughter?
Talk!
Where did we go? I can´t remember.
Stop that! Remember what I said?
Keep your hands off!
We´re going out.
You´re lucky I still need you around.
Otherwise, you´d be out.
Where are we going?
Remember Martin, the fund manager?
He´s got a lead.
We´ll talk about it on the way.
Give me the key.
Great! You finally missed a shot!
So, what´s the lead?
- Relax. Where´s the money?
- Here: $200,000.
This is only just enough
for a month´s fuel.
- For what - a spaceship?
- A yacht.
So where were we?
Right, evidence
was found in Mr Tsukamoto´s body,
which we believe
was left by the murderer.
It could be a vital key.
- What is it?
- I´ll ask the questions. What is it?
It´s a Japanese banknote
from the Second World War.
The killer must have made
Mr Tsukamoto swallow it.
- So...
- Sorry, that´s all.
For $200,000! That´s highway robbery!
Call it what you like.
Before you came in I sold this
information to five other parties -
they paid me more.
- How much did the first party pay?
- Shut up!
- How much did they pay?
- None of your business.
But I told them about 72 hours ago.
That´s all you can tell us?
OK, although this is unconfirmed,
I think I know who the killer is.
For the past four years,
there´s been an assassin in Southeast
Asia, called the Angel of Death.
He´s more of a vigilante,
he works alone.
He´s suspected
of killing 17 people.
But these people were so evil,
they deserved to die.
Angel of Death?
The Bible says the Angel of Death
is God´s mercenary against evil.
His mission is to spread justice
by killing wrongdoers.
In short, he´s God´s own hitman.
Now I´ve told you all about him,
let´s call it quits, OK?
Let´s go.
Martin, who was the first buyer?
I can tell you have a focused mind.
Tsukamoto´s grandson. Excuse me.
Why did you ask that?
Well, Eiji found out first,
so we´ll just follow him.
Aren´t you the smart boy for once!
This is a stupid idea.
We´ve been tailing him for days
but we still haven´t found anything.
Just relax.
Right, I´ll do that. You keep watch.
I had the serial numbers on the note
regenerated by the computer.
In Hong Kong, all banknotes were
registered even during the war.
How else could we claim compensation
from your people?
Oh, I found the owner.
He´s an old man.
Here´s his personal file.
At least now,
you´re getting your money´s worth.
- Get the cars ready.
- Sir.
Look, here they come.
I don´t want him killed yet.
Bring him to me first.
He´s not home yet, come back later.
Go in!
May the word of God enlighten you.
Fred, come on. Hurry!
There´s no sign of him anywhere!
Search the entire building
immediately.
I´ll wait here.
Don´t shoot!
Don´t kill him!
Can´t you go any faster?
Put him in here!
Grab him!
Throw him to me!
They´re downstairs!
Out of the way! Please don´t die,
Mr Leung! I need you.
Fred, hurry, close the gate!
Don´t move! Get over there!
I like the Japanese.
Yamaha´s are great!
Are you all right? Say something!
I can´t breathe!
Hang on, Mr Leung.
Hang on, Fred. You´re doing fine.
We´ll wait upstairs.
Come on, Mr Leung.
Oh, dear!
Hey, Fred! Let´s go.
Mr Leung, tell them
all about it. Mr Leung!
Please don´t die on us.
We have to know the truth!
He´s dead!
What did he say before he died?
Well, what did he say?
He said... Piss off!
He was worth $50.
Did you know that?
No, they´re not worth it.
I´m assigning you to another case.
I want you and your team
to bust this Mainland gang.
No-one else can do it.
Not until after this case.
Look Kwan, you´ve got to follow
orders. I´m still the Chief.
You´ve been driving the department
crazy since this started.
It´s not just that,
an old man was also killed.
Hold on a second. You and I
both know that´s not how it happened.
He was already dead before he was
shot. He died of natural causes.
Our men interviewed the neighbours.
We´ve done all we can.
It´s a hopeless case.
Take my advice...
let it go.
- There´s something I must tell you.
- It´s about time.
I´m not really an assassin´s agent.
I know that!
I´m the one they´re after -
the Angel of Death!
I don´t believe you.
They may think
I´m the Angel of Death.
But I´m not actually him.
What are you talking about?
I´ve had enough of your lies.
This is how it happened.
One day, I read an ad... for a killer.
Just like that exterminator ad
the other day.
But the terms of the ad
were very strange.
So I figured he was new at this gig,
and since I needed money to pay the
bills, I called him up and we met.
That was Mr Leung, the old man.
Anyway, he wanted me to kill someone
for him -
a Japanese officer, who´d killed
his family during the war.
I thought it would be impossible
to find this guy.
But Leung said he was right here
in Hong Kong on business.
´´Hundreds Protest Fascist Leader
Tsukamoto´s Arrival in Hong Kong´´
I decided there could be money in it,
so I accepted.
But I never expected
that aside from being old and senile,
all he had was a box of old Japanese
banknotes from the war.
They have no value at all.
Then later on, he told the story
to someone at the antique shop.
He finally ended up selling
his banknotes for $2,000,
then he called me up again.
By then I felt so guilty
taking money from that old man,
that I just gave him my bank account
number and I said:
´´Deposit the money when you read
of Tsukamoto´s death in the papers.´´
But then Tsukamoto did get killed,
so the old man deposited the money.
What makes it worse is
that I wasn´t the one who killed him.
It was someone else.
I´ve been looking for Leung,
to tell him and to return his money.
Now it´s too late.
Why didn´t you hide? And what
about that $5 you deposited?
I took out a mortgage
on the apartment.
I had to know if they were on to me.
They found the old man.
Besides if I... If we find the killer
we could still end up with $100.
So it is the money.
Someone´s coming.
Papa, what are you doing?
There was a mouse,
I was trying to...
I think he´s got himself
into trouble again.
Were you in a fight?
Of course not, we were just
cleaning, right, Fred?
What happened to your face?
I came to get the rest of my things.
Great! It´s best you moved out.
The sooner the better, right?
Do you really hate me
that much, Papa?
What are you talking about?
You´re the one who wanted to move.
- Sir, has she told you?
- Yeah, she´s moving out.
No, it´s my father´s birthday
on Saturday.
We´re also celebrating
Kelly´s promotion.
We´ll understand
if you can´t make it.
Of course I´ll come.
I wouldn´t miss that.
- When is it?
- Saturday.
See you there?
See you on Saturday.
Don´t eat too much junk food.
´´Fred, she looks like you.
Look after her.´´
He withdrew $20, then $30...
It must be here somewhere...
Let´s scan forward...
Just a little more...
Here it is.
According to Leung´s bank account,
the day after
your grandfather´s death,
he withdrew $200,000
and deposited it in another account.
- Can you trace that account holder?
- I already did.
This is the man you´re after.
Him?
That´s the weather for today...
- Ready?
- Let´s watch the news first.
A fire broke out at a five storey
building in Wanchai, this afternoon.
The fire started at Unit 504 on the
5th floor of the Chiu Chow building.
What´s wrong?
..whether the fire was intentional...
- They´re on to me.
- How do you know?
That´s where I used to live.
We´d better get going.
My God! They´re here!
Move it!
Now they all think
I´m the Angel of Death!
They all want to find me
so they can kill me!
Maybe it´s best
if I just leave this place.
Just take a boat and split.
You´ve thought about killing me too,
right? So you can get the money?
Yes, I have.
But I´m no match for you.
You´re... you´re no killer, Fred.
You´re too nice.
- What´s that for?
- Just take it.
- If it´s some kind of deal...
- Will you relax? It´s a gift.
Do me one favour - watch over Kelly.
She´ll be working with the sharks,
she´ll need protection.
Just take it,
so I know you´ll look after her.
I´ll look after her anyway,
even without the watch.
I thought so.
You like her a lot, don´t you?
I can´t take this.
I don´t have any friends.
You´re the only one I´ve got.
So take it.
Now, go, get out of here. Go on!
Go on! Get out of here, will you?
What´s the message?
´´Kelly: Are you coming?
Your friends have arrived.´´
Is something wrong, sir?
I don´t feel well.
You! Off with those clothes!
- How long have you known my father?
- A few weeks now.
- You must be corrupt.
- What makes you say that?
A lot of my dad´s friends
are criminals, except for Fred.
Are you?
Well, why don´t you ask your father?
He´s here.
I wonder what he´s saying
to Kelly right now.
Maybe he´s also after me.
Keep him busy while I talk to Kelly.
How do I do that?
Talk to him.
Dance with him if you want.
You remember Captain Kwan, Fred.
Why don´t you two catch up?
Care to dance with your old man?
I haven´t seen this suit before.
- Do you like it?
- Not really.
- Why not?
- It doesn´t suit your size.
That´s the price I pay
for having a daughter as tall as you.
What brought you here, Captain?
Word is Norman´s the Angel of Death,
so everyone will be after him.
His daughter´s innocent.
I just want to make sure
they don´t use her as a hostage.
You´re the Angel of Death.
Only you know he´s innocent.
- You´re sure about that?
- Absolutely.
Then kill me now.
You´ll get a hundred million.
Even if I killed you,
I wouldn´t get the money.
You have a good head
on those shoulders.
Come with me.
- David.
- This will only take a moment.
I want you to meet
my girlfriend, Kelly.
- Hello.
- Kelly.
Uncle would like you
to work for his law firm.
You deserve to work
for a more prestigious company.
We don´t usually accept new lawyers,
but I owe David´s father a favour.
Stop it, you´re embarrassing me.
Excuse me, Uncle,
I´m really grateful for the offer,
but I enjoy my job
as public prosecutor.
It´s a good place to learn, right?
Don´t be offended.
Good evening, sir.
Dad, this is Mr Lu,
Kelly´s father.
- Glad to meet you.
- You don´t seem glad.
What is your line of business, sir?
Oh, different things.
He used to own a taxi company,
now he´s in freight.
Really, I´ve heard
that´s quite lucrative.
Actually, I have no business.
You know what I really do?
I cheat people out of money.
- Papa...
- Kelly, what´s the point of lying?
They may not know the truth today,
but sooner or later they will.
And I´ve given you enough pain.
I wasn´t a good father.
I´m sorry, I won´t bother you again.
I just hope that...
some day I´d see you...
as a brilliant lawyer
that I can be proud of.
Well, sir, don´t be alarmed.
Kelly has been against my work
from the start.
Gentlemen, thanks
for a wonderful evening.
I have to go.
Now you can arrest me.
I´m ready to go to jail.
You´d better look for
somewhere to hide.
Like where, Captain?
They won´t give up looking for him.
Let´s go.
- Where are we going?
- We´ll tell Martin the truth.
- What if he doesn´t believe us?
- If he doesn´t, you´re history.
Kelly, don´t worry. I can be
like a father to you from now on.
Thanks a lot, sir, but I´ve decided
to break up with David, anyway.
Let her go. Don´t be such a wimp.
Hello, Martin speaking.
Martin, it´s Fred.
Norman´s here with me.
Everyone´s been looking for him.
Have the money ready
before we reach your office.
I´m not in my office.
I´m at the Tsukamoto penthouse.
Is there anything wrong?
No, everything´s fine.
We´ll be there soon.
Do you still believe
they´re going to pay you?
Everyone´s after me. I´ll wind up
dead anyway, so we may as well go.
If you hadn´t been in charge of this
hunt, I´d have killed you long ago.
If you get the cash,
give half of it to my daughter.
I have to make it up to her.
So you made it?
So, he´s the Angel of Death?
As far as everyone´s concerned,
Norman Lu´s the man.
And if I kill him now,
I get the reward?
- Of course...
- Let him talk!
- Immediately!
- I don´t want to hear any more lies!
- In my experience...
- I can transfer it to your name now.
- You´re lying.
- Why would he do that?
Two keystrokes
and I´m connected to the Swiss bank.
The amount is entered in your account
and you input your code number.
That´s it, the money´s yours.
Then, I´ll do it.
Fred, why did you have to kill him?
I can´t transfer the money myself
because he´s in charge of the hunt!
It doesn´t really matter
who kills him. The reward is mine.
I told you we couldn´t trust them.
You were right.
Great foresight, Fred.
All right, game´s over!
We´re outta here! See you around!
What about your five million?
Give it back.
Give it to them!
- Where´s the Angel of Death?
- He´s coming.
He better be quick!
It´s the Angel of Death.
It´s him!
So, you´re the Angel of Death.
Now you´ll pay for my grandfather.
I´ll deal with the lady,
I can take her.
What a woman!
No, I´ll take him.
There, can´t get far now, can you?
Now, it´s my turn.
So, you want to get a little closer?
Wow, you should´ve been a gymnast!
- Are you all right?
- Hospital bills cost a fortune!
Don´t worry about the money.
You´ll get the hundred million,
once you´ve killed him.
Can you do it?
No, I can´t.
Wait!
Now you know too much about me.
Hold it right there.
You can´t just waste all that money.
- What do you mean?
- We have to make use of that money.
- It´s $100.
- What do you suggest?
We have to invent a story - Eiji,
here, is the real Angel of Death.
He killed his grandfather
for the money.
The Captain found out...
oh, I´m sorry...
He asked you to help out
so he could arrest Eiji.
When Eiji fought back,
you had to kill him.
As for the man...
We´ll sort out the details later,
just give us the money.
No problem, guys.
Gentlemen, I carried out
your instructions -
and invested your money
in Coca-Cola shares.
Of course, I´d appreciate
20% of the annual profit.
Now that you´re all millionaires,
you have nothing to worry about.
Now I can buy my mom
a really big house.
Buy her a skyscraper for God´s sake.
I´m bringing Kelly skiing
in Switzerland.
You´re lucky, I´ve lost my job.
Well, I have this rich friend
who hires vigilantes for just causes,
and he´ll pay $3 per target.
Don´t tell me, I´m done
with that business, all right?
If you change your mind,
tell me about it, OK?
Thanks, Martin.
Can I talk to you in private?
You can talk here, I´m his agent.
I forgot to tell you.
I´ve got a new agent.
You replaced me?
There she is.
So you´re the one
who took my place?
I´ll be his lawyer from now on.
You mean,
you´ll be handling all his assets?
I´ll be handling your assets as well.
You must be dreaming! I´d never
let anyone charge me commission!
- I´d better retire.
- But you are retired.
I mean as a vigilante.
- As the Angel of Death?
- Yeah, you can take over.
I´m afraid I´m not
a very good killer.
That´s because
you´ve had the wrong targets.
If they deserved to die,
I´m sure you could do it.
Think of yourself as the new
vigilante... The new Angel of Death.
Let´s make it three Angels of Death.
All right. It´s a deal.