I had no dreams.
When I was nineteen,
I didn't do anything.
Every night,
all I did was hang
out with Taesoo
and fight with the gangs
in the neighborhood.
That was my life back then.
This goes 300km.
This baby is mine.
I'm serious.
And you're going to be
the only to ride it.
Remember the guys
we met earlier?
They want us to work for them.
I got us hired.
We can't be doing
this low life shit.
We both like the fast life.
I'm switching schools.
My old lady wants it.
For better grades,
I guess.
Going to college?
I never thought about college.
I had to get away.
Of course,
moving to another school
wasn't going to change
anything...
You.
You're late the first day.
I'm talking to you.
Hey!
Look at me.
If you cause any problems, I'll personally
take care of you. Is that clear?
Say something.
Yes.
I don't like your face.
Mr. Kim.
Our new student.
Get out.
This way.
Welcome.
So, you're Min?
I'm your home room teacher.
Hope you like it here.
Whan was the first guy
I met at school.
Whan was the kind of guy
who bragged about the fact...
that he started sniffing glue
in 5th grade.
I don't give a shit about
where you hung out, asshole.
Know who you're fucking with,
huh?
He was full of shit.
But he was O.K.
- Anything else?
- Up yours.
I went easy on you. Don't fucking
walk out on me. I'll kill you.
Come back here.
- Congratulations!
- Thanks.
Go ahead.
I got you a pager.
My mom got me one this morning.
I can get you something else.
Hmm... a boyfriend
with a face like Brad Pitt.
Can't get into college
with a boyfriend.
Whan, hey, Whan!
What's up?
Come on.
Stop sniffing glue.
Hey,
get your ass out here.
Fuck.
Man has no peace...
Consider yourself lucky.
I screwed my back up.
In one fight I took on 17 suckers.
If it wasn't for that,
you would've been fucked.
Another round?
Just kidding.
Let's go check out
the rich girls.
Introducing today's high light.
...Min!
$100
$100?
Hey,
that's not fair!
Congratulations,
he's yours.
Over here.
How are your grades?
- What?
- How are your grades?
- You can't go to college with that.
- Are you good in school?
Straight A's since first grade.
I like the Beatles.
Just do.
To tell you the truth,
I like you.
But remember,
you're still my slave.
Don't give this
number to anyone.
When I call, you have to come
no matter what.
Gotta go to study.
Bye!
My baby.
You've been studying.
Drunk again?
Watch who you hang out with.
I've been breaking my back
selling insurance
to save for your college.
This is Romy.
The third playoff between LG
and Lotte is at Chamshil tomorrow.
Go see the game and
write down everything.
If you screw up...
you're no longer my slave.
Got it,
Min? Bye!
Those LG cheerleaders...
had these thin hard bodies,
and could really move.
Bottom of the 9th with 2 out,
LG took out the 4th hitter
and sent in a pinch hitter.
They go on ahead and bam!
Get a hit.
Cool.
With exams next week,
how can you go off and watch a game?
They're still a week away.
Nerds really gross me out.
So you go to college,
and then what?
I can't believe you.
There you are.
Later.
If I knew you were such a baseball fan,
I would have taken you with me.
I'm not into baseball.
Sex, screen, and sports...
are for losers.
You think kids who watch baseball
do anything with their lives?
I'm going to college and
I'm going places.
All my friends are in the top
And 12 of them go to my school.
I may not make it.
Does that scare you?
No, but I don't
want to be a loser.
My pride won't let me.
Everything is about survival.
You do what it takes.
Does that turn you off?
No,
I respect people...
like you
with clear goals in life.
Of course,
a slave must respect his master.
Romy wasn't like
any girl I ever met.
She always smelled good.
She was confident.
Cut it out.
I can get off track like this.
I really like you.
So you've got to
go to college, too.
Min!
Hey,
someone's calling you.
Min!
It had been 4 months.
But...
Taesoo didn't say much.
I dropped out...
two months ago.
Hey, Min.
Check this out.
I asked the cook for
some extra noodles.
What's up?
Get me a drink.
And wait.
I just paged this
hot college chick.
Drinks are fucking on tonight.
- Whan.
- Huh?
Sorry man,
could you leave us alone?
Call me for the dough.
- So?
- Nothing...
just wanted to see you.
I'm going.
You're wasted.
You can't ride the bike.
Don't get off.
I got it today...
and I thought about
who should ride it if I don't.
You.
Got some business.
Stay out.
I watched Taesoo get
the shit kicked out of him.
Felt like shit
'cause I didn't do anything.
Yours?
Don't let this bike
get to your head.
You look like a degenerate.
Mom, it's me.
How come you're late?
Your English tutor's been
waiting over a half an hour.
Let go.
Don't you feel anything for me?
Before college,
I'm a studying machine.
A machine has no time for
any feelings.
Romy.
I started to like that girl.
The college exam was coming up.
All I could think about was
Taesoo and Romy.
Class was meaningless.
All I could do was to wait for
Romy to page me.
You messed up your exams?
I met some guys...
and I sort of got distracted.
Kyung,
how did you do?
Worse than me.
I don't know what you do.
You party all the time
and still ace everything.
Cheer up. What's important is
the college score, anyway.
In the worst case,
you can try next year.
Another year of this shit?
I'm afraid to look at my mom.
If I can't get into Seoul National
University, she told me to drop dead.
That's low.
But everyone in your family
went to that school.
He doesn't realize
what I put up with.
Mrs. Kim,
please calm down.
If he tries harder,
we'll see some good results.
These bad grades.
Least now you know.
I just want a diploma.
You can quit school
and take the college exam.
- You're smart enough.
- Don't be so tough on him.
And you should understand
your mother.
Are you going to
live with my mom?
What are you saying?
Don't be so rude!
Please,
be good to her.
Min, Min!
Where are you going?
I'm not going home.
Want a drink?
I'm going to call a friend.
Whan. It's me.
Sorry but I can't
make it tonight.
You know.
No,
it's not that.
No... you shithead!
Okay, sorry.
Romy!
Romy! Open up!
That...
was the last time I saw Romy.
What did I tell you?
Graduation is soon, so I go easy on
you, and all you do is make trouble.
- Wise up.
- I'm sorry.
Straighten up!
With these grades,
you can't even make it to
a junior college.
You'll never be anybody.
Straighten up!
You little prick!
What about trade school?
Hm...?
Kid, what do you
think you're doing?
Stop it.
Hey,
isn't corporal punishment illegal?
Whan, stand up.
At full speed,
the world becomes silent...
and I'm sucked into a point.
But I can never go through it.
The closer I get,
the farther it becomes.
Romy,
where are you?
Imagine a fucking big restaurant,
all mine!
I'll be cruising in a nice car,
in a black three-piece suit...
with a blond chick like
Meg Ryan next to me.
What do you think?
How about you?
What can I do?
I guess anything's
better than now.
Fuck, anything
but getting kicked out is O.K.
My old man's wish is
my high school diploma.
- Whan...
- Huh?
can I stay with you?
What's with this running
away from home shit?
If you don't want me...
What?
Are you out?
Half the rent.
Min!
Taesoo here.
Life ain't that bad here.
You know,
I work it.
I've been adding 10 more
push-ups every week,
and now,
200 push-ups are no problem.
Didn't take the college
entrance exam?
What did I say?
We're not cut out for that shit.
It's already been a year.
I miss you.
Hi, Min.
This is Romy.
Just because your master's not around,
doesn't mean you're not a slave.
It's very quiet
and comfortable here.
Sometimes boring...
But it's okay.
Sometimes,
I really want to see you.
I wrote you a lot of letters.
I've been meaning to send them...
but...
I guess I'm lazy.
I probably won't send this one.
Two years have passed.
As usual,
my life was nothing.
- The figures don't add up. Look at this.
- I don't know about it.
Hey, come here.
Why?
- Did you take the cash?
- Says who?
Who saw me steal?
Who else but you!
Books are off after your shift.
Hey, fuck you!
I ain't taking this shit from you
just because you own the place.
Fuck,
I'll quit!
What did you say?
- What's wrong?
- I don't know. He treated me like a thief.
So everything's my fault?
- You lame ass.
- What?
Sorry...
Fuck you!
You son of a bitch.
You're in this together,
aren't you?
You're both going
to jail tonight.
Motherfuckers!
I'll teach you.
You didn't steal?
Shit.
Did I ever lie?
I can't fucking believe this.
Did you see him steal?
Well, did you fucking
see him steal, huh?
You're accusing him
without any proof? Huh?
Is this how you treat
your employees?
That's it.
Call the police and...
we'll burn the place.
Good day,
motherfucker!
Hey, I'm sick and tired of
looking for work.
Let's get some steak.
Okay, I took some dough. You think the
motherfucker's going to pay us pension?
- You crazy mother!
- Okay, okay. Take it easy. Chill.
Why are you fucking around
with a pager that never beeps?
Trash it.
Did you look for a job?
Don't be giving me the eye.
My old man sent me
his pension money.
It's time I went into business
for myself. Be my own boss.
Not everyone can run a business.
You're too young.
21 is not a kid.
My old man says I'm the only one
who can build the family fortune.
All my folks did was have kids. I've
got 4 younger brothers and sisters.
Take it.
It's about $3,000.
You little thief.
How the fuck did you get it?
Hey, Min. Get your ass out
and take a look.
Isn't this cool?
Spelling off?
It's been a long time.
Yeah, I guess.
Taesoo came back.
I don't know why but seeing him
made me feel good.
He was my brother.
Look at this place.
I'll open up my own place soon.
You're here,
sir.
Go to Madam Shin,
like I told you.
Yes, sir
- Don't want any trouble.
- Sure.
Hey, let's get a
drink at Paradise.
About fucking time
I went to that club.
- How's business?
- We only let two tables in.
- Madam Shin in?
- Yes!
Hey,
who are you?
Assholes, they're my friends.
Let them in.
Wow, it's cool.
Fucking interior is fly.
Hey,
go on in...
- and I'll join you.
- Okay.
He wanted to be a partner
and now he wants me to quit.
I'm sick of this
business anyway.
Go tell him to give me
my money back, now!
You fucked up.
So pay for the damages.
What?
Are you threatening me?
Your true self comes through.
Fuck...
- Hey sis.
- Why, son of a bitch!
I never knocked
off a broad before.
Maybe it's time.
Hey, Taesoo!
Where have you been hiding?
I missed you!
Let's not complicate things.
Now,
this one is extremely cute.
You don't stand a chance.
- Hey you, come on out.
- Go, go.
Lucky him.
- Thanks for the drinks, Taesoo.
- It ain't nothing...
Take your bike.
It's yours.
I like the ones
with four wheels!
New gig.
Come see me.
I've got a lot to do,
but...
no one I can trust.
Our place will
be open in 2 days.
That's not what you're
cut out for.
Why waste your gift?
Is fighting a gift?
Maybe.
I'll make that gift rot forever.
If you become a CEO
or make it on the street;
it don't matter
when you're successful.
No,
that's not for me.
I want a simple life and...
don't think I'll make it big.
A long life.
That's my dream,
Taesoo.
A long simple life.
That's my dream, baby.
You haven't changed one bit.
You, neither!
You!
Hey!
Are you crazy?
Kissing me with that fucking
dirty mouth of yours!
- Whan...
- Hey, go away!
Whan. Let's go!
Sorry, Sunny.
We've got some stuff to
buy tomorrow.
Yeah, right...
Next time, you come alone,
okay?
Hey, Sunny.
Taesoo,
it's good to have you back.
Next time,
I'm buying.
Let's go!
- See you.
- Yeah, come see us again.
Our high school days were good.
Nothing to worry about.
Would you like to go back?
Fuck you! I still want to kill
that fucking student counselor.
Red pepper.
- Hey, what a fucking place!
- Business must be okay.
Yo,
what are you doing?
Asshole!
Don't tell me you don't know.
Motherfuckers.
You didn't inform us about shit.
Sorry.
We messed up.
Cut the bullshit
Get us some noodles, lame ass.
Sure.
Cool it.
Please,
I beg you.
There are sleazy motherfuckers
who take monthly protection money.
But we're not like that.
Once for the opening is enough.
Just bring $3,000 to the
pool tables cross the street.
$3,000?
Why?
Should I raise it?
You know what to do.
By Saturday.
You're not gonna pay them,
are you?
I ain't afraid of those fuckers.
- Whan.
- My life depends on this place.
Fuck, we pay them.
It's not even monthly.
We pay the cocksuckers and
do our business. Losers.
Fuck...
Romy was there waiting for me.
She was never out of my heart,
not once.
And there she was.
I've been in
Manhattan for 2 years.
I lived near the Central Park.
Know what I like about New York?
No one cares about
other people lives.
Nobody cares!
No matter what you do,
no one judges you.
Only in New York!
I didn't think you'd
keep the beeper.
I thought it would beep someday.
Got a surprise for you.
I recorded this for you.
Listen.
Are you back for good?
Sh...
This is the best part.
Min! It's me.
Sunny.
What are you doing here?
Wow.
Is this motorcycle yours?
It's so cool.
I've always wanted to ride
one of these things.
C'mon, give me a ride.
Please...
- Sorry but I'm busy.
- Hey, Sunny.
What are you doing here?
You live around here?
Bye, Min!
Come see me next time.
Sure thing.
Sunny, wait.
Let me go.
I'm busy.
- Sunny. When is your day off?
- Why? I've got no day off!
- No, wait!
- What do you want?
- Don't be angry.
- Why are you doing this?
I didn't see Taesoo much.
All we did was talk
over the phone.
Every time he asked me
to work with him,
I turned him down.
Something wasn't right.
That confidence in
Taesoo's voice...
But I wanted to believe that
he was doing fine.
There aren't good jobs
or bad jobs.
There are just jobs you do.
There are different parts
to a human body.
It takes different lengths of time for
different parts to be severed.
Sign over the right
of night club.
You've got some balls,
you dick!