We are going so fast.
Aren't you scared?
I'm enjoying it all the more now.
When you are with me...
I'm not scared at all,
In fact, this is great fun!
Watch it. You're going
to be really scared now
what are you looking at?
I feel like giving you a kiss.
- So give me a kiss
Close your eyes first
whenever you give me a kiss,
you make me close my eyes
How will I know how good
you are at kissing?
If you want a good kiss,
you got to close your eyes
Hey! You've woken up!
You speak as if this is the
first time I've ever woken up
Because that truck keeps honking away,
I got to wake up early every morning
why don't you keep that alarm clock
close to your own ears?
You ought to thank that clock which
at least wakes you up on time
Else, the whole world wants to fulfill
its dreams in the world of dreams itself
Hey Maninder...
- Yes sir?
Is everything okay?
- We've got to replace the carburetor
Take the carburetor from the new car
and fit it in this one...
and fit the old carburetor in the new car.
- Could you please explain in detail?
Sure, I will. If you put
the carburetor of that car in this one...
this one will work fine. And the car
that's here for wheel-alignment...
will soon be back for a replacement
of the carburetor. You get that?
Sure, I do.
- You've understood...
but make sure you don't
tell Arav about it
That's wonderful, Mr Vasvani.
What a con job!
We're here to fix cars
and make money
So get on with your work.
Don't waste my time. Go on
Go! Time is money
Hey Ali-bhai...
welcome to my garage!
Skip the crap! What silly jobs you do!
The cars get screwed in just two days
Not again?
Here's what I'll do
I'll entrust your car
to the real expert this time
He has only to touch it
and it'll be fine. Okay?
Arav...
Have you fixed the car?
- This one can't be repaired
It has a manufacturing defect.
Sue the manufacturers...
you'll get a new car.
- But how do I know that you're right?
What if I get stuck
in a legal battle?
I've never made a false claim
where cars are concerned
Okay? So don't you worry
I have faith in my abilities
Just wait and watch. There will
come a day...
when cars designed by me will
zoom across every street of the world
That's tops, I say!
God bless you!
"Sat Sri Akal, Papa-ji..."
You've wasted so many pages
to write just a single line?
Wasted pages? I'm writing a letter
to my folks, not wasting pages
And, by the way, how do you
write a letter in just a single line?
I'll show you.
- Go ahead. Let's see
Here's the pen. I wanna see
"I am fine here..."
"and hope the same for you.
Your son, Arav"
Is that a letter or a telegram?
You won't understand.
Just mail it to my address
You and I just don't think alike.
- Right!
You've come to America so that
you can earn money...
go back to India and settle down.
- Oh sure, that's spot on
But that's not what I want to do.
Why should I leave the country...
that's giving me everything?
Name, fame, progress... why?
Don't leave it, sir!
Who's asking you to leave it?
But do tell me something. What happens
of your folks back home?
They'll be fine. My elder brother
is around to take care of them
And once I get settled here,
they can come here and live with me
Sir, my designs are truly innovative
and distinctively a class apart
I seek your support to gain access to
the research and development...
department of your principals.
- Mr Kapoor, you will have to find...
alternative modes to access
the authorities
I suggest you send in
your proposal directly
Thank you
Fab job Arav! You have turned
my car into a new one. What did you do?
Nothing much, just a few
changes here and there
You're so talented, why don't
you start a workshop of your own?
If you say, I'm willing to invest.
- Mr. Patel...
you want to throw me out of business?
- Mr Patel...
my aim is not the opening of a workshop.
Basically I'm a car-designer...
waiting for the right opportunity.
- And this is the land of opportunity!
You don't know Mr Patel, Arav
He's opening a new discotheque
very soon...
to coincide with his nephew's marriage.
- I hope you guys will attend
By the way, Arav, give me
a demo CD of your designs
I know a lot of people
in the car industry
All right, sir.
- I have a piece of advise
You ought to visit the gypsy temple once
and try your luck
Look at them rocking!
Shake a leg!
It takes little to make a Sardar
break into ajig!
You get on with your luck!
I'm going to have a blast!
You can keep this.
I'll take out another one
Excuse me. It's not just
another piece of paper
we both made a wish
and picked it up
who knows? Maybe God wants both of us
to know the same thing
"You'll meet with your destiny today"
I can't believe this!
Are we each other's destiny?
I don't believe in things
like destiny
we reached the temple at the same time,
make a wish and pick up a chit...
if all this can happen,
why can't we be each other's destiny?
Because this is just a coincidence
and nothing more
It's all about perception.
What if we meet again?
We'll see
Hi, I'm Anna.
- I'm Arav. Take care. Bye
Anna! He's so handsome!
Straight out of a romantic novel!
"Girl you got me shocked
from the rhythm of your body"
"Burn coz its hot
like wassabe"
"Go low till you knock knees,
shaking that ass..."
"till we crash kamikaze"
"Take my hand,
make me turn around..."
"put that flower-band
in my hair-bun"
"Sway with me, lover-boy..."
"you have married me,
now put up with my airs"
"Love is real,
love takes time"
"Love is sinful
and divine"
"Look up at me, my love.
Raise your eyes"
"I'm a rare beauty, my love"
"Take me in your arms,
hold me to your bosom..."
"don't make me pine like this"
"On my moon-like face,
apply a dot..."
"embellish my beauty
with pearls and diamonds"
"Drape me in a sari
that glitters"
"You have married me...
now put up with my airs"
"watch me,
undercover cops can't stop me"
"Gonna lock you down
with my lock and key"
"Cause you could be Punjabi,
Gujarati, Parsi or a banging Bengali"
"Youth is but shortlived, my love"
"I just can't wait anymore"
"My heart is pounding,
I'm beyond reasoning..."
"fall in love with me"
"Lay a bed in the room,
give me all the joy in the world"
"Let your lips feed mine
the wine of love..."
"you have married me,
now put up with my tantrums"
"Your tight-fitting blouse"
"Your flowing scarf"
"Your skirt pulled up"
"They drive me crazy"
"They're others who dance
to your tunes, O pretty one"
"They're others who do up
your hair-bun"
"I'm one of those who don't
play up to women's tantrums"
"I'm the love that makes
makes women bow at my feet"
"win me over with your charms..."
"come rushing to me,
whenever I call"
"Give unto me your
youthful charms"
"Because I have married you...
don't show me those airs"
"Take my hand,
make me turn around..."
"put that flower-band
in my hair-bun"
"Sway with me, lover-boy..."
"you have married me,
now put up with my airs"
"Love is the King.
You're the Queen of the party"
"Feeding to have a scene
with this young hottie"
"Have a ball,
take a drag..."
"talk about the sex
and forget about the wedding"
Arav, you look dashing
in this black suit
Thanks
I'm waiting for a compliment too
Oh! So you are a shy guy by nature
Anyway, this is our second meeting.
Do you think it's destiny?
Mere happenstance
There are just a handful of Indians
in this city...
who keep bumping into each other
on festive occasions
It'll be a mistake to call it destiny.
There are hundreds of thousands of people
in this city
So, our meeting again has definitely
got something to do with destiny
Suit yourself with whatever beliefs.
- His belief, not mine
You'll surely accept it some day.
- Well, it's that...
wow! Friends already?
Nothing of the sort. Just a
coincidence that we've met again
My word! You need good-fortune for
such coincidences, my friend!
Bye!
Dammit! What wrong have I done?
- I was trying hard to shake her off...
and like an idiot,
you took up for her!
What a nut! You don't try to
shake off gals like her!
You ought to be chasing her!
Anna, he should be crazy about you,
but he's just not encouraging you!
Nams, some guys like it slow.
- Yeah
Even I like it.
This is the way... slow!
But not so slow as to get old
and proclaim one day...
"Darling, I love you"
Nams, he might not agree
with me today...
but one day he'll surely realise
that I'm his destiny
That trip to the temple
and our second meeting...
things like these don't happen
every other day
I'm just waiting for
our next meeting
There must surely be something that
will bring us close to each other
Excuse me. Can I test-drive this car?
- Sorry, sir. It's only for display
Can I check the interiors?
- With pleasure. All yours
You...? Here?
- I am, wherever you are
I'm sure you think this is
a coincidence too
Actually I am very fond of cars
well, cars are my life,
my passion... my destiny
Destiny? Cars? So we do have
something in common
It was nice talking to you.
See you again...
if there is a coincidence
Believe me, my destiny will surely bring
us together again. By a coincidence
This car was launched only today
and you've bought it already?
I haven't bought it,
I'm just taking a test-drive
when I asked for it, I was turned down.
How come you got it?
I'm well connected, you see?
You want a lift?
What are you so thoughtful about?
C'mon!
You are such a weirdo. Guys pray to
get a lift from a beautiful girl...
and you are acting pricey.
- Okay
Do me a favour, please.
- What?
Give me my bag lying back there
Here you are.
- Open it
Excuse me, it's very unsafe
to open a lady's purse
You won't be embarrassed. Open it
Done.
- So give it to me
Give you what?
- Give me the scarf in the bag!
I can't see anything. Hurry up.
- Here you are
what on earth are you doing...?
We'll end up having a collision
while you're tying up your hair!
God! Here's a harassed girl...
instead of helping her,
you're yelling at her?
Can't you simply tie up my hair.
Go on now. Do it
Are you serious?
- Tie it up, I can't see a thing!
What are you doing? Tie it up!
- As if I've done a course in this!
Sit still, will you?
Tie it up properly
Thank you.
- You're welcome
This is fun!
Amazing body!
- It takes years for a body like this
I can see that. But I've never
seen a shape like this one
And this colour... it's a killer!
I wish I could have it right now.
- What?
This car. I love its aerodynamics
Arav, what's your profession?
- I am a car designer
If I get the opportunity, I could
design a better car than this one
Anyway, you can drop me here
when are we going to meet again?
- Whenever your destiny wants us to
Take care. Bye
My laptop!
Hey Arav! Congratulations!
There's an urgent interview
call for you from BMw
All the best, my friend.
- Congratulations!
I won't be able to appear
for this interview
why not?
- What's the matter?
I forgot my laptop in Anna's car.
- So call Anna and have it brought here
I don't have her number.
- But you have her address?
Let's go and fetch it.
- I don't have her address either
She was giving it to me, but...
- You mean, you didn't take it?
God Almighty! When's this guy
going to have some common sense?
Guess what? You gave
a demo CD to Patel, right?
So I'll call Patel and have that CD
rushed back. Simple
I hope I don't mess up
this opportunity
Patel's cellphone is switched off.
But don't worry, Arav
CD or no CD,
you must go for the interview
Mr Arav Kapoor, we at BMw believe that
new talent has to be promoted...
and in keeping with this tradition
we have invited you here today
I'm very grateful, sir, but
the thing is... I have a problem
I lost my laptop yesterday, so I won't
be able to show you the designs...
and the demos I have made.
- But we have already have your demo CD
we have gone through your designs
and the opinion of my panel is that...
it's very impressive. So we have
decided to give you a go-ahead
welcome to BMw.
- Thank you so much
The administrative officer will
introduce you to your work-station...
as well as your personal assistant
Hi Arav.
- What are you doing here?
Call it a coincidence
By a quirk of destiny,
I happen to be your assistant
Oh, now I see.
You showed them my laptop
A coincidence. You forgot
your laptop in my car...
and when I looked into it for
your address, I discovered a genius
The rest, you know
I don't know how
to thank you Anna
You've made my dream come true
You deserve it.
So now do you believe in destiny?
Maybe not in destiny, but yes...
I have started believing in you
"He loves me...?"
"He loves me not"
"He loves me!"
"When you lose your heart
to someone..."
"you're on the horns
of a dilemma"
"O my love... I hope
I don't fall in love"
"when you lose your heart
to someone..."
"you're on the horns
of a dilemma"
"O my love... I hope
I don't fall in love"
"I hope I'm not bowled over
by her charms"
"I hope I don't find myself
lost in her eyes"
"I hope I do not err..."
"my heart knows not what anguish
love causes"
"when you lose your heart
to someone..."
"it's oh so difficult"
"O my love... I hope
I don't fall in love"
"what intoxication
leads me astray...?"
"What fragrance
my lovely memories exude?"
"Never was I in such a state..."
"what desires now consume my heart?"
"When you lose your heart
to someone..."
"it's oh so difficult"
"O my love... I hope
I don't fall in love"
"when you lose your heart
to someone..."
"you're on the horns
of a dilemma"
"It's difficult...
oh so difficult"
Nams! I'm in love!
I'm in love!
Madam, you've taken Arav
for your life-partner
But isn't it necessary to find out
whether he's your type at all?
Yes, you are right!
But how do we find out?
Simple, let's ask him
Stupid, as if I'd ask and he'd
tell me. It's not so easy
You're right.
What should we do then?
Got it!
Anna! What happened?
Did you find out...?
So tell me!
Please Anna! Tell me!
- Okay
The company's procedures. All employees
have to go through a psychoanalysis test
what's that?
Psychoanalysis.
- What on earth is that?
The company wants to know
what kind of a person you are...
your likes and dislikes and so on
Everybody's got to do it.
Take a look at this
Okay. Shoot
The question?
Sure. What are you fond of?
- I'm fond of food
I don't know how to cook.
- Stupid! What are cookery books for?
I love Chinese, Lebanese, Mexican,
Italian, Thai...
but nothing to beat
our spicy Indian food
Butter chicken, cottage-cheese
cooked in butter and lentil-curry!
They say, the way to a man's heart
is through his stomach
Isn't that a rather odd route?
- But guys love all the odd routes!
Should I let you into
something personal?
Promise me you won't laugh.
- I won't
Sure? Promise?
- Yes
I love watching cartoons.
- Cartoons! At your age!
Sorry
Give me a big box of buttered popcorns
and my favorite cartoons
Tom and Jerry, Scooby Doo, Batman,
Spiderman, Tin Tin, Richie Rich...
and so on
So cute!
What is your sexuality?
- What?!
I mean, are you bi, hetro,
metro, tetro...?
What...?
Well, I'm happy and gay.
- What?!
Why do all the guys with such
good qualities turn out to be gay?
I was only kidding
Thank God!
What would you gift
your girlfriend on a date?
How does that concern the company?
That's my personal life!
That's precisely why I'm asking you.
To know more about you
I'm asking you stuff from the
questionnaire. Take a look, if you wish
Let me see
Okay, go ahead
what gift would you give her?
A bouquet of flowers...
or an expensive platinum
necklace studded with diamonds...
or something that your
girlfriend is really fond of?
I won't gift her any of these.
I'll gift my girlfriend a cactus plant
Cactus!
Flowers can wilt.
Expensive gifts can be stolen
But not the cactus. We use the cactus
for the security of our homes...
and a cactus will always
remind my girlfriend...
that if anyone ever tries
to act smart with her...
I'm going to smash his...
Fantastic!
Unimaginably romantic!
He's just my type.
Arav was made only for me
Coffee?
Know something? That's just
what I was thinking about
And you said it.
- So I can read your mind
I'll go and get it.
- Okay
Young man, it's Friday night
when all your friends are enjoying
the week-end with their families...
why're you still working?
- Sir, this is not just work for me
It's my very life. If you don't
mind, may I ask you something?
Yes?
- Why are you working so late?
It's like this, son. I happen
to be the Chairman of this company
This huge empire you now see
was once a dream I so cherished
Like you, I too want to reach
these heights of success, sir
Very ambitious boy. What's your name?
- Arav Kapoor.
Nice meeting you. I can see that our
association will go a long way.
God bless you
Congratulations, Arav!
- Thank you!
It's because of you that
I was able to taste success today
You were the first one to spot my talent.
Arav, some people make
such a name for themselves...
that the world
remembers them forever
I'm sure you are one of them.
- You have so much of faith in me?
Yes, I do. And you owe me a treat.
- I'll fulfill all your wishes today
First things first.
Let's go and party
Okay
C'mon guys!
Cheers!
Arav, this is Virvani here.
- Yes, sir?
I have gone through the reports.
Well done, my boy
Thank you, sir!
We have finalized October 11 as
the date for the launch of your car
Cheers!
- Thank you, sir
Is everything all right?
I'm so happy... I'll go mad!
What happened? Will you tell us?
- Mr. Virvani just called
My car is being launched, Anna!
- This is great news!
Why are you looking at me like that?
I've been so immersed in my work...
I realise today how beautiful you are
I'm glad you've realised it at last
I've also come to realise...
that I'm in love with you.
I love you, Anna
I love you too
The function has started.
Why isn't Anna here yet?
A girl needs time to get ready.
So be patient
Hey Arav, congratulations!
Isn't this the moment you've
always waited for?
Arav, Mr Virvani wants to see you
in his chambers
May I come in, sir?
Arav, this is the most
expensive city in the world...
and this is the most expensive
piece of land in the city...
where our office is situated
This company thrives on hardwork
and intelligence...
but life feeds
on love and emotions
I lost my son and daughter-in-law
in a car accident
Everything was finished for me.
But thank God...
my granddaughter Anna survived
Anna means everything to me
I've given her everything
she has ever asked for in life
Today she has chosen you
as her life-partner...
she loves you a lot and I am sure
you reciprocate her feeling
Sir, I love her too.
- But mind you...
when I see Anna shedding tears...
I lose all control
I can never forgive someone
who hurts Anna
Sir, she'll always be happy with me
Ladies and gentlemen, let me have
the honour of introducing to you...
the most brilliant designer of
this amazing car, Mr Arav Kapoor!
A big hand!
My dear friends, till now I was
only sharing my product with you
But now I feel like sharing my
personal feelings with you guys
On this joyous occasion, I would
like to announce the engagement...
of my granddaughter Anna with
Mr. Arav Kapoor. A big hand!
"I feel love for you...
overwhelming love"
"As many times as I set my
eyes on you..."
"I felt overwhelming
love for you"
"I feel love for you...
overwhelming love"
"Spend with me
a few moments of solitude..."
"don't walk away,
having driven me crazy"
"My heart bears a burden,
it's difficult to rein it in..."
"I implore you, do not
smile teasingly like this"
"Don't twist my wrist..."
"Goodness!
Don't pester me like this"
"Someone might see us,
what will he have to say...?"
"Stop teasing me... go away"
"As many times as I
thought about you..."
"I felt love for you...
overwhelming love"
"I feel love for you...
"I'm in a daze,
I yearn..."
"what's happening to me,
little do I know"
"You are the one I desire,
you are the one I love..."
"whatever anyone has to say"
"Your enticing kohl,
your lush tresses..."
"your shy gaze that
lowers to my shoulders"
"The fragrance of your lips,
the magic of your face..."
"your charms have stolen my heart"
"As many times as I desired you..."
"I felt love for you...
overwhelming love"
"I feel love for you...
we're home.
- Hmmm.
Don't you want to go in?
- No!
It's said that men change
after the wedding
But you won't change, will you?
- Never
You'll forever hold me in your arms?
- Forever
And who'll design the cars?
Want me to tell you?
- Yes
Come here, I'll tell you.
- Hey, what are you doing?
Don't move.
This is my laptop. Okay?
I'll now switch it on
what are you doing?
Have you gone mad?
Hang on, my laptop will
fall down, stop moving
I'm now going to make my designs.
Okay?
You're tickling me! Let me go!
- You'll ruin my designs!
Let me go!
Cheat! You'd forget to step on the
brakes while you're at the designs
Stop teasing me, baby! Please let go!
- Know something?
I love the way you say baby
I wanna record your voice and
make it my ring tone. Say something
Hi baby, Anna here.
Hi baby, Anna here!
Now wherever I go,
I'll carry your voice with me
Relish the mangoes...
- Polishing off the mangoes, eh?
Have one, my friend
It's your house the mangoes
have arrived from
They're absolutely fantastic!
Oh yes, there's also a letter for you
Baby, why do you sound so worried?
Anna, I have to leave
for India immediately
But what for?
- My dad is not well
Is he okay?
- I've no idea
Quickly pack your stuff,
I'll drop you at the airport
I'm already there.
My flight leaves in 30 minutes
Okay! Call me once you reach there.
Okay, baby
I'll miss you.
- I'll miss you too. Take care
Come back soon.
- Bye
"Do come now, my sweetheart..."
"come and see what
state I've been in"
"Come, give me a hug..."
"I'm yearning to see you"
"I can't tell you
how much I've loved you"
"You are the one I have
awaited every moment"
"Awake or asleep..."
"yours were the memories
I was always immersed in"
"Parted from you, my love..."
"I've been through hell"
"Do come now, my sweetheart..."
"come and see what
state I've been in"
"Ever since I've received
word from you, sweetheart..."
"I've been on a strange high"
"I can't spend my time,
however hard I try..."
"your face just doesn't
melt of my sight"
"This good news, my love..."
"has awakened a pining"
"Do come now, my sweetheart..."
"come and see what
state I've been in"
"Come, give me a hug..."
"I'm yearning to see you"
"we are going so fast.
Aren't you scared?"
"When you are with me,
I'm not scared at all"
"In fact, this is great fun!"
Tell me something, Arav.
Do you like Kajal?
I do, grandma.
- And Kajal? Do you like Arav?
He's the only one I like, grandma
why don't we ask Arav's parents
to let him stay with us?
And if I send you away to Arav's place?
- That's fine with me!
Oh no. If I'll go away,
who will take care of you?
Well, well.
I never thought of that
Greetings.
- Greetings
Now tell me something.
What do you think of my Kajal?
Not just me, our whole family
likes her a lot. Come here, my child
Thank God.
Everybody loves my Kajal
But why are you asking all this?
I need to ask the opinion of
her prospective in-laws, right?
They are still very young. Let them
grow up. There's a lot of time
They have time, but I don't
I am the only one she has.
If something happens to me...
Don't worry aunty.
I give you my word...
Kajal will surely become
the daughter-in-law of our family
Oh yes!
Kajal, kiss this stone, will you?
You've got a great aim
No, it's your kiss
that does the trick
Guess why we love each other so much?
- Why?
Because we eat from the same plate.
It's supposed to make our love stronger
And when it makes love stronger,
you get married
I see. No wonder grandma
was talking about our marriage
But I am going away to boarding school.
- So what?
You'll be back during
the vacations, won't you?
No, I'll study for the next year
during the vacations
So you're going to forget me?
I'm only going to study,
not to forget you
we're wasting our time.
These trees will die
Saplings planted in the rains
don't ever die
Even if you forget me, these trees
will remind you of me
Bless you, son
Grandma!
Go on, son. Put all your heart
into your studies
You won't forget me once you've
become a successful engineer, will you?
No, grandma.
I'll never forget you
Bye, Kajal.
- Sweets for you
He's not going away forever, my dear.
It's just a matter of a few days
No grandma, it's a matter of years
Don't worry, these years
will pass very soon
Congratulations, Arav. You've topped
the exams in the whole college
You'll easily get ajob
in any automobile company
But I want to go to America for further
studies and design top line cars there
My visa and tickets have arrived.
I'm leaving in 48 hours
You mean, you are directly
going to the airport from here?
No, I'll go home first. So much
must've changed in ten years
I got to know of it only through
letters earlier. I'll get to see it now
Now look, Arav, I have no objection
to your going away to America
But before you go,
you'll have to marry Kajal
Marry! There's no way
I am getting married
But why not?
Papa, I've got to complete my
M. Tech and settle down
That could take 6 months
or even 6 years!
Yes dad, Arav is right
If he's sixty by the time
he settles down...
are we going to get him married
as an old fossil?
Marriage isn't just a formality,
it comes with a lot of responsibilities
I've yet to stand on my own two feet,
and you want me to carry another burden?
Daughters and daughters-in-law
are not a burden on the family
Mom! How am I going to
make you see reason?
I'm not mentally prepared yet
to marry Kajal
Great! I never knew you had to be
mentally prepared to get married!
Why don't you understand
my problem, Dad?
Please, Papa.
Marriage is a bond...
where two people come together to spend
the rest of their lives with each other
That's true, Papa. Kajal has been
waiting for Arav for ten years
It's better if we let her and Arav
take a decision on their own
You've changed so much, Arav
Everything changes
with time, Kajal
Men change, so does
their thought-process
Now look at this sun. It rises in the
morning and lights up the whole world...
but set it does,
every evening.
That's what we think, Arav
The Sun never sets,
it just hides itself from us
And we fool ourselves
that it has set
Kajal, I really thought that even if
my parents don't understand me...
you really will, because you've
known me since our childhood
That's precisely why
I don't understand you
Especially because I have known you
since our childhood
You are the only one
I've ever truly known
I still think of you
as my same old Arav
Kajal, I want to make a
few things very clear to you
It's true that we spent
some great moments together...
but now I neither have any
memories nor any longing for them
You might not, but I do
Love only gets deeper with time
why don't you understand? I don't
want to be tied down in relationships
Ten years is a long time, Arav
But how they went by,
one couldn't even realise
But Grandma doesn't have much time
See if you can convince her, I've
got used to living with memories anyway
My son, I'm counting my days
I want to see Kajal married
before I die
Accept my daughter, Arav.
Please marry Kajal
Once she's married...
I can tell her parents that I've
come after fulfilling my duties
"A traditional North Indian wedding"
I want to see you
as a successful man
The day you reach the dizzy heights
of success you want to scale...
we can have our nuptials
I'll wait for that moment, Arav
what a co-incidence Arav
It was raining the day you left...
and today when you have returned,
it's raining again
I've no interest in this rain today
I've come only to meet you
Only to meet me...?
By saying that, you've given me
the best gift of my life
Today even if you ask me for my life,
I'd give it to you with a smile
I don't need your life, Kajal
Then what is it that
you want Arav? What?
Divorce?
I still can't believe that Arav
could do a thing like this
I thought he had come back to
either stay or to take you along
I too believed that my Arav
had come back to me
Not even in my dreams could I imagine
that he would come here for a divorce
No, Kajal. Nobody's going to let him
break our house like this
Dad, Mom, my husband...
nobody's going to support him
wait till I go and tell everyone
Pressurising him might get me
the status of his wife...
but I won't ever get his love
So what are we going to do?
Arav lives in every memory
I have of my childhood
If distance has
made Arav forget his love...
then I only have to remind him of it
I'll remind him of our love
I'll remind him of our past.
I'll win him over again
I am with you
Promise me that this will remain
a secret between you and me
Damn! No network signals!
Good morning, Arav.
- Good morning, sis-in-law
So what's cooking?
- Your favourite. Porridge
Kajal told me how much you love it.
- My favourite? What's my favourite?
Funny! You don't even remember
your favourite dish?
I hope your stay in America
hasn't changed your preferences
Oh no
That's okay. Ask Kajal.
She might remind you
Should I?
- No, I remember now
I want some tea.
Bring it to my room
I'm giving sis-in-law a hand
Just go to your room,
I'll send it with Kaka, okay?
I couldn't find today's newspaper.
Could you bring it for me?
Brother's reading the newspaper.
Why don't you read it with him?
I'm going to take a shower.
Get me a towel
Listen... the towel's
already in the bathroom
Anything else?
- Nothing
Listen...
- Now what?
Dad has something important to discuss
with you. Have a word with him, will you?
I'll bring your tea there. Okay?
Come, son. Sit down
Arav, why don't you work here in India,
instead of America?
Daddy, I won't get that
kind of response in India...
why? Don't they make cars in India?
There are several big companies here, Arav
Brother, the cars I have designed are
all meant for the international market
Those cars are not meant
for Indian roads
And now when I am getting
recognition in America...
it's not wise to make a shift.
- Okay!
But make sure you take
Kajal along this time
That reminds me,
I have to book my ticket...
and I can't find my passport anywhere.
- Kajal, have you seen his passport?
No, he must've kept it somewhere
I had kept it in my suitcase.
And now it's not there
Help him find it. Will you, dear?
- Sure, Dad
You said it's not in the suitcase.
So what is this?
I wanted some privacy with you.
- Oh!
What? Why're you giving me
those looks?
I see you're in a terribly
romantic mood right now
And as far as I remember, till last
night you wanted to divorce me
And since this morning you have
been ordering me around like a husband
Get me a cup of tea, get me the paper,
get me the towel... come to my room
So here I am!
Tell me... what can I do for you?
Hold the tea-cup to your lips?
Read out the paper to you?
Or take you into the bathroom
and bathe you?
Yeah, let's do that!
Take off your clothes
You are wasting my time
as well as your own
I asked you to sign those papers.
Why haven't you signed them yet?
So time spent with me now
is time wasted?
Then what about those past three years
that I have spent waiting for you?
If you wanted a divorce, why didn't you
ask for it on the night of marriage?
Why did you ruin my three years?
Can you return those three years to me?
This is a pointless argument, Kajal.
You'll have to sign those papers. Okay?
It takes time to build
a relationship...
it also takes time to break it
I won't sign those papers so easily,
I got to show these papers to my lawyer
what will you show your lawyer?
What's he going to see?
Who knows what you've
written in those papers?
I'll have to consult a lawyer, right?
So now you trust your lawyer
more than you trust me?
You shouldn't even
talk about trust Arav
My grandma and I trusted you.
Else, why would I marry you?
By asking for a divorce,
you have broken everyone's trust
why should I trust you anymore?
Okay, you may consult your lawyer but
just tell me how much time it will take
That I can't say!
When you can't trust anyone
easily nowadays...
I don't know when will I find
a lawyer I can trust
Tell me something. I have heard that in
America when a man divorces his wife...
he goes bankrupt.
Is it true?
This is not America, this in India
and it doesn't happen in India
True. It doesn't happen here because
a wife never divorces her husband
But not to worry.
I'll think about it.
Kaka! Fetch a bucket
of water. Quick!
Go on...
- where? No!
Go inside, I say!
Kaka, I'll give it to him
Are you here, Kaka?
Hurry up and give me the water
Kaka! Can't you see...?
Pour it on my hands! Hurry!
Kaka! You've really gone blind!
Pour it on my hands... my hands!
What are you doing...?
Give me the towel.
Where's the towel?
You!
What are you doing here?
What noise is that in the bathroom?
That's what happens when there are
two people in the bathroom
Two...? You mean, Kajal and Arav?
Watch the fun!
There's the water.
- You played this prank, didn't you?
No, no,
It's hurting me...
but it's such a sweet pain
The pain of love is always sweet
Oh my God! What sound was that?
I think they've fallen down.
Happens. All the time
Aunty I'll also take a shower with you!
- Shut up!
Learn! Learn something
from your brother!
But in the bathroom...?
In a tight hug, smooching away...
drenched in the water!
Hi Anna!
- Hi Arav, how are you?
I'm fine
Don't pick up the phone, I was
trying your number and you called
That's telepathy for you. We both
miss each other at the same time
we might be in far away lands,
but our hearts are together
Anyway, how's your dad?
- He's much better now
So come back immediately.
I don't like it here without you
Same here, but a property
litigation has cropped up...
and I can't ignore that.
I want to get those papers signed...
and return to you with
all my issues resolved
Okay, baby, I love you
I love you too
How are you?
You didn't even inform us that
you were coming to India!
It wasn't planned,
it happened all of a sudden
were you missing your wife?
Forget about me.
Tell me what's up with you guys?
Nothing much! Days of romance are past.
We're now slaves to our wives
Forget that. Let's do something.
- What?
Let's play a game.
- Sure, but what game?
Word power.
- Word power?
What's that?
- I'll tell you
There's always a word to explain
anything in every language
Like "khushi" is the Hindi word
used for happiness
Correct. That's right.
- So I'll give a word in English...
and you must translate it into Hindi.
- No problem! Simple translation!
That's okay, but what will
the winner get?
Yeah, what's the prize?
- Whatever the winner asks for
Sounds great! So who's the first?
- Me
Tell me what you call
a button in Hindi?
A button? I'll tell you! It's called
"Ast vyast vastra niyantra gotika"
when your clothes fall off...
then the ball used to bring
them together is called a button
Great! Mind-blowing!
Merely saying mind-blowing
is not enough
How about my prize?
- Anything you want!
God bless my soul!
Give me a Punjabi kiss then!
C'mon... let's do it!
Enough, stop it!
It's my turn now
One moment. If I answer your
question, what will you give me?
Whatever you ask for.
- Yes!
It's a promise in everybody's presence.
- Sure, all right. But what if you lose?
Ask me the question first.
- What do you call divorce in Hindi?
Very simple..."talaak".
- Yes! Bravo, Arav! You've won!
No Arav, you have lost. Because talaak
is an Urdu word, not Hindi
And however hard you try,
you won't find the answer...
because in our culture, there's
no such thing as a divorce
So how can there be any such word?
You've lost, Arav
Now that Kajal has won, here's her
opportunity to ask Arav for something
what?
- Ask for whatever you wish
Ask for something. Go on!
Okay, I'll help you out.
Ask Arav for a kiss!
He'd accept that punishment
with pleasure!
"He does not understand
what my eyes convey..."
"my beloved is so wicked"
"Goodness me..."
"every man and woman knows
what I'm talking about"
"Secretly, silently..."
"secretly, he looked
into her eyes"
"I stole a look into his eyes..."
"I stealthily looked
into my sweetheart's eyes"
"How my friends burn in envy"
"when and how did you steal a look
into your beloved's eyes?"
"I refuse to believe what you say"
"I stole a look into his eyes..."
"O Moon, your moonlight
stokes fires of passion"
"My wicked sweetheart
does not understand..."
"his eyes continue to rove"
"Secretly, stealthily..."
"My anklets chime,
my dot shines..."
"I can't go to sleep,
oh what do I do"
"A fire rages in my heart,
my heart is pounding..."
"my scarf is slipping away...
oh what do I do?"
"Against my ornate bangles,
my bangles tinkle..."
"it's driving me out of my senses,
oh how it all torments me"
"I can't spend my nights
without you anymore"
"Secretly, I met my
beloved's gaze"
"Relent now, buddy-boy,
she's your wife after all"
"Go for her quietly,
she's your honey"
"Be a man,
make her day sunny"
"Give a kiss
and don't be funny"
"The clouds reach for my hand..."
"they call me their beloved,
it scares me really"
"They hover around me,
quietly and secretly..."
"they tug at my hand...
it scares me so"
"I'm a wanderer,
to move on is my lot"
"Like the burning embers,
I'm a wayward lover"
"why do you try to
shackle your beloved?"
"When and how did you
meet your sweetheart's gaze?"
"I refuse to believe
what you say"
"Secretly, I met my
beloved's gaze"
"Secretly, silently..."
"with the beloved..."
"my beloved's gaze..."
"I met secretly"
Kajal... where did you
go and get drenched?
She went away without
saying anything!
This is amazing! Kajal was
drenched and so you are
where did you go and get drenched?
Funny! This guys walks away
without a word too
what's up with them?
They get soaked in the bathroom...
and go out to get drenched.
- It's time you learnt from your brother
why? Does something great happen
if you get wet?
As if I need to explain that!
There! She hasn't said anything too.
Looks like I need to do something
You want to talk about something, bro?
- Nothing much...
Finish what you're doing.
I'll catch up with you later
what did you want to ask, brother?
- Nothing important...
just for the heck of it.
- Okay
Okay...? No, no!
It's not okay
I do have something to ask you.
- So go ahead.
Well, what is that
getting wet all about?
What? Why have you stopped?
Ask the question
Later.
- Why later? Ask him right now
I might as well be
enlightened too
what?
- Oh yes
It had something to do with getting
drenched, isn't it bro? So ask me
Getting drenched...?
- That's right... getting drenched
It's like this, dad. The car Arav
has designed does not have a roof...
so won't people get
soaked in the rains?
Right. In the rains,
that car's going to be flooded
Dad, this is a romantic car.
A two-seater. Only for couples
Apart from the joy of driving,
you can even enjoy getting drenched
But what do you do after getting
drenched? I mean, don't you feel cold?
My son, when you have a girl with you,
you don't feel the chill
Kajal, I'm sure this monsoon
is going to do something
I can see its effect on Arav.
- No sister-in-law
This monsoon's having an effect
on everyone, accept Arav
It was this very rain that
once brought us together...
but I'm afraid, it might
separate us this time
But I won't give up so easily.
As they say, pray sincerely...
and you will even find God
And then, Arav is not just my love,
he's also my husband
I can see only one way of getting
a divorce from her
what's that?
- I'll produce a few witnesses in court
what for?
- You've been in America for 3 years
During this period, this girl has had
an illegitimate affair with two men
Mr Lawyer!
Now look, I don't wish to
make her life a butt ofjokes
In that case, you'll have to
apply for divorce by mutual consent
Yes, I remember.
I'll be back home soon
Okay? Bye
That was my wife. She's fasting
for my long life today
Very well then. Have
those papers signed...
and I'll handle the rest
of the formalities
Aunty, are you not thirsty?
- No
Aren't you hungry either?
- Not at all
But I can't remain hungry for long
Kajal, Arav has gone to Delhi.
He'll be late
You haven't had anything since this
morning. So go and eat something
No, Mom.
I'll wait for him
All these years when Arav
wasn't here...
you ended your fast by looking
at his photograph, didn't you?
That was different, sister-in-law.
Today he is here with me...
he should be coming any moment,
I'll wait for him
The young master's back!
The young master has arrived
where were you all this while?
Kajal's been waiting for you
You're just not bothered about her.
- What was so important...
that you had to go away to Delhi
on the day she fasts for you?
You could easily have gone tomorrow.
It's so irresponsible of you
Go to your wife immediately
what the hell, Kajal! You very well
know that I want to divorce you...
so what's this farce for?
- This is no farce, Arav
It's our custom.
- I don't believe in such customs!
There are so many things
you don't believe in, Arav
But I do and so I observed
this fast for your happiness
If you really want to see me happy,
then sign these papers
what's wrong with me Arav?
Why don't you love me?
Why do you want me to
sign these divorce papers?
Because I don't love you!
I'm in love with Anna and Anna
is waiting for me in America
Till you don't give me a divorce,
I can't marry Anna...
so please set me free
from this relationship
Sign these papers!
"I have loved you so much..."
"but you do not love me anymore"
"I've had so much
of faith in you..."
"but no longer
do I trust you"
Divorce! That's a word not seven
generations of our lineage has even used!
And you want to divorce Kajal
because you love another girl!
You're out of your mind!
I didn't want to marry her
in the first place
You were the ones
who forced me into it
My son, if you end
this relationship...
our whole family will go to seed!
Mom, Kajal is just a friend to me.
I'm not in love with her!
Today you don't love Kajal,
tomorrow you won't love us!
You will leave all of us.
- Dad...
please don't get worked up.
It's a mutual decision
But what for?
- Because this relation...
has reached a point from where
it's going nowhere
Even if you wish to see me happy,
how can I be ever happy with a man...
who doesn't even love me?
"You are unfaithful..."
"I have learnt"
"where do you go away..."
"your gaze lowered?"
"May you be blessed..."
"with the joys you seek"
"Loneliness..."
"is all I have"
"wait for you,
I always did"
"wait for you..."
"I never will again"
"I have loved you so much..."
"I love you no more"
Parents must never force
their decisions on their children
One mistake of ours is responsible
for this situation
Please forgive us, my child.
Our mistake has ruined your life
No dad, you did it
only for my well-being
Maybe it wasn't in my destiny
My child!
Good bye
Aunty, are you leaving?
You will come back, won't you?
At least to meet me?
"How I implored you..."
"to be loyal to me"
"You are my own..."
"do not ever betray me,
do not ever cheat on me"
"For you, I could
lay down my life"
"Lay down my life for you...
I never will anymore"
"I trusted you implicitly..."
"Trust you, I do not anymore"
Isn't the lawyer there?
He's away for an important case
in Allahabad
Okay, the documents are signed
Ask him to complete the formalities
as soon as possible
Very well, sir
Hi babe, how've you been?
Hi sweetheart!
I'm missing you so much
I miss you too, baby
when are you coming back?
It's been so long
Is your work not over yet?
Did you get the papers signed?
Yes, I've got them signed,
now there's no problem
I'll be right there after Diwali
Now from where did this
Diwali spring between us?
This is my last Diwali in India and then
I'll celebrate all my Diwalis with you
All right, but you're coming here
straight to me. Okay?
Okay, I promise
I love you
I love you too, babes.
You take care. Bye
Mom, dad, let's light some lamps
and perform a prayer to the Goddess
A lamp won't bring any light with
our hearts so plunged in darkness
This was the last thing I expected
I thought this Diwali, all family
members would perform the prayers
But now I feel as if the Goddess
of wealth is annoyed with us
No daddy. The Goddess
can never be annoyed with us
Kajal!
- Sister-in-law
How are you?
- I'm fine, how have you been?
May you be happy, my child!
Kajal?
- Brother
How are you?
- Chintu!
Aunt has arrived!
Aunt is here!
It's Diwali night, so there
should be no darkness in the house
Come, sister-in-law.
Let's light some lamps
Kajal, you must have
left this house...
but not our hearts, my child
Very true, my child
You are no longer our daughter-in-law.
You are now our daughter
After ages I've seen smiling faces.
Thank you very much. Happy Diwali
I've forwarded the case, but these
formalities take time, Kajal
It's very important for me to get
this loan sanctioned as soon as possible
I can't promise you anything,
but I will definitely do my best
Thank you, sir
C'mon, Kajal. I'll drop you home
No, I'll wait for the bus.
- Please Kajal, come on
Kajal, can I ask you
for something as a friend?
What else do you want now?
Your anger is justified
But under the circumstances,
I know I have hurt you
That wasn't a good thing I did.
Please forgive me, if you can
when you look from a distance, the
two ends of a road appears to be one
But when the journey gets over,
you realize that they never ever met
Had we even lived together,
we would have never been happy
Can't you find a nice man
and settle down with him?
The end of a relationship
is not end of the world
But how about a girl for whom the whole
world revolved around one relationship?
Please stop the car.
I want to get down
No, I'll drop you home.
I need to talk to grandma as well
I haven't met her in a long time.
I don't know how I'll face her
Everything's just as it was earlier.
Nothing has changed...
when did this happen?
Six months after you left
Grandma passed away and
no one bothered to inform me?
Grandma told us not to
She knew that if you got to know,
you would come back...
and she didn't want to be
an obstacle in your success
And I... I was so obsessed with
achieving heights of success...
that I forgot my roots,
my identity
Grandma so badly wanted
to see my success
And now when the time has come,
she is no longer with us to see it
You have shared your grief with me,
but have you ever wondered...
what I went through?
I had no shoulder to cry on,
I was all alone
Arav, got some work with me?
Yes, actually I wanted you to
give cheque of $10,000 to Kajal
She needs it.
- Why should I give it to her?
You want to give it to her,
so do it yourself
$10,000 is 450,000 rupees.
Be honest.
Is it your first earning?
No, Kajal, it's...
- I don't want it
Kajal, please accept it.
For the sake of our friendship
You'll need it. I'll send you more,
should you need it in the future
Please keep this now.
- Okay, I'll keep it
But I wish to show you something
before I accept it. Come with me
which of these must I dispatch?
- Drop this one. Send the other one
Call for you, madam.
- Excuse me
Hi, Mr. Walker. How are you?
Yes, your consignment
is already on its way
It should reach you
the day after tomorrow.
The new orders? I'll check
my e-mail and get back to you
Thank you, sir. Okay
when did you learn to
speak such fluent English?
After you left, I had
to learn to keep up with you
Do you work here?
No, this is my partnership firm.
A & K Exports
You have a partner?
- Yes, a sleeping partner...
but despite repeated attempts,
he just doesn't sleep with me
Kaju, when did this all happen?
You've called me by that name
after so many years
Sorry, it just slipped out
After you left,
I had nothing to do
So I got together a few girls and
women and started this factory
Business flourished and
I applied for a bank loan
But grandma objected and
she gave me 500,000 rupees
where did grandma get
so much of money from?
She had some fixed deposits
in the post office
Fifty thousand rupees
in ourjoint account
And thus, it was A K Exports.
Arav and Kajal
Our last three years have generated
a profit of 570,000
Your share therefore works out
to 285,000 rupees
You want it in rupees or dollars?
Then why did you go to the bank
for a loan?
I have got a big order from Europe.
To execute it, I need 25 million
Could you come here, please?
- Sure. Excuse me
How we've lost track of time.
Will you have something to eat?
There used to be an eatery around,
remember? Famous for its parathas?
Yes, it's still there.
Remember how we used to run away
from our homes and come here to play?
And I used to take you
for a ride on my bicycle
And try to scare me as well.
- But you never got scared
That's because you were with me
Kajal, isn't this the place where
we had fallen from our bicycle?
You do remember everything
I can never forget
those moments Kajal
whenever it rains, I can
see us cycling on these tracks
You only remember the ride.
- No, what happened after that too
when lightening struck
we planted trees somewhere here, right?
- Yes
They must've withered away by now
Anything that's planted
in the rains never dies
There's your tree
I told you Arav,
I would never let them wither away
So this is my tree? And that one's yours?
- Yes, mine
They have grown, haven't they?
- Yes
Come here
Don't they look beautiful?
- Sure
Let's knock off some mangoes
Pass me a stone, will you?
You still have a good aim
Kajal, it's still
the magic of your kiss
Take off your sweater, you'll catch cold.
"Rainy days usher in..."
"days of reunion"
"The pitter-patter of raindrops
ignites fires of passion"
"How we have begun to falter in
our stride, we're indeed in a daze"
"These days of rains..."
"bring with them
times of a reunion"
"The night I so looked forward to
is here at last"
"I burnt in the flames of fantasy.
For years, I endured separation"
"But this magnificent cloudburst
has rekindled my passions"
"These days of rains..."
"bring with them
times of reunion"
"The night I
so looked forward to..."
"is here at last"
"Neither are you in your senses,
nor am I in my senses"
"I might yet stray...
steady me, please"
"Those are just my desires,
that's just my plea..."
"gather me in your arms tonight,
my love"
"Here are the days we
have felt for..."
"here are the days
when we meet again"
"The night I so badly
looked forward to..."
"is here at last"
"Youthfulness... it's crazy"
"A storm rages in their breath"
"Crazy... crazy moments"
"How desires seek to deceive"
"From my body billows a smoke..."
"let the clouds continue to pour"
"Pangs of separation,
I can take no longer..."
"how long am I to pine like this?"
"Days of love are here..."
"days of reunion are here"
"The night I so badly
looked forward to..."
"is here at last"
Arav, I am so very happy today!
Grandpa has decided that
we are coming to India...
and that's where our
wedding will take place
wedding?
We are flying out today.
I am dying to see you baby
I love you.
- I love you too. Bye
Arav, I am your elder brother
and I know you very well
You're feeling guilty for
having wronged Kajal
You feel sympathetic towards her
and nothing else
Sit down
I want to know just one thing.
You have left Kajal for Anna
But can you leave Anna for Kajal?
Never. Kajal is a friend,
but Anna is my love
There you go!
So where's the confusion?
You're right, brother.
I've already divorced Kajal
She's my past
and Anna is my future...
with whom I wish to spend
the rest of my life
Hi Anna.
- Hi baby!
How are you?
- I missed you so much
I missed you too
welcome, sir.
This is my elder brother, Dr Pranav
Hello.
- Hello
And this is Anna's grandfather
and this is Anna
Hello.
- Hello
Haven't your parents come?
- Ours is an orthodox family, sir
They will see the bride
at a proper ceremony
Anna, I wish to say something to you.
- What is it, Arav?
There is a difference between hiding a
truth and telling a lie, isn't it?
Yes, but why are you asking me?
Because I have hidden
the truth from you
I've a friend Kajal
Arav, is there any place
for me in your life?
Anna! For a moment I thought
I had lost you
For a moment,
even I misunderstood you
But then I realised that you had taken
the divorce for the sake of my love
Arav, you belong to me.
Only to me
I will always belong to you
Promise me that you will
never leave me again
I promise, I'll always be yours
Arav, shall I ask you something?
- Sure
I wish to meet Kajal. May I?
- Of course.
Arav, will you keep standing
or even introduce me to Kajal?
Oh sorry. Kajal, this is...
- Anna. Who else could it be?
Hello.
- Come, take a seat
How are you, Arav?
Anna, I got some work to do.
Have a chat with Kajal...
I'll join you later. Okay?
- Okay
Kajal...
- Yes?
Can I ask you a question?
- Sure, go ahead
You don't get the feeling that I have
snatched Arav from you, do you?
No, Anna. When he never really belonged
to me, how could you snatch him away?
Arav has shared neither his
sorrows norjoys with me
Our marriage wasn't a union of souls,
it was a compromise between two families
Arav never really loved me
Kajal, whenever a relationship breaks,
there's always a woman responsible for it
And I don't want to spend the rest
of my life with this feeling of guilt
I don't want to break your family
to build my own
I actually clung on to a relationship
that never really existed
Kajal, Arav told me
that you have a factory
Not a big factory like yours,
it's just a small set up
It's so nice to see
an independent young girl
It is very important
for a girl to be independent
Despite living in such a small city,
your ideas are so progressive
I am totally impressed.
It was really very nice meeting you
Friends now?
- Friends
I've no clue of Indian customs,
I've no idea how a bride dresses
will you help me, Kajal?
You've called me your friend.
And I'll definitely help a friend
I'll certainly help you Anna,
but on one condition
I want you to wear
my bridal jewellery
Arav, Kajal's going to help me dress.
- Yes, I heard that. Shall we go?
Bye, Kajal.
- Bye
Kajal, do you have any idea
what you are doing?
You are strangling your love
with your own hands
You won't be able to do it. You have
loved Arav more than yourself
It's going to kill you, Kajal.
Take my advise. Go away from here
How can I run away
from myself, sister-in-law?
Every tree, every leaf here
has been witness to my love
Every lane shares a bond
with my love
The clouds and the rains here have
culminated in my love, sister-in-Iove
And tomorrow, when I come back...
won't they ask me where I was,
when they saw my love being set afire?
No, sister-in-law
I will myself give my love
a decent funeral
"A thousand goals there will be..."
"a thousand caravans there will be..."
"your eyes will look for me..."
"but there's no saying
where I will be"
"My love, O my sweetheart..."
"I'm going dress your bride"
"I'm going to adorn your bride"
"The promise I made to you,
I will honour"
"I will keep my promise"
"Amidst the shadow
of the glittering stars..."
"may you be protected
from the evil eye"
"I'll give you all my love..."
"I'll dedicate my life to you"
"Although my eyes seem cheerful,
I weep at heart"
"when I take the blow..."
"Oh... how it hurts"
"My love, O my sweetheart..."
"I shall endure all the pain"
"I will dress your bride"
"I know it's difficult,
it's a moment of test"
"I will be shattered
in a moment..."
"I will transcend every limit"
"when I smile, she thinks
I'm in the habit of smiling"
"Blissfully ignorant,
little does she know..."
"this is my way
of hiding my grief"
"Oh my love, sweetheart..."
"I shall keep smiling like this"
"I will dress your bride,
O sweetheart"
"I will fulfill every promise
I've made to you"
"O sweetheart..."
"my dearest love"
Please stand up for the vows and take
the rounds of the sacred fire
This wedding is not happening!
This wedding can't take place!
Why can't it take place?
- Your divorce hasn't come through yet
what rubbish!
I myself got the papers signed
by Kajal and dropped them at your office
You got the papers signed by Kajal,
but you forgot to sign them yourself
You mean they are not divorced yet?
- No, not as of now
One moment, please
Mr. Lawyer, if he signs the papers right
now, then will the divorce be complete?
Of course it'll be complete.
What am I around for?
Does anyone here have a pen?
A pen, please
what nonsense! There are so many
people around and nobody has a pen?
Arav, even God doesn't want you
to sign these papers
Today I have realized
what true love is
Do you remember
the Chinese Temple?
What was written on that cookie,
"Today you will meet your destiny"
That was so true,
only we took time to understand it
Had I not come into your life, you
wouldn't ever have come to divorce Kajal
And you would never realised
how much you love her
I've only been a medium
to take you closer to Kajal
Kajal is your destiny
Do you really think you
forgot to sign these papers?
No, it was divine intervention
we often realize our mistakes
after losing our loved ones
You are lucky that Kajal
is still part of your life
Stop her.
Don't let her go away
Go on
Don't say a word.
Just go
Before I break down...
just please go away
No! He can't go away like that!
He can't do this to my child!
Let him go, grandpa.
His goal lies elsewhere
That I met Arav was
merely a coincidence
But it's not in my destiny
to have him for myself
He has betrayed you!
I'm going to ruin him!
You will do nothing
of the sort, grandpa!
Arav loves me very dearly. It's just
that he loves Kajal a bit more
I knew I'd find you here.
- Why have you come here?
I've come to ask you something
what?
Why did you sign the divorce papers?
- You were the one who forced me to
Couldn't you have turned me down?
- How could I? You don't even love me
who says I don't love you?
- You did
Forget what I said
Look at me
Tell me something, Kajal
who took you out cycling?
- You
who ate raw mangoes with you?
who spent hours with you in the rains?
- You
who haunted you in your dreams?
If I was the one who did all this,
I also loved you
I have walked out of my wedding altar
to come to you today!
Because I have realised...
I only love you, Kaju.
Only you
Now quickly give me a kiss.
- First you close your eyes
No. Today I won't shut my eyes.
I want to see how well you kiss