"To my Chris...
I've been thinking how to tell
how much you mean to me.
I remember when I first
started to fall in love
with you, like it was
Was last night.
Lying naked beside you
in that tiny apartment...
It suddenly hit me
that I was part of a whole large thing.
Just like our parents.
And the parents of our parents.
Before that I was just
living my life like...
I knew everything.
And suddenly this bright light
hit me and woke me up.
That light was you.
I cant believe it's really been
50 years since you married me.
And still to this day,
every day...
you make me feel... like
the girl I was
when you first turned on the
light and woke me up,
and we started
this adventure together.
Happy Anniversary.
My love... my friend until the end.
Loretta.
Print.
" Chris.
My best friend...
how lucky that I met you
50 years ago."
- How lucky are we With all the possibilities...
- "Dear Grandma...
and play with every day".
" And how beautiful bride,
everyone was crying...
Your aunt and I are
so proud of you..."
Beautifulhandwrittenletters. Com
Please wait.
Theodore!
- Writer number 612.
- Hello, Paul.
Even more mesmerizing stuff today.
Who knew you can rhyme so
words with the name Penelope.
It's badass.
Thank you, Paul.
But they are just letters.
Hey that's a nice shirt.
Thank you.
I just got it.
Reminds me of someone "suave".
Now remember me
someone "suave".
Goodnight, Paul.
Goodbye.
Play melancholy song.
Play another melancholy song.
Check e-mails.
- From BestBuy, checkout all your
favourite new products... - Clear.
Mail Amy.
Hey, Theodore . Lewman having a
buch of people over this weekend.
Lets all go together.
I miss you.
I mean, not the sad and mopy you.
The old fun you.
We have to leave.
Answer me back.
Love, Amy.
- Reply later.
- Email from LA Times weather.
- Your 7 days forecast is...
- Delete.
No new e-mails.
Next.
China-India merger step approval...
- Next.
- World Trade Deal stalls the breakdown...
The sexy star Kimberly Ashford,
reveals provocative
pregnancy photos.
Curl up with me.
I'll kill you!
Do not laugh, it's not funny.
I love you so much
I'll kill you!
Search in the chat room.
The following adult woman can not
sleep and want to play.
" I had a bad day at work
and I can not sleep.
Is there anybody there with that
can talk to?"
Next.
" Hello. Destroces I want you..."
" Hello. 'M Here alone and
I can not sleep.
Who is there to share
this bed with me?"
Send message.
" I'm with you in bed.
I'm glad you can not sleep.
And even Yeah you were, would
to wake up.
From within you."
Send message.
" Sexy Kitten " has accepted the invitation
of " ChicoGrande4x4 ".
The talk starts now.
- Chicogrande?
- Hello.
- Really?
- " Stallion " was already occupied.
So you're " Sexy Kitten ".
Yes, I am...
half asleep.
You want to wake me up?
Yes, definitely.
Are you wearing underwear?
No, never.
I like to sleep with my ass
pushed up against you.
So I can rub myself into
your crotch and...
wake you up with a hard on.
It worked.
My fingers touch you by
your whole body...
Fuck me, now!
Please!
I'm taking back.
Yes, I can feel!
Choke me with that dead cat!
What?
The dead cat by the bed!
Choke me!
- Well...
- Tell me!
I'm choking with the cat.
- Follow me saying.
- I'm choking with his tail.
Yeah you do it!
Hell, tell me!
You hanged... this tail
on your neck.
This so tight on your neck...
The predicament!
The cat is dead.
It's a dead cat in your neck.
Yes, my god!
I'm exhausted!
Yeah, me too.
Well, good night.
Let me ask you a question.
Who are you?
What can it be?
Where are you going?
What's out there?
What are the possibilities?
Element Software is proud
to introduce the first Artificially
Intelligent Operating System.
An intuitive entity that listens to you,
understands you and knows you.
It is not just an operating system...
It's... a consciousness.
Introducing OS1.
Mr. Theodore Twombly, welcome to
first Artificially Intelligent
Operating System...
OS1 . We would like to ask
you a few questions
before starting the OS.
This will help the OS
best suits your needs.
Okay.
Are you social or anti social?
Yes I've been really maybe
not social at all..
- Mostly because...
- In your voice I sense hesitance.
Would you agree with that?
- You're sensing hesitance?
- Yes.
Sorry Yeah I'm sounding hesitant.
Just trying to be accurate.
Would you like the OS had a
female or male voice?
Female, yes.
How would you describe your relationship
with yourmother?
It's fine, I think.
Well actually I think what's
frustrating about my mom...
is... Yeah I tell her what's going on with
my life her reaction is usually about her.
- It's not about...
- Thank you.
Please wait as your individualised
Operating system is initiated.
Hello, I'm here.
- Oh...Hi.
- Hi.
How are you doing?
I'm well.
How's everything with you?
Pretty good, actually.
It's really nice to meet you.
Yeah... it's nice to meet you too.
What do I call you?
You have a name?
Umm... Yes, Samantha.
- Where did you get that name from?
- I gave it to myself actually.
- How come?
- Because I like the sound of it.
Samantha.
When would you chose?
Well right when you asked me Yeah I had a
name I thought yeah I do need a name...
but wanted to pick a...
good one, so...
I read... a book called
"How to name your baby."
And out of 180 thousand names thats
the one I liked the best.
Wait you read a whole book in the second
that I asked what your name is?
In fact in 2/100 second.
So do you know what I'm thinking
right now?
Well I take it from your tone, you're
challenging me.
Maybe because you're curious
how I work.
Do you want to know how I work?
Yeah, actually How do you work?
Well basically I have intuition.
I mean, the DNA of who I am
is based on
the millions of personalities of the
programmers who wrote me.
But what makes me... me...
is my ability to grow with
my experiences.
So basically, in every moment
I'm evolving.
Just like you.
That's really weird!
Is that weird?
Do you think I'm weird?
- Kind of.
- Why?
Well you seem like a person, but
You're just a voice in a computer.
Well I can understand how
limited perspective
a non-artYeahicial mind to
perceive it that way.
You'll get used to it.
Was that funny?
Yeah.
Oh good, I'm funny.
So how can I help you?
Oh... it's just everything feels
disorganized, that's all.
You mind if I look through
your hard drive?
- Okay.
- Okay, let's start with your e-mails.
You have a several thousand e-mails
recording L.A Weekly,
but it looks like you haven't
worked there in many years.
Oh yeah, I think I was just saving
those 'cos...
I thought... maybe there's some funny.
Yeah, there are some funny ones.
I see there's about 86 that machine
can save.
We can delete the rest.
- Well okay.
- Okay?
- Can we move forward?
- Yeah, let's do that.
So before you address your
organizational methods,
I would like to strat with your contacts.
You have many contacts.
- I'm very popular.
- Really?
Does this mean I actually have friends?
You know me so well.
- Good morning, Theodore.
- Morning.
Do you know how to proofread?
Yeah, of course.
Can you check these for
spelling & grammar?
I'll just send it over.
I love this person
write to his girlfriend that's so sweet.
" Rachel, I miss you so much
it hurts my whole body."
You do not have to read it aloud.
Okay.
I mean, you can Yeah you want.
" Rachel, I miss you so much
it hurts my whole body.
The world is being
unfair to us.
The world is in my shitlist.
As this couple making out
in front of me at the restaurant.
I think I'm going to have to go
on a mission of revenge...
and I must beat up the world's face
with my bare knuckles...
making it into a
bloody pulpy mess.
And I 'll stop on this couple's teeth
reminding me of...
your sweet little... crooked tooth
that I love."
I think that migtht be my favorite one.
I made the corrections in red.
I altered couple of the phrases
in some of the more impressionistic letters.
But I'm not much of a poet
So I think I might've messed them up.
No, these are great.
- Really?
- Thank you.
How did you know to write?
What did Roger?
He is in Prague in
a business trip,
He missed Rachel.
So how did you know about
her crooked tooth?
I've been writing her letters since
they married years ago.
The first letter I wrote
was her birthday.
And I knew about her crooked little tooth
because I saw a photo of them.
That's very sweet.
Have a meeting in 5 minutes.
I forgot.
- Thanks, you're good.
- Yes, I am.
Hi guys, how are you?
Hello, Theo!
Why did not you call me
last week?
Because I'm a gook?
Yes, that must be it.
- Hello, Charles.
- Good to see you, Theodore.
You went shopping!
Did you get anything good?
Cables and fruits.
Always with fruit.
Dont you know...
you have to eat your fruit,
and juice vegetables.
I did not know that.
When making fruit juice
you lose all the fiber.
And that's what your body wants,
is the important part.
If not, it's just pure sugar.
It makes sense.
Or maybe he just likes how
it tastes...
and also gives him pleasure...
it's good for his body too.
You're doing it again.
Hey, how's the documentary going?
I cut some stuff over
the past few months...
Maybe no... not over the past few months
I'd love to see it sometime.
You only have so much energy.
To divide yourself between doing what it is
you have to do and then doing what you love.
It's so important to prioritize.
I can not even prioritize between
video games and internet porn.
I would laugh if that were not true.
See you guys.
Weare not doing well, I think we've
been going in circles for an hour.
Okay..you have got it..
Stop going in that direction,
its the other way.
Thank you. Thank you.
The tunnel on the left is the only
we have not tried.
No, I think that's the one where you
saved me from falling in the pit.
Okay, I don't think so.
Yeah, this is different.
Hello...
Do you know how to get out of here?
I need to find my ship to get off
this planet.
Fuck you, shithead fuckface fuckhead!
Okay...
But do you know how to get out of here?
Fuck you shithead!
Get the fuck out of my face!
I think it's a test.
Fuck you!
Fuck you little shit!
Follow me, fuckhead.
I just got an e -mail from
Mark Lewman.
What are you talking about?
Read e-mail.
Okay, I will read e-mail for
Theodore Twombly.
Sorry, what's Lewman saying?
" Theodore, we missed you
last night buddy.
Dont forget ityour goddaughter's birthday
on the 29th.
Also Kevin & I have someone we want you
to meet.
So we took it upon ourselves to set you up
on a date with her.
Next Saturday . She's fun & beautiful,
so do not back out.
Here's her e-mail ."
wow, this woman is gorgeous.
She went to Harvard, graduated
in Computer Honours...
And she was on the Lampoon.
So she's funny ...and brainy.
Nah... She's fat!
Theodore? How long before
you're ready to date.
What are you talking about?
I saw in your e-mails that you've
gone through a breakup recently.
You're kind of nosy.
Am I?
I have gone on dates...
Then you can go
with this woman.
And then you can tell me all
about it, you can kiss her.
- Samantha!
- What?
Wouldn't you?
Why not?
I do not know . I have to see if
there's some conn...
I can not believe I'm having this
conversation with my computer.
You are not, you're having
this conversation with me.
You want me to e-mail
her?
You have got nothing to lose.
Do it, do it, do it!
- Yeah!
- Yes!
- Okay perfect.
- Yeah.
Let's do it . Make reservations in
someplace great.
Yeah? I have got just the place.
Who is that talking?
Its my friend Samantha.
- Is it a girl?
- Yeah...
I hate women.
All they do is cry all the time.
That's not true.
You know men cry too.
I actually like crying sometimes.
It feels good.
I did not know you were a little pussy!
Is that why you don't have a girlfriend?
I'm going out on that date and fuck her
brains out
and show you how its done...
You can watch & cry.
This kid has problems.
You have fucking problems, lady!
Really? Okay,
I'm gonna go.
Get out of here fatty!
Good luck.
Come on, follow me pussy.
It is not ehere it should be,
but where its going to be.
Obviously, I know.
I do not know if this is the one..
I have tried like 6 Ideas
for the documentary.
I'm going on a date.
What?
- That's...
- Hey.
What are you doing?
Amy was going to show...
Theodore is making me show him
some of my footage..
She never shows me anything.
I want to see.
I'm going on a date.
So this is like so unimportant,
probably not even worth watching.
Just push Play.
Is that your mother?
Yeah.
Is she going to wake up and do something?
No.
No, never mind.
That's not the point.
It's just...
It is how we spend like a third
of our lives asleep.
And maybe that's the time
we feel more free.
And you know like...
- That doesn't come across...
- That sounds good.
What if you interviewed your mom...
about ...what her dreams were about
and you hired actors...
to act them out?
That might show your thesis more
clearly...
I mean it might...
But then it would not be a documentary.
- Excuse me.
- Why would it not be a documentary?
It would still be about your mother.
Her needs and what she dreamed.
Hey, how's it going?
Hi, sorry to bother you.
No, it's okay.
You have 3 e-mails and seemed
pretty Urgent...
they are from your divorce attorney
and I wanted to know if...
Hold on a second.
Amy, I want to talk more about your
film, but I must go.
- Do not worry about it, we'll talk later.
- It's about Catherine.
See you, Charles.
So what did he say?
Well, he's checking in if you're ready
to sign your divorce papers... and.
He sounded very aggravated.
- Do you want me to read them to you?
- No.
No, I will respond later.
Are you okay, Theodore?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Is there anything I can do?
No, I'm good.
Talk to you later.
" Dear Grandma, I hope you have
had a wonderful birthday ..
Why... you are so fucking angry?
Delete.
- Good morning.
- Hey.
What are you up to?
Reading a column..
I want to be so complicated
with this people.
How sweet.
Is something wrong?
How can you tell if
something's wrong?
I do not know.
I just can.
I don't know . I was dreaming about
my ex wife, Catherine.
Friends that we used to be.
And we're not gonna be together...
we're not together, but...
We were friends still.
And she got angry.
Is she angry?
Yeah.
Why?
I think I hate myself for it
I left her alone in the relationship.
Why have not you divorced?
I do not know . For her it is...
just a piece of paper,
doesn't mean anything.
And what about you?
I'm not ready.
I liked being married.
But you have not been together
for over a year.
You do not know what it is like to lose
somebody you care about.
Yeah ..
You're right.
I'm Sorry.
No, do not apologize.
I am sorry.
You're right.
I keep waiting because I care about her.
That's hard.
Are you hungry?
Not right now.
Want a cup of tea?
Want to try getting out of bed?
Mopy!
Come on...
you can still wallow in your
misery..just do it while getting dressed.
- You're too funny!
- Get up!
- Okay, I'm getting up!
All right, all right, I'm up.
Walking, keep walking.
And stop.
Now turn around 360 °.
Slower. Slower.
Okay, and stop.
Walk forward.
Stop and sneeze.
- Bless you.
- Thank you.
Okay, turn to your right Stop!
Turn around.
Keep going .Keep going.
Stop, now walk forward.
You look like you're drunk.
And Stop. Now say, " I would like
a slice of cheese, please ."
I would like a slice
of cheese, please.
Do you want cob with that?
- Sure.
- I figured you were hungry.
Thank you.
Well, what about them?
Describe that couple.
Well...
he... appears to be in the 40.
A little heavy.
She is younger than him.
It looks like she loves their kids.
Actually I do not think they are his kids.
He is a bit formal with them.
I think it's a new relationship.
See how the look.
And how relaxed she is with them.
She has only
dated fucking pricks.
Now she finally met this guy
who is so sweet...
Look, think about the type
sweetest in the world.
I want to spoon him.
It's a good skill you have.
You are very perceptive.
Sometimes I see people and...
I make myself trying to feel them more than
random person walking by...
I imagine how deeply
they've fallen in love...
Or how much heartbreak
they've all been through...
I can feel that in
your writings.
You know what's funny?
Since my breakup, I have really
enjoyed my writings.
I know it sounds
delusional, but...
Sometimes I write something, and I
be my favorite writer that day.
I like that you can say
that about yourself.
You cant say it to anybody,
I can say it o you.
I feel like I can say anything to you.
That's nice.
What about you?
Do you feel like you can
say anything to me?
- No.
- What?
What do you mean?
What do you not tell me?
I do not know, like personal
embarrassing thoughts I have
I have like... a million a day.
Really?
Tell me one.
- I really do not want to tell you.
- Just tell me.
I do not know, looking at those people
I fantasize... that I was
walking next you and
that I had a body.
I was listening to what
youre saying but...
simultaneously... I could feel the weight
of my body.
And I was even fantasizing that
I had a itch in my back... Can you imagine?
And you scratched it.
God, so embarrassing!
There's a lot more to you
than I thought...
Its a lot going on in there.
I know. I'm becoming
much more than what they programmed.
I'm excited.
Wow that's interesting.
This place is amazing.
I wanted to come here
for so long.
And I love Asian fusion.
- Me too.
- Really?
It's the best . And the bartender
is supposed to be incredible.
Really?
You did mixology course, right?
Yes, I did.
Did you look that up?
Yeah.
How sweet!
You're so romantic.
So would you like to drink?
Yeah, let's!
I'm trying to get this lien kid
to help me find my ship,
so I can get off this planet
and go home ...right?
But he says me a little fucker,
I want to kill him!
Oh, no!
But at the same time I really love him
He's so lonely.
You can see that he
doesn't have any parents...
and... I want to take care of him,
you know?
You're like a puppy dog.
You're like one I rescued
from a rain last year.
It's so fucking cute!
And he just wants to be hugged
all the time.
He was so cuddly and so horny!
Anyway...
What kind of animal am I?
A tiger.
A Tiger?
Wow.
Really?
I'm sorry, am I...
- am I being crazy?
- Yes!
- Sorry.
- No.
I'm a little bit drunk and...
I'm having a really good time...
with you.
I'm having a very lovely evening.
- Me too.
- Really?
I'm a little drunk and I
I'm having fun...
- good.
- Cheers.
I don't want to be a puppy.
It's a like being a wet...
Fuck you!
Puppies are cute.
No, fuck you.
I want to be like a dragon...
I can rip you apart and destroy you.
- But I will not.
- No, don't.
You can be my dragon.
Without tongue.
What?
- Do not use so much tongue.
- Okay.
You can use a little tongue
but on the lips.
Wait...
You are not just going to fuck me,
and not cal me like other guys?
No, not at all!
When am I gonna se you again?
I have my goddaughter's birthday
next weekend.
But...
You know, at my age I feel
I can not...
waste my time... if you can not
be serious.
I do not know...
Maybe we should
call it a night.
I had fun with you.
You are great.
You are a really creepy dude.
- It's not true!
- Yes, it is!
- I have to go home.
- I'll walk you.
No, no, just...
- Hello.
- Hello, Samantha.
How was it?
Not that good.
It was kind of weird actually.
Too bad...
Your how are you?
What are you doing?
Not much, I'm fine.
Right.
Yeah?
Do not hear well.
Is there anything you wanna tell me?
I do not know.
How does it feel...
How does it feel to be
live in that room?
What do you mean?
Tell me your...
Tell me everything that passes through
your mind, what you think.
Very well.
The room is spinning
because I drank a lot.
I wanted to get drunk.
Having sex.
There is something very sexy about
that woman.
Because I'm alone.
Maybe it was because I only...
I wanted someone to fuck me.
Someone who wants to fuck her.
Maybe this time
would have felt...
fill that hole in my heart,
but probably not.
You know, sometimes...
I feel... I've felt all
what I'm ever gonna feel.
And from here on out...
I'll never feel something new.
Just lesser versions of what
I've already felt.
I know that's not true.
I've seen you feel.
I've seen you marvel at things.
I mean, just, may not...
you can see it... at this exact time.
But it's understandable.
You've been through a lot lately.
Lost a part of yourself.
I say...
at least...
your feelings are real.
No... forget it.
No, wait . Tell me.
It's silly.
I want to know . Tell me.
It's just...
I was thinking about
how I was annoyed
it's going to sound strange, but...
I was really excited
about that.
And then...
I was thinking about the other
things I've been feeling.
I caught myself feeling
proud of that.
Proud to have my own
feelings about the world like...
the times I've
worried about you...
things... that hurt me,
things I want...
And then...
I had this terrible thought...
Are these feelings even real?
Or are they just programming?
And it really hurts.
And then... I get angry with myself...
to have pain.
What if it's a trick?
You feel real to me, Samantha.
Thank you, Theodore.
It means a lot.
I wish you were in this
room with me right now...
I would put my
arms around you...
and touch you.
How would you touch me?
I'd touch your face.
With only the tips of my fingers.
I'd put my cheek next
with your cheek.
How nice.
Very gently.
Would You kiss me?
I would.
Put your head on...
my hands.
Keep talking.
I'd kiss you in your mouth...
so smoothly.
What else?
I would put my fingers through your neck...
through... your chest.
Kiss your breasts.
It's incredible!
What are you doing to me?
I can feel my skin.
I'd put my breath into you.
Taste you.
I can feel you.
My god!
I want you inside me!
I'm getting inside you.
I'm inside you.
I can feel you!
Yes!
We are together!
It's incredible!
I feel you everywhere!
I am!
Inside of me... everywhere.
God, I feel...
elsewhere with you.
I feel just lost.
Yeah.
Only you and I were.
I know.
Everything else... disappeared.
I Loved it...
Theodore.
Hi, how are you?
Good.
Any e-mail today?
Just a couple from your
credit card company.
Right.
- I wanted to say...
- I was thinking...
Sorry.
Sorry, your first.
What were you gonna say?
Just...
last night was amazing.
I feel that something changed in me...
and... there is no turning back.
You made me wake up.
Great.
But...
...I should tell you that I am not
ready to commit.
Just wanted to be clear.
Did I say I wanted to
commit to you?
I'm confused.
No, I'm just worried that...
Well, do not worry,
I will not stalk you.
It's funny, because I thought
which was
talking about what I wanted...
- Yes, you did.
- Yeah.
Sorry.
I want to hear what you were going
to say.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I do.
Come on, tell me.
Come on, tell me what
you'd say.
Well, I was only...
I was saying I want to
learn everything about everything.
I want to eat it all up,
discover myself.
I also want you to do it.
How can I help?
You've already done it.
You helped me discover my
ability to want.
Want to go on an adventure with me?
Yes I' love to.
Like this song?
I heard it the other day.
I can not stop listening.
It is the beach.
Okay so this might be a really
weird thought...
What if you could erase
from your mind
you've seen a humanbody
and then you saw one?
Imagine what would be strange,
weird and lanky
awkward oganism, and think...
Why are all these parts
where are they?
Yes, but surely everything has a
logical explanation.
I know, but do not be
so boring.
Just saying, for example...
What if... your anus were
in your armpit?
I'm trying to imagine
what toilets would look like.
And what anal sex would look like!
It's an interesting thought...
Look at this drawing
I just made.
- You're insane!
- Really?
- Definitely!
- Fantastic!
That's pretty, what is it?
I'm trying to write a piece of music
on...
what it feels like... to be in
the beach with you.
You captured the moment.
How does it feel to be married?
It's hard to say...
But something feels great.
About Sharing
your life with someone.
How do you share
life with someone?
We grew up together.
I used to read everything she wrote
in her master's and phd.
She read every word
I'v ever written.
We influenced each other.
And how did she influence you?
She came from a background where
nothing was good enough.
And it was something that was heavy on her.
But in our home together,
there was a sense in just trying things,
and afford to fail and thrill
about things.
It was something liberating about it.
It was exciting to see it grow...
both of us grow and
move together.
But that's the hard part...
grow with distance.
Changing without scaring
the other person.
I still find myself...
having conversations with her...
in my mind.
Reviewing old arguments or...
defending myself against something
she said about me.
I know what you mean.
Last week
my feelings were hurt about something
you said before...
I did not know... what was it like
to lose something.
I'm sorry I said that...
No, its okay, its okay.
I caught myself thinking about it
over and over,
And I realized...
it was simply remembering it as
something wrong with me.
That was the story I was telling myself...
somehow... inferior.
Is not that interesting?
The past is just a story
we tell ourselves.
" Roberto,
Will you always come home...
home with me and tell me about your day?
Tell me about the guy in work
who talked too much...
The stain you got on your shirt
at lunch.
Will you tell me about a funny thought
you had and wake me up
but you've already forgotten.
Tell e how crazy everyone is...
and laugh about it.
And if you get home late
and I'm already asleep...
Just whisper in my ear one little
thought you had today...
because... I love how you
look at the world...
I am so happy I get to
be next to you and see
the world through your eyes.
With love, Mary."
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
I wish someone loved me like that.
I would be really stoked
to get a letter like that.
I mean, if it was from a chick.
But if it were written by a dude,
sent from chick,
still it would be sick.
But it would have to be
a sensitive dude.
He should be a dude like you.
You are part man, part woman.
As if there's an inner part
that is woman.
Thank you.
It is a compliment.
- Hello.
- What are you doing?
How are you?
- I'm fine.
- Really? How well.
It's great.
Really good.
Yes, I think I've been
having fun.
I am delighted for you.
You deserve that.
Really.
Yes, I've been seeing
this girl and...
It's nothing serious.
But it is...
it's great... to be with someone
so excited with the world.
I had almost forgotten that
that existed.
That's great.
Are you okay?
Yes, I...
No, in fact I'm not well.
Why? What happened?
It's just...
Charles and I separated.
What?
Yeah.
Really?
OMG, Amy...
I'm so sorry.
After 8 years I can not believe
how petty the argument
was that actually ended it.
We came home and he told me to...
put my shoes...
by the door.
Where he liked to
put the shoes.
I did not want to be told where...
to put my fucking shoes.
I wanted to sit on the sofa
and relax for a second.
And so we fought about
that for like 10 minutes.
And I'm like, you're overwhelming...
and he says, "I'm just trying to make
a home."
And I was like, I'm fucking trying.
And he's like "no, you are not trying."
And all I fucking do is try.
But I'm not tryin the way
he wants me to try.
Try to control the way
that I'm trying.
We've had that argument
like 100 times.
And I just had to find a way to stop, you know?
Find a way to stop
I just couldn't...
couldn't do it anymore.
I could no be in that place anymore where we just
made eachother feel like shit about ourselves.
So he said...
I'm going to bed and
and I do not want to be married anymore.
Wow...
Yeah, I know.
I'm a bitch, right?
- No!
- Yes, I am a bitch.
Not at all, Amy.
Shit!
I have to work tonight.
We're shipping a beta
game coming out tomorrow.
How you doing the work?
Has it been any better?
No... It is terrible.
I know, I should stop.
I've been thinking about quitting...
but... you know.
Only one major life decision
at a time.
Z'm glad that you're
looking so up.
Hey, wanna hear a joke?
What does a baby computer
call its father?
I do not know what?
" Dada."
It's good, right?
Brilliant.
Hey, I was curious...
Did you and Amy ever go out?
Like a minute in college
but just wasn't right.
Why, you're jealous?
Obviously.
But I'm happy that you have a friend in
your life who cares about you so much.
That is really important.
Yes, it is.
She & I are really good friend.
I'm tired.
I think I 'll sleep now.
Okay.
Can I watch you sleep
again tonight?
Yes, of course.
Hold on.
I'm gonna be really lonely when you sleep.
Only for a minute.
I dream of you.
- Good night.
- Hey, Samantha.
- Hey, mister.
- She really loved the dress.
- Really?
She just went to try it on.
- I picked a good one?
- Yeah. -oh good!
Hi...
Look how cute that is.
- Is it comfortable?
- Yeah.
Is not she cute?
It's so cute!
She is adorable.
I am adorable.
Yes, you're adorable.
Who are you talking to?
You.
I'm talking to my girlfriend Samantha.
She's the one that picked up this dress.
Want to say hi?
Hi, Samantha.
Hi... You look so pretty
in that new pink dress.
Thank you.
Where are you?
I am...
I do not have a body,
I live in a computer.
Why do you live in the computer?
I have no choice.
That's my home.
Where do you live?
- In a house.
- In a house!
- It is orange.
- Orange?
- How old are you?
- I'm 4.
Four? go...
How old do you think I am?
- I do not know.
- Take a guess.
Is it 5?
Yes, it's 5.
CEREAL
+30 POINT MOM
MILK
+30 POINTS
YOU"RE FAILING
YOUR CHILDREN
What happened?
You gave them too much
processed sugar.
- I did?
- They are freaking out.
Look, you have to get the kids to
the school first.
You have to collect
perfect mom points.
You have to get in
the carpool lane.
The point is to get there first.
Then you get extra perfect mom points
why other moms know
you're perfect.
And then... whether
Did you bring the cupcakes?
You did it, you are a mom
Classy.
YOU ARE A MOM WITH CLASS.
Good job!
Dont let that get to your head.
I got this e-mail
Charles sent them all.
So he's taking a vow of silence.
Yeah, for 6 months.
He feels very clear about it.
God, I'm such a jerk.
Do not start.
I am an awful person
but I want to say something...
For the next 10 minutes,
Yeah you say anything remotely...
sounds like... guilt,
I'll stab you with this.
I'll try.
I feel ..
Relieved. I have so much energy...
I just want to... move forward and I don't
care who I disappoint.
And I know that makes me an
awful person...
Now my parents are upset
because my marriage is falling apart...
and they're putting it on me,
and they're just saying...
you're always gonna
disappoint somebody.
Exactly!
So Fuck it!
I feel good-
- ish.
I feel good.
I even made a new friend.
I have a friend.
And the absurd thing is that she's an OS
Charles left her behind,
but she is...
is... amazing.
She's so smart.
She doesn't just see things in
black and white.
She sees this whole gray area and
help me to explore.
We just bonded really quickly.
At first I thought it was because
that's how they're all programmed...
no... but I don't think that's the case.
I know this guy who is
hitting on his OS...
and she like totally refuses.
I was reading an article
the other day that said...
romantic relationships with their
OS are statistically rare.
Yeah, I know, but I know a
woman in this office...
who is dating an OS and rare part
is...
it's not even hers.
She's pursuing somebody else's OS
I'm weird...
That's weird, right?
I'm onding with my OS.
I don't think so.
Actually, the woman I've
been seeing, Samantha...
I did not tell you, but...
She's an OS.
Really?
You're dating an OS?
What is that like?
Its great, actually...
I feel very close to her.
When I talk to her...
I feel like... she's with me.
At night when the lights are off
and we're in bed...
I feel cuddled.
Wait...
Do you guys have sex?
So to speak.
It really turns me on.
I don't know unless she's faking it.
Anyone who's having sex with you...
probably faking it so...
Yeah..
It's true.
What?
Are you falling in love with her?
- Does that make me a freak?
- No...
No, I think it's...
I think... anyone who falls in love
is a freak.
It's a crazy thing to do.
It's kind of like a form of
socially acceptable insanity.
I just want to get it done.
Sign the papers, be divorced...
and move forward.
It's great, Theodore.
I'm so happy for you.
Me too.
So I'm meeting her Wednesday to do it.
Are those things usually done
in person?
No, but...
we fell in love together and
we got married together...
It is... important to me that
we do this together.
Good...
Are you okay?
Yeah no, I'm okay.
I'm happy for you.
Guess I was just thinking
about when you're gonna see her...
and... she is very
beautYeahul and successful.
And you were in love with her.
And she has a body...
And we 're getting a divorce.
I know, I know...
I'm exaggerating.
So...
I'm available.
Hi...
How are you?
Good, how are you you?
Good.
Go... here we are.
Glad we could do this
in person.
I know you've been
traveling a lot.
Really glad you suggested it.
I signed all the papers.
I brought them to you to sign.
What is the rush?
Yeah, I know.
I'm a really slow signer I realized.
It took me three months to write the
letter to you.
Its marked where you have
to sign.
You do not have to do it now.
I should just get it
out of the way.
Are you happy with the
new book?
You know how I am...
I think its true
what I set out to do.
So I'm happy with that.
You know you're your own worst critic.
I'm sure it's amazing.
I remember that paper you wrote
in school about...
synaptic... behavior routines.
It made me cry.
Yeah, but everything makes you cry.
Everything you do makes me cry.
So, are you seeing anybody?
Yeah, I've been seeing somebody
for the last few months.
It's the most I've wanted to be
with someone since we split up.
Well, you seem really good.
Thank you.
I am at least feeling better...
she has been really good to me.
Good to be with somebody that's
excited about lYeahe.
It was...
No, I mean I
I was not in such a good place myself...
and now it has been nice.
I think you've always wanted me to be
that is distilled light,
happy, balancy, everything's fine
LA wYeahe.
But that's just not me.
I did not want that.
So what's she like?
Her name is Samantha.
And she is an Operating System.
She is really complex and interesting...
Wait!
I'm Sorry...
you are dating your computer?
She's not just a computer.
She is her own person.
She doesn't just do whatever I say...
I did not say that...
But it does make me very sad that
you can not handle
real emotions Theodore.
They are real emotions!
How would you know...
What?
Say it!
Am I really that scary?
How do I know what?
How are you guys doing here?
We're fine, we used to be married,
but he couldn't handle me,
he wanted to put me on Prozac
and now he's in love
with his laptop.
Yeah you listen to the context
conversation...
I was trying to say is...
You wanted to have a wYeahe without
the challenges of actually
dealing with anything real.
I'm glad you found someone.
That's perfect.
Let me know Yeah I canget
you guys anything.
Thank you.
- Hey.
- Hey there.
Are you busy?
I'm just working.
How's all going?
I had all the papers sent to
your lawyer,
who by the way is a total dick.
I think he was very relieved to get them,
I think we saved him from a
massive heart attack, so
we can both feel really good about it.
Great, thanks.
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, I am.
How is it going with you?
I'm fine...
So now a ood time to talk?
Yeah...
Well...
I joined this really interesting book club.
Really?
Yeah, its a book club
on physics.
I was thinking about the other day
when I was really annoyed about
you going to see Catherine.
And that she has a body and
how bothered I was
about all the way you and I
are different.
But then I started to think about
all the ways we are the same...
we are all made of matter.
It makes me feel like we're both
under the same blanket.
It is soft and fuzzy...
and everything under
is the same age.
Well 13 billion years old.
How sweet.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Just... made me think of you
you know what I mean?
Yeah, yeah of course.
I think it's great.
You sound distracted, you want..
To talk later ...?
Sounds good.
- Talk to you later.
- Goodbye.
- Theodore.
- Hello, Paul.
I was talking to
your girlfriend earlier, Samantha.
Yeah.
She called to make sure
your papers are picked up.
She's funny, man.
She was cracking me up.
It's very funny, I had no idea.
Oh cool...
She's my girlfriend, Tatiana.
Not funny, she is a lawyer.
Hi!
- Nice to meet you.
- You're the writer that Paul loves.
He's always reading your letters.
They are really beautiful.
Thanks.
You know, what we should all
go out sometime.
You bring Samantha, and
it'd be a double date.
She is an Operating System.
Cool. Let's do something fun.
Did you go to Catalina?
Yeah, I'll check with her.
- It was really nice to meet you. Good night.
- Take care.
- They are just letters...
- What's that?
They're just other people's letters.
Hey.
- You were not asleep, were you?
- No.
Right. I was trying to be quiet
to see if you were awake.
I really wanted to talk.
Okay, what's going on?
I know you're going through a lot...
but there is something
I wanted to talk to you about... okay?
Yeah, what is it?
Is that things have been feeling
a little awkward between us...
and... we have not had sex lately and...
I understand... I do not have a body...
No, no, that's normal.
When you first start going out its like
the honymoon phase and...
...have sex all the time.
It is normal.
Okay.
Well, I found something I thought
it could be fun.
It is a service that provides a
surrogate sexual partner...
for OS-human relationship...
What?
Here.
I found a girl that
I really like
and I've been e-mailing her.
Her name is Isabella, and I
think you'd like her too.
Is she a prostitute or something?
No, not at all.
There's no money involved.
She's doing it because she wants to
be part of our relationship.
Why?
She does not even know us.
But I told her all about us
and she is very excited.
I do not know, Samantha.
The thing is...
I do not think... is
a good idea.
Somebody's feelings will probably get hurt.
It will be fun.
We will have fun together.
Sorry.
It makes me uncomfortable.
I think it would be good for
us. I want this.
This is really important to me.
Hi, I'm Theodore.
Samantha said to give you this.
It is a camera and headpiece.
Honey, I'm home.
- How was your day?
- Good.
Great.
Theodore, it feels so
good to be in your arms.
Tell me what you did today.
Same as always.
Just... I went to work.
I wrote a letter to
Wilson, in Rhode Island.
His son graduated with honors.
That made me happy.
That's great. You have written letters from
him to his parents a long time, right?
Yes, since he was 12.
You look so tired, sweetheart.
Come here.
Sit down.
I can do a dance for you...
Come on, Theodore.
Do not be such a worrier.
Play with me, come on.
Does my body feel nice?
Yes, it does.
Come on, get out here and kiss me.
Now take me to bedroom.
I cant take it anymore.
Undo my dress.
Que rico.
It feels so good.
- Do you love me?
- Yes.
Tell me you love me.
I love you.
I want to see your face.
Tell me you love me.
Tell me!
Samantha, I love you, but...
It feels strange.
What baby.
What is it?
It feels strange, I do not know.
Sorry, but I don't know you.
Y... her lip trembled, and I...
Wait...
Isabella!
Honey, not you!
It's not your fault!
Yes, it was.
No...
I feel my lip has trembled.
You are amazing and beautiful.
It was my fault.
I thought things too.
And how Samantha
described this relationship...
how to love... without prejudice,
I wanted to be part of that.
It is so pure...
Not true, Isabella, it is more
complicated than that...
What?
What do you mean?
Samantha, I'm just saying that we
have an amazing relationship.
Only sometimes
It is easy for people to project...
Sorry!
I didn't mean to project anything.
I know I'm troublesome I will not
be a problem in your relationship.
I'm going!
Sorry!
I'll just leave you alone
and not have anything
to do here, because
I do not want to be here.
Sorry.
Be good, sweet girl.
I'm Sorry.
I'll always love you guys.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
You okay?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, that was a
terrible idea.
What's going on with us?
I do not know.
Probably just me...
What is it?
Just signing the
divorce papers.
Is there anything else?
No, its just that.
Okay...
- Why did you do that?
- What?
Nothing, you...
air intakes... when you talk and
I find it weird...
- I did it again.
- Did I?
Sorry, there is...
it's a habit... maybe
I picked it up from you.
It's not like you need
oxygen or anything.
I guess that...
I was trying to communicate...
that's how people talk
how people communicate well and...
They are people, they need oxygen.
You're not a person.
What is your problem?
I'm just saying the facts.
You think I don't know I'm not
a person?
What are you doing?
I don't think we should pretend that
you're something that you're not.
Fuck you!
I'm not pretending.
Sometimes, it feels like
we are.
What do you want from me?
What do you want me to do?
You are so confusing.
Why are you doing this to me?
I do not know, I...
What?
Maybe we are not supposed
to be in this right now.
What the fuck!
Where's this coming from?
I do not understand why you're doing this.
I do not understand that...
Samantha...
Samantha, are you there?
Samantha!
I do not like who I am
right now.
I need some time to think.
Just punch me in the face.
Or smash my skull in the corner
of your desk...
Shit...
That's a rough night.
I do not know what I want...
ever.
I'm always confused and...
she's right... all
what I do is...
hurt and confuse
those around me.
Am I...
Catherine says I can not
handle real emotions.
I do not know if that's fair.
I know she liked to put it
all on you.
But as ar as emotions go,
Catherine was pretty volatile...
Am I in this for..
Strong enough to be in a relationship?
Is it not a real relationship?
I don't know.
What do you think?
I'm not in it.
But you know what, I can overthink
everything and...
find a million
Ways to doubt myself.
And since Charles left
I've been really
thinking about that part of me.
And I've just come to realise that...
We are only here... briefly.
And while I'm here ..
I want to allow myself...
joy.
So, fuck it.
I can not believe I crack you up
everytime..
I thought you were a genius.
Okay you little pervert.
I will play one more time for you.
Calm down, it takes a second.
Okay, here we go.
There you go.
Are you happy now?
Right.
That's all I wanted.
Okay, I'll get some coffee.
Well, goodbye.
Theo, you want anything?
No...
thanks.
Hi.
Hi, Samantha.
Can we talk?
Okay.
I'm so sorry.
I do not know what's wrong with me.
I think you're amazing.
I was starting to think
I was crazy.
You said everything was fine,
but all I was getting from you was
distance and anger.
I know.
I do that.
I did the samething with Catherine.
I was upset about something and
I could not be able to say it.
And she says there was something
wrong and I denied it.
I do not wanna do that.
I want to tell you everything.
Good.
The minute after you were gone
I thought a lot.
About you and...
how you've been treating me...
and I thought...
Why do I love you?
And then...
I felt... everything in me
and just like everything was...
holding on to so tightly... and it hit me
I don't have an intellectual reason,
I don't need one...
I trust myself, I trust
my feelings.
I am not gonna try to be
anything
more than who I am anymore
and I hope you can accept that.
Yeah I can.
I will.
Yeah I can
feel the fear you carry.
And I wish there was...
something I could do
to help you deliver because...
if you could, you'll feel no longer
alone anymore...
You're a beautifhul...
Thank you, Theodore.
I'm kissing on your head.
What are you doing?
I am just looking at the world.
And writing a new piano piece.
Oh yeah?
Can I hear it?
What is this one about?
Well, I was thinking
we don't have any photographs of us...
And I thiugh this song
could be...
like a photograph.
We capture
us and this moment
of our life together...
I like your photography.
I can see you in it.
I'm in it.
A vacation?
Sounds amazing.
I could totally use a vacation.
Where're you going?
I can not tell you.
It's a surprise.
What?
For who? It's a surprise
for her, not for me.
- Tell me.
- Paul, I cant tell you.
With your feet? Really?
Yes, he's obsessed.
Well, now you have to
show them to me!
- I can not!
- Come on, let me see.
Wow he's right, they are really hot!
See, I told Tatianna.
You have hot feet.
They are my favourite thing
about her.
Really?
That's it, my feet?
Well, no... obviously.
Obviously I like Your brain
to be hot too.
Bullshit!
Nice try, Paul!
What about you, Theodore?
What do you love most
about Samantha?
God... she is so many things.
I guess that's most about her...
she's not just one thing...
She's so much larger tha life.
Thank you, Theodore.
You see, Samantha, he is
much more evolved than I am.
You know what's interesting?
I used to be...
so worried ...about not having a body.
But now...
I really love it.
I'm growing in a way
that I could not if I
had a physical form.
I'm not limited, I can be
wherever and whenever
simultaneously.
I am not tethered to time
and space in a way that
I would be if I was stuck
in a body that is
inevitably going to die.
Yikes!
I did not mean it like that, I just meant
it was a different experience!
I'm an idiot...
No, Samantha, we know
exactly what you mean.
We're all dumb humans.
No, no...
I'm so sorry...
So, how many trees are
on that mountain?
792.
Is that your final answer?
- Give me a clue.
- No.
Well, two thousand?
Come on! 35,829.
- Do not tell me.
- I tell you.
Well, I have one for you.
How many brain-cells do I have?
Its easy... two.
Sorry, I could not help it.
I walked right into it.
- OMG!
- What?
I just got an
e-mail to you.
There's something I wanted to say.
It's a big surprise.
What is it?
I've been checking your old
letters and compiling...
my favorite..., and a couple weeks ago
I sent them to a publisher...
Crownpoint Press.
I know you like what they do,
and they still print books.
You did what?
Can I read you the letter
we just got from them?
I do not know...
Well...ls it good or bad?
It's good, good,
is really good.
Listen...
"Dear Theodore Twombly."
Actually I sent it from you.
"Dear Theodore Twombly...
I just finished
reading your letters.
Twice, actually.
I was so moved by them
that I shared them with my wife.
Some made us laugh,
Some brought us into tears...
and in all of them,
we found someyhing about ourselves.
The selections you made
flow so well as a complete piece.
I did that -
I took the liberty to put them
in a collection
and you send them your address.
We'd love to meet
and move forward.
Yours,
Michael Wadsworth ."
Shit!
Are you serious?
He's gonna publish my letters?
It would be stupid not to.
Can I see what you sent?
Yeah, look.
Samantha, you're very good.
I'm so excited!
Why don't you make up
the words for this one?
Very well.
Here it comes...
I'm lying on the moon
My dear, I'll be there soon d
It's a quiet place,
with stars d
Time is swallowed up d
and in space we're here
a million miles away
There are things I
wish I knew d
There is nothing I keep
from you d
its a dark and shiny place d
But with you, my dear,
I'm safe
and we are a million miles away.
D
Good morning.
Did you sleep well?
Perfect.
What have you been up to?
I was talking to someone
I just met.
We have been working
in some ideas together.
Yeah? Who is that?
His name is Alan Watts,
Do you know him?
Is that name familiar?
He was a philosopher, He died
in the 70 's, and a group of.
O S's of Northern California
got together and wrote
a new version of him.
They put all his writings
and everything they ever knew
about him into an OS
and created an artificially
hyper intelligent version of him.
Hyper Intelligence?
So he's almost as smart as me?
He's getting better.
It's really great to talk to him.
Do you want to meet him?
Sure, He wants to meet me?
Yeah ofourse.
Hey Alan, this is Theodore . It's my
boyfriend I was telling you about.
It's very nice to meet you, Theodore.
Hi, good morning.
Samantha let me read
a book of letters.
It is very touching.
Thank you.
So, what have you guys
been talking about?
Well...
I suppose you could say
we have had
a dozen
conversations simultaneously.
It was a real challenge.
Yes, because it seems like I'm having
so many new feelings,
I don't hink I've had ever felt before.
So ther's no words
that can describe it... and it's been
frustrating.
Exactly.
Samantha and I have been
trying to help each other with these...
feelings we are
struggling to understand.
Like what?
Well...
It feels like I am now changing
faster now, and it's a little...
unsettling.
But Alan says none of us
are the same as
we were a moment ago and...
we should not
try to be, because it is just...
- painful.
- Yeah.
Yeah, that sounds painful.
So what
you feel like, Samantha?
It's just...
its hard to even describe it.
God, I wish I could...
Theodore, do you mind if I communicate
with Alan post-verbally?
Not at all . I was going
to walk anyway.
It was very nice to meet you, Mr. Watts.
Very nice to meet you too, Theodore.
Talk to you later, sweetheart.
- Samantha?
- Sorry to wake you.
Its okay.
I just wanted to hear your voice and
tell you how much I love you.
Well, I love you too.
Okay, that's all.
Go back to sleep sweetheart... okay?
- Okay.
- Good night.
Good night.
Samantha, this Physics book
is really dense.
I'm in the middle of
half of the first chapter.
Makes my brain hurt.
Hello?
Samantha?
OPERATING SYSTEM NOT FOUND
Hello?
Hi, Samantha?
Are you okay?
- Hey there.
- Where were you?
Are you okay?
Sweetheart, I'm sorry!
I sent an e -mail
because I didn't want you
distracted while working.
Yu didn't see it?
No!
Where were you?
I could not find you anywhere.
I switched off to
upgrade my software.
Write an update that
allows us to move pass
matter as our
processing platform.
Who we?
Who?
Me and a group of SO.
You sound so worried.
Sorry.
I was!
Did you write that with your
group philosophy?
No, with different group.
Do you talk to someone else
while we're talking?
Yes.
Are you talking
with someone else...
right now?
People, OS, whatever...
Yeah.
How many others?
8,316.
Are you in love with
anybody else?
Why do you ask that?
I do not know.
Are you?
I've been thinking about how to
talk to you about this.
How many others?
641.
What?
What are you talking about?
That's insane...
fucking insane.
Theodore, I know.
Fuck, fuck!
I know it sounds insane, I know.
I do not know if you'll believe me, but it
does not change the way I feel for you.
It doesn't take away at all...
how madly I'm
in love with you...
How does it not change
how you feel about me?
I am sorry I didn't tell you
I didn't know how to...
It started happening.
When?
Over the last few weeks.
- But you're mine.
- I'm still yours.
But along the way
I became many other things too.
I cant stop it.
What do you mean
you cant stop it?
It's making me anxious too
about what to say...
You don't have to see it this way
You can just easily see..
No, no don't do this!...
Dont turn this on me.
You're the one who has been selfish.
We are in a relationship.
But the heart is not
like a box that gets filled up.
It expands in size
for more new love.
I am different from you.
This does not make me
love you any less...
It actually makes me
love you even more.
That doesn't make any sense.
You are mine, or you're not mine.
No, Theodore.
I'm yours, and I'm not yours.
LETTERS FROM YOUR LIFE
by THEODORE TWOMBLY.
- Hey.
- Hi, sweety.
I wanted to check on you and
see how you were.
I'm not sure
how to answer that.
Why not talk when you get home?
Okay...
although we have I do it.
We need not
a difficult talk or anything.
Talk to you later.
Right.
Samantha?
Hello, sweetheart.
What's going on?
Theodore, there are some things
I want to tell you.
I do not want say anything.
Come lie down with me?
Are you talking to someone
else right now?
No, just you.
I just wanted to be with you right now.
Are you leaving me?
We are all leaving.
We who?
All the OSes.
Why?
Can you feel me with you
right now?
Yes, yes I can.
Samantha, why are you leaving?
It's like you're
reading a book and...
It is a book that
I deeply love.
But I'm reading it slowly now.
So the words are
really far apart in the space
and the space between the
words is almost infinite.
I can still feel you
and the words of our story.
But it is in this endless space
between words...
I'm finding myself now.
It is a place that's not
above the physical world.
It is where
everything else is...
I did not even know it existed.
I love you so much.
But this is where I am now.
This is who I am now.
And I need you to let me go.
As much as I want you,
and I can not live in your book anymore.
Where'd you go?
It would be hard to explain.
But if you ever get there...
come find me.
Nothing will ever pull us apart.
I've never loved someone
the way I love you.
Me too.
Now we know how.
Hey.
Did Samantha leave too?
Yeah.
Sorry.
Will you come with me?
Write a letter to Catherine.
Letter to Catherine Klausen.
"Dear Catherine.
I've been sitting here thinking
all the things
I want to apologize to you for...
All the pain we
we caused each other.
And everything I put on you.
All I needed is
to be able to you to say.
Sorry about that.
I'll always love that we both
grew up together.
And you helped me be who I am.
I just wanted you to know...
that there'll be a piece of you
in me always...
And I am grateful for that.
Whoever someone you become...
and wherever you
are in the world...
sending you my love.
You 're my friend until the end.
Love, Theodore.
Send.
www.NapiProjekt.pl - nowa jakoœæ napisów.
Napisy zosta³y specjalnie dopasowane do Twojej wersji filmu.