- Last place of employment?
- Denver, Colorado.
I worked there for ten years ...
but then things just dried up.
They lost 14 banks in one week.
There's nothing available for you,
right now.
They use their tongues to
deceive you. Venom is on their lips.
Their mouths are full
of bitterness and curses.
The fear of God
is not before their eyes.
They have taken
the hearts and minds of our leaders.
They have blinded us to the truth.
Our human spirit is corrupted.
Why do we worship greed?
Outside the limit of our sight
they're feeding off us.
Perched on top of us
from birth to death, are our owners.
They have us. They control us.
They are our masters.
Wake up.
They're all around you.
Sometimes when I watch TV
I stop being myself. I'm a star
I have my own talk show Or I'm
on the news getting out of a limo
All I ever have to do is be famous
People watch me
And they love me
I never grow old, and I never die
Excuse me,
do you need anybody?
- Maybe.
- I've got my own tools.
This is a union job.
May I please speak
with the shop steward, sir?
There's no sleeping on this site.
Sleep somewhere else tonight.
Excuse me, when do I get paid?
Thursday.
Do you need a place to stay?
There's a place over on 4th street.
They've got hot food and showers.
I don't like being followed
unless I know why.
I don't turn up with anybody
until I see where he's going.
They'll be serving food up soon.
This is Gilbert. Anything you need,
he knows where to find it.
- What's in the pack, tools?
- Yes, sir.
If you can use them,
you can fix the shower over there.
Let's get something to eat.
- More?
- Yeah.
I've got a wife and two kids
back in Detroit.
I haven't seen them in six months.
The steel mills were laying people off.
They finally went under.
We gave the steel companies a break.
They gave themselves pay raises.
The golden rule: He who has the gold
makes the rules.
If they close one more factory, we
should take a sledge to their foreign cars.
- You should have more patience.
- I'm all out.
The whole deal
is some kind of crazy game.
The name of the game is:
Make it through life.
Only everyone is out for themselves
and looking to do you in.
You do what you can, but I'm going
to do my best to blow your ass away.
- So how are you going to make it?
- My chance will come.
I believe in America.
I follow the rules.
Everybody has got
their own hard times, these days.
You thought press-on nails would
impede all the active things you do
We've got beautiful, natural-Iooking,
easy-to-apply nails
There's seven different colors
Our impulses are being redirected
We live in an artifiicially-induced
state of consciousness
Goddamn hacker. That's the second
time tonight that asshole has cut in.
The movement began eight months ago
by a group of scientists
They accidentally discovered
these signals being sent
That thing's giving me a headache.
It must have taken him months
to figure out how to do this.
The under-class is growing
Human rights are non-existent
In their repressive society, we
are their unwitting accomplices
Their intention to rule rests with
the annihilation of consciousness
We have been lulled into a trance
They have made us indifferent
We are focused
only on our own gain
They are safe
as long as they are not discovered
That is their method of survival
Keep us asleep Keep us selfiish
- Keep us sedated
- Blow it out of your ass.
- Choir practice was late last night.
- The church lets us use their kitchen.
- Till four in the morning?
- We care for a lot of people here.
The sleeping middle-class
is suddenly becoming poor
We are their cattle
We are being bred for slavery
- Not again.
- We cannot break their signal
The signal must be shut off
at the source
- I have a headache.
- Me too, honey.
- What was that all about?
- That idiot's licking his nuts again.
THEY LIVE WE SLEEP
There's nothing wrong with it.
Only a few seconds got on the air.
Forget about breaking their signal.
They justjam us out again.
- Put the shipment out on the street.
- It won't work. We've discussed this.
We have no other choice.
Robbing banks. Making our own lenses.
We just can't reach enough people.
We've got to find strong people
who'll work with us.
I'm just leaving. Your door was open.
I just thought I'd close it.
- Neighborhood watch.
- Let me touch your face.
Now your hands.
You're a working man.
The revolution ...
- Let me show you.
- Maybe some other time.
This world may have blinded me,
but the Lord let me see.
You'll be back.
I've been hearing stuff on the street.
Weird stuff.
An epidemic of violence
is what they're saying.
I was talking
to one old boy from San Anselmo.
He says up there they're talking
end-of-the-world kind of stuff.
- What are they doing?
- Shooting people, robbing banks.
A whole lot of people going crazy
over some nutty dream they just had.
The truth is, this kind of shit
happens at the end of every century.
It's just people
afraid to face the future.
What's happening?
I was inside there. It's full of boxes
and some kind of lab setup.
- What do you mean?
- The singing is a tape recording.
Leave it alone, man.
It's none of our business.
Gilbert is in there helping them.
I've got ajob now.
I just keep walking the white line.
I don't bother nobody. Nobody bothers
me. You should do the same.
The line in the middle of the road.
That's the worst place to drive.
- I'll see you later.
- See you later.
Step down. Easy. This way.
Now we cross the road.
It's dirt here.
Go, go!
Frank!
Leave us alone.
We know you.
''Though I walk through the valley of
the shadow of death, I fear no evil.''
- Come and join the party.
- You go with them.
Did somebody start WW III?
Oman's collection
puts passion before fashion
Out goes glitter
and in comes divine excess
The warm collection revels
in freedom of expression
OBEY
MARRY AND REPRODUCE
NO INDEPENDENT THOUGHT
CONSUME
BUY
OBEY
DO NOT QUESTION AUTHORITY
What's your problem?
How are you today, sir?
Thank you, sir.
Here you are, sir. Thank you.
Are you going to pay for that?
THIS IS YOUR GOD
I don't want no hassle.
Pay for it or put it back.
Sleep
She didn't even go to Lamas class.
I told her,
for yourself and the baby, go.
- Did you go to Mary Ellen's?
- She served tortillas! So dated!
- I'm so depressed. What do I do?
- Go for it, man.
That's easy for you to say,
you got the promotion.
The feeling is defiinitely there
It's a new morning in America
The old cynicism is gone
We have faith in our leaders
We're optimistic
as to what becomes of it all
It really boils down
to our ability to accept
- There are no limits
- I figured on something like this.
Excuse me.
You look like your head
fell in the cheese dip back in 1957.
You're okay.
This one, real fucking ugly.
I take these glasses off,
she looks like a regular person.
- I put them on, formaldehyde face.
- That's enough, or I call the cops.
The cops?
You need a Brazilian plastic surgeon.
I've got one that can see.
He's a tall, Caucasian male.
Unarmed, wearing sunglasses.
I don't like this one bit.
Not one bit.
That's like pouring perfume on a pig.
Settle down.
Where did you get those glasses?
- The tooth fairy.
- I'll bet.
- We've got him.
- Cut yourself shaving?
You look as shitty to us
as we do to you.
- Impossible.
- Don't make us splatter your brains.
You stumbled onto something here,
but maybe we can all benefit from it.
Let's go someplace quiet
so we can talk this over.
You bastards die just like we do.
I have come here to chew bubblegum
and kick ass.
And I'm all out of bubblegum.
Near the entrance. Has a shotgun.
White male. 30s. Long hair.
- Momma don't like tattletales.
- Wearing sunglasses.
And who are you?
Come to show them where I am.
Drop it.
Beat it.
Take it easy.
We're just going on a little ride.
Close the door.
Drive.
Not too fast.
They're gone.
- Just keep driving.
- Where am I going?
- Are you married?
- Yes.
- Please, don't lie to me.
- No.
Live alone?
- Your place.
- I'd rather not.
I'm afraid I must insist.
Hi, Holly!
- I don't know what you want.
- Just quiet.
It's like a drug. Wearing
these glasses makes you high ...
... but you come down hard.
- Things didn't turn out well today.
- You're not the only one.
I'm sorry,
but I needed you to get away.
You have two guns.
You're not sorry, you're in charge.
We're in trouble. They're everywhere.
You can see them with these glasses.
We're being controlled by these things
and we've got to stop them.
I'll do whatever you want,
just don't hurt me, please.
Listen to what I'm saying to you.
You're fighting the forces of evil ...
that can only be seen with sunglasses.
- Take a look.
- I'll wear your glasses, if you want.
If I don't see what you see,
I'm going to see it anyway.
- You have it your way.
- It's not my way ... It's your way.
- Don't fuck with me.
- I'm thirsty.
Go ahead.
I'm sorry I have to be here.
- So your name's Holly?
- Holly Thompson.
That's a pretty name.
What do you do?
Assistant program director. Cable 54.
A TV station? They're sending
signals out of TV sets.
No, I'm all right.
Holly Thompson.
8634 Circle View Drive.
Yes, I'll hold.
Frank?
- Don't let anybody see you.
- I've had a rough couple of days.
I want nothing to do with you.
How many people did you kill?
- They're not people.
- You crazy son-of-a-bitch.
You ain't showing me nothing.
I've got a wife and kids.
Leave me alone.
Get out of here.
No!
One week's pay.
It's the best I could do.
Wait!
You'd better find someplace to hide.
- Try these on.
- You crazy mother!
- Put these on.
- Stay away from me.
I'm trying to save you
and your family's life.
You can't even save yourself.
I'm giving you a choice. Put these on
or start eating that trash can.
- Not this year.
- Okay.
Come on.
I don't want to fight you.
Stop it.
Put on the glasses.
I told you
I didn't want to be involved.
Dirty motherfucker.
Take a look. Put them on.
No!
I'm sorry.
Put the glasses on. Put them on!
Fuck you!
Look! They're everywhere.
They can see us.
They're at 5th and Spring.
Hold on. You aren't the first one
to wake up out of a dream.
What's that?
Brother, life's a bitch ...
and she's back in heat.
I want a room.
Ain't love grand?
CONFORM
Don't wear those glasses too long.
It's like a knife in your skull.
- How long have they been there?
- Who knows?
- Where do they come from?
- They ain't from Cleveland.
I don't need that shit!
What are we going to do?
- Wait.
- Wait for what?
When you get your master plan,
you let me know.
If we can see, we've got to find
the people who made these.
Yeah, if any of them are still alive.
A long time ago,
things were different.
Daddy took me down to the river and
told me about the power and the glory.
I was saved.
He changed when I was little.
He turned mean.
I ran away when I was 13.
He tried to cut me once
with a big old razor.
He held it up against my throat.
I said: ''Daddy, please.''
He kept moving back and forth,
like he was sawing down a tree.
Maybe they've always been with us,
those things out there.
Maybe they love it,
seeing us hate each other.
Watching us kill each other off.
Feeding on our own cold hearts.
I've got news for him.
There's going to be hell to pay.
I ain't Daddy's little boy no more.
Frank?
There's a meeting tonight at 11.
Watch out no one follows you.
The world needs a wake-up call.
We're going to phone it in.
Hey brothers ...
There's something new going down.
They're using candyfloss packaging
to cover up a toxic waste dump.
Frank, glad you made it. Take your
glasses off. We're all human in here.
They're brand new.
We got the first shipment today.
They won't hurt.
There's less interference.
Go ahead.
- Any trouble getting here?
- No.
The city is crawling with cops.
Most of them are human.
They've been told we're Commies.
Some of them have been recruited.
- People are joining up with them?
- They sell out.
Promotions, bank accounts,
new houses, cars.
Perfect, isn't it?
We'll do anything to be rich.
Fluorocarbons have increased since
1958 Earth is being acclimatised
They are turning our atmosphere
into their atmosphere
- What do these things want?
- They're free-enterprisers.
The earth is just another developing
planet. Their third world.
deplete the planet,
move on to another
They want benign indifference
We could be pets or food
But all we really are is livestock
We need an assault unit.
Someone to hit them hard.
- You've got it.
- Ever seen their disappearing act?
Once.
- What's that?
- One of their watches.
Two-way radios.
You can listen to their broadcasts.
They've got secret code.
They push a button ...
All of a sudden they're gone.
I've been trying to figure it out.
Listen up. We're obviously
not getting to enough people.
There should be twice as many people
here. We're getting too sloppy.
Their detection
is becoming more effective.
Stay aware. Go to work.
Do what's expected of you.
We've become reckless.
The movement is suffering.
Stop talking about it. It's time
we started spilling some blood.
Wait a minute! We don't stand a chance
with a few guns and grenades.
- What are we supposed to do?
- We bide our time.
We locate their signal
and shut it off.
Dave works at KRDA.
He may have located the signal.
KRDA is clear.
The transmission is going out clean.
The signal is from somewhere else.
It's important to find out exactly
where this signal is coming from.
I've got to talk to someone.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
- I thought I'd killed you.
- I thought so, too.
I didn't know.
I'm so sorry.
I just want to ...
Can we ...?
Get out!
- They're killing everybody.
- I've got to find her.
There's nothing you can do out there.
If I can get this working,
I can listen in.
- Frank...
- What?
- Get set.
- Shit!
- What was that?
- I don't know.
Your wristwatch has malfunctioned.
This entryway will disappear ...
Move! Down there!
Seven seconds.
Six seconds.
Two seconds.
One second.
If you need assistance
in finding your destination, -
- bilingual instructions
are posted in each corridor.
- What language is that?
- I don't know.
- Where are we?
- I think we're under the city.
Some kind of underground base.
- There's got to be a way out.
- I hope nobody saw us drop in.
Operation Steelfist is a success.
We have eliminated the terrorists.
We got 'em!
We wiped 'em out!
It's a win, man.
They got to meet the A-Team.
I'm hearing something.
By the year 2025,
America and the entire planet -
- will be under the protection
of this power alliance.
The gains have been substantial for us
and for you, the human power-elite.
You have given us the resources
we need for our expansion.
In return, the per-capita income
of each of you has grown.
This year alone,
it's an average 39%.
I've received word that our forces
have won a major victory.
The underground terrorist network
has been destroyed.
The situation is normal again.
Hi boys, I didn't know
you'd been recruited.
You should have dressed
for the party now you can afford it.
I'm proud to be here.
Have you seen the whole place?
- I haven't had a chance to.
- I'll show you around.
I knew we had a lot in common
the first time we met.
- Where the hell are we?
- Backstage of the show.
This place serves its purpose.
Did you get here using one of these?
I know it's only for emergency,
but they're so much fun.
You think that's something,
take a look at this.
- Take a closer look.
- Attention, commuters
Flight Alpha 7 to Andromeda
is now ready
That's where they come from.
I don't know how it works.
It's a gravitational lens.
It puts a bend in the light and
you move from place to place.
The whole thing
works like one big airport.
They've got their act together,
believe you me.
Evening, boys. Looking sharp.
Wait till you see
what I'm going to show you now.
Here's the brains of the operation.
The signal goes out through
the satellite all over the world.
Pretty fancy.
I'm not too familiar with it.
This is as far as we go.
Can you get us inside? I've never
seen the inside of a TV studio.
- You look like the one to ask.
- I guess it wouldn't be a problem.
Those boys over there
are friends of mine.
My buddies would like the grand tour.
Can we go inside?
Be serious.
Do you have authorization cards?
Right here.
Watch the door.
- Soundproof. Where's that signal?
- Up on the roof.
- If Holly made it, she could help us.
- You're making a big mistake.
- We made the mistake?
- No, listen.
I thought you understood.
It's business, that's all it is.
You still don't get it.
There ain't no countries anymore.
They're running the whole show.
They own the whole planet.
They can do whatever they want.
We can have it good for a change.
If we help them, they'll leave us
alone to make some money.
You can have a taste of the good life.
It's what everybody wants.
- You'd do it to your own kind?
- What's the threat?
We all sell out every day,
might as well be on the winning team.
See you, boys.
Let's go.
Was that the two minute break?
We must be running long.
What the hell is going on?
Down!
- Now what?
- Find out where the hell we are.
Excuse me!
Do you know Holly Thompson?
Holly Thompson.
Assistant program ... something.
Security alert. Sections Delta
and X-ray report to the fourth floor.
Who's Holly?
Shit!
I hate to interrupt. Could you
tell me how to get to the roof?
- How do I get to the roof?
- Turn left at the end of the hall.
There's got to be more than one way
to get up there.
Security 950. They're on the move.
- I hear them on the 19th floor.
- We're on the 21st. We've got them.
Holly!
Come on!
Security alert.
Intruders heading for the roof.
Frank! Are you and Holly clear?
I'm clear, are you?
Don't do it.
Don't interfere. You can't win.
Drop your weapon.
Stand away from the dish
or we'll open fire.
- Come inside with me.
- You have ten seconds. Nine ...
Eight. Seven.
Six.
The Oscar winners
give a press conference
- Gloria, you look like shit
- What happened?
All the sex and violence on the
screen has gone too far for me
I'm fed up with it Film makers
have to show some restraint
What's wrong, baby?