The enemy is very cunning.
Where are Prince Aya
and Princess Kaurwaki?
Burn this village, burn everything...
either they'll come out or burn alive.
Where are Prince Aya
and Princess Kaurwaki?
No. Stop.
Stop, we are here.
Please let them be, I beg you.
Kaurwaki.
Good that I found you.
That woman, she said...
Where are Kaurwaki and Aya?
Bheema?
Where is Kaurwaki?
What happened, Bheema?
Bheema, where is Kaurwaki?
Bheema... I ask you,
Where is Kaurwaki?
Here's your 20th tactic.
What about the 19th one?
Speak up, friend. Your turn now.
No running off today? You've lost?
Get up.
You're not even worth a thrashing.
What's this? Lost your mind?
Let go of my hand. Let go.
Who are you people?
Let me go.
Wait.
- But Prince Asoka, he tried to...
- Spare him.
'Prince' Asoka?
- You'll stay here.
- Pawan is waiting for me.
His kind never return.
He will, Bheema. His horse is here.
How is the wound now, friend...
Prince?
Prince, my problem is that my fist
moves faster than my mind.
Why haven't you left?
How could I?
You saved my life.
It's my duty to guard you for life.
From now, in war and victory,
Virat will stand by you.
I want death not victory.
Was she beautiful, Prince?
Very.
- Are you going to Pawan?
- Yes.
I will come too.
You will not.
You will go to Kalinga with Bheema.
If I don't go, you don't either.
Should I call Bheema?
Call him.
Come on.
Lets take Pawan's horse with us too.
- How much longer?
- I don't know.
Asoka's winning war after war.
He seems undaunted by death.
Each victory is a step closer
to the throne.
You must stop him at Ujjaini itself.
Friend.
Do you know any Pawan? A soldier
in the Magadha Army, rides a horse.
No.
Let's go. It's raining.
Come.
No herb or medicine is helping him.
How does one save the life of a man
who has no desire to live?
Kaur... waki, Kaur... waki.
'Kaurwaki'?
- Prime Minister, where is Asoka?
- I don't know.
You don't?
Or are you hiding something?
Why all this loyalty to Asoka?
My loyalty is to the throne of Magadha.
Prince Asoka is getting better, isn't he?
Physical wounds will heal.
But wounds of the heart...
Haven't you seen how he calls out
her name even in his sleep?
Kaurwaki, Kaurwaki, Kaurwaki.
Are you crying?
You see, my heart is rather tender.
- Kaurwaki was very lovely?
- Yes.
But you are too. You too.
And you, most of all.
What kind of love is this
that lives on even after death?
When you left you did not look
back even once.
A bright glow
pervades
and fills
your eyes
Your eyes warn...
"Don't touch me"
Your dreams too...
are reflected
in your eyes
I've searched and searched for you...
In the sweep of the skies above
hoping to find you encased in a cloud
I have looked and looked for you
in every nook and corner
hoping to spy you walking
on a river bank
I held on to time
To ask where you are
I asked the river
and the vast ocean
I walked the crest of waves
feeling your caress
Stop. What are you doing?
I won't let you kill this harmless bird.
Move away.
Why?
It deserves to live as much as I do.
- Move!
- Release the arrow.
Devi...
Where were you, Devi?
The ceremony awaits you.
Come, dear, come here.
She's exquisite.
They make a lovely couple.
I met Prince Asoka today...
She's so shy.
She's quite spirited though.
He's become so vicious.
Everyone’s scared of him but not me.
Why whisper? Tell us too.
What do you think of our son?
Tell me, dear. Are you happy?
Congratulations, she has agreed.
- Asoka's in Ujjaini, badly wounded.
- Take advantage of this, Sugatra.
How? He is guarded on all sides.
It's impossible to break through.
Difficult but not impossible.
Here, take this medicine.
With this your fever will lessen
and you'll sleep well.
It's Devi's wedding today.
She won't be here.
Today, you will listen to me instead.
Drink it?
A little more?
I forgot to apply the herbal paste
on Prince Asoka's wounds.
Grandmother, I'll be back soon.
Make something for me as well.
Halt.
- What are you taking inside?
- Medicine.
Go in.
Pass me some water, please.
Who's there? Wait.
What are you feeding him?
Let go.
Friend?
Prince Asoka? Here?
How did this happen?
Come on let's go.
This wedding cannot be.
Where are you going?
Please don't go.
It's no fault of this child.
You've no right
to ruin her life like this.
I will not let you leave.
I request you to please wait.
If the Prince's request is a command,
we will not leave.
Poor Devi.
Who will marry her now?
You won't push me again,
will you?
My warrior.
Did she love you
as much as you love her?
I know that only Kaurwaki
lives in your heart.
I cannot take her place.
Please forgive me, Devi.
Why? There's so much love
in your heart. Maybe my destiny...
No. It's not love, only pain.
Love wounds in a way
that does not let you live or die.
If I had seen her just one last time.
Kaurwaki is right here with you,
in your heart.
But where was I
when she needed me?
I promised her...
that while I was there
she would come to no harm.
Where was I, Devi?
Where was I when she was dying?
Where, when she took Pawan's name
in her parting breath?
The intoxication
of our night together
Has not left me
The sensuousness of your body
is still entwined in my arms
I opened my eyes
but that didn't disturb my dream
Yes. I recall
Yes. I do
The dream which your lips gifted
me stays with each breath I take
Even in your absence
The thought of you excites me
When I turn over in my sleep
my dream just takes another hue
When the thought of you
enters my mind
those moments bubble
under a sheet of water
My body is on fire
Yes. I recall
Yes. I do...
The seasons that bind
you to me are countless
They contain promise
of several lifetimes
My sorrows are trivial
I wish for a long night
and a longer day
I wish for a life endless
enough to contain our togetherness
Yes, I recall
Yes, I do
The dream your lips have gifted
me lingers with each breath I take.
I am looking for Pawan,
a soldier in the Magadha Army.
Pawan? We don't know.
Ask her, she knows everything.
I too waited for a long time
for him but he never came back.
What kind of people are these?
Come on, let's go.
As per your wish, your highness.
We have served food to all.
Eat well, such a feast is rare.
Mother, look. She is Devi, the girl
that Prince Asoka has married.
Please serve to those there
and those too.
Have you heard? Prince Asoka
is returning to Magadha with Devi.
The stars predict tension
in their marriage.
You and your stars. They're married
so what tension could there be?
Here, eat sweetmeats.
- Why are you distributing sweets?
- His wife gave birth to a son.
But you have not been
home for more than a year, right?
- We were his emissaries in love.
- But...
No buts... give your sweets and go.
Long live Prince Asoka.
You're here to see
Prince Asoka as well?
No, I am looking for Pawan.
Look who's coming.
Let's go from here. Come Aya.
- I will not go.
- Enough of this madness.
- You have looked for him enough.
- I will not leave without Pawan.
Do as you please.
Look for your Pawan.
When you're done, return to Kalinga.
Prince Aya. Let's go.
I don't want to go.
Bheema, let go.
He acted as he thought appropriate.
Give him my blessings.
Your Majesty, at least meet him once.
There is no place for a Buddhist girl
in this family.
Tell Asoka to return to Ujjaini.
General. We feared that even you...
General, I promise you...
Whoever conspired to kill Prince Aya...
will be severely punished.
No need of that. Prince Aya
and Princess Kaurwaki are alive.
Impossible.
Aya...
This is not possible.
You have lost, Prime Minister.
Your conspiracy misfired.
A lie. I have served Kalinga all my life.
I am innocent.
Forgive me, Minister.
They've come to know.
Take him away.
Such a traitor should be sentenced
to death.
- Take him away.
- I am innocent.
Didn't I promise you that
we will be together in Kalinga?
Yes, only Pawan is not with us.
How much longer will you wait for him?
Till his return.
If he doesn't?
That could be.
But I'll still wait for him.
You knew I would not spare your life.
Even then, you joined hands
with Susima?
What's your life worth now?
Answer me?
What is it?
I must tell you something.
Go on.
Calm down first.
What is it?
A son? My son?
I will teach him everything.
Everything.
I will teach him to fight
with the sword.
I will teach him
to fight like a warrior.
My son.
The first heir to the Mauyan empire.
The Emperor of Magadha.
I will take him in my arms
and put him on the throne.
What if it is a daughter?
No. It will be a son.
Go and tell Susima, it will be a son,
the emperor of Magadha.
Wasn't it your dream
that I sit on the throne?
I give you my word
I will strive to be an able King.
You will be proud of your Susima.
Devi is expecting.
Susima, the word is out
that an heir is to be born.
- Asoka's son will occupy the throne.
- The people will never accept him.
- Am I right, pundit-ji?
- That's right.
A son born of a Buddhist mother
cannot claim the throne.
The people have no choice, Susima.
And you? You're incapable
of producing an heir.
It's destiny.
You tell me, Pundit-ji.
What fate awaits Asoka's child?
Think before you answer, pundit-ji.
Asoka's son will not live.
Destiny. It's all destiny.
Who is there?
There is someone here. Soldier.
- Everybody leave.
- Friend?
I said, everyone leave.
Leave.
Come.
Speak to me, Mother.
Please, Mother. Talk to me.
I did all that you asked me to.
Please, Mother, talk to me once.
Speak to me just once,
for just one moment.
If something happens to you,
all hell will break loose.
I will destroy everything.
Everything.
Vitasoka, tell Mother to talk to me.
Please, speak to me.
- Please don't.
- Don't stop me today.
Somebody has to stop.
- Anger destroys everything.
- Then let it.
I will never let you touch my child
with a killer's hands.
So, you've come to kill your brother?
Kill me.
Pick up the sword, Susima.
What about your mother's death?
Take your revenge, Asoka.
Why hesitate? Go ahead, kill me.
Pick up the sword, Susima.
Your mother was like my own.
I'd love your son as my own.
Only if you were not Asoka.
But you are Asoka. It's destiny.
Pick up the sword, Susima.
To help you defeat me?
I won't allow you that pleasure.
Let history note
that Asoka did not win the throne...
he had to kill to get it.
- Pick up the sword, Susima.
- No.
I was not a murderer, Asoka.
You left me with no choice.
Moment to moment I lived in fear
of your snatching the throne from me.
To sit on the throne
you must kill your own brother.
You will have to become 'Susima'.
Kill me, Asoka. Kill me.
You need courage to sit on the throne...
and also to kill your brother.
Kill me, Asoka.
I knew that you are incapable
of killing your siblings.
I know you cannot.
That's why the throne is mine,
not your's.
Destiny...
What should I do with the brothers?
Kill them all.
I have killed all my brothers, Susima.
Now can I sit on the throne?
Long live King Asoka.
What's the matter?
Why are you all so quiet?
There's nothing left to say.
Asoka killed all his brothers.
And no one said a word.
Who can say anything?
Even King Bindusara is no more.
Entire Magadha is terror-struck.
Strange.
Keep quiet, idiot.
Know what people are saying?
An evil man now rules over Magadha.
'Evil' Asoka.
You will not go anywhere, Devi.
You know I will not let you go.
- I am leaving.
- What was I to do?
They killed Mother.
I should forgive them?
Yes.
I don't have such a big heart.
I know. That's why I am leaving.
You are not leaving.
I am going.
You should know.
Where is Sugatra hiding?
He won't say anything.
He does not know.
Then his life is meaningless.
Friend, please stop. Enough.
Nothing will stop me now, Virat.
I will be the greatest emperor on earth.
Greater than King Bindusara,
stronger than Chandragupta Mauya.
The greatest, ever.
Susima said, "To rule an empire,
to be a great Emperor...
one needs to kill."
Please rest, Prince Sugatra.
Give the senate time to think about it.
My death is certain if Kalinga
does not grant me asylum.
I plead with the senate of Kalinga
to protect my life.
Kalinga has given asylum to Sugatra.
Why? Had they not heard my order?
They say Kalinga owes nothing
to a man who killed his brothers.
My relationship with Kalinga
is a strange one.
Till today no one has attacked Kalinga.
Kalinga is a democracy.
Your grandfather dreamt
of a united India.
Make that dream come true.
Attack Kalinga.
Kalinga.
We will always win.
Pawan's with the Magadha Army.
Will he too fight us?
- Pawan will never fight us.
- That's true.
Order me, Your Majesty. I'll make
them stare into the eyes of death.
Fear will render them useless.
They will forget patriotism.
What are you saying?
Friend, this is against the rules of war.
War has only one rule, Virat.
Victory.
We'll burn their houses,
destroy their fields.
I told your father. This village,
these homes, these people...
all belong to Emperor Asoka.
Which means all belong to me.
You too are mine.
Your father is very brave.
Such cruelty? Is he human
or a monster? Who is this Asoka?
- Why kill so many innocent people?
- He'll do anything to win the war.
- He has not spared his own brothers.
- Then he must die.
- I can take you to Asoka.
- Let's go.
Kalinga has attacked!
Look, there he is.
Sugatra?
Come, come, Sugatra.
You've missed your brothers so much
that you came to meet them?
You want to fight me?
One more time?
You won't face me?
All right then,
strike from behind.
Come Sugatra. Attack me!
Come, attack me.
You can kill me...
but you can never defeat Kalinga.
The Magadha flag will
tower over blood-stained Kalinga.
Give my greetings to Susima,
my loving brother.
What will become of us, now.
How will we fight this war?
This is not mere soil.
It is our ancestral heritage.
Nobody can take it from us.
Should we lose,
what will we tell our children?
Why should we lose?
Why should we not fight?
We will fight... together!
All my sons were killed in the war.
Had I one more, he would fight too.
She is my daughter.
Now she will fight.
- Every man in Kalinga will fight.
- Every woman in Kalinga will fight.
Yes, we will all fight!
You don't know him.
He will do anything to defeat Kalinga.
At any cost he wants victory.
Only victory.
My wish is that
when my child opens his eyes...
he should see only love not death.
The first words he hears
should be of love, not shrieks of pain.
Everything will be destroyed.
Everything.
- Where to, friend?
- A war awaits me. Have you forgotten?
Before that you have
to fight another war.
Really? Who is this new enemy?
The one who stands in front of you.
No. You are a friend, my only friend.
Then listen to your friend and stop.
Enough!
When will you stop killing
innocent people?
How much longer will you fight?
Till I win.
Till I win it all.
Then today you will not win over me.
One moment...
- You will kill your own friend?
- I will go to any length to stop you.
Remember, friend, the 19th tactic?
- Enough, Virat!
- No! Never.
You're alive...
because you are a friend
You are nobody's friend.
You are your own enemy.
That's why you are called
'Evil' Asoka!
Today we'll have a feast
in Kalinga.
But Emperor Asoka has
not come yet.
You don't need
elephants to crush ants.
Charge!
Come on, move back!
Follow them.
Cowards! Running away
from the battle field?
Pawan!
- We have lost the war.
- We cannot lose.
I will go and fight.
We cannot lose!
Please don't go, Prince.
Please stop.
What happened, Vitasoka?
You wanted to be a poet.
Then why this guise?
I know what you want to say.
The tormentor Asoka! Evil Asoka!
Is that what you want to tell me?
I have heard it all before.
I have come to tell you that
you have become a father.
My son!
Mahendra is your son and
Sanghamitra is your daughter.
Where is Devi, Vitasoka?
I am their father, Vitasoka.
You are only an Emperor.
Emperor Asoka.
Donning another garb does not
change the truth, Vitasoka.
War is the truth. Wars happen.
In war, you either win or die.
And I have won, Vitasoka!
I have won.
Yes, you have. You have won
the tears of widows...
the cries of orphans
and enflamed bodies.
You have won it all.
Vitasoka, I have won.
I have won, Vitasoka.
We've never collected so much wealth
in any other war, as this.
We've never killed so many people
The bigger the victory,
the more the wealth!
You have stumbled on a fortune,
such a beautiful and strong horse.
They say it belongs to 'Kaurwaki',
the one who inspired...
the farmers and women to fight
against Magadha's army.
Who cares?
The horse will fetch a handsome price.
Kaurwaki...
Water...
You have not won...
I'll never let you win.
Kaurwaki.
I am alive! You have to fight me.
Throw down your sword Kaurwaki,
the war is over.
The war is not over.
You have to kill me too.
How can I kill you?
I am your Pawan.
You are not my Pawan.
You are Asoka... Asoka!
Forgive me.
Why did you not come?
I waited so long...
Where did I not look for you?
I searched everywhere.
Pawan...
Aya!
Where were you?
Asoka took away all my land.
No one can take your land from you.
It is your's.
I have come back.
You will not go again?
No, never again
Promise me?
I promise.
See? I did not even cry.
Pawan? Did the prince return?
Yes... he did.
With horses and elephants?
With hundreds of horses
and elephants.
Then?
He took the princess
on his horse and rode away.
Then?
They lived together.
Happily?
Yes, very happily.
Pawan, it's getting dark.
The sun, moon and stars
are fading.
No, Aya...
nothing will happen.
Nothing will happen to you.
The sun, the moon, the stars...
are all yours.
Pawan...
I have become the greatest emperor.
The mightiest ruler.
I have won it all.
I have also destroyed it all.
What did I win?
What can Emperors win?
Only wealth, land and kingdoms.
My destiny transcends
an Emperor's.
My destiny will be that
of a traveler's...
who completes his journey.
And today I start my journey.
A journey of love, peace
and nonviolence.