Get up!
Kwai, go now, they are coming close!
I can't move! I can't!
We can't be caught by those bastards.
Let's go, they are after us.
Kwai...
Go now.
Ferry Station, Hong Kong
Are you Master Wong Fei-hong?
Yes, what's the matter?
A lady asked me to send you
this bunch of flowers.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Fei-hong, I can't come to see you off.
Because I am following an important news.
3 branch leaders of the "Boxer Association"
are wanted by HK Gov't.
It's really exciting.
I'm sorry, I'll come to visit you when I'm free.
Yours Aunt Yee.
3 tickets to Canton.
They're the wanted criminals.
Go and catch them.
Go!
Don't go!
Yuen Long, Yuen Fu, Yu Pao,
you bastards of the Boxer Association!
Surrender if you are wise!
You're surrounded.
The Boxer Association?
You bastards, do you want to arrest me?
You are dreaming!
Attack!
Leave us alone,
or I will kill this guy!
Be careful of my flowers!
You shut up!
We are civilized, don't be that rude.
So what?
So, I will counter attack!
- It's OK, hold the kid.
- Thank you.
- Who are you?
- Wong Fei-hong from Fu-shan.
Wong Fei-hong?
Let's go!
So what?
Let's beat him to death.
Yes!
Channeling?
Shit! I can't make it.
I am protected by God!
Go now.
My God, come and help me.
Please, The God of Monkeys,
come and help me.
Please, The God of Kwan
Please, The Prince Na Chai,
come and help me.
You are bluffing!
How dare you!
Master Wong,
thank you very much.
- Don't mention it.
- I am leaving.
Please.
- Take them away.
- Yes.
Go.
Wong Fei-hong,
the Boxer Association won't let you go.
Po Chi Lam Pharmacy
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8...
Why do you push me out?
12, 13, 14
You are look like a cripple.
- But you play like a cripple.
- Yes...
Stand properly.
"Single leg crane"!
Why did you kick me away?
This Po Chi Lam is rather small.
Relax.
It's OK.
Thank you, Master Wong.
Now, take this herb home,
drink the tea and you'll be alright.
Ah So.
What are you doing?
I just wanted to fetch a piece of water-melon.
But I was kicked back by the juniors.
Pal, why are you hurt like this?
I was fine before coming here.
But I was seriously hurt by your students.
Are you coming for medical treatment?
No.
But now, it is.
Fu.
Master, we don't mean it.
It's too small, you can't give treatment
when we are practising.
More and more students joined us.
Why don't we rent a bigger place?
I know it!
But the rental rate is high in Canton,
how can we afford it?
Master, if our patients are hurt by us
when they come for treatment, that's a pity!
You are so talkative!
So, you'd better give me some idea.
Master Wong, you'd move this time.
Who are you?
I am the representative of the landlord,
this is a letter of rent raising.
You needn't look at it,
3 times will be added to your original rent.
I don't think you can afford it,
you'd better move!
Watch the stance!
My cousin can be claimed as foreigner,
in fact a banana.
I'll teach you some English,
so you won't lose face.
Alright.
In morning, how do you greet others?
Good morning.
How to greet others at night?
What?
Good night.
How about in the afternoon?
Afternoon?
Good afternoon, I guess.
Good afternoon.
Just say sorry, if you bump into someone.
Sorry, sorry.
How impolite is the Cantonese.
What shall we do now, dad?
Let's find a place for a rest,
then find out where the monks are.
Let's go!
My dear cousin...!
Cousin Robert!
I am not your Robert.
Foreigner?!
Say hello!
Good morning.
- Good morning!
Hello Benjamin.
Hi, Robert.
He is Robert.
I'm sorry, Benjamin!
I'll call you later!
Bye bye.
Bye bye!
Cousin Robert.
Hi, my dear cousin.
He is my senior.
You come early.
You've told me
that many flats with low rent are available.
You must help me to rent any of it.
Oh! I'm busy.
What did he say?
I don't know.
It means busy.
Busy!
Many customers are waiting for me.
The electricity supply is always out of order,
it always...
See, it's out of order again.
Why don't you drink some brandy first.
I'll fix it and I'll come back later.
Take you time...
OK, bye bye.
It's imported wine.
It's called brandy, the taste is hot.
You know, someone only drinks a mouthful,
then he will be fainted.
I haven't tried it before.
How poor are you! What a shame!
You are poor!
I haven't tried it before.
- Do you want a try?
- Sure.
Come on.
I am really blind!
I can see nothing, am I fainting?
- What'll we do?
- No matter how, let's drink!
- Why not drink it all?
- It's great!
I beg you, leave some to me.
You are so greedy!
Come on, I beg you!
Ghost!
I am scared!
Drinking brandy will make one see ghost.
Ghost...
They beated me.
What's the matter?
Why are you so rude?
Shit, cousin.
You are shameless, heartless, you bastard!
Why did you hit my client?
He is human!
I mistook him as a ghost.
- Where did you get hurt?
- My heart!
Your heart?!
You hurt his heart.
My lung too.
Your lung?!
Oh, you hurt his lung.
What lung?
Lung, lung for breathing!
I don't know what you are talking indeed.
Oh, My God!
How can Wong Fei-hong's students
do whatever they like?
Are you from Po Chi Lam?
Sure! Don't you think we are the dogs of
Po Chi Lam?
So what?
I admire Master Wong very much,
may I know your name?
I am Wong Fei-hong...
Wong's student Leung Fu,
he is my junior Ah So.
How are you?
They are my sisters.
Ching Ha, Chow Hung and Man Yuk.
Your look is a little bit weird!
Yes, it's strange!
You are kidding.
Why don't you apologise now?
Say sorry!
Sorry! Sorry!
Mr. Wong, they want to find a new place
for Po Chi Lam's removal.
They want a spacious apartment.
You have a good place, right?
Yes, it's next to my shop, a spacious one.
About the rent, I will make it 70% less.
It's very kind of you to give us
such a low price!
I wish to learn Kung-fu from Master Wong.
If I can make it,
I will give you a commission equivalent to
3 months' rent.
Cut the crap, let's go now.
Mr. Wong.
You may call me Mass Tar Wong.
My surname is Wong, named Mass Tar.
Spell M-a-s-s T-a-r! Mass Tar Wong.
I admire you so much.
You are flattering me.
Are you satisfied with this house?
He likes it so much!
If the price is OK, I will move Po Chi Lam here.
If you think it's rather expensive,
I may lower the rent.
We may share the sacrificial pork
on the 2nd and 16th of the month.
We are running business together.
Oh, your flat is for business purpose too.
I wish to learn Kung-fu from you actually.
You are flattering me.
Hey, why not go for a drink?
It's my treat.
Lets go.
Our master promised his dad not to drink.
Sure, sure.
Let's make it a deal.
Fine.
- Fu.
- Yes
Fix the contract with Mr. Wong.
I've to greet the new military officer now,
excuse me.
See you.
Good bye.
You are welcome.
Who the hell is that military officer?
This way please.
Please.
Are there anyone practising Kung-fu inside?
Our Excellency wants to do some exercise.
Master Wong, after you.
Are you Master Wong?
I am Wong Fei-hong, how are you,
Your Excellency?
Give Master Wong the tea.
Sit down please.
I have just come here to take care of
the law and order of this place.
I know Master Wong is
the master of the local militia.
Your students are all geniuses of martial arts.
So I would like to meet you...
May be, I need your help in future.
You are flattering me.
Please be seated.
The Governor is taking opium now.
He will come out later.
I have heard that your Kung-fu
belongs to the school of Shaolin.
Your No-shadow Kick is really famous.
But, what sort of Fists do you play?
Kung's? Tiger and Crane?
Or Cross Fists?
Sir, you mean famous, it's being exaggerated.
Please don't misunderstand.
Master Wong, you are wrong.
It's a bad habit of keeping
your Kung-fu secretly.
You are naughty!
Master, is this officer an idiot?
Don't be big mouth.
Yes.
Thank you, Master Wong.
You are really great!
Your Excellency,
I am a doctor and know little Kung-fu.
How can I compare with you?
Master, he did it on purpose.
You are nosy.
Me?!
My Kung-fu is not great.
I can't make any muscle
after numerous practices.
But, I know one person,
whose Kung-fu is great.
Who is it?
He is a notorious robber,
he robbed and raped.
If he were not drunk that day...,
...we would not have caught him.
Kill me if you have guts!
Don't play any trick!
Why are you so fierce?
Master Wong is here.
It's not your turn to be fierce.
Wong Fei-hong?
Don't be misleaded by this Skinny!
He is protected by inner air.
He is hard to be killed...
Right? He didn't make a noise.
I want your life!
Help! Save me please.
Be careful!
Master Wong, please beat him for me.
Bravo, please kill him for me.
You bastard, I want to kill you.
What's the matter?
Nothing special, a prisoner escaped.
He is executed to death just now.
Master Wong, I am sorry!
I will buy you a drink one day.
I promised my dad not to drink.
Sir, I've to finish some personal matters first.
Good bye.
Thank you very much.
See you.
Wong is quite famous locally,
why did you fool him?
You needn't do so.
Such a proud guy!
I should show him a lesson,
otherwise, he will be our obstacle.
How can you let him...
to block your road to success?
Thank you everybody.
To be the chairman of "Moral Reform Society",
I don't think I am qualified to do so.
Fei-hong, you'd not be that humble.
In these days,
most of the youth forget morality.
It's hard to find a youth
with a righteous heart like you?
So we prepare this signboard to you,
"A humble and righteous symbol".
This is the present for your new school too.
Thank you very much.
Buddies, let's do some exercise to warm up.
So you will have perfect performance
in the coming lion dance show.
Hey, guys.
Miss, you have so many sisters!
She is our mother.
Auntie.
Be quiet, our master hates us being courted.
Are you that afraid of him?
Right, we just chat, isn't it sinful?
We haven't seen such dumb bell!
Master Wong, you have good students.
They are so smart.
Handsome.
With good spirits.
They are talkative too.
All are decent.
What are you doing?
We just chat with our neighbours.
Is he your master?
He is quite handsome.
Do you take females as students?
They dress so little and look bitchy.
You can tell they are not decent girls.
Stop chatting with them, got me?
He is blaming us.
Let's fool him.
Give me the drum.
- Good!
- You play the drum very well!
Don't see and don't listen to the indecent things.
My drum play is to remind you all these.
We know playing drum too.
We can sing!
Hi!
Get ready the lion.
Yes.
Isn't our neighbour shop opening today?
Why don't they have any ceremony?
Yes, no ceremony is held.
That's a female lion.
It's a bitchy lion! So bitchy!
Master, it's time to worship our ancestors.
Ah So, you take care of here,
I am going to worship the ancestors.
OK, I have got it.
Hey man, I want it.
Help yourself.
Congratulation!
Wish you all the best.
Thank you!
Master, there is a guest for you.
Aunt San, serve the guest.
Mister So, here you are!
Mass Tar Wong, you have recruited
so many female students.
It's hard to teach the girls Kung-fu.
Students?
I only know how to teach females.
I am not interested in teaching boys.
Mass Tar Wong, how humble are you!
No, I mean it, I will teach them
how to be good hookers!
What? A brothel?
Heung Chi Kun?
Damn!
Po Chi Lam is opened next to a brothel.
The ancestors will get angry too!
Master, shit!
- What?
- Yes.
Pick up the spirit tablets at once.
This is a brothel.
Ah Fu!
Ah So!
Master!
Mass Tar Wong, yours...
It is a high classed amusement night club.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
But you haven't asked me for details.
Ah So,
why didn't you inquire the details first?
I am sorry, I forgot to tell them.
I am sorry, I will move
right after I find another place.
Don't maybe, I won't take any rent,
let me provide catering, OK?
Master Wong...
Master...
You are losing my face, you know?
I will talk to you later!
What are you going to tell me?
I don't think you are so foolish.
Master Wong is so angry that,
please ask mercy for me later.
I do want him to take me as student!
Is he your friend?
No.
Who are you?
How can you talk like this?
Damn it.
You are not righteous!
I am not lucky to be Wong's student.
So, just forget it.
Mass Tar, is she a hooker too?
What's her price?
Damn you!
She is my God-sister.
Woo, she is beautiful!
Let me try first.
Miss, are you a student?
I am Ah So.
I am Ah Fu.
Are they your friends?
I don't know them at all.
Who are you?
Go!
How can you be so impolite, I wanna beat...
How can you beat your sister-in-law?
How do you know she will be your wife?
I don't know, I will discuss with
my little brother first.
Who is your little brother?
After drinking this nutritious medicine,
they can't hear.
The company which sell this medicine
refuses to be responsible.
So, we decided to report to the police.
But, it's not the most important thing!
First of all, to treat these kids first.
I will give them a treatment,
if it doesn't work, come back to me again.
The foreigners are aiming for money!
It's too bad to sell such harmful medicine!
The foreigners come a long way to China,
they just want
to earn large sum of money from us
What gentlemen, what democracy or freedom,
are all excuses for them to cheat money.
We have to strengthen ourselves,
so as to have better future.
Master Wong, we'd better leave now.
Please.
Hey, let's go.
They are deaf, they can't hear you.
Yes.
Let's go.
Please.
Ah So, Ah Fu!
I am coming.
- Master!
It's pay day.
Fu, you first.
Your salary is 8.5 taels.
After minus your lunch fee,
only 6 taels are left.
Thank you master.
Ah Fu, your clothes are getting old.
Take these 2 taels and by some new ones.
Thank you master.
How lucky!
My clothes are getting old too.
Ah So, your salary is 7.5 taels,
plus the cleaning fee, that is 4.3 taels,
you will get 11.8 taels,
I won't be that mean, why not round it up?
Make it 12 taels, OK?
OK, but you borrowed 7 taels from me.
And you cheated my money twice in buying food.
You have taken 13.8 taels already.
You owe me 2 taels.
It'd be 1.8 taels,
You said you are not mean!
I will lend you 2 taels.
Don't waste it.
Thank you, Master.
Don't go to the next door.
How can we afford to go there?
Ask all the juniors come in.
Here come the hens.
Go, go, make it the other day.
Hold it.
Master, please take it,
I come to join your Kung-fu teaching school.
I am not a good teacher,
so I dare not take you as student.
No, I wish to be your student!
If you take me as your student,
I will be responsible for all your expenses.
I am busy, I have no time to teach you Kung-fu.
Are you kidding? Listen to me.
Just teach me something,
I will be satisfied then.
In fact, I have learnt some Kung-fu.
Say, Tiger stance, Crane stance
and sissy stance!
I have learnt some of it.
You are that great,
it needs no further learning.
That's different, I want to improve myself.
Do you insist to listen the truth?
Yes...
I won't take a pimp to be a student.
You operate a brothel next to my school
and you didn't inform me.
You make me lose face!
If I take you as my student,
should I call you Mass Tar (Master)?
So, you are the master of Mass Tar!
Why don't you practise now?
Don't you allow me to piss?
Hope you won't come to our school again.
Master Wong.
Take back your hens.
They love hens, I guess, none is left.
I am sorry, I can't help.
Come and discuss later.
I charge 10 taels for that.
What are you talking?
Play the Tiger and Crane stance now.
Come
Coming...
What are you doing?
You will be killed,
if you play like this during fighting.
Master, won't be that bad next time.
I am not bad! But you!
Yes! It's fine.
Ah Fu
Yes
I am now going out, lock the door.
Master, isn't it necessary?
Why?
Do practise the Kung-fu.
No one should step out of here.
Don't go to the next door, got me?
Master, trust us, I will keep an eye on them.
You needn't lock the door.
I am not trusting you only!
I have been beaten by master for you all.
What are you going to appreciate for it?
Damn!
Stop sighing please!
I think, I am not that lucky enough
to be Wong's student.
We can stay for a while.
We have to leave soon.
Luckily I built a secret passage
between 2 houses.
It's for the convenient sake of the sugar daddies.
But our master is not a suggar daddy at all.
Otherwise, we will make him join us.
Shit, tell me which man is not fond of woman?
Right!
Our master is so decent!
I don't think so,
he hasn't met the one he loves, right?
Let Chor Hung and Miss Nine seduce him.
If he is not tempted, I will cut myself.
Which part will you cut?
My tits.
Save it for your sons.
If you want to bet, let's bet for 10 taels.
I don't think you can seduce my master.
He is not easily be tempted.
I won't give it a damn.
Do you have money?
You have, haven't you?
Me?
Just collect the debt tomorrow.
10 taels!
Hurry up. Work hard!
Please help!
Come and help, come on...
What are you looking?
Why do you hide a woman inside the box?
Are you abducting?
None of your business, go away.
Why are you fighting?
Sir, I am glad to see you here.
They hide a woman inside the box
and want to smuggle her away.
It's abduction!
- Really? Let me take a look.
- Yes
Fine.
Where is she?
Where has she gone?
Fu,
I know you always make trouble in the pier.
Since you are the student of Wong Fei-hong,
so you abuse his name to do bad deeds here!
Are you blackmailing them?
No, I didn't,
they did hide a woman inside the box.
Well,
why don't you open those boxes and check it.
Fu, you want to ruin other's property?
Are you a poor learner,
or is Wong Fei-hong a poor master?
I can defeat you by single hand!
- Take him away.
- Yes
Ask Wong Fei-hong,
see how he teach the students.
Where is Ah Fu?
He has gone to the pier for work.
Listen, I've been searching
a suitable treatment for the deaf kids.
But, I have none improvement.
This medicine is a serious poison.
It will hurt the hearing system
if you drink too much of it.
I want to drink some,
to feel the effect.
How can you choose such a stupid way to test.
If it poisons you, it'd be shit.
Limited quantity would be alright.
Pay attention to me.
If you find that I can't hear clearly,
remind me at once.
Yes, master.
Lock it properly.
He knows it is poisoned,
but he does want to drink it.
He may be losing his mind.
May be, he is lacking of something excited!
Say women!
That's why he has so many acnes on his face.
In fact, we give him two women, it's right.
We needn't feel guilty!
No guilty!
Hey, the women are coming.
- Yes.
- Hide up!
Master, 2 patients come to see you.
You know I never give treatment at noon.
Master, we come a long way here.
Please be merciful.
What's wrong with you?
Everyday, right at noon, and right at 4 a.m.
We feel itchy, from foot, and then to waist.
Then to the busts,
and to the head.
From head and then to the back.
And it goes downward, till...
There!
May I feel your pulse?
Fine.
Show me the wrist only.
I don't feel anything wrong about you.
But my heart beats quickly!
Me too,
why don't you listen to it, it's beating!
- Beating quickly, listen!
- What are you doing?
Listen to my heart beat!
There is difference between
Chinese and Western treatment.
Please dress up.
Master Wong.
Oh, they are the bitches from the next door.
I have to punish you.
I know what sickness you are having.
What is it?
Your blood stream doesn't go smoothly.
The joints go wrongly,
and the nerves are not in good order.
Really?
If you don't take treatment at once,
you may be cripple one day.
Kidding? How to get cured then?
Help! It hurts.
Please lower me down, please let us go.
Help, please let us go...
Are you feeling better?
Very good, we are fine, please let us go.
So long! I am dying!
No, we don't want treatment anymore.
Tell me, who instructed you to be here?
Don't!
If you don't tell me, I will...
Oh, you love hookers too!
I can't tell from your appearance.
Don't misunderstand.
They are patients.
Men always love women.
You shouldn't be shy.
Anyway, the brothel is right next to you.
It's convenient to call for hookers.
You...
Fu.
What's the matter?
He, he framed me.
Your students bullied others in the pier.
They didn't pay,
so he framed them to be kidnappers.
He beated others too.
But, it's lucky of him to meet me,
we are friends,
if only he didn't kill,
I would let him go.
Officer, if he committed any crimes,
I would not stop you punishing him.
A poor master, a poor student of course.
Master Wong, if you want to call
for hookers again, be careful.
I am leaving, so as not to stop you
from making fun.
Hey, what do you mean?
You know what I mean.
I won't see you to the door.
A humble and righteous symbol?
It's broken.
Why don't you leave now?
I am sorry, Master Wong.
Go.
I don't mean a mess.
Go, go now.
Ah So, did you call them here?
I, in fact, actually, not at all, may be,
there is a chance...
Fine, fine!
See! I have warned you!
Damn, he said fine!
What a big trouble!
Ah So is in trouble now.
He must be scolded by Master Wong.
Kidding, it's so noisy!
Master, how are you?
I am fine.
Fu, let's go and see the Kung-fu performance.
Dear friends, my daughter and I
visit here for the first time.
Our money is used up,
so we want to perform for some money.
Hope you're generous to pay for our performance.
Dad, you perform stabbing in the throat first.
Young Master.
Hey, girl, it's nothing special!
What do you want?
Why don't you perform stabbing the tits?
I will pay you 100 taels if you perform this.
Dad, forget about him.
Should I lend you my stick?
Damn you!
Help! Help!
Yin-er, it's enough.
Thank you for saving us.
You're welcome.
You are strangers, aren't you?
Right, we come from Shansi.
I am Wong Fei-hong,
you are Kung-fu masters,
why do you perform in street?
We're far from home,
in fact we don't wish to perform for money.
We are both inside the world of martial arts,
if you need money,
Master Wong, we perform only,
but we are no beggars.
Thank you anyway.
Well, I won't push you.
If you have any needs,
come to Po Chi Lam.
Thank you.
Dad, Master Wong is a kind hearted man,
why are you treating him that cool?
It's a world filled with traps,
you can't trust anybody easily.
By the way, we come to find your sister
and those perverted monks.
Don't involve in any other business.
Dad, look! Nun-yan Temple.
Let's go in and have a look.
Don't go!
Do you wanna go?
I will beat you to death.
How dare you escape?
Help!
Save me!
Nun-yan Temple is really suspicious!
Master, our Legate Officer from the
Holy Temple is long waiting.
Please forgive me.
Master Liu Hung, long time no see.
The Holy Master asked me to send
his regards to you.
I haven't seen him after I come to Canton.
How is his healthy?
He is fine.
But, the suppression from the government...,
...he is a little bit unhappy.
After the women are sold to South Asia,
we'll have much capital to use,
please ask Holy Master not to worry.
But 3 branch leaders of ours
are kept by the British in Hong Kong.
Really?
It's requested by the Ching Gov't,
we're going to save them.
Who is it?
Super Kick, be careful!
Go now!
- Dad!
- Go now! Hurry up!
Damn it, where have those wolves gone?
No business at all!
I have to buy some food
to worship the God tomorrow.
You lost, undress now.
We only have clients who won't pay!
I have to take a rest!
Po Chi Lam!
Which sugar daddy comes that late?
Who is it? No one appears!
What's the matter?
What a perverted wolf! He is so anxious!
Let me have a look! Here comes...
a woman!
She is the girl we saw in this afternoon.
Help her up.
No hurt can be told from her body.
But her organs are hurt.
Let me fetch her some pills.
Master Wong.
I want to see Master Wong.
I am Mass Tar Wong.
Not you,
I want to see Master Wong Fei-hong.
Right.
I am his student, Leung Fu.
Who beat you so seriously?
The perverted monks of Nun-yan Temple did it.
Nun-yan Temple?
Hey, please speak clearly.
Nun-yan Temple is a bad place,
the monks kidnapped the women.
And sell them to South Asia as hookers.
My younger sister has been caught by them
to Canton.
How do you know it?
I traced the clues and followed them
for 2 and a half years.
They are from a heresy.
They earn money from abduction.
My dad and I sneaked into Nun-yan Temple,
but we were hurt.
I don't know my dad is alive or not.
I have to tell Master now.
You are sick! It's a good chance,
we'd make good use of it.
- How?
- If we destroy the gang,
and make this an achievement of our Master,
Master will forgive us then.
You idiot! She is good in Kung-fu,
but she is seriously hurt!
If we go, we may be beaten to death.
We'd use our brain.
Call the cops at the right timing.
So they will be caught red-handed.
That's great!
Are there any traps inside the temple?
There is...
How can you come out to scare us
without any make-up?
We scared each once, let's break even.
Are we going to Nun-yan Temple now?
Are you afraid?
Sure, I am not good in Kung-fu.
If there is a fight, it means dangerous to me!
Cause you're not good in Kung-fu
and you don't seem to be powerful.
If you are as strong as Ah Fu,
the monks will suspect us, right?
That's right.
Don't show up.
Watch Miss Nine and her.
You will achieve this time.
My Master will take you as student after that,
trust me.
Well, I have to take this risk then.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
are you coming for worshipping?
Our young masters have heard
that it's good to beg for marriage here.
So they come to beg for marriage.
It's wise of you,
our God will give believers good marriage.
I want pissing.
Please take him for pissing.
Coming.
Miss, please.
I feel someone watching us.
Me too, it seems to be horrible.
Yes.
Don't scare me.
A bad luck mark.
If you want to beg for marriage,
stay here for one night.
Tonight at 12 a.m.,
the marriage star will enter your life.
After receiving the spirit of it,
you will get good marriage.
To stay one night here?
She is great!
Isn't it?
Damn it.
Miss Nine.
It's a trap!
Are you leaving?
I am coming to help.
Why are you so clumsy?!
Why did you push him away?
I am sorry, I will make it sharp next time.
One more, an easy one.
Hand this to me. You guy save the girls.
- Alright
- Give you a fist.
Ah Fu, Ah So, come out and serve the tea.
Please!
Where are the kids? They should be blamed.
Uncle Cheung, take a seat please.
Thank you.
Ah Fu, Ah So!
Master Wong, may be they have gone for a walk.
I have told them not to go out.
They love fooling around and fighting.
They may murder someone one day.
Master Wong!
I remember you, you are the one
who performed Kung-fu in the street.
Yes, Ah Fu and Ah So have gone to
Nun-yan Temple.
What?
Are you dying? Go to hell!
Shit!
What are you laughing? We are all tied.
We are civilized, let's forget fighting.
But peace!
I tell you, I will take revenge!
Let's stay in peace.
May I stop?
Why do you still hit me?
I have stopped!
What is it?
Arrest them.
Flying Tiger and Crane!
Master.
Wong Fei-hong.
Run for our lives!
Master...
Do you still treat me as your Master?
Miss Nine has been caught by them.
Where is Miss Nine?
Over the sacrificial stage.
Bring me there!
Where is the sacrificial stage?
Tell me.
It's over there.
Go.
What are you doing?
To save her from the trap.
You know it's a trap.
If three of us all go in,
once the door is shut, how can we get out?
You are right.
Stay here!
Yes.
Go!
Master Wong!
Wong Fei-hong, you offend our God.
Our God will punish you.
Why don't you kneel down?
You swindlers!
You misuse the God's name for abduction.
Wong Fei-hong, you are sinful!
I am now giving you a way out.
I will recruit you as student.
Confess now.
What? Let me send you to hell!
Shao Lin Fists?
We are from the same school,
so we are schoolmates.
How can you beat your schoolmates?
We are from the same school,
but you are a bad student.
Master Wong.
No-shadow Kick from Fu-shan.
Wong Fei-hong, you said it's No-shadow Kick.
Can't Wong Fei-hong tell lies?
Stupid!
No-shadow Kick from Fu-shan!
Wong Fei-hong, you are cocky,
I won't let you go.
You hate me telling lies,
you hate me telling truth too,
it's really difficult to serve you!
It's my turn.
This is for Miss Nine.
This is for Ah So.
This is for Beggar So.
Who is Beggar So?
I don't know who is Beggar So too.
I know I am a good boxer until now.
- Search every inch of it.
- Yes.
Your Excellency.
Master Wong, I am pleased that you are OK.
Dad, why does Wong Fei-hong
stay with the man who hurt us?
There must be something wrong.
- Let's go.
- Yes.
The monks are hooked with the government.
It's wise that we didn't trust Wong Fei-hong.
I think we'd better leave now.
Your Excellency, there are many women
kidnapped inside the temple.
Please send them home.
Women?
Are you kidding?
Those 2 perverted monks
have almost caught Miss Nine.
But the master of this temple
reported to the police station that,
he said that you came to mess up the temple.
What?
Please give us a fair trial.
It's a base of abduction,
how can he frame us of messing up?
You used to mess up in the pier,
therefore, I trust him more this time.
Master Wong, although we are friends,
but, it's my duty, I can't help you always.
You'd better ask those girls
who are kept inside the sacrificial stage.
Sir, there are only injured monks,
we have found no woman.
How dare you mess up the temple!
You hurt the monks and
ruin the reputation of the monks.
I know you are a great Kung-fu master,
but you should behave yourself!
Ah So, what did he say?
Are you kidding?
He shouted and he almost made me deaf!
Can you hear that?
Sir, Wong Fei-hong hurt 46 monks.
Most of them are seriously hurt.
Many may became cripple.
The temple is seriously damaged,
it needs to be repaired.
Please give us a fair trial.
My reputation is ruined by this rascal.
Hope you would help the innocent monks.
You hide so many dressless girls,
how dare you claim you're framed?
Yes, we went for worshipping,
A monk sneaked in and wanted to rape me.
Me too.
So, where are the women
and where are the monks?
Sir, the Nun-yan Temple is filled with traps
and they're heresy.
I saw the women being abducted
are kept in the temple.
So I have to self defend.
They have the freedom to worship their own god.
But you've no proof to say they are abductors.
Wong, I can't help you this time.
Master, he didn't help you.
Don't you think I am deaf?
Well, I decided,
defend Wong Fei-hong now.
No, how can we demonstrate
the lion dance tomorrow?
Master, they are framing you.
Shut up.
I would like to leave for a while,
all of you stay here.
- Sir.
You come to bail Wong Fei-hong?
Sir, 4 commercial associations
would like to bail Wong.
Hope you would let him go.
After the celebration, we'll investigate
this case and find out the truth.
If you think 4 associations are not enough,
we may ask Mr. Sasin, the manager of the
13 companies to bail him.
Are you threatening me with the British?
After careful consideration,
since Wong is bailed by
4 commercial associations,
and the case is really suspicious,
I decided to defend the master
and the monks of Nun-yan temple.
Wong is temporarily released.
I will investigate the case
and the final trial will be held later.
Sir, we are innocent.
Master, we can go for the lion dance tomorrow.
Bravo!
What's happened?
The men from the commercial association
come and help.
I don't think it's easy to frame him.
They want him to give lion dance!
Well, I'll make him lose face then.
Give the medicine to Wong Fei-hong.
So, let's forget those few hundred taels
which you owe me.
No, I can't do this.
No?
I will take you to prison then.
Thus you will suffer something more than death!
Hurry up...
Our pyramid lion dance will make them all eyes!
Have the tea please.
Why the tea is a little bit sour?
Really?
May be the tea leaves are expired,
I will ask Uncle Fok to buy some.
He must buy some cheap leaves!
Well, Mr. Wong Fei-hong
gives the puppet a real life.
It looks like a real lion!
What? You said he is a liar?
No, a real lion!
He said Wong is a liar!
What'll we do now?
It's a big day today, don't arrest Wong
although he is a liar.
I think so.
Lions pyramid!
Forward!
Bravo! You're great!
- On the shoulders.
- Yes.
Wonderful!
Oh, cockroaches!
Be careful!
It's so tricky!
Are you kidding!
Moving of centipede.
Swing!
Master, the centipede is really tricky.
Centipede dance is some hex from the North.
It's very dangerous, you'd be careful.
Kidding!
Get the bait.
Bravo!
Watch the kick!
Why can't master follow the beat of the drum?
Let me do it!
Step back!
Watch my stance.
What are you doing? Stop!
Congratulations!
The centipede can start the fire!
Master, you'd think something to defeat
the centipede.
Make use of this chance to teach him a lesson.
Cut the crap, let's fight one by one.
Master Wong, don't go.
So what?
The master of Nun-yan Temple,
has just committed suicide in the prison.
It'll arouse bad feeling from the public
if the news is announced.
Master Wong, you'd discuss it
with the government.
Your Excellency.
I can't hear what you are talking about.
I am deaf.
They are coming out.
Please.
I have come to a conclusion with Master Wong.
He has a problem of hearing,
so I will announce it to you now.
Since Master Wong is the coach
of the local militia,
if we charge him destroying the temple
and killing the master,
it'll bring all of us a difficult problem
in handling the case with justice.
So Master Wong'll leave here for a while.
He'll go back to Fu-shan.
Po Chi Lam will be attached by the government.
No one should enter.
You are lying!
Master won't leave Po Chi Lam.
- Shut up.
- That is our home.
Listen to me.
I have decided.
I can't hear what you are talking, but...
I hope you will remember
what I am going to talk.
Master...
Master Wong!
His Excellency tells the truth.
Master!
Damn you bastard,
how dare you attach Po Chi Lam!
I will sue you with all my best.
I forgot to tell you,
you operate the indecent nightclub,
we have got proof,
the government is going to
attach your business too.
From tomorrow onwards, no business!
I don't think you can make a dead set at me.
Let's wait and see.
Master Wong, I am busy, see you.
You will be busy,
Busy for your family's funerals.
Ah So, pack some clothes for me.
I am leaving.
I don't want to drag you down.
The government wants to go against me only.
We are not capable to fight with them.
Let's wait a better chance for counter attack.
I will go back to Fu-shan to cure my ears.
Stay here, don't do anything impulsively.
I am sorry, Master.
You are a man, don't cry.
He cries too.
It's different,
he can't be counted as man.
What am I then?
Master.
Fu, don't argue with anyone in the pier.
You'd take care of your buddies.
Yes.
Master.
Take care!
Anybody here?
Miss Ti, it's me, Wong Fei-hong.
You are shameless.
Miss Ti, I can't hear you.
Are you still acting?
Dad.
Don't get mad.
He hooks with the bastard officials,
there must be trap.
Master Wong, we have left Canton.
Would you let us go?
I... I can't hear what you are talking about.
I am deaf.
He mistook the medicine, so he becomes deaf.
Are there any tricks?
His pulse is abnormal,
it is the symptom of being poisoned.
I have treated some patients
who got blind and deaf in Shansi.
Let's take research, hope it would cure you.
I have thought some possible solutions too.
But, it's hard for a doctor to cure himself.
If you can help, that's good.
My solution, "3 needles shooting",
it's difficult to do it myself.
To stab 3 needles into the body
at the same time.
So I need your help.
Come and buy duster! It's cheap.
Fat hens!
It's cheap!
How much does the hen cost? Mr. Pimp.
Don't call me Mr. Pimp,
I'm Mass Tar Wong.
30% off if you call me Mass Tar Wong.
Idiot
You are insane.
If you scold me, I will beat you.
Brother, we'd better not to quarrel with them.
No matter how, I am a famous pimp.
Mr. Pimp.
Damn you!
How dare you beat the officers?
Are you looking for trouble?
I don't know it's you.
Don't sell right here! Get lost.
What do you mean?
You always give us trouble.
You just forbid us to sell here!
What do you mean?
Cause you offend Mr. Lui,
he instructed me to give you hard time.
If you don't go, I will beat you.
I am scared! What is law and order?
If you dare hitting me right here,
I will eat up all feathers.
Don't quarrel with him.
What'll we do now?
Hi, you look poor!
I come a long way to search for you.
Lui Yat Siu wants to make a dead set as us,
so we can't earn a living in Canton.
I have found a job in a brothel of Hong Kong,
you are the No.1 pimp,
why don't you start your career in HK?
But we don't have the travelling expense.
I earned hardly for limited travelling expense.
So I can't help you two.
If you can get some money, come to me,
let's go together to HK.
What'll we do?
Nothing can do, we have no money!
Hey, I've some golds hidden in Heung Chi Kun.
Come on...
It would be shit if we are discovered.
It's dark here, no one would discover us.
When this house was under construction,
the Fung-shui master told me
to hide gold under the poles.
There are 10 taels of gold hidden.
Once get it, we'll have enough money
to go to Hong Kong, come on.
Will it be taken by the workers
who did the decoration?
What a big mouth!
Here is the pole.
Where is she going?
I thought I have killed her,
but she disappeared.
Master would punish us if he knows it.
- Search now.
- OK.
- Will she run to the street?
- Let's go out and have a look.
Don't make any noise,
or we'd be in deep shit.
Sorry.
Many girls... are kept next door.
Go and save them.
They will be shipped...
...to South Asia...
Those bastards lock the girls in Po Chi Lam.
Go and save them...
- How are you?
Stay here, I would take a look.
Don't!
It doesn't matter, if she tells the truth,
I would sue them.
No! Don't go!
Wake up.
Master Liu Hung,
Wong's students could do nothing now.
But I have found that,
Wong didn't go back to Fu-shan.
He hides up in a village near by,
staying with the Kung-fu performers.
3 days later, the 13 companies will hold
the stone-laying ceremony.
We have to kidnap their manager Sasin.
Will Wong Fei-hong bother us?
In order to be safe,
I have sent someone to kill him.
He is deaf, he can't escape.
That's good. Wong caught 3 branch
leaders of us for Ching Gov't.
We have to kidnap Sasin.
So the British will give Ching Gov't pressure
to release our buddies.
Don't worry,
the Express Dowager is paying attention to us.
We will be treasured by her one day.
So we will have great power
and control the whole country.
Be careful not to disclose your real identity.
Who knows it, will be killed.
Who is it?
It's you, Mr. Pimp.
You attached Po Chi Lam and Heung Chi Kun
to keep girls!
You bloody bastard!
Bloody bastard?
You have heard our talk? Haven't you?
Master Wong would punish you two.
Bastards!
He is too nosy! Damn Wong Fei-hong,
he caught our buddies.
So we should go against him.
Are you coming to challenge me?
Say Wong is a bastard,
then I will let you alive.
OK, I say. Wong Fei-hong is a hero.
Say, Wong Fei-hong is a bastard wolf.
Long life to Wong Fei-hong.
Say?
Say, Wong is shameless.
Wong is your dad.
Don't you scare death?
He is nothing worth,
but don't bother the neighbours.
Fong, Yuen.
Dig a hole and bury him.
- Yes.
Let me show you to the door.
You perverted monks.
Mass Tar Wong!
How do you feel?
How are you?
Go now.
I am now sending you to hell,
...to serve your master.
Your crane is not as powerful as mine.
Hurt?
Ah Fu.
The Flying Tiger and Crane.
Please stop!
Let's take risk.
What are you doing?
Save Mass Tar!
Hurry up!
Brother, how are you?
Inform Master Wong now.
Lui has sent someone to murder him.
He is seriously hurt,
let's send him for treatment first.
There is no time left,
go and save Master Wong.
Why not take to Master's home?
Are you kidding?
When did you become so clever?
Watch him.
I have discovered a big secret too.
Don't tell us now.
Why?
It's common in the film that,
once a person got hurt seriously,
he'd die after telling the secret.
Cover the mouth...
Master Wong!
It's poor to be deaf.
In fact you are handsome.
With good Kung-fu and strong enough.
I wish I had a husband like you.
It's good to marry you, right?
Why are you laughing?
You are like a fool.
Am I pretty?
Do you like me?
You look silly!
It's useless even I am willing to marry you.
Why are you still laughing?
Stupid.
Yin-er, have you got the herb?
Dad, it's ready.
After taking these,
you will be totally cured.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
I am sorry for bothering you.
It doesn't matter.
Dad.
What?
Can he hear us?
He has recovered two days ago.
But he improves very much today.
Where are you going?
What a shame!
What is she doing?
Maybe, she feels happy for me.
Master Wong!
We will soon reach there.
Master.
How is he?
Go now.
Lui Yat Siu attached
Po Chi Lam and Heung Chi Kun.
In order to keep those women
and the perverted monks.
He discovered this,
and was seriously beaten.
Master Wong...
He can't hear you.
Why don't you show him a sincere eyesight,
with tears!
This is your last chance.
My master is mean and old fashioned.
Sometimes, he is cunning too.
But, anyway, he is a good master.
Get this chance to join his school.
You understand me very much.
Sure, I have strong observation ability.
Can you listen?
What do you think?
Why don't you inform me first?
You said I am cunning.
I am sorry.
The heaven will punish you.
Punishment at once.
Keep on shooting.
Why do you leave a dying person here?
You bastards!
Are you scared?
You have a red face.
It's very hot!
Who is it?
Master Wong, Lui Yat Siu they...
They have a secret mission.
What is it?
They plan to kidnap Sasin,
on the anniversary celebration
of the 13 companies.
What are they aiming at?
They are from the Boxer Association,
They want to trade Sasin
with their buddies who were caught.
Master... I think I am dying.
But I have a wish.
I beg you, take me as your student.
OK, I promise you.
Leave with peace now.
Master, I am still alive.
Why did you freeze?
I am tired, I want a rest.
Damn you!
What? Again?
No, it's my ass... it's attacked by the arrow.
Go and help Master, quick.
Give me a weapon for self defense.
Take it.
I am dying.
How can you give me such thing?
You're too bad.
I am scared!
Don't be afraid.
When I lie on you,
I feel like holding my sister.
Just take me as your sister.
Go.
Arrest him.
Get going!
Stop chasing.
Master, we can't stay here.
Of course.
What'll we do then?
Go back to Canton,
to fight with that centipede again.
Sit down... Take a seat.
Thank you.
Do you want to watch the bait?
It's a very good show. Exciting.
Hi, John. Hi, David. You look fine.
Hurry up!
Stop.
We come to report...
You are not allowed to enter.
What are you talking about?
The centipede wants to kidnap Mr. Sasin.
I don't know what you are talking about.
The centipede is played the men
from the Boxer Association.
Get lost, I know English.
Ask your boss to leave at once.
The centipede is very powerful.
We come to save him.
Give us $150,000 bonus.
We don't want HK Bank cheque.
But Holland Bank Cheque.
Get them out of here.
How are you?
Are you fine?
How can you beat others in such brutal way?
Cousin Robert!
- Oh! Excuse me.
- Sure.
What's the matter?
I.. I...
I am happy to see you here.
What's the matter?
The players of the centipede are
from the Boxer Association,
they want to kidnap Mr. Sasin.
Follow me.
I will take you to see Mr. Sasin, hurry up.
Luckily we meet cousin Robert.
Freeze.
Do you want to ruin Mr. Lui's plan?
They're bad guys. Watch them.
Wong Fei-hong?!
He must be coming to save Mr. Sasin.
Forget about him, go!
Yes.
The Swinging of Centipede.
Turning of Centipede
How dare you kill me?
I kill whoever blocks my road to success.
Damn you! You betrayed us?
You shouldn't hit your cousin...
Oh yes, I shouldn't hit my cousin...
But I should hit my cousin hardly.
Go to hell.
Your Kung-fu has improved.
Master Wong taught me that.
Wanna go?
Lui Yat Siu.
Damn you, but you can't hear me at all.
You can't escape now.
Wong, you always ruin my plan,
you know, our God will punish you!
China is suffering now,
you bastards still create internal troubles,
I want to terminate you!
Continuous Kicks?
If I guess it correctly, you must be
Lui Fai of the Boxer Association.
But, it's too late.
Not late!
No Shadow Kick.
I know your No-shadow Kick is powerful.
I do have preparation.
Your toes are broken.
How can you use your No-shadow Kick again?
Wine can't give you guts!
You promised your dad
not to drink any wine.
Well, I will represent your dad
to punish you.
You have asked me before,
what kind of fist I am playing?
Now, I am going to tell you.
Isn't it Lui Tung Bun's Fist?
No,
it's Drunken disciples of God.
What kind of stance is it?
It's Han's Flute!
Wrong!
It's the Drunken Crane.
Continuous Swinging Punches!
Wrong again?
I seldom drink wine,
because I can't stop giving heavy punches
if I get drunk.
Really?
The punch is not heavy enough.
Drunken Tiger, to catch the wolf!
Are you drunken or not?
It doesn't matter to be drunken or not.
Drunken Fist? Great!
You look awful!
I want you to cry.
Laugh now.
Thank you.
Master Wong, thank you.
You are bad egg too.
If you sell the harmful medicine again,
I will teach you a lesson.
OK...
Master Wong.
You may find your sister now.
How can I find her in such a big world?
Anyway,
I will treat Miss Nine as my sister.
Master Wong...
I have been stepped by hundreds of people,
I am dying.
I have a big secret to tell you.
Damn!