brother!
brother!...
killing and spilling no drop of blood,
that's marvelous!
simon the snow blower!
you have evidence? don't rattle on!
brother, look!
what's up?
don't move!
Look behind you! My brothers!
l know, this is the lmperial Manager,
Eunuch Liu
And he is Hawk brother six
My younger brother is
the best apprentice of Mr. skilful
He can make clay dolls of anyone
he has seen
that means, it is these three clay dolls
that killed him
but Manager Liu is not that powerful
who is it?
Hawk brother six is worse,
he only knows how to gamble
so the real murderer is this one
but his face is blurred and
can't be recognized
there's no way to guess
what's the matter?
killing and spilling no drop of blood,
is he really simon?
Must be him
Manager Liu, l asked you to fetch the
tianshan snow Lotus, have you got it?
then get it now
yes
sister, who are you giving
this tianshan snow Lotus to?
this tianshan snow Lotus is
very precious, l want it for myself
l heard it is good for the eyes
the skin, and for general health...
lt's death penalty for cheating the king
Phoenix knows
tianshan snow Lotus' main function
is to cure poison
l don't care whom you give it to
Anyway, it's good that use it
to save and not to injure
thank you, brother
l knew you are an understanding
and good emperor
you are eccentric, full of tricks
tell me, have you found your lover?
of course not!
Really no?
No
you know
you are of royal blood like me
you don't have the right
to choose the one you love
ln the eyes of the common people,
they envy us
but then l envy them more
because they have the freedom to love
you speak my mind
you must have found a lover
who is he? tell me!
l said no
No? Are you telling me or not?
No... tell me, yes or no?
No! l'll mar your face!
this is Master ball
He will take us to Hawk brother six
so you are the famous
lmperial Agent dragon 9
you are so handsome! l like you!
brother 9.9.
why are all eunuchs like this?
bear with him, treat him
as your girlfriend
you are so handsome,
you are bound to be courted
the palace is like a maze
why don't you get lost and go to my room
wouldn't that be nice?
lf l am so unlucky to go to your room
l'll hit your head in one blow
you are bad
Normally, the eunuchs in the palace
and the guards can't go around
so Hawk brother six has found a place
where no one know
And set up a gambling house there
the eunuchs and guards
treat it as a club
He is so popular, does he know
how to serve the eunuchs' asses?
Place your bet!
Hold it...
three sixes. l get all!
l am glad l was late
you are dragon 9, right?
what's the matter?
well, l know you are a practical person
lf l want a deal,
l have to gamble with you, right?
How do you want to gamble?
Up to you, if you win
these 5,000 taels are yours
what if l lose?
lf you lose, l don't want money
l just want to know...
...who this clay doll really is?
How come you have this clay doll?
lt's with you...
these three clay dolls are found
on the body of shi Zilun
He must have found out something
he should not know
and had himself killed
okay, l take your bet
we'll play dice,
whoever gets the greater number wins
okay
Have you thought carefully
do you know his other name?
l know what?
He is the "dice devil"
that's right,
everyone calls me the dice devil
l have never lost
Come on
All 18 dice are "6", that makes 108
l'm finished. your turn
okay
so you take that as shaken?
yes, and l have won too
that's one point greater
one point greater!
that's not shaking the dice!
you haven't said
l can't shake it that way!
you...
what about me?
you have so many "fans" here
supporting you, be a gentleman
okay, dragon 9, you are smart!
Everyone knows that
so can you tell me
who this clay doll is now?
l never thought
our meeting would be overheard
He is...
be careful!
He's dead! stop fooling around!
He's killed to keep his mouth shut
He must be a great kung-fu master
and very wicked too
of the three dolls, one is dead,
one is unknown
the only one left is Manager Liu
wait...
where are you going in such a hurry?
Manager Liu is dead!
we are going to his funeral
Cool-son yeh, where are you?
you must take care yourself,
don't be killed
why are you sighing?
why are you here?
there are two persons dead in the palace
Everything is a mess, so l am here
How's your injury?
this is the tianshan snow Lotus, eat it
l'll recover as soon as possible for you
then, l can get ready soon and win!
l know you will win
thank you
does the emperor know about the duel?
He knows, and he knows you will win too
one of us would lose
lt's not who wins that is important
this duel has become too important
lf we don't finish it,
l'm afraid it won't happen again
l'm sure you'll win!
what's the matter with you?
Nothing
Cool-son yeh, whether you live or die
win or lose
l'll be by your side
why do you treat me like this?
when l am blocking the sun for you?
where's Cool-son yeh?
Cool-son yeh?
was he around?
you weren't having a "wild game"
with him here last night?
stop blabbing here!
ls Cool-son yeh really injured?
top secret!
lf you don't want to tell,
l dare not ask
l just want to remind you
Remind me of what?
Mastering the sword
is a very lonely business
to be an invincible swordsmen
you have bear loneliness
which no normal person can bear
As his woman, it is more difficult to
describe the pressure she has to suffer
this is all so hard to understand
lf you fall in love
with an invincible swordsman,
you've to share his loneliness
and also suffer the torment
of losing him at any time
lt's not easy
lt's funny to see you talking
to me so seriously
okay, l am going to investigate now,
interested?
lnvestigate what?
shi Zilun truly is my closest disciple
He has learned 70% of my skills
Mr. skilful,
can you return this clay doll?
l am his master, what do you think?
No one has ever been
so rude to Mr. skilful
give me an hour
l guarantee l can return this clay doll
soon we will find out
who killed shi Zilun
the murderer is so eager
to shut his mouth
there must be a great plot behind this
you call this logic?
why are you still here?
waiting for you
How can l work with you watching?
go out for a walk
and come back in an hour!
Let's go
we have a whole hour
what shall we do?
Anything you want to do?
who has anything to do with you?
lt's so romantic to walk with you
in the sunset
l really will excrete and throw up
l walk with you because l think
highly of you, don't think you are
lf only you were Jade
she is so understanding, really
l know, no matter what l do,
you won't treat me as a girl
you are a girl
you are the sister of the emperor,
Princess Phoenix
who dares make friends with you?
what difference does a princess make?
A princess can also fall in love!
A princess can also love and be loved
so you have fallen in love with that...
lf you keep rattling on, l'll kill you!
white Cloud City Master
is so prestigious
and is a relative of the Royal Family
l am only concerned about him
Have you ever thought the murderer might
be the white Cloud City Master himself?
that's impossible
l think the third clay doll
may be simon the snow blower
How come?
because be seems so uncertain
may be it's true?
simon the snow blower
being the bad guy...
How funny!
see! l said simon the snow blower is bad
where's Mr. skilful?
Right here!
killing and spilling no drop of blood...
who else can it be
but simon the snow blower?
lt's impossible!
Nothing is impossible!
simon the snow blower must
still be around
lf he fights with you
you think you can win him?
He won't fight with me
that's right, he will use worse methods
to deal with you
l had a little donkey, l never rode it
does this bring your...
...childhood memories back?
yes! l am searching
for the feeling of childhood
but...
from my chest to my pelvis,
it's all broken
give me a break, please
okay, l spare you
what bloody place is here?
you cowards!
you use dirty tricks to hide us here
lf you have the guts you come down
and fight with dragon 9 alone!
sure! Have the guts to come down!
Noble persons don't do sneaky things,
l dare you to come down to fight me!
Come down!
didn't you say that your "telepathic
Microsteps" is the best on the earth?
go! go ahead!
okay, come on, one, two...
why didn't it work?
Let's try again. one, two...
why can't we fly up?
l forgot to tell you, the "telepathic
Microsteps" is not for facile leaping
lt's just used to avoid weapons
to run away
you are always bluffing!
but there is a method which works
then use it! Quick!
Help! Help...
that's your solution?
that's not bad. you don't have
to practise and it costs nothing
Help! Help! Help...
don't play with my things!
wow, this is a great umbrella!
when l go back,
l will ask dragon 7 to make me one
give me!
kill you...
don't cry, that's okay
don't cry, it's only a small scorpion
see, l am not afraid, why should you be?
be good, stop crying
l hate little animals, they make me sick
this scorpion is very good for health
lt smells so good, want to taste it?
don't do it, l'll beat you!
okay...
be a good boy
lt's bad!
Push hard!
trading places!
Help! Help...
l never imagined that l,
dragon 9 the hero
would be beaten by these traps!
what?
you're useless!
lt's all your fault!
lf you're not careless,
we would not trap here
dragon 9
simon, is that you?
simon? who is it?
lf you are my friend, just go
No, l have lots of questions for you
why don't you answer me?
you shouldn't stay here for long
why don't you help him?
He doesn't need help
on these trivial matters
you don't think he only knows
how to "blow snow" do you?
lt's delicious, good taste... thank you
No wonder no one knows
you are in the capital
the city is the best place to hide
our cake shop has a hundred years
history in this capital
one hundred years!
No wonder it's so delicious,
what's it called?
this is the wife Cake
l like it very much too
Let's order more take away,
l want more cakes!
lt's really delicious!
Come eat quickly!
Mind your manners when you eat
you are a princess!
l am hungry!
l follow you in your investigations
and almost got myself killed
And now you start lecturing me
when l eat, what's wrong?
go eat then
you're suspicious about me?
Are you full?
so you have decided to go
for the duel with Cool-son yeh...
at the summit of the Forbidden City?
yes
do you know that
big outside bets have been placed?
May be that's...
the reason why someone wants
to cast the blame on you
He must be a great master
He has killed Hawk brother six,
Manager Liu...
and Mr. skilful in my presence
to shut their mouths
there must be a big plot behind all this
but what are they doing?
l really don't know
Are the people placing
their bets on me...
or Cool-son yeh?
you
Moustache gold has regretted
placing his bet on me?
you can think l am lying!
l would bet on you even if l have
to pledge my underwear, you better win
the cake...
...tastes good!
what're you doing?
Russain soup
try some!
yes!
l heard he is very cool
and very cold-blooded
you believe that?
Not really, l think
he can is very gentle and considerate
l heard he only has feelings
for his sword
and nothing else
Not really,
l think he is very passionate
but l heard he killed your master!
l heard that
Princess Phoenix is a nosy body
l didn't believe it then,
but now l tend to agree
okay, l was just over curious that's all
we are both girls, l just want to know
How you can make a cool man
become gentle
you are a princess,
don't you have a lot of love...
and care from others?
Everyone envies me for being born
in the royal family
but in fact, l feel lonely and pathetic
you have not been loved before?
l don't know
then have you ever truly loved a person?
l don't know if that is love
because it is great happiness
to love someone
and to be loved by someone
Eat your wife Cake
l think you want to marry too much
you are getting crazy!
you are jealous
who cares
what's that?
Flying dove mail of our tianshan Clan
what's up?
lt's my two brothers yen Zizhun
and Xiao zichong
Here's the foe that killed your master,
why don't you take revenge?
l have found out that
my master is truly the thief ghost
but then, he is still our master
and he raised us up for good sake
we disciples should take responsibility
l told you earlier
brother shi's death can't have anything
to do with blow snow
you call him by his first name
so your relationship must have surpassed
pure friendship, right?
l think the one who put poison on us
and who killed Zilun are a team
they want to shut our mouths
but simon the snow blower can still cast
blame on someone else
that's impossible
such a highly skilled swordsmen
would not need to use poison
thank you
so you've kept your image even though
you spend your time courting women
you ask him to come and
you don't take revenge
what do you want?
we have a favour to ask from you two
tell me, l'll see what l can do
Please take good care of my sister
one more thing, Master dragon 9
l want two gold medals from you
wow, you say you want it
do you know how much it costs?
How much?
5 million taels for one!
but, if you really want it,
just give me a small red packet
thanks
Unconcerned persons prohibited
from entering palace
Am l unconcerned? l am Princess Phoenix!
l am sorry
l can't let anyone in
without instructions from above
How dare you?
l tell you l am not in a good mood,
l give you one more chance
Are you giving way or not?
but...
Princess, they are only following orders
Please don't make it difficult for them
l only want to find someone in there
what's wrong with that?
who do you want to find?
that's none of your business
of course
but if you want to find Cool-son yeh
then may be l can help
you know where's him?
l have secretly placed a bet
so l have a duty to protect them
till the duel tonight
take me there yes
Cool-son yeh
lt's you?
you don't look too well,
have you recovered?
l'm fine
l have seen
simon the snow blower's skills
Although it is not as powerful as
your "Hovering Heavenly Fairy"
but his stances are very quick
and very forceful too
that's good
why?
lf he is not a good master
then it's meaningless for me
to have the duel with him tonight
but you have not recovered yet
l'm okay, it's going to be fine
but... can't you refit a date?
No. No one...
...can back out from the fight today
Neither of us can change it
we must fight
Men are that strange
Honour is more important than life
so tonight we can die,
but we cannot back out
why can't l know you before the duel?
whatever happens tonight,
it does not matter
lf you are by my side
l have no regrets
Really?
No
No one has thought highly of me
in my whole life
you know that l am
the illegitimate child of Pingnan king
l have royal blood
but l can never be emperor
that's why l spend my whole life
practicing my sword
so that l can be king
in the art of sword
Either l become king
or l become a bandit
you will win
thank you
Are you ready?
do you love me?
do you know that...
every girl wishes
to hear her lover say it
you understand
you must come back, l will wait for you
No need to wait! lf you wish,
you can come along. sister-in-law
who is your sister-in-law?
Just now you forgot your manners
and embraced him
you must be my sister-in-law already
How about it?
tonight's going to be
a grand event of the capital,
everyone's attention is drawn to it
the Powerful Four in the Palace
only issued eight gold medals
l have given five
to unimportant people...
...of the remaining three
lf you really want to go,
l can give one to you
l'm not going
you don't want to go
or you dare not watch?
l want to wait for him here
that's good,
no one knows what will happen tonight
And there's another master in the palace
who has not appeared
don't worry, l'll be back
Let's go
Hey, don't be so selfish
you've got one, l've got one too!
give me some time, l'll be back soon
Jade
All these years,
l have not given you anything good
Each time when l am tired
you always know how to make me happy
tonight is an important occasion
Not just for simon the snow blower,
even l am not sure if l can come back
so l want you to stay by my side
and take you to watch the duel
you are really willing
to take a prostitute with you
and acknowledge me as your woman?
what about being a prostitute!
l am not much better?
l used to be only an usher
at the theatre
and learned some special martial arts
Come here, put this on
do l need to wear this?
lt's so ugly, l don't want it
you don't want it,
or you don't want to wear it?
l'm not going
why?
because l want you to know...
there is a woman here waiting for you
you must come back!
okay, l promise, l'll be back!
this umbrella can do anything,
but not stop the water!
what's wrong! this is murder!
you know, l hate women who pretend to...
...have manners!
l like you that way!
l love you!
gold medals on sale... 100 tael for one
gold medals on sale...
terrific! l got the gold medal now!
How many medals did
the Powerful Four give to you?
Eight, l give it to you...
and lmmoral wu, two sons of the
tianshan Clan, Honest monk, Priest wood
the remaining two were left for Jade
and simon the snow blower's girl
but she didn't want it
do you know, everyone is saying
they have a gold medal and that...
...they can use it as a pass...
...to enter the palace
to watch the duel of the century
lt's as exciting as going to a concert
don't worry, the eight gold medals
were issued by Nie kung and the others
He can tell which ones are genuine
don't shout!...
you suspect my medal is faked?
do you know that l lmmoral wu,
spent 5 million taels to buy it?
stay calm!
okay, here comes dragon 9
lf you don't believe me you ask him
whether my medal is real or faked
that's true, l have given
out gold medals, but only six
l don't understand
why so many people have a medal
dragon 9, my medal is real, right?
More real than your mom!
Look, what shall we do?
l don't know myself
don't push! Let me go in!
simon the snow blower...
this sword of mine is named "the giant"
3 feet 8 inches long
Made with ice under the sea
lt can cut the thinnest of hair
And has been fed with the blood
of 178 famous swordsmen
Mine is 3 feet 9 inches,
Made from iron of the western district
lt is not worse than yours
so is your heart at peace?
we'll fight next year!
tang Ao, give me the cure!
the poison in me
has been passed on to you
you're dead!
l am not Cool-son yeh!
tang Fei...
No, you can't die! tang Fei!
then where is Cool-son yeh?
who are you?
How dare you! l am the emperor
you dare to sneak into the palace
and put on the king's robe
do you know
your whole clan would be executed?
How dare you!
l am the real emperor
you have stolen my throne for years
lf you kneel down and beg me,
l can spare you the death penalty
you...
you are too much!
your two majesties,
please allow me to say something
Liu?
shouldn't you be dead?
there's a vampire grass out there
within 24 hours after a person is "dead"
the body is stiff with no breath
lt's no different from being dead
guard!
your majesty
the guards are at taihe Palace
watching the duel
Cool-son yeh?
that's right
but the real Cool-son yeh
is here waiting to be emperor
so you two have conspired to rebel
we were linked by royal blood
l am much smarter than you
and my kung-fu is invincible
why did my father had to be sent to
Pingnan for being an illegitimate child
and l even lost my title
because l am an illegitimate child?
and have to my mother's last name
brother...
...you call that justice?
these rules have been set by
the royal family, we just have to obey
lf l become emperor
l will improve the livelihood
of the people and expand our boundary
our prosperity will surpass
the tang and Han dynasty
And we will even be stronger
than the times of genghis khan
think about that
And your death would be worthwhile
you think that if you kill me and take
my throne, the people would obey you?
your majesty do not have
to worry about this
l have been your servant
since you were a child
l am familiar with every inch
of your face
so l have made a mask bearing your face
when you die and the new emperor
takes your throne
l am sure no one will recognize
one year later, l will meet
with my brother Cool-son yeh in the west
l suddenly feel a calling from heaven
and become a monk,
passing on my throne to Cool-son yeh
then the country will prosper and
the civilians will adore me
great! so you have it well planned
Pull out your sword
why?
l don't kill anyone without a weapon
l have been appointed by heaven
lf you wish to act against the wishes
of heaven, then just come along
l am willing to do it for you
you dare!
the lnvincible Umbrella!
lt can attract all hidden weapons
on earth
weapon!
Just the two of you?
your majesty
do you know
why l knew of your plan a long time ago?
because the jade imperial seal
you returned
last time was too perfect
the real one has
one of its corners broken
shi Zilun knew your conspiracy
with Hawk brother six and Manager Liu
so you killed him
the third clay doll was actually you
Hawk brother six is really dead
and his death is faked
you switched all attention to the duel
at the summit of the Forbidden City
so the Powerful Four guards could not
protect the emperor
then you sneak in to try and
take over the throne
Cool-son yeh, you were acting
with tang Fei at Chun Hua House
so you cheated me to believe
you are injured so l pity you, right?
too bad,
heavens vengeance is slow but sure
tang yong did not know the truth
And killed his own brother
And the truth spilled out
Cool-son yeh...
you have cheated me and used me
guard!
yes!
Arrest Cool-son yeh and Liu tong!
Hold it! you think you can arrest me?
of course l can't do it alone,
but there are 50,000 soldiers out there
and 800 lmperial guards...
you fight till tomorrow till
you are totally exhausted,
and you die all the same
you were a nobleman,
why choose to be a bandit?
the victor becomes a king and
the loser a bandit
Now...
l have only one request
what is it?
Please let me have the duel
with simon the snow blower
on the summit of the Forbidden City
lf l can't fight with him,
l will regret it for the rest of my life
How dare you negotiate?
why not?
Uncle Pingnan, you are a nobleman
Although illegitimate,
l always considered you a hero
l now allow you to have the duel
with simon the snow blower
And whatever the result,
you can commit suicide
what do you think?
thank you. your Majesty
Night of the full moon,
summit of the Forbidden City
l hope you have a fair duel
l don't mind you
Cheating me or using me
l just want to know one thing
Have you ever really loved me?
yes
No lying?
No
Everything, has been as planned
but there was a little mistake
l fell in love with you
then do you wish me to be your wife?
l have said that...
...no matter you win or lose,
live or die
l will be by your side
Leave me alone
Are you alright?
Cool-son yeh, how dare you!
whoever gets into the way?
go!
go away
l am in pain...
do you wish to be my wife?
of course, l do!
l love you
Cool-son yeh...
don't leave me alone, bring me along
don't worry, he'll be fine
give me a hug!
Are you alright?
Hey... don't say such things in public,
it's nauseating
what does it matter?
Can't l care for you?
Look at them,
they are saying love words too!
l don't care...
l have waited so long my legs are weak
okay... we will go back and take a bath
you don't have to help me
l will rub your back, how's that?
yes
l love you
Let's forget them
Let's go back and
play eight-and-a-half limbs nine limbs
disgusting!
simon, come on!
Hey, jump up!
How can we don't have
a New year sex in Lunar New year?