Gita!
I want to talk to you
about something important.
I cannot keep it in me anymore.
Go on.
I had recognized you at the
bookshop in Delhi.
And I'd guessed that you had
come to take Kaveriamma away.
You did not make a mistake
in the address of Charanpur.
I had deliberately given you
the wrong directions.
Why is that?
Call me childish...
... but I did not want you
to reach Charanpur
and to meet Kaveriamma.
For all that you're doing for the
school, I'd like to thank you!
But I cannot let you take
Kaveriamma away.
Why?
You want her so that
she can take care of your house
and do all the household chores.
How dare you say that?
How can you accuse me
of such a motive?
I have travelled 12,000 miles
only out of concern for...
... Kaveriamma's well being.
If you were so concerned
then where were you when she
was in an Old Age Home?
It was I who traced her
and got her here.
Maybe, that's because
you needed someone to take
care of Chikku and your house.
Why did you come back?
Why did you have to come back?
We were so happy.
You have everything in life.
But all we have is Kaveriamma.
You are not the only one
with a right over her.
I agree that she is
like a mother figure to you...
... and you like a son to her.
But she is a mother to me too.
I don't want to
become an orphan again!
I understand Gita.
I will not allow you to take
Kaveriamma away from me.
Kaveriamma will come
with me to America.
Whether you like it... or not!
I'm in a dilemma Fatima.
Mohan is asking me to go with him,
while Gita expects me to be here.
I just don't know what to do.
Allah knows, when Mohan arrived
I was so happy for you.
But I never thought things
would get into such a tangle.
You'll have to disappoint
one or the other.
I'm not clear whether I should go to
America with Mohan or not!
I don't understand why he
wants to take you there?
To work there? Did you ask him?
No Fatima. He respects me.
He'll take good care of me.
Well, I hope you are right Kaveri.
Otherwise who is to know what
tomorrow has in store?
Kaveri, why don't you ask
Mohan to stay on over here?
No, he won't agree.
Remember one thing...
... every piece of ice is inevitably
ordained to melt in its own water!
Get him to understand
this perfectly well.
We played a lot.
Kaveriamma...
... you can stop looking
for a groom for me!
I have decided... not to get
married at this point!
But why?
Yes. I want to focus all my time on the
children and the school's progress.
That's alright, but...
Furthermore, I'm not yet prepared
for marriage!
Well done!
This is a good move
to stall Kaveriamma from leaving.
But then, come to think of it
who will want to marry you anyway?
Now, don't get me wrong!
I'm not saying you're not beautiful.
But this attitude, tonnes of
ideals and principles...
... who'll suffer all this?
It's a good thing, you have
decided to opt out yourself.
But there is one crazy guy,
who might want to marry you.
Yes Mohan, the precipitation
measurement list has been drawn up.
You understand what I'm saying?
- Yes Vinod.
We've tested the dual frequency radar,
the horizontal & vertical resolution's fine
Yes, but the waveforms need to match
with the longitudinal parabolas.
Of course, of course
they work in alignment.
Nivaaranji... Nivaaranji...
Here speak to Steve.
- Hi Mohan.
Steve, what about the
geometrical axis function?
It's being calibrated. The baseline
parameter's been optimized.
See, the sun-synch orbit needs to be in
alignment with the radiometers of TRMM.
Ok, I'll make the remaining readings
and call you in a couple of days.
Ok, thanks.
Hey Mohan so how's everything else?
Everything's fine. All is well.
So, have you found yourself
a village belle?
Actually, you can say yes.
What?
You're kidding me right?
- No.
What's her name?
Her name is Gita.
Kaveriamma lives with her.
I don't believe this!
Except, she's no village belle...
She studied in Delhi
and now she runs a school here.
Have you told her?
Does she know?
How can I tell her?
- What do you mean?
I mean...
I mean she's got a different set
of ideals et al. She's just different.
Come on!
You can't make that mistake.
You have to tell her how you feel.
All right... if you say so.
Listen I'll catch up with you later,
gotta go now.
Your two weeks are almost up!
I know.
I'll be back soon.
You should have been back already.
- But let me propose to her first.
I'll be leaving soon,
catch up with you later, bye.
Bye.
Gurnaamji, how much was that?
32 minutes. Is it ok if I pay tomorrow?
- Yes.
My apologies Mohanbabu!
The electricity is problematic here.
Why are you trying to
corrupt Chikku's mind?
What are you talking about?
Haven't you been talking to him and
his friends about going to America?
No Gita, I was just explaining...
Am I teaching these kids so that they can
go abroad and settle down like you?
You NRI. Non-Returning Indian!
Hand me the mug, please.
You don't even know how to have a bath.
You should learn from Chikku.
Gita, I think you need a vacation.
Why don't you come back
with me for one?
Gita, you are very mischievous.
Where's the bucket?
Listen...
- No. You listen to me.
What?
- I like you very much... Gitli!
What?!
- It's true, Gitli!
I liked the way you handled
that man in the bookshop.
Don't try to sweet talk me.
Kaveriamma will stay here... with me!
You're misunderstanding.
I really like you.
Shut up! And don't you try
to corrupt the kids again, ok?
I'm not corrupting anyone.
I'm only bathing.
More than the kids, you're the
one who needs an education!
You can keep calling out to
YOUR Kaveriamma now.
All right now, remove your notebooks.
The topic is General Knowledge.
So who's going to tell me...
... the names of five of the most
important rivers in the country?
I'm sorry to be late teacher.
Look ahead.
Today I'm going to take your class!
First question...
... name five main rivers in India?
You...
... tell me!
Let me think.
Ganga, Jamuna, Narmada...
... Bharati...
... Panchgani...
Bharati? Panchgani??
Are they rivers?
Vidya, you tell me.
Ganga, Jamuna, Narmada...
Godavari and Brahmaputra.
Excellent Vidya!
Second question...
... name the new state that has
been formed in North-West India?
I know this one.
It was a part of Uttar Pradesh, right?
Yes Chikku. You tell us!
It's Uttaranchal!
- Oh yes, Uttaranchal!!
How could I have missed it?
I forgot!
Well done, Chikku!
Now the last question...
... if our new student does
not know the answer...
... we'll have to demote him to
a lower class.
How many lion heads does
the Ashoka pillar have?
This one is easy.
Three.
Noooooo! It's got four!
Excellent, children!
The lesson of the day is...
... before gaining knowledge
about foreign lands,
it is important that one should
know one's own country first.
Don't forget to do your homework.
The rivers Ganga and Jamuna have
their confluence point in Allahabad.
The new state Uttaranchal...
... is the 27th state of India
with Dehradun as its capital.
This is the land where the
Mahabharata was written!
The Ashoka pillar rests
in a circular abacus,
which is girded by four animals.
The bull of the West...
... the elephant of the East,
the horse of the South...
... and lion by the North.
Gita, the blackboard is clean.
Gita... I am...
Gita... !
But all my answers were correct.
This is Natthu, the potter and
this is Shankar...
... he makes baskets.
Both of them want us to admit
their children in school.
What Mohanbabu said to us
the other day touched our hearts.
We don't want our
children to suffer like us.
On the morning of Dussehra
(Indian festival)
you can come and enroll your
children in the school.
Yes ok.
The tides have begun to
change direction.
Haven't they?
I'm sorry.
Mohan!- Yes?
Mohan, I have some work for you.
- What work?
There's a place called Kodi a
few miles from here.
Gita has some family property there,
which has been leased to a
farmer called Haridas.
He has not paid his rent for
some months.
I want you to go an
recover the money.
Me?
But why do you want me to go?
Can't you send someone else?
If you go and ask
he just might pay up.
Oh! So you want me
to be a collector now!
Ok, when should I leave?
I have to fuel up the caravan.
You have to leave now.
- Now?
Yes, and you can't take the caravan there.
- Then?
You will have to take the train
for three hours to Narsinga...
... then a boat journey across
the river to Maangaon...
... and finally three hours by bus...
and you've reached Kodi!
Sure, that's pretty closeby!
- You'll return by tomorrow evening.
And Mela Ram will go with you.
He knows the way.
Kaveriamma...
- Yes?
My vacation is nearing it's end.
What have you decided?
You finish this work first.
Come on Collector saheb... !
Why are you sending Mohan?
I sent Haridas a message only
a few days ago.
I know what I'm doing!
Good morning sir.
- Good morning Melaram.
I'm all set to take you on a
sightseeing trip of the village.
Ok, I'll take your leave.
Mohanbhaiyya, you'll
bring me a toy, won't you?
Of course! Gimme five... yes!
And what shall I bring for you?
Nothing.
I know you don't want me to leave,
but I have to go for Kaveriamma.
And listen, don't think
about me too much.
Don't miss me too much.
Now what makes you think
that I'll miss you?
The look in your eyes!
They give your feelings away.
O beloved, most beloved, surely
I am infatuated with thee
Thou hast endeared my heart
O beloved...
O beloved, most beloved, surely
I am infatuated with thee
Thou hast endeared my heart
O beloved...
My heart's bewildered
My body with fire kindled
It's monsoon of my dreams
The courtyard of my eyes streams
The pitcher of my heart is overflowing
O beloved...
O dear who hast drawn so near!
O dear who hast endeared my heart!
How canst I recount
What hath been thy bequest pray how?
Somewhere art buds of
a throbbing heart
Somewhere the dream-lanes
Mirth that dwells in the heart,
How shallst I articulate?
Thou swayeth me so
That oft times I am embarrassed
It seems I have lost
my path
Ever since I have seen the
haven of love
Haven of love
O beloved, most beloved,
surely
I am infatuated with thee
Thou hast endeared my heart
O beloved...
Now that thou hast met me
This world's transformed
Methinks the flowers have begun
to beset my path
And I fancy too
That this earth's renewed
The sky too freshly spun
in our love
Wanton breeze singeth some melody
River too narrates some tale
All's changed, my love
since my eyes courted thine
I have lost presence of my mind,
gone is my treasured selfhood
O beloved...
Haridasji!
Yes?
I'm Mela Ram and this is
Mohan Bhargavaji.
Tell me.
Kaveriji and Gitaji have sent me.
It's about the land's rent.
I understand.
Come in.
You have travelled a long way.
You must be tired. Please rest.
Make some bread.
Run along now.
Please come in.
You really shouldn't have bothered.
How is that possible?
A guest is like God!
We've served what we have;
you eat and then we'll talk.
Ok.
If I had the capacity to pay,
I would have come to Charanpur myself.
Sir, I was a weaver before I
took up farming.
Since the advent of machine
woven fabrics in the market,
weaving had ceased to
be a lucrative business.
So I became a farmer.
I took Gitaji's land on lease.
I'd imagined, once the crops flourished
the children's life would improve.
But it was not to be!
Why?
By taking up farming,
I had changed my profession.
The village elders did not accept this
and looked upon me as an outcast.
They felt a weaver should remain a weaver,
even if it meant, that he had to go hungry.
I cried, pleaded...
but no one listened to me!
Nobody offered a drop of
water to irrigate my land.
Entire crop dried up...
.... and whatever survived,
the villagers refused to buy.
It is because of this, I've not
been able to pay Gitaji's rent.
But this is wrong.
It's unfair. It is an outrage!
It is the way things work here.
Not a morsel to
fill our stomach,
no clothes to wear,
no roof above our heads,
no education for children,
nor land!
The thirst in my heart alone
knows the taste of my tears!
Then what did you do?
What could I do?
I thought about migrating to the city,
hoping life would be better there.
Those who had been there,
recounted the anguish in the cities.
A labourer goes there to work,
and falls into the grip of contractors.
He either returns hungry,
or never returns.
And soon, the wife has to
sell the little land she has.
No sir, no!
I couldn't feed my
children in this life...
... what is to happen after me?
And about Gitaji's money,
I have nothing to offer
except helplessness and shame.
Nothing...
Thank you for the food, Haridasji.
Haridasji, I'll take your leave.
Please don't mind. Here's
some money. Keep it.
Mohanbabu, it's very kind of you
but I can't accept it.
Please Haridasji, I want you to keep it.
When you have it, you can
return it to me.
But I don't know when I will
be able repay it.
Don't worry about it.
Here Chotu, this is for you.
Share it with your sisters.
Please give Gitaji
and Kaveriji my respects.
Water for sale... water for sale...
25 paise for a glass...
25 paise for a glass of water...
Saheb, please have a glass of water.
Mohan you're back!
How was your journey?
Ok.
- Did you meet Haridas?
Yes. But I could not get the money.
His situation is pathetic.
He can't pay the rent!
Instead, sir gave him money
from his own pocket, before leaving.
I couldn't bear to see
Haridas' condition.
I don't think you should expect
any rent from him.
Mohanbhaiyya, did you get me my toy?
I couldn't get anything.
Come Chikku.
Mohan this is the general
state of affairs.
What is money when compared
with the value of human life?
I'm glad you gave him money.
Now don't get disheartened.
Rest a little.
Kaveriamma...
... how do I wrap this around?
Kaveriamma has left for school.
For the decorations.
I don't know why she wants
me to wear this dhoti?
What's wrong with my jeans anyway?
It is the appropriate thing to
wear on Dussehra.
If you wish I can tie it for you.
How do you know?
Have you ever worn one?
It's not a saree, ok!
Ok then! Do it yourself.
All right, all right.
Just do it quick.
Come...
Give...
Hold it.
What the...
There, it's done.
Sure, it's done...
... but I hope it doesn't
unravel in a crowd! Or else...
Shut up!
Today is the auspicious day of Dussehra.
It was on this day that Lord Rama...
had slain Ravana and marked the
triumph of good over evil!
I am very happy that on this day
we initiate new students in the school.
May the Goddess of Knowledge
be with you.
It's Lajwa.
This is our little granddaughter Kusum!
Now, go and play.
Mohanji, where are you off?
Why don't you spend some time with us?
I'm impressed. How well you've
tied your dhoti Mohanbabu?
How did you manage to learn so quickly?
It's pretty easy. It was tied in seconds.
You're looking like a bridegroom.
Thank you.
So how long have you lived abroad?
It's been almost twelve years now.
You must have adapted yourself
completely to their way of living?
We would also like to know a
thing or two about America.
Well... America is a big country...
We've heard that it's also very rich?
Rich it is. But there are several
reasons for that.
One among them is that their land
is rich in mineral resources...
Even our land is rich, but in crops.
Our strength... lies in our fields.
Do they have problems of rain?
Are they affected by drought
and famine like us?
And what about electricity?
They've set up infrastructure to provide
all the basic amenities to the common man.
Electricity, housing board, healthy
food and free education.
We have one thing,
they don't have and will never have.
What?
Culture and tradition!
Yes, agreed.
And till we have that,
no one can destroy us.
Ours is the greatest country in the world!
Absolutely!
Culture and tradition is our strength,
don't you agree?
Munishwar...
I don't think... Mohanbabu agrees!
Do you Mohanji?
You're right.
I don't agree that ours is the greatest
country in the world!
But I do believe that we have the
potential and strength to become great.
Both these countries are economically,
sociologically and culturally apart.
I shouldn't say this but since you have
broached this topic, let me say that...
... whenever we suspect losing
in comparison...
... we clutch on to our favourite refuge...
... culture...
... and tradition!
America has progressed
on its own strengths.
They have their own culture
and own tradition.
It would be wrong to claim
that their culture
their tradition and beliefs
are inferior and ours are laudable.
It's wrong.
But I have heard that
there they discriminate against
members of ethnic races.
Yes! There are clashes sometimes.
Aren't they everywhere?
What is important to analyze is that
we make differences based on caste.
You talk as if we have created the caste,
class, religion and the social system.
This hierarchy of caste is ancient
as is culture and religion.
And colour and creed.
Remember, one's caste is
a thing that can never die!
Just because a custom is ancient,
it does not have to be right.
Why are you imposing your
views on us Mohanbabu?
I am not imposing any views.
I am only speaking of things I've
experienced while living here.
And I've realized that we keep
fighting amongst ourselves...
... when we must fight against illiteracy,
over-population and corruption.
Every day, in our streets and homes,
each one of us keeps saying
"The country has gone to dogs. The
country is on the path of destruction!"
If we keep saying this, we will
one day actually land up there.
You'll need to do
something to remedy this.
You too!
Not just the members of the Panchayat
but everyone in the village.
You are blaming the members of the
Panchayat for your problems.
But when you step into their shoes, you'll
do the same thing. This applies to me too!
The dalits blame the brahmins...
... and brahmins claim that their
piety is despoiled by the dalits.
The blacksmith and potter blame
the moneylender.
The land owners blame the peasants,
but they don't give them their rights.
In what way are we great then?
If we have problems in the village,
we point our finger at the State...
... and the State at someone else.
We all are finding fault with each other!
The fact is that we're all to be blamed.
Because the problem... is us!
Me... you...
... all of us!
Have you lost your head?
What are you saying?
All I know is that...
... a weaver who changed his
occupation by becoming a farmer...
... cannot feed his family
or give his children an education.
He can only watch his kids
die of malnutrition.
Every moment weighs terribly,
we're beset with a calamity
O scion of Raghu race,
come to rescue me
Come, O Raghu stalwart,
O lord, I beseech thee
Adorable lord of my heart,
O my good Ram, appear
I recite thy Name,
hear thou O Ram and come
Proclaim glory of truth
by beat of drum,
burn Lanka of sins
At once come, rescue me and
heed loud proclamation mine
Every moment weighs terribly,
we're beset with a calamity
O scion of Raghu race,
come to rescue me
Forget Ram, look!
It's Ravana who hast come
His mighty shadow hath
spread over all quarters
Why dost thou recite Name of Ram?
Why dost thou sing rosary of Ram?
This Ram - Ram thou hast
begun by rote
O Sita!
what virtue didst thou
see in Ram to quote?
Who can recount all His virtues?
Lexicon too falleth short
Who can reach the summits
Where my adorable Ram sits
Ram is most excellent in this world,
unswerving in virtue
Most puissant yet
possessed of restraint
But now his restraint too
hath suffered diminution
O Ravana! It's not too
late to beg for mercy!
May the glory of truth be
proclaimed by beat of drum!
Lanka of sins shouldst burn
Here cometh Ram; we bow unto Him
Accompanied by noble
brother Lakshmana
Every moment weighs terribly,
we're beset with a calamity
O scion of Raghu race,
come to rescue me
Shouldst Ram possess strength;
shouldst He valour proclaim
Why hast He not come to rescue thee,
thy fame?
He whose glories thou
singeth untiring
Pray, where is that Ram at
this moment, uncaring?
Ram resides in mine heart;
Ram is mine breathing part
Ram is soul mine,
Ram doth my life define
Ram in all my moments liveth,
it's Ram in every breath
Ram is in every hope of mine;
Ram is in every wish and pine
Ram verily in compassion stayeth,
in peace too dwelleth Ram
Ram for sure in unity is,
progress too is glory His
Ram, in contemplation of devotees,
and of enemies alike liveth
Forsake sin, O Ravana! And thou
shalt find Ram in thy heart
Ram in thy heart,
Ram is in mine heart
Ram in every home and abode,
Ram at every threshold
Whoever shouldst oust Ravana
from the heart, to him doth Ram dart
Every moment weighs terribly,
we're beset with a calamity
O scion of Raghu race,
come to rescue me
Look Lord Ram has come,
Mine Lord Ram has come
Here comes the scion of the Raghu race,
Here he comes to rescue me
Look Lord Ram has come,
Mine Lord Ram has come
Here comes the scion of the Raghu race,
Here he comes to rescue me
Siyavar Ramchandra Ki... Jai!
(Glory unto Lord Ramchandra)
The burning Ravan is looking
prettier in the darkness.
Every moment weighs terribly,
we're beset with a calamity
Quiet! Please be quiet!
Why do I feel that...
... all of you have started
enjoying living in this darkness?
You've adjusted to this darkness?
For how long are you'll going to
take your problems lying down?
But what else can we do, Mohanji?
Will you do as I ask?
Have you once again come up
with some strange solution?
Please have mercy on us!
Wait Munishwar...
What do you want us to do?
Is there a spring on
the nearby mountain?
Yes there is. So?
I need a hundred men.
A hundred men?
You shall have them.
You shall have a
hundred men!
Thank you Dadaji.
Sir, one hears lightning had struck
this spot several years ago.
Since then there has been
this gush of water.
Wonder what he's upto!
This is Point A1
We shall build a reservoir here.
I mean a water tank.
The water will be
acccumulated here.
From here, there will be a water pipe
which leads to Point A3.
A3 will have a shed with a turbine,
I mean a machine.
When the water falls on the turbine,
it will rotate with great speed.
And if all things go right,
electricity will be generated.
We'll form four groups.
The blacksmiths will cast the moulds.
The 2nd and 3rd group will do the
digging work for the tank and so on.
Now let's form the groups.
Quickly!
This boy looks promising!
Surely seems like.
Reservoir will be made here.
Length 5 metres and breadth 1 metre.
I mean, 5 arm's
by 1 arm's length.
For this we will have to clear out
all the stones and bushes.
Is that clear?
- Yes.
It's 7 feet and 6 inches.
Shall I try it?
Where's Mela Ram?
What is this?
- From boot to suit, total American sir!
But why?
Now that we are going to do
business together...
I thought that I should look
like a 40% partner!
This is my passport and this is
my VISA form, fully filled out!
Once it's stamped...
Ballu, show him an
alternator powered 24 watts.
Please come in sir.
Here's your water, Dadaji.
- Thank you, Santaram.
How's the work progressing on the hill?
It's getting on perfectly fine.
How long will it take?
- It will be completed very soon.
You take rest!
I'll take your leave now.
Jai Ramji Ki!
By the way Vinod, will the turbine
principle work in power generation?
Yes. Why do you ask?
You know what, I am trying to
generate electricity here.
Electricity? What the hell
are you talking about?
No, no Vinod, I'm lighting a bulb here.
John is beginning to lose it by the day.
Speak to him, and
buy me some more time.
We've started working nights.
- Common Vinod handle it for me.
I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
- Bye.
25 x 75 is equal to...
- 1875.
23.3 x 33.9
789.87 = 790.
I'm about to finish this.
I've fallen in love with you.
What did you say? Come again.
See! Just see!
It's you and me, and long solitude!
How delicate are these shadows!
Listen in; heed the heartbeats
Listen in; heed the song of silence
Listen in; heed what the night hath to say
Night's come;
with desires nameless and many
She narrateth a hundred woes;
I listen to her epiphany
Night unwindeth,
unabashed stripeth her cloak
Pearls, scattered as it were; I pick
You have chanted some spell in words
Lamps are alit in my eyes
The darkness of my
nights hath poured out
Melaram ready?
- Ready sir.
Release the valve.
Release the valve further.
Good!
The water will gush to this
turbine through this pipe.
The turbine will rotate with
the force of water.
With this steering wheel, we can
control the water flow.
We need to release enough water
to make this pulley rotate
and make this alternator spin
at the speed of 1500 rpm.
And if this happens,
electricity will be generated.
Lonely went the day
and nights sans you,
overcast with desolation
And now it seemeth the nights,
kissed by the day art perfumed
for you art my companion
I was incomplete sans you,
more complete now none couldst be
In yours, my world I discovered,
yet I am all lost
Both of us have now learned,
art of living well earned
Like Midas touch, our living
how well hath altered
Both of us have now learned,
beauty of life well earned
O joys, we owneth a score,
enough and more
What are you'll doing?
There will be electricity in
your house, Dadi Setu!
The wires are up. Now all that
we have to do is wait.
Ready...- Ready sir.
Nivaaranji ok?
Yes Mohanji.
Mela Ram, release the water.
- Ok sir.
Open the valve...
Slowly...
Electricity will be generated at 230 Volts.
Come on...
Nivaaranji, is the valve fully open?
- Yes Mohanbabu.
Mela Ram, is the valve fully open?
Fully open sir. Totally open.
Sure?
- Sure Sir.
Gita, come.
Hold the steering.
Hold it.
If the valve is fully open,
how come there's no pressure?
Has the pressure increased?
Yes!
Jafarbhai, how many rpm?
800 sir.
I say, how long now for the electricity?
Have patience Munishwar, patience!
Electricity!
Electricity.
Mohanbabu, we have done it.
Electricity of our own village!
Generated with our toil and sweat.
Just like this project, we must
think of newer and innovative ways
to solve our village problems.
Sarpanchji, come quickly!
Dadaji's health has deteriorated.
Dadaji...
Electricity? Is it here?
Yes.
The day...
... I saw you...
... I felt...
... something special about you...
Now that you're here...
... I can...
... die in peace.
But Mohan, you've already been away
for five weeks. This really isn't right..
I'm extremely sorry John. I've just been
caught up with some personal work and...
We are in Phase II of Core design here.
There can't be any further delays!
I understand John. I've just finished
what I needed to do here and
I'll be back in three days.
Three days it is!
- Of course John. Yes... I will.
What surprises me is how you
can think of going
after all that you have seen
and learnt here.
It's true Gita.
I have learnt so much here,
gained so much here.
Felt the problems here...
... but I cannot live here.
And I cannot live out of this country.
I am willing to marry you...
... but I won't go to America.
I know that you are not going to
come with me.
Mohan, I've given it lot of thought.
At this age, I'll not be able to adopt the
ways and customs of another country.
I am happy here.
Now that you are leaving...
... I will miss you very much.
If you were here, our family
would have been complete.
I'll take your leave.
May you live a long life son!
We had forgotten that you were a guest.
A visitor must leave one day.
We'll miss you very much.
When you come here next
you'll surely find Internet
in Charanpur Post Office.
Every little lad will email you.
What we couldn't have,
is our wrestling match.
I am sorry Mela Ram that
I have to leave suddenly.
But I'll surely send you
the sponsorship papers.
I don't need them anymore.
I'll be fine here.
Your presence in the village has
changed some things around here.
Some things have definitely changed.
But you had planned your migration.
When the creeper in your house crosses
into your neighbor's compound...
... one's own house is ruined.
It's like a lamp on your threshold
giving light to the neighbour's house.
All the best Sir.
Thank you Mela Ram.
Mohanbhaiyya, this is for you.
I will put this up in my house.
Listen, study well.
Right!
Where is Gita?
I haven't seen her around since morning.
I have to leave now.
Or else I'll miss my flight.
- Ok.
Please explain to her, ok?
Go son! My love and blessings
are always with you.
Don't worry...
Bye.
Gita, you're impossible!
You're here and...
... I've been looking for you all over.
I did not want to talk to you
before the villagers.
I'm saddened with your decision
but I can understand your predicament.
I can understand.
Gita, I too understand...
... but please don't mistake
my helplessness for betrayal.
I did not mean to hurt you...
- Mohan.
I love you.
I want you to be happy wherever you are.
This is for you.
What is this?
Open it.
What's all this?
The summation of all our traditions!
Little flowers of our profound faith!
Our fields...
... our greenery...
... rivers...
... our culture...
... all these will keep reminding you of us!
And maybe...
... maybe compel you to return!
Please stop! Don't go!
And as we can see, we have some points
here that the satellite travels
along the way to capture data
of the Global Precipitation.
Next we're going to see the territory
of the GPM instrument,
as it goes from Australia to India
This country, thy soil
It's thy motherland!
She calls thee
This is a bond that can
never be severed
The scent of the soil:
How canst thou fail to remember?
No matter where thou wanderest
Thou art bound to return
From newer paths thou toureth
From thy sighs hushed.
From thy forlorn heart
Some one shalt beckon
This country, thy soil
It's thy motherland!
She calls thee
This is a bond that can
never be severed
To thee hast thy life
Words to proclaim:
Thou hast gained all
What dearth to name hath thou?
All the happiness hath
showered, though:
Thou art far away from thy home
Come, return O wanderer
Where someone wouldst
name thou a kin
And summon thee to the native soil
This country, thy soil
Is thy motherland!
She calls thee
This is a bond that can
never be severed
Now that you're here...
I can... die in peace!
It is like a lamp on your threshold
giving light to your neighbor's house.
I've made up my mind, Vinod.
I must go back.
Not again!
How can you go back for a girl?
Just persuade her to come here.
Its not that Vinod!
It's not only about
Gita and Kaveriamma.
This is the moment decreed
In which concealeth
Full eon
entire existence
Don't thou dare ask why roads two
Cross thy path through
Thou art the one to resolve the road
Thou art the one to discern the code
Which direction? Whither dost the
path leadeth to true abode?
This country, thy soil
It's thy motherland!
She calls thee
This is a bond that can never be severed
I got it.
Just because you lit a bulb
now you have delusions of sparking
a revolution in the whole country.
You're being foolishly romantic!
Let's leave aside sentiments...
Have you figured out what you are
going to do there?
I have a few ideas.
- Like?
I could be a Project Manager for
Vikram Sarabhai Space Centre.
I can... I can work in tandem
with NASA from there.
There's a lot to be done there.
You're impossible.
I can't understand you!
If you can't understand
even after hearing all this...
... then its pointless telling you anything.
You'll have to come there and see things.
Otherwise you'll never understand!
We're just a few minutes away from the
launch of the GPM Spacecraft
on an important scientific mission to
better understand the global water
cycle here on earth.
GPM will allow improvements in
predicting precipitation forecasts,
and better predict flood hazards.
We are not tracking any technical
problems at this time.
All systems are GO on the launch vehicle.
Weather forecast is very good for today.
Just a few minutes away from
launching the GPM spacecraft.
This spacecraft will give us information...
... that will help us
better predict precipitation
In addition, we can
better predict flood hazards.
T minus 20 secs.
T minus 15 secs.
T minus 109876
We have a GO for main engine start
32 booster ignition...
.... and Lift-Off!!
John I tried to knock some
sense into his head
and tried to convince him
not to leave but...
Mohan, you do realize
what you are going to lose.
John, I know what
I'm going to gain.
But you're aware, you could
have gone places.
I am going places!
All right Mohan. Go light your bulb!
Nobody has ever thrown me like this.
Where did you learn
these wrestling tricks, Mohanbabu?
Where there is a will, there is a way.
Afterall, a marshmelon changes its colour
in company of another marshmelon!
Do you understand now?
Excellent match, Mohanbabu.