[The main suspect, involve in robbery,
Yuza, (31), please call 110 if see him ]
Yuza
Don't make me angry
Stop, Yuza
Don't run
No, help
Stop, Yuza
Let her go
Be careful, I'll kill this lady
You can't runaway
Yuza
What is your opinion about
the testimony yesterday?
Mr. Beiduo, please answer us?
Please answer, Mr. Beiduo
Mr. Beiduo, please tell us the truth
Are you bribing the mafia
with the money of buying organs
I don't remember such thing
You are using NPO's name
I don't know
Please give way
The children's life are deprived
Mr. Beiduo, please answer
Please answer our question?
Mr. Beiduo
What happened?
What happened
[ Law court ]
Ah, Maruo
See, he's out
He's out, he's out
Mr. Maruo
Murderer
Do you ask forgiveness
from the victims' family?
Please give way
You are very annoying?
The judgment is out
Maruo
[ Weird situations happened over all the
place, the cause of death is heart paralyse ]
[ The suspect dead of heart paralyse ]
[ 3 people die, it's hard to explain ]
[ It happens continuously,
the cause is unknown ]
[ Heart paralyse, 3 members died ]
[ The death is increasing ]
[ It happens continuously ]
Although the cause of
death were heart paralyse
but all the victims
didn't have medical record
Are these coincident?
Police is carrying the investigation
What happened?
[ The murderer was dead of heart paralyse ]
[ Heart paralyse again ]
Next it's the report of
the weird death recently
Minister of Health and
Welfare has announced today
they are starting the investigation
to figure out,
whether it's relevant with an unknown virus
153 cases are confirmed
Besides, all the victims were criminals
or suspects
Includes all the suspects
and criminals who are free from prosecution,
the same and weird situation
is happening in the world
Police is investigating the reasons
of the weird incidents in the world
Criminals who didn't get
the punishment under the law
now are punished by God and sent to hell
God is angry with sinful human beings
and gives the punishment
The light is with us
[ The legend of the Saviour, KIRA ]
[ The criminals are decreasing,
KIRA is alive, he will not tolerate to crimes,
he is the messenger from the hell ]
[ KIRA the saviour ]
KIRA is so powerful
Who is KIRA?
What's his background?
How come you don't know?
He is the saviour
[ Praise KIRA ]
[ KIRA, please kill as
many criminals as possible ]
[ Make the world peaceful ]
[ I would like to laugh at
those criminals who are in fear ]
KIRA merely kills people
[ Who is KIRA? What do he want? ]
[ KIRA is the angel who wants
to vanish the criminals ]
[ Although I can understand everybody's
feeling but I can't agree with KIRA's actions ]
[ Although he kills.
But he only kills criminals ]
[ KIRA is righteous ] [ I hope he
can kill the people who look down on me ]
Have you read the BBS?
No reply
No
[ I hope he can kill all
the bad persons around me ]
[ Name: Chu, KIRA is the best ]
[ Name: RD, Rubbish should be
placed in the bin, thank you KIRA ]
[ The victims are criminals,
KIRA is righteous ]
[ Name: None, KIRA is the devil,
he should be punished ]
[ I hope he may kill the people
who look down on me ]
[ Name: M, the crimes have decreased ]
[ Name: RD, thank you for giving us a good sleep ]
[ Name: M, nobody bullies me
in the school already, thank you KIRA ]
This
[ What do you think about KIRA? ]
He is a fake person in the internet
I think he is real,
this is the hot topic now
It's true.
I think this people exists
Actually, those who are dead,
were bad persons
I think his way is very dangerous
It's no use to let the bad persons to live
Kill my parents next time
Ah, just kidding
Breaking news
One of the money lending company
from Tokyo
is being robbed by a man
The suspect is figured out
This man is called Hiromitsu,
According to the police
Hiromitsu is 45 years old
His purpose is robbing
Please see the live situation now
Now, somebody is coming
out from the entrance
Special task force is entering the office
The criminal is inside the office
All the staffs are coming out
All the hostages are safe
The latest news
The criminal has died
According to the hostages
Hiromitsu was pressing his heart
and fell on the ground
Death again
The criminal who was reported just now
Yes
It's indeed KIRA
It was done by KIRA
Well done
It's powerful
You're really Light
You're really superb
How come you can get that ball?
Thank you
It has trouble you
How dare the future chief inspector gamble?
I'll treat you
I don't want to use your 'dirty money'
This is through effort
Originally I would like
to give you a treat today
Why?
I've seen the notice board
Congratulations on your law paper
but I am embarrassed
I am the one who wants to become police
Shiori you have your own pace, be patient
I hope I can have the same pace as you
I absolutely support KIRA
KIRA is the saviour
However, if you look from
the angle of human rights,
misjudgment cases and preventive theory
I totally do not agree with KIRA
[ Premonition! KIRA's killing name list!! ]
If compare with law study,
which one would help the world better?
It's KIRA definitely
My discussion group
is discussing KIRA's topic too
KIRA is a virtuous God to many people
It's too much to call him as 'God',
say he is 'virtuous' will show he's ego
Ego?
No matter what kind of criminals,
they should be punished by law
If I have the same power as KIRA
maybe I'll do the same things
One month before
I hacked into the police's database
How the bad persons committed crimes
What's their punishment?
Whether their punishment is reasonable
but I discovered
This is the limit of
what I believe in justice
These...
[ suspect, Zoitai ]
[ Robbed and Hurt people in Tokyo,
now he is hidden in Tokyo ]
[ Matsuda, free of prosecution, making
fake passports and sell it to mafia ]
Most of the heavy criminals
[ Unsettled law case ]
Due to many reasons, he has never
be arrested, and he is not punished
This is the confidential data [ Tako, killed
5 children, insane and never be prosecuted ]
[ One month before ]
You killed people but never be arrested?
Don't you feel it is unfair?
I don't know,
what have I done when I'm angry
Then
I heard some noises from far away
Noises?
What did they say?
They said let me kill you
I said only
Don't, it'll reduce your life span
Have you heard it?
When the judge announced
that I am not guilty
The crying from the parents
of the death children
Give my son back
What are you looking at, bastard
What?
Flash back
When the knife stabbed into the body
The feeling of stabbing inside
Why? Why I would be here?
I remember nothing
Nobody can prosecute me
[ Six, the law practice ]
The suspect Meiyuan
but I discovered
Robbed 120 things, worth 30 million yen
The name whose be written will die
[ The murder case of a high
school girl, today is trial ]
The murder case of a high school girl
which was happened October last year
Today he was brought to a trial
During the trial, the suspect
Mitashi did not feel regret
[ Mitashi, the suspect ]
The victim's family felt angry
The victim named Jojin
was 17 years old at that time
She was kidnapped by Mitashi
and killed by a knife in a garden's toilet
He exposed it to the media
He's cruel
Police is investigating...
Are you ready?
How about handkerchief and ticket?
I bring it
Goodbye
Ok
Ah, brother finally you woke up
It's so comfortable, university's student
Be careful, there are
many bad people outside
Yes, I've to go now
Goodbye
Light, eat quickly,
I want to do the cleaning
I'll eat now
[ Die in the prison ] [ Mitashi ]
Light, do you still want to eat?
The little boy last time
Death Note
[ Tako ]
Where's the pain?
Are you ok?
Somebody please help
Wake up, wake up
Wei, Tako
Tako
What is happening?
Wei, Tako
Tako
He is dead
Wei, what happened actually?
It seems you like it very much
Why?
Can't believe this is real?
Now it's the arrival of
the Death God (Shinigami)
I'm the master of that Death Note
Do you want it back?
Since the day you picked it,
it belongs to you
So do you want me
to pay it with my life?
I won't do anything to you
If you don't want the note
then you may pass it to somebody
At that time, I just have to
vanish your memory about Death Note
It really doesn't cost anything
If you really wanted to know
The person who has used the Death Note
will feel fear and miserable
However, you won't
Can other people see you?
Those,
who has touched the note, may see me
What's your name?
Are you interested to me?
Just call me Ryuk
Ryuk
[ 4 months later, Police Station ]
This case has no clue
The victims were scattered
around the world
The same point
is only they were criminals
Besides, they don't have any connection
What do you think, chief?
About the death of the criminals
there is no possibility of a new virus
Do you mean we should pass the case
to Ministry of Labour and Health
From my intuition,
this is a mass killing case
I will not allow absolutely
using this way to punish criminals
He'll pay for it later
[ Police Station ]
It has troubled you
Matshida, when did you returned to Japan?
Yesterday
ICPO judges the criminal in Japan,
so I come back
Why does ICPO have such judgment?
The first case has happened in Japan
Why does L think,
that the criminal is in Japan?
L??
Who is that L?
He has solved many
problematic international cases
He can be called as the
well-known secret detective
He is our last solution
Watari
He is the only
contact person with L, Watari
So everybody please listen to L's message
Japanese police officers,
how do you do, I am L
Now, the mass killing
that happens in the world
is mostly caused by a genius
These were mass killing
This is the epidemic disease in Asia
This the death information
caused by the virus
They're distributed according to their
gender, age, nationality, crimes history
It's called regular distribution
If it happens naturally,
it will appear in this kind of soft chart
And this is the chart of the mass killing
I see
So you're meaning,
these were not a natural occurrence
instead these were murder cases
Yes, let's call the criminal as 'KIRA' first
However, even if you confirm
these were done by people
but you cannot judge
these were done by 'KIRA'
Especially all the cases at
the same time in the world
If these were done by a group,
there were at least 80 criminals
The successful rate of 80 criminals
is almost zero
I can confirm
this case was done by personal
If we can't figure out the way,
of when he commits crimes in the world
this hypothesis is not correct
Through the front fighting
we may find KIRA through analysis
prove the way he commits crimes
How?
We talk later about this thing, please wait
Since now we establish an investigation team
Mr. Yagami, you are the leader
Yes
[ The legend of the Saviour, KIRA ] You may find
thousands of 'KIRA' WebPages in the internet
The whole world
knows the existing of a righteous person
That's KIRA, me
It seems you're having a good mood, Light
Everybody knows the bad guys are being
vanishing. Everyone is not dare to voice out
Innocent people will say 'KIRA keep it up'
Sinful people will be very afraid
The history is changing
Only the Death Note can create a
perfect world that is without crimes
The future is in my hand
This is righteous
The program discontinues for a while
ICPO
International Criminal Police Organization
Who is he?
ICPO
It is broadcasting in the world
My name is Lind L. Tailor, just call me L
This time I got the mission from ICPO
I am assisting in the serial killing
of criminals' case
First please let me do the exclaimation
This is the most cruel
case from the past history
The main suspect in this case,
we call him 'KIRA'
He is the uncommon people who has
the strong desire to show himself
The immature criminal who
is wearing the righteous mask
lmmature, indeed
I, L promise to catch KIRA
Please
KIRA, I can predict your thinking
It's because your actions are immature
You're sinful
KIRA, you are cruel than other criminals
You are also immature
Let the world see it, L
However, I know many
people are supporting KIRA
It is because KIRA punished those
criminals who haven't get the punishment
I am enjoy fighting with you, L
However, if we agree with your actions
then the civilization societies
will become the barbarian societies
40 seconds
L, are you ok?
Anything happened?
Bring him away, hurry up
What is happening?
It's so scary
Stop the broadcast
Call the ambulance
It is shocking me, I merely guess
KIRA, you are able to kill
people by not using your hand?
You listen, KIRA
The person you've killed just now,
is a death penalty prisoner
He had never be reported in the media.
He was arrested secretly by police
Through the law negotiation,
let him replace me
I'm still alive
Come on, come and kill me
It seems you cannot kill people at sometimes
Furthermore, I've got a
very important information
You are in the area of Kanto, Japan now
Although we claimed this is
live broadcast in the world
Actually it only broadcasts
in the areas of Kanto, Japan
It's because the first victim was
the criminal who was reported in Japan
So I focus you in Japan
Now the investigation's scope is smaller
Nice Out
This is not a game,
please watch yourself
I'm sorry
The investigation's scope is smaller
KIRA I'll arrest you and solve the puzzles
Then I'll send you to death penalty
Send me to death penalty...
I represent righteous
Righteous? I am the only
one who represents righteous
Save the threaten human beings,
I'm the God in the new world
Those who against this God are sinful
Both insist on righteous
are fighting one another
Human beings are interesting
Let me be the witness in this battle
I knew it
Chief, it's confirmed
The fake L
who appeared on the TV has dead
He uses this reasoning to
find out KIRA, L is amazing
Can we sacrifice the death penalty
prisoner for the purpose of investigation?
If we do so, we have no different with KIRA
[ Mysterious person L, who is he!?
L vs. KIRA,
police begins the investigation officially ]
Welcome home
Thank you
[ A genius killer,
KIRA vs. L, LIND L. TAILOR,
the death penalty prisoner,
dead in the live broadcast ]
Welcome, welcome
[ KIRA killed people in a flash,
killed the criminal in live broadcast ] Thank you
[ Officially investigation,
LIRA vs. Famous detective L,
used the death penalty prisoner ]
[ Famous detective vs. KIRA ]
[ LIND L. TAILOR, the death penalty prisoner,
dead in the live broadcast ]
[ KIRA killed the death penalty prisoner,
who is L? ]
It's really scary,
I thought it may be faked at first
Finally it was real
Sayu, what is your opinion to KIRA?
I think it's not so proper
since the police are here
Law court...
What happened?
The live broadcast yesterday
You're talking this thing
Good, come in first
Sayu
I've never thought somebody may get killed
through the live broadcast
Use the death penalty prisoner's life
as a bait
This is not proper
Light, you're really agree with KIRA
If compared with L
KIRA is a killer
This is different with Light's virtuous
Indeed, KIRA scares the criminals
He merely uses the terror to treat us
It's called 'revolution'
Normally some people
will betray to the revolution
Your girl friend is opposing you
You are annoying me
Ah, no.
Excuse me, we've better go out
Do we want to try?
Ok
Sorry, in the public...
Unless the situation is critical,
if not I can't make it
If she knows you're KIRA,
what would she think?
Shiori will have to understand KIRA
So L, now starts the investigation report
Thank you
According to L's instruction
This chart is drawn according
to the time of death victims
It has no special features
Do everybody know the
prinzip of probability?
The prinzip of probability?
The prinzip of Naturality which was
invented by Bernoulli in year 1718
[ One of the data appears many times ]
Can L see that?
I think it links with L's computer
[ Use the prinzip of average
to get the correct answer ]
[ Uses these data and
restructure according to 7 days ]
Is L controlling?
Em, it may be
What is this?
It seems I've seen this shape before
Ah, it's timetable
It looks like university student's timetable
From the third section to the
fifth section on Monday got class
Tuesday got class from morning time
Brother, you're having good mood recently
No
Any improvement with Shiori,
you must tell me
I've never promised you such thing
Oh, I want to listen also.
What is happening between both of you?
Dad
Ah, Light don't change the topic
You're back
Welcome home
Dad, listen to me.
Brother and Shiori
What are you talking about?
What are you talking about Light?
Come, today you're tired
It has been a long time I don't eat at home
You really look exhausted?
Why you mentioned really?
Dad, are you responsible for KIRA's case?
Why you think like that?
If it is not a heavy case,
then Dad won't be so stressed
I would like to help dad
Light, your reasoning really help us
to solve many cases all the way
You're really smart
I feel honour to you
I feel honour to you too
Really?
However, my opponent
is a devil killer-KIRA
who can kill many persons
without using his hand
I cannot involve you
However, if you hand over to me...
Cannot
This is my case
You should solve the cases
in 5 or 10 years later
Now you should prepare for that moment
Be patient
I understood, dad
So I go to study now
For 10 years later
Dad
However if anything happens to dad
At that time, I will send KIRA for execution
You've never thought about your dad
is the responsible person for KIRA's case
This is the daily report
in the police office
I am reading today's content
They know KIRA is a student
24 criminals die in a day?
Furthermore, one person for every hour
What happened actually?
The information about KIRA is
a student is not trusted anymore
This is not KIRA wanted to tell
What do you mean?
KIRA wants to imply he has the power
to control the time of death freely
Time of death? Freely control?
Wei, Ryuk
The afternoon after the
revolution is so peaceful
The rate of criminals has decreased
That's because of KIRA
The world becomes peaceful
and no more criminals
Who will expect this day is coming
What happened to you, Ryuk?
You don't want to eat today?
Don't worry, nobody will see it here
There is somebody following me, since when?
The morning before yesterday
Why you never tell me?
I am not at your side, so do L
I think he's police officer
No, police officer won't do so
Light, our shinigami are depend
on the human life span to live
What do you mean?
The names written in the death note
will die before the end of their life span
Shinigami will get the unused life span
So what do you think how
we get to know their names
You can see it
You're right
As long as we see the face,
name and life span will...
So you see my life span
and can see that guy's name
Don't you want it?
This pair of God of Death's eyes
I see, so what is the price?
Half of your remain life span
No talking
So how you get to know his name?
Sir, there's third victim in the prison
The criminal names Bai
hurt his finger inside the prison
wrote down a strange star's symbol
on the wall
left a letter by using a false name
and...
ran out from the prison,
30 meters away from the toilet
and died of heart paralyse
Mr. Yagami
About the victim this time
Please don't announce the information
other than he has died of heart paralyse
Reason?
KIRA might use the criminal
for his experiments
According to the water Department,
the tank is on the building
and the pipe is under ground
See, even though they do not announce
but the condition at the time of
victims death are recorded very clearly
It's unexpected that all the things happened
according to the written in the Death Note
It's amazing
[ Runaway after killing 3 banking officers ]
Today about 2:40pm
In a bank in Kanagawa
3 men with weapons stormed inside
Killed 3 banking officers,
robbed away 2.5 million
Police arrested 2 criminals
At the moment, police are in the
effort of arresting the runway criminal
The runaway suspect named Ozuki,
36 years old
have record of killing and drug possession
Ryuk
Will the people who touch
the death note can see you?
Yes, why?
Suddenly criminal Ozuki
shoots the bank staff
The situation becomes chaotic,
Janton and the other suspects...
The bus starts moving,
please watch your safety
It has been a long time
I haven't taken a bus
Actually since three days before,
somebody is following me
Why are you following me?
Are you a detective?
Who instructed you to do so?
I don't know what you mean
If you don't want to die
then follow my instructions
Don't move, sit well
Light
Contact your company
This is number 124 Joben... JoJoben
I'm hijacking a bus
If you don't want me to kill the
hostages then prepare a hundred million yen
I'll try to control him
Don't
It's dangerous
If it's critical, I'll do it
What's your background?
Are you trustworthy?
I am police's son
Release your hand
Wait
I'll save all of you
The people who is following other people,
how he's going to prove that he's innocent?
Partner?
You're purposely let other
think there is only one criminal
Actually you're afraid somebody
is watching from behind.
There has such case happened before
Good
FBI?
Name, name
Raye Penber
Wei, what are you doing?
Wei, you are so daring
What... what is that, the thing behind
Can you see me?
Don't kidding, since when you're there?
I see, that's paper from the Death Note
Bastard
Lean on the floor quickly
Excuse me,
I am Death God so you can't kill me
Stop, quickly stop
Yes
Ozuki, die in accident 29th March 2006
At 10:12am
drive towards Okugawa bus station
The Nanjing bus which drives to Okugawa
Taking a gun which has 8 bullets
Try to rob the profits of Nanjing Bus
but see the hallucination
and shoot it
[ Chest, pain ]
As the bullets has finished
so he gets down of the bus in fear
It will be ok
Wait
If you have anything to ask,
you may find me died in an car accident
I won't hide or runaway
You're back
I'm back
What happened?
Any problems?
No, nothing
When will we visit priest?
Saturday, can you make it?
Raye
Your opponent is KIRA
Don't force yourself
As long as there is instruction from L,
the people who don't care about their safety
is you
It's because you are here
These are the latest
letters left by the victims
L, do you know
Shinigami
Only eat...
Only eats apples
It's impossible FBI only send a agent
to carry the investigation
L thinks that KIRA exists
in the surrounding of the police officers
so he privately instructs FBI
to investigate the relevant police officers