The city is shocked
by the missing babies.
Within 3 months,
18 babies had been stolen.
No findings
have been reported by the police.
But I'm most professional.
There we are! Stop!
I'm coming!
Something wrong!
Damn! Forget it.
Be careful.
Let's go to the wonderland.
Please.
This way please.
It's a handsome and quiet house.
There is no people nearby.
Only 5 minutes' ride to market.
So many merits?
Of course, there's some defects.
But not that bad. Follow me.
It's perfect except that...
there's not been much renovation!
You call that renovation?
But the structure is ok.
It's just a little fire.
Darling.
Let me show you something.
Nature!
You move in and will love it more.
What do you think?
Damn!
I did ask to have it renovated first.
Wasting my time!
I'm lucky!
Jesus, even a jerk won't buy this!
Let's go...
Stay!
Darling. Buy this house. I like it.
It has character.
Character? Really?
You know what kind of house I like.
I know.
- So, pay a deposit first.
- Quiet.
Stealing my car? You go ahead.
Ok... we go ahead.
Incredible!
Of course, my hubby is a cop!
- Keep going!
- I do.
18 babies
have been missing these 2 months.
It looks like the work of one person.
So far, no missing baby's family,
they have received any blackmail letter.
Nor has any group claimed responsibility.
Commander, this is bizarre.
Shall we approach Wonder Woman?
Though she helped us before,
we still don't know who she is.
We can't reach her after all!
All missing babies are boys.
This shows it's not blackmail.
Maybe it has to do with evil religions.
Is anyone rushing out?
No.
Commander.
"Your son will be next."
Babies' ward is upstairs.
Operation Room over there.
I'm worried about our son.
Let's take him home now?
Lau!
If we bring away this new born baby now.
The doctor wouldn't
be responsible after discharge.
- Lau...
- Alright! Leave him here.
Why not call Wonder Woman for help?
Sorry we got no way to contact her.
I've sent more men here.
Things can go wrong anywhere.
- Please take care of my wife!
- Yes, Commander.
Come,
there was a traffic accident just now.
Warden said those beds might be needed.
He asked us to think about it.
You go out first.
Lau, it's my son they're after.
What about... Swopping?
Whose son?
That's too immoral...
It's your son they want.
Anyway, they will find him out.
Yes, if others know,
it'd be embarrassing!
Let's brace up.
Brace up...
Sorry.
Officer Lau said
no entry without permission.
Forget it!
What's wrong?
Catch them!
- My son!
- Take my son!
Which is our son?
Either can be!
Which?
Wonder Woman!
Its blood is left on the wall.
Not ours!
It's a baby girl!
It's my daughter!
I'm scared to death...
Get somebody to collect blood sample.
Yes, Officer Lau! Come with me.
Tung, one more baby is missing.
I'll be back late tonight.
Alright.
Are you sad?
No! Mind your work.
Bye...
I'll chop your head off next time.
Guard the door.
Master, here is the baby boy you want.
Take the 19th prince inside.
With other princes together.
Yes, Master.
San.
Your heart is beating too fast.
Not quite.
Memory does you no good.
Feelings and emotions too.
I don't have any.
I'll wait for the next propitious day.
And among the babies.
Choose one to be the king.
China must have a King!
Either you climb up by yourself.
Or you fall down! No one can help!
Climb up!
Ching, climb up!
Don't fall down!
Having a nightmare again?
May I come in?
I'm working. Don't disturb me.
I've been always
dreaming of the invisible robe.
Last night, I dream it finally worked.
Has it always been kept in the safe?
Yes, why?
The police called today.
Ask me how one can be invisible.
Before the invisible robe is finished,
you don't want others to know about it.
I want to keep it secret forever.
Because this invention
may easily be used
as a war weapon.
Then why're you still working on it?
This invisible robe mean a lot to you?
When I'm glued to my work.
I feel happy.
Aren't you worried that I may steal it?
No! People don't steal from themselves.
- Some coffee?
- Yes, please.
Miss.
The dates of birth of those 18 babies...
Are they related in any way?
Strange!
They are have a royal destiny.
All fated to be emperor!
Emperor?
Who's caught so many little emperors?
Sister!
You want some? Come over then.
Come on!
Are you talking to me?
No!
Sister, may I kiss you?
Why are you smiling?
Am I? Not really!
"Chemicals Factory."
Go down...
God! Who are they, Lau?
3 armed robbers with criminal records.
Just robbed a cash escort car.
And were driven there.
8 hostages inside,
including drivers and guards.
So, what to do?
We've getting them out.
Give me one!
Get ready!
Fire!
Don't panic, tear bombs only. Wear mask!
Come out! Damn! Get out!
Give me the revolver!
Don't fire!
Listen.
There're many more hostages inside.
Get me a helicopter within 2 hours.
Or I'll kill one every 5 minutes.
Good morning everybody!
Who's she?
Professional shooter-Chat.
Sir, don't call me that way.
I only kill those that deserve.
Call me thief-catcher.
The police won't hire you.
Hire?
Sir, I do you a favor this time.
It's free!
Get them!
I turn in, don't fire!
Rescue the hostages!
Lie down...
Go and see if there's others.
I'm married.
Only I can get your son back.
Pay me 500 thousand if found alive.
150 thousand if you don't mind he's dead.
I only take gold. Ring me if interested.
My phone number!
"The mysterious man confides,"
"the 19th baby will be missing tonight."
"And the time of his next crime."
"Apparently challenge the police."
The newspaper has been used!
The one placed the ad.
was not here for babies.
- Ask the others to be alert.
- Yes, officer Lau.
Mrs. Lau, you may go.
Please show me your pass.
What brings you here tonight?
I promised the head nurse
to come and help.
The old lady up there...
Won't do physiotherapy until you come,
right?
So you know already!
I'm busy, can't take care of you.
- Do take care.
- You too!
You're the one who placed the ad?
You're a cop?
Listen,
I'm going to kill all babies tonight.
What are you doing?
No...
Stand still, or I'll kill her!
Calm down!
Drop that! Or I'll kill her.
You drop it first.
- I'll kill her!
- Okay! I drop it!
Go inside! I'll kill her!
Go inside!
Those doctors killed my son.
This is revenge!
I'll kill at the babies!
Doctor Wong,
please hurry to Casualty Ward.
I'll kill all the babies!
You're bleeding! Wipe it off.
I'm fine!
Do you think we can break the door?
No way! It's so thick!
Let me try!
The keys are just outside!
Almost get them!
Keep cool!
The loony won't be back so soon.
I'm worried about the babies only.
You heard what he said just now?
Let me try!
Why don't you go?
Roger. Stay calm. Say it slowly.
- One only?
- Yes!
So late! New to here?
- Take him out.
- Yes!
Don't move! Get up!
I won't leave any baby alive!
Lau!
I subdued the loony already!
I know!
Thanks for informing me in time.
- I didn't come for nothing!
- Yes!
- Any reward?
- No!
Don't keep the old lady waiting.
Done already!
Naughty! Laughing at me?
Are you leaving with me?
No! The real one hasn't turned up yet.
What?
Why so surprised?
Busybody! Take you out for a ride!
Let's go!
Officer Lau, a baby is stolen.
Don't shoot! The baby might be there!
Attention. Don't fire!
Don't fire!
I'm leaving!
The thief-catcher?
Keep awake, more fun to come.
Isn't it fun?
So there you are? Follow me!
Take a rest first!
Can't believe it!
Lagging behind! What a shame!
So sinister, not even a noise!
A woman!
A bitch!
Why did you steal so many babies?
What? You blame me for that?
You look pretty smart...
So you're the Wonder Woman?
And you're the thief-catcher?
Don't get in my way then!
How can you use the baby as bail?
How despicable!
That's enough!
Put the baby down first.
Let's see if you can make me do so!
Warm-up just now. Ready?
Wait...
What's it?
The invisible thing?
One more?
It seems to be on my side!
The baby?
Be careful!
How's the baby?
Wait, who are you?
Everything's fine now.
Alright,
don't try my patience! Who are you?
Let's go, Chat!
San, it's you?
Let's go!
Don't pull me. I can walk on my own.
I suspect the thief-catcher you hire.
How do you know?
Ask her to bring the baby back at once!
Call the doctor.
How's the baby?
- Save him!
- Count on me!
To Casualty ward!
- Doctor, how's the baby?
- Sorry.
It's too late.
Call his parents.
Yes, Officer.
Ching, don't go!
Master hates dummies like me.
I'll miss you!
Take care of yourself.
Don't cry!
- Ching!
- Let her go!
Kneel down.
Tung, you must stay here.
And finish the task alone.
You're going to uphold justice for me.
On your own.
Tung, why are you crying?
No, I'm not.
Tell me why.
Nothing.
How's the case to-day?
The baby fell to death!
It's been 10 years. You're still great.
Where did that monster
get invisible robe?
He's behind all this.
Will you interfere?
No, thanks!
When I escaped from that cave,
you spared me though you caught me.
Now I take good care of myself.
Why did he catch so many babies?
He'll choose one to be king.
The rest to leave behind.
They'll become his killers, like us.
And turn them into our generation.
San, do them a favor. Simply kill them.
For 3 years, that monster corrupted me.
After I had escaped from him.
I spent 10 years returning to normal.
I don't want all babies
becoming monsters.
Pretend that you know nothing at all!
Leave this case alone!
If Master gives orders.
I'll kill you as well.
Do it then!
You won't be lucky next time!
Can I pretend that I know nothing?
You are not Ching anymore.
Start from today,
you are called San Chan.
Get the invisible robe within 10 days,
and kill the doctor.
Do it or you die.
"Copy"
What are you doing?
It's dangerous here. Go out please!
What's so dangerous? You're always here.
You're keeping something from me?
You knew everything already!
The invisible robe is belonged to us.
Yet I don't know that
it can stand UV light.
No, not now.
If it can,
you'll be the first one to know.
You kept your work secret these days.
I'm working on this plant.
They were dead before.
But they're alive again.
Any flowers?
Yes. In a month time.
Ching.
Will you put them under the sun everyday,
and water them at night for me.
Lucky stars,
you taught me how to make them.
You shall see the flowers bloom.
Get the invisible robe within 10 days,
and kill the doctor.
Do it or you die.
Your men kept me for over 2 hours!
Don't blame me. It's accident!
Accident? The baby died because of you!
What?
It's all the Wonder Woman's fault.
You may go now.
But you can't deceive yourself.
Don't make a scapegoat of me!
Ok, I'll keep an eye on it.
Mainly keep an eye on my son, Miss!
Don't worry. I'll help my client.
Thank you!
I'm asking for trouble!
Well done.
Why are there so many bird cages?
Oh no! That Monster's here!
You've got the needles.
Let's see how long you can stand!
You know who the intruder was?
No.
I have someone in mind.
But she should have died 10 years ago.
Right! I killed Chat myself.
Now only Wonder Woman could get in.
She's been meddling with our plan.
She's probably the intruder.
Let me kill her, Master.
Leave such things to others.
Kau,
kill the woman and,
if necessary, die with her.
You monster!
I won't let the needles go up to my head!
This case is not related to the others.
We promised the Mayor that
it wouldn't happen again.
Here's your deposit!
What deposit?
I quit the case of your son's business!
We'll talk later, I'm in the meeting.
No! Let's cut it off.
You must have got hold of something.
For the babies' sake. Please tell us.
What good does telling you?
If you can handle it you won't hire me.
For the justice you should...
To hell with justice!
I almost got killed!
You killed the child!
Tell me what you know!
You think I'll listen to you?
You will!
When that baby fell down just now.
You saved it without a second thought.
Yes, I killed the baby.
But I'm dying too.
Let break it even!
Won't you leave me alone?
I only want to die peacefully here.
I want to know who snatched the babies.
Don't hurt the Invisible Woman!
She's only a puppet.
That old monster!
I won't let his needles killing me.
Don't do that!
Go away before I lose my mind.
No.
You'll die!
If for a good reason, it's ok.
I can stop the needles
from going further.
But I can't get them out.
OK! I'll help you to get the babies back.
If we are to succeed,
we must get San to help us.
The Invisible Woman?
Yes! Before I find her,
we must be careful.
Because he found me entering his cave.
He thinks that was you.
So, he sends Kau out to kill you now.
A loony holds hostages in the station.
He has destroyed the computer system too.
A cargo train is dashing
toward the station now.
When will it be there?
In about 5 minutes.
I've got it.
All units get ready.
Mind the mines!
Don't step on it.
Don't move!
Be careful! There are mines!
Go now!
The train will be clash in one minute.
Go in! Save the hostages inside first.
Why don't you go in?
Run!
It's coming.
Wait for me.
Go to hell.
Let's go!
Supervisor, how can we stop the train?
The loony's destroyed the computer.
Can't stop it now!
Run! The train is here!
Take this!
Let's go!
Hubby.
What did the doctor say?
If lucky, you could walk within 6 months.
Otherwise?
Otherwise...
You may become a cripple.
Cheer up!
As Wonder Woman's hubby,
I'll stand by you.
When did you find out?
At the station,
when you looked at me,
unwilling to go in.
No more chuckling from now on,
and no more secret tears.
Just tell me everything.
Okay?
Oh, darling!
There's a flower bud!
What's wrong? Sit down first.
No, I just got a clue.
I must write it down now!
Sit down first!
Now, you go out.
How long have you known this?
I knew it.
When I was working on the invisible robe.
I found that it emitted toxins.
So I always tell you to stay out of here.
But the flowers have a bud already.
It tells we'll be alright.
Come on, get out of here!
How can I leave you like this?
Where are my glasses?
You're wearing them!
Before the robe is completed...
I will not die.
I can smell the fragrance of your hair.
"Don't cry"
Let's look at the flowers outside.
I'll be alright. You get out of here!
Let me in!
I'll stay even if you can get in.
The robe will be ready
when flowers bloom.
You promised to
take care of them till then.
You forget that?
San.
You still go to see that monster?
Anyway, he won't let the doctor live.
He'll kill him once the robe is finished.
You're poisoned by his needles?
If you help us.
Wonder Woman and I may kill him.
If you fear death, so why help her?
I won't thank you anyway.
You saved my life.
But to protect the doctor,
you let that monster control you.
You know you've harmed so many babies?
You can deceive others but not yourself.
Wonder Woman can help you now.
See you at the same spot tomorrow.
I'll wait till you come.
Don't fool me!
I can't wait, hurry up.
I'll made it!
Ching...!
Lucky star!
Ching, I make the invisible robe!
Why you still haven't got that robe?
It can't work under the sun yet.
Without it,
the king's army may be weakened.
It'll soon be finished.
Give the doctor a few more days.
Get it anyway,
before tomorrow sunset.
Kau will help you then.
Master, in your plan, all my work,
it is so inconsequential.
If I find a king among those babies,
you'll be honored for your services.
All princes should be asleep.
You should go to sleep too.
If they can all be invisible,
they'll be better fighters than Kau.
The world
will then be mine and the King's!
You see how important you are?
Yes.
The 18th of September.
Today...
I finally solve the UV light problem,
but that's the end of my life too.
From the first working day,
I knew I would die of toxins.
If Ching weren't here,
I wouldn't be able to face my life.
If she knows that I only hope,
to take her hands
and see flowers with her,
will she... still kill me?
The day will come soon.
Get the invisible robe anyway,
and kill the doctor!
Doctor, I'll never return to you.
I won't leave until I see you.
Believe me,
you are in great danger.
Leave the lab now!
Damn it! Even the Wonder Woman is late!
I shouldn't say wait until they came!
Should I leave or not?
Great. Here you're!
Master sent me to kill you!
- Wait, San.
- Just do it.
I won't let you go this time.
You can do it without any conscience?
I must execute Master's order.
But I can promise you.
I'll do you a favor after you die.
Wait! The one to die... May be you!
Tell me your last wish now!
Take care of doctor then.
Doctor?
Save Doctor for me.
San, what're you doing?
She's not coming to kill.
She came to kill herself.
You give up your life to save him?
My life?
I am just a beast to kill.
A beast won't have feelings.
Or sacrifice itself for another.
Life is meaningful
if you can face yourself.
I simply can't face myself.
I can't face him either.
San...
So you're all leaving?
Damn, can't you stay?
My own bike is better!
Wait for me.
San! You can change yourself from now on?
So what? I'm still San!
You can be another Chat! Like her.
Too late! Leave me alone!
Shit! Even a bike can't catch them up?
Go!
You've shunned the past.
So this is your true self!
I shan't live on then!
No!
God!
You two are in great trouble!
So lucky. Brace up!
Tung?
Ching?
Let go of my hand, or we'll both fall!
No!
Hold it!
I can't hold on any longer!
I won't let go! We must be together.
It's you!
You two knew each other?
I don't remember.
The past is not important.
But to-day, well lived.
Say! What do you want to do?
Master sent Kau to kill Doctor. Save him.
Doctor?
Give it to me.
The invisible robe is UV light-proof now.
Nobody can find it.
No!
Ching, I want to talk to you.
All inside the gife box.
However hard you hit, it's useless.
He'll stick to what he wants.
No!
You can't give him.
I've got nothing now.
I can't let him die!
Sorry!
Master can't make you kill me.
It's not that easy!
Wait...
Idiot, here's the tape. Come and get it!
Goodbye!
It's too hot to stay here.
It's better to have this thing destroyed.
Let's go!
You go first.
- What about you...
- Leave her alone!
Where are we going?
To save the babies from the cave.
Only two of us?
Let me get my stuffs first.
May I look at the blooming flowers?
All the babies are here.
Don't touch anything.
Babies will die if there's a fight.
Must have it done completely.
What are you doing?
It's a tragedy to see them grown up.
They're no longer human beings.
They'll all be like Kau, the beast.
If I were them, I would rather die.
No time for mercy!
Let's go!
Monster, come and let die!
Beware, there is full of methane.
Monster, like methane more than oxygen.
I'll kill you!
How dare you are to come here?
Attack her.
Supernatural power?
You kneel down? Where's your guts?
I can't help it! My legs get limp!
You think you can beat me?
It's no use kneeling. Guards, go.
Yes.
We've got no exit now.
Let's you get Master, I handle others.
Go!
It's an honor to die before me.
I'm excited. Is the methane caused it?
What to do? We can't get him.
Don't let him concentrate.
I'll kill you this time.
Tung, go with Chat.
No, I'll fight to the end.
No.
You'll get poisoned if you stay.
Go.
Get some oxygen first.
Go to hell, all of you!
He's blown up to pieces this time!
Why this one so late?
He's still alive!
To hell with you!
He's afraid of light!
Some more.
Is my face still looking good?
What?
I don't know if you're alright.
But you scare me!
He's not yet dead?
How can that be!
His body is gone,
but his mind still there.
He's gained control of me.
Let me help you.
Don't get near!
I can't control myself.
Go. Quick!
- Go with Chat.
- That way!
Ching.
Don't let me do it again.
Shit!
Go to hell!
Go!
You son of a bitch!
He's controlling my mind, go!
We won't leave you behind.
I feel so good to see you again!
Sorry!
San!
- San!
- Ching!
I'll die with you, monster!
China must have a king...
What's important is to-day, not the past.
China must have a king!
We watch the flowers bloom together?
Doctor!
Ching!
You won't die.
Get to the ground first.
Otherwise I'll die.
Are you alright?
Where's Chat?
Get something good.
Take one, or when the pass comes,
we'll look shabby!
Come on, put them on!
The police has solved the babies case.
Most missing babies have been found.
Here's our live report.
We heard that 3 heroines solved it.
How are they related to the police?
They are close friends of the police.
What are their positions?
No comment.
When will they come again?
When we are in need.
What are their names?
Their names?
They are called "The Heroic Trio".
When did we get that name?
Where does the name come from?
It's an improvisation only.