Up. Come on. Up.
[Groans]
Come on.
[Laughter]
His skull can't be
as thick as we thought.
[All laugh]
VIANNE:
It was like swatting a fly.
Ohh. The worst is over.
He found out
what you're made of.
[Laughs] So did I.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Mmm !
How long have we got?
She's at the hairdresser
for an hour.
[Gasps]
Fuffi?
CAROLINE: Fuffi.
I'm so sorry, but I have
to break the appointment.
FRANÇOISE: Is something wrong?
CAROLINE: No. I volunteered
to distribute these.
I promised the comte I'd have
them out by the end of the day.
FRANÇOISE: Count me in.
Not that I expect any of them
to stop by for a hairstyle.
CAROLINE: It's not just that.
The comte feels
we must stand firm.
We cannot trust these people.
Before you know it,
they'll be doing jobs for food.
They'll be begging
at our doors.
FRANÇOISE: Not at this door.
CAROLINE: Good, Fuffi, good.
[Exhales]
ARMANDE: Rub, rub.
Rub harder. Rub.
[Exhales]
ARMANDE: Rub. Rub.
[Luc exhales]
ARMANDE: Rub it. Hard.
Keep your head still.
- Aha!
- Bravo!
[Laughter]
[Vianne and Josephine
stop clapping]
Hello, Caroline.
ARMANDE: If you want to
blame someone, blame me--
corrupting him with cocoa.
Oh, how dare you, Mother.
He's happy. He's fine.
Look at him.
Mama, I--
Well, what about you, Mother?
CAROLINE: Are you fine?
I bet she has conveniently
forgotten to tell you.
ARMANDE: Carol.
Why don't you show them,
Mother?
Are you afraid to?
Why don't you show?
CAROLINE: Insulin shots.
She has diabetes--
very advanced.
CAROLINE: She could be blind
within a year.
Yeah. Couldn't you
call me a drug addict?
It sounds a lot more glamorous.
And you--
you sit here feeding her sweets.
ARMANDE:
There are worse ways to die.
CAROLINE: Why don't you
just give her rat poison?
It would be faster.
ARMANDE:
Carol has a flair for drama.
She needs to be in a place
where she can be taken care of.
Le Mortoir?
I'd rather be in Hell.
Ah.
You may get there, Mother.
Luc, come with me.
I don't want to.
He's happy here.
It's good for him.
I will decide what is good
for my son, Madame Muscat.
[Clink clink]
Give me another.
It's my life.
Let me enjoy what's left of it.
Fill 'er up.
Armande, why didn't you tell me?
Is this a chocolaterie,
or is it a confessional?
Don't you dare pity me.
[People chattering]
SERGE: Sorry, we're closed.
She just wants a soda water.
I don't serve animals.
[Serge lights match]
[Serge douses match]
Right.
[Humming]
- Hello.
- Hi.
I just made a fresh
batch of monduon.
Anybody interested?
My tummy hurts.
VIANNE: Oh.
I've got just the thing
for that. Come in.
ROUX: What about boycotting
immorality, then?
[Laughs]
Come in.
VIANNE: An old remedy.
From the cocoa tree.
GATI: Tastes strange.
Mmm. Maybe your daddy
would like a taste.
He's not my daddy.
He's my pony.
ANOUK: Here. It's a lot
better than those leaves.
Tastes good.
Come on.
ANOUK:
Pantoufle wants to meet you.
ANOUK: He's my kangaroo.
Go ahead. It's your favorite.
What makes you so sure?
Go on. Taste it.
Hmm.
That's fantastic.
Oh, thanks.
I have a knack for guessing.
It's good--
not my favorite.
Sorry?
[Gati and Anouk laughing]
All right.
Thanks very much.
You know, I could fix that,
if you like.
Not with glass, but...
I can make you a nice
strong one out of wood.
VIANNE: That's nice of you...
but I insist on paying you
for your work.
That makes two of us, then.
ROUX: Bye.
Thanks again.
REYNAUD:
She's laughing at us.
Now she's got one of those
river people working for her.
PERE: Is that a problem?
Christ teaches us--
Look at this.
She's soliciting for stalls
and street performers...
for a fertility celebration
on Easter Sunday.
She's cackling at us.
When are you going to do
something about it?
Oh, there.
ROUX: What part of Australia
is Pantoufle from?
ANOUK: A small town
outside of Sydney.
ROUX: What does he eat?
ANOUK: Leaves, bugs...
and worms, of course.
What about chocolate?
Kangaroos don't eat chocolate.
Has he ever tried it?
ANOUK: [Whispering]
Have you ever tried chocolate?
He's not interested.
ROUX: Not interested?
Mr. Pantoufle, you surprise me.
A world traveler
such as yourself...
not interested in new flavors?
You should be ashamed.
I have a very nice
truffle here...
JOSEPHINE:
if he wants to try it.
You're wasting your time.
Oh, I'm sorry.
[Roux hammers door]
How do you know
you don't like chocolate...
ROUX:
if you refuse to try it?
Do you like worms?
What?
How do you know
if you've never tasted one?
Ha ha!
Ah.
[Vianne and Josephine laugh]
Ew.
Subtle.
Zesty.
[Vianne laughs]
Disgusting.
[All laugh]
Go on, my little friend.
ROUX: Be free.
You tricked me.
PERE: Satan...
wears many guises.
At times, Satan is
the singer of a lurid song...
PERE: you hear on the radio.
At times, the author
of a salacious novel.
At times, the quiet man
lurking in the schoolyard...
asking your children
if he might join their game.
And at times,
the maker of sweet things--
mere trifles.
For what could seem
more harmless...
more innocent...
than chocolate?
[Sighs]
A bit of a squeak.
[Charly barks]
Hey, Guillaume!
I've got something new
Charly's going to love.
[Laughs]
[Whimpers]
Come on, Charly. Come on.
It's me. I should go.
No, it's not you. It's--
ANOUK: Uhh!
VIANNE: Where have you been?
I was worried.
Hey! I'm talking to you.
ANOUK: It's just like
all the other towns.
Anouk.
VIANNE:
Just tell me what happened.
Are you Satan's helper?
[Sighs] Well, it's not
easy being different.
ANOUK:
Why can't we go to church?
Well, you can if you want,
but it won't make things easier.
Why can't you wear black shoes
like the other mothers?
He's a fine piece of work,
our little nobleman.
No wonder his wife
goes gallivanting off.
She's been in Italy for months.
Did you know that?
Armande...
the whole town's against me.
[Sighs] What can I do?
Throw me a party.
VIANNE: Ha ha ha! What?
ARMANDE: Wednesday's my 70th.
Let's show the bastards
we're ready to go down dancing.
[Both laugh]
But a party?
You're not well.
You have to face it.
OK, OK, OK...
But you do this for me,
and I promise...
I'll check into Le Mortoir
the very next morning...
without a care in the world.
[Sighs]
If I threw a party in this town,
no one would come.
They don't need to know
who's throwing it.
Armande, listen, I--
No, no, no.
You listen.
I need this.
ARMANDE: Huh?
When I need help, I ask for it.
[Guitar music playing]
WOMAN: Boys,
bring me some more wood.
VIANNE: My mother
used to sing that song...
when I couldn't sleep.
And did it help?
[Playing guitar]
I still didn't sleep,
but, yes, it helped.
How's the door?
It squeaks.
- Does it?
- Ha ha!
How's Anouk? Is she well?
Oh, she's better. She's fine.
ROUX: Good. How are you?
I'm throwing a party...
If anyone shows up.
Thanks.
Who's invited?
A bunch of townspeople.
Tell me something.
Why do you give a damn about...
what these narrow-minded
villagers think?
You're not scared of them,
are you?
Coming to the party or not?
I can't.
ROUX: There's a boycott
against immorality...
and I must respect that.
That is a problem.
Then, I'll leave you with
this test of your convictions.
What is that?
Your favorite.
My favorite?
Is that right?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I'm undone--
but not my favorite.
Hmm.
I'll come round sometime...
get that squeak
out of your door.
[Wind blowing]
[Window bangs]
[Music playing]
A lot for you.
You see? It's perfect.
[People chattering]
[Chattering stops]
Bon appetit, everyone.
GUESTS: Oh!
Ahh.
[Whispering]
If the comte finds out...
ARMANDE: The comte isn't here.
He wasn't invited.
ANOUK: Is Luc coming?
I'm sure they have other plans.
Luc?
CAROLINE:
Why are you sleeping?
Hmm?
Are you not feeling well?
Happy birthday, Grandmama.
ARMANDE:
The invitation said 5:00.
LUC: I should have read it
more closely.
If you had, you'd know there
was supposed to be no gifts.
Don't worry so much
about the "supposed to."
LUC: Like it?
You made me younger.
Very diplomatic.
Mmm.
[Laughs]
[Laughter]
I have two announcements.
GUESTS: Shh!
Number one--if you like
what you tasted here...
you're going to love
my chocolate festival on Sunday.
Advertise on your own time.
What's for dessert?
That brings me to number two.
It is my duty to announce...
that there is no dessert
here tonight.
GUESTS: Oh!
WOMAN: No dessert?
VIANNE:
Because it's on Roux's boat.
Any complaints, see me.
[Music playing]
[People laughing]
Ha ha ha!
SERGE: Monsieur le Comte?
Who's there?
SERGE: I must speak to you.
MAN: Whoo!
You see, Monsieur le Comte?
You see?
There's Josephine,
that stupid cow.
Something must be done, Serge.
Something must be done.
["Caravan" playing]
- You done yet?
- Almost.
- Almost?
- Hmm?
ROUX: Come on, leave it.
You're done.
Come with me.
Come on.
I have chocolates everywhere.
What? You're all right.
Do you think everyone
had a good time?
Shh.
Mmm. Mmm.
Ha ha ha ha!
I'm tired.
Vianne, Roux.
Thanks.
This was...
Thank you.
VIANNE: I'll take you home.
Oh, for God's sake,
don't fuss.
You'll ruin
a perfectly decadent evening.
I'm not partial
to big, sloppy good-byes.
Ohh.
Armande.
[Rubs back]
Hmm.
LUC: I'll take care
of the dishes.
ARMANDE: I think I'll sleep
in my chair tonight.
VIANNE: Do you like it?
Taking your home with you
wherever you go?
Yeah. Why not?
Your way must be harder--
each time having to make
a new home from scratch.
Well, maybe this time
I'll get it right.
What do you mean?
Maybe I'll stay.
VIANNE: What?
Don't you ever think
about belonging somewhere?
The price is too high.
You end up caring what
people expect of you.
No.
Is that so terrible?
Having people
expect something of you?
How does Anouk feel about it?
What?
All the moving around.
No, she's fine.
She handles it beautifully.
She makes friends easily.
She has such an unusual...
She hates it.
[Vianne moaning softly]
[Laughing softly]
Vianne.
ROUX: Vianne, come on.
Come on.
[People shouting]
MAN: Get 'em out of here!
We need more! Hurry up!
Anouk!
CHILD: Mommy!
CHILD: Aah!
Anouk!
[People shouting]
No!
Jesus!
ROUX: Come back!
VIANNE: Anouk!
ROUX: Come back, Vianne!
VIANNE: Aah!
VIANNE: Anouk!
- Stop!
- No!
- Stop it!
Stop it! Stop it!
- Come back!
- No!
[Explosion]
[Crowd screams]
[Coughing]
No!
Come on!
[Both panting]
[Crying]
Why did you stop me?
It was too late.
[Sobs]
ANOUK: [Faintly]Mom!
There she is.
Oh, my God, there she is!
Mama!
Anouska! I'm coming!
Oh, my God.
ANOUK: You're hurting me.
VIANNE: Oh, my God.
[Cat meows]
[Vianne singing softly]
[Knock on door]
ROUX: I just wanted
to make sure that...
Yes, we're OK.
You?
And I came to say...
To say good-bye.
Yes, I know.
What?
Your boat.
You've lost your home.
No.
Just a way to get
from place to place, really.
So, how will you...
I'll manage.
[Sighs]
Well...
VIANNE: Well...
Vianne...
Listen, I...
VIANNE: I know. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Your papa used to ride this bike
every single morning.
He would have wanted you
to have it.
Just you promise me
you'll never run away again, OK?
LUC: Mama, she...
CAROLINE: What?
What's wrong, Luc?
PERE:
Though we cannot know...
Armande Voizin's
last thoughts...
we can hope they were
thoughts of penitence.
We can hope she asked God...
to forgive
the self-indulgence...
that aggravated her illness
and caused her death...
and we can pause
to reexamine our own lives.
We can resist those...
who would lead us
into temptation.
PERE: Blessed is the one
who endures temptation...
for when he has stood
the test...
[Wind blowing]
ANOUK: Mama...
Can we go home now?
Of course.
Whatever you like, Mama.
Vianne, did you want me...
to start the ganache
for the festival?
Vianne?
Did you--
What are you doing?
VIANNE: Leaving.
First thing in the morning.
Is it because of Armande?
That was not your fault.
It's time, that's all.
This is who I am.
Did you believe
anything you told me?
JOSEPHINE: Did you believe
I could be better?
Was it all a joke?
I have to pack now.
If you leave,
everything will go back...
to the way it always was.
It is the way it always was.
Not for me.
CAROLINE: I know how you feel.
REYNAUD: Beg your pardon?
I suppose it can't be easy...
having her gone.
Can't seem to get used to it,
no matter how much time.
Ahem. But I...
look forward to her return.
I don't believe anyone
would think less of you...
CAROLINE: if you were to say
she was never coming back.
Good night, Paul.
[Panting]
Caroline!
I'm sorry.
I need to talk to you.
[Knock on door]
Come in.
Monsieur le Comte.
It's all right.
Sorry to bother you,
Monsieur le Comte.
REYNAUD: All right.
It was the right thing to do,
wasn't it?
SERGE: Of course it was.
I know it was.
It's everything with Josephine.
REYNAUD: Serge...
What are you talking about?
SERGE: The fire,
Monsieur le Comte.
I know it was
the right thing to do...
but I can't get rid of
the faces and the screams.
The fire...
The fire was an act of God.
It was me, Monsieur le Comte.
[Sighs] What?
You told me. Remember?
SERGE: "Something
has to be done, Serge."
You did, didn't you?
People could have died.
REYNAUD: You want
their blood on your hands?
On--on my hands?
Should I go to Pere Henri
and ask for forgiveness?
Listen to me, Serge.
Listen very carefully.
REYNAUD: You must leave
this village at once...
and never return.
Why would I leave
my home and my cafe?
Because I'm evicting you,
that's why!
What you have done
puts you beyond anyone's help...
beyond my help, anybody's help!
Now get out!
Unless you will tell the police
what you've done!
REYNAUD:
Get out! Get out! Get out!
Oh.
[Wind howling]
[Softly moans]
VIANNE: Time to go.
Hmm?
Oh, no.
I'm not going.
Well, it's hard for me, too.
Pantoufle hates this.
VIANNE: Stop that.
Please put it on.
I hate you.
You're entitled.
I said put it on.
Ouch!
Well, then, do it your self!
I can't!
Get up.
I have a bad leg like Pantoufle.
Stop that. Get up.
ANOUK: Pantoufle can't walk.
I can't walk.
Walk. Walk!
You're hurting me.
Well, stop being...
[Grunts]
Let me go!
No!
It's not fair!
Stop it!
I'm not going!
It's--Stop it!
[Vianne gasps]
I'm sorry, Mama.
ANOUK: I'm sorry.
ANOUK: Don't worry, Mama.
The next time will be better,
won't it, Mama?
It will.
ANOUK:
It will be wonderful.
I'm ready to go now, OK?
[Banging noises]
[People talking]
[People talking and laughing]
[Indistinct conversation]
LUC: Like this, Mama?
CAROLINE: That's right.
ALPHONSE: Is this right?
No, no, you've got to cut
on the corners like this.
So, just stop them.
CAROLINE: Higher.
How do you like these almonds?
JOSEPHINE:
Are they chopped fine enough?
Are they OK, Vianne?
PERE: Christ is risen.
My friends, let this Easter Day
be for us, too, a rebirth.
Let us strive--
REYNAUD:
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, don't bury
the word "rebirth."
Let it ring out.
Let this day be
for us, too, a rebirth!
You see, we are extolling
our--our parishioners...
to--to resurrect
their moral awareness.
Hmm? OK, good, good.
T-try again.
I think we've
gone over this enough.
Let's call it a day.
What?
I'm very tired.
Fine, fine.
Well, leave it with me.
I may have one
or two suggestions.
Thank you, Monsieur le Comte--
Just a couple of suggestions.
A revision here and there.
We want it to be perfect
tomorrow, don't we?
- Yes.
We must resist the shallow,
worldly temptations...
of our mortal--No, no.
We must renounce shallow,
worldly temptations...
of our mortal flesh.
[Women talking]
[Reynaud gasps]
Caroline.
All my efforts
have been for nothing.
I've suffered willingly.
I've fasted.
I've hardly eaten for weeks now.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry,
my suffering is nothing.
It's just that I...
I feel so lost.
I don't know what to do.
Tell me what to do.
[Grunts]
Aaah!
[Grunting]
[Gasps]
Huh.
[Panting]
[Grunting]
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
[Laughing]
Ohh!
Unhh!
[Laughing]
[Sobbing]
[Pere whistling]
[Fizzing]
VIANNE: Drink this.
Drink this.
It'll refresh you.
I promise.
Go ahead, drink.
I'm so sorry.
I won't tell a soul.
VIANNE: Hmm.
Better get cleaned up.
Easter Sunday.
The sermon.
I didn't finish it.
I'll think of something.
I'm not sure what the theme
of my homily today ought to be.
PERE: Do I want to speak
of the miracle...
of our Lord's
divine transformation?
Not really, no.
PERE: I don't want
to talk about His divinity.
I'd rather talk about
His humanity.
I mean, you know, how he
lived his life here on Earth.
His kindness.
His tolerance.
Listen, here's what I think.
I think we can't go around...
measuring our goodness
by what we don't do.
PERE: By what we
deny ourselves...
what we resist...
and who we exclude.
I think we've got
to measure goodness...
by what we embrace...
what we create...
and who we include.
[Pipe organ playing]
STORYTELLER:
It was certainly not...
the most fiery sermon
Pere Henri would ever preach...
nor the most eloquent.
But the parishioners
felt a new sensation that day.
A lightening of the spirit.
[Accordion music playing]
STORYTELLER: A freedom
from the old "tranquilité".
Whoa! Fantastic!
Monsieur le Comte,
try one of these.
Thank you.
STORYTELLER:
Even the Comte de Reynaud...
felt strangely...
released.
Although, it would take
another six months...
before he'd work up the nerve
to ask Caroline out to dinner.
As for Josephine...
she took over the lease
at the old cafe...
and gave it a new name.
[Wind howling]
[Door banging]
STORYTELLER: But still
the clever North Wind...
was not satisfied.
[Inhales]
STORYTELLER:
The Wind spoke to Vianne...
of towns yet to be visited.
Friends in need,
yet to be discovered.
Battles yet to be fought.
By someone else...next time.
And so it was,
the North Wind grew weary...
and went on its way.
When summer came
to the little village...
a new breeze from the south
blew soft and warm.
Just needed an adjustment.
Hope it'll be better now.
ANOUK: Roux!
STORYTELLER: My mother
knew Roux's return...
had nothing to do
with a silly old door.
So did I.
I thought you'd never guess.
My favorite, hot chocolate.
I knew that.
STORYTELLER: As for Pantoufle?
Well, his bad leg
miraculously healed...
and he hopped off
in search of new adventures.
I didn't miss him.