Yao?
Last night outside a hotel in Tsimshatsui
Mr. Lee Fung
was attack by a man
His driver & a bodyguard
were also killed in the incident
The case is now with the homicide squad
Police also urge any citizen
who witness the incident to report
to police
- Who are you?
- Order delivery.
- Teddy Wong
Your still trying to run!!
Why are you looking at my upper part?
Why are you looking at
my lower part first?
You two, stop looking at each other
- Look at me instead.
- Who's he?
He's your assistant Teddy Wong
Normally I won't assist those
Who can't beat me in 5 seconds
Well then, how long did he take?
I forget but I think he passed the exam
- Why are you staring at me?
- Well you staring at me first
Staring at you for I want to see clearly
what kind of fool are you
I'm staring at you for I'm wondering...
If I can tear your skin off this time
Come on, I Have been standing there
for a century
you guys are still staring at each other?
Shut up, you're only supposed to be
an assistant
My dear lady, I'm just reminding you
The Organization is very satisfied
with your work.
Your next target is the godfather
of the largest gang in Japan
Kishudo
Come check his details out
Ok
Mr. Kishudo
Where is Frank?
Who are you?
I'm police officer Sunny.
I am here to protect you
Protect me? It's not an easy job
That's my responsibility.
I'll do my best
They are my subordinates
Very well then, watch out for strangers
at the front door
Miss Huntress
Sir, your cigarette...
Be careful of the ashes. There is an
ashtray over there
Please use it
Ash tray, Boss
Mr. Kishudo
Protect Miss Huntress
Wait, I'll do it!
Mr. Kishudo! Mr. Kishudo! Mr. Kishudo!!
Yao!
Do you know that person?
- Is this the one?
- No
This?
No
- This?
- Yes
Miss Yip, we want a face
not a mask
Well, but that's what I can see
I can't possibly see through the mask
Then who's Yao?
Why did you keep calling his name
Because his physique reminding me of
an old friend
Then where is he now?
- Gone.
- Gone?
Please cooperate with us
We know everything about you
You're a Manchurian.
You used to live in the USSR
You fled to USA a year ago
Yet, what make you come to HK?
You can get the answer
in your file, sir
I come to teach dancing
You've seen his face
He'll definitely come back
I don't think he'll kill an innocent woman
Miss Yip could you put your confidence
into a stanger?
What did she say?
She didn't utter a word
You know how each of us invested in HK
If we don't finance your government
for another cross harbour tunnel
You probably have to swim across the
harbour everyday
We're responsible to protect Mr. Kishudo
3 hours ago
Now you're responsible
to arrest the murderer
- I understand...
- I'm sorry
If we have any further evidence
We'll keep you informed
Miss Yip, I've heard that you know,
the murderer
- No.
- Thats good then
because if you saw him,
he will definitely come after your life
He won't let you go
A good citizen
should always cooperate with the police
All I saw was a washed face
Everyday I live like a mad woman
I wore this sweater with Yao's close up
printed on the front
I went searching for him. They all thought
I'd lost my mind
But I simply couldn't think of
any other way besides this
They arrested me 4-5 times
They locked me up and kept asking
But I never gave up
I knew that he would not desert me
Unless he died
I lived like this for an year
He's not dead. I feel, we've been
getting closer
The man I saw today, could that be him?
But the Yao I knew would never kill
- It's you.
- Yes, me. Miss Yip
You come to kill me?
I'm sorry, If you didn't see me and
identify me,
I wouldn't have to kill you.
Are you Yao?
No, my name is Freeman
Always wearing a mask & killing
And you think free?
I don't know, anyway
You'll be my first woman to kill
May I have a better look at you?
I want to know you're not Yao
Alright, look carefully
I'm May Yip
You've never seen me before?
Yes I have
Outside hotel
Do you remember me, then?
I remember you always
I have to kill you then
Yao
Why do you always shoot from the back
Alright, I'll do it again in the front
I'll destroy this place
Tell me,
will you return to take me away with you
Isn't he taking you to the hospital now?
How about the last time?
So there was the last time
I told you you've met this woman before
Do you love me?
I'm sure he does
Yet he'll be in deep trouble if you're
not dead
Can you promise me one thing?
I'll promise whatever you say
Don't speak, you're bleeding
Close your eyes
Drive faster!
I'm driving very fast
I hate it when a gun is pointing at my head
Then don't pretend to be a hero.
Heroes can be assholes too.
Why didn't you kill the girl
Cause she looks good
I guess that's just natural
At that time, I indirectly killed an
innocent girl
I don't want another one
Then tell me
Are you falling for her?
I don't know, don't keep asking me
I don't care whether you like her
She can identify you
You have to kill her, forget it
Mr. Frank will go to pay respect
to Kishudo this Wednesday
This will be your only chance
Mr. Frank
Hold my gun and wait out there
Both the dead and I want some peace
Here is my gun
Unmarried, you shouldn't have to be a nun
Sir, please donate some money
for renovating the church
Ok, for the beauty of your Angelic face
Keep it
Close the gate
Down!!
So you're that old fool's new student
You are the one to come for me
I came to avenge for Pearl
You were just lucky that time
You won't be so lucky today
Lets see who's lucky this time
Those who see me
I will kill them!
never want to kill me
Next time you go to a church,
Wear more clothes
You worried that I might catch a cold, dear?
I'm afraid God might like you too much!
What?
If I want you to hold me,
Will you always hold me like this?
Yes, of course I will
You have everything now
Quickly, send me to the hospital
I don't want to die here
Hurry up
Bow, second bow, third bow
Thanks from the family
Madam, there's something I've to tell you
Don't say anything.
You can tell me instead
Frank's my husband, leave this to me
Sunny, please this way
Sorry, but this is my duty
Yes, we are Triads
But Kishudo treated me very well
Even I didn't love my husband anymore
he was still my husband
If you need to search, please go ahead
Thanks for your cooperation
Although we didn't get along fine
I won't let anybody fool around
with your coffin
Search me instead if you insist
I am not a good woman anyway
I'm Frank's Wife, your not afraid?
Me? Of course not
You'll find I'm a lot of trouble
Oh? You bite or you fight?
Well you just won't find me easy
I don't think so! At least you're easy now
Though I didn't love Frank
he still was my husband
So please try your best
to arrest the murderer
Don't worry, that's my responsibility
I don't want a murderer, I want a dead murderer!
I will only arrest the murderer alive
But, to bring in a dead murderer,
I won't be able to do it
I know you can do it,
because
what we did earlier has been recorded
Why did you do this?
Well I've told you
I'm not a good woman
but I'm not ungrateful
Just that I have no other choice
I have no other choice
May I borrow your shampoo?
Sure
Cold? You look very pale
Yes, it's only 1 degree out there
- You switched on the cold water
- Yes, I know
- Oh, nothing. I thought the shower
was out of order. - Thanks
You handed me the conditioner
Wounded by bullet?
No, it's just an old wound
You didn't kill her
- I will kill her.
- Yes
You gonna save her? Kill me first!
I don't care what you say
I'm having fun here
Frollicking? Okay I won't interfere
Kill that woman
- Don't move!!!
- Yao
If anything happens to her
I'll kill you
Kill me then
Go
- It's mine turn now?
- Go to hell
Because of this sweater
I've been arrested a number of times
For being a hooker?
For disturbing social peace
I wore this day & night
Running around searching you
Also these Rubles are yours
Some extra left after you bought me
the Xmas present
You've been hanging on to this money
and the sweater?
Why did you get marry again?
Again, I wasn't even married to you
So you're not my wife
of course not
I don't get it, what a silly girl you are
What did you think they are doing
Throwing the garbage into the sea
You stupid, they are denying this wish
To a place
Wonder if they can get as far as USSR
Yeah, that reminds me of my childhood
I used to send my wishes to my mother
Stop bluffing. You are orphans
We grow up together in Russia
We don't know who were our parents
I almost forgot
You know everything about me
Here's a wish for you
You made this with the Rubles
Guess if I put some money in
you probably know better than I do
It's great I mean the atmosphere
I mean the food
Goodness the lighting makes me dizzy
After all that I'm glad
We are finally back together again
Hmm, it's strange
I feel I've been here before
- You remember?
- Remember what?
Start to count down from 30,29,28
29,28,27,26
People say it's best to make a wish
at midnight
Sure close your eyes
Alright
I wish that we'll never apart
19,18,17...
I wish I can always be with Yao
Merry Xmas!!!!
I sincerely wish that your silent night
can be a peaceful one
Why did you come out here?
I want to make a wish
A wish? What did you wish for?
I wish that we will never part
Lie. You've been eavesdropping on me
Stop, no, stop playing
May, if you never found me,
what would you do?
I'll continue looking for you
Till I'm old with white hair,
I'll still look for you
So, you'll be old and ugly
Even if you find me, I won't recognize you!
How did you think we'll spend our
Xmas Eve together when we grow old
Just like the old couple we met just now?
I think you like me very much
No, you'd like me more, Come on
This is a Hong Kong policeman
Have you ever seen him before?
Why are you crying?
It's you, your dripping saliva
You are wishing that we'll never apart
I'm wishing that we'll live happily
ever after
Oh, there's someone
Hardly ever in my life
I'd be nice to anybody
But I'll break it once for you. Car's is
over there. Go
Thanks
Yao, there's a lot of weapons
- Hurry up
- Bye
May, I don't know where I should go
Tell me dear, do you want to come
with me
Even in death, I'll follow you.
Let's go
It's so dangerous for you to be with me
They are only after me
You better run for your life
I'm not leaving you
Hong Kong police, my name is Sunny
This guy has committed
serious criminal offence
We come to arrest him ok
This is Sunny from the Hong Kong police
Come, this guy committed serious offence
Please cooperate
We'll force our way in
What?
First unit get ready.
Fire
Don't cross the border
Stop! Before we fire
- How about now?
- Sit tight
Jump over here
- May! Jump!
- How about you?
Don't worry about me! Hurry up and jump!
Take care!
Yao!
Damn it, the car is gonna blow!
Jump on!! Quick!!
- That woman!
- Bring her out!
Go bring that woman back!
Why are you so cruel?
That's my way of handling problems
I believe in justice
Not power
Do you love me than?
I don't think this is the right time for
this topic
Fine, we'll cut the crap, just get her in car
Bring her to the car!!
Where is Yao?
You'll see him soon
Master, I've brought May here.
You are the one Yao falls for?
Master, aren't we supposed to
get rid of her?
You are the one I should get rid of
betrayer!!
Don't panic. I won't kill you
For that I've to wait for Yao
Why did you bring me here?
This is where you came out!
If you want to rescue May
from the dead Master
You simply have to go right back
Put this robe on
Yip, Let's see who's the Lucky one this time
It's either Yao or me
It's you!
I said that I'll personally kill
Any of my students
Well, my student kill me today
- Yao!
- May!!
Yao! Yao! So you have finally recovered
your memory!
Dont' say anymore
I don't want to know about the past
All I care now is that I am finally free
and deep in my heart I only wish
For one thing
I want you to come with me
Would you?