10 minutes, just 10 minutes to go
we'll make it, no sweat
Eight, seven...
Six, five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One!
Happy New Year!
The first fatal accident this year
happened at 12 midnight in London...
two blocks from Trafalgar Square
where the 1997 countdown took place...
Mum, it's Dad!
Rubbish, it's not your Dad
Look, it's really Dad!
Can't you tell it's Dad?
Shut up! It's not him!
Dad's doing business in Hong Kong.
How can he be in England?
- But it's true, look!
- This is not him!
Mum, what are you talking about? Look!
We've got to go to London right now
This is not true and I am not going!
- Happy new year, mate
- Same to you, mate
So, you're saying, that the deceased
gentleman was your father...
but the woman who was with him
at the time of the tragedy...
was not your mother
Well, I mean... yes...
So, who was she then?
She's my mother
Sir,
this is the young lady from Hong Kong
And your father couldn't come either,
I suppose
Yeah
Hi, I'm his son, are you her daughter?
Are you two related in any way?
Listen, I don't know him,
and he doesn't know me
Only my mother knew his father
and that's about it
You understand now? That's all
They didn't just know each other,
sweetheart
We checked with
the Royal Hong Kong Police...
and were informed
that they had a joint bank account
in Hong Kong...
and they had a house there
under both their name
Their personal belongings
You may take
your respective parent's bodies
home after the autopsy...
Or you can have the bodies cremated here
in London
But it'll be a lot less complicated and
everybody will be
a lot less miserable...
if you have the bodies cremated here
in London
But it's up to you
God of hope and giver of all comfort...
We commend to your tender care those
who mourn the loss of loved ones
Give them the peace
that passes all understanding...
and make them to know that...
neither death nor life can separate them
from your love
We have entrusted Raphael and Vivien
to God's merciful keeping...
and we now commit their bodies
to be cremated
Ashes to ashes, dust to dust
In sure and certain hope
of the resurrection to eternal life...
through our Lord, Jesus Christ...
who died, was buried,
and rose again for us
To Him be glory for ever and ever
Amen
I'd like to go to... 138 Pokfulam Road
What "flam"?
Quick! what's this?
I can't read your hand-writing
Driver, please reverse a little
Miss, this is not even a pick-up zone
And you have the nerve to ask me
to reverse?
Do as I say
The meter's leaping anyway
You'll buy that, Brother?
I want to go to Hong Kong U...
What 'You'?
Hong Kong... Hong Kong University
Hong Kong University, that's a big place
Step aside, I'll do the talking
The house is not far past HKU
Just before Queen Mary Hospital,
turn into a downhill road
And go right up to the end, that's it
You, remember to lock up
The house isn't yours alone
You look so dumb
Remember to go to the lawyer's office
at Prince's Building tomorrow
Do you know where Prince's Building is?
It's in Central
Do you know where Central is?
Look, I was born in Hong Kong
I know where Central is, OK?
If you're born in Hong Kong,
don't speak English, show-off
I hate that girl
I hate this city.
I hate this whole damn thing
What the hell am I doing here anyway?
That girl is just like this city...
a bunch of flashes
and inside nothing
Gotta finish everything as soon as
possible and get the hell out of here
Hong Kong, my ass!
Well, Uncle Derek?
Just call me Derek
Though I'm your Dad and Mum's friend,
first name will do
Then please go on, Derek
In fact
I've known about their affair all along
Once I was thinking one day
I'll be handling their divorce cases
Yeah, Mum says
you're most good at divorce cases
A connoisseur!
I handle all divorce cases
that make cover stories
of Gossip Weeklies
You knew my Dad very well?
Of course, as well as could be
We went to university together
as fellow Greenhorns,
ragged by "Seniors"
It's like going through
the Vietnam War together
How could I not know him well?
We are the champions! We are the heroes!
We are the Ricci boys!
We are the champions! Champions are we!
We are the heroes, always will be!
Ho Sai Hall girls, pretty and sexy
Ho Sai Hall girls want to be my wife
Born beauties, but all as so lonely
Attracting bugs, rats, cockroaches rife
Raphael gave all
he'd got in doing anything
Sometimes even the boys felt
he's going too far
That time the Seniors
wanted to stub his pride
They punished him to use 50 dirty words
in one sentence...
and to yell it out in public
Every word had to be a swear word,
that's tough
In HKU's history only James Wong,
Andrew Wong and your Dad did it
Vivien was punished by her Seniors too
She had to go to a designated store
to buy ice-cream...
and give to
the Chairman of Ricci Hall Association
She's not allowed to take a ride
but to walk back up
And the ice-cream must not melt
It was August-September weather!
You rag freshmen this way now,
they'd sure complain
It's no big deal
No big deal? It's very big deal
Human Rights Law,
Equal Opportunities Commission
Environmental Protection Department...
They'd definitely sue your pants off!
On second thought,
if you want to sell the house...
you'd better wait till your parents
return and confirm by signature
Lest you two have any arguments again
But you can put it on the market now
Ask them to come back
when you've finalized the terms
Well, whatever
David, remember to take Buster with you
when you go
Maggie, please bring Buster in
Buster? Who's Buster?
You mean they've even got a kid...
No, Buster is the puppy
your Dad and her Mum kept
Every time they went abroad
they left him with me
Quiet, don't be naughty
Why me? Why not her?
Well, "see a man about a dog", right?
Come on, Buster, be good...
- Hubby, there's a lot of leakage stains.
- S'that so?
The leak-proof here is lousy
Wife, d'you think there're termites here
No, we've lived here so long and
haven't seen one termite. Relax
But this house is very tattered
Course not, it's only 5 years old
The paint on the wall's a bit cracked
just whitewash it. Relax
Renovating this place will cost a lot
Course you've got to brush up a bit
before moving in
Madam, this place suits your fancy?
This place is out of the way,
and this shack is worn-down
Cut the price
Madam, come on
It's a quiet surrounding
See the beautiful seaview?
It's hard to find in Hong Kong
Miss,
we're just an ordinary household...
buying a house to live in.
Our kids are small
This is a remote spot
Don't ask for too much
Quiet surrounding and nice view?
That's good for keeping a concubine,
means nothing to us
Forget it then, We're not selling!
OK, Miss, meet you half-way,
I'll up$0.2M
Not selling! Not selling! D'you hear?
Young man, you're a sensible one.
How about this shack?
You heard? This shack's not for sale now
Go shack-up elsewhere
Let's go, wife.
Our money's good for any house
Scumbag!
People nowadays are so foul mouthed,
all babblers
Yeah, your Mum's hardly a concubine,
at most a mistress
Why don't you dry up? So what's your Dad
Gigolo? Paramour? Or home-breaker?
And don't forget
your Dad and my Dad were friends
"Thou shalt not covet thy friend's wife"
know that one?
Don't you try to intimidate me
with big words
How d'you know it wasn't your Mum
who seduced my Dad?
How dare you suggest my Mum's a seducer?
Say it again and I'll sue you for libel!
Lunatic!
I don't know what you are talking about
Banana, stop speaking English
It's out of fashion
Now we go for mother tongue teaching.
Practice your Putonghua
Who cares what's fashionable
in Hong Kong?
You ugly Hong Kongers
rude and money-grabbing
I don't know
why my Dad would fancy your Mum
Got to be bad taste!
I don't know
what my Mum saw in your Dad either
loud bugger
Who're you calling bugger?
You and your Dad and your dog
limp and loud cur!
Buster! Shit!
Buster, no!
Come on... come on
Hey, no!
What a dog! Be careful!
Uncle, please page Room 432 for me
Just call me Henry
They've been calling me
Henry for 52 years
432, please come to Reception
She seems to be out
Right, what's the dog doing here?
He belongs to 432
I'll leave him here
Please give him to her, OK?
No can do. Dogs're not allowed here
It's against the rule, you know?
I don't really care.
I've enough trouble as it is, you know?
Young man, relax,
I'll figure it out for you, OK?
Rules are sometimes made to be broken
Take the female residents in the past,
after midnight...
Henry, please page 432 again
Come on now
What's the hurry?
You must be courting 432
What's that?
432 is the daughter
of she who used to be 403
And 403 was an even more popular girl
613 and 809 of Ricci Hall went up
to the roof all the time...
to teach her play ball they said
613 is now in Legislative Council,
a fence-sitter
It's 20 years ago
Ah, time for dinner
Dressed like that for High Table Dinner?
How time's changed!
Please be seated
I'd like to introduce
our guest speaker this evening...
Doctor Bernadette Tsui
The dilemma of a modern educated woman
in an ever changing society...
is often reflected in the difficulty
of forming any positive orientation...
Comprehendeth I not a single word
of yon banana's utterance
It giveth me fright stupendously
Fear thee not, for she be nought
but a stupendous stupid one
For you
Thanks
What gift doth young hero present?
It be a thornless rose
Barn dance on Saturday night, OK?
Call me and we'll talk about it later
Your Ho Tung Hall phone is always busy
Come on, say you'll come
Go first, hurry
See you Saturday.
This flower is a pledge
It's only Wednesday.
How can it last till Saturday?
Put an aspirin in the water everyday
and it'll last
I don't believe it.
The Medic boys taught you that?
The English Literature boys did
It's a deal, OK?
An aspirin a day, while he is away
Thank you. Thank you
Woolly Susie! Hey, Woolly Susie!
What're you doing here?
To give you back this dog
Nuts, it's not mine
He belongs to both of us
Buster was kept
by both my Dad and your Mum
He belongs to both parties
Listen, man's belongings to the man
woman's to the woman
This dog is male. He goes to the man
How can you tell he's male?
I can't even tell if you're a girl?
What? You having male menopause?
Take him back I don't want him
Buster!
Where shall we sup?
Kwan Yick Street
Called your Ho Tung girl already
Really? Is she gorgeous? Of course
Look out, a dog!
Buster! Buster's knocked down!
You hit a pup! Get down and look
Clumsy fool, don't you know how to pedal
Buster's bleeding! What shall we do?
Is there a vet nearby?
There's one down in Water Street
Taxi, I'll call a taxi...
It's just downhill. It's faster to cycle
- Can I borrow your bike?
- Sure, take it
Taxi!
Go to hell!
It's just down the road
- Wait for me!
- Come on
Remember to return after use
to Ricci Hall C-9
- Okay
Help! You sure you can handle this?
Yes, shut up
- I'm scared!
- Don't worry
It's come to, alright.
Bring it back tomorrow for follow-up
Sorry to have kept you so late
It's OK.
Tell your girl friend to make it rest
She's not my girl friend
Sorry, your sister?
She's not my sister either
Whatever. By 1997, everyone's a comrade
- Right, thank you
- You're welcome
Buster Baby
You must be obedient
Your masters are gone, never coming back
If you're disobedient,
nobody'll keep you, you know?
Now you're left on your own, you hear?
Buster, why did they go just like that?
Without even saying goodbye
They didn't love you,
so you've got all those hang-ups
Is everything they keep so weird?
Why do you say that?
Well, I feel that Buster's just like me
Ask him to go east, he goes west
Ask him to eat, he sleeps
Ask him to sleep, he pees
Rebellious and obstinate
Come to think of it,
he's a bit like me too
Cool, tough
Zero EQ, but full marks in IQ
And always challenging
the existing system
Enough, enough.
Don't you know you're exaggerating?
Is he heavy?
Let me carry him for a while
Careful with his leg. It hurts
No, I don't want to rush it
I'll marry you
He didn't enter, so it should be okay
But lingering about is risky enough
When was your last period?
Mine's very irregular
Sometimes in 2 months, sometimes 3
Sometimes even only once in 6 months
That's bad. Why did you give way?
No market value now
I didn't want to...
but hated to push him away
I only gave half way
Give him an inch and he takes a yard,
the rogue!
He's got a whole yard?
It's a saying!
What d'you mean a whole yard?
Did you or didn't you do it with him?
Was it nice?
Get lost, you nympho!
Nosy Parker! See how nosy you look
Nosy? I'm not nosy!
You are, Fatso!
Wake up, time to work!
It's so damn noisy here all day long!
I'm starving
Beautiful, really beautiful.
Let's have a snack
Let's go to Water Street for sweet soup
I'm starving
Sweet soup, OK? Herb and egg tea?
Ah! 7001, you're gorgeous!
Here it comes again
Everybody says
his girl friend is 01 of her class
What're you looking at? Come here
This place is pretty cool.
So this is a Mini Hall?
Yeah, it meets the Hong Kong
Housing Department specifications
35 square feet per head
That's different.
That's for resettlement areas
This is a resettlement hostel
Be satisfied
Chow time!
Let's play "Spin The Bottle"!
What's that?
"When, Where and With Whom",
your first time
The one pointed at
by the bottle must confess!
When: 18, where: 7-11,
with whom: sister 13
Wow, 3 seconds! Fastest gun in the west
"When, Where, With Whom", shoot
And it has to be me?
Just your luck.
Stop whining, talk. When?
OK, sweet eighteen
Where?
At my place
With whom?
Actually
it's outside the door of my place
It's so damn noisy! I give up!
With whom?
Michael
Michael who? Michael Chang?
Michael Jackson? Michael Douglas?
Go to hell!
Nuts, forget it! Next
Spin again...
Me? Speak, "When"!
I was 20, she was 18
Who? Where?
The place was her house...
outside her door
Outside the door again?
Well it was outside the door
With whom?
I'm Michael
Your turn at last Yes, big shot?
OK. Ready?
"When"? On my 21st birthday
"Where"?
A bedroom en suite facing the sea
How romantic! How classy!
"With whom"?
Even if I tell you, you don't know her
Wait, I heard you're only 20
Can't I plan
my next birthday gift for myself?
You're a virgin!
Woolly Susie, he's yours
You're so foxy, fox him!
Fox him! Fox him! Fox him!
Cut the crap!
Box him! Box him! Box him!
I quit, next one
Down with Japanese militarism!
Defend the Diaoyutai Isles!
In today's Diaoyutai Movement
everybody may have a halo overhead
But the same movement in those days
was not widely acceptable...
because it's impossible then
Demonstration? 10, 5 or 3 people
that's unlawful assembly already
Arrests were made every time
So when you went on one
you felt like a martyr
This sort of thing is unimaginable
for people nowadays
Don't forget the 8 years war!
Beware another Japanese invasion!
Defend the Diaoyutai Isles
with our lives!
Don't forget the 8 years war!
Beware another Japanese invasion!
Defend the Diaoyutai Isles
with our lives!
Let's go. Arrest for unlawful
assembly leads to a criminal record
No fear! If I join the Police Force
I become their superior!
Defend the diaoyutai Isles
with our lives!
Down with Japanese militarism!
Protest against Japanese invasion!
Listen, you mob
Your assembly is unlawful
You have one minute to disperse
Or else the Police will make arrests!
Diaoyutai, ours...
Ready! Charge!
Yes, Sir!
Charge!
Push! Push! Push!
Raphael, let's go. Will you listen to me
No!
God damn it!
Raphael!
Go, Vivien, never mind them.
Hurry and go!
Raphael! Let go of me!
Raphael!
Hurry and go! Never mind them!
- Tiger, have you seen Vivien?
- No, I haven't
Shut up! Let's go!
The demonstrating crowd
has not yet dispersed after dark
The Police will bring unlawful assembly
charges against these 21 demonstrators
This concludes our report
at Victoria Park
There was great confusion at the scene
The demonstrators retreated
from the Park
into the heart of Causeway Bay
Baby, don't mix up with
such impetuous people
The Cantonese in Hong Kong
are trouble makers
The Police arrested
21 demonstrators altogether
They are Gus Mok,
Ng Chung Yin, Wong Hing Wah
Raphael Hui, John Sham,
Chung Ling Ling...
Baby, where are you going?
Your hair's still wet
Leave me alone!
Bookie-learner,
your wife's here to see you
We are the best!
I was so worried you'd be arrested too
How's your head?
Still hurts a little, no sweat
I brought aspirins for you
An aspirin a day, while she is away
Wash it down with a glass of water
No need. I'm good in swallowing medicine
They've confiscated the"Yukio Mishima"
Says it's Japanese and gives wrong ideas
Leaving just this "Gorky's Collection"
They think he's a Chinese named Gor
Go now. Girls shouldn't stay here long
No sweat.
There're so many cops here, it's safe
Are you really OK here?
I'm OK
You heard them calling me bookie-learner
All those "ring leaders",
"big bosses" take good care of me
There are many drug addicts here
When it's urine test time,
I substitute my urine for them
I "pass water" for them,
they "carry water" for me
I provide the urine
for the whole detention center
They take good care of me. I'm fine
Ping Ching and Derek couldn't
get permission to visit you
Maybe they've taken their pictures
during the demo
Ping Ching asked you to keep cool
They also asked me
to bring you this sweet soup
I got it from Water Street
And this tape
I've applied for ages to bring it in
Listen
I'm going
Pissing for others?
I'll beat the piss out of you!
U boy! U boy!
Hands off, you've got nerve!
I sentence you, Raphael Hui,
to three months' imprisonment...
but you will be put on probation
for two years
Dad, let me carry it for you
Have you signed in this month?
Yes, I have
You're graduating in 2 years and
you had to get into such trouble
How can you find a job in future?
I've talked to my Warden
He'll help me lift the probation order
He knows people inside
In Hong Kong,
gweilos talk better with gweilos
So you understand that
This is only Hong Kong, why make trouble
Registered mail, please
Shut up in your hostel all day,
you don't know it's tough outside
One stamp short and the letter can't
get out of the Fragrant Harbor
Dad, I'll go first
You're mistaken
First floor, not ground floor
- What a lousy postman!
- Sorry, sorry
Dad, I'll continue my study in France
France? What are you doing in France?
Hong Kong is hopeless
Go to France? You think
it's as simple as sending a letter?
You have money?
I'll figure it out myself
Don't worry
(1971-The Fiery Age
for University Students)
I never thought
my Mum's been a revolutionary
And I never thought
my Dad's been in prison
And just for a far away and remote isle
My grandpa had fought against
the Japanese
So he'd had a part in World War II,
right?
My great grandpa was sort of a
revolutionary too, fighting the Manchus
Great grandma said
his name's on the 72 Martyrs' Tomb
So what have our generation ever done?
9701, you're gorgeous!
Here it comes again!
I meant to build a bridge here
in Hong Kong
Every big city should have
a beautiful bridge
In the U.S.A.
you've got the Golden Gate Bridge
In Italy, the Bridge of Sighs
In England, there's Cam Bow
Cam Bow, what a nice name for Cambridge.
I like it
Where are you going to build this bridge
Don't know yet.
Got to look down from a plane...
to see which is the best location
Why don't we go and
learn to fly a plane together?
Good. And I promise you
the first day I've learnt how to fly...
we'll fly together that very first day
So let's go and have lessons tomorrow
I'm leaving next term
You really have to go?
I've made something for you
when I was inside
Your hand?
See, identical
The lines of your palm
are so complicated
It's my name!
My lines of life, Career and Romance...
are all composed of your name
Come
Where to?
Don't you want it very much?
Don't be silly
Maybe next time
Raphael, it's me
What time is it at your end?
Can't hear? Can you hear now?
How are you?
I'm very well over here, you hear?
Is your job over there tough?
The job's fine, fine
Anybody making soup for you?
Sure, smoked oysters with octopus
and pork bones
What bones?
Pork bones
Did I wake you up?
I told you not to move out of Ho Tung
Couldn't find me?
Yeah, my boss is a jerk
Every time there's a call for me
he says I'm not in
How are you? When are you coming over?
Soon, I've got many jobs in hand
Two private tutoring,
two evening schools. Please wait for me
Stand in for me tonight, please
Thanks, I'm counting on you
Please
Paris, 3 minutes, Raphael Hui
Raphael, it's me
You haven't called for so long
I'm very busy these days,
no time even to eat
Really?
I thought you've had another girl
No, you hear?
The French girls here are ugly
They don't shower, just spray perfume
Don't be silly, OK?
But when are you coming back?
You've taken so long
Well it takes that long
to read Architecture
Why don't you come over first?
I can't. The way my Dad is
how can I go away?
Why don't you try to understand
my situation?
You keep saying I don't understand you,
d'you understand me?
I've told you
I won't come back without a degree
This I'm determined
I say so and it'll be so
Hello?... What?
Hello?... Say something, there's no time
You don't make a sound,
it's wasting money
Next time... I'll...
I'll call you again
when I've saved enough money
Substitute
Tutor them for me.
I'm going to evening school
Hello
When your grandpa passed away,
your Mum didn't say anything
She just went on studying
and took up 7 part-time jobs...
making $700 a month
$700 was quite something in those days
I know, she very much wanted
to go to France at that time
But she never mentioned it, not a word
Pity my Mum didn't go to Paris
Or else
she'd have reunited with your Dad
Wouldn't that be nice?
But you can also say
it's a pity my Day went to Paris
If they hadn't parted,
wouldn't it be even better?
If that's the case,
then wouldn't you become my brother?
I guess so
- Who wants to be your sister?
- Who wants to be your brother?
If that's the case, that's tragic
If, if, how can there be so many if's?
Baby, that young man's not bad
Good guys are hard to come by
Granny, it won't work
Why not?
Cause he's Raphael's son
So? What's wrong with that?
Granny, he says
he won't have girlfriends until 30
Thats sensible
A man won't mature until 30
Take your Mum's case
If she'd met Raphael later...
wouldn't it be nice?
But these things are hard to say
Sometimes it's too early,
sometimes too late
Who knows?
Just like the English word
you just mentioned. What was it...
You mean, 'Timing'?
What 'ming'?
It's T-I-M-ing, Granny
Ah, Too-lncomprehensible-Mystify-ing
Today we practice
pronouncing plosive sounds
Paste the strip on your nose and
repeat after me
Ping as in pingguo (apple)
Ping
Pin as in pinbo (strive)
Pin
Pin as in pinqiong (poor)
Pan as in panwan (yearn)
Pan
In 5 years Hong Kong will return
to China's sovereignty
If you don't grasp the time
to learn Putonghua...
by 1997 you'll lose out in all aspects
You are all top executives
of large organizations
I'm sure you understand this
and I need not say more
OK. Next, who'd like to try?
OK. You then
"The 7th month of 1997"
"The silly month
of nineteen ninety silly"
"Hong Kong Special
Administrative Region"
"Hong Kong Special Apprehensive Region"
Not"Apprehensive Region",
"Administrative Region"!
"Apprehensive Region"
Try again Yes
"Si Shi seized the sail and
sailed the seven seas"
See See See See See See See
We are the best
Have you been seeing the old classmates?
I heard that
Ho Tung Hall will soon be torn down
Yeah,
but Tiger and her gang had all emigrated
Two-thirds of my classmates are gone
Even Mum has gone to Vancouver...
and taken an English name called Nancy
Sounds like a dance hostess
She flies between here and there,
free as the wind
Well, all the emigrated Riccians
have come back
There's no place like Hong Kong
There are so many opportunities here
Is Ping Ching in Vancouver?
No, he's in Toronto
He says there's more business over there
He works as an immigration lawyer there.
He's doing fine
How about your wife?
She's in New York with our son
Both of them don't like Hong Kong
Having got the passport,
they didn't want to come back
And you? How about you?
I live at my Mum's place
My daughter's keeping me company
in Hong Kong
I want her to have
a good grounding in Chinese
But I've also got
an advertising company in Shanghai
So I'm always travelling between Canada,
Hong Kong and China
And you? Have you seen any old friends?
Sometimes
I see the university guys more often
And the revolutionary ones... less
Why?
Mao Zedong said, "Revolution is not
giving dinner parties"
Now I'm often giving dinner parties
for my clients
Revolution...
I guess I'm a revolutionary renegade
After all, revolution comrades
are mostly momentary hotheads
Friends at university, however,
are slow water that runs deep
Ladies and Gentlemen
Let's welcome my old friend Raphael Hui
to sing for us
No, Paul, you sing
No way,
didn't you sing this song every time
you're here?
Let's give a big hand
for a lovely beautiful song...
"Try to Remember"!
This is Mrs Hung. Is Ping Ching there?
Mrs Hung,
Mr Hung's gone to a meeting in Kingston
Thanks
Vivien, it's me
Are you interested in learning
to fly with me?
OK, Raphael. We'll just check the oil
Undo that,
just bring it out far enough
How much is it?
Five quarts? Yes, that's correct
So just pop it back in again
Take out some gas
watch its color, then smell it
If no water's got in then it's OK
Be especially careful with the propeller
It might have been hit by rocks
and has cracks
That will affect the safety of flying
OK, I get it
Clear prop!
Hong Kong Tower, Cessna India Golf,
with information Charlie...
request taxi
to light aircraft holding point
India Golf, you are cleared
QNH is 1007
Hong Kong Tower
Hotel November,
taxiing to the holding point
Raphael,
we need to stop just behind India Golf
Tower: Cessna India Golf
ready for departure
runway 13
India Golf, runway 13
Your are cleared for take off
What?
It's impossible
No drain pipes at all,
and you call it a skyscraper?
Raphael, what is it?
It's outrageous!
Every time I go up to see it,
it's not ready
Well,
now the whole building's erected...
there's no sewer pipes
toilet pipes or water pipes...
whole building no pipes!
- Ah, no-pipe building!
- Shit!
No wonder you're mad
You can't win.
They've got the upper hand
I'll draft a new contract for you
and call the municipal council
We'll sort it out, OK?
Thanks
Happy hour?
No "happy hour" for me, I'm dining in
- Going home?
- Yes
Going home?
Yes, going home
When did you become so well-behaved?
I'm going home, you have a happy time
Foget it, Mr Hui,
experience the vicissitudes of life
You mean"viscosity"of life?
I'll pack up and leave.
Really, not tonight
Hello?
Hello? Hello... Hello?
I just can't get these few notes right
Never mind, take your time
There's no time. I've promised Mum that
I'll return to the U.S...
after selling the house and
watching the hand-over ceremonies
Is there anything
you want to do before you go?
I'll keep you company
I...
I don't want to wait until I'm 30
Come over here
Look at this one. she suits you,
the Prom Queen
What Queen? Queen of puddings?
No way, too far
Don't be too choosy
There are 8 universities
in Hong Kong now
Quality's average
How about this one?
She's the model wife type
That one's gorgeous
Which one?
That one, beside the Lily Pond
She's gorgeous?
Yeah
Really gorgeous?
Very gorgeous
OK, I'll go get her for you
The one standing by the pond!
Yeah, the one by the pond
A bit more, more to that side, right
Good, that's it
OK
You really got the pillar box at auction
Yeah, the goddamn Cultural Center
Even stolen goods are priced so high
How much?
$25,000
That's expensive!
Only nostalgic dinosaurs like us
will buy such things
When my Dad was a postman
$25,000 was 5 years' wages for him
I think this looks
like the one outside Ho Tung Hall
It really looks like it...
the pillar box
where I sent you letters everyday
Vivien, look
All the letters I sent you!
20 years, all here
They'd gone round the world,
finally returning to Hong Kong
Let's put them all back in
1973, go back in
This one...
It's your birthday, remember?
Is that so?
And that one
This one?
Yeah, Valentine's Day Right
And this one,
another birthday card I sent you
Yes, I still remember
that winter I received this...
Rephael!
Raphael!
Surprise! Surprise!
It's a pity Ho Tung Hall
will soon be torn down
We've grown up together with her
Together we lost, together we won
Now, let's relive the joys and
sorrows of those days
Recognize yourself? So young and strong
We'd better break up
You've said it many times
This time I mean it
As you please
All the classmates are back
When I see them...
I feel so guilty
Then go home and be a good wife
From the very beginning
I wasn't a good wife
Nor a good lover
I'm going
From now on, you needn't call him
furtively behind my back
And you needn't find excuses yearly
not to spend your birthday with me
And Valentine's Day...
- Moon Festival...
- Christmas...
New Year...
I hope you won't forget...
each day that we were together...
was so happy,
and I loved you so very much
Then I hope you'll remember the days
when we're apart
I love you most
when you're not by my side
Looks awful!
Raphael, have you seen Vivien?
No, I haven't
Where have you been?
Just looking around
Why are you here?
What are you doing here?
I remember that year...
greenhorns raiding the gong
You Riccians grabbed our gong right here
Who's the one who grabbed it that year?
It's so long ago, I don't remember
D' you remember?
No, was it Derek?
Of course not!
It's Raphael who grabbed it from Vivien
Don't think I've forgotten
Let's go
What's to become of us?
Don't worry too much. It's no use anyway
When we were students,
we thought we could control everything
Now we know nothing's up to us
That's true
- But one thing I can be sure about
- What?
I'm sure we'll both get
our pilot's license next week
Let's fly together then
Next Sunday's your birthday
Let's fix on that day
Good. We'll train up
and fly out of Hong Kong together
Yeah, where do you want to go?
I want to fly to England
To look at the Thames from up above
Flying from bridge to bridge
all the way to Cam Bow...
Ladies and Gentlmen
another private pilot!
Drinks are on me today! Cheers!
Vivien
Happy birthday!
Raphael's present for you
Where is he?
He can't make it.
He's got business in Mainland
I know. His wife's suddenly come back
But today's my birthday
And the first time
I've learnt how to fly
And our first time to fly together
He promised me
Let's go!
Derek, does Raphael really love me?
Yes, of course
So does he love his wife too?
Well, it's like this... he...
You mean he does
Can't say he doesn't
Put it another way, you can't say
you don't love Ping Ching
How come a person can love 2 people
at the same time?
Even a clever one like
you can't answer that
Sis, if I can answer...
how come a person can love 2 people
at the same time...
I'd have got the Nobel Peace Prize
before Nelson Mandela
Good answer!
I've got my license today and
can take passengers
Hop in
Come on
Are you scared?
You're such a nice guy,
too bad I don't love you
Please stop talking...
and concentrate on flying.
I'm really very scared
Take care of Buster for me
I'm going to a meeting in England
After that I'll stay there and
have a break into the New Year
- You'll be over there into 1997?
- Yeah
You're leaving Raphael behind?
Tell him I'm through with him
Tell him not to look for me
If we go on like this I'll go crazy
I think my Mum wants to be buried
with your Dad too
This should be the best way
Yeah, I think you're right
Let's get Uncle Derek to help.
He knows many people
I checked already
The biggest one is sixteen inches...
and shoots up two thousand feet...
and stays there 20 seconds.
Pretty cool, huh?
- 20 seconds?
- Yeah, that's long, right?
Well, my Mum's loved your Dad
for over 20 years
I miss Dad again
It's just daybreak, who are you calling?
I'm calling Dad
David...
Listen
Hello, this is Raphael
I can't answer your call right now
Please leave your number and
I'll call you back when I return
We've made it look so nice,
and we have to leave
It's really beautiful
Give me the books and records
You can take the plants and goldfish
to your hall
What a pity
Soon as we make them lively
they have to leave this home
Never mind
Buster, you'll live with granny
from now on, you know
You've finished composing this song?
Yes
This number is in memory of my days
in Hong Kong
I dedicate it to you
Thank you
What's the title?
I haven't named it yet.
Let's use your name
OK
Actually, what's your Chinese name?
Cam Bow
Cam Bow?
Why? It sounds awful?
My Mum gave me this name
If it sounds awful, let's use your name
No, I'm also called Cam Bow
My Dad chose it for me
When... when's your birthday?
I won't tell you
In an hour's time, Hong Kong will return
to Chinese sovereignty
There'll be a fireworks display,
the largest ever, in Victoria Harbor
Many citizens have come
to the waterfront
to take up vantage points since noon...
making both sides of the harbor
overorowded with spectators
Hurry, there's a crowd.
We'll be late, quick
- Have you brought everything?
- Yes
Sorry we're late, Derek
You almost didn't make it.
This is Samcon
Here's your pass. Come with me, quick
Hong Kong should have its own separate
trading and financial system...
The establishment of the Hong Kong
Special Administrative Region...
is a celebrated event
for the Chinese Nation...