This is for plastics,
this is for wood, this is for veneer
But use this one for painted veneer
And this is multi-purpose.
Use it for anything, got that?
Can't I just clean everything
with that one?
No
Why not...
It's not professional
I see
Why do we carry it around?
It's for just in case
Excuse me, we need to clean the restroom
Stay in touch, OK?
Yeah
And swear to me
you won't get into trouble
I won't
You swear?
Yeah
Listen
Why don't you divorce him, Mom?
Just get a divorce.
You're still totally fine
What are you talking about?
That's the one thing that worries me
Who else will play mother in that family?
What difference does it make?
It's more complicated than that
You sure?
Playing mother isn't all bad, you know
I just don't get it
I'm off
National Border
There's no question that
he owes 3 months' worth of lunch money
I see.
I give it to him every month
Also,
he's excused himself early...
...countless times
Do you know of a reason?
I don't
Is he bullied?
If anything, he does the bullying
Which student?
Me
What?
I'm an adult so it hardly bothers me,
but your son is definitely
out of place here
I see
It's something
your family should discuss
Yes
Hey!
You can't just barge in!
What is that?
It's nothing!
Get out!
What did you do with your lunch money?
You haven't paid in 3 months
I was embarrassed
when your teacher told me
What did you spend that 15,000 Yen on?
This?
No, I found this on the street
Then what did you spend it on?
And tell me the truth
On piano lessons
I'll get a job and pay back
the 15,000 Yen, OK?
You're kidding.
Piano lessons?
You should have told me.
I would've paid for them.
But you said, "No piano"
Yes, I did
But pocketing your lunch money is worse
Go ahead, learn piano
I think men who play
the piano are attractive
Don't tell Dad
You know he'll never let me
OK
Kaneko Piano School
Welcome home
It seems Kenji's been sneaking off
to piano lessons
I see
He's been lying to us this whole time
He's a mess
Kenji, get down here
I need to talk to you!
Honey, please don't get too mad at him
I won't. But he needs to hear
some straight talk
We got a letter from
the Kaneko Music School
It says you should apply to
the Jr. High at a Music School
What's going on? Tell me
Tell me!
I just studied a little piano
Behind our backs?
Who cares what I do?
I told you "No piano"
That makes no sense
If you think I don't make sense,
come out and say so
Don't go behind our backs,
hoping you won't get caught
I hate that kind of cowardly attitude
more than anything
Honey, this...
The letter from Kaneko
It says Kenji's a genius piano player
That he's a rare child prodigy
How can you possibly believe that?
How could our child be a prodigy?
Who the hell is this Kaneko, anyway?
This guy's a real bullshit artist
My teacher, Kaneko, isn't like that!
Besides...
What?
She's a she, not a guy
You're a real idiot
These music schools praise everyone
That's how they make a living
I'll quit playing piano!
So just leave me alone!
This is all
your fault for not telling us
You're lying
What was that?
You're lying when you say
you'll listen if I talk
No matter how much I talk to you,
you won't change your mind!
Just like Ero-Bayashi
All you really want is to lecture me
and act tough!
Honey, stop it!
Are you OK?
You go on upstairs
Don't hit him
Sure
Why can't he play piano?
Once I've said "No",
I can't take it back
It affects my authority as a parent
I was too lenient with Takashi
So I'm shoving our parental values down
Kenji's throat, if I have to
You have to help me
He needs a clear message from both of us
What's that look?
I saw you the other day
You were standing in the free food line
at the park
You're unemployed, right?
You knew?
Yes, all along
Why didn't you tell me?
Because if I do,
your authority is screwed
Screw your authority
What?
Kenji!
Honey, call an ambulance!
I was just trying to catch him...
Shut up and call!
This is the 11 O'clock News
The U.S. Has announced
it is expanding its war
in the Middle East and is planning
a military troop surge
According to the Dept. Of Defense,
this deployment will include soldiers
of any nationality
This means it is likely
that the 138 soldiers
recently recruited from Japan
will also be deployed
A growing number of Japanese youths are
volunteering for the U.S. Military
We interviewed youths
in order to find out
what they think about this
I support it
We have a lot of trade with America,
so if American has a problem,
that means Japan's directly affected
So I think
it's a good thing to cooperate
with America to try to
help solve their problems
I think like...
like it's really great
if they're serious about it
I support the troops...
The Japanese Constitution explicitly
prohibits our country from going to war
So I couldn't believe it...
that our government let them join up
Kenji!
How is he?
I detected no brain abnormalities
He does have a concussion
but he's fine otherwise
Thank goodness
Take care
Thank you
I told you not to do that!
Come
Takashi!
I'm home
I'm exhausted
You should have told us
you were coming home
We saw it on the news
and were so worried about you
But I'm glad you're home
I killed so many people
I killed too many
Takashi...
Excuse me, I need the number
for the Foreign Ministry
My son volunteered for the U.S. Military
I wanted to find out
if there's any way to determine
his safety
Yes
Whether he's safe...
Oh, I see
So it's impossible...
No!
It's not
like that
3 Hours Earlier
You scream, I'll kill you!
The cash! Where is it!
You don't have any?
Liar!
There's no cash here
Why!
That was close
She saw my face!
Fuck, she saw my face!
What should I do?
Get up!
What are you doing?
You're my hostage.
Come with me
May I take my jacket and purse?
Can you drive?
Yes
OK, do it!
Oh, right
What are you doing!
Put it back!
What kind of car is this?
I don't know
I just stole it
Drive!
Who's that!
My neighbor, Okada san
Not a cop?
No
Just go straight
Yes
The next left
You forgot to signal
Oh, sorry
Not those!
Watch the road!
Yes
Um...
What?
Can you put that thing down?
Do you do this sort of thing a lot?
A lot?
Are you nuts?
Why, then?
I was good at picking locks
I could pick any lock in a flash
So I decided to go professional
A professional thief?
Of course not
A locksmith
But I quickly failed
I'm not a good businessman
No matter how many times,
I always failed
I just can't get along with people
And now finally...
I even failed at robbery
I understand
The hell you do!
I can always crash this damned car!
Um, can I use the bathroom?
Running away?
No!
Welcome
Why did you come back?
That was the deal, right?
What are you thinking?
Nothing
OK
I'll drop you off at some station
I'll go on alone
You go home
I can't go home
I've come this far,
I can't go home now
Hey, Sasaki
Taguchi, what's up?
Running away
For real?
I'm so sick of it all
School, cram school, family hour
Give me a break
Hey, thank you
How about your piano lessons?
I quit
Yeah?
Grownups just please themselves
It's Dad, shit
He's chasing me
Hey, what's wrong?
It's an asthma attack
Are you OK?
Are you OK!
I'll go buy juice
Don't go
You'll be fine
If they find me, Dad'll beat me up
I'll be right back
A dead end
I don't care what happens anymore
How about you?
I'll go see what's up ahead
Do you think I can start over?
From this moment on,
do you think I can start over?
Is that land over there?
Or a boat?
I can't see
I can't see a thing!
How wonderful it would be,
if my whole life so far, turns out
to have been a dream
And suddenly I awaken and
I'm someone else entirely
How can I...
Start over...
I want to start over
To start over
What am I doing...
I'm nothing more than a string of failures
I'm just a total failure
Don't hurt yourself, please
You're the only person who can be you
That's all we have to hold onto
Are you...
actually...
God?
Hey, wake up
What do you think that is over there?
It looks like a star,
but it's so low in the sky
Hey, wake up
Wake up, wake up!
Hey!
Gotcha!
He was sneaking into
the baggage compartment
A fare cheater?
Hey, is that true?
He won't say a word
I understand.
I'll take him in.
Name, address, phone number, school name
I don't care which, tell me
You can't go home if you don't talk
You won't talk?
You leave me no choice but to book
you as an adult fare cheater
OK with that?
This way, straight
That way
Don't move
Hey, get up
They dropped your case.
You're free to go.
I'm home
Where's your father?
Not home
Aren't you hungry?
Yeah
I'll cook something
What?
Lost and Found Box
You look strange, Dad
This is the 9 O'clock News
Since last month,
the U.S. Military has been
expanding its war zone
in the Middle East
But the Department of Defense
is expected
to announce yet another development
later today
According to sources,
they are expected to announce
a pullback in U.S. Troop strength
in the Middle East,
with the result that the 3,000
international volunteers,
including the 138 Japanese soldiers,
will be returning to
their native countries
4 Months Later
It's been a while
I hope you are all well
Recently,
I've learned that America isn't
the only one that's right
That is why I've decided to stay
in this country a while longer,
so I can understand them better
I've come to the conclusion
that the best path for me,
is to fight alongside the people
of this country,
in order to find true happiness
Please don't worry about me
I'm doing fine
I'll write again
Shiroyama Music School Prep Audition
He's so good
I know
He's next
I hope Kenji will be OK