Let's go and catch some dragonflies
and butterflies!
Tomorrow...
take him to the fields...
to work, will be good.
Ah Niu.
Ah Niu, Ah Niu, Ah Niu...
Follow me, follow me.
C'mon! Follow me.
The work you did was for nothing.
Aunt Yue Ci won't let us say anything,
but she's helping you redo it.
Seedlings have life too.
They can't stay too close...
or it will hinder growth.
Just like people.
In life, we must respect each other...
that way we can live peacefully and happily.
I'll remember that.
Grandma, let's eat!
Ok.
Grandma!
Yue Ci.
Grandma.
In a couple of days,
it will be time to go to the cemetery.
Go to the gravesite...
to visit your parents.
Ok
Grandma said, in a couple of days
I should go and visit my parent's graves.
Drink some water.
I would like to discuss something with you.
You're leaving.
I would like to go back...
to visit my parent's graves.
Filial piety is important, you should go.
I will come back.
You're been here for many years now.
I've always known
that you would leave this place one day.
Actually I...
This is a change of clothes for your journey.
Please take them.
I haven't told you my name yet.
You don't have to tell me...
where you came from, or where you're going
I don't have to know either.
I just need to know you as Ah Niu.
My name is Huo Yuan Jia.
I'll remember it.
"1907, Tian Jin"
- Here's something good to eat!
Money. Money
The Word of God is truth!
Believe in God and get eternal life!
Really, it's true!
Trust in the Lord and get eternal life!
All his words are in here!
God's words are here!
Huo Yuan Jia!
No. 1 in Tian Jin!
He came back!
Huo Yuan Jia has come back
to fight in the arenas again!
- Master...
- Uncle Lai Fu
You're back!
Good! Let me carry this.
Sorry, I failed in my duties
in taking care of your family assets.
Master, I'm so sorry.
I was always looking to the day
when you would return.
Nothing has changed in this room.
It's been hard for you.
It's my duty.
Master!
After you left,
the creditors came here everyday to collect.
All the things in the house,
were taken by them, one by one.
In the end,
they even wanted the house to pay off the debt.
All of the things in this room were kept intact...
only because someone
sent a package of money to us.
After much thought,
I believe the person who did that was Master Nong.
I don't need them any more.
I don't think my parents
want to see them again either.
Honourable Father...
Only now do I realize, that year on the stage...
why you didn't deliver the final blow.
You, are the real number one in Tian Jin.
Honourable Mother...
You taught me moral values,
but your son was too foolish to understand.
Don't worry...
I will not disappoint you again.
My child...
I didn't take good care of you
while you were alive,
but instead brought great misfortune upon you.
I wasn't a good father.
Madam, in the past I wronged Master Qin.
Today I've come to pay my respects to him.
Mummy, mummy...
Extra! Extra!
A strong foreigner, O'Brien,
has swept the fighting scene in Asia...
with thirty two consecutive wins!
Twenty five challengers were seriously injured!
He scorns the Chinese calling them
"Sick Men of Asia!"
No one dares challenge him!
Jing Sun.
I've done you wrong.
There are many things that, only after the fact,
does one realize that they were wrong.
The wrong pains my heart.
I don't want to mention the past again.
It's all over.
Jing Sun...
It's hard for me to ask...
but you're my only hope.
I need to borrow some money.
Still going to fight in the arena?
Yes.
We are no longer friends...
why should I lend you money?
Master.
Mr. Huo,
this is a gift from my master.
Who is your master?
He's Nong Jing Sun.
"1909, Shanghai Racetrack"
Ladies and gentlemen.
The person appearing before you today...
can single-handedly move a train,
with a single blow,
can punch a hole through the Great Wall of China
What baloney!
With his little finger,
he can squeeze to death any Chinese fighter!
Introducing, the strongest man you've ever seen...
O'Brien!
The challenger today...
Huo Yuan Jia from Tian Jin!
Good!
Sign the agreement first.
Tell him...
fighting to the death...
has been China's bad practice.
But we have another tradition...
it is making friends through competition.
Good!
Let the competition begin!
Thank you.
"Huo Yuan Jia defeats O'Brien.
His skill astounds Shanghai"
"Huo Yuan Jia mobilizes martial art schools.
Seeks end to school bias"
"Huo Yuan Jia assembles martial arts masters.
Plans to establish Jing Wu School"
"Shanghai Foreign Journalists Club"
Master, an invitation.
Jing Sun, I didn't expect it would be you.
You still treat me as friend?
There's no way I can forget you, my friend.
No way!
Come, have a seat, Yuan Jia.
I've ordered your favourite wine.
Come!
What's the matter?
I've quit drinking.
It's been many years now.
You liked to drink in the past.
I've quit to right some of the wrongs I've done.
Good!
Then, we'll use tea instead of wine.
Yuan Jia...
your fight has regained the self-esteem
of our countrymen.
The Westerners have forced us into this position.
And there should be a Chinese person
that will stand for us!
As a friend...
I'm really happy for you!
Please try some.
Jing Sun...
When are you leaving?
Since I've come, I'm not leaving.
What about your restaurant?
I sold it.
Sold it!
Business was good, wasn't it?
You want to start the Jing Wu School.
Without money how are you going to do it?
But the restaurant was your life!
Compared to what you are doing...
my little restaurant business isn't much.
Yuan Jia...
I'm not a martial artist.
I can only contribute a little...
to help you succeed.
As per our discussion, here are the regulations.
Please see if it is okay.
Jing Wu School has three ideals:
Educate the body, the mind and morals.
Martial arts is a method to become stronger.
No matter what style or school...
by interacting with one another
to understand the essence.
With a strong body and a clear mind...
people can renew and strengthen themselves.
Never harm your fellow man.
Do not abuse martial arts.
Virtue and morality are the core ideals.
Constantly strive to become stronger!
"1910, Founding of the Jing Wu School"
"Shanghai Foreign Traders Association"
Yuan Jia.
Among the competitors,
there is a Japanese man, Tanaka Yasuno.
He would like to meet you.
I heard that he is the best of the best.
We can only learn if we spar with the best.
Yuan Jia,
this competition organized by the foreigners...
I smell a rat.
Why are they making you fight
four people consecutively?
I think they're trying to use this
to humiliate us.
And to make the Jing Wu School
lose standing in Shanghai.
Yes
I have to fight all four
and I have to win every single match.
It isn't fair at all.
But in life...
who can guarantee that everything will be fair?
For Jing Wu School...
I have no other option.
But if...
Jing Sun.
I need to discuss something with you...
What is it?
After this match,
I want you to be the next president.
Why?
I want to go back and visit Yue Chi
and her Grandma.
I promised them.
So, you really don't know anything
about the art of tea?
It's not that I don't understand,
I'm just unwilling to understand.
I don't want to categorize tea.
As long as it's tea it's fine with me.
But tea also has different levels
of quality and grade.
What is good? What is bad?
They all grow in nature.
There is no good and bad.
It seems you still don't understand.
Otherwise, you would realize
which one is good and which is bad.
You're right.
My belief is that...
the quality of the tea...
is not determined by the tea itself.
It's decided by man.
Different people have different tastes.
I'm unwilling to make this choice.
Oh, why?
Enjoying tea or not depends on your mood.
If you're happy...
is the quality of the tea that important?
I've never thought of it this way.
In your opinion,
there are many schools and styles of martial arts.
None are of themselves superior or inferior?
That is my belief, yes.
Then, I would like to ask you,
since there are no
superior or inferior martial arts.
Why do we still seek
improvement through competition?
I believe that there really is no
superior or inferior martial arts.
The difference lies
in the ability of the practitioner.
Through competition we can discover...
and get to know, our true self.
Because our real opponent...
may still be ourselves.
Only through competition,
can we recognize our true self.
You mean the worst battle
is the fight within oneself?
Your words have gained my sincere respect.
We're here to make friends and appreciate the tea.
Let's skip all the talk about the tea...
and taste the tea.
Let's taste.
"1910, Shanghai"
"Theatre Biarya, France Constitution"
"Match Venue"
Ladies and gentlemen...
the last fight of the day...
Tanaka Yasuno of Japan vs...
Huo Yuan Jia from the Jing Wu School!
What's this all about?
Four against one?
Why didn't you tell me before?
This is what the Trader's Association
and the Jing Wu School agreed upon.
You need not be surprised.
You call this a competition?
This is murder.
You worry too much!
Huo Yuan Jia has defeated...
the fighting elites from different countries.
This arrangement was his wish.
Mita-san.
What are you up to?
Is this for the honour of Japan?
Or simply for yourself?
To me, what's really important
is the spirit of martial arts.
We compete to win.
Let's begin...
Yuan Jia, my friend.
This competition is unfair to you.
If you choose another day for the fight
I have no objections.
I understand your good intentions.
But I am already standing in this arena...
there must be a conclusion.
Please!
Start!
Great, Master!
This round ends in a draw.
Next round will be barehanded.
Both sides please prepare!
Mita! Where have you been?
We're going to lose!
Don't worry gentlemen. I have it under control.
Yuen Jia!
Stop!
- What happened?
- What are you doing Tanaka!?
Yuan Jia!
- Tanaka!
- Go now, go!
Yuan Jia, what happened?
How are you?
- I've been poisoned.
- Poisoned!?
How?
What happened?
- What are you doing?
- Water!
Water?
What happened to the water?
The water must've been poisoned!
The proof has been taken way!
Yuan Jia, let's go to a hospital!
Master, we'll take you to a hospital!
I've used too much strength.
The poison has already spread. It's too late.
Master, I will avenge you!
Zhen Sheng!
You shouldn't talk of revenge.
Hatred will beget more hatred.
I don't want to see any enmity.
The most important thing
is to strengthen yourself.
- Yuan Jia!
- Master
Yuan Jia, let's stop the fight!
- I'll take you to a hospital, let's go
- Jing Sun!
Jing Sun!
I'm just a fighter...
It took me many years to understand
what martial arts really is.
And what I can accomplish with it.
This competition isn't finished.
People can't choose how their lives begin.
But they must have the courage
to walk till their last step.
Master...
Tanaka! What's wrong with you?
Hurry up and finish him!
What do you mean?
You need not ask.
I must win this fight! Regardless of the means!
Constantly strive to become stronger!
Constantly strive to become stronger...
Just watch...
Don't fight!
Living on is more important than anything else!
Listen,
living is never a single person's own affair.
If we must fight, I will not hold back.
That would be my honour.
Master...
You lose! Huo Yuan Jia lost!
Go! Go! Faster!
Go, go, make the announcement!
Wait a minute!
Huo!
Yuan!
Jia!
- Huo Yuan Jia...
Tanaka! You useless trash!
Look what you've done!
I lost!
Who says that? Who?
I understood deep within me.
I was beaten convincingly.
Who do you think you are?
How can you decide on your own?
Are you fit to be Japanese!?
You!
You shame the Japanese!
"Huo Yuan Jia passed away after he reached
the hospital. He was 42"
"After he died,
his spirit in martial arts continued"
"Even today,
the Jing Wu School has opened various branches...
in over fifty countries
and territories all over the world"