That was tiring, huh?
Man, 30, Flees After Murdering Wife
You have grown a lot!
Get in!
So?
Have you led a happy life up till now?
Tell me something interesting
about your life.
The world of men has grown agonizing
for you, hasn't it?
Leave me alone, Master.
Can you not see that I am suffering?
What causes you to suffer?
My only sin was to love.
I wanted nothing except her.
So?
She went with another man.
Ah, that was it.
How can that be?
She said that she'd love only me.
- And then?
- I couldn't bear it anymore.
Didn't you know beforehand
how the world of men is?
Sometimes we have to let go
of things we like.
What you like, others will also like!
But still, how could she do that?
The bitch!
- Is it so unbearable for you?
- Yes!
Shut
Young fool!
Though you can so easily kill …
you yourself cannot be easily killed.
Carve out all of these characters
with the knife.
And while you cut out each one …
drive out the anger from your heart.
Holy one!
We've come to investigate something.
- Drop the knife!
- Otherwise I'll shoot!
What are you doing? Continue cutting!
Prajñāpāramitā Sutra.
It helps restore inner peace.
Please let him finish.
How long will it take?
Until tomorrow morning.
No connection.
- No?
- It's quite a deep valley, isn't it?
What?
They make white paint from these mussels.
I know.
Stand up.
It's time to go.
Detective Choi …
let's go as we are.
Detective Chi, the boat won't go forwards.
Ah, now it's moving.
Shut
Winter
…and Spring