http://subscene.com/u/659433
Improved by: @Ivandrofly
Hello, darling.
It's your mother.
Thank you for showing me
your new apartment. Um...
I'm worried about you.
I mean, how can you
live like that?
Anyway, would you call me back?
Let's get together again.
I love you.
Control.
It's all about control.
Every dictatorship
has one obsession.
And that's it.
So, in ancient Rome,
they gave the people
bread and circuses.
They kept the populace
busy with entertainment.
But other dictatorships use other
strategies to control ideas.
The knowledge.
How do they do that?
Lower education.
They limit culture.
Censor information.
They censor any means of
individual expression.
And it's important to remember
this, that this is a pattern
that repeats itself
throughout history.
Okay.
See you next week.
- Hi.
How are you?
I'm good.
See, every dictatorship,
there's only one obsession
and that's control,
they want to have control
over the people.
In ancient Rome, they
gave bread and circuses,
they kept the populace
busy with entertainment.
In other dictatorships,
they have other strategies.
To limit information, to
limit ideas and knowledge.
How do they do that?
They lower education,
limit culture.
They censor any means
of self-expression.
But it's important to remember
this, this is a pattern
that repeats itself
throughout history.
You don't go to the
movies, do you?
Movies?
Yeah, are you a movie guy?
In your free time, I mean?
I don't know,
I don't go out that much, I
don't really like movies.
Oh.
You don't have to go out to
enjoy a good flick at home.
That's true.
I usually just rent them.
Most people don't these days,
but it's what I do.
Is there a reason why
you're asking me this?
No.
'Cause you brought it up and
I thought, you know, maybe
you had a recommendation, or
you saw a movie that you liked
and you want to
tell me about it.
Oh, sure, I mean, there's
always something.
- I could go for something cheerful.
- Hmm.
Where There's a
Will There's a Way.
It's true.
No, it's a movie, I saw it a
little while ago, but, um...
I remember, I liked it.
Hmm. Where There's a
Will There's a Way.
Yeah, that's it.
Local film, if you...
I'll keep it in mind.
I think I'm drunk.
You wanna go to bed?
Hmm?
No, I'm gonna finish
grading these papers
and then I'll come
join you, okay?
Mr. Henderson, my
husband will be back.
Your husband just won a
heck lot of money from me.
By the look in his eye he
didn't have an intention to...
Ow!
Stop!
Okay, okay, okay.
What's wrong?
I'll call you tomorrow.
Sorry I'm late.
Uh...
All right.
Last class we talked
about dictatorship,
so today we'll start with Hegel.
It was Hegel who said that all the
greatest world events happen twice.
And then, Karl Marx added, the
first time it was a tragedy,
and the second time
it was a farce.
It's strange to think...
A lot of the world's
thinkers are worried
that this century will be a
repetition of the last one.
And there's an interesting
observation, a creative act of memory
to remember something,
to remember somebody...
I'm looking for Call me L8R or
Passenger Without a Ticket.
Shit.
Anthony?
Anthony!
Hey, long time no see!
I couldn't tell it was you with that beard.
Is that for a movie?
Yeah.
Man, you haven't been
around here for ages.
Yeah, I don't know
how long it's been.
Six months, I'd say.
Six months or more.
Yeah, so how's everything?
Great.
Are you meeting someone here?
'Cause there's no one around.
- No?
- No,
you know no one comes
in on Saturdays.
Oh...
I was supposed to
pick up the thing...
For the movie. Um...
And I forgot it was Saturday...
'Cause my head is, like...
You actors are something else.
Hold on, let me see if
there's anything for you.
Great.
Yeah, here it is, look.
Oh, that looks like it's it. That's
definitely it. That's definitely it.
- There you go. All right?
- Okay.
- Hey, don't be a stranger.
- I won't be.
Good luck with that movie.
Great, I will... Yes.
Anthony Claire.
3650 Rathburn Road.
Hello?
- Good afternoon, I'm calling...
- Hey.
Um, I'm calling to speak to...
Where are you calling from?
I'm sorry, I think there's
been a misunderstanding.
I'm calling to speak to
Daniel Saint Claire, the...
Anthony?
Anthony, you called home.
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
What are you doing?
My name's not Anthony.
You're not Anthony?
No, I'm calling to speak to Daniel
Saint Claire, the actor. Um...
If I'm not mistaken,
that's Anthony Claire's.
name that he uses
for the movies.
For his work.
Right.
Right, well, Daniel
isn't here right now,
maybe I could get him
to call you back.
Okay, I'm sorry to bother you.
What?
I... I...
Who is this?
Hello? Who is this?
He doesn't know me.
No.
- Okay. I'm gonna...
- Anthony?
I'll call back later.
Hello?
Hello, this is Anthony...
This is Anthony
Claire, isn't it?
Who's calling?
Um...
I called before. I was talking...
I talked to your wife. Crazy.
You're the one.
And you call here again, I
will call the police...
I... No, no. Just hear me out.
Can you say something again?
Can you talk again?
Who is this?
That's crazy. That's amazing.
Our... Your voice is just like mine.
Do you hear my voice?
Your voice is just like mine.
Shit.
- Listen...
- Sorry, please, please, please.
Just listen to me for a second.
Just listen, okay?
Just hear me out.
I know this sounds crazy. I'm sorry.
I got excited before.
When I get excited, I just
act a little strange.
So just hear me
out for a second.
I've seen three of your movies.
And you're great in them.
You're great in them.
We look exactly alike.
And I called your
wife earlier today.
And she said that... She
thought that I was you.
And I'm just... I'm confused.
And I know this call must be just as
confusing for you as it is for me.
And I just... My name is Adam Bell.
I'm a history teacher.
And I just think
that we should meet.
Hey, hey, hey, okay. Okay.
Listen to me. Never
call here again.
Who was that?
It was that same guy.
What did he want?
I don't know. He sounded crazy.
Like, he sounded like a
stalker or something.
A stalker?
Yeah, he said that he
was a fan of mine.
That he wanted to, uh,
meet up or something.
- What?
- Mmm-hmm.
- No.
- Yeah.
You're messing with me.
Right?
- Anthony?
- Uh...
Do you want to get
something to eat?
Who was on the phone?
Helen, the same guy who called before.
The same guy.
That's who was on the phone.
I told you that. Why would I
tell you any differently?
Are you lying to me?
I...
You're lying to me.
You're acting crazy.
I'm not crazy. Who
was on the phone?
I told you it was a man
who was on the phone.
Are you seeing her?
Helen, I don't want
to get into this.
Are you seeing her again?
We need to get something to eat.
Let's go get something
to eat and then...
I don't want to get anything...
it was a man! It was a man.
What do you think it
was, a jealous husband?
Yeah.
I don't want to get into this again.
Okay?
I don't want to get into this.
I'm going for a walk.
Yes.
Yeah, it's me, man.
That's so strange. I had a feeling
that you were gonna call.
You had a feeling,
what's that mean?
It's a, you know, just a figure of speech.
It's not...
Right. All right. Well, look,
I've been thinking about it.
I want to meet.
Okay.
I know a place called
the Breezeway Inn.
It's about an hour outside the city.
Do you know where that is?
No.
All right. Well, then I'll call
you on Sunday with directions.
1:00, okay?
Okay.
All right.
Uh-huh.
- Well, see you soon.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'll see you soon.
Hello.
Hi.
Is everything all right?
How many months are you?
Uh...
Six.
That's nice.
I should be going. I have a
class, I have to teach in it.
Ah...
Never know how your day
is gonna turn out.
Have a nice day.
What's up, honey?
Hello?
Hi.
It is a scorcher out there.
The last 10 minutes of my run,
this 22-year-old kid or
something like that, he was...
He was following
me the whole time.
Never gonna beat this kid.
And he dropped.
Do you think that I should cut my
beard off 'cause it's fucking hot?
Wait, why did you call me earlier?
Did you call me for a reason?
Honey, where are
the blueberries?
Where are the blueberries?
I told you, like, two days ago.
The organic blueberries. Not
the conventional blueberries.
I can't use 'em in the shake.
What's wrong?
I wasn't... Only I was
saying 'cause I read it
in a magazine that blueberries,
the organic ones are better
than conventional ones...
Are you gonna tell
me what's wrong?
I...
I went to...
I went to see that guy.
Who? What're you talking about?
The guy on the phone.
I went to his work.
Why did you do that?
That's dangerous, honey.
I wanted to know.
Are you okay?
He had the same voice.
He looks exactly like you.
What do you mean,
"Exactly like me"?
What's happening?
I don't... Really don't know
what you're talking about.
I think you know.
Hello?
I told you.
- Show me your hands, man.
- Why?
Come on, show me your hands.
Maybe we're brothers.
We're not... We're not brothers.
We're not brothers.
How do you know?
Do you have a...
Do you have a scar
on your chest?
This one?
You do, don't you?
I, uh...
- When's your birthday?
- This was a bad idea.
I think I made a mistake here.
Um...
I have a...
I have this. I went to...
The company that represents you,
they gave that to me... To you.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry, honey.
That guy won't be
calling here again.
Fuck.
There must be some difference.
There isn't.
It cannot be exactly the same.
We are.
Did you take your clothes
off in front of him?
No.
Okay, then.
You didn't eat.
The last thing you need is to be
meeting strange men in hotel rooms.
You have enough trouble sticking
with one woman, don't you?
Here.
I don't like blueberries.
Of course you do, and
they're good for you.
I am going to pretend I never heard
a word of what you just told me.
I just wanted your advice.
You don't want advice. I don't
want to hear any more about this.
You are my only son.
I am your only mother.
You have a respectable job,
you have a nice apartment,
and since we're
being frank here,
I think you should
quit that fantasy
of being a third-rate
movie actor.
Eat those. You want some coffee?
I have a question for you.
Did you fuck my wife?
Did you fuck my wife? Did
you sleep with my wife?
You fucked my wife!
Did you fuck my wife?
That's good. That
is fuckin' good.
This is what's gonna happen. You're
giving me your clothes and your car.
I'm gonna take your girlfriend
on a little romantic getaway.
Tomorrow, I bring her home.
And I'm gonna come back here,
bring back all your things, and I'm
gonna disappear from your life forever.
And then I'll be gone.
What are you doing here?
What the fuck is this place, man?
You live here?
I have some questions for you.
Please go or I'll
call the police.
Go ahead, call the police.
What are you gonna tell 'em?
What are you gonna
tell 'em, man?
Why'd you come looking for me?
I don't know. I don't know.
I just...
I needed to know.
You need to know. Yeah. Okay.
But when you called my house,
you talked to my wife.
Why'd you do that?
She happened to
pick up the phone.
Okay. Yeah, but...
Can I ask you something,
just man to man?
Um...
Did you sleep with my wife?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Did you fuck my wife?
This is crazy.
Just answer the question, man.
Just answer my fuckin' question
and then I will leave.
You're fuckin' crazy.
All right.
I'm fuckin' crazy?
You brought my wife
into this, man.
So I'm gonna bring your girlfriend
into the picture as well.
You want me out of your life? This
is what's gonna happen first.
You're gonna give me your
clothes and your car.
I'm gonna take your girlfriend
on a little romantic getaway.
I'm gonna bring her back home tomorrow,
and I'm gonna come back here,
and I'm gonna bring
back all your stuff
and I'm going to disappear
from your life forever.
Then we will be even.
Mr. Claire. Good afternoon.
Everything good?
Yeah, I just...
Uh, forgot my keys.
Is Mrs. Claire not home?
Do you want me to open
the door for you?
That'd be perfect. Yeah.
I can't stop thinking
about the other night.
Can't get it out of my head.
I know I shouldn't
talk about this,
but I'd love to go back.
Uh-huh.
I heard they changed the
lock and sent out new keys.
But...
I don't think I'm on the list.
I need to go back.
I'll see what I can do.
I don't...
I don't know if that's
going to be possible.
Call me if you hear anything.
After you.
Okay. Here you go, Mr. Claire.
Thank you.
Hello?
- Anthony?
- Hi.
The light's on, you
freaked me out.
Sorry.
What're you doing home? I
thought you were at your mom's.
Oh, I canceled it, I...
Should've called.
I stayed longer at the pool,
'cause I thought you
weren't gonna be home.
Uh...
Do you need anything?
I'm fine.
I'm gonna go to bed.
Okay.
Are you sure you
don't need anything?
'Cause you...
When you came in and you said
that you went to the pool,
I just thought maybe that you've
been there for a long time,
and you had to walk home or
whatever and you must be...
Is everything okay?
You're six months pregnant,
so I didn't know.
No, I'm fine.
Why don't you come to bed?
I...
Aren't you gonna take
your clothes off?
Yeah.
Did you have a good
day at school?
What?
Forget it.
What? What? What? Whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa!
Mary. Mary. Mary.
What's wrong?
The ring. The mark
on your finger.
What are you talking about?
I've always had this.
No. No!
Who are you? Don't touch me.
Don't touch me.
What are you talking about?
- Don't touch me!
- What are you talking about?
The ring. The mark
on your finger.
What's wrong?
I just couldn't sleep.
Yeah, I couldn't sleep either.
I'm sorry.
Why are you doing this to me?
What? What am I doing to you?
I want you to stay.
- Stop the car.
- Stop the car? Stop the car?
- Stop the fucking car.
- I'll stop the fucking car.
You want me to stop the car?
Get out. I'm sick of this shit.
I can't even talk to you.
Fuck you.
You're behaving like a child.
You're not a man.
- I'm not a man?
- Enough. You don't need to get me started.
I'm not a man?
I'm not a fucking man?
Get out! Get out!
- Get out! Get the fuck out!
- Let go!
Sunshine, a high of 24 today,
clear tonight with a low of 13.
Here's James with a
look at traffic.
The westbound Lake Shore is closed
between Bathurst and Strachan,
as crews clean up debris from a collision
that happened early this morning.
Police have not released
any details at this time,
but we do know there
was only one vehicle.
I forgot to tell you
that your mother called.
You should probably
call her back.
Okay.
Helen, did you plan on
doing something tonight?
'Cause I think I have to go out.
Helen?
http://subscene.com/u/659433
Improved by: @Ivandrofly