STUDIO 2.0 presents
In association with OCN
KOCCA, and KTB Network
a J TEAM Studio production
The world has run out of
all forms of energy.
People built a new city
by making
a new energy with
their excrements.
Soon after the city's leaders
announced two legislations
to generate and
control the new energy.
First, installing an ID chip
in each of the citizen's anus
to monitor their
defecation level.
Second,
provide defecating
citizens in return
one addictive "juicybar".
Later, defecation amounts
have skyrocketed,
but the city became
full of addicts
due to the
juicybar's strong addiction.
Illegal trade of juicybars
became prevalent,
and the juicybar's
side effects
have created
dumb pint-sized mutants.
These mutants organized
a gang to plunder juicybars.
They became known
as the 'Diaper Gang'.
They're coming.
Hey, they're coming!
They're going. They're going.
They're coming.
Outta my way!
Hey slowpoke,
think you're faster?
You betcha!
Hey!
Bald bastard.
AACHI & SSIPAK
We are the forgotten orphans.
We once dedicated our crap
and youth to this city.
But what did our leaders
do for us?
Did they appreciate us
for our crap?
Never!
We became addicted to juicybars,
so we can never shit
or even reproduce because our
dicks have shrunk like peanuts.
Then they ran us out of
this city like garbage!
Why?
Because we've evolved into mutants,
liberating ourselves
from having to shit
all the time!
Diapers! Diapers!
Nonetheless,
we're in shitcreek now.
Juicybars is our only
source of food,
but we haven't had any
for a month.
And why is this?
Because of that
special cop, Geko?
No.
It's because
a whole bunch of you
piss-ass dumb shits
can't even blow away
one fuckin' cop!
Stand up!
This is your last chance to
redeem yourselves.
Tell me where
we can find juicybars
for our hungry brothers.
Kindergarten defecation classes.
Where were you before?
A kindergarten defecation class.
A juicybar factory?
No, a juicybar market?
No, how about...
You freaks don't deserve to
be called gangsters.
Know what punks
like you are called?
I know! Hoodlums!
Yes, hoodlums!
What?
I mean, these hoodlums...
A lot of hoodlums are
dealing juicybars in Section 4.
Hoodlums, you say...
You bonehead!
There's only eighteen in here,
not twenty!
You swiped two, didn't you?
Count it yourself, idiot!
You hopeless chimp.
You won't get your cut unless
you get two more.
And no chick as well.
Got it?
You twirp!
Why am I always doing
the dirty work?
Hey, you get the easy way out.
I always risk my life
being on the lookout.
Go and get some more.
We need to make up for it.
You little piss ant!
Then every chick we
find tonight are mine.
And if you cheat me again
and take off,
you're really gonna
pay this time.
Damn it, that hurt!
Stupid mutt!
Today the police
scored big again
for mopping up the
Diaper Gang.
We will rigidly tackle
any insincere defecation!
Have any problems defecating?
Well, I'm constipated.
Drink! Dump-free Yogurt!
FLUSH ITALL DOWN!
Now get ready, gear up and...
Headbump!
One, two, givin' it to ya'.
Don't get too wasted now.
Stop showing off and
do some kickin'!
Here comes daddy!
Your juicybar is being prepared.
Sorry to disturb.
Man! That's one hell
of a dump!
Juicybar delivery complete.
Smells damn good, too!
The way kids shit these days
is so impolite.
He's such a hopeless case.
His damn showing off gives
me the runs.
Abio, showing off here is useless.
We're in the can.
Screw off.
Run!
It's too damn hot
for this crap.
Let's go.
You little punks.
You assholes swiped a ton of
juicybars in Section 4.
Think you're big shots?
You cheating scums.
There's taxes on what you made.
What?
Bastard got some balls!
You little shit,
stop being a wus again.
Look here, cue ball.
Unless you want me to make sushi
out of your tongue,
bring me 100 juicybars a day.
Damn, you got cavaties.
Be a good boy!
And grow some damn hair!
You know my boss's cell
in prison, right?
Hand the juicybars over to him.
Let's go!
Oh yeah, Jimmy says hi.
You got a really good friend!
Ciao!
Jimmy, you son of a bitch.
John Doe is this month's
"King of Defecation".
If you become the "King",
you'll receive
unlimited VIP service
with beautiful girls
at a luxurious resort.
Try your best to defecate,
and be the "King of Defecation".
You can be the "King", too!
Foul bastards.
How dare they stuff things
into the sacred anus.
Those beasts are the real traitors
of our establishment.
They're evil to our society.
Don't you think, Captain?
Chief, so you mean...
They're illegal anus users?
- Like this, bitch?
- Harder!
- Like this?
Cut! Cut!
Cut!
You idiots,
get it right for once!
How many times
I gotta tell you?
Think we're shooting
a cheap porn?
You sluts.
Each whip should be
the sublime.
A girl who sacrifices her
anus to save the world.
Oh how beautiful she is.
Once this film is complete,
it will be praised
by critics and moviegoers,
and be a world-wide success!
Oh my Lord, how art thou
I be this talented?
Bullshit!
Hey asslover,
you're in deep trouble!
You freak!
Dr. Strange sawed another guard
into pieces again in prison.
That crazy old fart.
He'd be cooked on the
electric chair
if he hadn't created our cyborg.
Move him into the special cell
so that he can't touch anyone.
And report that he's
cooperating very well with us.
Yes, ma'am.
Geko, good work and...
My report for today.
99 kills and no arrests.
That despicable cyborg, how rude.
ANAL INSTICT
S&M MIZERY
HORNYALIENS
You freak,
what's with your room?
Don't you have anything kinky?
He's totally high, man.
Don't sweat it, dude.
Keep stuffing his face.
Look at him.
I'm telling you, he's toasted.
Okay, okay.
You like feeling high,
you pervert?
From now on, you're Shitman.
Shitman. Shitman.
Yes!
I am!
Shitman!
Shitman, shall we save
the world now?
Here comes Shitman to bring
peace to the fuckin' world!
That was so cool.
Let's take him to
a higher place this time.
Then he'll croak for sure,
you meathead.
We need him for something else.
What the hell is this?
Pigeon poo?
Is this the right way?
Yes, sir!
I'm positive this is
the way to Section 4's prison.
Oh, how corrupt the world is.
A prison is a hideout
for hoodlums?
I'm bored!
Give me a vacation!
Who stole my Teddy Bear?
This sucks!
The world's too corrupt for
good citizens like me.
80 juicybars from the
Razor Gang in Section 3.
25 juicybars from the
Cobra Gang in Section 4.
A measly 25 juicybars?
The Cobras seem to be
out of heart lately.
Yes, they do.
I'll break your balls
if you sleep on the job again!
Someone's here to see you.
What does he want to
snitch this time?
- What the hell?
- What's that?
Why are you stripping?
How dare you, you looney!
What are you going to do?
Charge me for smoking?
What's gotten into his head?
Of course it's prohibited,
you freak!
Who the hell do you
think you are?
That freak turned out to
be a useful friend.
Hey lady, time for the
'Misery' version.
Misery.
Misery. Misery.
Misery...
One, two, one, two.
You freak!
I'm gonna slice you in half!
Write it again!
Didn't I warn you not to kill
Misery without my permission!
This is much better
than the movie.
If you won't give it up,
then don't hit me at least!
Crap, it's my first erection
in three years.
You pervert.
How dare you hit your director!
Director, my ass.
You crazy bitch!
You call an animator
a real director?
Yes, I do.
What a bummer.
Hey, kid!
What are you looking at?
Who are you calling "kid"?
You rude bitch!
Isn't she totally hot?
Damn horndog is at it again!
Peabrain!
We have to finish the job first!
You horny bastard!
Diapers, diapers, diapers.
Die, you mushroom head!
Shoot that crazy bitch!
I mean that crazy asshole
right now!
Absent-minded myself.
What's this red crap?
Is the ceiling taking a shit?
What the hell are all these diapers?
Is this some kindergarten?
Let's go if it's all done.
Go, go, go!
One, two, one, two!
Where am I?
Aliens?
Then that means...
Come to mama!
You evil beasts!
Alien Queen!
Give me my baby back!
Come on, bitch!
Oh no.
How can I give you a slow
and painful death...
I don't know why
I did that, but...
I'll compensate
you with juicybars.
Do you have any juicybars?
Well, I don't have any now,
but if my movie
becomes a big hit.
Movie?
Yes.
When my heroine takes a dump,
juicybars come gushing out.
Doesn't it sound like a hit?
Juicybars gush out
with just one dump?
How is that possible?
It happens only
in a fictional world.
Stop bullshitting!
Just tell me how.
Or else, you'll die
in the real world!
Right, I mean my movie is
about a holy sacrifice.
I mean in order to
enlighten her...
God digs out this
corruptive chip from her anus.
Yes, digs out.
Then, he sticks a blessed chip
back in there,
so...
So whenever she shits,
tons of juicybars gush out.
In other words...
Yes! It becomes a magical anus!
A magical anus...
So he digs it out
and sticks it in?
You've been implanted with
an ID chip at your birth.
This is your soul mate
to supply you with precious
juicybars for a plentiful life.
This ID chip in your anus is
your second identity.
Why didn't I think
about this before?
Since you gave me
this great idea,
I'll put these chips
into your rear with honor.
But...
I don't shit very well.
Nobody here can
shit better than you.
I'm extremely constipated,
and I even have hemorrhoids.
Sorry, I do a lot of
things with my butt.
Gross.
Drop him.
Wait!
I'm gonna have an audition for
a girl who's good at shitting.
Wait!
Please don't kill me.
If you don't kill me,
I'll stick those
chips into a girl
who can shit
several times a day.
I beg you!
There she is.
She's going.
"Wanted ASAP"
"Excellent defecation skills"
"Need actress
with experienced anus"
"Jimmy's Pure Cinema"
Jimmy, that tough cockroach.
He's still alive.
Hey, let's beat the hell out of
Jimmy in front of Beautiful.
If I show her how strong I am,
I'll sweep her off her feet.
So Jean D'Arc is this lady
who was born to save the world.
But one day
a juicybar tycoon shows up.
May the anal force be with me.
Show me the anus!
So angry Jean D'Arc
tramps on him.
Oh my god!
But he turned out to
be an angel
looking for the city's saviour.
Oh, Jean D'Arc!
I will give you
a blessed anal chip.
Save the world with this.
That's stupid!
It's so boring.
How about a woman who saves
a man with her breasts?
A very, very rich man.
Hey, I'm the director here!
Oh my.
This is a film
about a noble sacrifice.
I mean, art...
An auteur film.
You know what
an auteur film is?
Why do I have to know that?
Being pretty is enough.
Come on baby.
Change it into tits, okay?
What the hell do you know?
A ditz like you will
never be a star in this business!
Then do it yourself,
Mr. Auteur.
Ciao!
- Rock, paper, scissors.
Bend over, asshole!
You see, there are all
kinds of shit in this world.
Some are soft, some are hard,
and some just don't
turn out right.
But in the end, shit is shit.
The same goes for chics.
Then is my
Beautiful Shit inside?
Not a bad show.
Jimmy's bolder than I thought.
What are they doing, damn it?
What is it?
Oh, nothing.
They're just chit-chatting.
Well, it looks too loose.
Can she take a good crap?
Look how elastic her anus is.
Ten times a day
will be no problem.
I'll stick it in beautifully.
What the hell?
Damn it.
You idiot!
Jimmy, that son of a bitch,
is dead.
What are you doing,
you perverts!
What is it?
Run!
Oh, my tummy!
What's wrong with your tummy?
You perverts also with them?
No way.
How could we possibly
be with those jerks?
We were just passing by and...
Damn it!
What a major bitch.
She's the one who followed us.
Rotten perverts.
Why into my anus
of all places?
Damn it.
You must be constipated.
You think that will work?
No.
For constipations...
GOLD LAX!
And SILVER LAX!
Shut up!
She's a real pain in the ass.
How could she shit now?
Isn't she super sexy?
You blockhead!
Just bring her juicybar
after she finishes.
ID check complete.
Your juicybar will be delivered.
Oh my goodness!
Is it broken?
If anyone is on patrol in
Section 4, please comply!
What's with all these juicybars?
What did that pervert do to me?
She's pretty,
has an awesome personality,
and she's so fertile.
I love you!
She's a walking
juicybar factory.
Now I know why the
Diaper Gang wanted her so bad.
She takes one dump and
tons of juicybars are delivered.
Anyway, what should
I do with these leaches?
Beautiful,
trust me from now on.
I'll be your manager,
and we'll...
Flies like him tend to
swarm around
a beauty like you.
Let go! Gonna kill
a friend over a chic?
Whatever.
Remember when you ran away?
Don't worry, sweety.
I'm your man from now on.
You traitor!
Forgive me for asking you this,
but since I helped you
find their place,
mind if I go home now?
Help me!
Eat this, you diapers!
Turn left! Left!
Is that left, you idiot?
Sons of bitches.
You show your juicybar trick
to the whole damn world?
That was the first time
I pooped so many juicybars!
Then what's up their asses?
How should I know what's in there?
I'm no ass expert.
Then go find out
and resolve this!
Who do you think I am?
This is 0497.
I don't see anything strange.
Not a soul in sight...
Shit! The Diaper Gang!
Cease fire!
Find the girl!
Find the girl, find the girl.
What are you waiting for?
Go after them!
This is evidence one
discovered on the scene.
His name is Jimmy,
and was presumed to be killed
by the Diaper Gang.
He pretended to be
a movie director,
and has a criminal record with
regard to illegal movies.
They were at the crime scene,
and were presumed
homeless hoodlums.
If an error occurred
in the computer on the
numerous ID registrations,
these two culprits are
very likely to have the answer.
So if we analyze
the defecation data
of the checked IDs...
Get to the point!
How are they related
to this case?
Well, they had
an illegal affair...
Shut up, you idiot!
Mobilize all the forces
and catch them all.
WANTED
We found her!
We found one woman
who last defecated
in our records.
The rest of the IDs have
no record of defecation.
The Diaper Gang
cannot defecate.
So their need for juicybars
makes them a big suspect.
If we capture her,
we'll be able to uncover
everything about this case.
A SWAT team is
now positioned
to track down
any massive supply
of juicybars within
three minutes.
Get to the point!
So will you catch them or not?
I will catch them, ma'am.
If you miss them this time,
you'll be the first to die.
Man, this is frustrating!
Look, I'm not
the same old Aachi.
If you wanna survive
in Section 4,
you better not get on
my bad side.
I got many customers waiting
in line besides you, old man.
Alright, I won't get upset.
Anyhow, hoodlums like
you walking
into this fancy hotel
is humiliating.
So quietly use the back door.
Senile old bastard.
Who does he think
he's talking to?
Beautiful, the old man is
coming to buy some juicybars.
How about a nice
whole-hearted shit?
Moron.
I'm the one who
feeds you punks.
What? Moron?
You bitch!
We got them!
All enforcements mobilize
to coordinates 646!
Just rough them up a little.
And remember,
my share is two thirds.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Let's go!
Hold your gun right, idiot!
I got no hair,
but I got the body.
I'm such a hottie.
Cut the crap.
Old man, I told you
to use the back door.
You think my words
don't count?
You son of a...
One, two, one, two.
Ready! Ready!
Throw it!
Who the hell are you?
Where is she?
Who are you talking about?
I can't remember all my chics.
One, two...
You'll be okay, sweety.
Damn it, this is humilating.
You know who I am?
Wait! Let's talk!
So, well...
Over there...
Put your guns down!
- Don't move or we'll shoot!
- Put your guns down!
You little assholes,
how dare...
Who the hell are you?
Going up the stairs with
one leg is a pain in the ass.
What are you waiting for?
Go inside!
Move it!
Diapers! My leg!
Sons of bitches!
My money! My money!
You stupid old man,
don't be such a meanie.
We're in trouble.
We need back-up.
What are you doing?
Get in there and fight!
I hate you. Boss!
You bastards!
I have grenades!
Shit.
Damn it!
My hands are burning.
Get them!
Hurry and stand up!
You sons of bitches!
What have I gotten myself into!
How did things
turn out like this?
And is that little rat
alive or what?
Hold on tight, babe.
You little rat!
You're alive!
You idiot!
How could you bring
the Diapers with you?
I didn't, you moron.
They're the ones who followed me!
- Asshole!
- Yeah, asshole.
Man, you never make
things any easier.
Shut up and just follow me!
Crap, we're screwed.
Oney, do something!
Yeah! Bring it on!
Shit, we got a code
fucking red here.
Get them!
Get them! Get them!
Let go! Let go!
I said let go! Let go!
Damn it.
You son of a bitch!
Hey, who do you think you are?
You asshole.
Think you're a tough guy, huh?
Get him!
I'm a fake.
You lost.
Large illegal distribution
of juicybars...
The toilets in Section 4
were attacked...
The Diaper Gang attacked...
Growing crimes
by the Diapers...
Citizens, please stay calm.
We will poke out
the axis of evil.
Useless idiots!
Wipe them all off this planet!
This situation is terribly...
I won't eat it! I won't!
I'm not a shitmaker
for you dwarves!
- We were annihilated.
- You idiot!
According to a recent report,
a female in her 20s
seems to be related
to this case...
The Diaper Gang will rule
this city soon.
Yesterday we were
forgotten orphans.
But tomorrow we will stand up
as remembered orphans!
Diapers! Diapers!
Damn it!
I was a juicybar tycoon
just the other day.
The Diapers are rich now that
they have Beautiful,
while we're homeless fugitives.
That bitch!
It's all her fault!
This sucks.
How dare you call her that!
Shut your trap!
Beautiful made you rich
with all those juicybars.
Make me rich? Screw you!
You see us with
any juicybars now?
Then what the hell did you do
when my Beautiful got caught?
You're the one
who fainted after one punch!
I'm going.
Where are you going?
I'm going to save Beautiful.
What?
Hey, meathead!
Talk some sense!
Even the pigs can't beat them,
so what the hell
are you gonna do?
I'm going with or without you.
Cowards like you
will always live off of
snitching juicybars.
Hey!
You don't know
what true love is!
Hey!
You stupid romantic.
You dumb Romeo!
We have a traitor among us.
Otherwise,
it's impossible for the Diaper Gang
to obliterate us like this.
Actually, since Geko was
in charge of the
Diaper Gang until now,
we don't know their strategies.
No excuses!
Think we're weaker
than those dwarfs?
We need another plan.
Doctor, long time no see.
I'll get straight to the point.
Can you revive Geko?
I created him,
so it won't be so difficult.
But, I need a lot of corpses.
Very fresh ones.
If you can bring him
back to life,
I'll bring you all the
filth in Section 4.
I'm happy to hear that.
And one more.
Give me his corpse, too.
As you wish.
Damn it.
Wait, you!
You're that little shit!
What's up?
You little prick!
Don't you have anything
better to do?
Go to school, shithead.
I was a juicybar tycoon
just yesterday, damn it.
Tell me! Tell me now!
Where's my Beautiful?
Who are you?
Where's Beautiful?
Tell me where Beautiful is!
You sons of bitches!
Shit!
My motorbike! You assholes!
What the hell
are you doing here?
Just passing by, bonehead.
Then keep going, you twirp.
Mind your own business,
jackass.
You little turd.
Screw you and that
pride of yours.
What, you little dwarf?
You son of a bitch.
You're the worst character
in this movie!
Screw you, asshole!
My baby,
daddy will do you good.
You're so adorable.
If you bring me the scientist
who created Geko,
I will dispose of the Chief.
And I want the number
two position in your gang.
It's yours.
But if you're thinking
of betraying us
or plan to do
something stupid,
then you'll suffer a pain
worse than death.
If you don't kill the Chief,
she'll kill me first.
You can be assured that
I'll never betray you.
I'll be ready for you tonight.
Now do you feel like talking?
I don't know. I don't.
Bastard must be
high on juicybars.
How the hell do you not know
where your home is?
Asshole!
I have no idea!
He's really not gonna talk.
This punk's pretty loyal.
We better just kill him.
No! No!
Doctor, from now on you'll
work for us.
Now even mutants come
looking for me.
This will be quite a new thrill.
I'll go to any place
that has fresh corpses.
Escort him out.
Escort, escort.
When will you dispose
of the Chief?
No betrayer like you deserves
to be in our gang.
When will you dispose
of the Chief?
You raised a good assistant.
If you have the guts,
come to the desert.
You despicable fool,
how dare you betray me.
We can't find any traces
of Dr. Strange.
HAIL THE DIAPER KING!
Damn it, it's boiling hot.
True love conquers everything.
My Beautiful.
Attack!
What the hell is that?
Did they already clash
with the pigs?
That spells bad news for us.
This won't work.
We should think over our plan,
and then come back.
We gotta finish what
we started whether it
kills us or not.
Stop trying to be a hero and
let's just go back.
- You!
- You blockhead,
go without me.
I don't wanna die.
Execution to all who are
caught red-handed.
Geko, you lunatic!
It's dangerous!
Get out of here!
He's coming, he's coming.
Isn't that Beautiful?
Where?
He's coming, he's coming.
Damn it! My head!
Long live the Diapers!
Juicybars! Juicybars!
I told you we should've
just gone back!
Then what about Beautiful?
Who's more important?
Me or Beautiful?
Beautiful.
Think you can kill me?
I'm afraid not.
I told you we should've
just left!
But you go nuts over a chic!
Screw you!
Beautiful.
Stop talking crap!
Beautiful!
- Beautiful!
Hold on tight!
Hold her tight, idiot!
Beautiful's in danger!
Hurry! Pull her in!
Do something!
Put more muscle into it!
No!
Beautiful!
Very interesting-Iooking specimens.
Geko passed the XX point, roger!
Okay, roger!
Hey! Get it ready fast!
Fast! Fast!
What the hell is this?
Untie me!
You crazy old bastard!
Screw you!
He's coming, roger.
What? Coming?
Hey! He's coming!
Here he comes!
Fire!
Stop acting like Paris Hilton!
I let you slide until now,
but you've disrespected me.
I oughta slice your belly
and yank out your chip.
Get ready to die!
Don't touch Beautiful.
You damn hoodlum,
you're such a pain in the ass.
But no more games.
Hey! I'm right over here!
Srew you!
No!
Die, please! Die!
- You...
- Wait, that's...
Jimmy the freak?
When did you start working
for the pigs?
But I killed you with
my bare hands.
Let go!
Let go, you filthy bastard!
Die! Die!
You son of a bitch!
What the hell?
No!
You worthless hoodlum.
Stop, you blue asshole!
You belong down there.
You son of a bitch!
Beautiful.
- You bastard!
- Beautiful.
Beautiful!
Come back here!
Save the world like
you said you would.
Die!
Hey, it stopped.
How dare you.
Around and around we go!
Die!
Cut!
Cut! Cut!
You sluts!
I told you not to do it that way!
How many times do I
have to tell you!
You are charged
for interfering with
police duties,
for organizing an illegal clan,
and for murdering a policeman.
Whether dead or alive,
you're coming with me.
Beautiful! More!
Stretch a bit more!
Oh no, what is this?
You filthy bastard.
Nothing went right whenever
you showed up.
I didn't do anything!
I swear!
Idiot!
Please do something about this!
I don't want to die!
I hate you!
Beautiful! Try harder!
Do something fast!
Stretch out a bit more!
I can't anymore!
Stretch more!
Damn it!
I can't anymore.
- More!
- I can't! I can't!
A little bit more!
I can't stand it anymore!
Be patient, sweetheart.
I'll find you one soon.
Let's find you the right toilet,
so you can let out a big load!
What are you so happy about?
We're millionaires now!
Did you say "we"?
Who's "we"?
We're business partners of course!
Who asked you to be my partner?
In business,
logistics is more important
than production.
Got to know your stuff.
That big mouth never shuts up.
Anyway, your share is
one-fifth.
Stop talking and let's
jet out of here.
If you take a dump on the road,
it's a huge loss.
My shit is supporting you guys.
Better be grateful.
Let's go to the city
and run it dry!
SO LONG!
I'm going to have fun with
this new friend.
RYU Seung-Bum, YIM Chang-Jeong,
HYUN Young, SHIN Hyae-Chul
executive producer
KIM Seung-Bum
directed by
JOE Bum-Jin
screenplay by
JUNG Hye-Won, KANG Sang-Kyun
producer KIM Sun-Ku