Tickets! Great tickets.
Front row seats,
right in the action.
I mean, you can smell...
the sweat.
I guess...
I...
I don't really have to.
Oh, why don't I
call Tony, and he can come
fill in for me, right?
Great.
Oh, yeah! Thank you.
Honey, you're more than welcome.
Yes!
Oh, look what time it is. Huh?
This is a once-in-a-lifetime experience,
and I'm going to share it with you.
Reaches up,
she brings it down.
It was the most powerful thing
I've ever... seen.
And after all this,
he still didn't leave you?
Oh, I'm telling you,
this calls for drastic measures.
Come on, guys,
concentrate.
Are you being clingy?
Clingy, needy, whiny...
Baby talk?
Occasionally. I mean,
I could kick that up a notch.
I used to obsess
over Mike's old girlfriends.
Or better yet, talk about
all your old boyfriends.
It's good, it's good, it's good,
but it's not going to crack this guy.
I mean, this is Defcon Five,
and I have to do something
truly appalling...
it's not funny.
Look, I have to think
of something before tomorrow.
Wait, why not tonight?
Poker night. Boys' night out.
Oh, Mike used to have a boys' night.
Boys' night?
You're giving him a boys' night?
They do it every week.
Before... he met... you.
What are you suggesting?
I think you know
what I'm suggesting.
- Feel lucky, boys?
- Yeah.
Gentle Ben, that's two bucks.
I'm feeling luckier than you.
Glad to not have to sit
through a Celine Dion concert.
That's what true love
is all about, my friend.
I fold.
All right, I'll see your two,
raise you fifty.
She's in love with you?
You kidding me?
She's planned the wedding.
Call.
All right, guys,
- read 'em and weep.
- Oh, shit.
Got ladies over fours, huh?
- Damn.
- Nothing.
I have a three and an ace.
It does not get
any better than this.
Look at that.
Bennykins, I'm home.
Hi, honey.
Hey, Andie.
She has a key?
Is that legal?
I wasn't expecting you.
How'd you get a... key?
Oh, honey, Francesco,
your super,
he made me a copy.
Francesco, huh?
Hmm. All right.
You're not mad, are you,
Benky Wenky?
- No, I'm not mad.
- You're not mad?
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm not mad, I'm not mad.
- Oh, good.
- You know the guys.
- Everybody, Tony, Clar, Francis.
- Oh, yes!
- Hey.
- Watch out!
Hi.
Tony, hi,
- Tony!
- Yeah!
- Ronald.
Joe.
- Joe.
- Hey, Andie, guys.
I didn't mean to interrupt
your little game.
We got it, we got it.
We're all straightened out.
I brought some yummy snacks.
Snacks? Hmm.
The game is hold 'em.
Three up for company,
ante a dollar, please.
Oh, Tony.
Hmm?
- Yucky, yucky pizza.
- Oh.
- Yucky pizza.
- Oh, no.
Yummy, yummy,
cucumber sandwich.
Oh... oh.
- First card up is a nine.
- Thanks.
I'll take one.
Yeah. Sure, yeah.
Good boys. Good.
Here we go... get rid
of those over there.
Thank you very much.
- Three up, three up.
- I went a buck. You follow?
Look around the horn,
look around the horn,
look around the horn.
Ssss...
Thanks, Benny.
Thayer.
That means you, too, Thayer.
Oh, yeah.
All right,
everyone in for a buck.
Next card, five,
nines and fives,
nines and fives.
That's back to you, Tito.
Oh! Nine and a seven.
Go for the straight.
Hmm.
Round two.
Tone, the bone, you're up, man.
She told you my hand.
Peekaboo!
- Oh, hey.
- Hi!
Guys, are we going to play cards here,
or what's going on?
What game are we playing?
We're playing hold 'em?
All right,
I'm already maxed out.
We got a nine up, nine up, guys,
- nine up, nine up.
- Blow.
Blow.
Nobody likes a Mr. Sniffles.
I hate Mr. Sniffles.
Come on, stuffy head.
Good, good, good.
Ooh... white.
- Healthy boy.
- Good. Mm-hmm.
- Healthy.
- Hmm.
Tone, get your head
in the game. Please?
Oh, no.
Are we playing?
Oh, no!
Our love fern!
It's dead!
No, honey, it's just sleeping.
You let it die!
Are you going to let us die?
Hmm?
You should think about that.
What the hell's a love fern?
All right, guys,
let's try to get through
one hand.
Is she on something?
God, I hope so.
Hi.
Are you saying I'm some kind of
- mental person?!
- No, no, no, he wasn't...
Oh, Tony!
What? He was talking about...
- Come on.
- That's it!
- Andie.
- That is it!
I'm taking this love fern
with me.
Hang on.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
ho, ho, ho, ho, ho.
What just happened in there?
I'm going to go listen.
- Yeah.
- Quietly.
Look, this is getting
really creepy.
All right? You're acting
completely insane.
You know that?
Oh, so I am insane.
No, you're acting insane.
Shut up, Krull.
Oh, he is an innocent animal.
And he'll live, okay?
I'm talking to you.
I don't know
if I can be with somebody
who doesn't like animals
and thinks I'm a mental person.
That's what I'm talking about.
Where's the sexy, cool, fun,
smart, beautiful
Andie that I knew?
All right? The one who wanted
to be a serious journalist, huh?
You're up, you're down,
you're here, you're there.
You're like a freakin'
one-woman circus, Andie.
So I guess this means
we're over.
Yeah, I guess so.
Fine.
Oh, finally.
- Ooh!
- Whoa!
It's over, man.
Oh, man, that's...
No, no, no, no, no.
- No, no, no.
- It is, man, it's over.
- Four days. Four days.
- Four more days!
Guys, you were here...
did you just witness
the one-woman homage
to The Exorcist?
You saw it, huh!
Yeah, I did.
I thought it was sexy.
Yeah.
It's not sexy.
- He's right, he's right.
- No, forget it.
So, do-do you think Spears
and Green are going to be
comfortable in
their new office?
Oh, absolutely. Sure.
- Maybe he's excited that
- Guys, stop.
He's going to be
selling Nerf footballs
- Hey, hey, hey!
- For the rest of his life!
He may get, like,
a really good douche campaign.
Hey, that's done!
What? What?
- Couples therapy.
- Of course!
What?
Every time my wife
wants to divorce me,
I suggest couples therapy.
It'll buy you
at least four days.
She-she hates him!
Therapy. Couples therapy.
Yeah, couples therapy.
Couples therapy!
- Couples therapy.
- Come on!
Couples therapy.
- Couples therapy.
Couples therapy!
Whoa!
Ah!
Andie!
Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, listen.
Can you forgive me, sugar puss?
Look, I don't know what
I was thinking, all right?
I-I'm sorry.
I am way out of line, Andie.
Can you... can you give me
another chance?
Haven't you had enough?
Hey, look, I'm willing
to do anything.
Get up.
I'll do...
I'll do anything, Andie.
Get up.
Look, what do you think about...?
What do you think about...
couples... therapy?
Couples therapy?
Couples therapy.
Look, Thayer up there,
he's got this doctor.
He says he's a hell of a guy.
No, I know a therapist
who will work wonders
with somebody like you,
Benjamin.
Yes, that's what I need.
I will call and schedule
an emergency session.
Baby, wh-whatever it takes.
Kiss.
Thank you, sweetheart.
Thank you for understanding.
I love you, Binky...
but I don't have to
like you right now.
Thank you, Andie.
Ah, damn it!
S-S-Shit!
If you're really going
to commit to this,
you're going to have
to open up...
- Yeah.
...and dig deep.
Okay.
Bare that beautiful soul.
Let me see your teeth.
Andie Anderson.
Benjamin Barry.
Please come in.
Hi, welcome.
Before we get started,
how are you planning on paying
for the session?
Sweetie?
How much is it?
$300.
$300?
Mm-hmm.
Whatever it takes, yeah.
So, tell me,
how long have you guys
been seeing each other?
Seven days.
Interesting.
Is it too soon
to be seeing a therapist?
Well, Ben,
seven days isn't like
a lifetime, or anything,
- It's like a week.
- It...
Did you hear that tone?
How can we not have
a gulf between us
with a tone like that?
How are things
between you sexually?
Oh!
Ooh-ooh.
No, no...
- we haven't had sex.
- Oh, no.
Ben has a little, bitty problem.
- I don't have a problem.
- Oh.
Yes, you do.
- No, I do not have a problem.
- Yeah.
It's a big problem.
- I do not have a problem.
- You have a problem.
Look, look, look, wait a minute.
The one night that we even
thought about
getting close to having sex,
all right, she up and decides
she's going to nickname my...
Penis?
Yeah. "Princess Sophia." Ha!
You want to talk about
shooting a man's horse?
Whop! Come on!
I thought it was
a beautiful name.
Hmm, I see, Benjamin.
And when was it
that you first realized
that you were attracted
to other men?
- What?
- Oh, that's serious.
Hmm.
Benjamin, this is a safe space.
Look, it's just simple...
I like women, okay?
It just happened that way.
Methinks thou doth
- protesth too much.
You see? Stop it.
This is the shit
I'm talking about.
What the hell was that?
Whoa, whoa.
What did I do?
I mean, this is what she does.
Stop that!
You know, I'm hearing a lot
of latent anger here, Benjamin.
Rage-o-holic.
I'm not a rage-o-holic!
- I called that one.
- Stop...
You know what...
take a deep breath for me, Ben.
Okay, and let it go.
Just let it go.
Yeah.
Yeah. I feel better.
Okay. Come here.
I've seen this before.
- I've seen it many times.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
Whoo, would you two
like to be left alone?
No.
Maybe you should get a room.
You are hitting
on our shrink!
- No, I'm not.
- Yes, you are!
No, I'm not.
And you are
a pathological flirt!
Jesus, five seconds ago,
I'm gay.
Now I'm a pathological flirt?
I sweat when I get nervous.
Which one is it, Andie?
And besides,
why would I need to hit
on another woman?
You've got more than
enough personalities
to keep me completely occupied.
That was hurtful.
Okay, Ben.
Are you ashamed of Andie?
- Of course he is!
- I'm not ashamed.
Of course he is.
You are!
I'm not ashamed.
How do you think
that makes me feel?
I'm not ashamed of you.
It's like, when I talked
to his mother...
he freaked out.
No, see, you-you did that
behind my back.
She did it behind my back.
I just wanted to say "hi."
Andie, you want to talk
to my mother?
Y-You want to talk to my mother?
Talk to my mother.
Hey, you want to talk
to the whole family?
You can talk
to the whole family.
Hell, we can go to Staten
Island, spend the weekend
with them, Andie.
Now, that is
a positive idea, Ben.
It... it is?
How about it, Andie?
What?
Would you like to go
to Staten Island?
Uncle Ben, hi!
Thanks.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, Mom, Pop,
we're here.
Yeah, bullshit!
Who's that handsome guy?
That's my dad when
he was an ensign in the Navy.
He got stationed here
about ten years ago.
- Bullshit!
- Uh-oh.
Hey, darling.
Hey, sweetie.
How you doing?
I'm glad to see you.
Good. Perfect timing.
You know who this is?
I do, and I need you
to check the baby,
see if he needs changing.
I know who that is.
- Hi.
- Hi, Andie, I'm so happy
to have you here in the flesh.
You're just as pretty
as you sound on the telephone.
Glenda!
I'm coming!
Jesus, Mary, and Joseph.
Excuse me.
Show her upstairs, okay, hon?
Oh, yeah.
And this is Joey, Jr.
Bullshit!
And the whole family suffers
from Tourette's.
I hope that's not a problem.
You're so handsome.
Joey, he suffers
from being a stinky rose.
We're going to go get you
cleaned up, sir.
Go on out back.
Have a good time.
Okay.
Ooh!
Got you.
Okay!
You're it.
He got you.
Oh...
Uncle Arnold says
he's got three kings.
Yeah, right.
Okay, Uncle Arnold.
Now, dare I say it, or not?
I'm just going to say it.
Okay, I'm going to say it...
bullshit!
Hi.
- Honey?
- Oh, wow.
Andie.
Whoa, ho, whoa, well, well!
Come on out here, Andie.
- Meet everybody.
- Okay.
I want you to meet
Ben's father, Jack.
- Well, hello.
- Hi.
Welcome to our humble abode.
This is Andie, Jack.
Oh, thank you.
Nice to meet you.
And this is our Uncle Arnold.
- Hi, Uncle Arnold.
- Oh, hi, good morning.
This is Andie.
You got to watch him.
He farts like a howitzer,
but he's family,
so what are you going to do?
Intestinal complications.
Yeah, right, Arnold. Prunes.
Did you meet Joey?
A female Andy.
L-E.
Nice to meet you.
Okay, here we go now.
The game is Bullshit,
and you are just in time
for the lightning round,
my dear.
I don't really know how to play.
Well, we're going to teach
you how. It's very simple.
Trick is to get rid
of all the cards
in your hand, all right?
So I'm going
to look in my hand,
and I'm going to see
what I've got here.
And, well, do you know?
I've got two aces here.
Well, two aces.
What do you say to that?
What are you
going to say?
- I say bullshit.
- Mm-hmm.
What did she say?
I didn't quite hear.
Did you guys...?
I didn't hear what she said.
What did you say?
I said bullshit!
All right!
Well, she knows how
to play the game,
Yes, sir.
Hey, big daddy,
come to Papa.
Get on over there, big man.
Slick as a whistle.
How you doing, Unc?
Hi, Ben.
- That's my grandson.
- Pop.
Hey, how you doing, buddy?
Got a game of Bullshit
going here?
A little game of Bullshit.
Want to join us?
Good luck.
What'd you leave me with, Joe?
Look at the expert here.
Okay, now, we went
through the deck.
We're going to start
at the beginning now.
So we go to twos.
Let's see, now.
I've got myself one deuce here.
Bullshit.
Whoa!
Bullshit, Pop.
He's a human lie detector,
isn't he?
Try this, son:
Two threes.
Mm-hmm.
One four.
Three fives.
Bullshit.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You see whose name's on top
of the board over there?
Yes, it says "Ben,"
with a star next to it.
You still want to bullshit me?
God, you must be so proud.
I'm doing my best.
What do we got?
Yes.
- Did I b-b-bullshit?
- Got, uh...
No, I told the truth.
Three fives.
He's good. He's the champ.
All right, all right.
Lighten up on me, Jim.
What am I?
Sixes to you.
One six.
One six, all right.
Whoa, look at what I got here.
You see, the key to this game
is being able to read people.
Two eights.
Bullshit.
Bull... shit, Mama.
Huh?
I-I'm going to have to hurt you.
Uh-huh. You see,
Mom's never been
that great at it, but why?
Just 'cause I'm so pure
of heart.
- So pure of heart.
- Bullshit.
Hello, hello!
Yeah, where is everybody?
Hey!
Ho!
Hi.
This is Andie.
Andie, this is my sister, Dora.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
Andie is kicking Ben's ass
in Bullshit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Oh, I like this girl.
- That's right.
Ben's starting a little
card collection.
All right, let me get back
on track here.
Gentle Ben starts with three
ladies, and that's to you.
What do you got to say
about that?
Bullshit.
You heard me.
I said bullshit.
Ooh-ooh.
Ah. Mm-hmm.
Uh-huh. What is that...
seven in a row, Sparky?
I think somebody's met
his match.
Well, I-I, it's...
all about... reading people.
Loser.
Okay. Two kings.
Bullshit?
Bull... shit!
Yeah, you!
Nah, nah, nah, no!
You have met your match.
And you, Mom...
Miss Pure of Heart.
Pop, I told you.
You're hiding behind a badge.
I didn't see anything.
Cheated me.
Betrayed by my own parents.
The only honest man
in this place
is Uncle Arnold, who's asleep.
But I won.
I'm going to go inside
and play with the kids.
Maybe they won't lie,
cheat, and steal.
Okay, keep my name
on top of the board.
Now, Andie, I hope you know
that we are expecting you
to come back here,
because you have held Ben
to his lowest Bullshit score...
Yeah, yeah.
...since his tonsillectomy,
and we are thrilled!
Lowest!
Why, were all his other
girlfriends Bullshit losers?
What other girlfriends?
Ma, he's picky.
You are the first girl
he's ever brought home.
Don't you break
his heart, now.
And that dress. Andie, now,
does that come in my size?
Yes, sir.
My turn?
Yes, ma'am.
It's... heavy.
Turn it on.
Good.
- Keep this clutch in.
- That's the clutch.
Brake here on your right.
Your gears are on the left.
- One down.
- Okay.
Now, when we take off,
you're going to give
a little bit on the clutch.
Uh-huh.
And you're going to go
a little bit here.
A little give, a little go.
How's it go?
A little give and a little go?
That's it.
Whoa!
A little clutch and
a little brake. There we are.
You got it?
I got it.
You got it.
Whoo!
Voila, voila, voila, voila.
I mean, there's a lot of cool
things about a bike, you know?
Use less gas.
In traffic jams, you park
wherever the hell you want.
But at the end of the day...
Thank you.
...chicks dig 'em. Ah!
- Oh!
- Hey!
You look so cute.
Can I ask you a question?
Well, yeah.
Chicks dig this?
Yes, chicks dig this.
I turned!
Oh, oh, oh,
you're driving like a pro.
Yeah, look at you.
Ooh!
Look at this look.
Yeah, now, this shower...
...whoa...
is a little bit tricky.
The hot is actually cold.
The cold is actually hot.
You got to crank it
all the way up, at first,
and...
if somebody flushes
the toilet in Bayonne,
you are going to get scalded.
The towels are right there.
Everything all right?
Is this okay?
Oh, no, it's more than okay.
I love everything
about this house:
The noise, the smells...
Oh, well, the smells...
that's Uncle Arnold,
I mean...
What's wrong?
It's just that when
your mom hugged me today,
she really hugged me...
for winning a game of Bullshit.
Sweetie, that's a good thing.
Smile.
Smile. Now come on.
Give me a smile.
Okay, that's good, that's it.
Yes, you're scaring me.
This is home, huh?
This is home.
Hey, listen,
tomorrow night my boss
is throwing a party
for that diamond account
I was telling you about.
I want you to come with me.
Okay.
Okay?
Yeah.
As my girlfriend.
Are you calling me
your girlfriend?
Yeah. I think I am.
Won't tomorrow be the tenth day
we've been seeing each other?
Mm-hmm.
Maybe after that we'll know.
Listen, don't make any plans
for day 13, okay,
because...
we have a game to go to.
Uh-huh.
Oh!
They're not as good of seats
as you got us,
but this is Game Seven, huh?
Yes?
Ah, come here.
Okay.
Yes?
Lana,
I can't write this article.
Is your computer broken?
I've gotten to know this guy.
Andie, do you see any
patches or insignia
anywhere on my clothing?
No.
It's because I'm not your Girl
Scout leader, I'm your boss.
You'll write the article.
This cover is
at the printer
as we speak, with a special
section on diamonds,
which is going to take care of
my ad quota for the entire year.
I want copy on my desk
in 48 hours.
Okay, but, Lana...
No "but, Lana." You'll do it...
because you're
a professional.
Yes, I am.
You're beautiful.
You look pretty good, too,
Sparky.
Champagne, madam?
Thank you.
Chalk one up
to couples' therapy.
Wow. Some party.
Hmm?
You're going to do great.
I'm going to go to the bar
and get us a couple of drinks.
Oh, good idea.
Okay? And while I do that,
would you please...
head over there, and...
frost yourself.
I can wear those?
Yes, ma'am, you can.
Phillip.
Lana.
I don't see you
at a party for ages.
Now here you are,
throwing the bash of the year.
I'm glad you could make it.
Like them?
Ah, it suits you.
I know!
Harry Winston.
How did you get
all these jewelers
to agree to appear
at the same fete?
At the request of Mrs. DeLauer.
Really?
Yes, you see,
Mr. DeLauer controls
70% of the world's diamonds,
and Mrs. DeLauer
controls Mr. DeLauer.
You're bad.
Ah! Enjoy.
Lana!
This is real?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no...
I insist.
Montrez-moi Isadora,
s'il vous plait.
Yes, sir.
Such beauty
should be celebrated.
Oh!
Isadora.
Oh, no, I'm Andie.
Oh, and a pleasure to meet you,
Andie, but this is Isadora.
Tourne, tourne, s'il vous plait.
84 carats,
named for Isadora Duncan.
Congratulations.
You got her here.
Yeah.
But the question remains...
Does she, or doesn't she?
We're going to find out.
An angel of God.
- Thanks.
- I am Frederick.
Andie Anderson.
Well, it looks like you've got
some competition, anyway.
Miss Anderson will be wearing
Isadora for the evening.
Enjoy the party, Andie.
Merci beaucoup.
Oh, that's stunning!
Fabulous!
Excuse me.
Two champagnes, please, sir.
Pardon me, young man.
Would you be kind enough
to order me a whiskey sour?
Yes, ma'am, I can.
Mrs. DeLauer?
Yes.
I'm Ben Barry
with Warren Advertising.
How do you do?
The pleasure's mine.
It's nice to finally meet you.
I'm very happy to meet you, too,
that's for sure.
Can I get a whiskey sour, please?
I can promise you
that our presentation
will not weary you
in the wrong way, Mrs. DeLauer.
I cannot wait to see
what you present, Benjamin.
Ladies, do you
see what I see?
Oh, Phillip, that's ridiculous.
She couldn't possibly.
Don't be so sure.
She might possibly.
I think I'll go find out.
E-Excuse me.
You're Andie, yes?
Yes.
I'm Phillip Warren.
Oh, you're Ben's boss.
That's right.
Hi, pleasure to meet you.
Pleasure to meet you.
Well, I understand you've been
an inspiration to Ben
in more ways than one,
and I must say,
you look rather inspired yourself.
There isn't a diamond
in the room that sparkles
like a woman in love.
Oh, no.
I'm not in love.
No?
I guess I was mistaken.
No, no, no. I mean...
I mean, I've only known him
for ten days. I...
You can't...
I can't... I can't be...
Ben is a very lucky man.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah.
Mr. Warren,
please don't tell him.
Please don't tell him.
Hey.
Ben, Ben.
Hey, hello, gentlemen.
She loves you;
she loves you not.
What-what is it?
I don't know.
We'll see.
Ben.
Mr. Warren.
Saw her, met her.
She loves you. You win.
Get ready to pitch.
Congratulations, point man.
I'm very proud.
So, you're the new
point man on the DeLauers.
She loves me.
Good for you...
and... good for whoever she is.
Ah, well...
thank you so much.
Oh, you're so very welcome.
Gloating, are we?
Yeah, pretty much.
Warren told us, so...
Yeah, you don't mess
with my man Ben.
Mm.
Your man Ben
is a cheater.
Mm-hmm. The girl
has known about the bet
from the beginning.
She was playing along
so Ben would win.
Tell him to enjoy his
short-lived, ill-gotten victory.
We're going to talk to Warren.
No.
- Let's...
- Come on...
Hey.
Remember us?
- Hi.
You know, uh, Warren
is going to come over here
in a minute,
and it would...
it would be so great if you
could just, you know, like,
act like you don't know
anything about the bet.
I mean, if-if you could tell him
that you-you really,
truly love Ben, you know,
and you weren't just,
you know, pretending,
so he would... he would win,
that would be... huge.
So what's the average
Composure reader like?
Spunky, insatiable.
Uppity? You bet.
If you'll excuse me, Lana,
there is a beautiful
young woman
in a yellow dress
that I must go to.
Andie?
Yeah, she's my "How to" girl.
How to?
Yes. Right now, she's doing
an article called,
"How to... Lose a Guy
in Ten Days."
Just look him
straight in the eye...
Yeah, and just,
and just, you love Ben,
and you never heard
anything about any bet.
Yeah. Love.
No bet. Okay?
I understand.
Awesome.
Yeah, that's good.
Thank you.
You look beautiful.
This poor schmuck
she's been pretending to date...
well, not even
pretending to date...
she's actually dating the guy.
She's doing the most
atrocious things to him.
She's... she's actually
named his...
She's named his...
You're Krull.
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I ask you all kindly
to be seated?
Now that we're all
suitably frosted...
Benjamin, where have you been?
We haven't much time to play.
Ah! And the ladies
do look lovely...
please help me give
a warm welcome
to our special guests
of the evening,
Mr. And Mrs.
Frederick DeLauer.
And now, I want to introduce
a true musical legend
who will perform
some of his Oscar, Grammy,
Tony, and Emmy
award-winning songs,
Mr. Marvin Hamlisch.
Thank you very much.
I really do apprec...
Wow, yes! Give another hand
for... Marvin Hamlisch
is in the house!
Ow!
A lot of you out here
don't know Benjamin Barry.
Well...
shame on you.
'Cause he is a very talented
advertising executive,
a knowledgeable sports fan
and a wagering enthusiast
but most impressively,
he is one hell of a singer,
and he has prepared
a little musical snack
for his new special friend,
Mrs. DeLauer.
Oh. Oh, isn't that wonderful?
So, Ben, why
don't you come up here
and sing your song?
Oh.
Come on, Ben.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Benjamin Barry.
Come on, Ben.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
Andie, Andie.
Whoa, whoa, don't run off.
Don't run off!
Ladies and gentlemen
you do not want
this young lady
to leave the room.
Thayer. Tony.
Would you stop her, please?
You see, tonight, the
really special event
is that we will be singing,
her and I, a duet.
Yes, Miss Andie Anderson.
Could you please give
a warm round
of applause! Thank you!
Andie. Andie Anderson.
Knock 'em out.
Let's see what
our song tonight will be.
Maybe one of her
personal favorites.
Marvin, do you know,
"You're So Vain"?
That's not one of my songs.
Can you work with me, Marvin?
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah, yeah
You walked into the party
Like you were
walking onto a yacht
You had your-your hat pulled
down real strategically
Over one eye, you had a scarf
I think it was apricot
Strategically tipped
below one eye
Yeah, yeah, yeah
One eye in the mirror
As you made sure
you had a real cool...
- Gavotte.
- Gavotte. Yeah.
And all the girls think
that they'd be your partner
They'd be his partner
'cause he's so vain
You probably think
this song is about you
Ben Barry, you're so vain
So, so vain
You probably think
this song is about you
Don't you? Don't you?
Tone deaf and drunk is not
a good combination.
No, you-you fooled
me to win a bet...
Oh, I fooled you?
And you should feel ashamed.
Look, you took me
to a goddamn
Celine Dion concert.
You made me miss the big game.
Oh, smart guy's a rhymer.
Well...
Do we want everybody to know
your lovemaking is lame?
Oh, maybe because
you named my penis.
Yeah, you named my penis.
You named my penis after a dame!
No, I really think
you have to get over that.
Come on, you're so vain.
- No, you're so vain.
- You are so vain.
This is the worst thing
I've ever heard.
And you know that this song
is about you, don't ya?
- No, no.
- Because you're...
You're so vain.
...so vain.
- You're so... vain.
You do know the words
so well, don't you?
There she goes,
ladies and gentlemen.
There she goes.
Thank you very much.
Thanks, guys.
Take it from here, Marvin.
Wasn't she wearing
the Isadora diamond?
Isadora?
Oh, mon dieu.
Scurit!
No, no, no, no, no.
Hold on, Andie Anderson.
I'm not done with you.
You used me...
Oh, I used you?
...to get ahead in your work.
You arrogant...
- Hold it!
...backstabbing jerk!
- Lady, hold it!
- Come on, Andie.
All right,
you drove me half insane
for a goddamn magazine article.
Oh, yeah, and you told people
you could make any girl fall
in love with you, and I...
- Ma'am?
- I was exhibit A.
- Now folks, time out.
- You talk about integrity?
- What?!
Look, please,
just give me the necklace.
Then you guys can go on
and kill each other.
So that's what I was, huh?
I was a guinea pig.
Somebody you could test
your theories on?
Yeah, and I...
and I was...
just a girl
somebody picked out in a bar.
Yeah, you know what? Big deal.
Hell, I'm sure now
you can even use it
as a little twist in your story.
It's a good idea.
Maybe we should bet on it.
You know what?
You did your job now, Andie.
Yes, I did.
You wanted to lose a guy
in ten days.
Congratulations.
You did it.
You just... lost him.
No, I didn't, Ben.
Cause you can't lose something
you never had.
Well...
...it's not what I expected.
It's better.
Congratulations.
This shows me
you're ready to be unleashed.
From now on,
feel free to write
about anything.
Anything?
Wherever the wind blows you.
Even politics?
No, the wind's not going
to blow you there.
What about religion,
poverty, economics...?
This wind
is really more
of a light breeze.
What can I write about, Lana?
Whatever you want.
Shoes.
Laser therapy,
dressing for your body type.
Use your imagination.
The sky is the limit.
Thank you
for this opportunity, Lana.
Okay.
And thank you for
making it easy
for me to turn it down.
No. I mean, look,
it's not something I'm proud of.
Obviously, if I could...
do it over again,
I'd do some things differently,
you know?
Say, it's good to talk
to you, though, man.
It really is.
Ah, I know it.
You are the only one...
that knows us both.
Yeah.
Hmm.
You want to go?
You want to go to the game?
Well, go ahead,
'cause I'm not going.
Seventh and final game
of what has been
a classic series between...
Sweetie, I wouldn't have gone,
either.
I mean, I-I would have liked
to have gone,
but they probably
wouldn't let me.
You're doing the right thing.
Oh, sweetie.
There's the Chinese.
I'm coming.
Okay.
Okay, so that's going to be...
Michelle?
Andie...
that wasn't the Chinese.
It's Mike.
Mike?!
Yeah, what do I do?
What do I do?
Talk to him.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Mike?
Mike?!
Hi.
So, um...
what are you doing here?
I don't know exactly.
Um...
It was last night...
I-I was...
I was just lying there
and trying to sleep, and...
you know that... that perfume
you sprayed on my pillow?
Oh, yeah.
Well, that smell is gone now,
and, uh...
Michelle, I-I want it back.
I, um...
I don't know
if you can have it back.
Right.
Yeah.
Okay.
But I... I'm willing
to-to consider it.
Okay.
- Yeah.
- Oh, my...
These are for you.
Thank you.
Hi.
We could... kiss.
I remember where you live.
Who needs men?
Ladies... frost yourselves.
Mmm...
Beautiful.
And cut it.
Very nice.
You like?
Oh, it was superb.
Okay, let's go one more.
Right away, people.
Real good.
I'll keep working on it.
Tim, can I see playback?
Open me, Ben.
Please, break my binding.
- Jesus.
- Please.
- Get that out of here, man.
- Please?
Straightening this out.
You might want to read this.
Ah, no thanks.
Yeah?
"I've lost a guy,
and I don't know why.
"What went wrong?
"When I started writing
this month's column,
"I wanted to commit the certain
silly dating faux pas.
"What I didn't realize was
"that I was making
the biggest mistake...
of all."
Here. Trust me.
Read it.
Come on set.
Andie Anderson?
Excuse me, ma'am.
Holy crap.
Where's Andie Anderson?
She's not here.
- Where is she?
- She quit.
She's got an interview
in Washington.
When is she leaving?
- Today.
- When?
Well, like, now.
You're not a therapist, are you?
Oh.
No.
Good job, though.
You owe me 300 bucks.
Andy!
Hey!
Ben!
Pull over, we need to talk.
Are you trying
to get yourself killed?
If that's what it takes, yeah.
Now pull over the cab.
Sir...
excuse me, sir.
Can you please pull the car over?
We're in the middle of a bridge, lady.
I can't pull the car over here.
Okay, well, do you have an ashtray
or something I can throw up in?
Gee, lady.
Watch it, broad!
What the hell was that?
Is this true?
Ben, please.
Or are you just trying
to sell magazines?
I meant every word.
Well, where you going?
I have an interview.
Yeah, in Washington.
I know.
Where you going?
Ben, it's the only place
I can go
and write what I want to write.
No, I'm not buying that.
You can write anywhere.
I think you're running away.
Why don't you save your mind
games for your next bet, okay?
I am not running away.
Bullshit.
Excuse me?
You heard me.
Bullshit.
Hey, lady, what do ya wanna do?
Take the lady's luggage
back to her place.
She has alternate transportation.
You callin' my bluff?
You bet I am.
Look who made the trip with me.
It's our love fern.
Oh, Benny-boo-boo,
boo-boo-boo.