Presented by
CJ Entertainment
in association with
Discovery Venture Capital
Corea Entertainment
production
Hey, transfer student.
I'm here to give you a lesson,
not to play hide-and-seek.
Pricks like you always think
it's cool to fail a grade.
Look at him.
You, son of a bitch.
This is a no-smoking area!
- You bastard!
- What?
- That hurt.
- Why'd you hit me?
- Wasn't it blue?
- It was pink.
Are you okay, Jong-soo?
Our leader's still alive.
Did you hit me? It was you, huh?
Tell me, you shitheads!
Who the hell
threw something at me?
Hey!
You rotten punks.
If I told you to behave,
then you should listen.
This is why
I can't wear skirts.
Where are you going, asshole?
I heard you're the boss here.
Of course I am, asshole.
You son of a...
Then keep being the boss.
I don't care.
Hey asshole,
think you'll be the boss then?
Fuck, you're just a tutor.
Fuck? Oh my godness!
You little twirps.
You wanna die?
MY TUTOR FRIEND
You couldn't hold out
and quit again?
Mom, I can't do it.
Think making a living is that easy?
Have you forgotten already?
After your father lost his job,
I had to work so hard...
Okay, just give it to me.
Deliver it to Room 201, 202
in Chungwon Building.
I got you another tutor job.
If you give up on this one,
I'm giving you up.
Mom!
Remember my rich friend
I told you about?
She wants you to teach her son
for three months.
All you have to do is
making him study for two hours.
Do your best. This job will cover
your tuition for a semester.
She's right.
So, you must be Su-wan.
I'm Ji-hoon's mom.
How do you do?
It's the last room upstairs.
My poor face...
So you're the new teacher.
Nice to meet you.
Wow, you're handsome.
Kim Ji-hoon?
Ji-hoon is my elder brother,
I'm Sae-hoon.
I see.
Nice to meet you.
Same here.
You're very pretty.
Cute boy,
he's got good tastes.
Good luck with my brother.
This is a teenager's room?
It's big enough for a family.
Hi, I'm Choi...
I'm Choi Soo-wan
your new tutor.
Damn it, I told you
I didn't want a tutor!
Stop staring, damn it.
So you're 21?
So am I, born in March.
Got a problem with that?
How dare you?
Regardless of age, I'm your teacher.
I don't know
how you got that way.
No, I don't care. You little prick
better behave, got it?
...is what I want to say.
Fine then. It's fine with me.
Frankly, I don't like
to be called teacher.
So let's be friends.
So how shall we have class?
I'm busy with
classes on Tuesday, so...
Tuesday and Thursday,
from seven to nine.
And from one on Saturday.
Textbooks, procedures,
it's all up to you.
But it's up to me
whether I come or not.
Just fill in the hours and go.
Money?
I'll just give it to you.
Mom, do I have to do it?
So what's your point?
Alright, I'll do it!
I'll just do it, okay?
Smoke later.
I'm smoking
because I'm pissed now,
so are you asking me
to be pissed later?
It's hard to have class.
Then don't piss me off.
Damn it.
Then don't piss me off, too.
And textbook?
This is my English textbook.
Don't push it, okay?
What are you doing?
The best of its kind.
What is?
Don't you know?
Looks just like a flat screen TV.
Study!
Your nickname's
Country Chick, huh?
How'd you live
with a face like that?
Is this your tutor uniform?
You wore it last time,
so did you even wash it?
Kim Ji-hoon speaking.
- Gross, he's got the same ring tone.
- I don't want to go.
Where?
There aren't any hotties there.
I'm getting tutored right now.
So what are you bastards
doing not studying? Hang up.
Try reading it.
This is boring.
Man, this is so boring.
Where are you going?
No, I just came in.
I was studying,
and went to the store.
Tell your teacher
to have dinner with us.
That's why I came home early today.
It was on such short notice,
so I'm sorry there isn't much.
But eat plenty.
Yes, Ma'am.
Let's pray.
Like I've always said,
we're able to sit at this table
thanks to our heroes.
Due to the gangsters who fought
for us since Japan's occupation,
Sirasoni, Kim Du-han, Lee Jung-jae,
lm Hwa-su, Yoo Ji-kwang,
We're sitting here thanks to
these wonderful and great ancestor.
I'm grateful for them to bring
this tasty food to our table.
Thank you. Thank you.
The end. Let's eat.
Have a nice dinner, teacher.
Sir, what is this?
It's delicious.
Cow testicles.
Hey! Don't eat
at my house anymore.
You're disgusting.
Stop staring or I'll turn your eyes
into golf balls...
...is what I said to myself.
Please forgive
my evil thoughts.
When I tutor him,
I imagine ripping his guts out
and letting it rot.
I imagine him getting run over,
and his two legs break.
I imagine a brick falling on him
and smashing his brains.
Father, please forgive
these sinful thoughts.
Now that your sins
will be forgiven...
Wait, there's more!
When that bastard
smokes in front of me...
The way you smoked in the gym
looked spectacular.
When you spun around
and flicked your bud,
your back was so flexible,
and your legs were so stretched,
it was the greatest move
I've ever seen.
Actually, the gym is
no-smoking area.
By the way, how did you fall
two grades behind?
Kim Ji-hoon.
I'm Madeleine.
It's Yang Ho-gyung.
You're not Madeleine.
I use my Korean name
only for official reasons.
Do what you like.
Give it to me.
'Contradiction. ' Calvin Klein.
You use cologne, right?
I thought this would suit you.
Contradiction. Isn't it perfect?
The two of us meeting
in a place like this.
This is a contradiction.
Why don't you just marry him?
That's the idea. I finally met
the dream guy I was waiting for.
Dream guy?
Ho-gyung, one sec.
Hey, you old fart. Heard you
got a taste of living abroad, dickhead.
No wonder I didn't like you.
Yeah, so how'd you ever know
what goes on in the other land?
That queer hairstyle...
Oh gosh. I'm sorry.
You shouldn't have acted weak
from the beginning.
Now it's time to come out strong.
Whatever he says to you,
pretend not to listen.
And drill him with hard questions.
Throw them at him.
And then say,
"You don't even know this?"
- Okay, he's dead meat now. Victory!
- Victory!
Just do it!
Hi, Country Chick.
As if the moon went into the clouds.
As if, like, or as.
These are used for similes.
Number three is correct.
Can you give me some examples?
Ugly like Country Chick.
Ugly as Country Chick.
As if the Country Chick is ugly.
Excellent. Next question.
You feeling alright?
Why are you smiling? Wanna die?
- It's good to smile.
- On pretty faces it is.
The next question
deals with a group of poets.
Oh boy, this might be
too hard for you.
It's blood.
Hurry and wipe it!
You'll stain the desk!
Is the desk more important?
Whenever I see blood, I feel nauseas,
okay? Hurry and wipe it.
Where are you going?
We're not done yet.
Change your damn ring tone.
Hi, you've reached
Kim Ji-hoon's phone.
Who the hell are you
to answer Ji-hoon's phone?
Where the hell are you?
Why are you with Ji-hoon?
Give him the phone. Now!
What? You bitch.
Do you want your head
shoved down the toilet?
Come the hell out.
So I can put your face
in a mixer and drink it!
Ji-hoon, honey.
Are you still in the shower?
Hey!
Hurry and come out.
Since you're gone... Go to hell!
Stop the circus act.
Forgot your clothes?
Then turn around,
so I can get dressed.
What are you doing?
We have an hour left of class.
Then go in an hour,
and say I'm sleeping.
No, I can't do that.
Just shut up and go later,
I'll give you the money.
Hey.
Do you want me so much?
I can't lie.
Hold it in, okay?
How could you want your student?
You're scaring me.
That's not what I meant.
Why do you want to
get tutored anyway?
If it's to make a fool of me,
then stop getting tutored.
I'm not doing this for myself,
my old dad wants me to.
My old dad is really scary.
He'll cancel my credit cards
if I don't do this.
So don't get so upset.
It's bad for your health.
Let's live easily. See you later.
Hey! Hey!
Who are you?
Were you that bitch
on the phone?
Why are you coming out
of Ji-hoon's place?
I'm his tutor, so what?
Tutor? You're in college?
Then how come
you look so tacky? Watch it!
You're in high school, huh?
I'm older than you, so be nice!
Wanna play it rough,
tacky girl?
Hey!
The way you look is a relief.
I know it'll never happen,
but if you flirt with Ji-hoon
for even a second, you're dead.
Just tutor him well. Got it?
You rotten tramps.
Don't you have any older sisters?
Do it with the light on, idiot.
You scared me.
Hurry inside.
Hey, Kim Ji-hoon! What's up?
You're my handsome man
I fell in love at first sight
If it's okay,
I want to wake up by your side
Feel it!
Don't worry at all
I already know
what you're thinking
I don't have any
past love or memories
I love only you
Why don't you trust me?
You're the only one
in my life till I die
No, even if I die,
my love is only for you
So please open your heart,
trust me and love me
I reserved...
You idiot. You hit the cancel button,
not to reserve button!
Asshole!
What did you do now?
Wanna die?
It wasn't me!
Freeze, it's the police!
Tell them there's one more.
Say they missed a pretty boy
looking bastard, okay?
- Go!
- Get the hell going!
They said Kim Ji-hoon
isn't a minor.
Shit, that's right!
Get it right, you asshole!
You sons of bitches!
Fuck!
Why haven't you left yet?
You're not asking
to stay over, right?
You're not my type.
Take a taxi and go.
What's wrong with you?
Gone crazy?
I've met a lot of misfits before,
but you're the worst.
Why do you go to school?
To show off your money?
Even though you pay me to tutor,
you shouldn't do this.
I should get some respect at least.
You're not even a person,
so what's the use in learning?
Watch your mouth.
Why? You wanna hit me?
Fine! Hit me!
You should be ashamed
of being two grades behind.
Then stay in high school until
you're 30 or 40, you bastard!
As long as I got paid,
I thought it would be okay,
but I can't sell out
my pride anymore.
Bye.
Guys who are all talk
aren't really tough. He's a fake.
You need to be tougher
on guys like him.
But seeing the way he acts
and looks at me,
could he really hurt me?
It's all an act. Sis, you don't know
high school kids these days.
A third of our class pierced their ears.
Some even pierced their bellies.
Why isn't mom answering the phone?
Shit! What a shame...
Aren't you coming in?
Sit straight.
Don't be late anymore.
Call me two hours earlier
if you're late.
So I won't waste my time.
I thought you didn't
want to come anymore.
If you disagree with me, then fire me.
And we'll call it quits.
I've had a truckload
full of tutors before you.
But I was never the one
to say quit first.
They're the ones
who left first.
I thought you'd quit
in less than a month.
But this is fun.
I've never quit something
I started.
We'll see who is fun.
We were going to
study phrases, right?
Hey, do we really
have to study?
Then what else
is there to do here? Date?
Let's study.
Chinese phrases are usually
on tests, so listen carefully.
You know
'Four Enemies One Soul, ' right?
Yeah, fighting thugs
on all four sides.
'Small Needle Big Molehill.'
Exaggerating your ass off.
'Dark Play Good Shot.'
Good shot?
I know good shots.
In pool, you have several
good shots to win the game.
Like for example,
you have the snap shot.
'True Intimacy Friendly Foe.'
Listen carefully. You may think you
have a lot of friends now,
but if you're not true to them,
then it won't last.
If you run out of money,
then they'll leave you in a flash.
Watch your mouth, bitch.
What? What did you just say?
What the hell are you doing?
No smoking during lessons.
Do it on break time.
No, just quit instead.
Damn it.
Cheers!
What did I tell you?
You have to come out strong.
That was my advice.
I'm the one who said
guys are hypocrites.
So I'm the one
who gave her courage.
Hey, hey. I'm the one who taught her
the special methods of tutoring.
What's wrong with you two?
It's my life that I'm risking.
So this occasion is for me. To me!
Remember, come out
strong one more time,
then you'll totally control him.
Don't worry.
He's in the palm of my hands.
English idioms can only be memorized.
Since your brain is blank,
it'll be to your benefit.
Really funny.
You should memorize
these idioms.
Be careful, watch out, take care...
That's what you should do.
Put up with, bear, and stand
are other examples.
They always come out on tests,
so memorize them.
Here's an easy way
to memorize them.
Imagine a bear standing.
The bear stands, so...
That's right. When a bear stands,
so will his dick.
Get your head
out of the gutter.
You better not
hit my head again.
I told you to turn off your phone!
It's yours.
Hello?
Si-kyung, is that you?
Where are you? Really?
When? I missed you so much.
You sent a postcard to our club,
but you didn't mention me at all.
When? Really?
Okay. Bye, bye.
What?
There's actually some guy
who calls you?
He's on a different level
compared to your airhead girls.
I bet he's ugly.
He's more handsome than
any actors on the planet.
I haven't seen him,
so don't lie.
He's not a bonehead like you
who only likes pretty girls.
So you accept the fact you're ugly?
It's a good thing.
It's mine.
Kim Ji-hoon speaking.
I can't hear you.
Speak slowly and clearly.
Really?
You can't!
I can't let you go today!
If you keep this up,
I'll tell your dad!
Get out of my way! It's urgent!
I won't move.
I'm not kidding, damn it!
You can't go!
You're driving me crazy.
Hey! You rotten bastard!
Engine stop!
What situation is this?
We're on our way out
to buy a textbook.
Your teacher can buy it herself.
We were going to pick it together.
And she didn't know
the bus to the bookstore.
You little...
Yes, we need
an English textbook.
One that fits Ji-hoon's
level just right.
Then go buy a book,
and take a picture with it
to show me proof.
Ji-hoon! Ji-hoon!
Hey! What are you doing here?
So they're up there?
Yeah.
You two wait here.
Hey, so why did you come?
Think I wanted to come here?
So you couldn't resist
and sided with him?
You worthless traitors.
Hey assholes,
Ji-hoon's nothing without money.
Today, I'm going to make you all
regret siding with Ji-hoon.
Shit, do you like
getting your ass whooped?
What? So he's in a fight right now?
You idiot, think you
came here for a date then?
I thought you liked him,
so how could you be so calm?
Stop acting
like you're his mom.
If you're that worried,
then go up yourself, damn it.
Stop smiling, you asshole!
Hurry and get off.
Get over here. Come closer.
The textbook.
Hurry and stand straight.
Lean forward. Lean.
Smile.
Smile. Raise the book.
Smile!
Isn't he Kim Ji-hoon?
It is him!
Know him?
So this guy is your student?
So my temperamental sister
is still alive?
Hurry and tell me
what you know about him.
I heard this transfer student
trampled all over Lee Jong-soo,
the boss of Surim High.
He was a third year senior.
I heard he was so fast,
you couldn't see him move.
But why's he getting tutored?
Were there any rumors
that he didn't hit girls?
None.
I thought he was a fake.
But I didn't know it was him.
Can I have this picture?
I wanna show it off.
Officer!
Where are you going?
Please don't leave.
You can't leave, okay?
Mommy!
You scared me.
Going somewhere, Ma'am?
I have an alumni meeting.
Didn't your mom tell you?
Oh, right.
So no one's home right now?
Ji-hoon is, why?
Stop that! My Ji-hoon is not
that kind of boy.
But still.
Have a nice class.
Go driver.
What was I going
to teach you this time?
What's wrong with you today?
You were going to teach verbs.
'Tutor Freezes to Death
After Teaching Verbs'
Verbs might be
a bit hard for today.
What else?
What's wrong with you?
Feeling sick?
How about prepositions?
Prepositions?
I like sex positions better.
What are you doing?
Let's study instead.
Bear me my child.
No! No!
No, we're still too young.
Are you fantasizing?
What's with you? I already have
too many girls who want me.
Take this off, too.
But I'll have to go barefoot.
I know that, you idiot.
Hurry and take it off.
See if he has anything else.
Satisfied now?
Hey, take this, too.
I'll tell my brother you said hi.
Of course you will, boy.
Wait. Put these on at least.
If you get to know me,
I'm a good guy.
Be careful going home.
Sometimes I vomit blood.
I must have tuberculosis.
Do you know that
it's contagious?
I look too healthy to be sick.
So all this came from a
middle school kid's bag?
Yes, isn't it great?
We should make him
into a regular here.
If you beat up Ji-hoon,
we'll give you everything.
Only if he comes.
Why do you scums always
hang out at a pool hall?
Got nowhere else to go?
Think we like coming here
because we wanna?
Then tell me where else
we should hang out, asshole!
Stop babbling, idiot.
Are you Kim Ji-hoon?
Maybe.
Be nice to him, asshole!
He's a Makjubshi Gang boss
and they control this turf.
You look like a
real pain-in-the-neck.
Hey, have you heard
of our gang?
I don't care what gang it is,
but your zipper's open.
Bastard.
Gonna hit me when I look down?
Crazy bastard.
Then leave it open and fight.
Son of a bitch.
It's blood.
Big trouble.
If he sees blood, he goes nuts.
You stood me up again,
you rotten bastard.
Why aren't you giving me
the chance to talk to you?
Anyway, lessons are over.
I'm too scared of you,
so I can't come anymore.
I'd rather my mom kill me.
Good-bye.
Stop pretending,
and help me up.
What happened to you?
It's blood!
Don't scream, okay?
Be quiet or die.
Wanna die?
Will you be quiet?
Come on, damn it. Stop looking and
bring the bandage. It's in that drawer.
Okay.
What shampoo do you use?
But I use soap.
Don't be so rough, damn it.
Name.
Kim Ji-hoon.
Age.
Twenty-one.
Employment.
Student.
What college?
I'm in high school.
Are you proud of that, asshole?
Here's your plane ticket,
so go back.
I won't.
Go before I get angrier.
I blocked your expulsion,
but there's no use in staying. So go!
No, you go.
I'm too old to study abroad,
idiot!
I told you to
punch faster, boy.
Go.
I won't go.
Give me all your credit cards.
Father! Please, not that...
Did you call, sir?
Clean out his pockets.
Dad, you're being too cruel.
Don't come closer.
You'll die if you do!
Dad! Dad!
'Su-wan's Fried Chicken'
Open the door and come out!
Okay, already.
So what brings you
to a chicken store, Madam?
Don't be so cold.
You being the only friend
I can turn to makes me mad.
So you came to
pick a fight again?
Ji-hoon was never like that.
Even though he fought sometimes,
he was a nice boy.
And he never started the fights.
I think it was wrong
to send him to America.
It was my idea, you see.
It's been a week
since he ran away.
What if something bad
happens to him, Kyung-ja?
Why is he so late?
Don't you have tutoring
lessons today?
That's too bad.
Si-kyung isn't your man anymore.
Here he comes!
It's a gift from Ji-hoon.
Wow, can I try it on?
Think it'll look good on you?
Shall I buy you one, too?
Get a life.
Think you can afford this?
Wow, Ji-hoon,
what a great watch.
It's a Bvlgari. It's my present to him.
It must be really expensive.
'Are you some kid to run away?'
'Think you're cool?'
'Hungry, huh? I'm eating noodles'
'I envy you to
run away at that age'
'No, I wanna come, too'
'I like getting paid still,
so don't come back'
'Wanna come home, huh?'
'Why won't you study abroad?'
'Can I go for you instead?'
- Kim Ji-hoon speak...
- You finally answered!
Think this phone is for you?
Why'd you fill it
with messages?
Let's meet. Where are you?
Why?
You hate going abroad that much?
Others would die to go.
Forget it.
I'll go crazy talking to you.
Hey,
let's meet at your place today.
Just worry about your own life.
Come back,
so I can give you a present.
I'm hanging up.
Anyway, why do you
need to go to school?
Since you're rich,
you won't have to worry later.
My old man wants me
to graduate high school. Satisfied?
You like your dad, don't you?
I knew you had a nice side in you.
What the hell?
Why did you come here?
Think this is your home?
You told me I had to
fill in the hours to get paid.
You greedy snob.
You make me sick.
Then what about you? You came
for your present already?
Present, my ass. What is it?
Give it to me.
Here it is. I'm your gift.
Have you gone nuts?
I don't want it.
Listen carefully.
I'm your guardian angel who'll
help you go, I mean, stay home.
What for? You want something
from me, huh?
Dummy.
You should be grateful.
Fine. Just don't call me
Country Chick anymore.
Do I look like a Country Chick?
No, her sister.
Su-wan, Ji-hoon's
father is here. Ji-hoon!
You can't go!
Go study abroad.
No.
Want a beating?
Kim Bong-man!
What is it?
Sir, just give Ji-hoon
to me instead.
Wait a minute. Ji-hoon still hasn't
fulfilled his military service.
And he has no job,
but you want to marry him?
Pardon?
No, that's not what I meant.
I meant as Ji-hoon's teacher.
Sit first.
Sit and let's listen to Su-wan,
I mean, his teacher.
Please sit.
Yes, if he studies abroad,
it'll open up new doors.
And maybe he'll change
into a new person.
But it could turn into a failure
if he doesn't want to go.
And Ji-hoon could become a
drug addict and join the mafia.
So what are you saying?
So if you could just trust him...
You're telling me to trust him?
Although I know
it'll be hard to do...
To be more exact,
since this is about
Ji-hoon's life,
I think it'll be good to
respect his decision, sir.
If he makes the wrong decision,
then we have no choice
but to decide for him.
I'll raise my average above 50
on the next mid-term.
What did you say?
Ji-hoon!
I'll get above a 50, okay?
Wait a minute, sir!
From an expert's perspective,
this is an abnormal act of...
Shut the fuck up!
It's none of your business!
Do you know me?
I know what I'm doing.
Have you really gone crazy?
Speak Korean
so I can understand.
I'll get above a 50, okay?
If I don't, do as you like.
Fuck! Fuck!
Just tell him
you'll go abroad.
Make some sense. Pack!
And I'll reserve your ticket.
Do you think raising your grades
is as easy as fighting?
If you don't wanna help,
then leave!
Yeah, you won't need my help
since you speak English well!
Why do you need tutoring?
I can speak English,
but I can't read it!
It's different on tests!
This is insane.
Then why did you
make that promise?
How do you expect to raise
your average from 8 to 50?
God can't even help you.
Feel bad? I'm sorry,
but I have to say it.
It's better than
a promise you can't keep.
There's no use in having
an I-can-do-it attitude.
Stop speaking nonsense,
and tell me what to study.
Peasants' Uprising of 1895.
Are you feeling okay? Did you hurt
your head when you fought Jong-soo?
He's a cruel bastard
for hitting your head.
Do you know about
the Peasants' Uprising?
What?
It was caused by a death
in the Ulmi Year.
Do you know what death it was?
What?
Queen Myungsung was killed
by the yakuzas.
Know who Queen Myungsung is?
Come on.
Think I'm that dumb?
It's Actress Lee Mi-yeon.
You idiot.
It wasn't her in that TV series?
It was Kang Soo-yeon, idiot.
Fuck, why does he have
to study all of a sudden?
I should've just picked randomly.
That's what I'm saying.
Here's some solid advice.
Do as your father says.
Wanna die?
Go become a mafia gangster,
and form a global gang.
Yeah, becoming a national hero
will be easier.
You call yourself a tutor?
Then you think
a tutor can do magic?
What will you do
if I get above a 50, huh?
From here to there are the
questions I taught you before.
So you could've
gotten a 60 score.
But the result? Only 18.
Anyway, so what'll you do
if I get above a 50?
You get above a 50?
Then I'll dance on stage
at our school festival.
That would be fun.
You made a promise, okay?
Sorry to call all of you here.
I have a problem,
so you'll have to help me.
I'll assign you a subject,
So make 100 questions each.
At least half of them
must be on the test.
It's mine.
Ji-hoon, you can smoke
two cartons during class.
Ji-hoon, please.
Let's talk about it.
Let's be reasonable!
You can't do this to me!
I helped you with the test!
The next entry is
a Junior majoring in English.
Let's welcome Choi Su-wan!
Hi, I'm Choi Su-wan,
a Junior majoring in English.
I hope you enjoy it.
Bye.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
Weren't you embarrassed
for a girl?
Why didn't you
just dance naked?
It looked like a strip show.
Who's the one
who told me to dance?
Have plans this sunday?
None of your business.
Just tell me. Although I know
you won't have any.
Our club is visiting
an orphanage. Why?
Is that bastard going?
Who? My honey, Si-kyung?
Honey, my ass.
Why else would I be going
if he wasn't?
Hey, is that a volunteer's attitude?
Think what you like. Bye.
How do you do?
I've been thinking a lot.
It's been on my mind constantly.
So I've had many sleepless nights.
Just say you want
to screw her, asshole
Si-kyung.
Su-wan, it's not a choice,
it's fate.
I'm fine with throwing
my everything away.
My family, friends, and future.
My mind and body
isn't mine anyway, Su-wan.
Si-kyung.
Si-kyung, are you okay?
Hey, Kim Ji-hoon!
What are you doing there?
What'll you do now?
They're not your friends anymore.
Look at my arm.
I can't bathe and wipe my ass.
And look how dirty my hair is, asshole.
Know how precious
the right arm is?
Shit, only if your big head
hadn't dodged him.
Fine, I saw you in action
at the pool hall,
so I'll make you Number 2,
okay?
Number 2?
Shit. Ji-hoon, you bastard.
What's taking you so long?
Are you drunken?
You're pathetic for a tutor.
You don't wanna get paid, huh?
What?
Hi.
How long have
you been drinking?
Sorry.
Let's have today's class here.
Today's subject
is broken hearts.
Did you get dumped?
Nope.
Yeah.
Nope
Wanna die? Stop screwing around.
Everyone, I've been dumped!
I've been dumped!
Everybody,
I've been dumped...
What the hell
was so good about him?
At first,
I liked his soft smile.
And then...
I liked his voice.
And since I liked liking him,
I liked him even more.
And then I loved him.
Since I loved him,
my heart became broken.
But I could only let him go.
There's nothing I can do.
I'm stupid, heart-broken,
hopeless, and down.
Hurry and get up!
You're too drunken.
Ji-hoon, what are
you two doing?
Now you're trying
to seduce him with tears?
Ji-hoon, don't trust her.
Since you're studying with her,
the guys are leaving you.
Hey, I'm really tired already,
so you better go, okay?
Ji-hoon!
It's you. The City Chick.
Nice to see you.
Wanna drink with me?
Have you gone nuts?
You're always mean.
Stop acting so drunk,
damn it..
Why'd you hit my pretty face?
Come here and
I'll give you a kiss. It's so soft.
You crazy bitch!
Ji-hoon!
Let go.
You're really overdoing it today.
What's gotten into you?
This is the place.
Why? Wanna throw up?
On a rainy night...
By a red telephone booth...
Under the streetlight...
I wanted my first kiss
at a place like this.
You're really overdoing it.
I even practiced a pose.
Like this.
Why? Why does God
have to be my rival?
Hey!
Who are you to make her cry?
Su-wan may be a Country Chick...
Man, I'm pissed.
She's not worth
getting hurt from you!
I think there's
been some mistake.
Mistake, my ass.
I don't know who she is,
but if I see that
she's worse than Su-wan,
you and her are dead.
Got it? So who is she?
Fine, the sweetheart
who's in your heart now.
This is making me sick.
Who is she? I said who?
You're making a mistake.
It's not a woman.
I'll be a father soon.
- What?
- A father.
You rotten son of a bitch.
You already have a kid?
Rotten bastard.
Thanks for the milk, asshole.
You bastard.
Why'd you hit him? Why?
Do you have to keep this up?
Okay, hit me. Hit me.
Are you really a girl?
Why does your punch sting?
Feel better now?
Was he your first love?
Has this happened to you?
Think I'm the type
to get dumped like you?
Have you ever
truly loved someone?
Probably not
with a temper like that.
Wanna fly into the sky?
I'm serious.
Like it?
I like it! Very much!
Tomorrow is our last lesson.
That's right.
Hey, Su-wan.
What?
I've been thinking.
You're a pretty cool chick.
Now you know?
This is the first time
I've told somebody this,
but I think I like you.
Hello?
Su-wan. Su-wan.
Can't you hear me?
Su-wan, can you hear me?
What? What? I can't hear you.
Su-wan, pull the left string!
Don't panic.
Su-wan, are you okay?
It hurts.
You have to study English consistently.
There's no other way.
Study the idioms and synonyms
I wrote down before your test.
You've done a good job.
Well, I...!
I hope I was a
good teacher to you.
There's no need to emphasize
that you were a teacher.
I understand.
Wait a sec.
Oh boy, my legs hurt.
Su-wan!
Oh my gosh, it's my friend.
What are you doing here?
You bad girl, how'd you
catch me on a date?
This is my friend, Su-wan.
- Hello.
The guy I mentioned.
The med student.
Hello.
Yes, hello.
Who have you been
hiding from me?
No, he's the one
I've been tutoring.
The bad student?
So you two are dating now?
Think I'm crazy to
date a high school...
It looks fishy to me.
This doesn't seem like
a place to study.
It's our farewell party.
Wanna join us?
No way.
We're getting very intimate.
Have fun with your teacher.
I'll call you later.
Why? Envious?
Of course. He's handsome,
and has a good major.
Snobs. And being rich
would also be nice, Right?
All you care about is status.
That was mean.
Is that your standard
for guys, too?
Guys like that wouldn't be bad.
But it's crazy to date
someone in high school?
That's now what I meant.
I thought you were different.
But you're all the same.
You all think superficially.
What makes you so different from
Ho-gyung who's materialistic?
What is it?
This is yours.
Why should I accept this?
Then don't. I bought it for you,
so it's not even mine.
What is it?
Does Kim Ji-hoon's tutor
live here by any chance?
Su-wan? She went on a delivery.
Stop! Wait!
What do you want?
Are you Kim Ji-hoon's tutor
by any chance?
Not anymore.
Grab her!
Come with us for a moment.
What are you doing?
Hello?
Say something! Speak!
It hung up.
Damn it!
What bastard is prank calling?
Hold on for a sec, idiot!
What?
Choi Su-wan?
I have to make a delivery,
so stop this.
Hello? Hello?
Who? Lee Jong-soo? Hey!
My ear's gonna fall off,
you bastard!
Of course you have to come.
Here?
Catch her, you bastards!
Hello?
You're with Jong-soo, huh?
Where are you?
Damn it,
I'm running right now!
So you ordered the chicken?
I doubted it at first.
But I'd never think he'd like
a Country Chick like you.
Your job was to tutor him,
not seduce him.
Here's the chicken,
so pay me 216,000 won.
I wanna throw you like
that chicken and crush you.
Why'd you throw it?
Who are you to do that?
My dad raised them himself,
and my mom cooked it.
And you throw it away?
Stop it! Stop it!
I said stop it!
What do you want?
She's mine,
so you stay out of it!
No she's not, she's mine.
You bastards.
It's not your day to tutor,
so be quiet.
You're a hostage today.
Ji-hoon's bait.
Pay for the chicken.
Pay for the chicken!
Hello?
We're waiting too long
because of you, asshole.
Are you testing my patience?
- Shut up your mouth!
- Let me go, you bastard!
Are you okay?
Do I look okay to you?
Let's go.
Ji-hoon!
He's here. I said he's right here.
You can't leave now.
Jong-soo, you've gone insane.
Ji-hoon, I can't
take it anymore.
I wanna make sure today.
Is it that bitch or me?
Move, bitch.
If you listen to me,
I'll let her go, but if not...
No, you move!
Ji-hoon!
That's the bastard!
Who the hell are you?
They're the bosses
of the Makjubshi Gang.
This is fucking humiliating,
but I had to call them
because of you, asshole.
Damn it, who the hell
are you guys?
What do you want?
With that Country Chick,
no, with Ji-hoon...
No, I came to talk
to both of them.
Hey, what I want is that...
It's my turn. I brought her here,
so butt out.
Damn it, I'm the one
who went to the store.
You idiot, all you had to do
was have her deliver to you.
Stupid idiots.
Hey! Hey!
Are you okay?
What if I'm not?
I see you're still feisty.
Hey, I told you to stop smoking.
Out of breath already?
Very nice. Who gave it to you?
Stop it.
I thought you'd call me.
What's wrong with all your friends?
Get some new ones.
I sure do know
how to pick them right.
The necklace.
Looks good on you.
Wait for me!
Wait for me, asshole!
Like I told you before,
what I want is that...
Go home, you bastard.
But I have something to say!
Hurry and tell me who it is.
Is it me or this bitch? This bitch?
Yeah.
But I like you!
She's not the only one
who likes you!
I like you, too!
I can be a better
girlfriend than her!
Hey, stop crying, damn it.
Why do you bother people?
It's my hobby, why?
Go ahead first.
First, we'll take care of them,
then it's our turn.
Do as you like.
Stop crying like a baby.
I heard a lot about you,
so show me what you got.
Shit, I've been showing it,
so where were you? I'm exhausted.
Can I ask you something?
Asking questions
is a good habit.
Is this your skin?
Hey! Move those hands!
Ji-hoon, where are you going?
Please transfer to another school!
Stop staring, damn it.
Screw you.
Do what she says.
Starring
Kwon Sang-woo
as Kim Ji-hoon
Kim Ha-neul
as Choi Su-wan
Executive Producers
Lee Kang-bok & Lee Seo-yull
Produced by
Jang Jung-gwon
Original Story by
Choi Su-wan
Screenplay by
Park Yun-seon
Directed by
Kim Kyung-hyung