You okay?
Isn't it amazing, Nishi?
Gramps, I...
Er, what I said back there was...
I'd become a bad person!
I wanted to boast about my evil ways.
I wanted to be known as a tough, rugged man!
I wanted to walk over everybody.
But I wound up here and...
I struggled!
But I managed to survive!
I can swim again!
Catch things, walk, see.
Isn't that fun?
Seawater's salty! This place stinks!
But it gives me joy!
Would you rather lie around doing nothing?
Or would you rather feel alive?
Which is more fun?
She sure can swim!
She wanted to go to the Olympics
till she was about 15.
Had a coach and all.
Come to think of it,
I remember her winning something!
Bronze at the Kinki Races.
Stopped when her boobs got bigger!
No kidding! Gotta go with the flow, huh?
Yeah, with the flow!
How is it?
Wow! Fantastic!
Right, my turn!
Quality entertainment coming up!
Got one!
Nishi!
Nishi, remember when we found a stray dog?
In kindergarten?
And you said you'd take care of it?
That made me so happy!
Yeah?
I'm gonna take him home with me.
You will? Thank you!
I already have a sea-monkey, so it'll be fine!
Wanna see? C'mon, I'll show ya!
Myon.
So this is the new plot!
In the far, distant future,
where the world is starving from
over-population and environmental destruction,
Earth decides to send
a spaceship in search for food.
But something goes wrong.
They land on a strange planet.
There's water and oxygen,
but nothing edible for humans!
Except for one thing, they soon discover.
A certain creature's poo.
Ooh, gross!
And it's the perfect food for humans.
"It's delicious!"
But the creature's unbelievably bad at hunting
and on the verge of extinction!
There's only one?
Our men help the creature hunt, look after it!
And they live like that for a while
until a new enemy arrives.
Higher species of plants begin to fight
for food, which is also creature chips!
A poo-war, huh?
But what happens then? The crew?
Guess we need to send them home safely, huh?
The planet is ideal in its own way, but...
In fact, the planet's some kind of cell!
Our crew must've ended up there
after being shrunk!
A cell?
Yeah, of a human body.
Whose?
Yours.
Mine?
Let's just say... it was the leader's fault.
His love for his girl,
his determination to find that planet,
his desperation led the ship there.
But one day, they realize
their bodies have grown bigger.
Why?
Wonder why!
And they hear a voice! From inside your tummy
as you're sitting in the toilet.
"Oh my God!
We're growing bigger and bigger!"
Yikes!
But they can communicate that way.
And they realize their inside your stomach.
- Then what?
- They've gotta get out!
- From where?
- At this point, they're moving along the colon!
Not happening!!
But what else can they do?
They keep getting bigger.
Your belly'll explode!
- I said no!
- "We're almost out, don't flush us!"
I AM flushing them!
"We're out! We're out!"
NO!!!
Myon!
Nishi!
Nishi! Myon!!
We're up here!
You guys OK?
A-OK!
I'm relieved! We were worried!
That was a surprise attack! So sudden!
Told ya so! It's wicked, man!
A miracle, I say!
The Other World by Robin Nishi.
The guy's a fucking genius!
Cut class and meet me at the arcade!
The Strawberry Plaza in ten!
Roger that.
This place's so commercial.
Dude, chill...
Isn't that...
Robin Nishi!!!
"R! Nishi Book Signing"
Check out the chicks!
Fuckin' cool!
Excuse me, you're Robin Nishi, right?
Hiroshi, you idiot!!
Fuck yeah!!
Sorry!!
We're huge fans!
The Other World rocks!!
Wanna grab a bite?
Follow me!!
Seriously?!
Eat!
Yes!!
- This is like, your average day??
- Yeah!
- Awesome!
- I feel so alive!
Robin, I'll pick up the tab!
What're you talking about?
Hiroshi, you idiot!!
Hiroshi, kids shouldn't worry
about things like that.
Have fun and become a man!
Not a clone, but someone who transcends!!
First contact with aliens!
And directing this epic moment
is the artist who made it all possible...
Salvatore Antonio Yang Gogh!!
"HELLO"
The crowd's cheers've gone up a notch here
at the 1st Cosmic Swimming Contest.
Representing Earth!
Matt Beyond Thorpe Myon!!!
And so the race begins
as we witness history in the making!
First corner and into the gate!
Cameras are not allowed inside!
And they're coming out! 4 in the first group!
And she's there!
Matt Beyond Thorpe Myon,
representing Earth!!!
Isn't this supposed to be extinct?
This one too!
"To Yang and Myon"
Think we can get out of here?
Want to?
We might be happier here.
Jump!
That's odd and it wasn't even time yet.
Good God! I was about to go fetch you!
Gramps.
What's going on?
The water level's increasing.
And he's eating less.
Meaning?
Can't say for sure, but he could be dying.
Dying? But what happens to us then?
Eventually, this place'll sink.
We've gotta leave. It's that or drown.
But how?
The boat, of course!
- The cops'll be looking for us.
- So?
The Yakuzas'll come after us!
So what! I wanna get out!
'Cos there's so much out there!
So many different people,
living different lives!
Incredibly good guys, bad guys...
Folks completely different from us!
It's one huge melting pot!
See, it's not about success,
dying in the streets, who's better, who's not!
I just want to be a part of it!
I realized that even if I've no connections,
no talent,
even if I'm one big loser,
I want to use my hands and feet to think
and move, to shape my own life!
We can just die here or we can try!
See what we've got!
It's impossible.
Motivation's not gonna get us over that wave.
We need a motor boat!
We've got a motor!
Right here!
But there's no fuel...
Sure there is!
We came here by car, remember?
Yes!
It could work!
It will work!!
We're going to make it!
We're so gonna make it!
Get up there!
The World Cup ends tomorrow
with its final match...
As the world awaits to find out
who'll be the winner...
We're near Osaka again!
Oh, yeah!
I think this is our only chance!
Maybe the whale's come here for us!
And we're going for it!
You're older. Lend it to her!
I don't want to!
Yang.
Don't run like that, Myon'll follow you.
Sorry, Myon...
I don't like that uniform!
- I'll work!
- Sorry Yang!
Wanna try?
Myon.
Yang!
Thanks!
I'm not gonna let you carry
all the load anymore!
I'll grow up.
I'm sorry.
I always knew you were the one
that needed support.
It's your turn, now!
Go ahead!
Here we go kids!
Yes sir!
Run!!
Water striders float...
...using surface tension
from the hairs on their legs.
I'm sorry.
Your bones won't get strong
if you don't drink milk.
Yes, mom!
Ah, not again!
I'll put it in your food then!
This'll be perfect.
- Hey, wrong nail!
- The baby!
- You OK?
- It's heavy!
There!
Mmm, too much space for a little kid!
Ah, he'll be big in no time!
Wonder what he'll be like.
Be right there, sweetie!
Your fever's just gone down you know.
I'm fine.
See you later!
See you at 10!
Keiko? It's me!
Myon? I've got an art show.
That's great!
And she's going for the rope!
"A Lonely Death"
We've got no money either!
Worn by...
There, found it!
Jun!
Hi!
That's insane! They're Yakuzas!!
I told you to wait till tomorrow,
so shut up and wait, you punk!!
Sorry about that! Now back to your interview...
That's her!
Myon!