What do we say now?
Anything
Anything you want
How many kids do you have?
Nothing like that
Was I any good?
You don't know how seductive
you really are
So you looks so normal
You're really fantastic
I thought my whole body
would be sucked into you
Does your wife know
about your lifestyle?
As long as she doesn't
see it, she's okay with it
She knew about this
before we married
I've always been like this
Even before I ran away
from Seoul
Why did you leave Seoul?
Why'd you spend 2 weeks
in the hospital for a head wound?
That's not fair
One advantage of
living up the hill
- Tricky, aren't I?
- As much as me?
You got me there
Su-jin
this is an internet joke, what's
soccer players' favorite drink?
Penal-tea!
What happened to my hair?
No, it's pretty
I'll brush it when we get home.
Don't worry
it looks good
- Hey, Doctor Choi
- Oh, hello
- We should go fishing sometime, huh?
- Yes, I'll look at my schedule
Bye
Hello?
- Who was that?
- No one, maybe they'll call again
It's nice out,
wanna go for a hike?
Why don't you go with Su-jin?
I don't like hiking
I wanted to go as a family
We've never gone out
since moving
It's too late to hike
It'll be lunchtime soon
How about hot springs, then?
I'm a bit stiff these days
We can have sushi on the way back.
How about it?
Mommy, hurry up
Daddy!
- The hot spa was good, huh?
- Yeah
- Do you have some lotion on you?
- You didn't put any on?
I didn't like the one they had
Did you put some on Su-jin?
By the way
- Hon?
- Hmm?
You know Prof Hwang?
He asked me to try
writing again
He thinks I have a lot of time
in a place like this
I guess everyone's out
on Sunday
Stop by the store,
let's get some drinks
Honk! Honk! Big car coming.
Move away, please
Mommy, let's get some ice cream
- Do you want something?
- Anything's fine
I'll wait here
Is something wrong?
Do you know how I got out?
Over the window!
Look at my feet!
Is someone here?
I don't like such dangerous acts
- I couldn't keep our appointment
- That's no problem
You came to say that,
this late?
The light was on
I'm leaving
No one saw me
Mi-heun, wait
Our promises are
like sea buoys
They don't really mark anything
Stop there or just float past them
It doesn't make a difference
Mi-heun
Hey, Mi-heun
Where'd you go?
I was worried about you
I went for a walk
At this hour? In your pajamas?
Who cares?
No one's around to see me
But when did you leave?
When you went to the bathroom
Are you crazy?
Weren't you scared?
No I went to the lake
What's wrong with you?
You make me crazy
Can we do it?
Mi-heun?
It's okay, isn't it?
Here they go again
What?
The wife! She does this
every year
She invites some outsiders
has an outdoor party
and keeps the village up
all night
They say she runs a restaurant
in the city
Probably just a pub
Is there anyplace cool around?
It's so boring here
- Shall we go to the beach?
- The beach?
- Is it nearby?
- Of course, it's not far
Wow, you came pretty far
I love you
Does this mean I lost?
- The game's over?
- You mean it?
Can't I?
No. It's not that you can't
I just said it
for practice
to remind myself of the rule
lf you only knew
You don't know how hard
I'm trying not to lose this game
Oh, it feels so good
Darling?
Wait, wait
In-kyu
Darling?
They're looking for you
In-kyu! In-kyu!
Want to put in a pond
and raise goldfish?
Su-jin will like it
There's a place by my shop
They'll give us a good deal
Let's do it later
No, it's best to do it now
I've one more thing to say
I want to write a novel again
Hello?
Yes, yes okay
- Who was it?
- Wait
What? Where are you going?
Um Mi-sook's mom is sick
- Who?
- You know, at the rest stop
So why do you have to go?
I'm the only one she knows
- But this late at night?
- I'll call when I get there, okay?
I parked at the post office
Is something up?
Not that I know of
It's just, different
Isn't it fun and thrilling?
What'd you say to him?
Why?
Relax
On my way home,
I realized I really needed you
I didn't come to joke
You've got to relax
and take us less seriously
Come here
Where were you this
afternoon?
This place was closed early
I just went for a long drive
Honking loudly and
speeding, I bet
I'm going to my mom's
next week
Can I try it?
Want to meet me there?
Can you meet me if I go?
It's my sister's memorial day
Let's meet at night
The garlic is great there
I don't make it often
Take some home for your family
Why didn't you bring Su-jin?
I'm only here for the day
Besides, she's busy these days
playing with friends
Where's the brother in law?
He has a new wife,
don't bother
Hae-jin should get
close to her, too
She's never seen your sister
Shouldn't we go to the temple?
The monks will pray for her
And don't bother coming
next year
We've left this to the monks.
No need for us to fuss anymore
You want to go for a walk?
Do we have to?
It's like downtown Seoul here
Look, just go back
Why'd you come?
If you hadn't,
I wouldn't have waited
Don't get angry
Look at me
I hate the way I am
This is just crazy
No need to drag this on.
Let's end it
I'm not angry with you.
Stop it
lf you're tired of us,
just say it
There isn't any commitment here
It's not that I don't want it.
It's the complete opposite
You don't really understand me
We came way too far
While coming here,
you know what I realized?
What's that?
I'm disgusted with how I am
how I live, how others live
I even thought of going back
But after 4 hours
I couldn't
It'd be crazy for me to go back,
and there's nowhere I want to be
It's the story of my life
I'm not angry with you
I know I'm bad
I've never kept a promise
in my life
When I get older,
I'll be just like my dad
I ran away from the one I
confessed love to go,
just like him
I cut my hand so
I'd remember not to love again
But here you are
My nurse said rumors about
us are all over the village
Someone in the next town
even asked
how the doc and his lover
were doing
Let's spend the night
together anyway
It'll be our first
full night together
You could call it
our first night
You men like first too much
What if today wasn't the first
but the last,
how would you spend it?
Do the laundry
Clean the fridge
Go to the hairdresser's and say
"Do whatever you want with it"
for the first time,
put Su-jin's things in a box
and write 2014,
so she can find it as an adult
Go to Jinju to eat pizza.
Write a letter to a friend
Look at all my old report
cards and pictures
Oh, and change my underwear
And me?
When will you meet me
on the last day?
on that day?
From morning till night, all day
All day Beginning to end
I wouldn't let you go
for a moment
Let's go
You're right.
We came much too far
The game's over
Let's not meet any more
Say that you love me
I don't want to
play games anymore
- Mommy
- Huh?
I'm hot. Can I get out?
What's all this?
I put the store up for sale
I'm running off to hide again
So he can't find me
Is something wrong?
Why?
You seem different
Huh?
I've heard about it
They all know except
my husband
When are you leaving?
The next owner will be here
soon
Keep in touch. I'll write
My name's Eun-Yeon
Na Eun-Yeon
Don't say it
No one's called me that
since I left home at 15
I just wanted you to know
my name
Hello?
It's me. Where are the stop smoking
tapes that were in the car?
I threw them out
But they weren't yours!
You knew I was trying to
quit smoking!
You should've at least asked!
- Wait! Someone's at the door
- Shit!
- I'll call you back
- Hey! Mi-heun!
- Who is it?
- Here to construct the pond
- Pardon?
- Pond construction, ma'am
Hey, mister! Sir?
Hey, stop for a sec
I'll take the kid out
for a while
- Okay, but be back before lunch
- I will. Thank you
No problem! Go on
Bye, sweetie
You bastard!
Get on
People are looking.
Get in now
I have to go pick up Su-jin
You go first and wait for me
One big change in life is
more than enough for me
If you and
I live together
we'll just end up repeating
the same mistakes
Just like with your husband
you'll end up lying to me
And I'll meet another woman
and be forced to lie to you
That's absurd
What do you know
about me and my husband?
What's the big change?
I can just eat you up
right now
Like a man-eater
I need you
Don't go seeing anyone else yet
A woman who makes me
warm soup every morning
And has my baby through her body
Coming home at night
and falling asleep in her arms
It's no longer possible
We both tried it before
We both failed at
that sort of life
What were you doing there?
I'm talking to you!
I went to the spa
When did you arrive?
An hour ago
I was here for three hours!
I went home early
but no one was home!
The workers were mad
about missing lunch!
I looked for you
and Su-jin everywhere!
I found your car here,
so I waited
I asked if anyone saw you
or Su-jin inside the spa
They said no!!
I waited since then.
It's six now!
Where's Su-jin?
You know there's nothing
but a motel through there!
Where is she?
Playing at a friend's house
Explain yourself
Is it true what everyone says?
Let go
Get off, now!
Get out!
Now, explain! I'm listening!
You think I'm sacrificing my life
to live in this hell-hole
so that you can fuck some doctor?
I have nothing to say
- Let's end it
- What?
I want a divorce
You think I'm crazy enough to
give you what you want?
God forbid!
I'm gonna make sure you
pay for this!
- When did it start?
- As soon as we moved here
Where do you think you're going?
Stop right there!
You can't go! Fuck!
Hey, miss, is something wrong?
Are you okay?
Are you sure?
How'd this happen?
You're unreal
A jerk who seduces crazy women
in the country with bad games
Let's go to the hospital
I can't go into town
Let's just stay here, together
People believe that only the good
can fall in love forever
But the people who love
intensely are the bad ones
Immoral, weak,
selfish people
the poor, dark souls
I don't have a picture
No picture of Su-jin!
What am I going to do?
It's at the house
What if I forget her face?
What am I going to do?
What are we going to do?
I love you
What shitty luck
Let it go
Right, it's nothing
Where are we going?
I'm scared of your driving
You and I have no place to go
and no place to stay
Let's just go anywhere
But you know, we won't work
Are you okay?
Here
Yes, I'm fine
Deserted by family and friends,
I walked out of the hospital alone
And someone was kind enough
to tell me of his death
I left home
And a year has gone by
When the sun rose,
I got up to work on a day to day job
When I got hungry,
I filled up on cheap food
At night I returned to my one room
home and fell asleep, alone
Sometimes, memories would
crowd in and stab my heart
Often times I'd wake up at
night and cry like a mad woman
But I believe
I'm more alive now
than I ever was in the past
It's like I'm walking toward
a world tossed by wind
Vitality starts with misery
My sadness reminds
me that I'm alive
That one dazzling moment
in my life
The all too short summer,
that year
I didn't have the chance
to say I loved him
Even now, I remember
I can hear his final laugh
Are you ready?
Ah yes
Okay, let's take your picture now
Tilt your head a little
to the right, and turn
That's great
Can you put the bag
down from the chair?
Great
Is today a special occasion?
Taking a photo by yourself
No, I just have no picture
Director BYUN Young-joo