Understand?!
What are you doing?
Don't know.
Don't know? I've made it clear.
Scatter, scatter.
Help, help.
You're smart, why are you so smart?
Don't go too close.
Hey.
Dead?
Yes, dead already.
Sir.
The Mission has been completed smoothly.
Star Chow, where're your men?
All dead!?
We want a supervisor, we want team work.
Not going alone like Rambo.
The hostages have been rescued.
Rescuing is just an item in this exam.
What matters most is the safety of your juniors
and your leadership but I can't see anything!
Sir, give me a chance.
What are you doing?
Don't!
Sir, could you please reconsider?
Who is it?
Yes.
Yes, Sir. The boss wants to see you.
Yes, Sir.
Good morning, Sir, I'm Star Chow.
Damn it, that adorable!
Turn a round for me,
don't be shy, come on!
Irresistible, I'm sorry.
Wanna get a promotion?
I don't want to be a gigolo, Sir.
I asked if you want a promotion.
I won't be gigolo, Sir.
That's nonsense!
I asked if you want a promotion.
Yes, but not at the cost of my chastity.
Who wants your chastity?
I want your youth.
Youth and chastity are equally important
to me.
Fine, fine, I see. Let me finish my words.
This matter is such,
one day, some students visited
our police station.
A pistol was lost afterwards.
Sir, we lose pistols very often.
But that pistol is mine!
I can share your heartbreaking feeling.
Yes, that pistol has followed me
for 30 years.
I've never shot it. It's for scratching itches.
Speaking of the itch and here comes.
Scratch me.
- The back?
- Yes.
It's a kind pistol.
Can pistol be kind?
It's got a kind nature.
If it falls in the hands of bad students,
tragedies will follow.
Don't worry, Sir.
I'll search the whole school
for your pistol.
If I can manage, I don't have to ask you.
I'm retiring, but I've lost my pistol.
I'll lose my face if others know.
So I want you to enter that school as a spy.
I'm not sure if I can teach.
Who ask you to teach? To be a student!
Student?
I joined the police force
because I hated studying.
I can't be a student. Sir, if you do so...
you're bringing me to a volcano
with lots of wild animals
and paying no attention to my wailing.
And are just kicking me cruelly...
into the exploding volcano.
How can you be so cruel?
You can live and die excitingly then.
Stop, no way escaping.
Here's a pager watch, put it on.
666 means I call you.
Say to me, "Good morning, sir".
Good... morning... sir.
Very good.
Don't let others know
or both you and I'll be in trouble.
I'll see if you guys will be late again.
What are you staring at?
School Discipline
You'll learn it by heart later.
That's the fresh boy.
Big stupid guy, from which class?
Could it be ours?
I don't think so.
Star Chow, I'm the Head of Discipline
of this school. My name is Lam.
A mosquito.
You transferred from England College?
Students from that school are rubbish.
I don't care what's between your family
and the school committee.
Edinburgh College is a prestigious school
and teach the best students.
I can't stand a single bad element
or I'll kick you out of here,
clear?
Yes, Sir!
You think that's interesting?
Bring him to the classroom.
Come with me to the classroom.
Around 1987,
an observation from the sky
above the South Pole...
revealed that there's hole
at the ozonosphere up above there.
Strong ultraviolet ray is harmful
to living organisms.
A less serious situation will affect the genes.
The worst case will kill the cells.
Plants will die as a result.
Ultraviolet ray can penetrate into the sea.
I lose freedom,
my heart's breaking my tears' flowing.
I've lost my way and gone astray.
My heart is breaking.
Who's attacking the police?
Attacking what?
You! Take the duster out.
I don't care you're new in here.
What are you dreaming? What?
Miss has got her pride.
The lesson restarts!
Let's start with the atmosphere layer.
The atmosphere is made up of several layers.
Calm down, everything will go very smoothly.
Step aside, everything can be as boundless as
the sea and sky
The layer nearest to the earth is called
the troposphere.
It's 15,000 to 50,000 feet above the earth.
It contains cloud and weather systems.
Ming Dynasty - Punishment
The Ming Dynasty particularly
stressed on punishment.
Disrespect Party politics and espionage
were subjects to punishment.
Turtle Wong.
Mr. Cheng what does it mean by espionage?
It's the current practice of spying.
The people involved are called spies.
These people are punished by castration.
Castration!?
Chopping sex organ, kid.
Chopped by how many inches?
That depends on how many inches you've got.
The wrong book again, absent-minded!
Really absent-minded!
What's that noise?
Thank you for your help.
Come... Quicker...
Serve him right.
You're laughing so happily you come out too.
Come...
What's your name?
Star Chow.
And you?
Turtle Wong.
What's your name?
Star Chow.
What's yours?
Turtle Wong.
What's your name?
Star Chow.
Let's begin, Star Chow.
This experiment is quite complicated.
We must remember each step.
Forgetting one single step
will be very dangerous.
Sorry...
the most important thing of this experiment is...
Memory.
If not, it'll...
will be very dangerous.
Stop!
Hey... get back down here
Hey, you, go away
Please, could you get down here first?
What are you doing? Who are you?
What's this to do with you?
Excuse me and you get down.
Why pulling me down here?
You're standing on my belly.
Don't go away, we're on the same boat,
we share the same code.
Code!?
Chicken, turtle, bone, boil, spoon.
What's the code?
- What's this?
- The code!
God! Everybody's abnormal here,
excuse me.
You can't climb out from here.
You can't walk out from here.
OK, I'll use the front door.
Not even with the front door.
What's it?
Nothing, this boy's gone mad suddenly.
Yes, I've gone mad. I want home.
What is it?
Sorry, Sir.
Don't block my way, please.
Excuse me, please.
Excuse me, I want to go.
Are you alright?
I'm sick, I want to go home.
Please let me go! Thank you.
You're not feeling well.
Yes.
Come with me.
Let's see if you've got a fever.
No.
Yes.
No, look at it yourself.
It's me who's got the fever, not the thermometer.
I'm feeling so bad.
Let me see your eyes.
Look down.
Look up.
Look at the left.
Hey, your eyeballs can't move?
It can't move since I've got a fever.
Are you pretending?
I'm Miss Ho, I'm not teaching your class,
but I'm the counselor of your class.
You go back to classroom first.
Come to me anytime if you've got problem. Be good.
Are you mad just because I've dropped
your pencil-case unintentionally?
No, I ain't, ain't.
I'm so frightened.
So, how much do you want?
That depends...
Only $300.
I'm not frightened now.
If I know you still got money with you,
I'll not throw your pencil case away,
but you!
I understood.
Good, the savior comes.
Don't get it mistakenly,
I'm not helping you guys,
and I'm not your savior.
You can! You look so cheeky.
They'll only bully you, not me.
Thank you very much!
Sir, I remember the code.
It's Dong Tong, Tong Dong Dong, right?
- It's you?
- Yes.
You should have said earlier.
I forgot the code earlier.
Sir,
I'm CID5798,
I'm sent here to cooperate with you.
Go home and have your hands stopped trembling.
My hands are not trembling.
It's Parkinson.
I'm only pretending.
That saves me from doing a lot of work.
The boss has asked you to stay at my home.
What kind of stick are you chewing?
To give up smoking.
Hey... Miss Ho? Forget about her!
Her boyfriend is the head of Anti-triad Unit.
What are you saying?
What?
I'm keeping an eye on that kid who's smoking.
You mean Johnny?
What is he?
The head of the 4 Tigers of Beacon Hill.
His big brother, Teddy Big,
is really somebody.
He's the most suspicious in the case
which our boss lost his pistol.
Keep an eye on him.
Go!
Big brother.
You asshole, what a lousy idea.
Now somebody's after us for money.
It's fine to traffic drugs,
why trafficking arms?
You said, arms-trafficking is profiteering
during the Gulf War.
You should've persuaded me.
What are we going to do with these AK47s?
If we got pistols, we can rob.
Johnny is here.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
He's cheeky.
Even you can be cheeky if you've got money.
You're here, come in.
They're for Feng-shui.
Keep your hands off.
I'm sorry.
How are you getting on?
You're cheeky now.
Don't worry, my dad has gone traveling.
He won't have come back
even our cars reach Shenzhen.
Let's see
and do pay us the money for the 2 cars
of my brother back.
I can only pay you when my clients pay me.
You're not that in need of money, right?
I need money badly.
The money I collected in the school...
can't even afford 2 nights in the Karaoke.
I've got a great thing, wanna see?
It's great.
We stole from the police academy.
Cop's pistol?
3 for each. Don't fight for it.
In memory of your fathers?
Do I still need to work
if I've got so many fathers?
They're all my ex-partners.
Good, noodles...
Cook some for yourself.
Come on, no...
Yes.
Cook oneself is illegal?
How many partners you've got?
But there're 10 here.
I have to prepare one to two more...
One to two more...
and see who's coming to me.
Maybe he needs it. Just keep as stock.
Would you mind?
What are you saying?
You don't understand?
It's better if you don't understand.
Die at an early age.
Eat your noodles,
I'll have supper outside.
Remember to do your homework,
you've to go to school on tomorrow.
- Damn you.
- No damning.
Nothing. Keep talking.
You're always so dirty.
I get used to it.
I worked as a servant in a school,
it was fine at first.
But I have to work under Sir Chow.
Really trouble!
What an ass.
What are you doing?
I'm less fortunate than you.
I'm following the case of Teddy Big.
Arms?
What a coincidence!
We are also after Teddy Big.
But for the pistol.
- Cop's pistol?
- Yes.
Really?
They're in the machine gun business.
Machine guns in HK?
Yes, goods have arrived.
Wow...
Why don't you arrest them?
The buyers are terrorists,
Boss wants to arrest all at one go.
That's tough!
It's life and death if something goes wrong.
We can't afford to alarm them.
Well, keep an eye for the pistol for me as well.
- Sure!
- Sure?
You have my word.
Among the gang of underground informers,
all are dead except you and me.
Of course, I'll keep an eye for you.
Everyone can die, except this.
Lousy.
Brother Teddy, stay calm.
We'll settle if there's any problem.
Remember Chicken Brand
whom you arrested 10 years ago.
He wants to say hello to you Inspector Wong.
Policeman.
Understand?
Yes, good.
Damn you.
No homework
I'm deserved to be punished.
No homework again
Look around at the class
Stare nothing at the class
It's all my fault.
Stand on one foot.
A show over there.
Watch only...
What?
I said watch only, don't laugh.
Ha...
Are you alright?
Does it hurt?
You just didn't take my words to the heart.
Star of the week
This student is brainless, he's hopeless.
Yes... always absent-minded, hopeless.
He's a jerk already looks as...
if he's sick.
Never seen a "star" like him.
You two should be looking for the pistol
not looking up the dictionary.
Boss,
he couldn't hand in his homework today
and was punished by not allowing to go back
the classroom.
You can look into the case
even if you're outside the classroom!
If I fail to hand in homework again,
I'm out of the school.
Then I can't look into anything.
Can you solve this calculation?
Let's see.
I know nothing about trigonometry.
When you first asked me to handle this case,
your attitude was different.
No, he's always like this.
I'm always like this.
My soft words are for cheating you
to get involved.
What about asking some other policemen
to come here...
and solve the Math.
You're an idiot!
That means disclosing the case to everybody?
Let me tell you finish this case quickly,
or I'll kick your brains out
with my Scissors Legs.
What?
I'll fly over and kick you with legs
like scissors and kick your brain out.
Scissors Legs, scared?
Very...
Scissors Legs, what a joke.
He was really powerful.
He was!
He was able to deal with 20 guys alone.
Or only be able to shoot 20 planes!?
Dad, are you alright? Dad.
Dad, go to hell, Dad.
How can you say that!
Damn it! I'm late.
It's only 6 o'clock.
I'm influenced by his hard-work,
I've to do a little revision too.
Yam...
I'm not called Yam.
But you really look like.
Have you finished your Biology?
Let me copy.
I won't even if I have. Are you nuts?
I'll give you $50 in return.
I do...
You want money before finishing the homework?
Stay away, one by one.
As many as you want.
Any compositions? Compositions.
Keung, yours is torn, go away.
- He's quite popular.
- Yes.
Copy this so late?
You're ruining your future. Hopeless.
Look, I've finished.
You think you are smart?
Of course.
I'm not mocking you.
I just want to say, from now on.
I won't let anyone throwing dusters at me.
I won't be punished by standing
onto the corridor
or standing on the playground,
or holding a damn cardboard publicly,
like a monkey. No!
Just keep copying...
Sudden test, those who fail will be standing
on the playground for a week.
Chinese History Test
- Mobile phone?
- Cool, isn't it?
What?
What? Chinese history test?
You two can handle it.
What? Boss, my Chinese History won't do.
Hold on! Mandy,
ask all seniors to come up here.
Ask them who was the one
who suppressed the "An-Shi Rebellion"?
A: Kwok Chi-Yee,
B for boy, is that clear?
Li Kwang-Bud, C: Li Hark-Yong...
It's Li Hark-Yong, not Lee Hack-Ken.
A is Kwok Chi-Yee,
B is Lee Kwang-Bud.
Which two of them are the heroes?
Kwok Chi-Yee and Chu Wen.
It seems to be Lee Kwang-Bud and Chu Wen.
So who's the hero? Answer me!
Kwok Chi-Yee or Chu Wen?
What? You look up the book?
No, I can manage... few more seconds.
Son, it's Chu Wen. Who's Chu Wen?
The answer is B.
Banana? B for banana.
Ask them.
What's the "Ox-Li Party Conflict"?
Search book again?
You even don't know this!
What have you studied? Shit!
Which big case are you in?
No idea.
A for apple, that's it.
Next question, listen carefully...
The answer is D, D for dog.
D for, D for dog.
B.
Uncle Tat, what are you doing here?
Well... collecting rubbish.
The female toilet is blocked,
can you do with that?
Come with me.
What, the test is over.
Sir, which case?
Three wolfs.
Dead already?
Reverse a previous judgment?!
Stupid me, I should have guessed that.
No.
No again.
You two are riding?
Falling instead.
So you two are cheating.
No, only me who's cheating.
Arrest me.
Come out with me.
A moment please.
He cheated in the Chinese history test by using
the Chinese literature book.
You are dumb.
That's not exactly cheating.
He was guilty.
I only want to let him have
the proper punishment.
What do you say?
Deduct 3 marks from his conduct as usual.
Stop it.
Please don't. A deduction of 12 marks
will let him out of this school.
Miss Leung, what about you?
Kill him.
What did you say?
That isn't what you want? Just cheating.
It's one of our experience of growing up.
Who hasn't cheated before?
But you even didn't use your brains to cheat.
Stand properly. Don't move!
You don't use your brains, you deserve it.
I suggest arranging for another test.
If he still doesn't learn from it,
test him again and again.
Until he passes.
That's punishing me, I can't afford the time.
- Save your time from going to The race-course.
- Yes...
I agree.
You can talk to his parents
and try to understand his family background.
Fine, I've decided.
He's punished by staying after school for a week
and cleaning the playground for 2 weeks.
Deduct 5 marks from his conduct,
re-test on next week.
Also, I want to meet your parents.
Parents? I don't have any.
I've got no relatives, no friends.
Who's your guardian?
I'm my own guardian.
If there's anybody you want to see, it's me.
His file.
Who's his guardian?
Uncle Tat?
Uncle Tat!
Stop it, God... big news.
Uncle Tat, is Star Chow really your son?
You're a senior to me, you say.
Star Chow, say!
Don't laugh, say!
Yes.
Yes... I'm sorry...
I bet, they look exactly the same.
What? The same?
His dad? Nonsense.
Hey, no... here...
Your surname's Tso, his is Chow, why?
How do I know? Why?
This is an order.
When he was born, I named him, Star Tso.
But then he named himself, Star Chow.
I don't know why.
Is this correct?
It's right.
Sir, excuse us.
Hold on, Uncle Tat,
we want you to come up here to tell
your son cheated in a test.
Cheated? That's disgraceful, no good...
You can't cheat, Sir, cheating...
Excuse us.
Hey, don't you see,
parents and teachers should cooperate
to teach him.
Right?
How long can we teach him?
Your son's been here for only 3 days
and he cheated.
- Give me one or two slaps and then go.
- No...
You should teach him effectively.
Don't be too serious.
Of course, not to be too serious.
Alright, I know what to do.
You cheated?
I'll beat the hell out of you.
Don't be too agitated...
I'll beat you...
- Dead already?
- Dead already.
- You're lying.
- No.
One more hit.
You son-of...
Sir Chow, please.
I have to use all my strength
to beat a strong man like you.
Well...
I'm old and lacking of strength.
After I beat you, my bones crack.
- Really?
- Yes.
I'm sorry.
Never mind, I'm in this business.
Go and see the doctor, I'll pay for it.
Thank you, thank you.
Uncle Tat!
Miss Ho.
Don't be so angry.
Star Chow, do you know how great your father is?
Don't mention it, all parents are great.
He can't go on like this,
let me be his tutor.
I've got no money to pay you.
We can't owe you this favor, Miss.
- Uncle Tat!
- Dad.
I won't take any money.
No...
I'll lead him onto the right track.
No... not good.
So, let's start from tomorrow.
Don't worry.
Thank you, thank you.
Thanks a lot.
Save it, it's a golden opportunity for you.
You said no to her, how dare you!
Be smart, don't reveal your identity.
Hey.
Somebody's looking for you.
Who?
Go up and you'll know.
OK. Coming.
I must show him how smart I'm.
He's coming.
Who helps him just stand on his side.
You want protection fee, I pay it for him.
You, Turtle, must have no idea of death!
Let me take your mouth as an ashtray.
Take him here.
Anything else?
Nothing.
So, don't call me up here unless necessary.
OK!
Hopeless!
Star, you're powerful than Bruce Lee.
Star, do you want to have your shoes cleaned?
Smart Star, have you got enough money?
I can give you.
What's more, if you're not neat and tidy,
I must beat you.
Your hand. Show me your hand.
I'm too old to be hit on the palm.
Show me.
Don't, no need, Miss.
That one.
I'll show you somewhere else to beat.
If you are cruel enough,
just use all your strength to beat me.
Like a garbage can.
It's shameful if Miss Ho sees this.
Hey, what's this? A toaster?
Throw the bread away.
The blue magazines in your room you have to...
Tidy up your room, stop eating.
- What?
- Let's play something.
OK, tidy this place.
Pretend to have Parkinson!
Is Parkinson your dad?
Always, so fond of this.
I don't care how old you're, I tell you.
The son shouldn't have a larger room
than his dad.
Miss, I'm not sure about this.
About what?