Abre los ojos.
'Open your eyes.
'Open your... '
Everything
In its right place
Yesterday I woke up sucking a lemon
Yesterday I woke up...
'Open your eyes.
'David, open your... '
'I suppose the empty
street meant loneliness. '
'You're a shrink. You've
got to do better than that. '
'I'm a doctor. Let's not
stereotype each other.
'Not all rich kids are soulless,
'and not all psychologists
care about dreams.
'The question is how you got here
and why you've been charged. '
'What do you want to know?
I was about to turn 33.
'I ran three magazines in a
worldwide publishing house.
'Most days I fooled myself into
believing it would last forever.
'Lsn't that what being young is about? '
'Believing secretly that you would be
the one person in the history of man
'who would live forever? '
Where are you going so early?
Don't record any more
messages on my alarm clock.
Why not?
I'll start to think we're
married or something.
Don't ever say that word.
I'll never bring you chicken soup
and fuck your brains out again.
- How's your cold?
- Still there. How about yours?
- You definitely took my mind off it.
- Really?
Yes!
Juliana here.
Hi, Rayna. I missed my
audition, I lost my head!
Listen, I have to go.
I'm with David.
Help yourself to whatever you want.
Set the alarm before you go. And...
You are the greatest.
- Bye, honey!
- Bye, honey. I'll call you later.
When?
- When?
- Soon!
I know you say
Maybe some day
I need never be alone
I know I say
It's the right way
But you'll never be the one...
Did you reserve the court?
Easy. I can't handle heavy
conversation at this ungodly hour.
Sorry to do this early.
I've got to be done by 10:00.
'You're not going to
make the 8:45, are you?
How did you find me?
'You have to check the
colours for the new issue. '
- What are the colours?
- 'Yellow and red, or the traditional white. '
- Got to think about it.
- 'David, please. '
'Don't be late for the 10
o' clock with the board. '
Don't tell anybody where I am. I
don't care if God calls. I'm very busy.
- Can't you get rid of that board?
- The Seven Dwarfs?
They drive you nuts.
That was the desire of
my father who hired them.
You fucked Julie Gianni
again, didn't you?
I know someone was there when
I called. You had that tone.
"Oh, no, man. I've got a
cold. I'm hanging in today. "
I had a cold.
- I was alone.
- Fine.
You can do what you want with your life,
but one day you'll
know what love truly is.
It's the sour and the sweet.
I know sour, which allows
me to appreciate the sweet.
Julie Gianni is a friend.
Sometimes we sleep together.
What? What?
My dream girl, Julie Gianni,
is your fuck buddy!
- What do you want to listen to?
- Slow down.
What have we got here? Barcelona...
Radiohead?
Look out!
Fuck!
We almost died.
I know. My own death was
right there in front of me.
You know what happened? Your
life flashed before my eyes.
- How was it?
- Almost worth dying for.
We're at the front door.
We're coming up now.
- Morning, sir. Sleep well?
- Yes, I did.
- Eaten anything yet?
- No.
David, you were playing racquetball.
I've been covering you for an hour
and you're playing racquetball.
We are exiting the elevator.
The board is not happy.
Hello, David.
You're in "The Post". Courtney Love
called to see if you got her e-mail
and Graydon Carter called to see
if you're still on for dinner.
The art department still need the decision
on the colours for the bikini issue.
Did I mention the board
is pissed? You're late.
David, hold up! Choose one!
Wait! This one? David!
They're all waiting for you.
- You changed your hair.
- Yes, and David...
...opinions are expected.
David.
Do you dream about the board,
the Seven Dwarfs as you call them?
Sneezy, Bashful, Sleepy,
Happy, Doc, Dopey
and, of course, Grumpy.
- How was Aspen?
- Good.
Now, I want answers and I want them now.
How's it going?
'They still look at me as
if I was 11 years old. '
He's going to inherit
everything. He gets it all.
- Are you scared of your dreams?
- It's a nightmare either way.
Is that how you explain
what's happened to you?
What happened to your face?
- I'm not talking to you any more.
- You don't want to show me your face?
No!
- Do you know why you're here?
- The conversation, the coffee...
David, the part where we parry and joust
and get to know each other
bit by bit... No can do.
We'll have to skip that because
you've been charged with murder.
In four weeks, a judge will determine
your fate based on what I write.
- So you will talk to me.
- There is no murder.
There is no murder!
It never happened.
I don't have to talk to anybody!
- Want me to help?
- Get away from me.
Easy, Face! Your whole
story's full of holes!
Stop. Stop! Please leave right
now. I'll take responsibility.
Please leave right
now. He's got control.
I'm going to get you,
daddy's boy, little freak!
- My parents are dead, you fuck!
- Enough!
- Is that true?
- Good cop, bad cop.
That you're a daddy's boy?
Primer on David Aames, Senior.
'My father wasn't built
for the 21st century. '
He never went to McDonalds.
He never watched television,
yet his biggest magazine
is still the "TV Digest".
'He and my mother threw the grandest
parties of the literary world.
'Ballooned, jumped out of
aeroplanes. He sought adventure. '
His autobiography is the manual
for every cut-throat
publisher in New York.
It's called "Defending The Kingdom".
Terminar com essa gentileza do Paul
McCartney. I've read it. Page 127:
"David Junior was a
delight as a child. "
Did I miss something here? Is
that all he wrote about you?
I don't think he ever got over the fact
that I'm absolutely
terrified of heights.
The irony continues.
When he and my mother were
run over by a drunken teenager
on New Year's Eve, ten years ago,
he left the keys to the kingdom...
...to me.
Who all thought they were first in line.
And you believe the
board, the Seven Dwarfs,
put you here to take
control of your company?
- What do you care?
- We're just talking.
Tonight's Wednesday night.
I go out for dinner with my
two daughters on Wednesday,
so I'll have to leave soon.
You understand that our
time is limited, don't you?
If I talk...
you'll just think I'm crazy.
With all the possible
respect I can offer a man
wearing a latex mask and spouting
conspiracy theories, David...
...believe me. You've
crossed that bridge.
Enjoy your dinner.
There are five basic
emotions in life, David.
Tell me, what emotion gripped
him before he entered that cell?
Was it guilt? Hate?
Shame?
Revenge?
Love?
I'm completely on the
wrong track, aren't I?
Who needs ice?
- Hey, Emma!
- David, happy birthday.
You have got the greatest
taste in shoes bar none.
Emma, have you met Lynette?
No, but I shudder to think
what we might have in common.
Did you invite the
entire snowboarding team?
It is my birthday.
- Say happy birthday to David.
- Happy birthday.
Welcome to Graceland.
Happy birthday, you sonofabitch!
Happy birthday!
Friends of me!
Let the fun ensue.
...the great John Coltrane.
They would love an article on it.
It's an amazing, amazing product.
No, that's OK. I've got it.
- Literary god, Brian Shelby.
- Happy birthday!
- And all the usual shit. How you doing?
- Living the dream, baby.
David Aames.
- To what do I owe this pleasure?
- The pleasure of Sofia Serrano.
We met today at the library.
- My coat's too big for your closet.
- We were pretending to be intellectuals.
- It's amazing. I love your coat.
- I overdressed. I mean, I underdressed.
I'll continue like you're
both listening to me.
- Do you have another room to put it in?
- I have ceased to exist.
Madison Square Garden is
nearby. It might fit there.
- Happy birthday.
- We picked it out together.
- Thank you.
- We picked it out together. We.
You're welcome.
Stop flirting and open it.
- Let's get a drink!
- Yes.
I'll leave this upstairs.
- Listen...
- Hey, Tommy.
Don't blow me off.
I'm all packed, I'm going back
to London and I understand.
You put me up for that attorney's
job so you didn't have to fire me.
A classy move. Your father
would have done the same.
- It's OK, Tommy.
- I became incompetent.
Is there anything more
unbecoming than an ageing mascot?
I cared for your father. I
lived and breathed for him.
These guys, the Seven Dwarfs,
they think you're stupid.
A corporate hazard, a rogue.
They'll find a way to
catch you out, David.
They're lined up for your
office, your life, your position.
And they're going to sell
this tradition of words
so they can eat in a better cafeteria.
What they don't know is
this. People will read again!
Yeah.
I got it.
They've even got a nickname
for you behind your back.
Citizen... Dildo.
You've got great instincts, but
I say this with complete love.
Claim your life. Learn
to be an asshole...
- Two's enough.
- Forgive me.
I still believe in this family,
David, even if it's only you.
Drive Tipp home.
Give him that big office
across from the Seven Dwarfs.
Set up a meeting with the other
attorneys. I'll be in early tomorrow.
Earlier than usual.
Hello, handsome.
- I've come to wish you happy birthday.
- Oh, man!
- I didn't invite you, Julie.
- That was a little weird.
That's how it works with
parties. You have to be invited.
Oh.
I'm mad at you, you dick.
We made love four times the other night.
- Was that good?
- Two's good.
Three... is very good.
- But four...
- Four's pretty good?
Four is...
Four is what?
Hold me, I'll leave and you can go
back and talk to that cute brunette.
Four is what?
I don't want to meet your fancy friends.
I knew them when I was fancy too.
Four is what?
She looks like a moth, David.
- A moth?
- Sometimes I worry about you.
Some clever girl in a silly coat will
come along and play you just the right way.
I'll lose my friend and there won't
be chicken soup parties for me and you.
OK.
When will you call me? Don't say "soon".
I hate it when you say soon.
So this is what's
become of rock and roll?
A smashed guitar behind a glass case
displayed on some rich guy's wall.
It was a gift, actually.
- I like it.
- Whoa! Whoa!
So how did you get all this
stuff? This apartment, this life?
I see.
How about if you help me?
Unless I'm horning in here.
- You are, but the food's good.
- I've got a stalker.
- It doesn't sound life-threatening.
- I need you to pretend
we're having a scintillating conversation
and you are wildly entertained.
- I know it's tough.
- I'll improvise.
She's right across the room,
burning a hole in my back.
- Red dress, strappy shoes?
- Yes.
She's really staring at you.
I'm having a drink.
- Shit.
- She seems to be crying. Less happy.
I think she's the saddest
girl to ever hold a Martini.
- Brian Shelby.
- Jennifer Kelly.
- You have another apartment?
- Sort of a day office.
- I am not going in there.
- I am. Goodnight.
...get one thing done
Don't like the direction
you are going to
you have come to...
- I hear her coming!
- Really?
No.
Now it has the attention that it used to
Stay home all night
with the TV and wife...
Brian. How are you?
We're safe, but I've
got nothing to drink.
Who did these paintings?
This is Joni Mitchell,
this one is Monet...
...and this one was done
by me. It is a snowboard.
Well, two of them are geniuses.
That is the real thing. His
paintbrush painted the vanilla sky.
Canvas. My mother's.
I'm surprised you're surprised.
- I can't keep this going.
- Me neither.
- I caught you.
- Brian, come in here.
- What's going on?
- I'm drunk.
- Julie Gianni is stalking me.
- She looked dangerous.
Nobody stalks me so I drink.
- We're out of drinks up here.
- Finish my Jack and Coke.
- Stupid glass.
- I've got it.
- It's the stupid guy holding it.
- Don't worry, no big deal.
- I'll get us all something.
- I'd better hit it. I drank too much.
- The party's just starting.
- For you it is.
- You are my guest of honour.
- Fuck you, David.
You're paying me to write
my novel, so you own me.
I don't own you. You are
brilliant, you are handsome.
But why do you have to hit on Sofia?
I wasn't hitting on Sofia.
Fine, whatever you say.
I'm crazy, I'm blind.
You're drinking Jack Daniels. When
you drink, you start with that...
...Frank Sinatra, "she shot me
down, give me a cigarette" thing.
- That I do. Give me a cigarette.
- I'll find one.
You're rich and women love you.
I'm from Ohio and I'm drunk.
- Can I tell you the truth?
- Everybody does.
I dig her. I've never said this
to you before about any girl.
But she could be...
Could be, could be, could
be the girl of my dreams.
- You're not from Ohio.
- I know.
But if she fucks up our
friendship, she can go to hell.
I won't allow it. We are brothers.
- I feel the same way.
- Sure you do.
Hey!
- How you doing? Gracias.
- De nada.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Where are you going?
- I am Frank... and Frank must go.
- What?
- I good you bid evening.
Wait, I'll go with you.
- Stay, baby.
- I'll give you a ride home later.
No, I have to work tomorrow.
You... are in great hands.
I'm just humouring myself
that my opinion matters.
You will never know the exquisite pain
of the guy who goes home alone.
Because without the bitter,
baby, the sweet ain't as sweet.
Have a good time.
Sweet and sour speech again.
Hey, I'm coming down
Like a wrecking ball
Breaking her heart...
A lot of people are scared of heights.
It's not the heights that bother me,
it's the impact that terrifies me.
- I won't stay long.
- Hey, Paulo!
Hello. I have to take you for a walk.
I need protection.
This is a lethal canine.
I love living here and
I refuse to clean up.
No problem.
I have to work around the
clock to keep this place.
- You really are a dancer.
- For 14 years.
But I don't dance like you dance.
- Do you want something to drink?
- Sure.
Hey, Paulo. Beautiful, beautiful boy.
What do you want for dinner
tonight? You want fried chicken?
Paulo!
- I like your life.
- It's mine and you can't have it.
I don't want to know the story
behind this photo. Who's Sergio?
- It's a nickname.
- Your nickname is Sergio?
It's a long story, and
we don't know each other.
- So many secrets.
- I'm really an arms dealer.
- I've never known an arms dealer.
- You do now.
What about you? What's your nickname?
Citizen Dildo.
You are not staying over.
Never run a company. Stay an
artist. Stay an arms dealer.
Please. Somehow I can't
play the violin for you.
Although it must be difficult
controlling all those people's lives.
Everyone at that party is
connected to you for survival.
It seems.
Ever been married?
No. Did you ever accept any
of your 12,000 proposals?
12,008. No.
You moved to New York to
dance, paint, act and deal arms?
Right. Do you want to hear
Jeff Buckley or Vicki Carr?
Jeff Buckley or Vicki
Carr? Both. Simultaneously.
Everyone said: "Don't go to New York.
" But I think good things will happen
if you're a good person with a
good attitude. Don't you think?
- You think I'm naive.
- No, I really don't.
'I dug her completely.
'Somehow, I'd found the last
semi-guileless girl in New York City. '
I have to get to sleep.
Truthfully, I'm also working
mornings as a dental assistant.
Boy, am I going to the wrong dentist.
'You didn't immediately
want to sleep with her? '
'Well, you know, I'm
a pleasure delayer. '
- How does that work?
- Pleasure delay? You don't know?
You keep a relationship casual
until the absolute breaking point.
Then one evening, or
afternoon, or morning...
It could be months from now.
- You know how it works.
- No, actually I don't.
- I've been married for 22 years.
- You've got dinner with your daughters.
That's right, I do.
Back then I had intricate systems
with women you wouldn't believe.
Like... what?
Hey, Doc. Don't get all melancholy
over the 30 seconds you
were single a long time ago.
- That's what you think I'm doing?
- Yes.
You might be right.
Let's continue. Time is not our friend.
Just our shortcomings. That's
all we're allowed to draw.
I've never drawn such
a true likeness before.
- Mine's finished.
- Already?
Done.
- That's how you see me?
- Maybe I didn't add enough money.
It's something you'd see on a
wall in a steak house in hell.
It's wonderful. Sign it.
- Let's see yours.
- No.
Give me that.
Just had to trust imagination
My heart going
boom-boom-boom
Son, he said, grab your things
I've come to take you home...
I feel bad. You said
to draw a caricature.
I know. I couldn't. I saw you like that.
It's very good.
- I'll sell it to you.
- You monster.
How much for?
One kiss.
That smile's going to be the end of me.
What happens when your
friend calls you tomorrow?
He just met you a few hours
before me. He'd do the same.
- I see that friendship is important to you.
- It is.
And as his best friend,
I know he's finishing a novel
about inadequacy and rejection,
so the longer I stay, the
better it is for his career.
Your career is the one I'd worry about.
Sorry.
You're more right than you even know.
I used to be one of
those guys that just...
...was snowboarding through his life,
with no focus whatsoever.
- When did you change?
- About five minutes ago.
Every passing minute is another
chance to turn it all around.
'And to those who think
that you're a charlatan? '
'I understand. A frozen head waiting for
reanimation sounds like science fiction. '
What are you watching?
It's the greatest show.
It's called "Sofia".
'Lt's a new science: Life Extension. '
'How do you accomplish such a thing? '
I've seen this 30 times.
'Life is full of surprises,
but the greatest surprise of all
'is that this doesn't
have to end... ever. '
We did a story on this guy.
He owns half of Arizona.
- Is he a fraud?
- How would you ever know?
Good point.
'Can you unfreeze a human life? '
'Take the case of Benny the dog.
'He was frozen for three months and
thawed out to live a normal life. '
That's comforting. It's safe for Benny.
I'm in.
'Boy will still meet girl,
they will still fall in love.
'Families will flourish,
but man will meet his mind. '
We'd better watch out.
'Raymond Tooley, creator
of Life Extension.
'The book is "Life, The Sequel".'
OK.
- Where are you going?
- I left my number on your fridge.
Come here. I want to tell you a secret.
I meant that to be your forehead.
Thank you for the inspiration.
I will now attempt to run
my company showing compassion
for the seething throng of my partners,
who root quietly for me to fail.
And for things you don't
even know. Thank you.
I'm going to work. I
have a company to run.
Pleasure delayer.
David Aames.
- Julie Gianni.
- Hey, handsome.
- You're following me.
- Just a little bit.
I wanted to finish what
we were talking about.
And?
How did it go with our moth girl?
Did she turn into a butterfly for you?
Yes, she did.
She did.
I could tell by the way you were
walking you didn't sleep with her.
Let me guess. You haven't
slept with her because
it's more fun when you draw
it out. Sex just isn't as good
if a woman hasn't told her
friends she'd never sleep with you.
You're right on the money, Julie.
She must be exhausted from trying
to be witty for you all night long.
- Sorry.
- It's OK.
You're never there for your friends
until they've given up on you.
I'm not blowing you off. I just...
I want to be alone for
a little bit. Trust me.
I have a lot of things to take care of.
If we're friends, which we are,
then you'll understand that.
I'm sorry. I got weird.
I missed an audition
and it made me feel bad you
didn't invite me to your party.
You want to make it up to
me? I won't tell a soul.
You look at me
You speak my name
I'm counting down
You are to blame...
Would you do a story
on me if I made a CD?
Do you like my music?
It's vivid.
If I weren't me, I would buy a CD by me.
You know, if you can reach one person...
Wow.
What's happiness to you, David?
What's happiness to me?
- What is happiness?
- For me...
...this is happiness.
It's being with you.
There's one thing that bothers me.
Why did you tell Brian that
I was your... fuck buddy?
I didn't tell him
that. I didn't say that.
- When did you stop caring, David?
- Caring about what?
About the consequences of
the promises that you've made.
- Promises?
- Yes, the promises.
I thought...
What are you talking about?
Do you understand how hard it
is to pretend to be your buddy?
David, I love you. I fucking love you.
I fucking love you! Fuck!
Don't do this, don't do this.
You fucked me four times
the other night, David.
You've been inside me,
I've swallowed your cum.
That means something.
Slow down.
Four times. It means something, David.
- Four times.
- Stop the car.
24 hours a day, I live
with this aching possibility
that you might call me to do something.
Let's go to your house
and we'll talk this out.
Let's just slow down. Will
you stop the car, Julie!
When you sleep with someone,
your body makes a promise,
whether you do or not.
Tell me something, David.
Do you believe in God?
What are you doing?
I love you. I love you.
Hello.
- You're amazing. Hola.
- Hola.
Did you get to work all right?
Yeah.
No, actually...
I had a horrible dream.
You dreamed you'd never see me again.
I left your apartment, I
went downstairs to the car
and my friend, the stalker,
had followed me there.
- Julie?
- Yes.
She wanted to talk to me.
I remember I had this buzz,
that buzz from you and me.
I think my mind was still on
that terrible drawing of me.
But she was upset.
I don't know. I got in the car...
...and she drove off a bridge
and committed suicide
with me in the car.
I thought you were
going straight to work.
But I survive...
with my arm...
and my face reconstructed.
And what's worse...
I can't wake up.
How was your house after the party?
Party?
- What party?
- The party.
Remember?
Red dress, strappy shoes.
I spilled something on your shirt.
Sweet and sour,
and the saddest girl
to ever hold a Martini.
'My dreams are a cruel joke.
'They taunt me.
'Even in my dreams,
'I'm an idiot who knows he's
about to wake up to reality.
'Lf I could only avoid sleep...
'... but I can't.
'I try to tell myself what to dream.
I try to dream that I'm flying.
'Something free.
'Lt never works. '
Is that the only thing you dream?
I don't remember.
Do you dream about the car accident?
Here's what you remember from a coma
- nothing.
- What happened next?
- What really happened?
Didn't you read the file? I was
out for three and a half weeks.
My face and arm shattered,
my jaw broken in four places.
No surgery could be
performed because of the coma.
You can't feel the darkness or numbness.
You can't even feel.
And then, I came back to life.
Just like that dog,
Benny. Benny the dog.
Only my life was no longer enjoyable.
There are blinding migraines
now. Nerve damage. Why?
This is how big business operates.
Random accidents, a lifestyle mishap.
They are not coincidences.
How do you think airtight
contracts are broken?
These are power upheavals.
I'm from Ohio. We don't
have power upheavals.
They're in the news every
day, right between the lines.
Someone did this to me.
My father wrote about this in his book.
Chapter one, page one, paragraph one.
"What is the answer to
99 out of 100 questions?
"Money. "
'David, I don't want to worry you.
'I'm holding them off, but
we've got a situation here. '
Only if you're mentally acute.
'I'm sorry that poor girl died,
'but you've handed the board
a gift with your mishap.
'They'd like to declare
you incapacitated.
'But you're back.
'You sound good to me,
so let's fight the fuckers
'and have a full recovery. Maybe
you should let people see you. '
The last time we were
together, you were in a coma
and you were very fucking rude
to me. You didn't say a word.
The rumours of my death
have been mildly exaggerated.
'Who could I trust? The ants
were taking over the ant hill.
'Who could I trust? '
'The cranial structure
was based on 30 pins,
'and fastened by micro panels
and bone from the mandible.
'The grafts have maintained
your cheek structure.
Unfortunately, as you were in a coma...
'Doctors. Their power is
in jargon, so you study up.
Is that the procedure for
all bilateral haematomas
in a LeFort llI fracture
of a comatose patient?
'You do your best. '
The potential for intra-cranial
brain damage was too great.
Beyond the cheek grafts,
are the pins fastened
with any kind of aluminium
which could cause the
pressure in my head?
We're working on prostheses,
but you're not at the stage
where we can experiment.
Experiment. Use me.
- The headaches will go away.
- These are more than headaches.
These are like steel plates
slicing through my every thought.
We're not cowboys.
We can't just wing it.
I can't think straight most of the time.
- We can increase your medication.
- Yes. Medication.
We'll continue to investigate.
However, there are so many others
who have not had the aesthetic
benefit of plastic surgery as you have.
This isn't about vanity, Dr Pomerantz.
This isn't about vanity. This is
about functioning in the world.
It's my job to be out there functioning.
I've got the money. I'll pay any amount.
Just invent something! Just play jazz.
You say you're the best face
man in New York? Prove it!
- We could do something about your arm.
- Fuck my arm!
Nobody here takes your
feelings for granted.
We prepared something based
on the preliminary examination.
Bring it on!
It's sometimes useful in the
early stages of rejection.
It's a facial prosthetic. It
was two weeks in the making.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome, doctor.
- A facial prosthetic?
- The aesthetic replacement does work.
Emotionally and actually.
The plastic in the shield
blocks out abusive rays
and assists in the
regeneration of cells.
- It's an aesthetic regenerative shield?
- That's correct.
The ergonomics of the plate
barrier allows it to interact
- with the movements of your face.
- I see.
- It's a helpful unit.
- Good.
For a minute there, I
thought we were talking about
a fucking mask!
It's only a mask if
you treat it that way.
No, it's great. This completely
takes care of Halloween.
But what about the other
364 days of the year?
'A new form of me began to take shape.
'I planned my re-emergence
like the Normandy invasion. '
Sofia. Sofia.
So-fi-a...
Serrano.
'I'll just say it.
'I did my homework. I read every memo.
'Thomas Tipp was right
- people will read again.
'I attended the monthly meeting
of the Seven Dwarfs by video. '
People aren't buying
books! Let's invest.
'Oh, baby. This was war.
'I grew stronger in ways I'd never known
'and on December 5th,
my planes filled the sky.
'The return of David
Aames, Jr. Citizen Dildo. '
Did you see his face?
You won't believe this...
...but this is me smiling.
It's been a long time.
I tried to see you, but
your people wouldn't let me.
I didn't want to see me, OK?
But then I woke up today, and finally...
...a good hair day.
You want to get together?
Sure.
- What?
- Let's go out and do something.
This weekend. I'll cancel
an operation or two.
We'll have fun.
Because I am all about fun.
'Our first guest tonight is
an amazing survival story.
'Please welcome Benny the dog!
'Welcome to the show, Gary.
'I have so many questions.
'Tell us what has happened to
Benny? What's Benny been through? '
'Benny fell into the water near our home
- 'and was frozen in the Skykomish river. '
- 'Ln Washington. '
'I went fishing, thinking he'd
been gone for three months,
'and I see him in a block of ice. '
'He is thawed out now, is that correct?
'He's not moving a lot. I'm worried.
'I'm worried about the dog. '
'He's fine. He's just lost
a little of his friskiness. '
Sofia? It's David.
I'm back in your life.
I saw you earlier today.
I was just watching our old
friend Benny the dog on "Conan"
and I thought of you.
Whatever. I...
...I loved seeing you today.
So I will see you soon.
You're a great dancer.
- What are you drinking?
- Nothing.
I'm in the mood for a cheap,
overpriced rum and Coke.
- Do you want one?
- Is there any other kind?
- I'll get us some.
- Where is the bathroom?
It's behind...
Over there, by the girl
who looks like Bjrk.
- I'll be right back.
- Maybe I should...
You look good. How's your book?
- Take it off.
- This is a facial shield.
It's kind of like a prosthesis.
Take off the mask. It's freaking me out.
I can't.
It's my face. This is my face.
Trust me, it's a little different.
If you're embarrassed, just go.
Nobody asked you to chaperone.
Sofia asked me.
She didn't want to be alone
with me? That's bullshit!
I'm being pretty cool
about this whole thing.
Talk to a shrink. Or are
you going to call me sometime
instead of hiding in your apartment?
Don't take it out on a
girl you only met once.
Did she say that? Once?
She said I met her once?
Just cut it out. I miss the old you.
We all miss the old you.
Because the new guy is shit.
That came out wrong. I love you. Period.
- How's your arm, man?
- Fuck you, Brian.
How about no sympathy? How
about that's the deal we make?
Give me a Budweiser
and a shot of tequila.
What kind of tequila?
- What did you say to me?
- I said, "What kind of tequila?"
Why don't you ask me to my face, bitch?
Patron, if you have it.
They are setting the stage
For the renegades
To control your mind
They planned it yesterday
Free Zulu nation here to stay
Let's get electrofied
Pump it, rockin' it, stickin'
it, funkin' it Afrika...
- Another shot, another Bud.
- This is on the house.
- Why?
- It just is... bitch.
...that's the way you say Zulu
Z- U-L-U that's
the way you say Zulu
Zulu nation Cities of Angels
Afrika Bambaataa
Zulu nation
Z- U-L-U that's
the way you say Zulu
Z- U-L-U that's the
way you say Zulu...
Patron!
Fix your fucking face!
- Hello again.
Idea
- let's start over.
How about if you help me?
Unless I'm horning in here.
"You are, but the food is good. "
I've got this little
problem. I've got a stalker.
"It doesn't sound life-threatening. "
I need you to pretend we're
having a scintillating conversation
and you are wildly
entertained. I know it's tough.
- "I'll improvise. "
- I don't talk like that.
She's right across the room,
burning a hole in my back.
Red dress, strappy shoes.
That's right.
I think she is the saddest
girl to ever hold a Martini.
- Are you OK?
- No.
What's wrong? Is it me?
- Is it me?
- I'll tell you later.
Tell me now. If something's
wrong, please tell me now.
- Just talk about everything.
- I'll tell you later!
Let's get it all out.
Say everything now.
Just say everything. Say
everything now, now, now.
I'll tell you in another
life when we are both cats.
I can't believe you just said that.
That's the greatest
thing I've ever heard.
That's hilarious. That you said that.
That's... You said that. You said that.
That is what I love about you.
That's hilarious.
I'll tell you in another
life when we are both cats.
Cats! Cats!
- This is where I leave you.
- I'll walk you to your door.
- I live just around the corner.
- I've got my bike.
- I'd rather walk.
- Don't be a drag.
Can't you see she
wants to go on her own?
Shut up, you're drunk.
I may be an idiot, but I'm not drunk.
Seriously, I don't need you
to walk me home. Thank you.
OK, then, so...
...we'll call you.
We'll go catch a movie or something.
So we'll meet up soon.
We'll meet up soon.
We'll call you again to go out with me.
We'll call you.
It's been a real blast,
David. I bid you good evening.
Wait, where are you going?
My bike is back over
there. We'll hang soon.
Bring your mask if you
want. I'm getting used to it.
- Wait a minute.
- What?
I don't know.
You drank too much. Call me tomorrow.
Tomorrow I'll wish I was dead.
No, you won't. You just need to sleep.
- Hey. Hey!
- What?
What did you say to Julie
Gianni the night of the accident?
- What?
- You told her she was a fuck buddy.
Never.
She was a little more
than pissed about it.
Have you been harbouring
this shit all along?
I never talked to her.
Whatever.
Anyway, who am I if I can't be the
one to tell you you're not ugly?
Come on! Give me a courtesy laugh!
Brian, I'm so fucked
up. I'm just so fucked up
We're best friends! We're bro's!
Come on, man. We're bro's.
Readying to bury your
father and your mother
What did you think when you lost another
I used to wonder why did you bother
Distanced from one, blind to the other
Listen here my sister and my brother
What would you care
if you lost the other
I always wonder why did we bother
Distanced from one, blind to the other
Oh... Oh...
Oh... but sweetness follows...
Open your eyes.
Boo!
- This is a cheap ploy for sympathy.
- I'm OK. I'm OK.
And it worked. Get up.
I agree.
This is a joke.
David, I'm not going to lie to you.
I liked the way you looked. But...
...you have to pull
it the fuck together.
If not, I'll forget the other guy.
You know that other guy? You?
I'm still that guy.
I don't have a mother saviour bone
in my body. It's not about that.
You are coming inside, but if this
turns out to be a big mistake...
...I do have the ability to fall
out of love with you like that.
'We created our own world together.
'Us versus them. '
- Where's Brian?
- Brian? He went with you, didn't he?
I thought you guys hooked up.
I wish you hadn't got in
the car with that girl.
Sofia, I...
Your eyes apologise better.
Come on.
Holy God! This is going to change
my life in a zillion different ways.
I must be nuts!
'We were quite a pair.
'Her believing in me, me believing
that I actually deserved it. '
Ah, Sofia.
I see you haven't
been wasting your time.
- Do you ever draw anything else?
- No.
Did you sleep last night?
I love you.
No, I did not sleep.
Got to leave early today, David,
so you'll have to be brief.
What can you tell me
about the name Ellie?
Ellie.
Was that a girl you were in love with?
I've only been in love once.
Apparently you kept
repeating it last night.
You did sleep, David. Your
advisor said you cried out.
- You had a nightmare.
- Everything's a nightmare.
You cried out for Ellie, David.
Do you remember what happened?
I... I don't...
Dig deep, David. Dig deep.
You cried out for Ellie. What
do you remember about Ellie?
Show me your face, David.
Help me open the door.
It's true you had an accident,
it's true you were disfigured.
But not any more.
Do you remember?
They did fix your face.
Take off that mask, David. You'll
see your face is perfect under there.
I never trusted the doctors.
What happened next was surreal.
That same arrogant bastard,
Dr Pomerantz, called me
and suddenly he was my new best friend.
David! My brother! I felt really
bad about our last conversation.
'He'd discovered a new form
of reconstructive surgery
'with the help of a
doctor from Berlin. '
Hello.
'Next thing I knew, they shot me
full of drugs I'd never heard of
'and away we went. '
What if God was one of us?
Just a slob like one of us?
Trying to make his way home...
He's got a good voice.
And facial tissue could be regenerated.
...the concept of endoscopic,
periorbital fibre optics.
- Where are we eating later?
- I can't even tell you what they did.
It seemed like science fiction.
Madonna had that song "Borderline".
That was a hell of a song.
This is going to be one
good-looking guy when I'm done.
'Obviously I was suspicious. '
- Wouldn't you be?
- Suspicious of whom? Of what?
Doc, once you've been driven
off a bridge at 80 miles an hour,
somehow you don't invite happiness
in without a full body search.
At the risk of boring you, I can
present the alternate argument.
I once knew a guy who was a real loner.
One day he woke up at 40
with two daughters that lit
up his life with purpose.
He suddenly goes to
endless school plays,
he gets home at 9:20 for
the evening discussion
and he has the time of his life.
His favourite Beatle was
once John and now it's Paul.
I always liked George.
It all depends on the
individual, doesn't it?
- Tell me, what's happiness for you?
- What's happiness to you, David?
- How about another question?
- You won't show me your face, will you?
So, back to the timeline.
Hurry, let's move through this.
David!
- David?
- What?
- You've got to take the plates off.
- I don't want to know what's under here.
It'll be fine, you'll see.
I called Pomerantz and
switched it to Wednesday.
What?
I hope that women at the front
desk gave you shit about it.
Another day won't matter,
and the Mustang will be fixed.
The plan was going in the
Mustang. It's not ready.
So we'll go tomorrow in the
Mustang, when it's fixed.
I know that the problem
wouldn't be you delaying
something you were dreading.
- Couldn't be that.
- No, couldn't be that.
I mean...
I mean... I agree.
I think it's very important to have...
...the right car...
...to take you...
...where you want to go...
...24 hours a day.
How bad is it?
Well, your ears are in the right place.
And the rest of it...
...is not too bad at all.
It's perfect.
When she said, "Don't waste
your words, they're just lies,"
I cried she was deaf
And she worked on my face
until breaking my eyes
Then said, "What else
have you got left?"
It was then that I got up to leave
But she said, "Don't forget,
Everybody must give something back
For something they get...
Do you love me? I mean really love me?
Because if you don't,
I'll just have to kill you.
In my next life...
In my next life, I'm going to
come back as this mole right here.
Seriously, this mole.
You'll have to wear bikini tops
to work so that I can breathe.
I love you. Love you.
I love you.
I can live right there.
Is this a dream?
Absolutely.
'We talked about the big
things, the little things...
'... and the big things.
'But, in truth, with Sofia
it was the in-between times. '
In the days When we were
swinging from the trees
I was a monkey...
Je t'aime.
Stealing honey from a swarm of bees
I could taste
I could taste you even then
And I would chase you...
- What did she say?
- I have no idea.
- How's things, Brian?
- Fine.
Brian, how's things?
Don't flatter yourself. I'm fine.
Besides, Sofia is great, but
by no means one of a kind.
She was a proximity infatuation.
Don't use that, it's mine.
Where did you get this camera?
I'm into things you
have no idea, my friend.
- Just so long as you're OK.
- Anyway, we're friends, aren't we?
- Always.
- That's right.
What's up with your face?
Fuck!
There's a seam opening or something!
- David Aames.
- You fucking asshole.
I know.
Was I snoring?
No. I think it was me. I
was thirsty, that's all.
I'm dreaming about you. Mmm.
I could listen to you say
"mmm" for the rest of my life.
Baby, what's wrong?
- Where is she?
- Who?
Who?
I'm Sofia.
I'm going to make sure that I tie
it four times. You know why, Julie?
Because four times
really means something.
Please don't hurt me.
I'm freaked out, it worked.
You won't get away with this,
so just tell me where Sofia is.
- I am Sofia.
- Where's Sofia?
- I am Sofia!
- Where is she?
I'm calling the police. Tell it to them.
You survived the accident.
Whose body was it?
It was the board, the
Seven Dwarfs, wasn't it?
You're trying to steal my life!
You weren't in an accident.
Now it's attempted murder!
I am Sofia, please!
Tell it to them.
This is David Aames. I need help.
I've captured an intruder
who's entered my home.
Oh, God!
Wake up man. Are you for real?
They've kept me here for three hours.
They think that I had
something to do with this.
Can you give us a minute here?
Thanks very much.
They think I had
something to do with this.
We're going to handle this
the way your father would.
- I've got it solved.
- You've got it solved?
Where is she?
She's going to be fine. This
whole file is going to...
Thank God you're here.
It's OK.
I love her.
Look at these photos, then
I'm going to destroy them.
Sofia's testimony is also
in here. It won't exist.
She's not going to press charges.
- Press charges against me?
- David, wake up.
As a friend...
...I think you should
see what you did to Sofia.
The press won't get hold of
this if you get away quickly.
This is Julie Gianni, this is not Sofia.
This is Julie Gianni.
I didn't do this to her.
Someone's setting me up.
David, the board and I have
taken care of everything.
They've been really great, actually.
All this is going to disappear.
We're all behind you, even the board.
Get out of here.
This is a revolution of the mind.
You're insane!
Don't ever hit a girl!
Hit me, but don't ever hit a girl!
It wasn't Sofia. It was Julie.
- It was Julie.
- It was Julie Gianni.
So Sofia was abducted by Julie
and now Julie is posing as Sofia.
You're in OJ land, man.
Julie Gianni is dead!
I don't care what they told you. I
can assure you Julie Gianni is alive.
- I didn't talk to them, I talked to Sofia.
- Where is she?
I just dropped Sofia off. I
saw everything you did to her.
I did not do that to her.
Look me in the eye and tell me that's
the girl you brought to the party.
Tell me that's your dream girl,
your proximity infatuation.
Yes! And you stole her from me.
The one girl I really wanted
and you took her from me.
You're insane. You're losing it, man!
- You have revealed yourself.
- Oh, yeah.
I'm with them.
Where did you get the coat, Brian?
Where did you get the camera?
How much did they pay you?
Listen to me, because this is the
last time we're ever going to speak.
- I was your only friend.
- You have revealed yourself to me.
Problems?
I'm in no mood to be fucked with, so...
There's an explanation
for all this, David.
You and I know each other.
You found me on the Internet.
I'm here to help you, David.
Who the fuck are you?
Why are you following me?
First of all, it's very
important that you calm down.
Calm down? Calm down!
You must overcome your
fears and regain control.
Take hold of your life again, David.
It's as easy as holding that glass.
What if I were to tell you that
you can take control of all of this?
Even me.
I'm straight, OK?
David, look at all these people.
Seems as though they're all
just chatting away, doesn't it?
- Nothing to do with you?
- No.
And yet maybe they're only here
because you wanted them to be here.
You are their god.
You can make them obey
you or even destroy you.
What I'd love for them
to do is shut the fuck up,
especially you.
You see?
You and I signed a contract, David.
'Who is the man in the
restaurant? ' Who is it?
Can you tell the difference
between dreams and reality?
- Of course. Can you?
- Think about it.
Think with your head. You
signed a contract, did you not?
- I signed something.
- Was the man in the restaurant there?
- Fuck!
- Accept your body's resistance.
Let your head answer.
- Yes.
- That's right. Who is Ellie?
- I don't know what's real.
- What happened that night?
- Somebody died.
- I don't want to remember.
You understand you hold
the keys to this prison?
- It wasn't Sofia.
- Who was it?
- No.
You want to let it
out, don't you, David?
You're about to tell me.
Tell me what your heart and soul
will not allow you to forget.
Did you kill Sofia?
I thought you were a vandal.
Who are you?
I'm Sofia.
You are not Sofia!
You are not Sofia.
I'm Sofia. We're going
to be together again.
You're going to forget about Juliana
and we're going to be together.
I'm not going to be
afraid of you any more.
I'll get you a cold
towel. I'll be right back.
I love you.
'Pleasure delayer. '
Sofia?
I am Sofia.
I love you. I missed you so much.
Where were you?
Forget it. I don't need
to know. It doesn't matter.
Just tell me that you love me.
I love you.
What is happiness to you, David?
For me, it's being here with you.
What the fuck is happening?
David was a real delight as a child.
I'm so afraid of how powerful this is.
Oh, David.
Red dress, strappy shoes...
That is the greatest
thing I have ever heard.
I'll tell you in another
life when we are both cats.
What's happening?
I did it, didn't I?
But I don't feel like I killed someone.
- I feel like I'm in a dream.
- Who was the man at the restaurant?
Sometimes the mind behaves
as if it were a dream.
Faces change, people
become other people.
The subconscious is a powerful thing.
You treated Julie
carelessly, didn't you?
Your feelings of responsibility
or guilt over Julie
might have turned Sofia into Julie.
- Do you know what derangement is?
- I need your help.
All I know is you killed your girlfriend
and I don't know what's in your mind.
I need your help.
I would work on this case forever if
I could, but we've run out of time.
What will you plead?
Temporary derangement.
That's your best chance.
I don't think they'll believe me.
Who do you believe?
Believe it or not, I care about you.
You've become like family to me.
I don't want to give up on you, David.
But I needed more. I needed an answer.
I even thought there was a chance
somebody was playing a trick on you.
Maybe it was the board. But
I can't exceed my duties.
I'm just a psychologist...
...and I have to go now.
Will I see you at the trial?
No, I'm just the opening act.
'Reassurance is our speciality.
That's the Life Extension creed.
'Benny the dog was
frozen for three months
'and thawed out to live a normal life.
'Life Extension can translate
to the human form, too.
'How do you accomplish such a thing?
72 cryonised patients are currently
held at our facility in New Brunswick.
We feature the finest scientific
technicians on the planet.
- The book is "Life, The Sequel".
- McCabe!
McCabe!
Come back!
Life Extension Corporation,
please. LE. We hold a court order.
I think I've been here before.
- Her name is Libby.
- Good morning, Mr McCabe.
I'm Libby. I'm here to assist you.
He's my son. He's very shy.
You're not with the media or
part of any legal consortium?
Welcome to Life Extension.
Take a look at our
proposal. Please follow me.
You can wait out here.
You'll be meeting Rebecca
Dearborn, my personal role model.
'I didn't need the pain any more. '
'Life Extension wants you to live. '
'I don't think that God
disapproves of this. '
Cryonisation, a journey of reawakening
after the preservation of the human
body at extremely low temperatures.
- They laughed at Jules Verne, too.
- David, you are not...
Mr McCabe, how are you?
I'm Rebecca Dearborn.
Life Extension, or LE as
we like to refer to it,
is a glimpse of the future. A
ticket, not in the juvenile sense
but in the deeply meaningful sense that
can only be borne in the human heart.
The DNA codes of the human
body have been broken.
Soon heart ailments, cancer, so much
more will be a thing of the past.
Very simply, your anguish,
your discontent, even your death
is no longer necessary
in a traditional sense.
Whatever malady hides behind
that mask, it's temporary.
Within an hour of your passing, LE
will transfer your body to a vessel
where you will be sealed and
frozen at 196 degrees below zero.
Power outages, earthquakes, nothing
will affect your suspension hibernation.
Have you signed a contract
with these people, David?
- What's the Lucid Dream option?
- Good choice.
The Lucid Dream is Life
Extension's newest option.
For a little extra,
we offer the cryonic union
of science and entertainment.
Cryotainment.
Some find this presentation helpful.
I have a universe inside me...
'Portrait of a modern human life.
'American, male, birth and death.
'Lmagine that you are suffering
from a terminal illness.
'You'd like to be cryonised
but you'd rather be resurrected
'to continue your own
life as you know it now.
'LE offers you the answer.
'Upon resurrection, you will continue
in an ageless state, preserved,
'but living in the present
with a future of your choosing.
'Your death will be
wiped from your memory.
'Your life will continue
'as a realistic work of art,
'painted by you minute to minute.
'You'll live it with
the romantic abandon
'of a summer day,
'with the feeling of a great movie
'or pop song you always loved.
'With no memory of how it
occurred, save for the knowledge
'that everything simply improved.
'Ln any instance of discontent,
you'll be visited by technical support.
'Lt's just around the corner.
'The day after tomorrow, another
chapter begins seamlessly.
'A living dream, Life
Extension's promise to you.
'Life part two. '
A living dream.
Your death will be
wiped from your memory.
I guess I missed that
one in "USA Today".
A dream. What if there was a mistake?
What if the dream became a nightmare?
Your subconscious can
always play tricks on you.
The subconscious is
a very powerful thing.
Did you sign a contract
with these people, David?
But this is a serious business.
The Lucid Dream is worth the risk.
And what is any life if
not the pursuit of a dream?
The dream of peace, the
dream of achievement,
the dream of hearing
someone say these words...
...when they truly mean them:
I love you, David.
- Te quiero.
- I love you.
And the way the sunlight
plays upon your hair...
Roam free, David. Most
of us live our whole lives
without any real
adventure to call our own.
It's hard to comprehend, but
they laughed at Jules Verne, too.
This is a revolution of the mind.
I'm picking up good vibrations
I want to wake up! Tech support!
It's a nightmare!
Tech support!
David Aames. I think it's time
we had a proper introduction.
I'm Edmund Ventura
from the Oasis project,
formerly Life Extension, LE.
- Tech support?
- Yes, I'm your tech support.
We first met 150 years ago.
Shit. You sold me the Lucid Dream.
- What the hell happened?
- I tried to warn you in the bar, David.
I told you that it all
depended on your mind.
All of this, everything
is your creation.
Now we're heading towards
your true moment of choice.
- True moment of choice?
- Yes.
When did the Lucid Dream begin?
- Do you remember the night club?
- We'll meet up soon.
That night, after Sofia left you
and you fell asleep on the pavement,
that was the moment that
you chose for the splice.
- Splice?
- Splice.
The end of your real life and
the beginning of LE's Lucid Dream.
A splice of many years
which passed while you
were frozen and dreaming.
From the moment you woke up,
- nothing was real in the traditional sense.
- Open your eyes.
Your Lucid Dream is
monitored by Life Extension
and a panel of experts
following your every thought,
even at this moment.
Forgive me, I'm blowing your mind.
I'm not a big fan of heights.
I know.
We erased what really
happened from your memory.
- Erased?
- Replaced...
...by a better life, under these
beautiful, Monet-like skies.
- My mother's favourite.
- A better life because you had Sofia.
You sculpted your Lucid Dream out
of the iconography of your youth.
- An album cover that once moved you.
- An album cover?
'There are some things that you're not
old enough to understand just yet. '
A movie you saw once that showed
you what a father could be like.
Or what love could be like.
This was a kind woman, an
individual. More than your equal.
You barely knew her in your real life,
but in your Lucid Dream
she was your saviour.
What happened in my real
life? Something happened.
- What did you erase?
- Do you really want to know?
Tell me everything.
The morning after the night club, you
woke up on the street, hungover and alone.
You got up and you walked
away. You never saw Sofia again.
I didn't kill Sofia.
No.
You battled your board, the Seven
Dwarfs, for control of the company.
In the end it was Thomas
Tipp, your father's friend,
who wrenched the company
back into your control.
Tommy.
But then...
...somebody died.
You longed for Sofia.
You shut yourself away
for months. You were alone.
You couldn't stand the pain
any more, the headaches.
- You could barely function.
- I found you on the Internet.
I signed a contract with you and then...
I remember.
Somebody died.
It was me.
'And on a day in late December...
'... you gave yourself to us.
'You're now in a suspended state.
'Your friend Brian Shelby threw a
three-day memorial in your old home.
'He was a true friend.
'You were missed, David.
'Lt was Sofia who never fully recovered.
'Lt was she who somehow knew you best.
'Like you, she never
forgot that one night
'where true love seemed possible.
'Consequences, David.
'Lt's the little things. '
The little things.
There's nothing bigger, is there?
Your subconscious did create problems.
Your dream turned into a nightmare.
The glitch has been corrected.
So all I have to do
is imagine something?
Like if I wanted McCabe
to come back right now.
Listen to me. These
people are dangerous.
We're in trouble. We need
to get off this roof now.
We're now on pause, and you're
about to return to your Lucid Dream.
Pause?
You won't remember any of this, nor will
you be charged for technical support.
It's now your moment of choice.
You can return to your Lucid Dream
and live a beautiful life with Sofia
or whomever you wish.
Or you can choose the world out there.
The world out there?
And you can bring me back?
Just like Benny the dog?
Yes, just like Benny the dog.
Your face and body can be fixed now,
but things are very different now.
And your finances won't last long.
Your panel of observers are
waiting for you to choose.
There are no guarantees. But
remember, even in the future,
the sweet is never as
sweet without the sour.
- How do I wake up?
- The decision is yours.
I chose this scenario, didn't I?
Yes, to face your last
remaining fear of heights.
David, don't listen to him.
This is the Seven
Dwarfs. It's a set-up!
You can't trust him.
Don't feel bad for him, David.
This winning man is your creation.
It's in his nature to
fight for his existence,
- but he's not real.
- I'm real.
I'm real. I have two daughters.
You know that.
What are their names?
I'm real.
I'm...
Mortality as home entertainment?
This cannot be the future!
Can it?
Goodbye.
It's been a journey of self-awakening.
Now you've got to ask yourself this.
What is happiness to you, David?
I want to live a real life.
I don't want to dream any longer.
Any last wishes?
Let them out there read my mind.
I wish you well, David.
Look at us. I'm frozen and you're dead.
And I love you.
It's a problem.
I lost you when I got
in that car. I'm sorry.
Do you remember what you told me once?
Every passing minute
is another chance to turn it all around.
I'll find you again.
I'll see you in another life...
...when we are both cats.
'Relax, David. Open your eyes. '