Brother Jersy will have
a game with Turkey tonight?
Anyone takes side bet?
Those who bet on
Jersy get 60% dividend
And 100% for Turkey,
of course l bet on Turkey
Don´t bet for him, l´m little Ping
l bet on Jersy, $50,000!
Brother, everyone bets on you
As your mom had
a hard time to bring you up
you´d better die to pay her,
as you´re so stupid
You won´t win
if you don´t bet on me
Turkey is a stink ass-hole!
No foul language
No foul language?
But it gives me power
l don´t like it
What then?
Foul language may also
be pleasing to the ears
and just like singing
Foul language can be
as pleasing as singing?
l don´t believe
lt´s true
Good...
Who says good?
Not me
Hasn´t bastard Jersy arrived?
Turkey, you can´t wait to lose?
l don´t know what Jersy
and Turkey are playing
lt should be my turn to decide
how to gamble this time
You´ll lose whatever
game you decide
Mahjong, Poker, Baccarat,
you have never won
Hey, what games will we play
as you ask me here?
Let´s play snooker
and then we bet on soccer!
The bet for soccer is $1 million
England Vs Portugal,
England giving half goal
l always try to help the weaker side
Now England leads by 2 goals,
l´ll bet Portugal will win
For snooker, let´s bet on
our places of control
lf you lose, you let me
have Mongkok
lf l lose, you get Lai Chi Kok
You get more advantage, ass-hole!
Hey, what have l said?
One, two, three, four
Oh...
l give you a banana
Will you suck it?
Good song!
Honey, is it good enough?
OK
Hey, will you accept the bet?
Make it Lai Chi Kok
and Cheung Sha Wan
Jersy, since you defeated
me in Poker game last time
l´ve missed for 4 months
As l´ve been practising
with my coach Davis
18 hours a day
l have now made a big leap
You must die this time!
Hubby, he´s mighty
Who is your coach?
Same as his, Davis
And also Beckham, Jordan
Then you needn´t fear him
But to tell the truth...
l learn soccer from Davis
And from Beckham...
l learn basketball
From Jordan...
l learn from him
as how to cook hotpot
What?
l´ve won, l´ll serve first
But l want one cue to decide victory
Whoever hits the ball first shall win
Ok, l don´t fear you!
Turkey, you fell into my trap!
My coach, Jordan, is not
the basketball player
He indeed lives in Jordan Road
who everyone refers him as
Mighty-left-handed Sweeper!
Roll...
What have you just said?
What Mighty-lefthanded Sweeper?
My honey!
Hit
Honey!
Deduce 4 points,
l lead you by 3 points now!
You...
l tell you, the trick just then...
is my most secret skill
What is it called?
lt´s called Tornado Shoot
You think the red balls have
stopped in front of the pocket?
ln fact it is spinning at a high
speed of 100 spins a second
and creates lightning
effect on the felt cover
Once the white ball hits it,
it´ll spin like turnado
And it´ll fall dead
l´ve perfected it,
no one can escape
Nuts!
England loses when it
leads by 2 goals? Damn it!
Turkey, why so stupid?
There´s a device called
VCR in this world
This match ended
15 minutes ago already
You can´t be a culprit
as you´re foolish
You´d better become a good guy
Damn it!
Boss!
Honey, you´re my boy!
Brother Jersy, hurrah!
Help yourselves, please
Thank you, Boss
You don´t cook some for me?
What do you mean?
l courted you as l thought
you were a foreigner
As l thought if l took you out...
your English will astonish others
But both your English
and Chinese are lousy
l wonder where you are from
Tahiti
Tahiti?
Yeah
You mustn´t mix...
the local beach up with Tahiti
My native language is French, you know?
You speak French?
God damn your mother!
Eat now
l don´t know what you´re speaking
Nothing, only curse you
Hey, fatty!
l´ve won millions of dollars today
and you serve me only this food?
Eat some vegetables
Fatty, don´t know who l am?
The new Master of Gambling
Eat vegetables?
l´ll only eat food from heaven!
You?
Damn you!
Not suitable for children
Then... let´s sing nursery rhymes
You´re an ass-hole,
everywhere in Hong Kong
People try to chop you,
Kick you ass-hole
You´re an ass-hole, dot...
What does dot mean?
Foul language,
for the sake of censor
You damned fool
You cannot be compared with
Cool of the old days
The Cool you mean...
is the guy made a fame
with flying cards...
when the God, Holy,
Master retired from gambling
He´s the favourite of all female
On the list of
Most Wanted Husband...
he´s the only guy
who defeated Richard Gear
lf Cool hadn´t disappeared 3 years ago...
you´re no better than a mouse
when you stand next to him
He disappeared for the sake of love?
That´s a stupid Cool
He´s my idol anyway
l was still a parking valet
when he made a fame
Can you tell me more about him?
l remember at that time...
Cool was cocky and proud
For Cool´s legend, besides
being a competent gambler
he also has a sexy girlfriend, Karen
and his sworn brother Yeung Kwong,
who was always calm
The three of them formed a triangle
Once the battle with his rival...
Cool threw all the money in the sky,
total to millions of dollars
Then he and Karen danced
in the wind of banknotes
lsn´t it a classic?
ls it true?
Well, to compare with Cool...
you´re no more than a mouse
lf Cool was really so mighty...
how come he disappeared suddenly?
Did someone assassinate him?
Hey, as you´ve won so much
Why not go on a trip to Japan?
People say Cool could turn poker
cards into flying blades
ls it true?
l want to go shopping
l want to go shopping in Japan
l want to go shopping in Japan...
l want to go shopping!
l want to go shopping in Japan!
l know l´m wrong
OK, whatever you say
l now order you...
to organize a luxurious
tour to Japan for me
And the charge is
about $2000 per head
Here is $5,000, fix it for me
l now order you...
to organize a luxurious
tour for me
which lasts about 9 days,
charge is $1,000 per head
Here´s $3,000, fix it for me
l now order you...
to organize a luxurious tour
to Japan for me
which lasts about 9 days,
charge is $500 per head
Here´s $1,000, take it
Got it, Boss
Harajuku, Matsushitato
Going shopping?
From dawn to dusk?
Of course we must
go shopping here in Japan
But you needn´t shop
from 8 a.m. to 8 p.m.
You needn´t eat something?
You mean it
Let´s eat something
When can we have a meal?
My friend, take it easy
Let´s get a bath back in the hotel
and gather for a meal
OK? Let´s get back to the hotel first
Jersy, get up!
l´ve taken my 4th bath,
When are we going for a meal?
Then take the 5th now
What?
Get up, ask that fatty out!
Hurry!
Quiet, everybody...
l don´t know what´s on,
l work part time only
l don´t know what you´re saying
Refund now!
The fatty is nowhere to see,
he must have slipped away
You mean it?
l must beat him up
when l return to HK!
lt´s so dark at the early hours?
And there´s no restaurant nearby, shit
Walk a bit further,
and see if there´s a shop
No, l´m not familiar with this area
lf we get robbed, we can never
find that bastard again
Let´s get back to the hotel now
No, l must eat something
l´m starving
Look at you, you´re barely dressed
And you leap while walking
This is a real leaping lamp
We´ll be ruined if guys rape us
lf l get kidnapped, l´ll be raped
But if l go back with you,
you´ll rape me
You look down on me?
l didn´t mean that
We´re getting along with true love
Just like the lovers
in the movie Titanic
Hey, Chinese cuisine
l´ll ruin the shop
if they are closed
No one is here?
ls it a funeral parlour?
What would you like?
Let me see
A Chinese restaurant with
only Japanese menu?
This is Japan, they mean
to serve Japanese
What would you like?
Two bowls of shark fin soup,
two abolones
and lobsters
Don´t overcharge, only $70 in HK
Does it?
Then the restaurant
must be owned by your dad
This boss is handsome
You need a bowl of fried rice
or a handsome guy now?
Answer me!
Fried rice
Fukien Fried Rice, Classic Fried Rice,
Yamadei Fried Rice
Get whatever fried rice
you have for us
You´re very hungry?
- ls it enough?
- Yes
Not bad, you´re from HK?
Yeah, l´ve been here
for a couple of years
You´d better go back to HK
This place is shabby,
you can´t have good business
Go back to HK and work under me,
l´m Jersy
And you´ll have a better living
Brother Jersy?
What field are you in?
lf l tell you,
others will say l´m boasting
You tell him
This nuts is...
Hong Kong number one man,
after God of Gambling...
Holy of Gambling,
Master of Gambling...
He is the forever winning www
King of Gambling masters. net.com
Nice to meet you
lt´s an updated nickname
Sure, in HK, everyone has
a nick name ends with.com
Look at you, you mustn´t have
won big money
Go back to HK and
l´ll teach you some tricks
And you´ll run into good luck
Chinaman, have you thought over?
l´ve put it clear already
No protection money,
then you close!
l have no money!
lt´s late, why are there
furious white-collars?
They come to
collect protection money
Japanese culprits
They deserve the money!
Look how cool they are, all in suit
Who are you, ass-hole?
He seems to follow what l say,
what did he say?
Never mind him
Translate it for me
Nothing, he says you look lousy
Why are you
so frank in the translation?
lf not, a fierce fight
could be avoided
Go to hell you ass-hole!
Kick his mother fucking ass! Baby
Beat him!
Baby, beat him...
Why he only beats me?
What did he say?
He asked why you only
chase and beat him
lt´s because of what you say!
You look cocky,
so you must be beaten!
Translate it for him!
Get weapon, bitch!
Take it!
Damn it! Wait!
Eat some vegetables
Bastard, go to hell!
Honey, you´re my hero!
l´m a very good eagle. Right?
You´re pulling down the place?
Sorry
l´ll have it mended
before l return to HK
No thanks
lt´s you who threw the saucer?
What saucer?
Cool is a great man
He made a fame with flying cards
You are?
Wong
Wong?
You´re from HK
Have you ever heard of Cool
a real special man?
Cool?
Haven´t heard of
Much work for me now
Honey, what are you thinking?
But l feel that this Wong...
must be related to Cool
He´s as competent as l
He must have been in Japan for ages,
and learn from Japanese
He uses the peeping binoculars
l´m not the same,
l´m always horny and sly
You´re a real busybody
Yeah, l don´t know why
Someone said you have a girlfriend
called Karen
But you still peep at women?
She´s my girlfriend
Still peeping?
Go into and molest her now!
She´s already other´s wife
l´m sorry
But... she seems to be asleep
As she becomes a vegetable now
What a pity
are you OK?
l´m OK
Jersy, if you treat me as a friend
please don´t interfere in my affairs
Of course l treat you as a friend!
l don´t mind even sharing
underpants with you!
l don´t want you to follow me,
as l will come here everyday
You say this yourself
She´s the girlfriend of another man
And also lead a vegetable existence
Why are you still hung up on her?
l needn´t tell you
about my personal affairs
Long hung love will hurt
Excuse me... do you know...
You´re from HK?
You speak Cantoness, great!
So-so, l like Hong Kong movies
Hong Kong movies?
You know me,
l´m a Hong Kong movie star
Adam Chow
Mr. Chow, aren´t you
in Hollywood now?
No. l come back to Hong Kong
l go to market to shop everyday
No Hollywood, no
Who are those guys?
Stuff, what kind of stuff?
They´re triad members
What is it?
l don´t care who he is, what is it?
Adam Chow of Japan
So they´re from underworld
Yes! God father!
OK...
You can piss on
the street from now on
Tell others Adam Chow,
l´m your protector
Now go home and eat shit
Thanks
Underworld of Japan?
l must get your background
Excuse me, l must go
and see my wife
Your wife... is she OK?
She´s become unconscious
since she got shot
And l keep talking to her everyday
l must also look after her
You´re so nice to your wife
Thank you
Excuse me
We mustn´t lay a hand on friend´s wife
But she´s wife of another man,
why not take a peep?
You go out for a while
Karen
lt´s good if you can hear
what l´m saying
Mr. Tetsuo has allied with me
From now on, casinos business
in S. E. Asia...
will be under our control
But he wants to find Cool
He says if the three
of us work together
we´ll become sure-winners
He´s my sworn brother anyway
Since many things
happened on your wedding day...
l´ve been missing him
lt´s good if he were here
At least...
he knows l come to
bath you everyday
After bathing you,
l can even enjoy your body...
every part of your body
l can kiss you too
l can caress you too
l can even beat you, just like this!
You´re dirty, let me clean you now
lt´s worse than porn VCD
Cool, you ass-hole!
What can you do?
He deserves this today
This time he loses totally
And he can´t have expected this
He can´t have expected her
beloved woman is ravaged by me
What are you looking at?
l don´t know what you´re saying
This is private place, why intrude in?
l come to...
l come to deliver pizza
Where is the pizza?
l´m too hungry and ate it
You still want one?
Let me bake another for you
You have good skills
Don´t think Jacky Chan is
the only kung fu fighter in HK
What is it?
There´s an unexpected caller
l know you have things to do,
judging from your appearance
l leave now
Damn it!
He doesn´t seem to be bad
Everyone spots on European Cup
will make big money
You find Cool, and
we three will work together
You´d better
take good care of your wife
Meet you tomorrow at the old place
Thanks for your patronage
Brother Cool!
Cool is dead, l´m only an ordinary guy
What ordinary guy?
l´ve learnt everything in that big house
That Yeung Kwong is a real maniac
And only you endure him
l wonder if you have
kidney stones, you poor
Stay out of my affairs
You mustn´t say so
You´re my idol,
l can´t bear others scold you...
let alone others bully you
l can´t be convinced!
l´ll return to HK
and get you help!
Don´t you hear?
Stay out of my affairs
Go away!
How come your make-up wears off?
Go to make-up,
make you more attractive
Good
Gossiping about that, go on
What is the relation among you three?
l can tell you,
but you must promise...
OK!
You must stay out of this
No problem
l think this incident...
dates back to 3 years ago,
on my very last game...
l know
Karen and you were dancing
And banknotes flew in the sky, right?
You know that too?
l wonder if anyone
upload it on the internet
That night, l had a game
with Joe of Causeway Bay
Pair 6
Pass
No pairs, Brother Cool?
Brother Cool, pair J
l wonder who will be
defeated this time
Pass
Pair J
Pair 2
You think your pair J
is big enough?
Of course l know
Triple Queens
Triple Kings, Triple Aces
Say, do l know?
Why didn´t you cast
when it was pair 6?
You want to know why?
As l love to see others...
falling to hell from heavens
What´s the problem of losing a bit?
lt´s worth just to see
how you behave now
You´re fooling me?
Here´s $10 million,
let´s have a final fight
You´re on your nerves?
Whoever loses shall
leave two of his fingers
OK, no problem
l can´t help if you think
you have too many fingers
Cool
We´ve got your wife and
children into our hands
You know what cards to
serve to Brother Joe now?
Yes, l do
Serve!
No need to shuffle, serve now
Yes
So good?
l might as well...
What are you doing?
Open the card?
No, l´m too bored only
Serve now
4 Diamond
2 Heart
So soon? Me too, 2 Spade
3 now
- Pair J
- Haven´t finished yet
Four 3´s, and one 9, anymore?
Pass
Then 6, 8, 10
and 7, 9, straight flush, you have?
lf you haven´t, last card
You´re in luck
My wife has become
famous of seducing men
All my 4 children are
not my offspring
Brother Joe,
you must kill them for me
l couldn´t ask for better, thanks!
What to trap me?
You should check beforehand
None of my followers will betray me
Ass-hole!
You don´t thank me when
l spare your fingers?
l suddenly want to dance
You don´t fear it´ll arouse others?
Arouse others?
Being in this world,
we either leave a bad fame
or a good reputation
lf no one will remember
me after a hard life
lt´ll be meaningless
Tonight, l want everyone...
to remember both of us
Cool, what is it?
There was a flaw, l failed finally
Just by chance
Not by chancel
For real gamblers,
a failure will be fatal!
Don´t be like this,
you´ve forced yourself too hard
l just don´t have alternative
ln all of Asia...
the two toppest gamblers
are Tetsuo and me
Whoever wins will become
number 1 in Asia
What if you become
number 1 in Asia?
But there´re numerous competent
gamblers, you can´t defeat them all
How long will the competition last?
Once l joined this field,
l´ve determined not to return
Cool, don´t be like this
We have lots of money already,
let´s not compete with them
OK? Promise me
l don´t want you
to go gambling again
Take your hands off
l´ll solve my own affairs, OK?
Who called just then?
lan called from USA?
Yes
What is it?
Police found cocaine at her dorm
But how come your twin sister...
is totally different from her sister?
Why must she give herself up?
You mustn´t blame her,
l have the responsibility too
Never mind her,
it´s not her first time
lt´s not your first time either
But did l leave you alone?
Sorry, am l disturbing you?
Not at all, what is it?
l´ve made appointment
with Tetsuo for you
at his underground casino
on the first day of next month
Take your time, l go inside
You failed again?
Just a bit
What if we ask our men here tonight...
and have a party?
Relax
You´ll make progress tomorrow, OK?
Come on, smile
Men, see what present
l have brought you
Everyone has left when l woke up
And l didn´t know Karen
left with Yeung Kwong
Not until a month
when someone told me...
Yeung Kwong co-operated
with Tetsuo in Japan
and he decided to get married
at the end of the month
The bride...
was Karen
Didn´t you see my girlfriend?
Brother Tetsuo!
Thanks for coming...
Please!
ls everything ready?
Yes, he´s at the tree
Range cover all this garden
Ask him not to fire too soon
That they only take action
when l drink with the bride
Got it?
Yes!
l´ll see who´s faster,
your poker card or my bullet
Excuse me, l must go out for a while
Where to?
l want to talk to you
Go out, all of you
What is it?
l find that it´s too hurried like this
Everyone says a bride runs up against
emotional impact before the ceremony
So it´s real
l´m serious
Haven´t we registered already?
But we haven´t finished
the ceremony yet
l´m disappointed in Cool
But that doesn´t mean
l want to marry you at once
lt´s unfair to both of us
Silly girl, don´t behave like a child
l want to get disengagement with you!
Come on
All my friends in HK, Taiwan, Japan...
and your parents
and also your brothers,
sisters are outside
Don´t tell me you
won´t get married now
Shouldn´t one give room to his lover?
Right
One should indeed
give room to his lover
l tell you
l never love you
lt´s nothing bad to sleep with you
The reason l get married with you...
is to make that foolish Cool show up!
You´d better finish this scene for me
Or else your family
can never leave Japan!
Karen!
Cool, take it easy
Take it easy
None of your business!
Watch out!
Karen!
You´re sly!
Leave me alone...
Go away!
- Give Karen to me!
- Go away!
She´s already been my wife,
none of your affairs now!
Get out of here at once!
Leave me alone!
Take your hands off!
Cool...
Yeung Kwong is now my partner
l hope you behave sensibly
and respect yourself
and everyone here!
Doctor proved that
the bullet hit her spine
And she may be
a vegetable in future
Why don´t you take her away?
They are already wedded couple
They´re married by law terms
Furthermore, Japanese police
have warned me
They ask me not to disturb them
So l can´t take her away
Then you go and
peep at her everyday?
You´re really a love hung!
That Yeung Kwong is an ass-hole!
He means to torture you with Karen
he´s torturing you!
This is a pay back to me
Mr. Cool
Mr. Tetsuo is waiting outside
Cool, l´ve been looking for you
l know
l always want to meet you
after the wedding, how are you?
Thank you
l want to find out
who between us is better
l still want to find it out
You needn´t prove, you´re
Asian number 1 already
Those games were just a nuisance
lt´s not real games at all
But l´ve retired already
Can you just give it
a second thought?
l´ll consent to whatever
conditions you ask for
l´ll not gamble anymore
You mean you´re tough
at that decision?
You´re sly,
you want to gamble?
So gamble with me
You? You´re not up to me!
Just come to HK for a try
And l´ll surely cut off
your little dick as snack
l´ll turn it into sush!
You´re afraid?
Cool
How is it?
lf you change your mind,
come to see me
l won´t see you off
Cheers!
Welcome
You won´t understand
l come to see... your boss
Don´t stir up trouble
Don´t think you´re taller than
you can bully me, ass-hole!
Dare stir up trouble?
Who are you?
Stop nagging me
Anyone speaks Cantonese?
You´re from HK?
Hung Hing member?
You speak Cantonese?
lf l had known, l wouldn´t
have kicked you so hard
OK, ask your boss
Tetsuo to see me
l come to ruin the place
What did he say?
To ruin the place
Bastard, you´re too daring!
Why did you beat him?
He´s my friend!
Only he speaks Chinese!
l don´t beat insider
Why you beat me?
Why beat him?
He beats you, so l beat him,
why you beat me?
Go to hell!
Son-of-a-bitch!
lt´s you again
l´ve told you at Cool´s shop
that l must find you
Chinese people have a saying
lgnorance opts for perfect
Don´t say these old-fashioned
Men in the underworld
nowadays are very clever
We´re so clever as to
caress buddies´ wives!
l won´t blame you
for the sake of Cool
Though you don´t,
l must get fussy with you
Anyway, l´m King Of Gambling
of Aberdeen this year
And you look through me?
This makes me lose face
l must have a game with you today
Want to have a game with me?
OK, if you can defeat her
With bigger busts,
she can be an AV girl
She´s number 1
of dice player in Japan
Well, l´m the most popular singer in HK
Stop bullshit, can we start now?
With tattoo?
l have it too