"Macau"
"Secretary of Judiciary
of the coloane jail"
Who is he?
He is Master Wong, he is a swindler.
He is very popular here.
He is greater than the Great Four.
His tips on horse races are always sharp.
I don't believe it!
My nickname is the Judge of the Casino.
No one dares to cheat in front of me.
- Give me an autograph.
- Enough, we'll continue tomorrow.
They said that you are a famous swindler.
It is a rumor, that's all.
You are really cocky!
Let me play a hand with you.
If you lose,
I get to give you ten punches a day.
And, for a whole year.
If I lose, you get to smoke free
for a whole year.
Very risky! Please don't!
What did you say?
What are the rules?
If you can find the Ace, you win.
Which one is Ace?
It's gambling anyway, let's bet more.
If I lose,
you get to hit me with a stick...
hundred times a day
for the whole next year.
If you lose, just let me hit you once
with the stick.
- OK.
- We have a deal!
This one... No.
This one... No!
This one must be Ace.
Very good...
Give me the stick.
Awesome! Master Wong is great!
Forget it!
Do you think I dare to hit you?
Just give me a smoke, OK?
OK... Help yourself.
Thanks!
Master Wong, you are awesome...
The Masked-man calling Leung Fon...
Leung Fon is here, over.
What is the situation now in school?
Very quiet.
We're informed that the kidnappers...
will come to kidnap
the Billionaire Ho's daughter.
You have to protect her by all means.
Sir, don't worry!
Miss Ho will be safe under my protection.
There are so many kinds of people.
Someone thinks that
because her family is rich...
then she can be proud to do
whatever she wants.
I hope she would be
dumped acid on her face.
Do you see that bitch with glasses
at the front row?
She always challenges me!
Take her to the bathroom
and teach her a lesson.
I am here to protect you only.
Please take care of your own problem.
I am not your hitman.
If anything happens to me,
are you going to be responsible?
If I were your dad,
I would have fed you shit.
Good!
Where is she?
Leung Fon, what are you doing?
We are trying to
get to know each other better.
Is this the proper way?
We are studying kung fu.
It hurts...
Why don't you quit school
and go start a career in Japan.
I will...
Out.
"I won't harrass
the female classmates anymore."
Sir, is something happen?
Emergency,
go up to the roof in one minute.
Remember, in one minute!
Sir, is something wrong?
Hurry down to the ground floor and check
if there're any ants on the floor.
Yes Sir.
Sir, there is no ant on the floor.
Go up to the roof and check
if there are any grasshoppers.
Yes Sir.
Sir, there are
lots of grasshoppers on the roof.
Dismiss.
Gentlemen.
Can you tell me how you know that
I am an undercover?
Look, a police acting as a student
to protect rich man's daughter.
Reporters again.
I have to improve my make-up skill.
Let's go.
What?
Let her go.
What the hell? Why are you alright?
I was almost exhausted. But luckily...
I used Yes!
I've become very energetic. Very good.
Let her go.
Hurry...
Don't move.
Go...
Sir, do you want some herbal oil?
It's OK, I have bandaid.
That's better.
Gas?
The whole room is loaded with gas.
I dare you to shoot.
If I shoot,
the gun will generate sparks
which will start an explosion.
The whole room will explode.
What should I do?
I am scared to run the 4 x 100 relay.
Because I don't like to finish last.
Do you know
what our opponents scare the most?
What?
It's you! Your armpit stinks.
They are afraid to get close to you.
Luckily I carry around with me a box
of "Silencer" lemon tea.
Sir, I have successfully stopped Miss Ho
from being kidnapped.
Please don't send me to do this kind of
low-class undercover case again.
I have acted as lawyer, doctor, nurse...
Druggy, gangster, student...
Jacky Chan, Andy Lau, Leon Lai...
Even that scary old lady
Elizabeth Taylor.
I don't want to do
this kind of stupid case again.
We will discuss it
in my office tomorrow morning.
Sir, I have decided
not to take on easy jobs.
Look at me, I am gifted.
I should be carrying out
some very big case.
Just tell me everything
you don't like about me.
You want my hair to go straight,
and I'll follow your order.
But... Sir...
Sir, how come you don't seem happy?
You bastard have got some guts.
I will soon put down my gun
and kick his ass.
Wait for it.
My nickname is Masked-man.
Don't talk shit about me again.
Sir, if you don't let me
do something more challenging.
I am going to quit.
We will talk again
after you put away your things first.
Sir, no matter what,
you have to let me handle this big case.
I will get it done.
Sir, talk to me.
Crazy!
I know you are the Masked-man.
You are fooling me.
Sir, I have been a cop for seven years.
I am honest and smart.
I only have one girlfriend
for all these years.
I've never slept with a hooker before.
The only time I went to a massage place
because I was drunk.
I saw brother Kai Ying!
I am a super, good, and nice police.
Damn, tell me earlier that
you're not my boss.
You've dragged me to deep shit.
You guessed it right,
but you don't trust yourself.
How can you go against
the Swindler Ferrari?
Ferrari?
Yes, this cheater makes money
faster than Soros.
This cheater lies better than Clinton.
He is the Handsome Dragon Ferrari.
Recently he helps the foreigners
to crush the stock market.
He has a newspaper which always
harms Hong Kong's reputation.
He steals money from the stock market.
And sells pirate VCD too.
The worst thing is that...
he gets all the beautiful girls.
And leave the ugly ones for us.
He should be executed for this.
Sir, don't worry,
I will go catch him for you.
OK! You moved me. I will send you.
If you are successful,
you will be promoted.
Thank you, Sir.
Guess what I've bought for you?
Kentucky fried chicken!
I haven't seen you for two weeks.
Don't you try to trick me,
take off your mask.
What are you talking about?
- What are you doing? It hurts.
- I am hungry, anything to eat?
Yes...
Sorry, I thought you were my boss.
I have been in love with you
for seven years,
and you can't recognize me!
You're not get used to it, that's all.
Don't get mad! What's wrong?
My brother-in-law will celebrate
his birthday. You've to go with me.
I don't know
your brother-in-law that well.
You should at least go meet my sister.
We will see!
I have accepted a very important case.
What case?
Who is she?
I don't know! May be my boss.
See you tomorrow morning at 9
at the beach.
God is fair to me.
I was born to be an undercover.
With my handsome look and wisdom.
I finally get to go against
tough opponent like Ferrari.
In this beautiful morning.
I came to this beautiful beach.
Asshole... Leave.
Since the person I am supposed to meet
hasn't showed up yet.
So, I've decided to try water cycling.
This girl is so cute.
When I saw her,
I have a very fresh feeling.
It's like...
Sir, don't you know
how to use this machine?
Of course! You stupid!
It's my fault!
Please call an ambulance for me.
You are a trouble to me!
Hello.
Can I have your number?
Go.
Good bye.
"Fuck you."
You are smart.
Giving me your name is same as a curse.
What is your name?
My name is First Love.
First Love?
The name First Love is very sweet.
She reminds me of the feelings I had
when I was still a teenager.
Every man dreams about this... First love!
Fat boy! Want me to kill you
and barbecue with your body fat?
Brother Lon, someone is picking on me.
Are you trying to scare me?
You must be Leung!
Brother Lon? Are you the person
I am supposed to meet?
So you must be Handsome Dragon
Ferrari's assistant, Brother Lon.
You are very smart, fat boy.
My boss is over there.
Brother Ferrari.
You seem to be a useful person.
I will give you a good assignment.
I'll try all my best.
Go play with my son.
If you lose, you will have to
face cruel punishment.
Please tell me
what punishment I'll receive.
No! Someone will get killed.
Let's go!
Very lucky! Thank you, Brother Lon.
No problem.
My boss wants you
to beat up that fat boy.
He didn't do anything to me.
It's hard for me to hit him.
Are you going to do it?
Of course.
OK.
You hit my boss?
Forget it... Just give him a beating
for one or two hours.
Ferrari, why does he want to hurt you?
Ever since I fought for the woman
in the NT. for their legal rights,
many people started to hate me.
People try to assassinate me.
Luckily you have many good bodyguards.
Now I don't have enough money,
I can't hire any more bodyguard.
You have no money, but I have!
Is five million enough for you?
How can I use your money?
Don't worry about it.
Come to my office tomorrow
and pick up the check.
He is Ferrari, isn't he?
Yes! So we have to
finish this scene together.
Boss, what should we do with him?
Sorry!
You must be Leung!
Yes, Ferrari.
Follow me from now on.
Fat Pig will tell you what to do.
Thanks, Ferrari.
You get the night shift tonight.
This must be money saving gangsters.
Why do they turn off all lights so early!
Hope you all fall and die.
Miss First Love.
Shut up.
You are a nice girl,
you shouldn't come to
this kind of scary place.
I will leave after I download
the criminal records of Ferrari.
So many people hate him.
He tricked all my dad's money.
My whole family was destroyed by him.
You better shut up and stand aside.
Or I will kill you too.
Don't worry, take your time,
I will watch out for you.
Who is there?
I can't stay and watch you die,
I am a righteous gentleman.
Let me be your shield.
Don't move... I've got her.
I am going to catch you.
I've got her.
Take me as your hostage.
Don't move! Or I am going to kill him.
- No... Don't come after me.
- Don't move!
It's very dangerous, I am going to die.
Don't come after me.
Look...
Blood!
Are you scared?
A little bit...
I am not scared of that little blood.
Have you finished looking at my body?
Almost.
What can I help you?
Wipe off the blood for me.
I will help you to my room
and get some rest, OK?
After I going to your room with you,
you will say...
Can I sleep with you for a while, right?
If you need any help, just tell me.
I am going to your room
and get some rest.
If you dare to come in,
I will put out both of your eyes.
You are insane!
You have so many toilets in your room.
Even a gentleman like me
can't hold myself down.
Why do you come in the midnight?
I called you for a whole week
and you never answered my calls.
I am working right now. Don't mind me.
Guess what have I brought you?
Pizza Hut only sells pizza.
You are so stupid.
You said that women
don't have to be smart.
I like it...
Good night! Go home.
- What's the rush?
- Go home.
Let me sit for a while.
If you don't want to go home,
let's make love then?
No...
You still remember that tomorrow is
my brother-in-law's birthday...
and we have to go to Macau, right?
OK! I will go to Macau with you tomorrow.
Let's not have bored games in future.
Let's try S & M from now on...
Like making love with animals, OK?
- OK.
- Let's go buy the boat tickets now.
Let's go.
Wait... I will play with you later...
Be careful.
- Sister.
- Pizza.
He is my boyfriend, Leung Fon.
He looks smart.
Thanks! Come on, sit.
Uncle, uncle Yee, Aunt Seven.
This Pizza's boyfriend.
His hair is ugly, he is stupid as well...
He is poor, he is not civilized...
He is weak in bed.
But he is nice, right?
I am very straight forward,
come on... Let's play.
Don't get mad. You are a nice fellow.
I know.
Suddenly, I felt danger.
I felt a very strong force
rushing in from the door.
The force tells me that...
a very important person is coming in.
Awesome...
La-di-da.
Hubby.
- Honey.
- Hubby.
No.
I told you,
when my bodyguards
are standing next to me,
no one is allowed to get close to me.
Your memory is very bad.
Sorry, honey.
Yeah... Congratulation...
Sorry! Today is not my birthday.
Today is my father's death day.
My wife made a mistake. So everyone
doesn't have to be this happy.
But you don't have to be sad too.
My dad was an asshole when he was alive.
He robbed, killed and raped.
His death is good to the society.
That's good.
But... My dad loved me a lot.
He robbed the bank,
because he wanted to buy me a toy car.
He killed because that person said
I was not handsome.
He raped because I told him
I wanted a sister.
My dad was a great father.
Your brother-in-law is something.
They are all fooled by him.
Of course, he is a sw...
What? What is he?
He is the supervisor
of the Millennium Celebration.
I really miss you! Come on,
give me a kiss.
You improved a lot. Your kiss
made his tongue tie a knot.
Of course, you punk!
- Where is my best friend?
- Who?
The one who will protect me
until his death, Brother Five.
Brother Five? Did he come?
Hey,
you have lots of white hair recently.
Help...
Go help her!
Why didn't you go?
Stop...
"Stop"
He is Brother Five? How come he won't
stop when you tell him to?
Of course! He is brother Deaf.
He is deaf and he can't hear anything.
Good friend...
"How's your wife?"
I told you not to
talk about my wife again. No more.
The truth is, couple of days ago,
I went to the hospital
because of cystitis.
I've waited for a long time
but my wife didn't show up.
I only saw reporters.
They started to talk about my past,
I can't believe that my wife's
acting skill is better than mine.
Like the old saying
"The wife is living happily,"
"and the husband is working poorly."
Today, my body is very weak
and my wife is leaving me.
Now everybody say my son is handsome.
I'm suspecting that he is not my own son.
I am very poor!
Is your brother-in-law armless?
No!
How come the two persons next to him
are like they are connected to him?
And, it is very hot right now,
but he is wearing cheetah skin
on his neck.
Why does he dress so loudly?
I won! It's a big slam!
No big deal, 113 folds.
Are your kidding?
What is your brother-in-law?
You know that I hate swindler.
Right! I am a swindler.
9 out of 10 persons here are swindlers.
You must be Pizza's boyfriend?
Right! I am her man.
Your name is?
Fon! And yours?
Master Wong.
You must be that
famous Jinx in the casino.
You will cheat on anyone,
the best swindler alive, Master Wong.
Thank you! It's a flattering to me,
that's all.
You need people
to get the domino for you.
Who do you think you are, a king?
Master Wong is still
serving his sentence in jail.
Today, he is the boss,
he applied for two hours leave.
After dessert,
we will have to take him back.
But, no one can contact him.
So, he is a prisoner.
Fon...
I am talking, you shut up.
Don't worry! Since we are happy today.
Let's play cards.
I don't like to gamble.
Just for fun.
I will be the banker,
you get to pick the cards first.
If you win I will give you $100,000.
If you lose,
you have to kiss my woman.
OK! Let me see how good you really are.
Are you done?
Three Aces in front,
I win 3 points first.
Straight heart flush in the middle,
I win 10 more points.
Straight spade flush at the end.
I will 18 points.
Three 8s.
Straight flush in the middle
and on the last row.
I'm the winner!
No! You win with three Aces in front.
You win 3 points.
You beat me with an ace on the last row.
Which you'll win 5 more points.
For the middle row, we break even.
Spade beats heart.
No, the rules of this game
don't state that.
I am the dealer, so I win.
The middle row counts double.
So I have 10 points.
The final is 10 to 8.
I win you by 2 points.
Fine! I will kiss your women then.
Get my women.
- Hi!
- Honey.
Kiss me.
Brother Leung, go ahead.
Can I do something else?
Look at them, two of them are pregnant.
The one in the middle is like
she is lacking of oxygen.
Why don't we play again?
OK!
Get down on your knees
and lick my shoes clean.
Brother-in-law, please!
Young man, you are cocky!
It's better for me to teach you a lesson
than being tricked by outsiders.
I will lick it.
It sucks!
So?
If you can't do it, let's forget it.
It's sweet?
Silly! The spider web is marshmallow.
The little dots are candies. The shit...
That's really shit!
Asshole! You tricked me too?
Don't get mad!
They are playing with you, that's all.
Playing with me?
Don't let me see you in Hong Kong.
Don't come to Macau and look for me.
Wipe it off for me.
You are pushing that
rest of them into my mouth!
You can't beat my brother-in-law.
He wanted you to lick his shoe this time.
I don't know what he will want you
to lick next time.
Let me tell you,
he is going to pay for this.
Does my mouth still stink?
Let me tell you, in my whole life,
I hate swindler the most.
My brother-in-law is the best swindler!
Best? He is just a small potato!
If I can arrest Ferrari,
I will at least be promoted by two ranks.
Ferrari? My sister said that he is great.
How can you beat him?
Why can't I beat him?
I am a cop, I can do it.
You don't have to get so excited.
I am worried about you, that's all.
Why don't we do something together?
No.
You promised to do it with me
after we come back from Macau.
Use this again?
If I wear that,
I will lose all the feelings.
Yes. But are you going to
go buy it or not?
It's very late.
You are a man, you can do it.
I will try.
Call the adult channel,
and order that movie...
The... Bra.
The one which a black guy starring in it.
What the hell?
All the stores are closed already.
In the midnight, where can I buy condom?
Transparent film will do.
Hello! I have told her
the things between us.
What did you say?
Asshole!
You are wrong.
You are at me for telling her
the adultery between us?
I am mad at you for telling her
before we have sex.
You will have a chance.
But... You have to help me
go against Ferrari.
I want to! But I don't have any idea.
I do. If you can stand a little pain.
Can you give me some happiness first?
Some other day.
Give me a kiss first, OK?
Can you let me kick your dick?
You can clean it up.
Asshole.
Brother Sing, it's deal, OK?
I am counting on you.
Don't go back tonight.
We will go play golf tomorrow.
OK.
Excuse me! Take Mr. Lee to rest.
Help yourself...
This way please.
Boss,
I finally captured the Spider Woman.
Didn't she kidnap you?
At first, yes!
But... She is a very stupid thief!
I acted like I was dead
and she believed me.
When she was not paying attention to me,
I pulled her hair.
And hit her chest hardly.
I learned monkey fist when I was a kid.
Trying to steal my computer files?
All you have to do is ask me.
Fat Pig, take her to my room.
Let me go...
Sir, I am Leung.
I am in Ferrari's house.
I am stealing his computer file.
Really?
I sacrificed a lot.
Call all the available units,
soldiers and whatever to come here.
If you come late,
my dream lover will get raped.
If that happens, I will be very sad.
I will become very Ionely.
OK! I will not put on my mask then.
OK.
First Love...
Don't come any closer.
Fat ass!
How dare you touch my First Love.
I have to kill you asshole!
Who hit me?
Who are you?
- It hurts?
- Who is she?
She is my wife! Who do you think she is?
First love?
Everybody treasures first love.
How would your First Love be in my bed?
Asshole!
Sorry!
Sorry? Go to hell.
First love...
It is very cold in this house.
Are you my boss?
I told you I don't have time
to put on my mask.
I can find First Love.
I can't find my first love too!
This is life. Where is the evidence?
Do you have any warrant?
Where is my First Love?
What the hell are you talking about?
Who are you?
Police! Hong Kong police, Leung.
I am an undercover
who is sent to arrest this fat boy.
I want to see your superior.
I am. But I won't be responsible
for his mistake.
You don't know me? I am Mr. Lee.
I want to complain that
he abused violence.
He injured my eye.
And he illegally broke us apart...
when we were having sex.
What are you looking for?
I don't know him.
You don't know me?
I played with your fat son.
Four of them picked on me.
My son is not a fat boy.
What's going on, honey?
Take it easy! I can handle it.
Are you playing me?
Your wife is a Chinese.
We have a marriage certificate.
Sir, he is lying, I am innocent!
What kind of disk is this?
It contains nothing but computer virus.
It erased everything
we saved in the central computer.
The whole system became
a giant video game station.
Sir, I made a mistake.
That fat ass Ferrari tricked me.
We can't catch Ferrari now,
we can't even catch a fool.
We are on vacation from now on.
Yes! We have been working real hard
this couple of years.
Let's take a rest, OK?
Do you know what you should do?
I am the king of undercover cops.
Now I'm the king of scapegoats.
It's the real me! I didn't put on a mask.
Put down your ID
and your gun and take a vacation.
Get in the car.
Tell me, where did you go last night?
Do you know
I was very worried about you?
Because of you, I lost my job too.
Don't cry, what happened?
You don't understand me too.
Don't hold me so tight.
I might lose control.
Do you like me?
Isn't this a little too straight forward?
- You pick on me.
- No.
You think I am a hooker?
No!
I know you won't. Wait for me.
My God, you suddenly give me
two girls with huge breasts.
I really can't take it.
I look very strong,
but I go to the bathroom
7-8 times a night.
I will give you one minute.
When I come out, I don't want you
to be wearing anything.
I've got the picture.
Group C, start interrupting the signal
to the TV station.
Forget about that asshole.
Let's play mahjong.
I won!
What a happiness!
Your boyfriend is strip dancing on TV.
No way?
It's him!
He's got a great body.
Let me see his ass.
What? Get to work?
Nice body!
That asshole does look like me.
You told me to take off my clothes,
but why are you still wearing yours?
Because...
Long Hair, Ken,
we have been friends for so long.
Tell me the truth.
After I put on this hat and glasses,
can people still recognize me?
Long Hair.
No...
Ken.
Will it be better
if I put some mustache on?
OK! Even Pizza
won't recognize you, right?
Yes!
I decided to commit suicide.
I don't dare to see Pizza again.
But before I die, I have decided...
I am going to kill you both!
Don't mind me, I am useless.
Are you a man?
I am a man.
Everybody in Hong Kong knows that
But, I am a shithead.
You are going to give up like this?
If you give up,
you will be a fool forever!
You have to defeat
Ferrari and First Love.
Then you will become a true man again.
I can't beat them.
Only one person can help you.
Who?
My brother-in-law, Master Wong.
Don't worry about it,
everybody will lose once or twice.
When my life is heading downhill.
It's sweet that Pizza has forgiven me.
She even tells me to seek revenge.
So I've decided to listen to her
and go to Macau.
And go look for her brother-in-law.
What? You want me to teach him?
OK, tell him to come look for me.
In tomorrow's horse race,
bet on "Super" on the 2nd race?
Let me think. Can you go out first?
Yes!
Pinky, cancel the meeting at 2:30 today.