We lost 300 gold pieces,
thanks to your meddling.
We won't go back empty-handed.
If your hands are so empty,
will you hold this?
Is it true they hired you
for only twenty gold pieces?
Yes.
The sword we stole was a treasure
given to them by the Shogun.
And they'll only pay twenty
pieces to get it back?
Ridiculous!
They're a poor, small clan.
Trying to swindle 300 pieces
for a sword is asking too much.
Shut up! Damn you!
Looks like a nasty
storm's brewing...
Can't waste my time here!
Oh, I'm sorry for you.
That was one hell of a storm!
No shit! My roof got blown off
and scared my wife so bad...
...that she went into labor.
It was really something.
That's your seventh kid, right?
Nope, the ninth.
Holy! You must
really love your wife!
Isn't that Sakichi's daughter
from Shimoda Village?
What's with her?
What's wrong?!
All... dead...
Everybody's dead.
Dead?!
Plague... Plague did it...
MY GOD!
This area's off limits!
No one goes through!
This highway's closed
until the epidemic is over.
Epidemic?!
The hell with that!
What is it?
Sir, my scout saw a
strange group of men...
...ride toward Shimoda
Village late last night.
It might have something
to do with this epidemic...
...so I came to tell you,
Chamberlain.
Meaning what?
That they spread a plague...
...as they passed
through the village?
Ridiculous!
Why would they do that?
Something's fishy.
Let it alone.
On second thought, we can't.
This is the order to all
of you in the Koga ninja team.
Go to Shimoda Village and
find what really happened.
Sir!
One more thing. If any of
your people get infected...
Understood, sir.
The first group will follow the
Shirakawa River from the north.
The second will cross
Taro Pass from the west.
You'll reach Shimoda Village
in about an hour. Understand?
Hikoza saw them. There were
only eight. No match for us.
Our real enemy is
this epidemic disease.
True.
Kagero...
You intend to leave
me behind, Hanza?
You have your
own duties, don't you?
Poison tasting is very
important. Don't forget that.
While our lord is away from his
domain, the work isn't necessary.
Until he returns...
I am one of the Koga ninja!
I cannot take you.
You all could be killed out there.
How can I...
...just sit and wait here alone?!
Kagero's gotten
even more beautiful.
All the more
reason to pity her.
It's her destiny.
She must hate it.
Enough.
Where are Hikoza and the others?
They were right behind us.
I'll have a look.
Hey! What are you doing?
What the?!
There!
Shit!
Kagero, get back and
tell the chamberlain!
Go now!
Just be quiet and you'll
live a little longer.
Either way's fine by me. A dead
girl might be an interesting lay.
That's better.
I'm busy here.
Get lost!
Didn't you hear me?
The highway's out and I had to
make a detour, but now I'm lost.
Can you tell me
how to get to Kakio?
Not very friendly...
I think I told you to get lost!
Forget it. Once I get
rid of this meddler...
...I'll take my time killing you.
What's wrong? Sorry you
didn't run when I told you to?
No, just thinking...
About your body.
Your body
can't be rock hard everywhere!
Move it!
Tessai!
You are indeed a sorry sight.
But no need to pursue him so.
I'll kill him!
No, you shan't.
Don't forget our mission.
Consider my word
as Lord Gemma's order.
Understood?
Shall we go?
Who was that freak?
Forget it. I don't want
to see him again, anyway.
I'm grateful to you.
I am Kagero of the Koga ninja.
Jubei. Kibagami Jubei.
Are you all right?
I don't need your concern!
The town of Kakio is in the west.
Our paths part here.
Who is it?
Kagero of the Koga, sir.
What's wrong?
Twenty ninja led by Hanza
attempted to infiltrate...
...Shimoda Village a little
while ago. They were wiped out.
Really? All of them?
Who killed them?
A very formidable opponent.
Beyond that, I cannot say.
Useless, all of them.
And you're the only survivor?
Until we learn who he is
and what he's up to...
...we can't risk sending our
men to that plague village.
The first task at hand is
to go back and find that out.
We'll figure out what
to do later. Now go...
Oh, hi...
I know the way now, so...
No, you're going the wrong way.
The river to hell...
...is THIS way!
Ow... Okay, it's out of your
system. Are we even now?
Not yet. I still owe you.
That's just excessive.
If we keep this up,
one of us is going to die.
"One of us?"
There's no reason we
should kill each other.
If you're not going
to end this... I will!
Like hell!
Strange skill you have.
But it can't hurt my body.
Seems that way.
What's wrong, monster?
Your skin's starting to crumble!
Die!
Splendid! Your sword flew
swift as the wind itself...
...and slashed your enemy
like a cyclone's touch.
He was no match for you.
Why don't you join me?
Your skills will be of great help
for me to fight the likes of him.
You're joking. Who'd want to
fight a monster like him again?
You'll have to.
They won't leave you alone.
You've just killed one
of the Eight Devils of Kimon.
You didn't beat him
by yourself, though.
That Koga ninja woman...
Interesting technique she uses.
Lord Gemma. Everything
is proceeding as planned.
It arrives from the Shogun of
the Dark by six tomorrow evening.
Very well.
Write to him in return.
"We return in three days.
There's nothing to worry about."
At once.
Isn't Tessai back yet?
Benisato went to look for him.
We're all alone.
Yurimaru...
I've always loved you.
Don't push your luck, Zakuro.
You're of no interest to me.
Now go and stand watch.
So, it's true.
May your dreams be pleasant
ones in Gemma's arms.
However, Yurimaru, Gemma makes
love to both men and women.
Do you know
he makes love to Benisato?
Apparently not.
Where are you headed?
No place in particular. You?
I'm looking for somebody,
and you look exactly like him, so...
Strangers can look alike.
I'm Kibagami Jubei, a wanderer...
It was most
certainly your face.
Tessai was able to make
an impression of it.
Just leave me the hell alone!
A cast-off skin.
She shed it
like a snake and escaped.
A gang of freaks,
one and all.
You've no obligation. I just
didn't want you to die yet.
Who are these
Eight Devils of Kimon?
A group of ninja who
work for the Shogun of the Dark.
You know of the
Shogun of the Dark?
He wants to rebuild the House of
Toyotomi, the ex-ruler of Japan.
He has 16 lords behind him and
is trying to expand his influence.
The most dangerous enemy
of the Tokugawa Shogunate.
His power is supported in the
shadows by the Eight Devils.
What are they up to
here in Mochizuki?
That's what I came here to
find out. It's a tough job.
Why don't you work for me,
for 100 gold pieces?
A Tokugawa spy wants
to hire a ninja?
I'm afraid I have no choice.
It's an emergency.
Only I managed to make
it here to Mochizuki.
The Eight Devils killed everyone
else in my party on our way here.
I need your help by all means!
You'll never get away from them.
You'll have to fight
them sooner or later.
Join me. You can kill two
birds with one stone, right?
I don't think so. Now why
don't you just leave me alone?
I see. Too bad.
Such a pity...
You'll lose your precious life.
You're stubborn.
No, what I speak of is literally
of life or death importance to you.
You see, the point of that
throwing star was poisoned.
It won't kill you instantly,
but in a day and a night...
...when it starts to work,
nothing can stop it.
Unless you get the antidote.
And only I know what it is.
Work for me and I'll tell you
the antidote along with the...
...hundred gold pieces
when the job is done.
You're bluffing.
I speak the truth.
Tell me now.
What's the antidote?
Not until you work for me.
Kill me and you've killed yourself!
Now you'll need the
antidote for yourself.
Poor boy...
You've so much to learn.
That isn't the one that hit you.
I threw THAT one away.
Shit!
Kibagami Jubei...
You've lost... amateur!
My name is Dakuan.
How do you do?
So, Benisato...
This man, Kibagami Jubei, is a
remnant of the Shogunate's spies?
Possibly.
Why didn't you kill him?
Someone interfered.
No excuses!
If he's a government spy,
he'll show up here soon.
Be sure to kill him this time!
I don't need your
advice to do that.
Yurimaru... I'll tell Gemma
about this in bed. Do you mind?
Not at all.
Jubei...
There's something
I've been wondering.
Are you, by any chance,
the ninja who killed...
...the chief retainers of the
Yamashiro clan five years ago?
He was supposedly a
master swordsman, like you.
The retainers who were killed
had gorged themselves with gold...
...they secretly dug
out of a hidden mine.
The ninja must have killed
them by order of the lord...
...who wanted to report to
the government about the mine.
Because if the government found
the hidden gold mine first...
...the lord would have
lost his fief.
But does that ninja know that
after the retainers were killed...
...the government received
no report about the mine?
Why? If a government spy
like you knows all that...
...then why don't
you do something?
No... Even the government can't
move without definite evidence.
Our spies tried many times
to infiltrate the clan...
...to find evidence,
but none returned alive.
The Shogun of the Dark...
He stopped them by
using the Kimon ninja.
Why is the Shogun of the Dark
helping the Yamashiro clan?
Simple. He wants the
gold mine for himself.
Do you know how he found the
gold mine before the government?
Because somebody
gave him the information.
Somebody who was the leader of
the ninja of the Yamashiro clan.
Himuro... Gemma?!
Precisely.
I doubt that. He isn't
in this world anymore.
No, he's still very much alive.
And you'll see him soon.
Himuro Gemma is the boss
of the Kimon monsters.
What?!
Shh! Not so loud!
You can't trick me
the same way again!
Don't be hasty.
You'll soon know the truth.
But you must admit that you
and he share a strange fate.
Stop!
You'd kill your own friend?!
- The lord orders it!
- As did our leader!
It's a trick! Now that we
know the traitors' secret...
...they want to get rid of us
by making us kill each other.
This is a trap for all of us.
Shinkuro, believe me!
Jubei... Forgive me.
Shinkuro!
His word...
...is law!
I avenged Shinkuro and others myself.
Gemma can't be alive.
We're getting close. This place
is thick with ghosts and blood.
Beyond lies hell itself.
Heaven must have sent
this mist to help us.
Hey!
Double damned mist!
How could he have
dodged Shijima's claw?
Who are you?
I heard a voice
chanting the sutra.
I was praying for
the dead villagers.
Don't you know an epidemic
is plaguing this village?
Poor soul! You'll never
leave this village alive.
Here now, let us go to
the land of Buddha together.
Have you seen a
traveling monk here?
He'll meet Buddha soon enough.
I'll send him there.
Such a benevolent nun...
Shit!
Another cast-off skin!
Gone...
He uses a strange technique...
As do you.
Very strange indeed!
Answer me. Are there any
others with you besides the monk?
Of course.
And not just ten or twenty.
You can send a snake for each
and it won't be enough.
Liar!
All right!
I'll tell you the truth.
There's two. One's the
traveling monk. The other...
...is right behind you.
Lose the snakes.
Down to the last one!
You'll be dead soon.
Get rid of them!
Now it's your turn to answer.
What are you doing
in this village? Talk!
Twice failed. Unforgivable.
I cast another line onto your
neck, but you didn't notice.
In the end,
just a foolish amateur.
Idiot! There's still time
to suck the poison out!
Poison doesn't work on me.
My body's immune to it.
I think I've cleared
my debt to you.
Yes. You saved me.
Your name's Kagero, right?
What are you going to do now?
That's none of your concern.
If it isn't, then what
the hell am I doing here?!
I have to discover their plan.
By yourself? Impossible!
They're too strong.
Think this over.
Stay out of my way.
I've no reason to
take orders from you.
Hold a moment,
ninja woman of Koga.
My name is Dakuan.
Why don't you join me?
This man is my
trustworthy assistant.
I wasn't planning on
helping a government spy.
Oh, quit complaining!
What do you say, woman?
Our aims may differ, but we
three share a common enemy.
And three is mightier than one.
And I happen to have some
information you don't know.
Such as who is giving
them their orders.
I'll tell you on the way.
I need no friends.
But I may need
your information.
Very well.
My, she's a lovely,
sexy little thing, isn't she!
What's running through
that twisted skull of yours?
Well now, that ninja girl
could prove very useful.
She has a technique to poison
the man she sleeps with.
The big guy you killed
had been poisoned by her.
Anyone who makes
love to her dies.
A perfect woman for
this hellish world.
Your skill is as
marvelous as ever.
No... He was able to kill
a mighty ninja like Tessai.
Don't be off guard.
It's possible he got away.
The four of you
will check it out.
You're a cautious one,
Yurimaru.
We have an important mission.
We take every precaution.
I know, I know. Don't worry.
Then go.
Yurimaru, Benisato's death...
How fortunate for you!
Only things he
killed were the fish.
Good. Otherwise we
wouldn't get our chance.
It's getting quite
interesting, isn't it?
How is it?
Just as we thought?
They poisoned the wells
and killed the villagers.
And then blamed it
on an epidemic disease.
A trick to keep
the villagers away.
They're planning something...
very extraordinary.
I'd like to
know what it is.
That's fine, just don't get
yourself involved too deeply.
It could prove fatal.
I see. Guide the others.
Run for it!
We can't outrun them.
Kagero...
So, the pollen is mixed
with a sleeping potion.
But how long will
it hold them back?
Why, you!
Girl!
You have to hold them off
till Jubei kills him!
Do whatever it takes!
Call off your wasps!
I'm afraid you
must beat me first.
You don't know
anything, do you?
Do you think I ran
in here to escape you?
No, I don't.
I have lots of questions for
you, but no time to ask them.
No, just one thing.
Tell me, is Himuro Gemma alive?
So what if he is?
Because I sent him to hell before.
Is that so?
Then I'll have to be careful.
Unlike Gemma, I don't have the
technique to reincarnate myself.
Reincarnation?
Fool!
You've damaged the hive!
The second you come up for air
is the second you die!
He's mine!
Keep your hands off him!
What about
the ninja girl and the monk?
My wasps should
finish them off soon.
How far is he trying to run?
What a poor loser!
Do you think he's fallen
victim to the throat needle?
No... The wasps in the hive
are trying to escape the water.
Desperately stinging his body
as they do so... Mushizo's lost.
Took his time about it,
but he finally killed him.
Reincarnation? Did he mean
Himuro Gemma's come back to life?
Impossible!
Reincarnation?
I've heard about the technique.
You must control your flesh and
blood down to the tiniest bones.
If your limbs or even
your head were cut off...
...you'd be able to rejoin them.
Reincarnation...
That's a technique of immortality.
It can never be achieved
by a human being.
Well, well...
That's a hell of a trick!
Anyway, the Kimon monsters
are now all after you.
That means I can move easily.
If you're lucky,
we'll meet again.
Why did you join him?
He hired me...
For 100 gold pieces.
You're a mercenary ninja?
One who'd do anything for money?
You could say that.
But he suckered me into it.
Trapped me.
I'll die of his poison
in half a day.
He promised me an antidote
along with the gold.
That's why I work for him.
I can't back out now.
You'd better run for it
while I divert their attention.
I can't do that.
I'd owe you another debt.
Forget about any debts.
And I told you I don't
have to take orders from you.
Besides,
I'm ready to die any moment.
Relax.
Stop pretending you're so tough.
What?!
It's this humid weather!
I wish a storm would come and
cool off that hot head of yours.
You're in no position
to worry about me.
Storm...
They came on the night
of that big storm...
Hey, where can I get
a good look at this area?
How about there?
Nothing.
Keep looking!
Hanza...
Wait!
Hanza!
There's a cliff
in front of you! Stop!
Damn!
Gotcha!
Shit!
Fool! They got you so soon?
We still had a lot to do.
The scent of blasted flesh,
grilled to perfection...
Such a lovely smell.
Don't... move...
That's enough. Let me go.
It's my fault
I fell for their trap.
Shut up! Don't talk!
Let go of me!
I don't want your help.
Shut up!!!
Go on, grab it!
Just gonna hang onto me all day?
I am Utsutsu Mujuro.
I've been longing to challenge you.
He's here for me.
Stay here.
You lured me here because I'm blind?
Is that your plan?
If you want to kill me,
then don't make a sound.
That's impossible. But maybe I can
turn your skill to my advantage.
I told you to stay back!
Your sight is your weakness.
Outta the way!
Impossible...
Would you give it a rest?!
What the hell were you thinking?!
What are you so obsessed about?
Shut up! You're the one obsessed
with repaying me for saving you!
You act like you've got
some kind of death wish!
Is it because of your body?
Is it true the men you sleep
with die from the poison?
Embrace me and you'll find out.
Idiot!
My body is saturated with poison.
It's so strong that a touch of
my lips will kill instantly.
No one can touch me.
Anyone who dares to... dies.
Did the poison
twist your heart, too?
How dare you!
I hate people who don't
value their own lives.
You've no idea...
You couldn't understand!
The cargo from the ship that ran
aground in the storm two days ago.
That's what they're after.
They butchered the villagers
like animals for it.
Where does this road lead?
Chamberlain!
Lord Hyobu, is it true?
That the Koga ninja who...
...went to investigate Shimoda
Village were wiped out?
Exactly.
But how?!
This is an emergency.
I'll take my men to the
village immediately.
No!
If this is serious
enough to jeopardize...
...the safety of our clan,
we must move very carefully.
That's how small clans
like ours can survive.
But...
The ninja woman who survived
is continuing the investigation.
Wait for her report.
You're tired from being
tensed up all the time.
Get some more sleep.
Those wheel tracks lead
to Kashima Harbor.
They're probably going to
transport the cargo out by boat.
If I don't stop them...
...the dead villagers and Koga
ninja will never rest in peace.
I'll cooperate with you
till the mission's over.
But if you insult me again,
I'll kill you where you stand!
Listen well, you who labor
for the Shogun of the Dark.
This mission could very
well decide our fate!
This ship will reach the
Mochizuki domain in a few hours.
We must retrieve the
cargo at any cost!
Understood? At any cost!
The townsmen must have cleared out
out fear of the epidemic.
One horse was enough
to scare them all away.
So, you're still alive.
I've been worried.
It's nice to see you, too.
They're waiting for a boat
to transport the cargo.
Did you check
what the cargo is?
No, I couldn't reach it.
But I can guess what it is.
Actually, I guessed before
I came here to Mochizuki.
What?!
You haven't figured it out?
It's something that has
to do with your past.
It's gold, boy. Gold produced
from that secret Yamashiro mine.
The ship ran aground
during the storm...
Probably on its way to the Shogun
of the Dark with caskets of gold.
Gold that's probably been
hidden for the last five years.
If it reaches his hands,
he'll be powerful enough...
...to topple the
Tokugawa government...
...and plunge the country
into another civil war.
We have to stop it at any cost!
Dakuan, you've got a tail.
What?!
Girl, what are you doing?!
I'm calling a Koga ninja bird
that's in this village.
Calling a bird? What for?
It'll carry my message
to the castle chamberlain.
I've discovered
what they're after.
In two hours, his army
will surround the town.
It's not as easy as you think.
The Mochizuki clan will probably
ignore this whole thing.
Why?!
The future of the clan is at stake.
This is a power struggle between the
Tokugawa and the Shogun of the Dark.
If a small clan like the Mochizuki
got involved, it'd be smashed!
See nothing, hear nothing.
That's the best course for the clan.
We'll find out soon whether or
not the Mochizuki will move.
So, now what are you playing at?
The man you hired is going
to die from your poison.
Tell me how to save him.
Amazing! You've fallen in
love with Jubei, haven't you?
Fool! I'm only doing it
to clear my debt with him!
I don't think so.
A ninja woman falling in love!
What's the point?
If you kill me,
there'll be no saving him.
Yes, and your mission
will be a failure.
Shit!
Uh-oh!
Calm down!
That's the real cure for him.
If you want to save his life,
there's no other way.
It's up to you.
It must have happened when
I went off for a moment.
She's most likely dead.
Well, we've got work to do.
We'll get no help
from the Mochizuki clan.
Don't fall for their trap.
Wait!
What if their ship comes
while you're at it?
Let her alone! A dead ninja
girl isn't that important!
Not important compared
to the great mission?
You're as much of
a monster as they are!
Fool! When you fight monsters...
...you become one yourself
or you can't win.
You damn fool boy!
Go ahead! GO TO HELL!
You god damned!!!
Are you all right?
Kagero!
You're hard to kill, but...
Woman, release his pain.
Kibagami Jubei?
Yes. But we've already
killed them all.
Idiot! They still live.
I'll kill him, for sure!
Stay where you are.
Lure them there and kill them.
Understand?
Yes.
Never would I have
imagined to see him here.
I look forward to
seeing you again, Jubei.
Gemma!
I'm sorry.
Forget it. I take it the castle
retainers haven't taken any action?
It's been two hours.
I see.
Why... You knew it was a trap,
but you came to help me.
It was stupid.
Why risk your life for me?
Because you're my comrade.
Comrade?
Yes. We've saved each other
over and over since yesterday.
You're a precious friend to me.
Stay!
The Mochizuki clan
is sitting this one out.
Your mission is over.
No, it isn't.
I'm still in debt to you.
You can pay it back later.
Not if you're dead!
I'll repay it here!
What are you doing?
The old man told me how
to counteract the poison.
"Kill poison with poison."
He said if you make love
to me, you'll be cured.
Take me...
Why?!
You'll die if you don't!
Why? JUBEI!
We've been waiting!
Load the ship immediately!
You! Well,
I warned you, didn't I?
We're screwed.
We'll never beat that many men.
I don't intend to let them go.
We'll make our stand soon.
What are you planning?
When they finish loading
the gold onto the ship...
...go to the tower
and ring the bell.
While they're distracted,
I'll sneak onboard the ship.
When we're out at sea,
we won't need any storm.
I'll sink it myself.
Very well.
By the way, did you make
love to the ninja girl?
None of your damn business!
Now get going!
Gemma... Where are you?
When I die, I'll take
you to hell with me!
The Mochizuki clan?!
They're moving against them!
Ah, Kagero!
You've done a fine job.
Hurry, before they get away!
Where are the others?
Don't worry. They've
got this place surrounded.
Then hurry!
Jubei...
Kagero!
Stop! It's a trap!
Fools! Sakaki Hyobu
died two days ago.
I killed him personally.
GEMMA!!!
Sir, please get
aboard the ship quickly.
The retainers of the
Shogun of the Dark are waiting.
Leave Jubei to me.
Upon my honor, I will not fail.
Please grant me this one wish.
Very well then. Go.
Stay out of this. Don't shame me
any more than you already have.
So, you are Gemma?
The Mochizuki clan
suspect nothing, correct?
Yes. All is well.
You've done a splendid job.
I admire you Devils of Kimon.
The Shogun of the Dark
will be pleased.
Writhe in pain before you die.
Yurimaru seems to have
suffered some ill fortune!
How careless of him
to have fallen into my trap.
It was your own fault,
Yurimaru.
Let's go.
Kagero!
Hang on! Kagero!
Jubei...
I told you not to come.
I wanted... to apologize...
It was the first time...
You didn't treat
me like a ninja woman...
...but like
a normal woman.
I knew I was becoming attracted
to you, and I was afraid.
So I tried to push you away.
Forgive me...
I don't care
what you think of me!
If for an antidote... or out
of pity... I don't care...
I just wish... that
you'd made love to me.
I was stupid... and weak.
Why couldn't I have
been more honest?
Enough.
Don't say any more!
Jubei...
I'm glad... I met you...
Gemma, with the gold's help
our dream will soon be reality.
"Our" dream?
Our great dream to
topple the Shogunate...
...and restore the reign
of the House of Toyotomi.
You don't understand...
How we, the former retainers
of Toyotomi, have suffered.
Now it'll be the Tokugawa who
suffer the agony and torment.
We'll use the gold to buy the
most advanced weapons from Spain...
...and defeat the
Tokugawa government.
That is the dream of all of us who
work for the Shogun of the Dark.
Nonsense.
What did you say?!
I said nonsense.
Hold your tongue!
You're a mere ninja!
My dream is different.
The gold isn't going
to the Shogun of the Dark.
What?!
We, the Devils of Kimon,
will take the gold.
You impudent!
I'll use it to organize the most
powerful army of ninja ever.
And we'll rule the country with
terror and power from the shadows.
Anyone who opposes me,
Tokugawa or Toyotomi...
...even the Shogun of the Dark
himself, shall die.
Meaning the true Shogun
of the Dark... will be me.
Well now, you're here!
I was just wishing you'd come.
I'm glad to hear that.
Of course.
Without your help, sinking
a big ship like this...
...would be impossible!
Pathetic old fool!
Over here.
What's wrong?
Fire in the hold!
We're gonna sink!
Idiot!
Put out the fire!
Impossible!
It's a sea of flame!
Put it out! Fight it!
Move it! Move it!
Forget it! Run!
Master Gemma!
Pass this message to everyone:
"Abandon ship and hide yourselves.
I'll call for you someday."
Go.
Gemma!
I see you brought back some
devils from your trip to hell.
Kibagami Jubei...
I should've finished you
with my own hands.
Stop your whining.
It's too late.
You want to avenge
the ninja girl Kagero?
She was trash in comparison
to what I've lost.
You alone I can't forgive!
I won't kill you yet.
Not before I make you suffer.
I'll make you pay
for smashing my dream.
Your dream? That you were going
to be the true Shogun of the Dark?
Don't make me laugh.
If you became shogun, you'd
make this a world of devils.
If you enjoy
their company so much...
...then go back to hell!
I'll kill you!
No one can kill me.
You of all people
should know by now...
I am immortal.
Is that so?
If you keep coming
back to life...
...then I'll kill you as
many times as it takes!
You fool!
GEMMA! HERE YOU DIE!
Jubei!
You seem to be rid of the
poison, thanks to Kagero.
The combination of a poison-
tasting ninja girl and...
...a talented lone wolf worked out
even better than I had planned.
Go away.
By the way, I'm sorry about
losing Kagero. A real pity, that!
But for a scant few moments,
she was able to...
...be an ordinary girl
and make love with you.
Was that part
of your plan, too?
Exactly. To read and
control peoples' hearts...
...is the true secret
of the ninja.
Still, only true sincerity
can move the human heart.
A twisted old bastard
like me couldn't do it.
You're a hell of a guy.
I really admire you.
As promised, I'll be waiting in
Edo with your 100 gold pieces.
Come and get it,
if you're still alive.
That makes us even.
Now never cross my path again.
You've beaten me. I thought I'd
shut your mouth in Edo, but...
Still, in your condition you likely
won't even make it to the shore.
Everything will end
just as I planned.
Come with me, let's go
out to see the stars.
Evening has only just begun.
I don't want anything,
only for you...
...to be at my side,
a smile on your face.
A distant summer,
the two of us alone...
Sitting on the beach
we used to walk.
Trying to retrieve
the gentleness...
...that we left behind.
A distant ballad sung
to no one at all...
I can still
hear it even now.
It embraces
my wandering heart...
...just like the cool night wind.
Looking at you,
only you...
...saying things
hard for us to say.
Times may have changed,
but I know...
...my feelings are
still the same for you.
A distant ballad sung
to no one at all...
I can still
hear it even now.
It embraces
my wandering heart...
...just like the cool night wind.