presented by Korea Pituers
a Popcorn Film production
starring
Cha Tae-hyun
Lee Eun-joo
Sohn Yae-jin
Lovers' Concerto
sister~
Hey, Ji-hwan
Ji-hwan
yes
Can I have a ride to
Grand Park way junction?
Sure, get in
Working and studying
at the same time is hard, huh?
A little
You're gonna suceeed
At whatever you do
Is that you, Ji-yoon?
Can't you smoke
better cigarettes?
Even high school kids
don't smoke that
Or stop smoking
if you can't afford it
How are you such an expert?
By any chance...
Forget it
You have another
strange mail
No name, no address
Who keeps sending this?
It's cute
Smell something?
Yeah, smells like soap
I also want to kiss
5 years earlier
Start
One Two
Three Four Five!
Yes! Lee Ji-hwan!
New record!
You've finally did it
Ji-hwan, you're a...
Did you just take something?
No, it's nothing
Do you have
strawberry juice?
Yes
Then I'll take two, please
- Something wrong?
- No
Your eyes are really red
Soo-in, come inside!
What are you doing?
Just a sec
Wow, it's so nice
Chul-hyun, a girl called!
Hello?
Ji-hwan,
you little bastard!
I'm hungry
- Again?
- Yeah
Excuse me
Mind if I sit with you?
Move over
I overheard both of you
talking earlier
The one with longer hair
Soo-in, right?
Yes
I'm Well, I'm not
very good with words
Soo-in
I fell in love
with you at first sight
Thanks for not laughing
Look so funny!
I'm going to the bathroom
- Kyung-hee
- I'm serious
Good luck
Let me be honest
I'm really sorry
for telling you this...
Ji-hwan Lee Ji-hwan
Yes
But you're making me
feel quite uncomfortable
uncomfortable, uncomfortable
Not comfortable
Here's a note for you
from that guy
What? What's that?
I turned the clock
back an hour
I wish you'd forget
everything I said
But if we run into
each other next time,
let's meet as friends then
I'm gonna leave for now,
but we'll meet again
We'll meet for sure
I'm Ji-hwan
Lee Ji-hwan
Remember my name, okay?
You're Soo-in
And you're...
What's your name?
Kyung-hee
Kim Kyung-hee
Right, Kyung-hee
Soo-in and Kyung-hee
Next time we meet,
we'll be friends, okay?
okay, see you later
Kyung-hee
Sleep over tonight
I snuck out,
so dad might get mad at me
Okay
Will it be okay with you?
Whose friend am I?
I'll just call home Let's go
I told you
not to be so nice
wash mine anyway
What are you doing?
Oh, this?
I heard this makes
Your breasts bigger
Wanna try?
No thanks
It's too hard
I really hate doing laundry
But you're so nice
to do all the laundry
Since I'm always home,
I'd feel guilty if I didn't
It's also good exercise
Stop Gonna give me
clothes again, huh?
Yeah
Hey, am I some beggar?
I have plenty more than you
I know
But they're useless to me
Why?
Why are they useless?
They're too big for me
Why do I keep losing
weight doing nothing?
Sorry
Know that you're
more sensitive sometimes?
It's not that
I don't like your clothes
Look, our styles
are totally different
When I wear your clothes,
it feels awkward,
as if I'm wearing a g-string
Have you ever
tried on a g-string?
Yeah, just once
It was really weird
It was so gross
I couldn't walk
It was, huh?
And really tight
How can a movie not have
a single kiss scene?
No fun
You said you
kissed before, huh?
Of course
With whom?
Would you know if I told you?
Just a guy
What does it feel like?
A kiss?
First of all,
Your mouth gets really dry
And then right here
Hey!
Here
Your nipples get hard,
then you get
really lightheaded,
and your arms and legs go numb
It can't be explained
Anyway, it feels really awesome
I like kissing better than sex
Sex?
Stop lying
Think whatever you want
But you have a big problem
Guys don't like it
if you can't kiss right
- Want me to teach you?
- Hey!
You have to learn
Don't!
Doesn't my face look weird?
My nose is crooked
and there's a mole by my mouth
I hate it
You're so pretty
That's why guys can't resist
No, you're pretty
Really?
Look, we can see both of us
I wish we could always
be seen together
'96 Soo-in & Kyung-hee
Shoot! Goal!
Man, that sucked
What's the score?
One to one
Can we join you?
For a big match against Japan,
someone's got
the wrong attitude
Hey
Goal! Lee min-sung!
My senior classmate owns this place.
I just work here part time
We didn't go to college,
and are just hanging around
You see, we weren't
good at school
We even barely
finished high school
I'm an English Lit major,
and I'm taking a break
My dream is to travel freely
My dream is to never change
even as I get older
My dad treats me
like a baby still
Yeah, but he's
much better than mine
My dad always drinks
My dad was died when I was twelve
Don't take it so seriously
I'm fine with it
Because my father
is always here
Don't you miss him, though?
I have his pictures
My father loved to take photos
We probably have as many as
ten family albums
When we look at them
when relatives come over, they think we're strange
Since we have fun and laugh
at the pictures
But we're laughing
because we're happy
There's a photo of us
at the amusement park,
and one in front of our house
when we first moved in
There's even a photo
of all the family naked
Hey, that sounds like a lie
It's true
We took baths together
until I was nine
Oh, yeah
How did you come up with that clock idea?
There he is!
Ji-hwan got a haircut
Do you mind moving your foot?
What did you say?
You prick
Move your foot
My friend finds it
uncomfortable
Hey, let's move back
Thanks Ji-hwan
Hey, you're pretty brave
I'm shaking all over
I've fallen in love.
What should I do?
It's no big deal
No, it hurts so much.
But I want to keep on hurting
It's Ji-hwan!
Oh no, it's a cop!
Hold hands
One, two, three
Match the steps
Left, left, left...
Dad, did you see
the movie Il Postino?
Il Posit?
Is that really a movie?
You have to see it with mom.
It's very moving
I've fallen in love
What should I do?
It hurts so much
But I want to
keep on hurting
Mom, have you
ridden the Viking?
Do you mind
moving your foot?
My friend finds it
uncomfortable
I've fallen in love
It hurts so much
But I want to
keep on hurting
Man, it hurts
But I want to
keep on hurting!
Oh my, Ji-hwan!
It's been so long
How are you?
Ji-hwan,
you little bastard!
How've you been?
Good, of course.
I almost forget your face
Am I coming at a busy time?
You're the one
who's been busy, punk
What's this?
Your pictures
I put some I liked
in my room
It's okay, right?
Of course
Still taking pictures lately?
No
My camera is probably
rusted by now
Well, taking pictures
can't pay for your tuition
You know what?
I liked your pictures,
but I liked watching you
take them better
You look a lot better now
That rotten little...
When are you
getting married?
I want to
as soon as possible
But she said she doesn't
trust me still
'96 Soo-in & Kyung-Hee
Don't you miss them?
I sometimes think about them
Chul-hyun
What if...
If
What if they
had called to meet?
Did they call you?
They did, huh?
Not really
I'm not sure
What's that supposed to mean?
Should I meet them?
What's the problem?
Do you still
have feelings for them?
At first, as time passed
I thought of them
hundred times a day, then ninety-nine,
ninety-eight,
ninety-seven,
and then when
I forgot to count,
I was confused on whether
they had black or brown hair,
or if I had
really liked them,
or wonder if
we really did meet
I thought about those things
'96 Soo-in & Kyung-Hee
I'm gonna marry him
He likes you, too?
No
Yes, probably
He always recommends
love stories and poems
And he smiles at me always
Ji-hwan,
can you do me a favor?
He always eats a little
That's why he
doesn't gain weight
It's so irritating
Want me to just
talk to him, right?
Yeah
Hi
Hello
Need a book?
That's okay
I'll pick one out
myself today
He's my friend from church
Hello
Oh, hello
- You pick one out, too
- Okay
Excuse me
What's the most
popular book these days?
What kind of books
do you like?
Well, anything
that's easy to read
Have you ever read
Hu Sam-gwan's Blood?
I already read that...
So...
I heard that this book
is really good
- This one?
- Yes
- It's great
- What is it about?
It's like a detective story.
The author is German
His shoulders are wider
than I thought
I better change the size
Isn't he good-looking?
It seemed as if he
was jealous of you, too
But Ji-yoon,
we look so much alike,
so wouldn't he realize
that we were related?
Look at our nose and mouth
And when a guy knows
some girl likes him,
he'll stay distant,
even if he likes her
No, we don't look
alike at all
Your eyes are more slanted
And you have a
bigger head than me
It's hand-made
I'm not sure
Min-sik!
Come here for a sec
Have you ever
seen this letter?
Oh, this
Do you know it?
Absolutely no idea
There's no address and no name
Who'd sent it like this?
My name is Hang Min-shik
I deliver mail
in a small town
I've been delivering
these strange mails lately
This is her room
I'm in love with this girl
I don't understand
why she doesn't send these letters
But anyhow, I'm just a postman
She's taking
pictures again today
Holding back my wish
to scribble with you together
I told you I'm busy
Just one more question
Are your dreams
often colorful?
- No
It's often for me.
Yes
Here are the results
Kyung-hee and I
are the same type
Someone who has one heart
to love only one person
Never cheats,
but due to obsessiveness,
you're likely to be a stalker
Fantastic.
One heart to love only one person
What about me?
What does it say?
Ji-hwan,
you're the most indecisive
Not any good as a lover
You imagine and decide on your own,
so you're left just liking the girl
If you do date,
you'll break a lot of promises
The worst of their kind
Do you believe that stuff?
That's girls for you
No need to get upset
Soo-in
Go help Ji-hwan
It'll be good exercise
Think so?
Ji-hwan,
what's your blood type?
Not again.
A type
Hey.
What are you doing here alone?
Oh, nothing.
Just hanging out
They're so lucky
Don't they look good together?
It's not easy to fall in love at first sight
It's so wonderful
Gonna stay over, right?
No, I got things to do
Like what?
I told you I gotta go
Kyung-hee
Why do you always ask favors,
and I have to carry them out?
Because you never asked me
Whatever
I'm tired of that face
Always pretending to be weak,
and as if the world will end
if you're not treated well
How long do you think
I'll be by your side?
Tell me.
Tell me!
Kyung-hee, I'm just...
Let's stop
I'm going, bye
Kyung-hee
Just like you,
I don't know what to do
They came at
five in the morning
They ran away
because their parents disapproved
I'm going no matter
what you say
Your turn
I'm going no matter what,
so don't worry. Sorry dad
Good enough?
Here.
Be careful with it
Kyung-hee, it's our school
The gate has changed
Wow, it's been so long
I wish we could go inside
Me, Too
Just ask me,
and I'll do anything
This is so great
Stop!
3767! Stop!
Ji-hwan,
what are you doing?
Just a minute
Come on
Ji-hwan,
someone's down there
What?
Don't wait and
just let it all out
It's fertilizer anyway
I'm sorry
Oh... my god!
Sure we can see fireflies here?
Yeah. But I think we came too late
Thought they'd still be here
Hey,
let's call the fireflies
How?
I saw it in some book
If you close your eyes
and call them inside,
they'll know to come to you
I don't believe you
Hurry up.
I'm closing my eyes
It's cold!
Hey, how come you guys
are leaving me out?
Isn't she cute?
Yeah.
Sometimes
I want to press her down,
catch her,
and then put her in my pocket
Then take her out
whenever I feel bad
Me, too
Ji-hwan
Thanks for coming with us
If it wasn't for you,
we'd never go on this trip
You see,
we never went on a normal trip before
I'm more grateful
Wait,
where's Kyung-hee?
Kyung-hee?
Huh?
Kyung-hee!
Aren't those her shoes?
I love you my friends!
Hey!
What are you doing here?
You're awake
Is Kyung-hee still sleeping?
Yeah
Didn't you two
sleep in your room?
Because of the mosquitoes,
we couldn't sleep
You must've been really tired
We tried to wake you up
several times
I see
Wanna talk about
our first love for fun?
First love?
It's better than
just sitting here
I like listening to
other people's love stories
Yeah?
Then you go first
um...
In junior high, this girl
worked at a comic book shop,
Because of her big eyes,
everybody seemed
to be attracted to her
She was really popular
among the guys
I went there everyday
to go see her
All the boys liked her
and came to the store
But one day
something happened