Too much for you? Give up?
Ay! Let go of me!
Ay! Let me go!
You've disappointed me.
Good! The best! I told you, Muay,
to bet on him. We're rich! Rich!!
Muay! Pick up the coins!
Enough for today!
You won't get your money back.
Ai Tim! You are so good, we have
a great opportunity to get rich.
Brilliant!
Ai Don!
Follow them!
Music!
Get them!
Quick! Let's go!
Ai Don!
Follow them.
This week I have to see customers.
I want you to get things ready.
Tell me first if there is a problem.
Yes Boss.
I want you to report everything.
Ai Hum Lae!
Where will we find Ai Bak Don?
You eat your food first. Eat!
Don't worry.
I'll find him! At the rice mill,
everyone knows him well.
Eat!
Muay! Tomorrow you'll go with me.
May be some chance to get money.
I can't. Exams tomorrow.
Exams! I've never seen you attend class.
How can you pass? Do you have
something special with the teacher?
What!
A joke, a joke.
You're a good student, you're clever.
Eat...
Thanks a lot for helping me to find Ong Bak.
Don't thank me.
Ai Yod, you owe me 3 months rent.
What are you going to do?
Er... Give me 3 days.
I'll pay you. This time for sure.
You said 'sure' too many times already.
I want money today -
otherwise you must move out.
Will you accept this ring instead?
OK
You must pay the rent within 7 days.
If you have no money again,
I'll kick you out, understand?
Son, I want you to return home with Bak Tim.
Don't worry if you don't have enough money.
I don't mind if you don't want to become a monk.
I only want you to visit us.
I miss you, son.
What's the matter!
Am I not as good as your ex-husband?
You spoil my mood.
Don!
I don't want to sell drugs any more.
Why?
I want to stop.
You want to stop?
Really want to stop?
Come here!
You think you can stop that easily.
You think you can, but you can't.
Who?
Huh! Ai Don.
Pi Ngek, Pi Ngek, Pi Ngek, Pi Ngek.
Where is Ong Bak?
I don't know.
You brought it here!
Ai Tim.
Get away.
Pi Ngek!
Get out quickly, Don.
Go, Go.
Call an ambulance for Room 212.
She's dying. Urgent!
Ai Tim! Come here quickly in a Tuk Tuk.
Hurry up.
You're dead.
Keep following me!
Come! You're dead.
Huh! Ai Tim.
Ai Tim! Brake! Brake! Brake quickly!
Oh Bhudda! Oh!
Spread them out.
Oh! Damn!
Get out!
You're dead.
Remember! You must search every
square metre. Don't miss anything.
Most important, you must not
allow any strangers in. Understand?
Damn them! They keep chasing after me.
Get in.
Today the Police and
National Heritage have found...
lots of Buddha statues and relics
on the Chao Praya river's bank
This finding of invaluable objects
is very significant.
Because every piece is a national treasure.
National Heritage is making a catalogue
for protective conservation.
We will report any developments to this story.
I told you not to cause trouble.
I didn't. They are looking for Ong Bak.
What's Ong Bak?
The head of the Buddha Statue that I brought to you.
Why does this man cause me so much trouble?
I lost my betting money,
and all my relics collection...
because of one peasant.
I'm sorry I can't save her.
Pi Ngek! Pi Ngek. Pi Ngek!
Pi Ngek don't leave me.
Who's she?
Muay's big sister.
You cann't leave me.
I have nobody.
Muay, Muay.
Ngek asked me to give this to you...
'For Muay College Fees'
I don't want it, don't want it
I want you. I have nobody else.
You can't leave. I've no one else.
Don't be so sad, Muay.
Birth and death are part of life.
I won't leave you.
What's this? What?
Where are you taking me?
Let's go, go quickly.
Go, go!
Do you know who I am?
How dare you attack my property!
I don't know. It's between Ai Tim and Ai Don.
True! I don't know.
I know that you are looking for this Head.
Do you really want it?
If you want it. I've a game for you to play.
I saw Ong Bak with my own eyes.
If you accept to fight for him,
he will give you Ong Bak and release Muay.
What are you going to do?
Tell me.
I will do anything...
to bring back Ong Bak to Ban Nong Pradoo.
I'll sacrify even with my life.
Why do you call me to leave the frontier?
To warn you to stay away from political
issues and I want you to make a bet.
Oho. You want to revenge that
country boxer to death!
How much you want to bet? Your call.
You don't call the shots anymore!
On the East corner is a Thai Boxer.
He's new to us.
The Burmese Boxer is on the West corner.
He's one of the best.
Now the fight has begun.
Ai Tim! Ai Tim! Are you OK?
Enough.
Hey! If you want Ong Bak, follow me.
You're crooks too.
Tim lost the fight so I could win the bet.
Huh! This is Pra.
It's just the head of some worthless
statue that you're trying to get.
I'm not interested in the head,
I just want you to box for me.
Don't dare challenge me because
I can make you live or die.
Damn you! You betray us.
Ai Tim lost the fight for you,
why don't you return the head to him?
Son of a bitch!
Calm down.
Finish them after I've gone.
You got hurt but I got the money.
Remember that I ordered this.
Get rid of them.
I can't help if they don't listen.
Huh! Kill them!
Pi Yod!
Damn! I told him not to make a noise.
Hey! Do it quickly!
Police may be here soon.
Hey! Go there.
Where is Ong Bak?
Hey! I go with you.
No, I can't let anyone die for Ong Bak.
Except me, only me.
Ai Tim, Ai Tim.
Let me help you.
I don't want to be like this.
I apologise to you.
Let me do one good deed
for Ban Nong Pradoo.
At least... Let me start the bike for you.
I, Bak Hum Lae, from Ban Nong Pradoo.
Don told me there is a secret cave
behind the next mountain.
Still not dead!
You want Ong Bak!
You have to exchange it with your life.
We're cutting the biggest head.
Ai Tim! Ai Tim... Ai Ti...
Ai Ham Lae! Are you OK?
Go and get Ong Bak. Go!
Don't worry about me.
Go and get Ong Bak.
Go!
Huh! Where're you running to?
Continue working! Cut the head off!
Be careful!
Last time I told him to lose.
The head is off now boss.
Good, pull it off.
Die... e... e...
You want this head!
I want to see if it's unbreakable.
Ai Hum Lae!
Ai Hum Lae... Are you hurt?
Take... take... Ong Bak
back to our... our village.
Ai Pi Yod! Ai Pi Yod!
What's happenning?
Ai Hum Lae.
Muay... finish... your studying
and find... a good job.
Bak Tim... Tell my dad
I can't become a monk.
Huh! What are you saying? Let's go
to hospital and you will be fine, Pi Yod.
Ai Hum Lae.
Ai Pi Yod, Ai Pi Yod. Huh!
You can't die! You promised
not to leave me, you can't die.
You can't do this! You mustn't
lie to me, you cannot lie to me.
Do you understand! You promised me!
I've nobody else! I've nobody else!
Wake up now! Don't do this to me,
you can't, can't. Understand!
Wake up now! Ai Pi Yod, you can't die.
You must keep your promise.