"Swaying and gyrating..."
"lighting fires in hearts..."
"with your eyes"
"Spark... sparkle"
"You're a spark"
Spark - Spark...
I'm a spark
Hi Rohit
Here...? So suddenly...?
What are you doing here?
Been thinking, Sanjay. Ever since
I came, something or the other...
- ...has been going wrong.
- Wrong? I never noticed anything?
Nor did I, until now.
But like I said...
- I've been thinking.
- And...?
After much deliberation,
I've arrived at a conclusion
There's someone behind all this.
Someone, who's trying... very
systematically, to break us up.
What are you saying?
There is someone who is determined...
not to let me marry Anjali
Really?
Who might it be?
I stopped him, I even tried
to reason with him
For friendship's sake,
I told him
I posed obstacles for him,
I lay a thorn in his path
Like a blossom,
I even tried wilting
Today, weds a friend.
But I am not happy
Love, culminates into marriage.
But...
why aren't you happy, Sanjay?
You are the one who doesn't want
this wedding to happen
But why?
But there can be only one reason.
You are in love with Anjali.
We're friends, you can tell me.
Yes, I love Anjali
Now that it's out in the open,
what to do?
For you, it's quite simple.
Now that you know everything...
I think you should just leave
and go back. To America
- Really?
- Yes
This is my story and Anjali's.
You just walked out of the woodwork
You see? Anjali doesn't love you
Anjali doesn't love me?
Look, in her life you're merely
a stand-in for me
In my stead
She went to America on my say-so.
The swing, that was mine too
You understand...? In my story and
Anjali's, you're my understudy
Now that I'm here, what need for you?
So pack. Go back. To America
You needn't inform anyone.
I'm around, I'll handle everything
Sure, you'll handle everything.
But taking your advice...
- ...will be a bit problematic.
- Tell me, I'll solve your problem
After all, I'm Sanjay, the magic man.
Say, what's your problem?
Problem is, I too love Anjali
I can't walk away from her, certainly
not when she's willing to marry me
That's her mistake, Rohit.
I'll make her happier than you can
That's what you think, Sanjay.
But there's only one way to decide...
Where lies happiness for Anjali.
Where?
You love her and I love her too.
Let's both try
You don't ask me to go away,
I don't ask you to go away
You can do whatever you wish
If you succeed,
then Anjali was never mine
If you fail to succeed,
then it's evident...
that Anjali and I share
that eternal relationship
Why are you wasting your time?
You're a nice guy
What's with Anjali?
You'll find scores of girls
No Sanjay. There's only one Anjali
And she can belong to
only one of us
Whose? Only time can tell
I got one advantage. I'm marrying her
in a week's time
You're running out of time
I got 22 years behind me.
You're the one lagging way behind
- You lose.
- We'll see
I warned you! The planetary alignment
for the engagement was inauspicious
The boy isn't to blame.
He is influenced by the illusions
We got to know in time. Else...
I'd rather this isn't discussed
Without discussions,
how do we arrive at conclusions?
Am I not to be given a chance
to defend myself?
What you saw was true, yet not true.
I did it, but I wasn't my self
Such was the circumstance,
such was the ambience...
I thought, if so many people
are trying to make me happy...
I ought to join them
lest they take it otherwise
I could've walked out...
and left them heartbroken
But in my folly I've broken the heart
of the man who took me for a son
Well what are the facts, Uncle?
Fact is, you saw me disgrace myself
But there's another truth.
No one means more to me than Anjali
Far bigger truth, Anjali trusts me,
wants to spend a lifetime with me
And yet another truth, Uncle.
You took me for a son
But can I ever be your son?
If I were, you would've forgiven me
If you will not touch me in pardon,
I shall never be able to face myself
Never
You can even face the Sun
After all, I have taken you for a son
- What happened?
- Don't worry, everything's fine
- Uncle has forgiven Rohit
- I knew Rohit would bring him around
That's what Rohit is like, isn't he?
Sanju, in all these days,
you still haven't told me?
How do you find Rohit?
Tell me. It's one big decision
I took for myself. What do you think?
Am I right? Tell me Sanju
how do you find Rohit?
Rohit is a nice boy, Anju
Great guy. He'll make you happy
What did you do to bring Papa round?
Fell in love with you
- What do you want?
- Love
Couldn't find it at the
bachelor's party?
I never imagined, you'd
admit defeat so soon
You praised me to the skies
Honestly, I was surprised
How to explain this? Deep inside this
scoundrel of a Sanjay Malhotra...
there lives this nice, noble
Sanjay Malhotra too
But it takes Anjali's tears
to draw out the nice guy
Like you, he is also a fool
being honest, being truthful
But it's only a matter of a few minutes
and those few minutes are over
Which leaves this Sanjay Malhotra
cunning, conniving
So wipe that smile off your face
The war is on
So this is going to be even more fun
And guess why?
Tomorrow... my relationship with Anjali
will have run the course of 3 months.
I'm going... to take her out.
She says, impossible
and I say, you have your magic-man
- He will bring you to me
- What makes that interesting?
Your Anjali is about to beg of you
and how will you refuse her?
That'd be interesting? Besides
the wedding is only 6 days away
Only six days.
In six days...
the earth spins around six times
Keep spinning your planet
let me make a world for myself
My wedding... is six days away
Enough of wordplay
Six days...?
Neither the car nor I
can get an inch ahead
From here you walk alone
You're nervous,
your heart is pounding
Because you don't know
what's about to happen
What might he do?
And what should you be doing?
Heart misses a beat?
My heart would, too...
were I in your place
And what'd you do?
For a moment, imagine
being in love with me
For a moment, let me imagine
I'm in love with you
And what would you do?
In that moment, I would've
tried to live a lifetime
Tell me, what would you do?
I...
would walk up to you, without taking
my eyes off yours... like this
- I'd keep looking at you...
- Then...?
Your eyes would hold mine
your hands would be in mine
- And your breath upon my breath
- And...?
And I'd carry you away with the wind
to the rustle of leaves...
and bathe you in a lake of dew
and in a moment stilled...
- I'd whisper in your ears...
- Whisper... what?
- Whisper...
- What?
It'd be...
Be it for even a moment
give me your love...
even if you're false
"Silken waves of breeze"
"Come embrace me"
"Our desires are alive
and so are we"
"Don't let this distance be"
"At wind's caress won't the
blossom be fragrant?
"How can I give you my fragrance?"
"The budding blossom is shy"
"Then this shyness is more
like punishment"
"Why are you so fervent?
It's only a little wait"
"Even a moment's wait
is cruelty"
"Our desires are alive
and so are we"
"I wanted not to speak out"
"But I couldn't hold my silence"
"Yet I haven't had my say"
"Be it whatever you tell me
or whatever you won't..."
"but don't look so lost"
"Come what may..."
"just listen to your heart"
"Whatever is heartfelt..."
"just tell me"
"I'm yours,
I swear by you"
"Our desires are alive
and so are we"
"A silken breeze winds..."
"let's draw closer"
"Our desires are alive
and so are we"
"Don't let this distance be"
Help
I just fell off a tree
Hurts
Why is the car going backwards?
Anju...?
Rohit! What are you upto?
I'm going to get killed
Let me sleep, Ria.
No office today
Sanjay, where are you?
Why is everyone staring at me?
I'd like to see Sanjay
- In bed till ten? Like always!
- Ria, you...?
Yes, I
Darling, will you please
tell these people how we're related?
Didn't I tell you
he'd come running?
Ria! What are you doing here?
I thought I'd surprise you
Didn't I tell you
he'd be happy to see me?
This is Ria
And Ria, this is...
H.P... V.P... Lucky... A.J.
And that's Raj
I've been introduced to them
and everyone here knows me
Darling, you're too much!
You haven't told them that we...
- We...?
- Boyfriend - Girlfriend
And you've been having this affair
for the last 8 months
So she's that
"little sister" of mine?
- And she has no one but you?
- And you have no one but her?
No...
- Here for Anju's wedding...
- And left your heart in Bombay?
- With his real girlfriend!
- So he calls every day to tell her...
- Oh I miss you, darling.
- Darling...?
I see! So dear nephew, is this your
love story... nice to meet you
- Try your best cover, but we know
- Anyone else knows more than me
Darling
Why are you shying away?
She's a beauty
- Given a chance...
- Would you...?
Smart, good-Iooking
Shall we... H.P...?
The journey must've been tiring.
Take rest
- May we excuse ourselves?
- As soon as Anju arrives...
- I will send her directly to you
- No, no...
- She will be glad to meet Ria
- Sure, she'll be glad
- I'm here, everything will be fine
- Why have you come here?
Raj, will you please
take my luggage in?
Yes darling...
I mean to say... Ria
Shall we... darling?
Darling, my foot!
What rubbish
Go on, laugh some more
Shut up, will you?
You've ruined my game!
Everything was so perfect
The wedding is only 5 days away!
Why did you have to do this Ria?
To help you, stupid! I'm here
for your own good
I just saw what good you're upto!
Do you realise what you've done?
My bachelor's party cost Rohit far less
than what your stupidity has cost me
- Darling...!
- Have you had your say?
- You're in love with Anjali, right?
- What rubbish! I'm in love with you
- Darling!
- Sanjay...
- Darling...
- Sanjay, I'm serious
When did you discover
you're in love with Anjali?
You realised, when you saw someone else
walking into Anjali's life
When you saw someone else getting close
to Anjali, you realised...
how close you are to her.
And just like you...
Anjali has never seen you
with another girl
- So...?
- When Anjali sees me with you...
Anjali should know too, no?
She might reciprocate what you felt
when you got news of her wedding
You understand, darling
Oh... darling
Anjali... this is Ria
Sanju, will you step out for a moment?
I got to tell you something
Sure, go along
I'll join you
Her luggage is in the kids' room
- Kapoor? Who's Kapoor?
- Mr. Kapoor in Mumbai
Runs a big advertising agency. Last year
at one of his parties... I met Ria.
You never even told me?
- Did you tell me about Rohit?
- I told you about my wedding
I'm not marrying her yet.
I'll let you know when it happens
You're going to marry her... this Ria?
Why what's wrong with her?
She's smart, she's sexy, beautiful
What do you mean, why?
You won't marry her and you won't
- I've spoken. Now do what you want
- Okay
- And by the way, what's she doing here?
- She's here for your wedding
You're my friend, you invited me.
She's my friend. In turn...
- Why did you invite her?
- May I not have a guest?
Girlfriend! If I invited Ria,
are there any problems?
No, she's fine
- You don't even know her
- I don't even want to know her
Worse, she's an eyesore.
If you say so...
I can accommodate her in my room
- Jealous?
- Why should I be jealous?
Because after you
she's the only other friend I have
Don't you ever compare me with her
"Are you the Moon in full bloom
are you a star?"
"Whatever you be,
by God you're incomparable"
That's my face pack commercial
- Modelling must be fun!
- Show us a catwalk
Right away
Nice prop
- But won't help
- Let's see
H.P. You still haven't
given me the pendant
Who can refuse you?
Here you are
Papa, Uncle, looks like you forgotten
all about a wedding just 3 days away
- So what do we do?
- Are you asking me?
Didn't Mr. Verma call you?
Papa, the jeweller is on the phone.
Am I supposed to organise my wedding?
No, that's my lot.
Excuse me, we got work to do
Shall we...?
- Uncle, have you nothing to do?
- Oh yes...
You know, such a lot to do
about the wedding... excuse me
- You're forever organising weddings...?
- Yes
- And you still haven't found your girl?
- I'm sure I'll find someone...
say one of your cousins?
Someone who's yet to marry...?
I haven't a sister, but they say
I've come of age
- They must be right...
- Uncle, there's work to be done
- May I help you?
- No thanks, son
What with the arrival of the new star
everyone's after her
- Sanjay is very lucky, isn't he?
- How come...?
- Finding someone like Ria...
- Actually I find it strange
- I never imagined someone like Sanju...
- Would like someone so modern?
For someone who lives in Bombay
could Sanjay like anyone else?
- You're cosmopolitan too. From America
- I'm different
I always wanted someone simple.
Like Anjali
But Sanjay's choice...
got to be Ria
- They look great together, no?
- Yes, great
I say, let's give them a wedding
the same day as us
He's right! Besides, we are
the only relatives Sanju has
My point! So what the point
putting off a nice thing?
But you must teach me
cheese omelettes
Sanju picks fights in the kitchen
- Your kitchen? Or his?
- The kitchen is the same
In Bombay, you're lucky to find
one kitchen inside one flat
I don't understand...
You and Sanju...
Sanju never told you? We live together,
in the same apartment
How many bedrooms?
You and Ria, live together?
In the same flat?
No, how could she live
in my flat? Never... no
- Why are you laughing?
- Nothing. Ria was just telling me...
how Sanjay broke down a bathroom
door to rescue her
- And she was clad only in a towel
- You said she never lived with you
She didn't. But of late she doesn't
have a place to live. So...
How magnanimous of you Sanjay,
to have given her shelter
Very soon, she'll make family
with you. All the best
The plan was nice.
Girl, jealousy... it always works
Maybe the living-together bit
was a bit too much?
They'll make sure
you're married
The likes of Anjali are best
for doctors like me
It's a Ria you need
Coming... aunt
We're finalising a wedding date
for you and Ria
Finalising
It's not working
Got to think up something else
Sanju, come out.
Tell your Ria to come out
Poor Bunty has been knocking
for the past half an hour
And the lady is taking her time
dressing to go out
- All dressed and raring to go? Where?
- Anju, the college re-union
The annual do, the old students
get together... never got the card?
I got invited before you. I've been
invited regularly these last 3 years
- I never went, not even once
- So sad
- You'll miss it this year too
- How come?
How can you go?
You're getting married in 3 days
But how can you go? I skipped the last 3
years because you weren't here
We promised each other, we wouldn't
go to the re-unions without each other
- Oh I forgot, sorry
- No problem. Change
Let's go downstairs
for a game of carrom
- I can't.
- Why?
Darling, I'm ready.
Let's go
I promised Ria. She wants to see
my college. I can't break her heart
Shall we... darling?
If you want come along
I'm sure Ria won't mind
My invitation says, I can bring along
a guest of my choice
- Then, you're coming?
- Of course. With a guy of my choice
"There's no one like us"
"We're the life of the party"
"Is there anyone else
...like us?"
"Why lament that you can't find
anyone else?"
"Is there no one else?
Well, I don't lament that"
"We're young, we're beautiful"
"We have no laments"
"The sights are already
driving me crazy
"Is anyone else around like us?"
I'm the life of the party"
"When you're with me
everything is beautiful"
"The road ahead is full of love"
"Come into my heart
let my search end"
"Anyone else around
like you and I...?"
"You and I have brought to life...
this party"
"Anything like you-and-I...?"
What a pair! That's how
a friendship ought to be
Wish I too had a friendship
like this
- Are you talking about Sanjay or Anjali?
- I'm talking about you
Sanjay is lucky to have you on his side.
That's what everyone says in Bombay
Only lucky guys get friends
I mean girl friends like Ria
- Hey what happened?
- Ria, will you spare me this act?
- Act? How can you call it an act?
- You're his friend. Not girlfriend
But you make a great friend. That's why
I wish I had a friend like you
Someone who would be willing
to help me to get Anjali
Between friends, you got to do
what it takes for friendship's sake
- From "Maine Pyar Kiya?"
- You watched the movie?
- Six times.
- I could be your friend
Off the record
Can I ask you something
off the record?
What makes you so confident that
whatever you're doing is right?
See them together?
- Sanju, I want that trophy
- You've taken three of five
- This is my turn.
- Sanju, please...
No, score is score
- Aren't they made for each other?
- Certainly not
Life's no dance competition, Ria
Nice dancing partners...
don't necessarily
make good life partners
The bigger decisions in life
can't be based on trivia
Say, if you never knew Sanjay
say, if you were my friend...
suppose I was the one who invited you
And now, look at them
Do you still say that Sanjay and
Anjali were made for each other?
Whatever you or I think
doesn't make a difference
What makes all the difference
is what Anjali wants
What Anjali wants
- You're a nice guy, Rohit
- I know
But sometimes, I'm afraid my ethics
might create obstacles
Gayatri...
girls all over the world
are getting married
But no mother-of-the-bride was ever
as harried as you are
What will people say?
- Ajit...
- Yes?
- Send the sweets to Rohit's house
- Yes uncle
Our son-in-law is one-in-a-million
It's a time to rejoice. And you...
What's going on?
Sanju, will you make Gayatri
see some reason?
She insists that a twitch
in her left eye bodes ill
Is Aunt's superstition
rubbing off on you
If you ever have a daughter
and come the time for her wedding...
- ...you'll know.
- What...?
Isn't it sad to know that my daughter
will be leaving me in a couple of days?
I got a wonderful idea!
Let me marry Anju
And I'll move in to live with you
Then Anjali won't have to go away
If that could've happened
no one would be happier than I
You'd be happy to give your daughter
away to a fool like him?
Your daughter has chosen someone nice
like Rohit. Thank God for that
And everything's working out fine
Most parents lose their sleep
over a daughter's wedding
And before we knew it
this match was finalised
- Before we knew it... just think
- What's there to worry about?
In front of so many people
it takes only one wrong word...
to hurt everyone. And it has
happened so many times
And I've heard,
seen such instances...
where one misplaced word can destroy
relationships that have lasted years
Are we about to forge new relationships
at the cost of old ones?
It deserves a thought
You're getting worried for nothing
I'm around, and you have my promise
No one will be hurt
no one will be sad
I'll make sure everyone is happy
I'm your magic man, am I not?
Listen...
- About Sanju marrying Anjali...
- Gayatri, you know what he's like
- He was joking. He wasn't serious
- What if he was?
- Uncle...
- Coming
Sanju is always joking
Sanjay, guess what Rohit told Anjali
over the phone? He said...
- ...you should hear it yourself
- You taped their conversation?
- Of course
- You're too much
- Should I not have done it?
- Of course not
Anjali and Rohit are getting married
What right have you...?
I'm not here to attend some Anjali's
wedding to one Rohit
I'm here to break up the wedding
You got to tell Anjali that
you're in love with her
Sanjay, will you tell Anjali
or won't you?
- Why not?
- I don't know...
- Then I'll tell her...
- No Ria... please
I don't think you need me here.
Then... I think I'll just leave
Won't you stop me?
- I don't know what to say...
- You needn't tell me anything
But you won't ever tell the one
you ought to be telling, will you?
Sanjay, my best compliments
It's your best friend's wedding
See you in Bombay. In the meantime
if you achieve anything, invite me
To your wedding
Uncle, this is splendid!
I did nothing. Sanjay did all this
He was up all night.
I don't think he has slept
Just like you kept awake
all through my wedding to Nilu
Yes, just like that
You like the design?
Eat this, Nilu, Gita... the bride's
trousseau is here
- Where?
- Downstairs
- Come on, leave that for later
- Okay, come on
You don't want to see
the bride's trousseau
I wanted to see you in bridal finery
But that isn't to be
Why are you leaving so suddenly?
Can't you stay for two days...
I got important work. I'm helpless.
If I could stay back, I would
I wanted to stay for your wedding.
But anyway... Sanjay is here
Aren't you afraid to leave your
boyfriend to a bevy of beauties?
Sanjay isn't my boyfriend.
We're friends. Just friends
- Then why all this...?
- Life plays such jokes with us
And we crack jokes with each other
...only so much to the relationship
In Bombay, Sanjay never fell in love
with any girl, nor can he ever
Why...?
Because the girl in his heart
isn't in Bombay
Aunt, your cab is here
- Not in Bombay? Where else?
- How can I say?
You are his best friend. You ought
to know what is in his heart
Seek within your heart,
you might find the answer
Yes Sanjay, tell me
I'm going
Back
You win
I lose
I don't know why I believed
why Anjali and I...
Without even thinking
how one mistake of mine...
might break so many hearts
Thanks to you, I stopped myself
from making that mistake
Anyone else in your place...
but how could you be someone else?
You are Rohit, the perfect one
The one for Anjali
I was Anjali's friend.
I'll stay a friend
But I won't be able to stay
I don't have the courage to see Anjali
leaving with someone else
Nor am I gentleman enough
to let you carry her away
Take care of Anju
The wedding is tomorrow. I won't
ask you to stay for the wedding
But today, won't you join in
my celebrations?
We just became friends, didn't we?
Yes, we just became friends
And I'll make sure everyone
joins the celebration
After all, it's my friend's wedding
"To the rhythm of drums,
her anklets chime"
"The bride wears a veil
the bridegroom carries flowers"
"And the Spring follows them
around the world"
"May all the happiness
in the world be theirs"
"Here's a prayer from my heart
for my friend's wedding"
"My friend has found love"
"For him, this is sweet victory"
"I'm so happy..."
"I'm so happy, I've filled this party..."
"with songs..."
"for a dear friend's wedding"
"There's no winning,
there can be no losing..."
"where there's love"
"If there be a contest,
there can be no love"
"Let's embrace..."
"friend..."
"here's a prayer from my heart..."
"for my friend's wedding"
"My childhood friends,
my childhood playground..."
"my toys, my swings,
I will miss everyone"
"How will I hide my tears?"
"My friend, hear what our
playground tells..."
"colour your heart,
you life in hues of love..."
"and even the jewellery
you wear will smile"
"Remember that, friend"
"My friend's wedding..."
"it's my friend's wedding"
So you're leaving? You lost
It's you who told me to put
my heart into the game
Win or lose, what difference?
Sanju are you sure?
- Are you doing the right thing?
- Yes Uncle, just as sure as you were
Hindustani women are incomprehensible
Try to get close and their decorum and
their decency stands in the way
And 12 hours before the wedding,
summons are issued
What's this sudden
show of affection?
Rohit, we've told each other
about everything...
except one thing...
that you perhaps forgot to ask
...and I forgot to tell you
What...?
Whether I ever loved someone
before you
- Did you?
- Yes
From the moment such thoughts
about a boy arise in a girl's mind...
- ...there has been such a boy.
- Who is he?
Sanju, my friend
...my best friend
But you saw Sanju. How can I even
expect him to understand?
He's lost in his own world.
I always hoped...
some time or the other,
Sanju would come up and tell me
But as time went by,
I realised I'm wrong
For Sanju, I'm just a friend.
Only friend
So I suppressed my feelings,
lest he found out
Then... you came into my life
You made me believe, I can have
a good life with someone else too
But before beginning this life,
I wanted you to know...
I'm building this relationship
on honesty. Yes, Rohit?
That's just why I called you out
Hello Rohit
Beautiful flowers, just like
your daughter
- You haven't gone to bed yet?
- Lost my sleep
- How come you're up so late?
- I made a promise to Anju...
that I'd decorate her wedding
hall myself.
I'm doing it up in flowers
May it be flowers, flowers for her
all the way and no thorns
Your prayer is already bearing fruit
If I ask you a question, will you
give me an honest answer?
- Yes, ask me.
- I wasn't your first choice for Anjali
- No son, it's nothing like that.
- I know... I know and it's okay
But there's something
even you don't know
I wasn't Anjali's first choice either.
What are you saying, son?
And for you and your daughter
the first choice was the same
Sanjay
In all these years, Anjali could never
tell Sanju how dearly she loves him?
And there's Sanjay. He loves
Anjali so fiercely...
he can't bear to see her marry
someone else
And I am the only man in the world
who's aware of their feelings.
The only man who can give
any twist to this tale
But what am I to do?
What do I do now?
Now I know, Sanjay was right.
This story is his. And Anjali's.
I had no place in this story
Sanjay left. Because he didn't
want to break anyone's heart
At least he knew
what he ought to do
Anjali told me...
because she wanted honesty to be
the cornerstone of our relationship
She knows too
what she ought to do
Now it's my turn. Even I know
what I ought to do
But what I must do, I cannot
bring about all by myself
I need a mother to bless my way...
to tell me, "Son, you're right"
"I am with you"
- Say, are you with me?
- Yes
- Hey... Say, how do I feel?
- How...?
Like I've fast-forwarded
a decade into life
I feel like we're both 35 and here
we are sitting at Gateway of India
You haven't found a boy
and I haven't found a girl
- Really?
- Yes
- So...?
- So let's strike a deal
At thirty-five if we're still here,
then we'll get married
- On one condition.
- What?
You'll still do the cooking
Okay, done
Talking about being 35...
I don't even know...
with Anjali gone, how I'll manage
to live beyond the day after...?
You... here...? Tomorrow's your wedding
Why did you leave?
- Ria fell sick all of a sudden...
- No Ria, no Rohit
No one's an excuse to my question.
You and I...
and between us, this one question
- Why did you leave?
- Because...
- because I...
- Because what?
Because I can't bear to see you
marry someone else
- Why can't you bear?
- Because I wanted to marry you
- Then why didn't you tell me?
- I was afraid Anju
If you refused...
It would've broken my heart.
What about all these years...
that I held my heart and I pined?
Did you ever think of the girl
who was with you all her life...
holding hands, sitting with you
on that swing...?
In the whole wide world, why does
she have an only friend?
A girl goes through her childhood
and her youth with one boy
Would she ever seek the company of
someone else... for the rest of her life?
Have you never wondered?
You never thought that all I needed
was only my friend?
The only one. You
How can a girl be expected to be
the first to express her feelings?
You never wondered? Never...?
- I'm... I'm sorry, Anju.
- Sorry? Is that all you can muster?
Won't you say what I've wanted
to hear all these years?
I love you
"To the rhythm of drums,
her anklets chime"
"The bride wears a veil,
the bridegroom carries flowers"
"And the Spring follows them
around the world
"May all the happiness
in the world be theirs"
"Here's a prayer from my heart
for my friend's wedding"
"It's my friend's wedding"