Well, there it is. It's OCP.
They screwed him up.
He must be going out of his mind.
It's not as if he can just say no.
They put all this nonsense
into his brain. He has to obey.
Take them out, all of them!
Can't be done,
not with this equipment.
Are you saying there's no way?
I can't believe that.
Sure, there are ways.
You can pull his cranial circuits.
Which would shut down
his life-support.
You could run a few thousand volts
through him.
Probably kill him.
I'll get some help!
- Get him inside!
- Come on, move it!
- Come on!
- Don't touch him, he's hot!
Use your jackets.
Why'd he do that?
Fried himself to get rid
of OCP's crazy commands.
- Nice and easy.
- He weighs a ton.
Out of the way! Move out!
- Think he's alive?
- I don't know. He's pretty hot.
Put me down.
All right. Come on, stand him up.
Are we cops?
What's bugging you, Murph?
Cain.
Cain's bugging me.
We have only just begun, my flock.
Soon we will expand from city to city.
The rich and poor alike
will know a paradise...
...for every moment of their lives.
This is a Nuke for every mood.
We'll offer the opportunity...
...to control every aspect
of their emotional lives.
Here with the white noise
and black thunder...
...and the red ramrod
and the blue velvet.
Frank. The blue velvet.
I think it's ready, sir.
Thank you, Frank.
Frank. The Benzedrine's
got my teeth wiggling.
Cut it with scopolamine.
- Five mils per.
- Yes, sir.
Made in America.
Yeah. We're gonna make that
mean something again.
- Hey! Cops!
- What?
Cops!
And they ain't carrying
no picket signs!
They're going to kick somebody's ass!
Give me your hand, goddamn it!
Christ!
Fuck.
Fuck!
Get out!
Bomb! Get down!
You son of a bitch!
Five hundred million in cash.
Nuke money seized by police.
But State Attorney Sphincter won't let
the bankrupt city government touch it.
Coming up next, threats from the police
union and cheers from the public...
...as Metro-North cops go back to work
and apprehend the Nuke lord, Cain...
...who may not live to stand trial.
They say 20 seconds
in the California sunshine...
...is too much these days...
...ever since we lost the ozone layer.
But that was before Sunblock 5000.
Just apply a pint...
...to your body...
...and you're good for hours.
See you by the pool.
Sunblock 5000.
Protection for the new age.
Subject is violently antisocial...
...given to delusions of godhood.
And he's hopelessly addicted
to narcotics.
Which offers us a simple
and infallible method...
...of insuring his obedience.
You're perfect.
I must have you.
What are you talking about?
It's like you don't even care!
- Just do what I say, Angie!
- He'd want us to come for him!
Forget about it! It's not gonna happen!
I'm through arguing with you!
I'm not asking permission! Cain is
in the hospital, and we're getting him.
You've really thought this out, haven't you?
What about the cops?
We've got guns!
- Damn it, Hob, Cain needs us!
- Fuck Cain!
- He'd kill you if he heard you.
- He's not gonna kill anybody!
- Shit, he's probably dead already.
- You just shut the hell up!
You mouth off like that again,
and it's no more Nuke for you, bitch.
Damn it, Hob, you know that's not fair.
Now, come on.
- It's been a bad time.
- Sure has. You're really hurting.
Yeah, so I'm hurting.
You're gonna get the shakes soon, Angie.
You got it bad.
You little bastard.
You just do what I tell you
from now on, Angie.
Start the motor and drive.
He'll kill you.
He'll kill us both.
Fuck him.
Oh, you're a mess.
I got good news for you.
You're going to have a chance
for immortality.
As long as nothing happens
to that lovely brain.
Dr. Weltman? It's Faxx.
I'm afraid we lost our patient.
Yeah, he just expired.
Contact the organ harvest team. We've got
six minutes before the brain's useless.
Night.
Come on. Let's move it.
We've only got five minutes.
Lock it up.
Move the screen in closer.
I can't read it.
- How'd we get this one?
- Well, Faxx found him.
He volunteered.
Volunteered?
Big-hearted guy.
Yeah, it's not the heart
we're after, though.
Speaking of hearts, how's Ilene?
Christ, does everybody know?
All right, hold your breath.
Showtime.
It's nice and clean in here.
There's no damage.
Here we go.
Easy.
We got it. Here it comes.
- Thing of beauty.
- Excellent.
I don't know about the rest of you,
but I'm hungry.
Thank you!
Yes!
Spider Baby Stalirski!
He's come out for Detroit,
and now you come out for him.
The lines are open,
waiting for your pledge.
If you want an honest government...
...that works for you...
...I'm asking you to dig deep
into your pockets.
I'm asking you to give...
...whatever you can spare!
Where does that put us?
Hi. Yes, ma'am.
Hello! This is Mayor Kuzak!
Could you turn down your set, please?
Your Honor...
...I have some very good news for you.
I think...
...the city is saved.
Now...
...you listen very carefully.
It's no bluff.
Someone's shown up to bail the city out.
- A rival corporation.
- The mayor isn't saying.
And whoever it is is taking great
pains to keep their identity secret.
They're paying in cash and they're not
moving the money through the banks.
Thank you, councilman.
That will be all.
You know, once you guys take over...
Your services to OCP
will be rewarded.
If the city can pay,
we'll be humiliated.
It's worse than that. We've shifted
80 percent of our resources...
...to the urban pacification plan.
If we can't foreclose, public confidence
in OCP will plummet, so will our stock.
Sir?
If I may?
There's another option.
We certainly have the surveillance
capabilities to follow the mayor.
It all depends how far
we're willing to go.
If anything went wrong...
As I said, sir...
...it all depends how far
we're willing to go.
We have no legal recourse.
There must be no witnesses.
You've gone too far! Give me...
Your blood pressure.
Get me fired if you want to.
You're not bringing illegal drugs to my lab!
I'll do worse than get you fired.
Now leave me alone!
Such terrible pain.
You don't remember me.
But you do remember this, don't you?
And we have it.
All the Nuke you'll ever need.
Not so fast.
I need you to do something
for me first.
Then the pain stops.
Good boy.
I don't like this. I think we'd better
get out of here while we can.
I know what I'm doing.
If you have any cash,
put it in your shorts.
That's just plain rude.
I wonder if any of you could help me.
I'm looking for a Mr. Hob.
So...
...how much you need?
Money, I mean.
Well, our current debt to OCP is...
$37,480,911 dollars.
Guess you're in some pretty deep shit.
We need all the help we can get,
young man.
Tell you what. Put me down for 50,
just to make sure.
- 50 cents, 50 dollars. That's cute.
- Don't be a queer.
Fifty million.
This is bullshit.
Let's get out of here.
Good God.
Gentlemen?
Well, will 50 do it?
Oh, yes. That'll do it.
- Don't you guys think that'll do it?
- Yeah.
Fifty mil. That will do it.
- That'll do it.
- These people are criminals!
Why do you have to label people?
- I hate labels!
- You shut up.
We cannot capitulate
in the war on crime.
I'd be voted out of office.
I don't think anyone wants that.
War on crime is fine with us.
It's business we're talking about here.
Do you have any idea
how many people we employ?
No. I never thought
about it like that.
Sharp kid.
So...
...your war on crime...
...you want to win it or what?
We're the only chance you have.
Listen to him.
He's got it all worked out.
Why do people do crimes?
- Why? Drugs. People do drugs.
- Because they want drugs.
The kind that cost too much.
Nuke gives high quality
at a cheap price.
If you get off our backs,
we'll make it cheaper.
And safer.
We don't shove our shit
down anybody's throat.
And we don't advertise it
like they do with cigarettes or booze.
So leave us alone...
...and anybody who wants it gets it.
So no more crimes.
You get to be the mayor
who cleaned up Detroit.
He's got a point.
Don't you think he's got a point?
Yeah, he's got a point.
What the hell is that?
Get out!
Marv, are...?
Cain.
Oh, wow.
You look great.
It'll take some getting used to...
...but it'll be great, Cain.
Lie still.
- I'm cold.
- You are going into shock.
I will call for a medical emergency unit.
Wait. No.
Don't leave me.
I won't leave you.
Who did this?
It was big.
Bigger than you.
It was Cain.
I'm gonna die.
You know what that's like, don't you?
It really sucks.
Yes.
Thirteen dead in what appears
to be a Nuke money massacre.
Among the victims,
two city councilmen.
Was the city trying to strike a deal
with the drug lords?
No comment!
I said, I have no comment!
No comments on these allegations.
These were men
who served this city tirelessly.
However, I make a promise
to the people of Detroit City...
...that no effort will be spared
to investigate this thoroughly!
But, Mr. Mayor, what about...?
I'm sorry. No more questions.
Our own Mayor Kuzak.
Now let's go live to Jess.
And here it is, the Civic Centrum, OCP's
100-story gift to the Motor City.
While debate continues
over OCP's hostile takeover...
...there's no denying
the mood down here is festive.
Citizens interviewed on the scene
expressed excitement and hope...
...that OCP will make good on its
promise of a better life in Detroit.
- Press!
- Sorry, folks, media only.
TV and press only.
You'll have to step back.
There he is!
Can OCP bring industry
back to Detroit?
Does OCP own the city?
Will you hold elections?
- Do we become OCP employees?
- Why not go to City Hall?
Just a minute.
I'll answer that, young lady.
City Hall is the decaying symbol
of mismanagement and corruption.
You get that?
This magnificent structure will be the seat
of leadership for the new Detroit.
And what better place
for a clean, fresh start?
And so, people of the press...
...city officials...
...in a few minutes
Omni Consumer Products...
...and the troubled city of Detroit...
...will join in a bold new venture.
Now I'd like to explain...
...just what this will mean.
Sometimes we just
have to start over...
...from scratch...
...to make things right.
And that's exactly
what we're going to do.
We're going to build
a brand-new city...
...where Detroit now stands.
An example...
...to the world.
My friends...
...welcome to our city
as it should be.
And as it will be,
in the hands of responsible...
...private enterprise.
And a special welcome...
...to Mayor Kuzak
and the outgoing administration.
We're not going anywhere.
Your Honor.
You'll have to tear down a lot
of houses to make that.
I mean, take away their homes!
We're going to raise towers
of glass and steel.
Every citizen will have a living unit,
safe, secure, and clean.
Now, please take your seat.
Won't be much room for neighborhoods.
Not like the kind we all grew up in.
Today neighborhoods are places
where bad things happen.
Don't be nostalgic.
What about democracy?
Nobody elected you.
Anyone can buy OCP stock...
...and own a piece of our city.
What could be more democratic
than that?
There's a lot of people in this town
that can't afford to buy your stock!
And they won't let you
get away with this.
You haven't been following the polls.
Sit down.
Sit down, mayor.
About a year ago
we gave this city Robocop.
I think he's worked out pretty well.
But things have become
rougher out there.
And now we need
a law enforcement unit...
...able to meet the enemy
on his own ground...
...and carrying enough firepower...
...to get the job done.
Ladies and gentlemen...
...with great pleasure...
...I give you...
...Robocop 2.
- Those bastards are maniacs!
- What's the matter?
I can't believe it.
It was them! They sent it!
Sent what?
Nothing.
There going to be a big call
for this unit.
And we'll make him right here in Detroit.
That means jobs
we can all be proud of.
And make "Made in America"...
...mean something again.
This single container...
...holds enough Nuke
to addict a city block.
A hundred of these
are produced every day...
...and sent to sweatshops...
...where urban slaves
prepare this poison...
...for our friends, our loved ones,
our children.
Now, I say...
...it's high time
we put an end to this plague.
Robocop 2 will seek out
every laboratory...
...every dealer,
and rid our city of Nuke.
Yes.
Things will be a lot quieter
with this boy around.
- What's wrong with him?
- It's nothing.
- Nothing at all.
- Turn him off.
I can't.
Cain! Let's step outside.
You! Get out of here!
You're obsolete!
That thing is a killer!
- It's not even armed! It's harmless!
- It's a killer, and I saw it!
- Take her out of here! Now!
- Let me go!
Behave yourselves!
- What's the deal here?
- Christ knows. Sounds like a war in there.
You're coming with me, Cain.
There he is!
- All right, get back!
- Are you jealous of the replacement?
This could look bad for OCP, Johnson.
Scramble the best spin team we have.
Ammo! Ammo!
Get down!
Hold your fire!
Hold your fire, damn it!
Let's get him out of here.
Watch his neck. He's hurt bad. Easy.
Shit!
I gotta get back.
Move it back! Move it back!
Let's give him what he wants.
Goodbye.
It's serious trouble.
So many dead and wounded.
There won't be trouble from the dead.
They'll have relatives. They always do.
- It'll be a feeding frenzy.
- It's only money.
- What about criminal proceedings?
- Well...
...we're looking at major indictments, sir.
Prison terms.
- What about me?
- You know we'll do whatever we can.
- That's not good enough.
- Sir?
What if this was the work
of one individual?
A person who had her own agenda, wasn't
in sync with the goals of our company?
Well, that usually works.
A woman who was not a team player.
Who violated our trust.
Easy, easy.
Well...
...we'd need some evidence
to support that.
Sir, whether it exists or not,
I know I can find it.
She did choose the brain, sir.
- Good thinking.
- Sir.
Thank God you're all right.
I was worried. I thought
it was going to hurt you.
It's over. It's all over.
I failed you.
Don't be hard on yourself.
Everything's going to be all right.
Johnson, that business
we were talking about.
Get right on it.
Yes, sir.
Just look at what they've done.
They are criminals.
OCP won't own this city for long.
And I'll see to that.
I'll take it to the streets
and the people.
What has it come to?
Businessmen can buy our rights
like stock?
You don't realize what we're losing!
- Right here, sir!
- Give us a statement!
Dozens are dead.
Is this your idea of a better life?
- Was this an experiment of some kind?
- He was crazy. How did it happen?
- Did you build it to take control?
- How do you account for this disaster?
Will OCP make reparations
to the victims?
That son of a bitch
is getting away with it.
We can't even touch him.
Patience, Lewis.
We're only human.