Please be seated, Star,
your hair's been ruffled.
Legs should be kept straight,
run quicker, somersault.
Yes... right...
You haven't put on your spectacles.
You guys look so bored.
Bored?
Let's ask Miss to take us out for a picnic.
Bring your girl-friends along.
With girls, we're fine.
Great, Miss.
Come on, help and light it.
It can't be lit.
Great...
You're too young to smoke. Throw it away!
I'll report to the police.
You're ruining your future.
Don't you smoke?
No, too expensive for me.
Don't believe me? Smell my mouth.
Are you silly?
Look, my teeth are clean.
Well, aren't you too young to have wisdom teeth?
How old are you?
I'm... 18 years old.
18?
Going on 19.
But you look mature.
Indeed, I'm ripe and ready to eat.
All classmates have girl-friends,
where's yours?
I don't have any.
I'm against dating during study.
It's a waste of time.
- You're cunning.
- Right.
- Really?
- Really.
I've seen your boy friend.
He often waits outside the school.
How do you know he's my boy friend?
I can tell.
He's quite good to you.
You're nosy
but I think he's not my type.
Right, you can't be reluctant to love somebody!
He's a cop. I hate cops.
Me too, I don't like them much.
What?
Annie, do me a favor.
Can I see your breast?
What?
One side will do.
Breast!
You lose nothing!
What a lousy Turtle!
You're dirty-mouthed.
Stay there!
Turtle Wong does look like a turtle.
Especially his head.
With a shell, he looks exactly like a turtle.
Turtle's result has dropped,
I must give him some tutorials.
But you're already my tutor.
You still have time?
You've progressed.
So, let me be his tutor.
I'm progressing. There should be no problem.
Can you manage?
Yes, as long as you're my tutor,
I can then manage to be his tutor. You see?
You see...
See?
This is my home, how's it?
Grandma, pour some tea.
Brother Star, make yourself at home.
Brother Star, which TV game you want to play?
PC or Nintendo?
Not now...
You're a nuisance. Pour some tea.
Have some tea.
Thanks, thanks.
You guys are classmates?
Yes.
Study together?
Classmates?
Yes...
You guys are classmates?
Yes, how do you know?
Stop it, you get back there.
Stupid.
Your Maria?
My Grandma.
Grandma? Where're your parents?
They seldom come here.
Brother Star, some great things for you.
Wow... you've got a lot of great things.
I'm coming here to be your tutor.
Don't be silly.
Grandma, try this.
It's free. What's the harm of trying?
OK.
Is it fun?
Try backhand, it's some interesting.
Try backhand and hit it at 90 degree.
Hold, let the head go up first.
Ready... Go.
Very good! Good hit.
Try with both hands. It's much powerful.
Hit his head. There, right...
Wow... crueler than me.
What about the Open Day?
You're responsible for the games.
The theme of the games is about fairy tales.
Snow White and the seven dwarfs.
What do you think...
Snow White and the seven dwarfs...
are sleeping in the same bed.
Seven guys, they've...
Enough. You're going too far.
Miss, these may not be something we like.
Why don't you ask for our opinion?
Yes...
Just ask Eleven.
Eleven, what do you like to play?
Video games.
The same for me.
Right.
Should we find something...
more interesting and exciting?
What about popguns?
Great...
Popgun is too violent.
It's quite violent
but violence is better than porn.
- Have your supper...
- Thanks.
Stupid boy, why don't you give a hand?
What are you doing?
Miss, have some soup.
Have a piece of pork chop.
Thanks. Uncle Tat.
Dad, you try some.
- No need...
- What about you?
You got high score this time.
Thank you Miss for giving me tutorials.
But Turtle has higher score than you do.
Really?
Look.
Thanks to me who gives him tutorials.
I instruct him to study everyday.
Isn't it great
if every student behaves like you?
Well, it's even greater
if every Miss looks like you.
There you go again.
Scissors.
Stone.
Paper.
I even couldn't hold her hand. Damn me.
Where's my kid gone?
Grandma, I'm not coming home for dinner.
See you.
Mobile phone, cool.
Brother Turtle, for this month.
Today is the beginning of the month?
Yes, look after me.
You should thank Brother Star.
Be smart. Brother Star hates dumb guys.
A waste of time.
Brother Star loves this book,
I treat this for next month.
Brother Turtle, this is to thank you.
Smart boy!
Something great to show you.
Calling you, buddy.
Why are you so thievish? Stay there.
I can too.
Brother Star,
you are silly to find means doing so.
You son-of-a-bitch.
Go away.
Open your mouth.
Let me off, Brother Star.
You keep running despite my shouting at you?
I didn't mean it.
What's your name?
Turtle Wong.
Where do you live?
Kowloon Tong.
The whole of Kowloon Tong?
Next to Ideal Hotel.
Turn around.
Hands on the head.
Stop playing tricks.
What's this?
Your phone.
I know.
So, why did you ask?
Mind your manner to cop.
What are these?
HK dollars.
I know.
So, why did you ask?
Am I not qualified to ask you?
Am I not qualified?
You're qualified...
Tell me what are these?
HK dollars.
I know.
So, why did you ask?
Son of a bitch, tell me.
Or I'll kick your brains out
with my Scissors Legs.
Don't do that, Brother Star,
the money is yours.
What's that to do with me?
Protection fee.
What protection fee?
I collect $30 from each classmate.
We're the richest and most powerful gang.
Most powerful gang?
Right, the Star Gang.
Big brother.
Listen, I'm not your big brother.
Take your money back. Go at once.
He's calling me, not you.
Call him, Grandpa.
Grandpa.
Good boy.
Brother, just forget it.
Let's not turn our place into anarchy
or we both will be in trouble.
I'm looking after you.
Anybody gives troubles to you...
means giving trouble to me. Right?
Right.
Want to get up a branch in my sphere?
We aren't Seven-eleven.
Such an idiot! Know nothing.
He's silly and knows nothing.
Let me see how powerful he is.
Sir Chow, Teddy Big arrives.
Seems to come here for you. Watch out.
Don't worry, it'll be fine.
Grandpa, come over here.
Don't call me Grandpa again, you guys.
Brother Star, Teddy Big, is coming to see you.
Who wants to see me?
He said he wanted to see the head.
That's you.
That's you. You're the head recently.
So what?
Hey, kid, stop.
Are you the big brother?
How are you, brother?
So, you're the head of the Star Gang,
how cheeky.
What did you say?
You didn't even inform me when you set up a gang
in my sphere.
What's your rank?
I'm second in my family,
I've got an elder sister
but she married a long time ago.
She's trying to emigrate.
How dare you talk to my big brother like that?
Cops're coming.
Kid, you're lucky.
Watch your steps,
you'll be less fortunate next time.
What are you doing?
Are you still the tutor of Star Chow?
Yes, though his performance is not that great,
but he's progressing a lot.
Do you know there's a new triad gang
in your school?
Triads again? I've told you before.
I won't tell you my students' particulars.
I'm not asking for that, I want to tell you.
The new triad gang in your school is
the Star Gang.
The leader is your student, Star Chow.
That's ridiculous, listen!
He's my student,
not a triad leader.
But he's a bad element in the school.
I say again,
"no bad elements in my school".
We're responsible for leading students
onto the right track.
Fine, forget it.
I don't want him to ruin our love.
Can you stop being his tutor?
I'm your boy-friend, I worry about you.
I teach students to trust those around him
and you ask me not to trust my students.
Hi.
Let's have our tutorial in the bedroom
because Dad's playing with bird
and I don't want to disturb him.
Are you alright, Miss?
Study in the bedroom.
Alright.
Having an affair?
What?
Have a walk outside.
Walk to where?
To Guangzhou if you like.
One for you, one for me.
You're wrong.
I'm right, yours is super thin.
- Really?
- Really.
I'm not the type you think and I'm not...
Hold it, she's a good girl.
Don't ruin her, 15 minutes will be enough.
Go, stop bullshitting.
Nuts.
Damn!
This is my home and you asked me to go out.
Are you father of Star Chow?
- Yes.
- He said Yes.
Hey, what are you doing?
It's only a gum. Chewing gum.
Start the lesson.
You think I'm an idiot?
I'm disappointed in you.
Help... help.
Uncle Tat. What's up?
How are you?
- Fine.
- Uncle Tat.
Stand aside.
Stop it, give me a chance.
Who asked you to come?
Teddy Big, please give me another chance.
Give you another chance to do what.
To go away.
Where you wanna go?
I don't know.
Go home and have a sleep. Your mom misses you.
You're no wonder the no. 1 in the SDU.
That's only basic skill.
Cops can't be as stupid as you.
You're right.
Dad, are you alright?
I'm fine, I'll rub some medicine oil...
- Let me rub...
- Good boy.
Stop pretending.
You're not a student and you're not his father.
We are indeed father and son.
Though I look younger than him,
he's my true son.
Actually, I can't tell you this
but I don't want to lie to you.
I'm a cop.
Sir Chow, everything's settled.
Do tell all.
I'm a cop and I'm in the school
to look into a case,
but I really want to help the kids.
I don't care and don't wanna know
what's between you,
but please stop fooling me, Sir Chow.
What are you doing?
Don't tell the others, OK?
Don't.
Will she tell the others?
She will, you go and kill her.
Yes, Sir!
Save your dirty words.
I should kill you first, save yourself!
OK...
Have I talk too much?
Do you believe I'll smash your head.
I do.
That's wonderful.
Yes...
You've been in the school for 2 months
and you've found nothing.
What have you done?
Tell me.
My way is like this.
First I have to communicate with
the students and teachers.
Yes, building a relationship.
No matter what.
Find out that pistol within a month
or both of you will be fired.
I don't care, I was born to be cheap,
I'm not ambitious.
I'll send you to work along the border.
Great... thanks a lot!
Don't be so rash.
You really scared us by your smash hands.
Yes, we're scared.
Please keep that smash hand away.
We are scared enough.
The students will do a good job
in the Open Day.
Great, last year was boring.
Alright.
Can you lend me your pager?
- What's for?
- Lend it to me.
The pager is mine...
Lend it to me.
The pager is...
I know, I'll return it to you afterwards Thanks.
If not for you,
I wouldn't have scored 80 in Geography.
the kids wouldn't have listened to me.
For you told me,
the goal of life shouldn't be for money.
Now I can tell you, my goal in life is you.
Sorry, for having lied to you in the past.
Sorry, because I'll always follow you,
Star Chow.
Hi.
Foolish! I'll keep the pager.
Hey, the pager is mine.
Why are you standing here?
You're blocking my way by standing here.
But the pager is mine...
Can you excuse me?
Somebody's chasing after you, run!
Turtle, go away.
Many against one?
- Sir, shall we start?
- Take a look first.
Don't go.
Damn!
Brother Star is in trouble.
Help him.
Let's start.
Cops, run away, the cops.
Brother Star, are you alright?
I'm fine, fine.
Sir, the fighting is in full swing over there.
What?
Report to us in the police station.
How are you? Are you alright?
I think I'm fine.
Take a rest.
Are you two alright?
Alright.
Have you seen Star Chow?
No.
No, go back and take a rest.
Have you seen Star Chow?
No, Miss.
Talk everything to my lawyer.
Turtle.
Miss, it hurts!
Have you seen Star Chow?
No, I don't know where they've taken him.
Have you seen Sir Wong?
Sir Wong... he...
Hey.
I'm not obliged to say anything.
But whatever I say may be used as an evidence.
I have the right to call my lawyer
and to have some tea,
but you've got no right to hang me up.
- It stinks.
- Hands off.
Want to beat my sole?
Treat me as a new comer?
Good, come. Beat my head instead.
Let's see who gets the trouble, come on.
Right.
I can beat you this time.
Miss Ho, you can't go inside.
Hey.
Are you alright? What are you doing?
Beating your own man? Actually...
Why are you here?
Crazy! Beat one's your man.
I've got something important to tell you.
Let me finish. Actually he's a...
Stop it.
Star, are you alright?
Ask if his hand is alright.
Go back and rub some oil
or your bones will crack.
Are you leaving?
They beat anybody no matter what. Go...
It's fine now, go.
You've made a mess instead of looking for
the pistol.
You will never get a promotion.
Maybe you don't want promotion, too.
Go away, get back to square one.
- Give me one more chance.
- Chance?
I've given you chances. Still ask for more?
Didn't I give you any chance?
I didn't say that.
We'll die together if you can't find the pistol.
Real Scissors Legs!?
No need to be that unhappy.
Very funny.
When is your birthday?
December 22, a party for me?
No, Mine is January 4.
Remember that my name is Tso Tat-Wah.
Giving a banquet?
No, this time it's either you or me.
There should be one who writes something
on the gravestone for the other.
Can you make it more explicit?
The arms?
I knew where Teddy Big put his arms.
Why didn't you say earlier?
I'm scared, big brother.
Call me Sir.
Attention.
Yes, Sir.
Do you know the consequence of not
telling the truth?
Yes, Sir.
So why didn't you tell?
- Afraid, Sir.
- I'm afraid too.
But we're the cops and must do our best.
Sorry, Sir.
Do you want to be an undercover forever?
Yes.
What?
It's interesting.
I'll accompany you when you die.
Stand straight and look at me.
Kiss you.
Son of a bitch.
It's this car park.
- It's here.
- Which car?
- How do I know?
- So?
Look into every car.
You're stupid.
Some noise outside. Go out and have a look.
Go in and have a look.
Anything?
Nothing.
So what's the noise?
Check around.
Great.
They're all long guns.
This one is short. This's cop's pistol.
Yes, this one...
What are you doing?
Bring them all to the police station.
The car will carry them. Put them down.
- Finished?
- Finished.
I haven't got into the car.
I'm here... hey...
Excuse me, what problem?
Everything's under control, don't worry, OK?
Boss, time to pee...
I'll show you something great afterwards.
You call me this early,
please show me something great.
Of course, something great.
Something great?
Keep it.
I've never thought it'd be back, smart boy.
- Stop crying. More to come.
- More?
Wake up, hey.
Wow... where did you find it?
It's really great before my retirement.
I can be the governor if I don't retire.
Wait a few more seconds.
Smart Star Chow, you've moved my arms?
Want to hear your dad's voice?
Kid. I'm fine so far, but...
Listen, if you want to see your dad,
meet me at the back of the school
in half an hour.
Remember, no tricks.
Hey, the foreigner's getting impatient
for waiting half day.
I'm calling him. Be more patient.
Ask him to shut up.
He'll see the guns in half an hour.
Why are you so nervous?
The guns are with me.
Call the SDU if necessary.
They can manage.
Then Uncle Tat will be more dangerous.
Remember he's a cop and an undercover.
He should know. He's old to suffer.
Hey, I know what you wanna do,
wanna show off again?
Don't. I'd rather kill you myself than
letting others kill you.
Hey. This is a kind pistol.
Don't.
It hasn't been used for more than 30 years.
Don't take it away. What you doing?
Driving away?
Drive if you have the guts.
Don't come back if you have the guts.
Young guys nowadays are so brave.
Where are the guns?
The weapons are there.
Release my dad.
Follow me...
Star, I haven't...
Go ahead.
What smell? It's gasoline.
Burn the banknotes...
It can't be fired! Isn't it too kind?
Go away!
Catch him!
Why coming back to school?
Wanna let your classmates to be in danger?
Today is a public holiday.
Shit, nobody's there to help then.
Higher. Hey... what are you playing? Stop...
What? Popgun again? Give us a hand.
Hold it, help me.
You should help too. Hurry.
What happened to Brother Star?
He said he'd help us.
He still hasn't showed up.
Brother Star must have been arrested by police.
You're silly. Miss Ho's seen him.
Really?
Miss Ho! Is brother Star alright?
Alright.
I'm right. Stop bullshitting.
You look dull. Are you alright?
I'm fine.
So many people here.
Why are you here? Today's holiday.
Go away. It's dangerous.
Go quickly.
Uncle Tat can run that fast.
- Come closer.
- Wait.
Damn it.
Have you seen Star Chow?
- No.
- Inside The maze.
Why looking for him?
None of your business!
Stay away.
Keep an eye on the students. Come here!
Attention please, if trapped inside the maze
and cannot find the way out.
Please shout for help!
That way.
Hey... what do you want?
None of your business. Don't make a sound.
Babe, are you scared?
Then you won't be scared.
Finished.
Miss Leung, call the police. Hurry.
Let's go and save Brother Star.
Don't. They've got pistols.
I've got one too.
Don't go...
- What are You doing?
- Wanna die?
Follow me.
- Hey, wait.
- Quick!
You go first.
That's the entrance, genius.
How do I know? Every door looks the same.
So you have to follow me. Stupid.
Here we're.
Call the boss right away.
What about you?
A lot of kids are there. I must go back.
But the pistol can't work.
I can manage.
No, I must stay and help you.
Seek helpers! You're too old to help.
Hey...
Have you seen him?
No.
You go that way. The rest follows me.
Turn left.
Keep on turn left, left.
Hands up. Don't move.
I've asked you not to move.
Go... quickly.
Kin's shot. Take him away.
Quickly. Damn it.
Go, wanna die?
Go... that way... that way.
Go... you kid...
Squat! Squat down!
That way, go.
- Quicker.
- I'll kill you with a shot.
Move!
No again? You didn't leave me one?
You're cruel to me.
- Brother Star.
Star Chow, listen, the kids are in my hands.
I'll give you 5 minutes.
If you don't come out, I'll kill them all.
Brother Star, they mean it.
Stop it... Don't make sound. Stay calm.
Do you hear me?
What are you best at doing?
We'll die this time.
Damn you. Shut up!
Listen. What are you best at doing?
Flirting.
What's besides flirting?
Nothing.
You're best at having fun.
You flirt because you want to have fun too,
Not because you want to marry.
OK, let's have fun with them,
And try to play a game
but we can't lose this game,
Or somebody will die.
Have you played such an exciting game?
No.
But we'll by no means lose.
All we have to do is to cooperate.
I'm the supervisor and you two listen to me.
We are in a favorable situation.
We'll sure win. Must be confident.
Are you confident?
- Yes...
- Good! Start!
Six of them. Give me any weapons.
Popgun.
Not popgun. I said no popguns.
This is a real gun with 5 bullets.
Only 5 bullets?
Star Chow, come out quickly.
Let's bet. Mark the time.
Good. Do as we planned, clear?
Star Chow, come out!
You think I'm kidding?
You hear me? I'll kill them one by one.
20 seconds left.
Come out!
Come out... or I'll kill them one by one...
Come out
or I'll blow their brains off.
Do you believe me?
So you don't believe me.
Good.
Run... quickly.
Fire... fire if you have the guts...
I'm afraid you don't have the guts.
She's the first to die.
Go ahead. That's none of my business.
Wanna cover you? You'll be shot anyway.
You know what will happen. Come.
You think I'll be scared?
I can kill you with only one shot.
Fire...
- I'll.
- Go ahead...
I count to 3 and let's fire together.
1,2,3... OK, sorry.
It's my fault, sorry.
You're no match for me.
Why taking this so seriously?
Guns down.
Go back...
Where's the money?
Not with me.
Here's the money.
Put the pistol down!
Do you dare?
Or I'll burn all the banknotes
and we'll all have troubles.
Got a lighter?
You don't have any?
No, how about you?
No.
Brother Teddy, can I borrow your lighter?
You asked for it!
Big Brother... watch out, go quickly.
So cool!
How dare you firing back at me?
Come out at once!
Wanna kill me? Come out...
Don't fire!
Guns down!
Boss.
Bingo!
Kid, I'm not the leader of the Star Gang.
I'm one of the Royal HK Police Force
also known as Scissors Legs.
Remember that!
Boss.
You'll leave scars on my pistol if you throw it.
I have no choice... Your pistol can't work!
I've told you this is a kind pistol.
You want to use it to kill? How dare you?
But you're so smart
to shot him quite accurately,
and maintain the police's reputation.
School of Police hasn't taught me this.
I learnt it in this school.
The men're coming. I'm leaving.
Don't tell them I've been here.
Thanks for arresting them.
Chief Inspector Chow.
- What?
- Chief Inspector?
When I say you are, you are.
Shouldn't I be the Chief Superintendent?
Brother Star.
Do come and have tea some time.
Pass this mobile to you, do call me.
I'll come back right after it rings.
- Take care.
Brother Star, how lucky you are!
Yes...
What are you waiting for!?