Wow!
That's just what I thought
Just a matter of time.
Everyone goes nuts here
Wow!
Oh... No!
You saw it, didn't you?
Here
You live with Alphonse, don't you?
Said he'd never come back
When you shower,
don't miss a spot
Fabulous!
Come on, Young-woo.
Shower when you can
Hurry up!
Scrub every part of the body...
Come on, hurry.
Before the rain stops
Aren't you sick of gazing at them?
Visibility is better after the rain
What's the point?
It's just a hobby
Oh, a hobby... Gotta take a piss
You got a lot of hobbies, huh?
Looking at stars... following
and yelling at a jet, going crazy...
Did you see that!
My pants!
Is it the antler of a deer?
No, it's not
So chilly!
Get away, you bad boy.
You do nothing but eat
What are you doing?
I found it in the storage
Don't bother
- We've got an electric stove
- Why not?
It goes well with the place
We can make tea, too
Make tea?
You are serious about
living here, aren't you?
Yeah, yeah, bury your bones here
When the winter's over,
I'm out of here
shouting hooray
It's not something new
Take a look
It sure looks different today
When familiar things look different,
they say it's time
How much time do I have left?
How much more do you want?
Wish I could see him before I die
It's so cold out there
I wonder where he...
Stop it
Let's drop it, okay?
I can't
You know what?
That's what got you sick!
I miss him so much
If only I could see him once
We've been good all our lives
Why do we have to suffer?
You're not sick, but senile!
Honey, I can't find him
Keep looking
No sign of him!
Come help me find him
Can't you see the line?
I can't leave now
Our son is more important!
You didn't even try
I pity you for not knowing...
what's really precious
Hot!
Christmas always finds its way back
And it's a white Christmas
White my ass!
Young-woo, let's drink.
It's Christmas Eve
What does the snow
bring to your mind?
That it's snowing
"It's snowing"?
I...
God, it's snowing a lot
It reminds me of my first love
She loved it when it snowed
Said she wanted to watch it snow
together until we die
3 weeks after I joined the army,
she sent me a Dear John letter
Hey
So I decided not to trust gals
who love snow
You know why?
Because their words melt away,
as does the snow
Even the melted snow vanishes
as people walk on it
That's why they are not trustworthy
Don't you have any memories
that the snow brings back?
No, nothing
I thought so.
It'd be strange if you did
What do you think about
when you look at stars?
That they're hung in the sky
"They're hung in the sky"
Should I keep talking or what?
So, you're telling me
you've never been in love?
What kind of life is that?
Well, what do I care?
Live like your master, Alphonse
I like you a lot
cause you're so much like a dog
Stop staring at me
Why am I so miserable
on Christmas
That's enough
Come on, tell me honestly
You don't have anyone
you wanna frolic with in the snow?
No
- Shit
- Are you okay?
Okay, Ok
No girl has ever loved you?
No
Look at me!
Check it out, dude
It's... Hot!
You don't feel anything
when it snows?
No
The whole world is white.
No feelings at all?
No
- Fuck me!
- What?
Think about it
It's been snowing all day,
and you say nothing but "No"
That drives me nuts.
Why is the snow white then?
Why not black, red, blue, or yellow?
How could you have no feelings
about that damned white snow?
Tell you what
Let's go snow-sledding tomorrow
if it clears up
Snow-sledding?
Who do you think I am, Rudolph?!
I hate snow!
I hate Christmas.
I'm a freaking Buddhist
Stop snowing!
Hon... Honey!
Finally finished
This is it.
When the snow melts away,
Will the walls around
your heart collapse as well?
You're good at answering.
Don't fail me now
They won't
You're unbelievable
Alphonse, take care
Don't eat too much, okay?
I'm really going.
I'm leaving before I go mad
Alphonse!
Hey!
Wait up!
Aaak! Aaak!
Hey, you!
What are you doing here?
Gosh, I feel alive again
I came hiking and got stuck
in the snow
How long have you been here?
A while
This is like a mountain cottage
I wouldn't mind living here
Not for too long, though
A week
A month at the longest
Can hikers stay here?
This is my workplace
It gets dark early up here
Thanks for the tea
It'll be nightfall soon
Play, movie
Concert, play, movie
Mrs.
- By any chance, are you into art?
- Art?
Excuse me
Aren't you the lady from the store?
What... what store?
You must be mistaken
YoungChun >
< WolDong
Where have you been?
I got lost
I'm so cold
The fire has died
Good morning
Alphonse
You were out of reach
Said he'd never come back
Then I figured out
that you were far away
But I didn't stop waiting
Did you get back at that dog?
It carries too much sentimental value
You know what?
I'm hungry...
I didn't have lunch
Okay
- Go ahead
- Yummy!
Still, I have no problem
using a scalpel
I know
What are those?
They're all stars?
Looks like
salt spilt on the table
God, it's beautiful
Feels like we're trapped inside a star
That's the Little Dipper, right?
Every time I see it
I think of you
What constellation
do I remind you of?
Never thought about it
Really?
Are you sure?
I'm leaving
It's freezing out there
If I freeze to death
give me a nice funeral
Hold on
There's one
Please sit
What is it?
You remind me of...
It's Andromeda
Andromeda was
a princess of Ethiopia
It has only happy stars with it
She was beautiful
and warm-hearted
What do you say?
A lot like you, huh?
Not interesting?
Are you okay?
Let's go!
Come on, I'll race you!
Soo-yeon!
Soo-yeon, are you okay?
No, don't pull it out
Let me carry you
Hang on
Hang in there
Stay with me, Soo-yeon
We're almost there
We're home
Soo-yeon, Soo-yeon
I'll go fetch a doctor
Keep yourself from falling asleep
Pick up, Please...
Alphonse, Come on!
Stay by her side, understand?
Come on, go
Alphonse...
There's no point
Don't be stubborn with me
I thought there was no illness
you couldn't fix
Or you don't want to
How can you be saying that?
You're so mean
Tell me
Don't you miss our son?
I looked everywhere for it
You've been hiding it?
I'm sure
he's a sweet person after you
No, he takes after you
A birthmark behind his ear
just like yours
I think my time's up
The thought of leaving you
breaks my heart
But it's more painful to live,
missing him
Don't skip your medicine
I think my heart is failing me
I'm ready
Let me rest in peace
If you find our son after I die...
please tell him
that I missed him
Honey...
I'm so sorry
I'd wanted to tell you that
all these years
I brought this upon myself
losing everyone I care for
We'll be reunited before long
I'll follow your steps soon
Nurse Kim,
Thank you for while
The Hospital closed now...
You're a doctor, right?
At the peak...
You have to save her
We don't have much time.
We must go now
Catch your breath first, son
You have to save her
The only girl I've given my heart
is dying up there
Please, you must save her.
I'm begging you
Please, doctor
Are you listening?
Please!
We don't have much time
We've got to go now!
I've just lost my lifetime love
And you're asking me save yours
Doctor?
Let's take a break
No time to waste.
I'll carry you on my back
You're desperate.
Lead the way, I'll walk
Never been on anyone's back.
It feels good, though
Why's that?
You smell good
Let your parents experience it
Wish I could.
I don't have parents
So many stars tonight
I had a son long ago
He was so fascinated by stars
It was as starry then
I think about my parents
looking at stars
Let's... take a break
Don't you want to save
the girl you love?
Keep walking
Come on, a little further
In here
Soo-yeon?
- What are you looking at?
- Huh?
- Put the kettle on
- Okay
Thank you so much, doctor
Don't worry
You didn't carry me for nothing
I need to rest
Doctor
Stars are so bright tonight
Has she come to?
Not yet
She'll be fine
I need to head back
It's too late, and the snow
is knee-high out there
You hurried me up here...
to save the girl you love
I need to get back to the girl
that I've loved all my life
You're so big now
Look at that star!
Soo-yeon?
Who treated me?
Stars...
Stars?
Yes
The stars came down and gone
I see...
Don't just stand there
Come closer... and hold my hand