Calm down, Miss.
I want to see him.
Where's he?
Mr. Hung is on his way.
Please calm down.
I want him here right away.
There she is, Mr. Hung.
Susan
Tiger!
What are you doing?
Is this a threat?
No.
I'm just hurt!
You know I'm called The Heartbreaker.
This was bound to happen.
What did you expect?
Don't hurt me.
Forget it. Where's the negotiator?
She's over there.
Susan!
Tiger...
She talked to the stewardess,
and learned you were dating her.
I think she's also your girlfriend.
What should I do? Who's in charge?
Over there.
Susan!
Tiger...
I thinks she's also your girlfriend.
3 people trying to kill themselves.
Where's the fire chief?
There.
Tiger.
Susan...
I think...
You're right. She's also my girlfriend.
What should we do?
- Tiger...
Quiet!
Let me think.
Miss.
You seem to be
the only rational girl here.
Any advise?
Are you hitting on me?
Pretty girl, you're smart!
You dated me already.
I did? When?
When I was 16.
You dumped me after 7 days.
You know how hurt I was?
You're...
Susan!
Did you take it well?
No.
I slashed my wrist and
overdosed on sleeping pills.
What are you doing?
Getting a tan.
Getting a tan?
Can't you see what's going on here?
What's your name?
- Susan
- What?
Susan!
You...
What's your number?
99172717
What kind of sunscreen do you use?
Nivia.
Try Lancome.
This place is a mess.
You should come to my house.
- I got a tanning bed.
- Where's your place?
You can do anything you want there.
Hi doc.
Still the same?
Can't believe
what those girls did to my body.
I'm over-exhausted.
Nothing to do with them.
It's because you party too much.
Your body is worn out.
You have to help me.
I've done everything I can.
Try Chinese doctor.
I did. They told me
Western medicine would help.
Then we have to try something extreme.
How extreme?
There are 3 places in this world
that can cure you.
Which 3?
One is Shaolin, the other is Wudan.
But they won't help people like you.
Why?
You're guilty of lust.
What's the third place?
This place was very well respected
in the past.
But today it's lost its influence
and forgotten by most people...
What's the name?
Think!
Omei!
Isn't Omei sect all women?
They're your employees in China.
Mr. Hung?
Where's Omei's representative?
Get her.
Over here.
Tiger Hung is known as
The Heartbreaker.
He has to be good-looking.
Don't bother to ask the ugly people.
What's your name?
May.
Which one of you is Mr. Hung?
Come!
Here!
Wise up!
Can't believe we have to walk.
How far are we from the top?
Almost there.
No way. Who will it be?
What?
Who will carry me?
Hurry.
Lower.
What's that?
Cable car.
Where is it going?
Top of the mountain.
Why aren't we on it?
It's expensive. 80 dollars per head.
That's 400 dollars for all of us.
It's just a few more steps.
A few more steps?
Shit! More stairs?
This is a mountain.
Shit!
Forget it.
Go get your Master.
I am the Master.
You?
I'm the temp.
Something happened here.
What? Everyone is dead?
Mr. Hung,
please promise me one thing.
Don't hit on my sisters.
We're simple people.
I can get girls anywhere.
Why would I come this far to do it?
A promise is a promise.
All clear!
What happened to your face?
3rd Sister told me
this would keep us safe.
Shit! I'm not interested
in mountain people.
So are my men.
Of course...
Thanks for the assurance.
I'll show you your room.
Prepare dinner for him.
Yes.
What's wrong with him?
How can he compare us
to mountain people?
The one in yellow shirt is pretty.
The one behind the tree
is very cute.
Fourth Sister is the best.
Third Sister is better.
She's mine.
Forget it. Boss already set his eyes
on both of them.
Didn't you notice?
You can forget about the other girls.
Boss will take them all.
We won't have a chance.
This way.
You'll stay here until you're cured.
Shit!
Enjoy.
Like the food?
Shit!
What does "shit" mean?
It means Omei is a bunch of crap!
Good thing I asked.
It'll improve my English.
May.
What does "shit" mean?
It means Omei is a bunch of crap.
What?
May, you've got good temper.
If Big Sister returns, they'll be dead.
If Big Sister returns, we'll all be dead.
Keep practicing your sword.
Eat more.
Keep practicing.
Put your clothes on.
What's wrong?
Let's go!
We're leaving.
What's wrong, boss?
This place is a fraud.
I don't want some quack doctor
killing me.
The cable car has stopped running.
I don't care. I'm leaving!
I got cash. I'll find a way. Let's go!
I got money!
Start the cable car!
So what? Leave or I'll let the dogs out!
Let's go, boss.
It's freezing.
No! We'll walk.
Who will it be?
Boss!
Hurry.
Where are you going?
Boss, it's just one night.
At least we have a place to stay.
Omei is a fraud!
Put me down!
Boss...
Incredible.
It's not like they can fly.
Boss.
Isn't that amazing?
Let's go back first.
We don't see it.
There isn't any.
But I saw it in my dream.
They used wireworks.
They must've took it down already.
Let's try her.
Easy on the lady.
Don't hurt her face.
Sisters!
Why are you here?
What is it?
They snuck up on me.
May!
I'm sorry.
We're losing the fat one!
You two must train harder.
- I'm sorry.
- What happened?
What?
I'm sorry.
You should never play around
like this again.
Boss, Omei is for real!
Your kidney is fine.
No internal injury.
Show me your tongue.
What's wrong with you?
You're in really bad shape.
You're better off dead.
Are you serious?
Heart.
Liver.
Spleen.
Lung.
Kidney.
This tree can cure me?
It has precious herbal essence.
It's over 500 years old.
This tree reminds me of a girl.
She had legs bigger than the tree trunk.
Another girl had great legs,
but her skin felt like tree bark.
Ants!
A big nest!
You're in luck!
Omei ants are a great cure!
They're in my pants!
They're moving upward.
Let them be.
They bit me!
They're in my crotch.
They're healing you. Let them be.
That's a lot of needles.
I'm like a hedgehog.
More needles give better result.
I knew a girl
who had a hedgehog hairstyle.
It made her look like a pig.
It was ugly!
But she had a great body.
So I made my move.
But her face kept getting in the way.
When I was with her,
I always had the urge
to cover her face with a pillow case.
It hurts.
The next batch of needles will hurt.
Acupuncture shouldn't hurt.
Omei style is different.
It'll give faster result.
It hurts!
Ouch!
Don't look under Grand Master's skirt!
I can't control the urge.
I just want to see what's underneath it.
Once when I saw a guy wearing a kilt,
I almost did the same thing.
You're really sick.
You don't have to cure this disease.
What's for today?
I'll teach you Revitalization Exercise.
Revitalization?
Perfect!
Can't follow?
Can't even see it.
I know something simpler,
but its 20% less effective.
Better than nothing!
Kneel down.
Slap yourself.
Slap here.
And here.
Do I start with the left hand?
Doesn't matter, just don't miss your face.
When do I stop?
Until your face is swollen.
But I'll look ugly.
Want to try the harder exercise?
I'll never be able to learn that.
Grand Mater must've been a pretty girl.
She looks like a 36G.
Hit your mouth.
It's equally effective.
How will I talk?
You'll find ways.
I had this really hot girlfriend.
She had a 42G body,
but got short legs.
The other one was just the opposite.
She had long legs,
but small breast.
Would be great to see her again.
Forgot to slap myself.
A few more slaps.
It's painful.
It hurts!
Have you found it?
I can't pee...
Found it.
This will release your bladder
right away.
I remember this other girlfriend.
- How fast did you say?
- Right away.
You can't out-run it.
Don't be embarrassed, you're ill.
This is humiliating.
I remember this other girlfriend.
She would wet herself when she cries.
Am I...
I found another cure!
What is it?
It cures constipation.
This day had to come.
Big Sister has lost it.
There's only 23 of us,
but she left 29 hand prints.
Ones on the right are us.
Ones on the left are our patients.
And the one on top?
That's Big Sister herself.
She plans to die together with us.
How about the footprint?
That's how she flew up there.
Big Sister is wearing Nike.
The other one is Adidas.
She must've found them at junk yard.
Big Sister is down in luck.
Why would a Omei Master
Iose her mind over a man?
Master, emergency!
Emergency!
I'm in pain.
Am I poisoned?
Go get their luggage.
What for?
Omei is in trouble.
No time to play with you.
I'll cure you now.
Boss!
Omei Needle!
Stay back!
Boss.
How do you feel?
One dosage a day. You'll be fine.
Go now.
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
What were you doing to me before?
Nothing.
They were just pranks
to make you pay for
what you did to women.
Screw you!
Forget it.
She saved your life.
See how you've recovered?
- Thank you.
How should I cook the medicine?
You have to tell me!
Use 3 cups of water.
How long do I cook it?
Until there's one cup of water left!
Thanks!
Don't mention it.
It's windy.
Let's go in.
Big Sister is here. Attack formation!
It's raining. Let's go in.
Don't!
Big Sister...
Don't call me that.
When Grand Master expelled me
from Omei,
I took an oath
to die together with Omei.
Today is Master's funeral anniversary.
We'll all die together.
I'm kill myself first.
Then I'll kill you one by one.
Don't, Big Sister.
Scared? When Master expelled me...
She never expelled you.
It was you who expelled her.
Why did I do that?
Master gave up her position.
You became the new Master.
Me?
You still are today.
I'm just the temp.
Why did I expel the Master?
You fell in love with a womanizer.
He broke your heart.
Master tried to comfort you.
But you couldn't let go.
You felt ashamed for
being a Omei disciple.
Then you lost your mind.
You told Master to leave.
When Master took you
to see a psychiatrist,
you expelled her from Omei.
How did the Master die?
She was 120 years old.
I killed her...
She died of natural cause.
Will you listen to me?
I've killed the Master.
I'll continue my killing spree.
Then I'll kill myself.
Heartbreak Sword Technique is
the only way to beat me.
Heartbreak Sword Technique!
"One Night Stand"!
Too slow!
"Bitter Argument"!
No power! No real emotion!
"Mixed Emotion"!
You call this "Mixed Emotion"?
Have you ever been in love?
"Deep Sorrow"!
Heartbreak Sword Technique...
...requires true heartache.
I'll show you how it's done!
Why am I here?
You came to kill us.
My condition is getting worse.
You should seek help.
Quiet!
Who knows how long
I'll stay conscious?
Omei disciple May!
As Omei's 28th Master,
I order you to perfect
Heartbreak Sword Technique
and to become the new Master.
You have to stop me
or Omei will perish.
You never know what I'll do.
What are you doing?
I'll show you how Heartbreak
Sword Technique is done!
You're not worth my time.
I'll give you one month to practice.
When I return I'll finish the job!
You'll all be my victims!
Scared?
What is "One Night Stand"?
What is "Mixed Emotions"?
"What is "Deep Sorrow"?
If the first 7 moves are associated
with heartache,
why is the last move called
"Eternal Harmony"?
Why is the Grand Master smiling?
What makes her smile?
Why is love so deep?
Love can't be studied.
Love needs to be experienced.
Big Sister was right.
You need to experience heartache
to perfect your training.
Practice only perfect your form,
but there's no soul.
I know.
I'll do anything.
But time is running out.
Where do I find someone
to fall in love with
and to break my heart?
Don't worry.
You have 3 options.
One is Leonard Dicaprio
One is Takuya Kimura.
But they can't help you.
Why?
You don't speak their language.
And they can't speak Chinese.
What's my third option?
The love we have is precious.
May it last 1 billion light years.
Doesn't light year measure distance?
Whatever.
Give me!
Tiger gave me this.
Tiger is mine!
May, Tiger is your only option.
Boss, look who's here.
Make way.
You look busy. I'll come tomorrow.
I'm like this every day.
Entertain the girls.
Cutie!
It's a beach party!
Understood.
Came to see me?
What did you do to your hair?
You're wearing a skirt?
Are you called The Heartbreaker?
What did you tell them?
Something cruel and mean.
What is it?
They're all different.
Every relationship has its taboo.
I'm here asking you for a favor.
How dare you!
After what your "therapy" did to me?
I know you want to get even with me.
But this is serious.
Just kidding.
It's already behind me.
You're my savior.
This beach party wouldn't exist
without your help.
So what's so serious?
You know, I'm the temporary Master.
My Big Sister Misery...
No problem. Understood.
You do?
The name Misery means
she's heartbroken.
She's probably a kung fu master.
You're obviously not her match.
As the temporary Master,
You must beat Misery to protect Omei.
Omei must have a way to stop Misery.
But it isn't easy to learn.
Must be something unusual.
What am I good at?
I only know how to break girl's heart.
I've seen your Grand Master's statue.
She looked graceful.
She was holding a sword in her hand.
So it must be a sword technique.
Therefore, you want me to hurt you,
to perfect Heartbreak Sword Technique!
Will you help me?
Got a place to stay?
- Not yet.
- Come.
Before breaking my heart,
will you date me?
Sure.
But I can't hold hand.
No problem.
No embrace, no kissing.
I can't sleep with you.
Of course not.
You can still break my heart?
Sure.
You're really incredible!
Awful.
What is this?
This is unacceptable.
Let's go.
Do you know who she is?
She's my savior!
Damn!
Let's go.
This room is awful.
No... It's great.
Thank you.
This is for you two.
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
I'm no good!
Don't' say that.
I appreciate everything you did.
I am helping you
for a selfish reason.
The first night at Omei,
when I saw you flying in the air,
I fell in love with you.
Are you serious?
It was love at first sight.
Don't tease me.
I'm tired. I'm going to the bathroom.
When I first met you at Omei,
I dreamt of our reunion.
I can give up my fortune for you.
Just pay me 10K everyday.
Ever since leaving Omei,
I dreamt of seeing you again.
If you will marry me,
I will give you my mansion.
Long time no see
I love you forever,
why are you laughing at me?
Long time no see
I love me, you love me or not...
I love you. Do you love me?
I don't understand English.
What does the last part mean?
I'll sing it again in Chinese.
Long time no see.
I love you forever, you...
Damn! It's midnight.
What's wrong?
- I'm going.
- You are?
If I don't get home by midnight,
My Ferrari will turn into a pumpkin.
You're leaving?
Bye.
I forgot something.
What?
Did you just kiss me?
You promised you wouldn't.
It'll hurt me more?
It's 4.
You're coming over? Why?
You miss me?
What do I think?
I don't know.
Do whatever you want. I'll wait.
Please leave me a message.
At around 5 this morning,
Police found a damaged Ferrari
at Hung Min Rd...
The driver could not be found.
According to the police,
The car belongs to millionaire
Tiger Hung, a.k.a. The Heartbreaker.
The incident is being investigated.
Police are trying to contact Mr. Hung.
Who are you?
I crashed my car.
Why are you hurt?
Your car looked fine.
That's why the car is expensive.
It protects itself, not the driver.
Just kidding. I'm okay.
See?
It's fake.
You can rub it off.
Try it.
See?
Here?
That's real.
Does it hurt?
Did your heart ache?
Great! Love has struck you.
That fast!
You don't have much time
left for the duel.
How about what happened last night?
All real emotions.
I got you a credit card.
Go buy some nice clothes.
You need to look pretty.
Why?
I'm taking you to see my parents.
Is it necessary?
The more things we do,
the more it'll hurt.
My parents.
Misery.
Uncle, Auntie.
A beautiful girl.
We've never met Tiger's girlfriends.
We didn't prepare anything.
Here's your gift.
No.
It's okay, we're family.
You're such a darling.
I have a bracelet for you.
Take your time.
She's pretty.
You want to get her drunk?
70%?
80% drunk.
It's done.
May, let's drink.
Come on.
I can't drink, uncle.
It's okay.
Cheers.
Drink.
My turn.
Cheers.
Race 1 Northern Blaze.
Race 2 Tincan.
Race 3 Blonde Okie.
Race 4 Lightning High.
Fifty Grand on each race, thanks.
Enjoy.
- Let's eat.
- Drink!
- Cheers!
- 82 LaFite
- Let's eat.
You have to try this.
Vintage Mow Tai. Cheers!
Cheers!
She said she can't drink...
But she finished everything!
I'm not scared.
Cheers!
Done! She's 80% drunk.
She said she can't drink...
She's really something.
She's a martial artist.
No wonder.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Thanks.
Leaving?
Yes.
Where's your parents?
You met them already.
How did I behave?
Did they like me?
You knocked them out.
That's great.
Where are we going?
Fei Ngo Mountain!
This is Fei Ngo Mountain?
Omei moutain is a sacred ground.
So is Fei Ngo Mountain.
They're sacred for different reasons.
Of course.
One is famous for martial arts,
the other for sightseeing.
Why are the cars moving funny?
It's difficult to explain.
Why don't I demonstrate?
First you lower the girl's seat.
Then the driver will climb over.
I want to go back to the hotel.
Sure!
I want to take a shower.
No need.
Come on!
Noodle?
I want to take a shower.
No need.
Lobster claw?
I want to take a shower.
Why is this lobster noodle here?
I saw you too busy betting horses to eat,
so I got you something.
I want to take a shower.
Go ahead.
It's delicious.
You want some?
You didn't have dinner either.
What's wrong?
I can't sleep with you.
Do you want me to hurt you?
You have to beat Misery.
I can't do it.
This is bad.
I'm at a loss.
I never hurt anyone
without sleeping with her.
I warned you before:
No kiss, no sleeping together.
And you promised!
Men always say yes.
What now?
Then...
Let's just get it over with.
No need to shower...
No!
What now?
We'll pretend we've done it.
How?
I'll show you.
Here.
So?
You got it all wrong.
You're inexperienced.
I'll show you. Come...
Let's say I'm you.
First close your eyes.
Then gasp with great satisfaction.
Do it 4 or 5 times, then smile.
Slowly turn your head over
and look at your lover.
Got it?
You try it.
First close my eyes.
Then gasp with great satisfaction.
Do it 4 or 5 times.
Then smile.
Slowly turn my head over.
And look at my lover.
You ruined it!
It's like this after marriage.
But this is our first time.
The first time I'll hold you in my arms
and talk all night
until day breaks.
What do we talk about?
Just nonsense.
But women will remember it
the rest of their lives.
How about guys?
We forget after waking up.
Then don't go to sleep.
But I'll get hungry.
No problem. Here is...
Lobster noodle.
It's finished.
What about me?
I asked you, but you didn't reply.
It's okay.
I also have... fried noodle.
It tastes better with chili sauce.
Got it!
How is it done?
The first night we would feed each other.
The second night we'll fight for the food.
Feed me first!
Here you go.
When I first met you at Omei...
Tiger, I bought you many things.
Shirts, pants, shoes, and socks.
Are you happy?
I'm in a great mood.
- Really?
- Also...
I bought you underwear.
First love is like this.
Calling Fatty, subject is coming down.
Calling boss,
subject is heading your way.
What are you doing?
What have I promised you?
That you'll help me.
To do what?
To perfect Heartbreak Sword Technique.
How?
By breaking my heart.
Where's she?
Find her!
Take the elevator!
What's wrong with you?
I'm scared?
Scared?
I'm scared of getting hurt.
Isn't that what you want?
How about not so fast?
I want the good times last longer.
You're running out of time!
Where's your dedication?
Say something!
I want to go back to the hotel.
No. You're coming to my place.
Why?
So I'll have you cornered!
Master!
Open up, May!
Don't you want to be heartbroken?
No... I'm scared.
Damn!
Where's the key?
- Here.
- Hurry!
Get her!
Don't go anywhere.
Stop her, Ben!
Where's she?
What's wrong?
Something got into my eyes.
Go wash them.
It's dusty down there.
You think I don't know?
Stop running around.
I won't next time.
I'm not feeling any pain.
Actually I think it's funny.
Why?
You don't know how to hurt me.
What do you mean? Where's the girl?
You all right?
She's having an asthma attack.
Let me...
Relax.
Done!
You house is dusty.
I won't get under the bed again!
Pay her...
Time is running out.
Think of something.
Get up!
Get out of the bed!
Go back to your room.
I like it here. Got a problem?
Are you the lady from last time?
Yes.
It's great to see you again.
Are you feeling better?
There's no way to cure asthma.
There is!
I got you some medicine.
Use 5 cups of water.
Don't over-cook it.
Thank you.
Good night.
You're not heartbroken?
Did you take the medicine?
- Not yet.
- Why not?
I'm taking prescription drugs.
I wanted to check with you first.
Good thing he called me over today.
I'm glad to see you.
You made the right decision.
I need to change the medicine.
Let me take your pulse.
You're pregnant.
It's my baby! Mine!
The father is not Chinese.
Right. He's Pakistani.
How can you tell?
Your pulse said it all.
So can I take your medicine?
Then... I'll make some changes.
Watch out for second hand smoke.
Cheers!
Want some?
Sure.
You should drink wine in the morning.
It increases blood circulation.
Bad news!
Boss, Cat is back.
Where's she?
She's outside the house.
Destroy all evidence!
Get her luggage!
I haven't finished breakfast!
Make sure Cat doesn't see anything.
Who is Cat?
She's Tiger's fiancee.
Their wedding is next month.
Tiger didn't tell you?
No.
Tiger doesn't like her.
We forced him into the marriage.
We don't like the girl either.
Then why make Tiger marrying her?
Business decision.
It's good for both families.
Leave...
Stay here, Cat.
Too late.
Who is she?
A friend.
Tiger!
Did you care about my feelings?
Listen to me...
How dare you to bring a woman home?
Look at her ugly face!
I'm canceling the wedding.
Cat... It's a misunderstanding...
It's not what you think.
You're the only one I love.
Listen to me.
Come on...
Cut! Cut!
She's not even watching.
What's wrong with you?
It's delicious.
Do you love me?
I do.
Why aren't you heartbroken?
When your parents mentioned
your wedding,
I was hurting inside.
But when she appeared,
all my feelings disappeared.
I just feel hungry.
You're a bad actress.
I only told you to lose temper.
Why throw cushions around?
You over-acted.
It's too exaggerated!
You're no better.
Why knock over wineglasses?
You're even worse.
Who told you to pick hair on the table?
May's got women's intuition.
She can tell what's real and what's not.
We should get the real Cat.
What "real Cat"?
The fiancee we want him to marry.
You know about our relationship.
We agreed to mind our own business.
If she sees this, she'll just say:
"Sorry."
"Didn't know your girlfriend was here."
"Have fun."
How can that break May's heart?
Can I go?
What's your hurry?
You're such a lousy actress.
You want a refund?
No need.
I'll make you pay for it.
Try me.
Cat?
Sorry...
Didn't know your girlfriend was here.
Have fun.
Who is she?
My girlfriend.
How dare you, Tiger!
Did you care about my feelings?
What?
We agreed to mind our own business.
But she's prettier than me.
Did I ever do that to you?
I think you're better looking.
She's like an angel!
She's fashionable.
She chooses appropriate attires.
She's got a great personality.
She's perfect except for her appetite.
How does she keep such a good figure?
Are you two serious?
How can I face my friends?
What do you want me to say?
I still think you're prettier.
Maybe she's got better temper.
What a show.
Is this another set-up?
You're not serious, right?
Tell her to leave!
Let me finish breakfast.
Is this for real?
Yes. You have to go.
Can I swallow my food first?
No, she doesn't like it.
Spit it out.
Please.
Stop!
Take your garbage with you!
Fatty!
Take care.
What are you doing?
She's leaving!
Your turn!
Take care!
What's wrong with you?
We've become good friends.
Do you want to help her?
You want her to beat Misery?
Like this! Beat it!
Beat it!
Trash everything.
What?
What's so funny?
I'm happy
because I'm finally feeling sad.
Don't cheer up.
Make sure you stay this way!
Then make me more upset.
Okay...
Good!
Return your clothes and jewelry.
Return everything!
You have to fight a little to feel the pain.
- No...
- Give it!
Give it!
No!
Come on...
Give it all!
No!
Let go. You're too powerful.
1, 2, 3
Take care.
The money is mine.
This makes up for your living expense.
Where will I stay without money?
Sleep on the streets if you have too.
What will I eat?
Try the trash can.
Get me a taxi.
Taxi!
Beat it!
Take care.
To which park?
Morse Park.
It's rundown.
Triangle Park!
Good idea.
Take her to Triangle Park.
Don't give me money.
Then you're on your own.
What can I do?
Then I'll pay for you.
But that won't break my heart.
Then I won't.
Pay or I won't drive.
Here you go...
Get in. Be careful.
You got a phone.
It's in my purse.
Your purse...
Got a battery charger?
There are no outlets in the park.
Batteries.
Bye.
Remember: Stay sad!
So you're Omei's Master.
This is a truly amazing
and shocking story.
I wonder what he's doing now.
Most likely busy with other women.
Where is my sword?
It's pouring!
Don't exercise after eating!
She's heartbroken.
She's completely crushed.
What's the big deal?
Did that come from her sword?
Must be kids shooting air gun at us.
Better stop doing that, kiddo!
Where's your manner?
Kiddo, I've called the police!
I dialed 999!
I can see you, kiddo!
I saw you, kiddo!
He fell for it.
We outsmarted him!
Yes?
What are you doing?
What's it to you?
It's pouring here.
I'm all wet.
Why do I care?
I practiced Heartbreak Sword Technique.
How was it?
Was it powerful?
I couldn't do the last 5 moves.
You need more pain.
Will you help me?
Sure.
I'll think of something tonight.
I'll come tomorrow.
Thank you.
Try to stay out of the rain.
Lunch is ready.
We got some for you.
Come...
No appetite.
Feeling sad?
He said he'd help me.
But he hasn't shown up.
You've waited all week.
He already forgot you.
Don't get her upset.
He must be busy preparing his wedding.
He'll come afterwards.
But he'll be married by then.
See? She's lost it again.
Air gun again?
Screw you, kiddo!
I saw you kiddo!
He's not scared.
We can't fool him.
I saw you, little girl!
It's a little girl this time.
I need more pain!
You said you would come.
I'm in pain.
Me too!
No. I'm doing worse.
Why? You're The Heartbreaker!
I think I messed up.
I came here many times before.
See? The invitation is crumpled.
A wedding invitation?
I figured inviting you to my wedding
would break your heart.
I think I'll die!
Let's forget all this.
Don't fight Misery. Give up Omei.
Then all I've done will be in vain.
It'll be a waste of your effort.
That's true.
On my wedding day, will you...
I will!
What?
I'll come early to get sad.
I thought you would...
What?
Nothing.
Steal me from the wedding!
Don't leave me, Cat!
Come on. Cat!
Calm down.
Excuse me!
Cat, I love you!
I won't forget you, Cat!
Cat is the center of the attention.
Where are Tiger's fans?
He hasn't been seeing them much lately.
Cat...
Don't do this to me!
Cat!
Tiger!
Here's one.
Finally!
I'll give up practicing
Heartbreak Sword Technique.
Don't get married.
Sure!
Tiger!
Wait. Something stinks.
Did you take a shower?
Yes.
Liar!
Where did you wash yourself?
Public toilet.
Why use public toilet?
Because I sleep in the park.
You know that.
You sleep in the park?
Then you must be a beggar!
Look! We have a beggar here!
Are you playing me?
Of course I am.
I'm famous for hurting people's feelings.
I've been waiting for this day
to get even with you.
Stupid!
Does it work?
Are you heartbroken?
I didn't know
if the wedding will do the job.
So I thought of this way to insult you.
I'm a man of my words.
I'll help you in any way.
You scare me.
I never know what you say is the truth.
Love is all about getting things
mixed up.
That's why it confuses people.
Are you in pain now?
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
Have you ever loved me?
Of course not!
It was all make-believe.
No real emotions.
Only acting.
Thanks for your help.
As long as you're feeling hurt.
I have one last kill for you.
Every relationship has its taboo.
Want to know what ours is?
You already said it.
I did?
What is it?
Done! Let's wrap things up.
Let's settle this.
How?
Divorce. Give me half of your fortune.
We're only married for 1 hour.
- 40%
- 20%
Deal!
Tiger, have you ever loved me?
Have you?
A little, but there was never any trust.
I feel the same.
What about her?
I never asked anything from her.
We never even sleep together.
Why go out of your way for her?
True. Why?
Love. What else?
Ladies and Gentlemen.
Today's wedding is cancelled.
Please take your gifts with you.
Big Sister!
Don't call me that!
What Master expelled me from Omei,
I took an oath
to die with Omei.
Today is Master's funeral anniversary.
We will all die together.
I'll kill myself first.
Then I'll kill you one by one.
Scared?
Big Sister...
I can feel your pain now.
Can we not fight?
You look sad.
Share your problem with someone.
Talk to your family or friends.
Or a psychiatrist.
Don't mind how people look at you.
Just think happy thoughts.
Easy said than done.
I know.
Look what I have become.
I wonder who it is
that caused you so much pain.
What's his name?
Tiger Hung.
Albert Yu is my man,
you stole him from me!
His name is Tiger Hung.
Not Albert Yu.
Will you listen to me?
Gift from Tiger.
Here's more.
Tiger my love!
Don't call me that.
Call me Master Tiger.
What "Mater Tiger"?
I'll marry May after she beats Misery.
By then I'll become Master Tiger.
There's no such a thing.
Omei Master must be celibate.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
May, I'm divorced!
Give up Omei. Marry me!
What are you doing here?
I'm losing my power!
That's exactly what I want!
I love you!
Misery is too powerful.
When I first met you at Omei,
I dreamt of our reunion.
Stop singing!
You'll get me killed!
I'll give you my fortune.
Boss, Misery is crazy.
If May can't beat her, we'll all die!
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Come!
May, I don't love you anymore.
Look at my girls.
It's no use.
I don't feel sad at all.
Damn!
This is not good!
Is there another way to beat Misery?
Yes.
Heartbreak Sword Technique 8th move:
"Eternal Harmony".
No one could figure it out
since Grand Master died.
"Eternal Harmony"?
What are the first 7 moves?
"Mixed Emotions", "Deep Sorrow",
"Bitter Argument"...
Understood.
All things come to a happy ending.
May, I've figured out
"Eternal Harmony"
Just think of all the good things
I've done for you.
See how Grand Master has a smile
on her face?
The key is...
"One eye open, one eye closed"!
Grand Master is smarter than that.
That's superficial!
Keep thinking.
There must be hints.
There's a clue under the skirt!
"One eye open, one eye closed."
"Remember the good and not the bad."
"This is where the answer lies."
"May eternal harmony bless you all."
That's what I said.
No it's different.
Congratulations, May.
He proved his affection for you.
You've recovered, Big Sister.
If a relationship can cause so much pain,
it's because
it also brought much happiness.
This is the meaning of love.
You've recovered.
Welcome back, Master!
What are you thinking about?
I want to create one more move after
"Eternal Harmony".
How should I name it?
Let's see.
How about "Sons & Daughters"?
Good...
What's the key?
"Eternal Harmony" focuses on
only the good thoughts.
"Sons & Daughters" focuses on
the bad thoughts.
How bad?
Like this.