CTB Film Company
Kazakhfilm Studio
With support of Cinematography
Department, Ministry of Culture
Olzhas Nusuppayev
Eduard Tabishchev
Olga Landina
Nurtai Kanagat
Gulnara Yeraliyeva
Bakhytbek Baimukhanbetov
Victor Sukhorukov
Producers Sergey Bodrov,
Sergey Selyanov, Sergey Azimov
SCHIZO
Director Guka OMAROVA
They said he can't study
with normal kids.
Look here...
He's just like that - he'll do
whatever they tell him.
Stretch your arms out.
Close your eyes.
Touch the end of your nose
with your finger.
Don't rush. One more time.
Well, of course he is slow
but basically he isn't dangerous,
he won't hurt anybody.
- What's your name?
- Schizo.
What Schizo?
They tease him like that at school.
He's Mustafa.
How old is he?
He'll be 15 soon.
Mother, you stay in corridor for
a while. I'll talk to him myself.
Okay.
Get dressed.
Why did you get kicked
out of school?
Bakha said,
"Do you wanna bonk Anelka?"
And you?
I said, "I do."
And then what?
And then
Bakha pushed me into the cloakroom
with the girls
and they bonked me themselves
on the head.
That's it?
I don't remember anything else.
Does your head hurt?
It hurts.
Go call your mother and
wait in the corridor.
Buy him this medicine, have him take
two pills at a time.
How is he, Victor lvanovich?
He has some deviations. You have to
go to the city, to a specialist.
Come by in a couple of weeks
for the paperwork.
You will have to pay, understood?
Of course I understand.
I'm already saving.
This is from our place...
sour cream, eggs...
Maybe I should talk to the teacher?
No, don't bother. I don't want to go
to that school.
You're right. You'll work for me!
And what if I can't do it?
Don't be scared! Stick with me,
I'll teach you!
That's it. Deal?
How many for you?
Four.
Let's go, I want...
- Let me finish cooking.
- Let it cook itself.
Mustafa is watching.
Come on, what is he,
a baby or something?
I'll turn off the gas.
- You're not scared?
- No.
We'll be there in a second!
A fool is one thing,
an idiot's even more so.
It's a trick, a trick, don't cheat!
You're cheating.
A jack, what a pity.
- What do you need?
- I've been standing half the day.
- How you doing, Sakura?
- Fine.
That's good.
Listen, Almaz.
Everybody knows my face there already.
I found myself a helper.
- Who is it?
- It's my girlfriend's son.
Make sure he keeps his mouth shut.
You couldn't find a bigger one?
He'll knock ours out...
I think it's worth the risk.
It's interesting for the crowd.
All right then, here are the rules.
You've got to make it to the end.
Understood?
Advance.
What about the rest?
You have to win the rest. We'll
start in a half-hour. You're first.
Who's this guy to you?
A friend.
You've known him long?
Can we trust him?
That's it. Get out of here.
Hey, what's with you?
You call this money?
I'll kill you for this money.
Get lost. You're gonna threaten me?
Go. Get out of here, you idiot!
I bet on the boxer.
I on the T-shirt.
They need a doctor there.
He needs help.
- Take him away from here.
- What's the matter?
Ali's bad there.
What Ali?
The one from the exchange.
Bring some water!
Forget about him,
go bring some water.
They finished me, bastards...
Take the money from my pocket.
Do you know the house
at the edge of town?
Her name is Zina...
You'll do it?
Hey, Schizo. You here?
Don't you get it?
I told you, forget about him
or I'll rip your head off! Got it?
Okay, guys!
I'm taking new "Benz", I'll stake
old one on the fight. Let's drink!
Oh, cool. Come on guys, come on.
To Almaz' new "Benz". To you, Almaz!
Dance with him.
Does Zina live here?
And who are you?
A friend.
Zina's on her way.
Do you have some water?
Wanna play?
Who's this?
Your friend.
I don't have this kind of friend.
What do you need here?
Ali asked me to bring money.
And that's all of it?
Yeah.
And where is he?
He left.
Left? Where did he go?
I don't know.
When will he be back?
Does he think it's possible
to live on this money?
I haven't paid the landlord
in three months!
I'll move to find work and let him
take care of his boy, understand?
Tell him that!
Left! He thinks I believe his lies?
Scum!
Hey, guys! Guys! Grab him!
I recognize him. It's him!
What's the matter?
He's recruiting people for work.
And he organizes fist fights.
So what, shit?
Who are you working for?
Cat got your tongue or what?
He's sick in the head.
You're the one who's sick.
What did you say, bitch?
Enough, put him in the tank.
Quick, quick, take him there.
- Go to hell!
- Come here, you bastard!
From the crowded city
with the skin-topped milk
It's always interesting for me
to go far away
To where there is a river
with a nice bank
And a heel, like a stove
will warm the sand for me.
The sky, the air,
and the naughty wind
And even the air will sing with me.
You, moron. Get the hell over here!
Quicker. Quicker.
Let's go, double-time!
To the cell...
Let's go.
So what, what did they want?
They asked me whom I'm working for.
You didn't squeal?
Good job!
What do you want?
Do you have money?
How much?
What do you need it for? For girls
or something? Okay, sit down.
- What's with you?
- Money.
Did you bring my car?
Sanzhik!
I've got to go...
You are rubies,
rubies, precious little gems...
What do you want?
Will you go to the restaurant?
Do you have money?
Got it.
We can stay at home...
It'll be cheaper.
Let me make a run.
You hang the laundry, okay?
What do you drink?
Vodka.
Do you know how much...
they would have ripped
you off for in a restaurant?
You go to restaurants a lot?
Yeah.
I used to go
to restaurants a lot, too.
Now I don't even
have a decent dress.
The sun rises
and sets behind the river.
Someone is quietly singing...
ah, ah, ah, ah.
Sing along.
And in the algae, the green algae
The girl's body floats.
Can you imagine Ali, that jerk,
dumps his kid on me and takes off.
And no help whatsoever...
I'll go to China to look for work.
People say waitresses
make good money there.
I'll marry a Chinese guy.
People say they make good husbands.
Have you heard it?
Listen, I forgot, what's your name?
Mustafa. Nickname's Schizo.
Short for schizophrenic.
Wait, I don't understand.
Are you sick or something?
Take your hands off me!
When you see Ali, just tell him
that his Zina moved to China and
sent his boy to an orphanage.
He was killed.
What are you talking about,
you idiot?!
Why didn't you tell me before?
Who are you? What are you doing
here? I'm going to kill you!
I'm Kulyash's son. Let me go!
And you are my uncle.
You bloody...
What are you doing here?
Listen, I'm late for work.
You coming with me?
- Your mother got married?
- No.
What, she lives alone?
No, with Sakura.
- He doesn't treat you badly?
- No.
Come on, faster!
Hey, did you cut it? Throw it!
I cut it.
Me, too.
I'm throwing it.
I'm throwing too.
Throw it!
What if they turn on the power?
There's no power here.
And what if they do?
It'll fucking kill 'em!
Come on, load it up fast.
Faster, faster!
Give me money.
Money. Load faster!
We have no time at all!
Here it is. Faster!
When is the train back?
How do I know? Daut, you know?
What, like I take trains
or something?
Okay, I am leaving.
Stop!
What did you come for?
I wanted to offer some work.
What work?
Fight for money.
You can't do it, you got old.
How much they paying?
A lot. The prize is a car!
No way.
Why would I lie to my uncle?
10 years ago,
10 cops couldn't put down
your Uncle Zhaken.
Even their electric clubs
didn't work. He busted their faces.
What kind of car?
A big one. An American Mercedes.
Stop, you little snot!
Why do you want to disgrace
your uncle?
Hold on! I'll show you!
Let's go. I'll show you how
Uncle Zhaken can't fight!
Why did you bring someone so old?
He won't even last 5 minutes.
He will. Even electric clubs
didn't work on him.
Okay, we'll see...
Are you gonna make
it at least 5 minutes?
I don't know. I probably will.
All right, pour.
Well, go on brother.
Don't pound him right away!
Stretch it out a little, okay?
Go on!
Beautiful. Good car.
Hey, give me the keys to the car!
Hey, Almaz, give him the car.
He won fair and square.
Give him the keys.
You selling?
I'm selling.
How much you asking?
Twenty-five hundred.
Dollars.
That's expensive, Dad.
I'll take it for two thousand.
I told you twenty-five hundred.
You just take a look at the wheels.
They're already old.
Weighted down, they'll go flat.
If you don't want it, don't take it.
I'm buying.
But you've got to bring it down.
Open the trunk.
Everything's fine.
Here brother. I'm giving you money.
Okay, take it.
You just owe me a bottle.
A bottle. All right, a bottle.
Dad, six seconds.
Well, all right. Pour.
Don't drink a lot. You'll fall
asleep and they'll steal the money.
Why are you constantly lecturing
your own uncle?
Did you see how I got him?
Come on, he messed up your face.
- Why are you so late?
- I had things to do.
- What is it?
- It's for you.
Oh my god!
- What do you think?
- Fine.
- Does it fit?
- Uh-huh.
Wow, you even chose my size!
- Will you have some watermelon?
- Uh-huh.
- Hi.
Look what I've got.
What have you got on?
Schizo gave it to me.
They're for swimming underwater.
Where did you get so much?
I earned it.
It's all for me?
For you.
Will you stay?
Are you sleeping?
No.
Well, what do you want?
Nothing.
Don't lie.
Do you know how to screw?
I do, and you?
I tried once.
And so?
Didn't work out.
Everything okay?
Don't go to China.
Look after the boy.
Okay, I'll stay.
Stop wandering out at night.
You have to look after your health.
- What are you talking about?
- This guy's related to you.
This is a total scam.
I don't have any relatives. Schizo
found him. I know nothing about it.
Listen, Sakura, this Schizo
is an idiot! But you're not!
I lost a fighter and a car!
Who's gonna give me my money back?
Almaz, I have nothing to do with it.
I swear!
If you don't bring me money
in 3 days, I'll put you in the ring
and kill you myself!
Do some sit-ups. How do you feel?
Fine.
- Have you been taking your tablets?
- Yes.
Come here.
Does he have a sex life?
No.
There is some progress, but you have
to take a treatment in Almaty.
I've already arranged it.
Here is the paperwork.
Go there tomorrow, straight away.
Thank you, Victor lvanovich.
So, you played the fool?
And you framed me?
He won fair.
Where's the money?
I spent it.
On what?
None of your business.
They called me on it! I can
get killed over this, understand?
Where's my money gone?
Sakura, did you take it?
Yeah, I took it.
What for? We have to go to the city
tomorrow for treatment.
Treat him for what?
He turned out to be the smartest.
Now you can save for the funeral.
What funeral?
The hell with you, you jerk!
Choke on the money!
It's my fault.
We need to pay them off
or they will tear us apart.
I know how to get money.
There's one job. We can take a lot
of money. There'll be enough for us.
But I need your help.
We are friends,
- aren't we?
- Fifty-fifty.
You'll go to the counter, show them
the gun, and say "Money". Got it?
Repeat what you have to do.
And why don't you go yourself?
I'll wait for you here. You're sick.
You won't get anything for it.
- But they'd put me behind the bars.
- How much should I take?
Take everything. Don't be a pussy!
Go, go, go on!
# Currency Exchange #
Give me the money!
Everything!
He's got no money left.
- How much is here?
- I don't know.
- Should I count it?
- There's no time.
Quiet. Understand?
You'll hitch a ride home.
Where's the gun?
I forgot it on the counter.
Should we go back?
Give me the money.
I need to take it right now.
Hey, leave them. I love apples.
Where's my share?
What share?
But we've got a fifty-fifty...
Forget about fifty-fifty.
And forget about me.
Go home. You need to get treatment.
It was fair. Fifty-fifty.
Say hi to your mother.
What?
You know how good
it is on the water.
- How are you doing?
- Good.
Is Zina home?
And how are you doing?
Not bad.
Bring me a notebook and a pen.
Did you take your pills?
No, I ran out of them.
Zina, give half to my mother.
Your friend, S.
Will you stay with me?
No, I have things to do.
You'll give Zina money
at the first snowfall.
And when will the snow fall?
I don't know.
You'll see for yourself.
Sometimes the snow doesn't fall
for a long time.
And tell her not to move away
for now.
Yes.
Well, bye.
Bye.
I didn't say anything in court.
They pronounced me normal
and gave me 6 years.
Mother sold the house
and moved to the city.
She visited me in prison
now and then.
There was nothing from Zina.
I didn't know what happened to them.
Then I got lucky. They let me out
on amnesty before my time was up.