When did you come back?
Why?
You're so happy to see me
I came to get my trousseau
Just kidding, let's go!
Great
Any new girlfriend?
Since I left?
No woman...
can tolerate...
my drawbacks
Have some self-confidence
You're so nice
I feel safe when I'm with you
You'll do anything to help me
And take care of me
I wish I'd known you...
...before he did
Impossible
He knew me at birth
Watched me grow up
Is he handsome?
Old and ugly
Protective too
Wake up, let's go
Do you know why I came?
Your trousseau
Before I met you
I had never dated anyone but
My fiance Shunichi Kikukawa
And after we met?
After we met
I discovered...
It's not how long you've known each other
But how you feel
I never thought of him while I was here
But I missed you every day in Japan
Love is different from friendship
So
I've decided not to marry
What are you doing?
Calling my mom
To tell her to cancel the wedding
Happy?
Answer me
Blue sky, I wonder why
You left out the rainbow
Cars jammed like busy bees
Who will look at me
The world may be exciting
I see just black and white
Nothing to love. Nothing to hate
Wherever the music
My shadow follows
And dances with me
My lonely, silent world
Had no beauty
My black, my white
They were my future
I knew, I must wait
For someone
To become my colour
ooh... lonely eyes
You are the ocean
Come to me
Open my dreams
ooh baby
I can't wait; a new life
A new heartbeat
You are my only colour
Blue sky, I wonder why
You left out the rainbow
Cars jammed like busy bees
Who will look at me
The world may be exciting
I see just black and white
Nothing to love. Nothing to hate
Wherever the music
My shadow follows
And dances with me
My lonely, silent world
Had no beauty
Baby, what's your name?
My name is...
Dreamy Wong!
I'm sorry
My black, my white
They were my future
I knew, I must wait
For someone
To become my colour
ooh... lonely eyes
You are my ocean
Come to me
Open my dreams
ooh baby
I can't wait; a new life
A new heartbeat
Here
They were my future
Thanks
For someone
To become my colour
ooh... lonely eyes
You are my ocean
My cold!
Open my dreams
ooh baby
Don't worry
A new heartbeat
You are my only colour
Welcome, Chairman, to Shanghai
We're ready...
I came to find my daughter
She should still be in town
Before she leaves
I must find her
- Let them see
- Yes
I announce
My son-in-law and I will reward
$3 million RMB
Find her first
Whoever finds my daughter
Will get all the money
Sorry
It's my fault
You're so ill
Need a doctor?
No doctors
I hate doctors
Just take care of me
I want congee
Yuri...
Eat; then take your medicine
I've never made congee before
Thanks
Yuri...
It's 3:00. Time for medicine
Must you be so punctual?
Yes, you'll get better faster
- Get up
- Thanks
Congee is ready
Congee again?
I'm well. Let's eat out
I don't want congee every day
It's only been 2 days
What?
Two days
Two days?
Let's go. My mom will find me
Let's go now...
You must eat
You're too weak
I'm still sick
You are?
What shall we do?
I'm heartsick
Do you treat all women so well?
Or just me?
Come, tell me
Tell me you only love me
You only treat me so well
Then my heart will recover
Tell me, good friend
I love to hear it
I shouldn't
I shouldn't?
Get out!
I never want to see you again!
Go to hell!
I'll get the door
I shouldn't?!
Coco?
Is Yuri here?
In the room
All Shanghai is looking for her
There's a $3 million reward
I'm afraid
they'll come here
Look, Yuri
My mom is good at this
Let's go
Thanks!
The stairs!
Open the door
Yuri's here! Come out...
Mr. Wong, here are
Two tickets on the next flight to Beijing
It takes off at 3, at Gate 17
Thanks
Beijing first, then the Siberian Express
To Eastern Europe through Russia
Fly to Paris, sail to Morocco
They won't guess that route
We'll enjoy ourselves in Africa
- Africa?
- Isn't it exciting?
I've always wanted to go
I love lions and elephants
You don't want to?
I'll go anywhere with you
Beijing...
- Let's go
- Wait
- Help, Philip!
- Henry?
Yuri's fiance is holding...
...Nancy and me...
...at knife point
They said if you don't bring Yuri back now
He'll throw us in the river
I think he's a man of his word
Help!
Henry...
What is it?
Henry said...
I must go take care of something
- Now?
- Yes
We fly in 2 hours
It's close by. I'll be back soon
- I'll go with you
- No!
It's dangerous
Come!
Hide; come out only when I call
- I'll be back soon
- Hurry
You're Philip Wong?
You're Shunichi Kikukawa?
You dirty scumbag!
You terrorize my friends
And you're eating cake!
Where are they?
You came quickly
Such a good friend!
You're at knife point?
Why are you eating chicken?
My baby cancels her wedding for you?
I thought you'd be handsome
So plain
You're... Auntie?
I don't know you
Call me Madame Sakurada
This is my son-in-law
I'm Shunichi Kikukawa, nice to meet you
You're Shunichi Kikukawa?
I'm just the translator
Ask before you grab next time
Mom, let me talk to him
Sorry my Yuri caused you so much trouble
She's a playful girl
Loves practical jokes
She wants to cancel the wedding!
Sorry
No one is clearer than I
That it was a moment of passion
It hurts!
So, sir, I hope...
You'll forgive Yuri
Yes
We have
the same necklace
Why?
Presents from Yuri
Now you see?
Bring her back
We'll take together, you'll know
If Yuri really loves you
You're untouchable
- Philip!
- Don't talk to me!
You cried for help to get me back
And you're eating chicken!
Why did you lie to me?
Her mom and fiance are understanding
So we called you back to help
Wake up
We're doing it for you
She's a powerful princess
He's a powerful man
They're made for each other!
A perfect match!
- A great pair!
- Match made in Heaven!
Your backgrounds are different
They're made for each other!
As are you and Coco!
Don't break them up
Don't block their way
Don't block my way!
Yuri...
Are you all right?
You've thought about this?
It isn't a moment of passion?
Of course it is, that's love
No one knows what's next
But I know...
...I won't regret this
We'll be in Africa
We may have problems
You're not just playing?
Do you think I am?
Why did you lie to me?
Shunichi Kikukawa is not bad
Why did you say he's old and ugly?
You checked up on me?
When did you see him?
What else are you hiding from me?
You don't trust me?
You have no faith in me?
I have no faith in myself
I afraid I won't be good enough
Afraid I cannot give you happiness
Afraid of many other things
Like what?
I'm not afraid of you, but you are of me?
I asked you to say "I like you"
You said "I shouldn't"
Do you know
How a woman feels
hearing that?
Sounds like I have a crush on you
I know
You don't want the responsibility
You're selfish
Otherwise, say it
I...
I what?
You can't say it
Because you're the one just playing
And you betrayed me
Thank you
Split the $3 million among yourselves
No need, it's so much money
No need...
Henry, give it back!
Thank you...
Yuri, I didn't!
No, you didn't like me
I was wrong about you
It's okay
He bullied me
Silly girl, no one does that when I'm around
No one can harm you
Too soft, I can't hear him
I can't translate
Mom, I'll return to Japan,
Marry Kikukawa
You scared me to death
Let's go This way
She said Let's go
End of translation
Great dancing!
Everything's back to normal
You worked hard, dry off
Traitor!
I didn't betray you
They followed me.
Could I stop them?
They gave me money
Could I refuse?
Must we do that, too?
Are you all right?
Still angry?
Will you feel better if you hit me?
I'll let you!
Hit me!
I'll have 3 years bad luck
Just once
We've been friends...
...since I left Malaysia
Twenty years
It's for your own good
Your relationship had to be tested
It's better to test it sooner
So you can find out
Are you still angry at me?
Are you?
Stop
Can't you see I've changed?
Let's have fun!
That's right
Leave some for me
- Cheers!
Hi!
You're here
We came to see you
You're not so cool today
He's hot now
When can we go out?
You won't turn off your phone?
Call me, I'll keep it on...
...for you
You turned it off for me
You're different
Come!
Can you handle both?
Let me have one
What?
Selfishness brings bad luck
- Stop it!
- Where to?
Your home
What for?
Coffee
Let's go, don't want to see
Am I famous?
For my coffee?
Got it!
Coffee time
Where's the coffee?
Where are you?
What are you looking at?
Aren't you getting coffee for us?
Who are they?
- Where are you?
- Wait!
March 31
Marriage? Whose?
Dreamy Wong!
Coco?
Why are you here?
You want fulfillment?
Might as well be me
I'm not so bad
Don't do that
You want a twosome?
Nancy!
Okay, you're a bore
But for a friend
What are you doing? Get up!
Here's one more!
Although I'm not gay
You wouldn't share with me just now
I'll let you do it!
For my good friend...
...who was hurt by love
I sacrifice myself
To rescue you from the abyss
Although I'm too plump
Hope you don't mind
You got it wrong
Am I like that?
It's only a coffee date
I know you're not like that
You miss Yuri
I'm not through yet
Don't try to stop me
Philip!
I've decided
I'm going to Japan tomorrow for her
I don't care
As a traitor...
I should repay you by going with you
We'll go, too
Are you traitors?
With passports?
You know the way, Traitor?
It's easy
Fly to Narita Airport, Tokyo
I know that
Take the JR Express...
...to Shinjuku Exit
When you get out of the station,
There's a Sakura Department Store there
See?
Here's one
How can we find her?
Start with this branch
That's crazy
Sakura Enterprises
Wedding-tomorrow-11:00 a.m.
- Summer Shrine
Let's crash the party!
The wedding has just started
Hurry!
After she drinks
They'll be legally married!
Say it now
I object!
Yuri!
- Get them out!
- Yuri!
I must speak to you!
- Say it!
- Yuri!
Mom, the press is here
Don't use violence
Yuri!
Let him speak
Let go of him
Speak
Many told me to come
But most of all
I wanted to
Because most of all, I feared...
...losing you
If I didn't come
I'd regret it...
...all my life
I was always...
...insecure
and lack of self confidence
Saw only black and white
Then I met you
I felt colours
You...
...filled my life with colour
You appreciate me the most
You said...
...you chose cherry blossoms
For their...
...short-lived glory
I tell you
I choose that, too
So I had to take this chance
I may not be able...
...to change your mind
But I must say it
I dared not say these words
I feared losing you
But...
...if I dare not say them
I cannot tell you
I'll take care of you all your life
Yuri...
I love you!
I love you?
I'm touched
Thank you
This is the best wedding gift
But sorry
You're too late
I wish to complete the ceremony
Go now
Give him this, a present
To thank him for coming
Yes, sir
Take this, from them
Thanks for coming
You may go
Pardon us
Sorry
What a waste
You didn't open the fan?
Don't want to
Don't take my fan!
No, look
April 1 st, that's today
I'll wait for you...
...at 11 a.m.
Ueno Park
One hour ago, not too bad
She's already married
And it's April Fool's Day
Up to you
It's okay to be late
We're leaving
Please, stop!
Great! Hurry!
Hi!
Are you looking for someone?
You are...
You don't know me
But you should know my lover
His name is Shunichi Kikukawa
Shinjuku... Colour?
I don't understand
Or Kikukawa Shunichi
Kikukawa Shun...
...ichi?
Hello
My girlfriend
Excuse me?
Yuri's and my late fathers were friends
They planned our wedding
In conjunction...
...with our companies merging
When the news spread
Our share prices kept going up
To maintain this trend
Even though Yuri and I...
...are like siblings
We had to get married
Which I needed,
to get my inheritance
But she nearly canceled for you
Fortunately at the airport
I was able to explain it to her
And she was willing
To be my wife in name
She also wanted to test you
We were worried
But you came
The fan was not made in vain
We'll secretly...
...divorce soon
Where is she?
Dreamy Wong!
You're late!
Come, see the cherry blossoms
- Goodbye!
Goodbye...
I've been practicing
Come