- Master, I'll help you!
- Oh? And who are you?
Protect 13th Aunt! I don't need help.
Leave her alone!
Reverend Father!
Wing, come and protect 13th Aunt.
They've gone backstage!
Let's see you fight up here!
Damn it!
- Why did you ambush me?
- It's you who ambushed me!
Foon? He's Foon?
It's dangerous here,
there are killers inside.
Question him!
- Foon, what're you doing?
- How would I know?
He's been hitting me
ever since he came in!
Don't move!
You say don't move,
but you still hit me!
Let's all stop this fighting!
Let's go!
Master Wong, don't move!
- Your Excellency.
- Silence!
Excellency, they left something.
"Glory to the Militia.
Death to foreigners"?
Weren't all the
Local Militia arrested?
How many have you sheltered?
Your Excellency. I'm being framed!
Don't listen to him!
Arrest these Shaho thugs!
What Shaho thugs?
That's the second time you've hit me.
Find out the truth
before you lay blame.
The truth?
- He's taking protection money!
- What? My Master?
Yes! That's him!
Master Wong? Isn’t he from Shaho?
Where's Shaho? Near the Yellow River?
You don't need to explain.
My men will soon arrest
your other members.
But I'm going to arrest you first
and close your clinic.
Then let's see you make trouble!
Many people have been injured.
Let me help them, then I'll go with you.
All right, go ahead.
You'll be guarded. If anything
happens I'll execute you on the spot.
Don't move. You're bleeding.
- So, fetch the medicine.
- OK!
Go away. Can't you see
the eviction notice?
That doesn't give you permission
to steal our stuff. Give them back!
You dare to hit us?! Go away!
Don't you have anything better to do?
Master, they were stealing,
I stopped them.
So what? Do you want to fight?
I'll fight with you.
- OK, let's go!
- No! I mean I'll fight you!
- Master, how can I fight you?
- Where'd you like to be hit?
Is it here? Here?
You want me arrested right away?
If not, don't stop me
from saving lives.
Master!
Stop acting up!
We'll arrest you,
if you get in our way.
Porky's smart,
escaping arrest this way.
Hit me! Such restraint!
Mr Cheng!
Still bleeding.
Fetch me the coagulant!
Coagulant!
He's dead. Tell his family.
So...
Fei-Hung!
What's this tattoo?
It reads, "Jackson".
Is it his ship's name?
Don't be scared. I'm Wong Fei-Hung.
You're badly hurt.
If you move, you'll tear the wound.
You're Master Wong? Help me!
Get up. Where are you from?
- America!
- America?
We crossed seas and were
denied medicine when we were ill.
Many were thrown overboard.
In America,
we were branded like pigs.
We were cheated
by the Chinese dealers here.
We signed contracts,
paid for food and passage.
Paid for so many things.
Those who tried to escape
were killed.
I came back to China.
I... I... Master Wong...
Don't worry, you're home now.
Let me see
if we can find your family.
Try not to think too much.
Kai! Keep his contract
with the foreigners secret.
- Or the Governor will arrest him.
- I understand.
Going to America's better
than staying here.
Don't miss out! Come on...
Take a look! You want one?
- Go to America? How?
- Take one. You want one, too?
The same America as in the newspaper?
If you want to go, pay an exit tax,
passage, rental, blanket and food.
You can get a 3 year contract.
It costs 2 years' salary?!
- You haven't got any money?
- No.
Then don't even think about it!
Shove off!
You want one?
It's a land full of gold!
A fight's about to start over there!
A fight?
Let's go and watch it. Come on!
Don't go, don't go!
You dare show off in front of
my house and hit my disciple.
- What's your name?
- Master Yim.
I warn you.
My swordplay is unmatched.
You're a guest,
so I'll let you strike three times.
On guard!
Second strike!
Just two strikes
and you already draw your sword?
You're not my match.
Let's forget it!
Don't go!
You dare strike me from behind?
'Iron Robe kung fu'!
I've let you thrust 3 times.
Admit defeat!
There must be a way to beat him.
Why are you following me?
My name is Foon. I'm from May County.
There are lots of gangs in this town.
My kung fu is poor.
I'm often bullied.
I can't even make a living.
Please take me as your student.
What's the point of being a kung fu expert?
I can't make a living either.
Master, are you hungry?
You take shelter.
I'll think of something.
Give me a drumstick!
Good stuff, eh? We only eat the best!
Gentlemen, come inside!
The soup's salty. Don't drink it.
The soup's very salty today.
Hey, why'd you steal my bowl?
Gentlemen, welcome,
come in and have a drink.
Welcome gentlemen,
let me sing to you.
Master, have some soup.
2 men drinking from the same bowl.
Pathetic!
Madam, shall I have them thrown out?
If I made my name here,
no one would look down on me.
Right,
you have to become the top dog.
Who's the best in town?
Master Wong?
Fei-Hung!
13th Aunt, you're right.
China must change.
Fists can't fight guns.
I'm under house arrest,
soon I'll have to fight.
Take care of yourself!
- Fei-Hung, I'll wait for you.
- You don't have to.
If you do, I won't die in peace.
You won't die...
I'm just a man...
Go home.
Wing, he...
Wing, go inside, it's raining hard.
Master didn't tell me to come in yet.
Wing.
- Come back to Lam Chi Bo.
- Master!
Come on in!
I...
Master, let me!
So!
It's raining harder than ever.
It's closed! Push off!
I'm 'lron Robe' Yim from Shandong...
I'm here to challenge Master Wong.
Please tell me
which of you is Master Wong?
- Master, a challenger!
- Wing, bring some tea!
- Master!
- Bring tea!
Please!
Kai, take the patients to one side.
Have a seat!
Fold the umbrella.
Have some tea!
Foon, what're you doing?
Foon?
Master Wong,
your techniques are famous,
especially your 'Shadowless Kick'
and 'Ten Forms Fist'.
I intend to open
up my own school here,
that's why I'm here to challenge you.
Soon the people will know
my martial arts is the best.
I'm under house arrest,
you could get in trouble.
I can't fight you today.
Are you a warrior or not?
Master Yim!
I've patients here!
It's not the right place to fight!
Wing, Kai!
Do you want to be thrown out again?!
What are you waiting for?
Take the patients to the back.
I'll take you inside.
They're going to fight.
How dare you touch our patients?
Move him or he'll get hurt
by my master.
Bullshit! If not for my Master,
I'd beat you up.
- Let go!
- No!
- God damn it, Foon!
- What?
You dare try again?
Yim, stop fighting.
If you don't stop, I'll fire!
Don't hurt my Master. Give it to me!
Master, are you all right?
I've mastered the Iron Robe.
I don't fear guns.
Wong Fei-Hung, I won so easily,
it doesn't count.
Let's fight again tomorrow!
If you don't come,
I'll assume victory! Foon!
You jerk!
You ungrateful shit!
Speak Chinese, you banana!
- Are you OK?
- Yes, I just slipped!
The guards were injured,
there'll be trouble.
The Governor's men will be here soon.
Wing, Kai, go inside,
take some money and go.
13th Aunt,
go and wake the man from America.
What are you waiting for? Go!
Take him with you.
So, you don't know kung fu.
- Don't wait for them. Go!
- Mas...
- Take care!
- I'll see you off!
Don't act on impulse.
- Master.
- Be careful!
Don't worry, your word is my command.
Wing, tell 13th Aunt to leave.
I let them go in order
to get the whole gang. Search!
Wait! I have many patients here
and many invalids.
Please don't disturb them.
You're asking me not to go inside?
There must be something hidden there!
My plan was to catch you off guard
and see who might be hiding
among your patients. Search!
Yes, sir!
Someone's getting away! After them!
Go!
So, go quick!
- Get them!
- Right!
Wing, fight!
What? Master?
Wing, I told you to fight!
- Manchurian Dog!
- You insult me?
Samson's Lift!
- Are we really allowed to fight?
- Yes!
Where's my gun?
Where are you going? Come back.
Shadowless Kick.
- After them!
- Yes!
Don't bother.
The man you want is here.
- Split up.
- Right!
This way.
Hold the pole, the rest go under.
Wong Fei-Hung,
I arrest you on charges of treason!
Your Excellency, I'll go with you.
- Kai!
- Master!
Kai, fetch medicine for the wounded.
Medicine from Lam Chi Bo
is the best.
How many of you are there?
- Are you all right, Your Excellency?
- You good-for-nothings!
We're almost there. Hang on!
Now we've got guns, we've got power.
We have to find women
for the foreigners.
Sha... Shaho Gang!
A woman!
Let go of So!
You get away!
Don't let her go!
Let go!
Sir, take care of yourself.
They are too many. Forget about me.
Go to hell!
Go!
- Let me go!
- Go!
There's one over there.
Get him! Get him!
Damn you, how dare you come to help?
Attacking the clinic?
Kicking Wong Fei-Hung?!
Challenging Master Wong!
- We're not going home.
- Let's wait here!
When do you think
Master Wong will get here?
Open your mouth wide.
Open the door!
Go away!
You dare shoot me?
You'll be shipped out tonight!
Do you hate me?
Will your skin need spicing up?
When you have to serve
those stinking labourers,
you're gonna wish it was me.
- Take her to my room!
- Yes, sir!
Boss, the one who beat Wong is here.
Great!
Good, now Fatshan will be ours.
Master!
You know each other? Foon is now
your senior. You can trust him.
He's our senior?
Call him Big Brother.
Big Brother!
OK...
Remember he's senior.
Master, I'm busy tonight.
Please excuse me!
We'll talk about
the new school tomorrow.
Get the presents
for the Master ready.
Master Yim,
this is to help you open a school.
The Yim's Fist Style
will soon dominate Fatshan.
Come... let's toast Master Yim!
Cheers, Master!
Don't move! What do you want?
Master Wong, we all admire you.
We know you've been set up.
Master Wong,
we've decided to free you...
and we'll take responsibility for it.
Master Wong, this way!
Great! Let's go, Master!
Master!
China is a land with laws.
I won't make a mockery of them.
- Go! Master!
- Go with them, Master!
No, Excellency.
I appreciate it, but I won't go.
Wong... Master Wong is over there.
Mas... Master!
Master, you're still here?
- So!
- Master... Mas... Mas...
Speak slowly.
Master, Aunt 13 and I took that man,
but we ran into the Shaho Gang.
They killed him
and captured 13th Aunt.
- Think of a way to save her.
- What?
Master Wong, let's go and save her.
- Wing, I'll give you a few men.
- Good!
- Let them go!
- Right!
Buck teeth So,
how come you spoke so fast?
I was... rehearsing all the way.
Isn't that Master Wong?
Aren't they the Local Militia?
Master, you're great.
You even beat Wong Fei-Hung.
Give us a little demonstration.
Just a little!
Bitch! The hell with you!
That's enough, master, enough!
Master, that's enough!
What's wrong?
This money is dirty. Don't accept it.
What? Is he insulting us?
What do you mean?
You're looking down on us?
Nothing in this world is perfect...
Virtue is often found among
the lowly...
Our priority is to make our name
in Fatshan.
When that's achieved,
we can talk about justice.
That's life. Foon, pick up the money!
Pick up the money!
You think you're a big boss?
I think you're a nobody!
Foon!
Pick up the money!
Make our name in Fatshan?!
That's life!
Boss!
Bastard!
Damn you!
13th Aunt, wake up!
- Bastard, don't touch me!
- Don't scream, I've come to help.
Foon, is it you?
So many people are coming!
Get that woman!
Foon, stop or I'll kill her!
Our boss? Go to hell!
Hit me? Damn you!
Master, they are inside.
Let's go in!
What's going on?
Master, Foon wasted no time!
He tried to force himself on my wife!
- No, it's not true...
- Shut up!
Foon, how dare you!
Apologise to your comrade!
Yim, we met at Lam Chi Bo.
Shut up, you bitch! Go!
You want to rebel?
Stupid! She's not his wife.
Really?
- She's related to Wong Fei-Hung.
- Wong Fei-Hung?
Foon is trying to escape!
Escape?!
How dare you.
Come back!
Get him!
- Take it easy!
- Yes, Big Brother!
- It hurts.
- Right!
Master,
these people have turned on me.
They'll do the same to you,
don't trust them.
You don't trust your comrades,
yet speak up for Wong?
How is it? Too tough for you?
Let him go.
I'll do anything you want.
What makes you want
to sacrifice yourself for him?
You dare try to bargain with me?
Are you really Master Wong's woman?
When I'm done with you,
your face will be so scarred,
even Master Wong won't recognise you.
Where's the woman
you took away today?
- Big Brother! Wong Fei-Hung is here!
- Master Wong?!
Arm yourselves!
Get all the guns out.
Go, get all the women on the ship.
Master, Wong is here.
You have to protect us!
Don't worry!
- Foon!
- Go!
13th Aunt!
Go!
Master Wong!
You're not needed here,
go search for 13th Aunt.
Yes.
Master Wong!
Master Yim, win or lose,
it's just a game.
You've got no excuse not to fight.
As you wish.
Down there!
"External Chi Kung"?
Today only one
of us leaves here alive.
Hey, how do you fire a gun?
Don't worry, we have guns.
You said you're good, come on.
I'll help you, Master.
Porky?!
Any more?
- Buck Teeth So!
- It's you?
Come up and get me down. Quickly!
13th Aunt has been kidnapped
by the Shaho Gang.
13th Aunt's been kidnapped
by the Shaho Gang, save her!
Hey, get me down,
Buck Teeth So!
Your Excellency.
Excellency, it's dangerous here.
You'd better leave.
Comrades, get inside!
Boss, what now?
Kai, I'll help Master,
you save 13th Aunt.
No, I'll stay! You go!
I'm Big Brother! You listen to me!
Neither of you have to stay.
Go save 13th Aunt.
Go!
All's fair on the field of battle!
You call this Yim's Martial Arts?
The world's full of surprises.
One must take precautions.
Be quick, the ship's leaving.
Take them aboard!
Go, bitch!
Fei-Hung... it's 13th Aunt. Fei-Hung!
- Fei-Hung! It's 13th Aunt!
- Bring her to the ship, go.
Mr Jackson, Master Wong is here!
Master Wong, take him on!
The ship's over there!
Hung, take them to the cabin.
Get down, quick!
There... there!
Master Wong!
Master Yim, our match is over.
Master Wong, watch out!
Master Wong, where are you?
We haven't finished yet.
Master!
I am a master of the Iron Vest...
Master Yim!
It's true. Our kung fu is
useless against the foreign guns.
You scum!
Master Wong, don't go!
Hold your fire!
Foon!
Kill him!
Watch out!
Master Wong, come on out
and fight man to man.
Fei-Hung,
he's got a gun in his knife.
- Don't fall into his trap!
- Shut up.
Bitch, you brought them here,
so I'll burn your face.
Let's see which is faster,
your fist or my gun.
Burn!
Let me go!
- Mr Jackson.
- Sir.
Mr Jackson and the Shaho Gang
sold women to America.
Your Excellency, save us.
The Shaho Gang
and Jackson stole guns.
By law, you can't kill me,
you must hand me to the Government.
- You've violated international law.
- Put down the gun!
Why won't it fire?
Did I forget to load it?
If you don't put it down,
I'll kill him!
Put down the gun!
You've offended a Chinese Official
in a forbidden area.
How will you explain that?
Don't let even one Chinese
leave alive.
Then I won't have to explain
anything to your Government!
You scum!
You don't have to explain!
- Your Excellency.
- You jumped from this height?
Child's play. No big deal.
Thank you, Your Excellency!
All credit to Master Wong.
- Don't mention it!
- Thanks, Master Wong!
China's changed so much.
How can I deal with it?
America?
Do they really have gold there?
If they really did have so much gold,
why would they come here?
Maybe we're standing on gold now.
After this ceremony,
you'll be my Master.
But 13th Aunt
and I are so close now...
We'll be together
from morning to night.
If one day she marries me,
then you'll have to call me Uncle.
I'll be your senior
so you'll have to serve me.
Foon, what are you thinking?
Have some tea, Master!