Hey
Are you upset?
Come on, stop it
You were okay yesterday
Stop pouting and say something
What do you say?
With a black suit on...
I might look like Bond
- I'm Bond, James Bond!
- Take them off
No more pouting, okay?
Okay
Hyo-jin
Have you seen 'Cinema Paradise'?
- No
- No?
It's playing
Trailer produced by AVProduction
My God, she's naked!
I said, 'Cinema Paradise'!
That is 'Cinema Paradise'!
New Nude Paradise
Oh god, this is so...
Answer the phone
Okay, I'll ring until
you answer the phone
- Hello?
- Hey, loser
- You busy this Saturday
- I have plans
Don't lie to me
Let's go do a survival game
No, count me out
Still upset at me teasing you
for not having a girlfriend?
I do!
She's right next to me
Stop lying
Let me talk to her then
Put her on
Hyo-jin, will you talk to him?
Who is it?
It's my friend
He wants to talk to you
Why should I?
No way
- Please do this for me
- No way
Put her on!
If you don't...
Okay, don't do that!
I can't believe this!
Give it here
- Hello?
- Alright, alright
Forget it! Who would fall
for a loser like you?
There are more fish in the sea
Unless some homely chick is
dying to get laid
Forget about it
If you change your mind
meet us at 9 on Saturday
Hey...
What the...!
You should help me clean
on your day off
Where are you going?
To practice shooting
Have you killed?
I smile at people...
they almost die, gasping
Look at her
Hasn't she become sassy so fast!
Bye
Have fun
We assassinated people
by putting poisonous mushrooms
in the soup
Or we let them eat swellfish soup
That's right
There's no antidote to it
Those were our days
Where the hell is she?
Is she coming or what?
Let's wait a little longer
She might be lost
You sure she lives in Seoul?
- Yeah, I am!
- Don't shelter her
We can't wait forever
- She's here!
- What?
Right there
Gorgeous, huh?
Huge!
I think she wears a C-cup
I'm pretty sure
she has it tailor-made
Say hi to my friends
from high school
Hi
- Hello?
- How are you?
Sorry I'm late
You should be
I'm not the one
Just because you live in Seoul
you don't have to know
where Galleria is
You called him the other night?
Right
Go-bong, let's go
My car is a convertible
I have a great stereo system
- Please, ride with me
- You call this a car?
We welcome you all
Conquer our headquarters
and you win the game
You already killed me!
I just made sure
Wait for me!
Hyo-jin, wait for me!
You're too slow!
What are you, a SWAT member?
No way, what are you...
Keep down!
Why don't we play in the stream?
We have to fight hard to survive
This isn't a real thing
No!
It stings like hell!
Hyo-jin, it stings a lot
Try not to get shot
Give me a hug before I die
They're all playing
in the stream
Who the hell is that?
Did you have fun?
Yep
It's a great way to relieve stress
You were like
'Zena the Princess Warrior'
We should do it again later
What's the occasion?
Mu-soon?
Why don't you try
our new product?
New burger with salad
it's only...
# Happy birthday to you
# Happy birthday, dear Hyo-jin
Come on, blow them out
Okay
I didn't know
it was my birthday today
How could you forget
your birthday?
This is why Mu-soon...
Here comes the finale
It's an ice cream cake!
God, it's hot!
Couple Dance Contest!
A stereo for the 3rd place
A digital camera for the 2nd
A camcorder for the winner!
- Let's go
- What?
Let's win some prizes
It's getting wild, guys!
Let's go
Hit it for the next couple!
What are they doing?
God, you guys suck!
Hyo-jin!
She's through!
Those who don't know here
are N. Korean spies!
Is it impossible?
I just wanna push back
the enlistment date
That's out of the question
unless you have a disease
I have a bad case of constipation
Doesn't that count?
Try our new lipsticks
Hi
Let me recommend this
It's a hot item
Having a hangover?
Stop it
Hey, dance queen!
She was wild last night
Tell me about it
What are you doing?
Kimchi burger and cider please
Did you say cider, sir?
Wow, the rumors were true
For here, right?
Kimchi burger please
It's KIM, all right
Should I do him?
Bring him alive?
Okay, I'll bring him alive
no matter what!
Okay
Comrade KIM!
Me?
My last name is PARK
You got the wrong person
You're dead!
Not bad at all
I never made mistakes
Do you know what flower
blooms on Peony Peak?
I guess that's a Peony
I'm here to meet Hyo-jin
You made a trip for nothing
She's not home now
Honey, should I make
swellfish soup?
With lots of mushrooms in it
I don't mind dying
Sorry if I surprised you
Mother!
What unit are you with?
Shut up!
You wasted that money
in a pyramid business?
What's that?
It's a scheme
They sell jade mats
You pathetic loser!
You should be sent to
a logging site in Siberia
and work your ass off
until your balls freeze off!
You're no different
You're supposed to be studying
Not following a chick around!
Do you have any idea
who we are?
Hyo-jin's parents
And my future...
Have mercy on me!
Get off of me!
No!
You can't die now!
Get away!
These are expensive!
You need some Viagra?
I didn't do it for my own sake
I wanted to make big bucks
So I could look after
senior spies like you
How could you get into
that pyramid thing?
Do you have any idea
how frightening it is?
They're better organized
than we are
What's Viagra?
All yours
What are you looking at?
Get out of here
If I can't date Hyo-jin
I'd rather die!
God!
I don't care what you do
Just get him out of here
- Don't lose any
- Okay
Don't be such a wuss
What'd you come over for?
I... just...
I saw you going after that guy
I had to do something
You thought I would like you
if you come here
dressed like him?
I'm not interested in men
Who's that guy then?
Huh?
He's...
He's my cousin
He lost a fortune
in that pyramid thing
Oh, I see
Take it
A lipstick?
It'll look good on you
Why are you giving it to me?
You put it on, and we can...
It's the last bus
Get on
Hurry up, kid!
Bye
I'm happy to find out
she's not spoken for
Why do I feel so empty then?
Due to personal matters
Hyo-jin's leaving us today
I'm sure you're all sorry
that she's leaving
Let's give her a big hand
Hyo-jin...
Damn
Now it feels real you're enlisting
I know
Does Hyo-jin know?
What are you, playing?
Do it right!
Okay
Hyo-jin!
You!
You've been impersonating me?
You're Hyo-jin?
That's right!
I'm the original Hyo-jin
You're a spy, aren't you?
I can collect $150K
if I turn you in
You don't think I can
because my dad is one?
Think again
I need money to pay back
loan sharks
Good thing I got you
You!
What?!
I'm serious!
They might sell me off
to an island!
- Shut up before I make you!
- Honey, honey
Apologize to your daddy!
What for?!
I'll pay off my debt with a bounty!
You too!
What'd I do to you?
Little bitch!
Hyo-jin, let's talk inside
I have nothing to talk
with a spy
Yeah, I'm a spy
Please let us go home
They're waiting for me
back home
My mom and dad
What's this, a soap opera?
Out of my way!
- Hyo-jin!
- Let go!
You think I'd go soft on you
because you're bleeding?
Wrong!
I can't believe this
- Hyo-jin!
- I can't believe this
First time back in a month
and you beat her up?
Who do you think you are
making my girl bleed?
I'm bleeding too!
- So am I!
- So what?
Spies don't fuss
over damn bloody noses!
What? Do you think spies are robots?
- We feel pain too
- Leave it!
You ingrate bitch!
I took you in
and you broke my girl's nose!
You're bad
I gave you the stereo
It's a piece of junk!
Take it back!
Hyo-jin!
Hyo-jin, what's wrong?
Sorry
I shouldn't have done that
I got you in trouble
I...
I have something to tell you
In fact...
I'm from the North
I know
You do?
And you're okay with that?
I know you live
in the north part of the river
Look, Hyo-jin
I have a favor to ask of you
Answer the phone
Okay, I'll ring until
you answer the phone
Answer the...
It's Hyo-gook
Hold on
My daughter gives me
enough headaches, okay?
You should sleep at home
Don't stay out all night
The submarine will be here
the day after
You shouldn't miss it
Okay?
The table is set
but you can't eat?
Jump on her
when she's drunk
Hey, listen
Once you enlist
that's it between you two
You have to make her yours tonight
Okay, Good luck!
Forget it, man
Come on
- She's my type
- No way
Her belly button is so clean
Nothing happened last nigh?
Of course!
I'm still a virgin
Thanks for massaging my feet
I can't let it get wet!
Hyo-jin, I'm going away
the day after
Where?
Far from here...
I will be gone for 2 years
Going abroad to study
because you can't make it here?
Huh?
Yeah...
So...
I was wondering
if you could wait for me
Go-bong, I wish I could
But things won't allow me to
I'm sorry
I've been seeing you
to have my pictures deleted
I couldn't afford to let myself...
...be known to the world
It's okay
Sorry I brought it up
I understand
I can use some music
- Do what like you?
- This place is packed
- You shut up
- This is fucking embarrassing
Hyo-jin, you're sleeping
next to me
I'm recording this
in my dad's favorite tape
If he finds out
he will be furious
But I'll be in the army
What can he do?
Beat up his son with a gun?
You're so beautiful
even while sleeping
I feel like kissing you
But I won't
Because I'm a guardian dog
of a Sleeping Beauty
I wonder how you'd react
when you find me sleeping
beside you
Your boyfriend is enlisting?
If it's alright with you
why don't you let it play?
Mu-soon!
Who are you people?
What are you doing here?
Who the fuck are you?
Me?
I'm... PARK Hyo-jin
What?
You told me it was her
That's right, boss
That is PARK Hyo-jin
Do your job right!
You're dead, bitch!
No!
Hey! Hey!
You're worse than leeches!
Okay, I surrender
Bye!
You're going back tomorrow
Drink all you can
- Thanks
- Bottoms up
Don't look at me like that
I know I've been bad
Good to have everybody
Let's drink
Good luck to both of you
- Cheers!
Not without me!
Angel: PARK Hyo-jin
Deleted
Would you like to close down the cafe?
The page doesn't exist
Mu-soon...
He's your first love, huh?
Why don't you try this?
Go ahead
You know what?
If you get too obsessed
with doing it right
you become greedy
and end up breaking it
Just like that
It's the same greed
that fails the first love
- Go-bong!
- Hey!
What are you doing here?
We'll take you to the base
No, it's okay
Where's Hyo-jin?
It's okay
I told her not to come
Let us come with you
It's okay
Who knows? I might run
into another angel on the train
Come on!
Bye
- Bye-bye!
- Bye!
- It's Hyo-jin
- What?
What happened?
I was worried you might
break out of barrack
No way!
What if...
What if we'd met earlier?
I have a message for parents
Please don't come too often
to see your sons
I also have a message
for girlfriends
Don't give them broken hearts
while you're separated
They're most depressed
when they get broken hearts
Help them commit themselves
to the training...
and send them a letter of friendship
We all thank
the families and friends
of our proud sons
enlisting in the army
with the deepest of appreciation
Salute to the commander!
Loyalty!
At ease!
Let's go, kid
You know what?
I wanted you to put this on
and kiss me
Hyo-jin!
Put that lipstick on
and come to see me!
I'm leaving you now!
But we'll meet again!
Hyo-jin!
Man!
He looks horrible
It must've been real hard
I knew from the beginning
that she wasn't human
I think she is...
An angel!
Comrade KIM bribed the commander
with Viagra
and escaped going to the mines
And the jade mat KIM gave me
turned out to be fake
I knew it!
Freaking pyramid stuff!
I got back from the field training
by the truce line
I hope for reunification
So I can see you again
Oh, I miss Hyo-jin too
How's she doing?
You're PARK Hyo-jin?
I said so, bitch!
God!
You think that name scares me?
Watch it before you get
a bloody nose
What?
You freaking impersonator!