Presented by
CJ Entertainment
In association with
Discovery Venture Capital
a cineWill production
You know,
I noticed a shelter outside.
Then you go, idiot!
Shit, I'd be better off
going back to the army.
Damn it.
What a pitiful sight.
I told you all not to
drink here, didn't I?
Didn't I?
Hey, you.
You're new here, huh?
Yes.
Get up.
Get up now!
Let me see your ID.
Right, you wouldn't have one.
Because you're filth.
Pardon?
Human filth.
All of you are trash
that disgust ordinary citizens.
Damn it,
how old are you?
I got a presidential plaque
when you were breast-fed.
You disrespectful prick.
You all are in big trouble.
You two come with me.
What?
Seems like filth
carry around IDs now.
Han Min-wook...
Nice.
What?
Mr. President!
Salute!
President?
President, my ass!
If you're the President,
I'm Kim Jong-il.
Yeah, Kim Jong-il.
THE ROMANTIC PRESIDENT
Produced by
Choi Jin-soo
Executive Producer
Lee Kang-bok
Producer
Jung Soo-hyun
Co-executive Producer
Seok Dong-joon
Starring
Ahn Sung-ki
and
Choi Ji-woo
Cinematography
Byun Hee-sung (K.S.C.)
Lighting Director
Jung Young-min
Edited by Kim Hyun
Music by Bak Hae-sung
Script revised by
Kwak Jae-yong
Associate Producer
Kang Sung-joon
Written and Directed by
Jeon Man-bae
Hey, where's an empty seat?
Are you deaf?
Where's an empty seat?
Here...
Thanks.
I'm Eun-soo, Choi Eun-soo.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, aren't you supposed
to introduce yourselves, too?
Right, I'm Jin-ah.
Cho Jin-ah.
I'm Sun-mi.
Are you a transfer student?
What's our
homeroom teacher like?
Is he cute?
We have a new teacher
coming today.
Hey.
Who's the boss of this class?
Boss?
Her.
Min-sook.
I see.
And the pushover?
The one in front, Bang-shil.
I see.
Hey, then who's the rebel?
Han Young-hee.
Students, settle down.
I said be quiet!
Had it hard without a homeroom
teacher for two weeks, right?
Well let me introduce
your new teacher.
Come in, Miss Choi!
Hey.
What?
Hello everyone.
I'm your new homeroom teacher
starting today.
You know my name, right?
Study hard
with your new teacher.
And make a fresh new start.
Just do it!
Excuse me.
I don't know what
your previous teacher was like,
but I can never forgive anyone
who ostracizes or harasses
other students.
Understand?
When class ends, Min-sook and
Bang-shil come to the office.
Okay?
So you're Young-hee, right?
Don't you hear me?
Please don't bother me.
Young-hee,
feeling sick anywhere?
I'm not sick.
Just don't act like you care.
What?
Don't act like I care?
I'm your teacher,
so how can I not care?
This sucks.
Young-hee,
stop where you are!
Stop right there!
Speak.
We met for
the first time today.
But are you mad at me
for something?
I'm not,
so don't bother me.
I guess it's no use
talking to you.
I'll have to
meet your parents.
My parents?
Then ask to
meet them yourself.
Fine!
What's their number?
It's 016-200-0001.
This is the President's office.
What?
The President's office?
Through reality-based policies,
President Han has improved
the lives of the less fortunate.
He's been single for ten years,
and had a piano concert for
the first time for any president.
With the "Piano President"
as his nickname,
he's very popular
among the youth and women.
But his support from elders
has considerably fallen.
With the local elections
two months away,
this will be a test to the
President's political ability.
Mr. President.
I think Young-hee
is in trouble at school.
Look here, Miss Choi.
How can you put me
in a tight position like this?
What are you trying to
accomplish with the President?
As a teacher,
I thought it was necessary.
I can forgive you for not knowing
that her father was the President.
But you shouldn't have
called him if you knew later!
Did you think the President
would call you to apologize?
Yes, this is the
principal speaking.
This is Han Min-wook,
Young-hee's father.
Mr. President!
I'm sorry I couldn't...
Mr. President, what is the
reason for your gracious call?
My secretary had
received an urgent call.
I was wondering if I could
speak to Miss Choi Eun-soo.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, Mr. President.
I know you're extremely busy,
but please hold for one moment.
Thank you.
Answer it!
Yes, this is Choi Eun-soo.
I'm sorry I had
called you so suddenly.
However, 35 students have been
waiting for me for 25 minutes.
If you'd like to talk,
please call me after class.
Have a nice day.
Look here, Miss Choi!
Hello?
Mr. President!
That doll is cute, huh?
Right?
Yeah, it's cute.
Steal it for me.
Huh?
Why? You don't want to?
But...
Welcome.
Hey, kid.
Hey, kid!
Damn it!
Hey you,
stop where you are!
Stop!
"I envy those orioles
who look so much in love."
"My lonely heart would
like to return to my beloved."
Now who'd like to read it
in Chinese characters?
Pyunpyun... Hwangjo...
Jawoong... Sangee...
- Welcome, Mr. President.
- Hello.
Thank you for coming.
Young-hee's classroom
is over there, sir.
I'm sorry.
I should've
visited you sooner.
But today's my first day.
So what happened
with Young-hee today?
Right!
In your last press conference,
you highlighted equal education
and teachers' authorities.
But one student used
her father's special status
to directly challenge
a teacher's authority.
In order to stop
this act from repeating,
and as parents are legally
held for a minor's crime,
I'd like for you to accept
Young-hee's punishment.
Wait.
So you're saying that
I be punished instead?
Yes, sir.
Miss Choi...
So I want you to write
"The Oriole Song" 100 times.
In Chinese by tomorrow!
I have to go to class now.
I bet the principal didn't sleep,
thinking he might get fired.
I wish I could've seen
the President's face.
Giving the President homework
is history in the making.
Think he'll really do it?
Are you on drugs?
Think the President will do it?
Mr. President,
let me do it instead.
How much do I have
before school ends?
If you speed it up,
we can arrive
before after-school class.
Damn, it would be
better drawing it instead.
Teacher!
Can't I get my dad
to do it, too?
Just bring it to the
office when you're done.
Understand?
Why couldn't
my dad be president?
That's why you have
to have the right parents.
97, 98, 99...
100!
You've done it,
Mr. President.
Congratulations!
I won't be tardy, right?
No, sir.
The school is
right over the bridge.
I'm exhausted.
But sir,
what does this song mean?
Anyone who went to
high school should know.
I was very into sports,
so I missed a lot of classes.
The King of Koguryu
wrote it for his beloved.
"I envy those orioles
who look so much in love."
"My lonely heart would
like to return to my beloved."
Mr. President!
I did my homework,
but as I crossed the bridge...
In other words,
the wind blew...
Well, I left the window open.
- And then the wind...
- Mr. President.
Just say that
you were too busy
or that you
didn't want to do it.
You don't need
to lie so blatantly.
Lying?
That's nonsense.
I did my homework,
and then right on the bridge...
That's enough!
I'll take your word for it.
I have class,
so I'm hanging up now.
Mr. President.
I'll order the coast guard
to find your homework, sir.
Don't talk nonsense,
and just get me some paper.
Choi Eun-soo passed
her teaching exam in 1997.
She started teaching Korean
at Jamshil H.S. In 1998,
and transferred to
Songpa H.S. In September,
Junghwa H.S. In June 1999,
Jangchoong H.S.
In September 2000,
Youngbok H.S. In March 2001,
Mijoo H.S. In March 2002,
and then finally to Hanil High.
She only taught for
six months at each school.
Only six months, I see.
Everyone, I have a
surprising announcement.
Our new teacher,
Ms. Choi Eun-soo
will represent
our nation's teachers
and have lunch
with the president.
Ms. Choi,
I hope you do well.
Yes.
Applause!
She's the pride of our school.
What am I gonna do?
When the President appears,
rise up and greet him politely.
Excuse me.
We're only having lunch, right?
I won't be dragged to
anywhere else, right?
Just relax while
you talk over lunch.
Hello?
Did you meet
my sweety Min-wook?
Did you mention me?
Hang up!
Rotten girl.
She thinks
she's a big shot now.
Miss Ha-rin!
Does a Mr. Shin Kwang-bae
live with you by any chance?
There's a letter for him.
I don't know who he is!
No.
I'm positive
a man lives there.
I said I'm coming,
so stop calling!
Here it is,
Mr. President.
Mr. President!
Please relax.
"The Oriole Song"
written 100 times.
I'd like to repeat that I did
do my homework yesterday.
It's not a lie.
And I stayed up
all last night doing this.
Please take back
that it was a lie.
You've written
each character very well.
Excellent work.
I feel like a elementary school student
all over again.
Shall we have lunch now?
Despite one mistake,
I gave you a perfect grade
for your sincerity.
A mistake?
Where?
Here.
On the third line, it's not
the "Ji" character for "earth."
But it's the particle "Gi".
You're wrong.
That line means
"a lonely me on the earth."
It's not "Gi",
but "Ji" for "earth."
Come on, Mr. President.
"Gi" is a particle that
connects the other characters,
so that line
means "a lonely me."
I won all the calligraphy
competitions with this song.
It's "Ji" not "Gi."
I am a language teacher.
I've taught this 100 times
a year, so I should know.
It's "Gi" not "Ji".
You're being stubborn!
Stubborn?
Want to bet on it?
I'm the President.
You're also
my student's parent.
Fine!
Minister of Education,
this is the President.
Yes, sir.
I just want to inquire
about something trivial.
It's about "The Oriole Song".
In the third line,
it's the particle "Gi"
not "Ji" for "earth", right?
It's "Gi", right?
Of course it's "Gi".
What fool said it was "Ji"?
You finished college long ago,
so you might be confused.
"Ji" should be right.
No, I'm sure that it's "Gi".
My doctorate was
on "The Oriole Song".
Your doctorate?
Should I bring you
my thesis now, sir?
Have a nice day.
He said "Gi", right?
I bet you're hungry.
You look so marvelous
playing the piano.
And a bit lonely, too.
I really wanted
to tell you that.
Thank you.
But I can't play too well.
Oh yeah!
Do you know
the theme song for
Love is a
Many-Splendored Thing?
Of course I do.
The movie with William Holden
and Jennifer Jones, right?
It's Andy Williams' song,
"Love is..."
Can you play that song?
Pardon?
That?
Well, I had a good time
thanks to you.
Please teach our students
to their full potential.
I was just thinking, sir.
Try pulling down
your bangs a little.
And don't wear ties
with stripes all the time.
Try on ones with pok-a-dots.
Then you'll look
ten years younger.
Hi Eun-soo!
Did you meet
my sweety Min-wook?
He's so incredible.
And don't call
the President sweety.
Did you tell him about me?
That there's a girl
who loves him?
Nope.
Hey, is there a law where
I can't become his wife?
Shin Kwang-bae.
Ha-rin, you've got
reserve forces training.
Sir, here's the location
for you to examine tonight.
How about if we
do this instead?
Did you know that I was
also an outcast in high school?
You, too?
This is a secret,
but I'm an outcast
among the teachers, too.
Don't stay home
this weekend.
Go out and meet
your friends, okay?
- Yes, teacher.
- Go Bang-shil!
- Go Miss Choi!
- Bye.
Here's Andy Williams' song,
"Love is a
Many-Splendored Thing."
Many splendored thing."
"It's the April rose that
only grows in the early spring."
"Love is nature's way
of giving a reason to be living,"
"The golden crown
that makes a man a king."
"Once, on a high and windy hill,"
"In the moonlight mist,"
If I stopped, then hurry
and give me a ticket.
Now they're having
their fun with people.
How are you?
Remember him?
It's good to see you again.
It's good to
see you doing well.
I'd like to make a proposal.
For the citizens who
have worked hard today,
I will bring all of you home
on the President's limousine.
How about it Mr. President?
Great!
Cheers for
President Han Min-wook!
"Yes, true love's a many splendored thing."
Frankly, I've given up
a lot on Young-hee.
But after meeting you,
I've mustered some hope.
That maybe you could guide
her into the right direction.
But lately I don't know
whether straightening up
a student is really right.
After going through
their own rebellious stage,
I think maybe they could
naturally heal themselves.
The bigger problem is that
she doesn't have a dream.
It's been so long
since I've seen her smile.
Perhaps when
she was six years old.
When I fell flat down on ice,
she smiled and laughed.
I really miss that smile.
Then how about we try
to find Young-hee's smile?
I'm not that confident, but...
Just do it!
Oh yeah!
Thanks for the cake.
I don't like them.
What?
I wanna be rained on.
Rain?
Please don't worry,
everything is fine now.
Young-hee, let's talk.
No.
Young-hee!
Let's talk first.
No, let go!
Why'd you hit me?
My dad doesn't even hit me,
so what gives you the right?
Follow me.
Do you want that?
Want me to steal it?
Why? Think I can't?
If I get caught,
I'll say I was menstruating.
Here!
Mister,
she told me to steal it.
Not again.
Hey!
Hey you!
Stop!
Smile whenever you
wanna smile, dummy.
It's worse holding
in a smile than pooing.
You're in high school,
but do you still like dolls?
That was the first time
I stole something.
It's easier than I thought.
Why did you stare
at the doll before?
I was talking to it.
Talking?
When I was young,
I fell asleep after
waiting for my parents.
When I wake up,
parents have already left.
And I'd find a doll in front of me.
And then I'd throw it away.
Afterwards,
there'd be another doll.
And I'd throw it away again.
Maybe it's some curse,
but the dolls talk to me.
About what?
About anything.
Common day stuff.
You made that up, huh?
How'd you know?
There are ways to find out.
But others believed me.
Teacher, you take it.
Hey!
Young-hee.