Hey, big eyes.
What's your name?
Hey, let me see your face
You pricks,
mind your own business!
Big eyes,
you're my girl
Everybody got that?
I read five of them
You're lying
You only read one
Huh?
What's your name?
Ji-hwan
Lee Ji-hwan
Can you fight well?
Yes, I can
he calls me
but I don't afraid at all
Because she was behind me
I raised my fists,
and went after him
screaming
It was good up till then
And then?
I got beaten
I couldn't hit him even once,
and he almost killed me
So,
she turned her
back on me and left
I guessed she liked macho men
I heard she married him,
and they run a tent bar now
The end
Now, it's your turn
When I was a kid,
I was in the hospital once
That's where
I met him
He was a notorious troublemaker
at that hospital
He played a prank
on the nurses,
and then hid in my room
the first time I saw him,
he smiled really stupid
We became friends quickly,
and my room turned
completely into a playground
He was special
He was very sick,
but a smile never left his face
When I think of it now,
it's really funny,
but I asked people
to call me by his name
Why?
Well, I thought that
even if
we were to split apart,
I'd feel as if
I was always with him
Ji-hwan
What, Soo-in?
We've finally made it
the snow on top of the trees
is so beautiful
people call it snow flowers
Wow, you could be a tour guide
We'll just have
to come this winter
Yeah
Let's come again during winter
I'm serious.
Promise
Seal
Doesn't seem like
it'll stop raining soon
We'd better hurry
- Yeah, let's hurry
- A little more
Let's stay a little longer
Hold on a little more.
We'll get there soon
Sorry for begging you to come
You know me.
Right?
I'm okay
Is she better?
Yeah, she just fell asleep
I'm okay
Never saw someone cry before?
No, it's just...
Just that it's awkward
Hey! I just got sentimental
since it's raining
Why? It's not cool?
Ouch, it hurts.
Stop it
Ji-yoon!
what are you doing there?
Ji-hwan
I want to be alone
Did that bookstore
guy hurt you?
No.
I don't like him anymore
He absolutely has no sense
And he's not that
good-looking up close
And he seems
to flirt with anyone
Plus,
he's going to the army
He seems so weak,
so how could they take him in?
Long time no see.
You must've been busy
Yes
A great book
came in yesterday
Do you wanna see it?
No, that's okay
I'm not gonna be here
for a while
So I made a list of good books
They're for you to read
Thank you
Take care
How do I look?
Where's Soo-in?
She wants to rest at home
yet
Does she still feel sick?
It feels strange
with just the two of us
It feels like we're dating
Let's skip the exhibition,
and go for a drink
I feel like drinking
Are you coming to Chul-hyun's
birthday party next Saturday?
Friend
Wanna learn how to
make a donut with smoke?
If you do this,
girls will love you
Wait
Lighter
What's wrong with you?
What's wrong with me?
Don't act
as if you're my boyfriend
Ji-hwan. Lee Ji-hwan!
Don't flatter yourself, okay?
I'm drinking somewhere else
Don't follow me
What are you doing?
I know you're a nice guy
So you don't have to do this
Stop it
You!
You look really mean today
Why? Just because
Because I'm drunk
You look very mean
because I'm drunk
Fine, it's all my fault
Let's cross first
Let go, you bastard!
Taxi!
Know why I invited
all of you here today?
No particular reason
Since life is
so dull and boring,
those who wanna sing, sing,
and those who
wanna drink, drink
Have fun till you die
Hey, stop babbling
- Everyone drink
- Hold on, I'm talking
I wanna get something
clear to you all
Especially to the ladies here
This woman here
is not my girlfriend
She's just a friend.
Only a friend
Alcohol friend
Please keep your eyes on me
Me, too Me, too
Let's drink!
Asta-la-via!
I didn't think you'd come
Are you sober now?
Are you still sick?
I'm much better now
Don't take it off
I'm okay.
It's too uncomfortable
Man, that cold
is lasting forever
Is it alright if I sing?
Oh, sure
* The child I'm looking for
* Is hard to see
* Who understands the world
* Who even loves tiny leaves
* Whoa, whoa, isn't common
* Yeah, yeah, is hard to see
* The child I'm looking for
* I can see
* My loving friend Ji-hwan
* My loving friend Kyung-hee
* Whoa, whoa, they can see
* Yeah, yeah, I can see
* Whoa, whoa, I can see
Ji-hwan, I have
something to tell you
Wanna go outside?
Sorry that I'm going early
No, that's okay.
You're sick,
so you should rest
Ji-hwan, wait
Stay still
Huh?
Close your eyes
Why?
Just close them for me
Okay, you can open them now
What was that?
I suddenly remembered a game
I played when I was young
Soo-in,
when you catch a cold,
it's good to
brush your teeth
and wash your
feet and hands often
And Soo-in,
I have a favor to ask
I think I like Kyung-hee
I'm just asking for your help
Kyung-hee, you're
looking at this, huh?
You like me too, right?
What are you doing?
Oh, nothing
I'm leaving
Kyung-hee
Will you give this to Soo-in?
It's nothing important.
It's just...
Don't read it, okay?
All right
There's a taxi
Taxi!
Bye
Get in
You go ahead first
No, just go in
Aren't you getting in?
Don't make me angry
Okay, get home safely
You better not look at it
Kyung-hee
It's strange
I could tell you in person,
but I felt like
writing to you today
Just read it to me
Really?
To my beloved friend Kyung-hee
Beloved?
I'm not reading it
Okay, I won't do it again
I had a really hard day
I had a hemodialysis twice,
and two
intramuscular injections
But I beared it.
I didn't make a sound
Good
Know what I thought about
to bear it?
You and Ji-hwan
I thought you'd come tell me
how fun it was with Ji-hwan
Okay, that's enough
I'll read it on my own
And this is for Ji-hwan
I thought you'd read it
so I was careful
Promise me
you'll give it to him
Hey,
those girls will never show up
What were you three
doing all that time?
Don't know where they live
and their numbers?
You're right.
What were we doing?
What have we been doing?
Hello?
Ji-hwan
What's wrong with your hand?
Just an accident
You should be careful
Yeah
I'm really sorry to say this
But we became
uncomfortable around you
You guys now make me
uncomfortable, too
If you're done, then go
It's late
By any chance,
are you Mrs Kim Yeun-soo?
Yes
I'm Lee Ji-hwan,
I called you yesterday
Was it the class of 1996?
Yes
You understand we don't
sell this outside
But you're lucky.
We're almost out of them
Thank you
By the way,
who are you looking for?
Yes?
Well, no
Just that my girlfriend
had lost her yearbook
No, please
I just thought
I could be of some help
You see,
I graduated in 96 as well
I attended this school
Oh, I see
It's been five years,
so she might've moved
And I'm also curious as to
who you're looking for
You see
It's two people
One is Kyung-hee.
Kim Kyung-hee
The other is Soo-in?
Shim Soo-in?
Do you know them?
So that's who
you were looking for
Sure, I know them
since they were famous
They were very sick
They barely came to school,
and were always together
Others were both jealous
and sympathetic of them
They were very sick?
My goodness.
You didn't know?
Actually, I was also shocked
when I first heard it
They were absent a lot,
but they never showed it
I'm sorry to tell you this
Soo-in isn't in Seoul anymore,
and Kyung-hee passed away
Pardon?
What are you talking about?
Kyung-hee's dead?
Yes, it's so awful
I was a sophomore then
It's been five years already
Kyung-hee's dead?
Kyung-hee?
Soo-in will be hard to find
After Kyung-hee died,
Soo-in's health got worse
She had it hard
Since they relied on
each other so much
Holding back my wish
to scribble with you together
But Min-sik
will be in late today
Can you tell me
where I find him?
Ji-hwan!
Ji-hwan! Ji-hwan!
Ji-hwan, where did you go?
You scared us
Hi!
* The child I'm looking for
* is hard to see
Do you have a girlfriend now?
Kyung-hee, I found Ji-hwan
I found Ji-hwan
Really? That's great
Hold on
Soo-in, let's change
our names from today
I'm Soo-in and you're Kyung-hee
Why?
Why do you wanna change names?
If we do, even if we're apart
we'll think of each other always
That'll be fun.
You're Soo-in and I'm Kyung-hee
When I think of it now,
it's really funny,
but I asked people
to call me by his name
Why?
Well, I thought that even if
we were to split apart,
I'd feel as if
I was always with him
Next.
Number 42, Shim Soo-in
- Yes
Kyung-hee,
Yes
Soo-in -- Kyung-Hee
You're so lucky
to ride on this
You know what?
Nurse Park and Dr Kim
had a fling
They were caught kissing
in the medicine room
- Kyung-hee
- Yeah?
I love you
Me, too
Ji-hwan, she's here
Hi
Oh yeah, I forgot
You had a small scar here
So this mole
was on the left side
I wasn't sure
Kyung-hee's got a boyfriend
I'm taking her away!
No!
Don't take her!
It's Ji-yoon, the one who
always borrowed romance novels
Do you remember me?
Hi.
I miss you
Congratulations, be happy
Thanks, go and eat
See you at the reception.
Eat only two servings
Your wish came true.
Congratulations
Congratulations.
Thanks Ji-hwan
Congratulations
Thank you.
Congratulations also
on getting back together
How about a picture for this moment?
I'll take it for you
Should we?
No
You look fine
You have to give it to him
Hi, Ji-hwan. It's Soo-in.
Are you doing okay?
Of course.
Soo-in, are you doing okay, too?
I think I'm going far away
I really don't want to go
What will I do if I
miss you and Kyung-hee?
Ji-hwan,
take care of Kyung-hee
I know without you telling me
that you two like each other
Here's some advice
about Kyung-hee
Kyung-hee's favorite food are
sponge cake with yellow jam
and strawberry juice
And she likes guys
who has a funny bright smile
Look carefully
between her eyes
If she has three wrinkles,
it means she's feeling sick
So send her home quickly
She likes to hold hands,
so do it often
My beloved friend, Ji-hwan
Today I feel like eating the
instant noodles you made for me
Change into this
Dad, you're really handsome,
but there's something missing
What is?
- Dad, come here
- Yes
- Stay still
- Yeah
Hi, Ji-hwan.
It's Kyung-hee
I'm alone right now
My dad suddenly
had to go to Seoul
You better not laugh at this
When I go away,
I told him I wanted a beautiful
funeral like in the movies
It'll probably cost a lot
since I wanted a fitted dress
I wanted to look pretty
for people one last time
Especially you
I'm worried about
your company test
Since you came to see me often,
you didn't have much time
It was awkard and silent
between us,
but I was happy, thinking about the old days.
How about you?
I did, too
I think I'm a very lucky girl
All I have are happy memories
Soo-in, who made me
laugh all the time
And for making me realize how
wonderful taking pictures are,
my beloved Ji-hwan
Ji-hwan, a nice gentleman
who accepted my awkward kiss
This is embarrassing,
but I really liked it then
I want to erase this line
Forget it, I'm too tired
Coming to my funeral, right?
You have to come.
Since I miss you as well
If a single guy
doesn't show up,
people will feel
really sorry for me
Oh yeah, I have something to tell you.
You might get angry at me
Remember that letter
for Soo-in?
I ripped it up
I feel better now
for telling you
You'll forgive me, right?
I'll tell Soo-in
when I meet her
Ji-hwan, I love you
I loved you before
and I love you now
Good-bye, Ji-hwan.
Good-bye