Welcome to "Sunset Boulevard".
I'm Ed Sikov,
the author of "On Sunset Boulevard:
The Life and Times of Billy Wilder".
This is the cut of the film seen by most
audiences on its release in 1950.
But this is not the way that
"Sunset Boulevard" originally began.
Paramount Pictures previewed Wilder's
original cut in Evanston, Illinois.
Audiences there saw
a very different opening sequence,
and they rejected it, violently.
The credits began in a similar way
with this moving camera shot,
but then Wilder took us
to the LA County morgue,
which is where we meet Joe Gillis,
played by William Holden.
He's got an identification tag
on his toe because he's dead.
From an early draft
of the script, quote:
"For a moment,
the room is semi-dark."
"As the music becomes 'astral',
a glow emanates from the corpses."
"The long row of tags sways in the
breeze from the ventilator system."
"A man's voice says, 'Don't be
scared, there's a lot of us here."'
"Gillis says, 'I'm not scared."'
"His head doesn't move, but his
eyes wander to a nearby slab."
"There, under a transparent sheet,
lies a fat man aged 60 or so."
"His eyes are open too,
and directed at Gillis."
"The fat man says,
'How did you die?"'
"Gillis: 'What difference does it make?"'
"They discuss how the fat man died,"
"then Gillis says, 'Me, I drowned."'
Then Wilder got even
more morbid and risky, quote:
"On a slab against the wall
lies a blond boy of eleven."
"His swollen child's face also peering
through a transparent sheet."
"The boy says, 'So did I. I drowned,
right off the pier at Ocean Park."'
"'lt's only bad
when you try not to swallow."'
"'lf you let it in your mouth,
it doesn't hurt."'
"'I wish my folks
would come and get me."'
"Fat man asks Gillis,
'Where did you drown? The ocean?"'
"Gillis says, 'No, a swimming pool."'
"Fat man says,
'A husky fellow like you?"'
"Gillis: 'I had a few extra holes in me.
Two in the chest, one in the stomach."'
When, in Evanston, Illinois, the corpses
started talking, the audience laughed.
Derisively. Wilder was shocked, and later
said, "I sat there a few minutes,"
"then left the theatre."
"I sat on one of the steps leading
down to the toilet."
"That was a black moment in my life."
"A lady came down who had
also left the theatre and said,"
"'Have you ever seen such shit? '
I said, 'Never."'
So Wilder reshot
the opening sequence.
Wilder and his collaborators, Charles
Bracket and D M Marshman Jr,
wanted their film to be
an "Inside Hollywood" thing,
the sights and sounds
of Greater Tinseltown,
so they used many real locations
to get across the flavour.
Gillis's apartment is above
Franklin and lvar Streets,
it's still there,
it's called the "Alto Nido".
Wilder had been living
in Hollywood since 1934.
He was born in Poland,
grew up in Vienna,
worked in Berlin as a screenwriter,
then went to Paris and Hollywood.
He loved Hollywood,
it was his kind of town:
a little bit hard, a little bit mean, where
you could make it big or die trying,
a place where dreams
can both come true and die.
That's the case with Joe Gillis,
as we'll see.
Gillis's lack of success
was familiar, even to Billy Wilder.
When Billy made "Sunset
Boulevard" he was a hot director,
but back in Berlin in the '20s he was
a nobody, unable to sell his scripts.
He had to start again
in Hollywood too,
hustling ideas to people
who didn't want them.
This scene with Gillis
also sets him up as an operator,
a tough-talking, sarcastic,
would-be hotshot.
"You say the cutest things,"
he snarls to the repo guy.
That's something Wilder himself
would have said.
Wilder arrived in the US speaking
little English, but he learnt quickly.
He loved the rhythms
of American speech.
Gillis's line, "Hear about Rudy, the
shoeshine man?" is a great example.
"Rudy never asked about your finances.
He'd look at your heels and know."
It's a kind of street poetry.
Paramount pervades this film, quite
a daring thing for Wilder and the studio,
given this movie's bleak
vision of life in Hollywood.
When Gillis goes to Paramount begging
work, he enters not by the main gate,
but by the smaller, more beautiful gate
at the corner of Melrose and Bronson.
Paramount is where Wilder
made his last six pictures:
"The Major and the Minor", "Five
Graves to Cairo", "Double Indemnity",
"The Lost Weekend", "The Emperor
Waltz" and "A Foreign Affair".
It shows Wilder's clout that Paramount
allowed "Sunset Boulevard" at all.
It was the most bitter film
about Hollywood then made,
and it remains so still.
Paramount could have made Wilder
create a fictional studio, but they didn't.
We really do see Paramount
here and elsewhere.
That's how confident they were of
Wilder in 1949, when the film was shot.
Now, Gillis calls Sheldrake "a smart
producer with the ulcers to prove it".
Wilder battled with executives, but he
knew the difficulties in making a film.
It's stressful, which is why Sheldrake
is burping and guzzling antacid here.
Enter Betty Schaefer,
played by Nancy Olson.
This was only her second picture,
but she was nominated for an Oscar,
in the category of
"Best Supporting Actress".
She was paired with William Holden
in three other films:
"Union Station", "Submarine
Command" and "Force of Arms".
Holden made a splash in 1939 with
"Golden Boy" as a boxing violinist,
but after that he was stuck in
forgettable, nice-guy roles.
He'd made almost 25 pictures
before "Sunset Boulevard",
but audiences still didn't
really know William Holden,
so they could accept him easily as an
unknown, unsuccessful screenwriter.
Now, here we have to question Gillis's
description of Sheldrake as "smart".
"We always look for a Betty Hutton,"
he says. "Is this a Betty Hutton?"
The idea of Betty Hutton
playing a rookie shortstop
is a joke of Wilder's
requiring some explanation.
Gillis's script, "Bases Loaded",
is obviously not a "Betty Hutton".
Hutton was the bright and winning star
of "The Miracle of Morgan's Creek"
and the great musical
"Annie, Get Your Gun".
Gillis gets the joke. Such lines
show the comic side of this film.
After Sheldrake proposes
"Bases Loaded" as a "Betty Hutton",
Gillis asks him, "Are you trying to be
funny, because I'm all out of laughs."
Gillis may be out of laughs,
but Wilder never was,
especially not in "Sunset Boulevard".
Here we are at Schwab's Drugstore.
This "combination office,
Kaffeeklatsch and waiting room"
is another one of Wilder's
"Inside Hollywood" locations.
Hollywood lore has it that Lana Turner
was discovered there drinking a soda.
Originally, the Schwab's scene came
with a notable Hollywood personality.
Wilder filmed this scene with the
gossip-columnist Sidney Skolsky,
but it ended up
on the cutting-room floor.
In a way, this golf course is still
another central Hollywood locale.
It is a place where film industry
relationships are nurtured.
Gillis doesn't get that at all,
calling his agent a "big faker".
He says, "He was hard at work in
Bel Air, making with the golf sticks."
"Making with the golf sticks"
is not how Gillis would talk.
It's pure Billy Wilder. It's the syntax
of an Eastern European Jew,
not a Mid-Westerner like Gillis
or the Pasadena-bred William Holden.
As for the agent's reference to the
"Mocambo-Romanov's rut",
these were two well-known
nightspots in Hollywood.
They were frequented by big-name
people with big-budget wallets.
Wilder himself loved these places
and the power scene they represented.
Something about the title of this film:
Sunset Boulevard is a famous
avenue in Los Angeles.
It goes from Silverlake to the Pacific
Ocean, over which the sun does set.
But Sunset Boulevard also refers
to the characters in this film,
particularly the one
we're about to meet.
She's been nearing the end
of her day for some time.
Gillis also seems
near his end in Hollywood.
He dreads returning home in disgrace,
having failed in his dreams.
Now, you'd never call Billy Wilder
a great action-film director,
but this is pretty effective
as a chase sequence,
and it's made all the more tense
by Franz Waxman's score.
Waxman had known Billy
since Berlin in the early '30s.
Like Wilder, he left Germany
to escape the Nazis.
Some thugs beat him up on the street,
which provided physical incentive
to leave for Paris as soon as possible.
Now, is it an element
of chance, or fate, or both,
that leads Joe Gillis
into this driveway?
His tyre blow-out appears a blessing,
causing him to out-fox the repo men.
But then... I don't want
to get ahead of myself.
The house that Wilder found
for this location shooting
was not located in the 10000
block of Sunset Boulevard
as the script has it,
but at the corner of Wilshire and
Irving Boulevards, six miles away.
It was owned by J Paul Getty's ex-wife,
but she hadn't lived there for years.
It was the kind of house "crazy movie
people built in the crazy '20s".
Unfortunately this one, like most
of them, was later torn down.
Coming up is another example
of Wilder's street-poetic writing style.
"Miss Havisham,
taking it out on the world"
"because she'd been given the go-by."
It's not exactly how English professors
describe Charles Dickens's character,
but it works really well,
and it sounds terrific.
Notice the oblique way
Wilder introduces,
or, rather, re-introduces Gloria
Swanson to movie audiences in 1950.
Here she is, in long shot,
through the blinds,
with sunglasses covering her eyes,
but a beam of light on her face.
He's drawing out this introduction,
teasing us with it.
"Who is this woman?"
we find ourselves asking.
As I see it, this is when
the film starts to turn comical.
It's weird comedy,
but comedy nonetheless.
Gillis is entering a demented
fun-house world here,
and the nightmare is that,
once he enters, he can't escape.
Max, the butler, is played by
the extraordinary Erich von Stroheim,
who directed such classic films as
"Blind Husbands", "Foolish Wives",
and his masterpiece "Greed",
originally filmed as a seven-hour film.
It was cut to a quarter of that length,
helping to ruin Stroheim's career.
By the 1940s, Stroheim was reduced
to playing in B-pictures such as
"The Mask of Diijon", at the end
of which he beheads himself.
Look at Holden's gesture here.
That is a comic double-take.
And here she is: Norma Desmond.
Just look at her.
Look at her clothes,
look at her room...
Look at the dead body on the
massage table in front of the fire.
"He always liked fires,
and poking at them with a stick."
Who is this corpse? This is black
comedy, pure and not-so-simple.
Oh...
In real life, Gloria Swanson
was not like Norma Desmond,
though she later wrote that
she knew who she was playing,
and her character clearly
had much to do with herself.
It's a fantastic performance by Swanson,
who wasn't the crazy diva she plays,
but a hard-working woman who kept
busy after her screen career ended.
She ran a company
and had a radio show in New York.
She was by no means
the reclusive lunatic we see here.
This is one of the most quoted lines
from "Sunset Boulevard".
"You used to be big," Gillis says,
and Norma is not pleased
to hear that.
"I am big," she corrects him.
"It's the pictures that got small."
But what's usually missing when
people quote it is the punchline:
"Uh-huh. I knew there was
something wrong with them."
In any case, Norma Desmond is big.
Her gestures are oversized,
her emotions even more so.
She's grandiose and unnatural-looking,
given her excessive make-up.
By 1950, acting was more naturalistic
than it was in the silent era,
when actors relied on big gestures to
get their characters' emotions across.
In fact, Holden had been playing
guy-next-door types for the last ten years.
Both his characters and pictures were
small compared to Norma Desmond.
It doesn't take much for Norma
to start railing against the film industry.
She's obviously quite mad here,
but she has a point.
Gillis has another Wilderesque smart
remark to make, this time about talk.
"That's where the popcorn comes in.
You buy a bag and plug up your ears."
He follows up with another crack
like Wilder would make:
"Sh. You'll wake the monkey."
But, as we're about to see,
Joe Gillis is essentially a sell-out.
He's going to be working
for this nutcase.
She offers him a job and he takes it.
And he hates himself for it.
This is a recurrent theme
in Wilder's work:
people who sell out
in some form or another.
There's a sense of self-contempt
that pervades Wilder's films.
Two of his best films to come,
"Ace in the Hole" in 1951
and "Stalag 17" in 1953, are about
men who'd do anything to get ahead,
even, or especially,
if it's completely immoral.
And there, of course,
is her screenplay. A lot of it.
Norma's reaction to the word
"comeback" is also justifiably famous.
"I hate that word," she cries.
"It's a return."
Oh, that's what it is.
In this scene, Wilder's camera dwells
on the creepiness of the mansion.
The overblown and antiquated quality,
the sheer absurd excess it represents.
The house is just an architectural
extension of Norma herself.
It's an expression of her character.
Notice what the script is about.
As she says, "Salome. What a woman."
Now that's hilarious. Salome gets
John the Baptist's head served to her
which is also what Norma Desmond...
but I'm getting ahead of myself again.
Watch how these two people interact:
Norma Desmond, from another era,
and Joe Gillis, Hollywood 1950.
A lot of the tension comes from
the interplay of two styles of acting,
competing performance styles:
Norma's, the colossal expressivity
of the silent era;
Joe's, the muted, underplayed
style of postwar Hollywood.
This is an amazing posture
Norma assumes here.
That cigarette holder, that claw.
It seems to suggest a vampire.
It's also worth mentioning Edith Head's
costuming, which is spectacular.
Head's problem was to dress
a character who is out of time,
but also rich enough to buy anything,
including the most expensive
clothes in Beverly Hills.
So Norma's clothing had to be in style
and out-of-date at the same time.
Edith Head solved this
by mixing glamorous postwar styles
with the odd throwback
element here and there.
A beautiful hat trimmed
in outrageous feathers, for example,
and, certainly, a lot of leopard skin.
The doorbell rings and it's time for,
as Gillis says, "comedy relief".
The monkey mortician has shown up,
so we don't forget the corpse upstairs.
As Gillis reads his script, he's saying
he's concocting a plot of his own.
But in fact, he hasn't. Norma Desmond
has beaten him to the punch.
He's been trapped in Norma's world
since coming in the door.
In other words, he's taken the place
of the old chimp, or "chump".
While Norma is busy
trapping poor Joe,
I'd like to mention that when Wilder had
no money in Berlin in the late 1920s,
he worked as a dancing
gigolo at the Hotel Eden,
waltzing ladies around
the dance floor for pay.
He found it demeaning.
Many of his films are about sell-outs,
men and women who sell themselves,
both literally and figuratively.
Joe Gillis ends up doing both.
As demented as Norma may be,
she has the authority, the power.
Here again, she's setting that trap
and he's walking right into it.
What Max is about to tell Joe
in the scene above the garage
is also true of Gloria Swanson
in the 1920s.
She was a huge star
who was treated like royalty.
As Wilder himself once said,
"This was a star who was carried from
her dressing room to the sound stage."
Gillis's remark about Max is also true
about Erich von Stroheim:
"I pegged him as slightly cuckoo too."
Stroheim was slightly cuckoo.
He had a thing for sexual kinkiness
in the films he directed himself.
Wilder and his co-writers,
Bracket and Marshman,
created a classical
screenplay in three acts,
and Wilder will now show that
the end of act one has arrived.
After we see the rats
in the empty pool...
After Wilder shows us
the monkey's burial...
Since Gillis has taken the monkey's
place, we can safely bid bye-bye to it.
Gillis says, "It was all very queer,
but queerer things were yet to come."
With that, the curtain falls, and the
first act of "Sunset Boulevard" is over.
The second act also begins
with voice-over narration,
as Gillis explains
his situation to us.
The shot of hands playing the organ
is unusual for Billy Wilder.
It calls attention to itself
as arty and stylistic.
Wilder favoured less
showy shots than this,
but he obviously wanted
to show the baroque,
even Grand Guignol nature
of Norma Desmond's warped world.
It's an extreme world, expressed here
by those hands in extreme close-up.
Look at the mise en scène in general:
the setting and props, in particular.
Norma has surrounded herself
with hundreds of pictures of herself.
She literally lives in her own world.
Narcissistic, unable to distinguish
between the images of herself
and what she has actually become.
And what is she wearing
around her neck?
As Gillis blue-pencils
Norma's awful script,
and as she reacts badly
to the changes,
it's worth mentioning that Wilder rarely
let his actors change his dialogue,
and, in fact, he sometimes timed
their line deliveries with a stopwatch.
Later, during the production
of "Some Like It Hot",
Wilder held up filming deciding
whether to allow Jack Lemmon
to repeat the simple line:
"Now you're talking."
Despite the fact Wilder was a great
screenwriter and Desmond is not,
maybe Billy is identifying
with her a bit here.
Again, watch this incredible
performance by Gloria Swanson.
Drag queens cannot get this across
when impersonating Norma Desmond.
She's hilarious, even ridiculous,
but she's not a total caricature.
Swanson's Norma Desmond
is still a great actress.
Larger than life and able to sustain
that gigantic quality very well.
Norma was correct earlier on:
it is the pictures that got small
after the silent era.
But that doesn't mean her
silent screen-style acting is a joke.
The film they are about
to watch is called "Queen Kelly",
which starred Gloria Swanson and
was directed by Erich von Stroheim.
According to Wilder, it was Stroheim's
idea to use this footage.
You can see here how gorgeous
Swanson was in her youth.
And how photogenic.
"We had faces," she says,
and she's right.
It's worth noting that "Queen Kelly"
was a disaster commercially,
in fact, it was never completed.
It was another nail
in the coffin of Swanson's career
and it basically ended
Stroheim's career as a director.
Just to mention, some critics have
called "Sunset Boulevard" a film noir...
...but as you'll see, the lighting alone
makes it a monster movie at times.
And here we meet the waxworks,
Norma's friends.
First, Anna Q Nilsson, a Swedish
actress, a precursor to Greta Garbo,
H B Warner, a fine dramatic actor,
and then, the great Buster Keaton,
one of the two great comedians of the
silent screen, the other being Chaplin.
Wilder had approached another
silent star, William Haines,
who became a renowned
interior designer in Hollywood,
but Haines turned him down.
"No mascara," he told Billy.
Aside from the spectacle of three huge
stars now reduced to "waxworks",
look how dreadfully Norma
belittles Joe in this scene.
She's emasculating him just as the
repo men come to take away his car.
He calls it a matter of life and death,
as the loss of a car in LA could be.
This scene marks the end of whatever
sense of independence Gillis has left.
He's forced to realise here just how
much of a kept boy he has become.
And here it is: Norma's fabulous
1932 Isotta Fraschini.
"The whole thing was upholstered
in leopard skin," Gillis comments.
It's gaudy, almost like a bordello,
and I think Wilder presents Gillis here
as a kept boy in a male harem of one.
And, of course, she starts in on
his clothes. She's picking on him.
He's humiliated.
He can't even chew gum.
So off we go to the haberdashers,
where Gillis gets some new duds
and a lot more humiliation.
The salespeople here obviously know
what's going on in this relationship.
Apparently, they've seen
this sort of thing before.
This guy tells Joe to "take the vicuña
coat as long as the lady is paying",
and Wilder tracks forward on that
vicuña line, very far forward.
It's funny, and the smirk
on the salesman's face is priceless.
But look at Holden's face.
He's really, really humiliated.
It's funny but also very sad.
Billy Wilder's essential tone
in three words: funny and sad.
If you look for symbols in movies,
screenwriters and directors use water
as a way of cleaning up some mess.
In "Psycho", Janet Leigh
decides to give the money back
and immediately takes a shower
to wash her crime away.
But here, this downpour only serves
to force Gillis into the mansion.
There's something corrupting about
this rain, it's dirty and depressing.
Now Gillis has become
quite the hunky whore.
Like the leopard skin
upholstery of Norma's car,
this creepy house, so overdecorated,
really starts to look like a bordello.
As Max says, "It was
the room of the husband."
"The husbands, I should say."
In other words, this is where Norma
Desmond keeps her sexual toys.
But Wilder adds a new revelation:
"What's this with the doors?"
As Max tells him, they've had
to remove the locks because
"Madame has moments
of melancholy."
In fact, so did Billy Wilder.
Like a lot of comedians,
Wilder was often morose,
hyper but morose, and moody.
The difference is that Wilder
only had moments of despair,
whereas Norma Desmond is suicidal
and more or less insane.
And look at her room. Again,
an extension of her personality.
Norma's New Year's party
is a pivotal moment.
It's a series of scenes,
beginning with this one.
It marks a major transition for Gillis's
character, and for Norma's too.
And this transition takes
a little while to play out.
On the stairs, Gillis says,
"It was at the party"
"that he discovered what Norma
Desmond really felt about him."
My question is, where has he been?
Hasn't he been watching this movie?
I guess not, he's in it.
The point is, he's been narrating
but he's understood nothing.
He's been a dope, a sentiment
to which I'm sure he'd agree.
In fact, he does call
himself an idiot here.
Notice Norma's outfit here.
She's got that drape over her arm.
Looks rather like a veil, doesn't it?
Yes, I think it's symbolic:
Edith Head's update of Salome's
famous Dance of the Seven Veils.
For Wilder, the dance we'll soon see
also serves as a prelude
to the last scene of the film.
As creepy as this is,
it's also quite dazzling.
Unlimited champagne, that enormous
cake, your own band playing,
Valentino's tile floor...
Gillis's situation may be sordid, but he
has good reason to go through with it.
We're meant to understand Gillis's
self-prostitution very clearly here.
He's living the good life. So what if he
has to hold his nose sometimes?
But the film is more
balanced than that.
Look how happy Norma Desmond is
when she's dancing with Joe Gillis.
When she stops being the lunatic
and dances with the man she loves,
Norma Desmond becomes
almost appealing, even beautiful.
Well, a little bit anyway.
Wouldn't it be great to pull off wearing
that cigarette holder like her?
How many people can do such a thing?
In a way, she's truly magnificent.
The gift she gives
Joe is another matter.
Why? Because it pushes Gillis
over the edge, it's the last straw.
Norma is now drunk and jealous,
an unpleasant mix given her dementia.
Still, as melodramatic as Norma is,
one can't help feeling sorry for her.
Leave aside the fact
that she's a gargoyle.
From her perspective, and maybe
from ours if we have any sympathy,
she's also an attractive,
wealthy woman in her early fifties,
who has fallen in love with a very
handsome and virile younger man.
Holden himself was 31 at the time.
It's painful for Norma to realise,
to her huge humiliation,
that she's just not desirable to him.
It's painful for us as well,
and I think Wilder is asking
us to feel sympathy for her.
Notice the focus pull from Gillis in the
foreground to Max in the background.
Wilder shifts the camera's
focus to Max
because what Max
is doing as a servant
is what Gillis would be doing,
figuratively, if he stayed at the house.
At the same time,
Wilder sympathises with Gillis.
It makes perfect sense for him
to leave. It's the right thing to do.
But his self-extraction from that house
isn't as smooth as he'd like.
His watch chain
catches on the doorknob.
And right away, we see the life
to which Joe Gillis is returning.
He's alone, and hitchhiking
in a downpour.
Quite a come-down from that mansion,
and all that champagne and caviar.
I must confess, Artie Green's party
is one of my least favourite scenes.
It seems a little too carefree to me.
I'm sure that hungry young people
in Hollywood can have great parties,
but this one seems forced.
They're singing the Oscar-winning
song "Buttons and Bows",
with the song's composers,
Jay Livingstone and Ray Evans,
sitting at the piano.
Another "Inside Hollywood" reference.
And we meet Artie Green finally,
recognisable to vintage TV buffs
as Jack Webb, Detective
Joe Friday from "Dragnet".
Webb wasn't just the star,
he had conceived the series,
first for the radio in 1949, the year
"Sunset Boulevard" was in production.
Adolphe Menjou is the same
vintage as Gloria Swanson,
the star of such films as
Chaplin's "A Woman of Paris",
and Joseph von
Sternberg's "Morocco",
almost always playing a dapper
and expensively-dressed fellow.
That's why Artie Green
compares Joe Gillis to him.
And here's Betty Shaefer again,
now revealed to be Green's girlfriend.
But notice how Wilder sets
poor Artie up for a fall.
He's no match for Gillis
in the stud department.
First Artie comments on
Gillis's gorgeous face,
then he compares himself
to the society queen Elsa Maxwell.
Maybe Wilder wants us to see Artie as
less interested in Betty than he claims.
But we'll soon see,
even before Betty does,
that Betty finds herself drawn far more
to Joe Gillis than to Artie Green.
While Betty and Joe set up
their working relationship,
here's more about Nancy Olson.
Despite her Oscar nomination,
she lost to Josephine Hull,
who was in the Jimmy Stewart
comedy, "Harvey".
She had roles in nine other films
over the next five years.
She retired from the movies in 1955,
though she made more films later.
She was married to the
composer Alan J Lerner,
and later to the president of Capitol
Records, Alan Livingstone.
Holden went on to star in
three more films for Wilder:
"Stalag 17", "Sabrina"
and "Fedora".
He became one
of Wilder's closest friends.
He also appeared in other films,
from Joshua Logan's "Picnic"
to Sam Peckinpah's
"The Wild Bunch".
Gillis has a fairly dirty line here:
"Maybe there's some paper around."
I'll spell it out: he means toilet paper,
something the Production Code would
have banned as a direct reference.
Wilder clearly thinks
toilet paper is a funny medium
on which to write notes
for a Hollywood screenplay.
Just when Joe thinks he'll
be respectable again,
his past comes to haunt him,
as it often does in film noir.
He has broken
Norma Desmond's heart...
...and she has responded
by slashing her wrists
with his razor blade.
So much for his new independence.
Now, in addition to self-contempt,
he can add tremendous guilt
to his list of emotional problems.
And back he goes.
Even in the face of Norma's
suicide attempt,
Max is protective
of her public image.
The musicians mustn't
know what happened.
Yep, it's another Hollywood cover-up.
Wilder knows how that place operates.
He'd lived and worked there
long enough to know.
This is a subtle and nuanced tone
Wilder achieves in this scene.
Gillis pities Norma,
but he still despises her,
and what she's done to him.
Norma is humiliated,
but she still maintains her pride.
When she delivers the line,
"Great stars have great pride"...
...I think we believe her.
The slightly high angle
here is important.
Gillis is narrating this morbid story,
he's effectively looking down on
himself as he makes his fatal move.
Namely, back into
Norma Desmond's arms.
And then this sad,
hideous, desolate gesture.
The third and final act
opens with Betty Schaefer
trying frantically to reach Joe.
Max says he's not there, but we
know he must be living with her,
and romancing her once more.
Here's the "stray dog" as Max calls
him, showing some beefcake.
We can see exactly why
Norma keeps him around.
Joe is back to being a kept boy,
and Wilder displays
the goods for us to see.
Notice how Joe plays the role,
even more than before,
as his relaxed physical manner
in front of Norma indicates.
This is a Production Code-approved
way of saying they've slept together.
If there's any doubt
what's going on here,
Franz Waxman gives us a lurid
saxophone interlude in the score,
when Norma hands Joe the money.
She's obviously paying for
something other than cigarettes.
And back to Schwab's Pharmacy.
A bit of dialogue here
drives the point home again.
"Where have you been
keeping yourself?" says Betty.
"I haven't been keeping
myself at all," he replies.
It's funny to watch
Betty develop a hard edge
the minute Gillis threatens
her career aspirations.
"I don't want to be a reader
all my life. I want to write!"
Despite her fresh face
and winning demeanour,
Betty is just as hungry as everyone
else in Hollywood, including Wilder.
Here's what seems to be another
overt symbol: the circling umbrella.
It's the vortex
into which Joe has fallen.
The world of mad Norma Desmond,
re-enacting her glory days.
The Mack Sennett Bathing Beauties,
Sennett being a successful comedy
producer during the silent era.
He's most famous for the
"Keystone Cops" films.
Here, Norma also recalls Mabel
Normand and Marie Prevost,
two more important figures
of early cinema.
What we're seeing here
is pretty absurd,
yet Gloria Swanson
invests this whole scene,
and its aftermath, with a genuine
joy at performing again.
Norma Desmond and Gloria Swanson
are both great performers,
and they know it.
As they prove,
with what we're about to see.
Charlie Chaplin as the Tramp,
one of the most frequently imitated
characters in all cinema.
But, like most of the imitators
of Norma Desmond herself,
these imitations usually
come off as superficial.
Swanson's, though,
strikes me as very, very good.
There's an effortlessness to it,
just like Chaplin had.
The comedy equivalent
of great dancing.
Amazingly enough,
Paramount has called.
And this is when
the scene turns grotesque.
Norma, still in her Chaplin outfit,
turns back into Norma.
It's one of Swanson's best scenes,
because she's forced to deliver
this speech with that moustache,
and she still makes it work.
Norma has talent,
charm, fame, fortune,
and it seems her dream of
returning to films will come true.
And yet, she's obviously
quite out of her mind.
Max, in this scene, notices
her make-up is a bit off.
He notices this through
the rear-view mirror,
because Max has had experience
with this sort of thing before.
But we don't know that yet.
According to Billy Wilder,
while filming this scene,
Erich von Stroheim crashed into the
Bronson Gate because he couldn't drive,
but that story is, like some of Billy's
best stories, probably fabricated.
It's lucky for Norma that Jonesy
the guard recognises her.
Only the old-timers recognise her,
as we'll soon see in greater detail.
For me, and for many people,
getting inside a studio is pretty
exciting, and Wilder knows that.
In the sound stage, we have a great high-
angle shot encompassing everything;
the set, the camera, the boom,
the crew, the lighting superstructure,
and he punctuates the shot
with that flashing light bulb,
just to pump up
the energy a little more.
Despite its bitterness toward Hollywood,
this is a movie for movie lovers,
and this whole sequence
is about loving movies.
It's a Cecil B DeMille epic,
so we've got these glamorous
Biblical creatures running around,
in inane and overblown costumes.
Notice the chain of command
leading up to Mr DeMille:
the second assistant goes
to the first assistant,
and it is only he who dares
to approach the mastermind himself.
Despite Wilder's attempt
to soften DeMille
by handing him that line about how
millions of fans gave Norma the brush,
DeMille comes off
as a fairly sour figure,
a manipulative autocrat making
one of his risible extravaganzas.
DeMille agreed to the role for
a healthy salary and a new Cadillac.
Wilder's original idea was to have
Hedy Lamarr sitting at her chair.
DeMille is filming his 1949 epic,
"Samson and Delilah",
starring Hedy Lamarr
and Victor Mature.
According to Wilder,
Lamarr asked Paramount
for $25,000 for a cameo,
so they dropped the idea.
Again, this is exciting for those of us
who haven't been inside a sound stage.
Notice the contempt with which
she brushes this boom away.
There really was
a Hog-eye at Paramount,
an old-timer electrician
named John Hetman.
Here Wilder makes it clear Norma
Desmond isn't entirely forgotten,
as all the other old-timers respond
to her with awe and admiration.
Billy himself remembered
the old silent stars.
In fact, one of the articles he wrote
as a young journalist in Vienna
was an interview with the great
Danish movie star Asta Nielsen.
But Paramount doesn't
want Norma at all.
The studio only wants her car
for a Bing Crosby picture.
Billy had worked with Crosby
on "The Emperor Waltz",
and he found the experience
less than satisfying.
Crosby was the only star
Wilder worked with
who got away not only with
changing Wilder's dialogue,
but with hiring his own hack writers
to rewrite parts of Billy's screenplay.
Look at how Wilder has DeMille spoil
Norma's brief return to the limelight.
He orders Hog-eye
to turn off the light,
and her few true fans disperse.
Billy makes DeMille seem even worse.
DeMille doesn't even have the guts
to tell Norma the truth.
Here's where Joe meets Betty again
in her office in the writers' building.
The idea of collaborating on
a screenplay was dear to Wilder.
He always worked
with a writing partner.
She's glad to see him,
maybe too glad.
She is, after all, still engaged
to marry Artie Green.
Joe's not a bad ideas man,
as far as screenwriting is concerned.
He delivers the idea of the two
characters meeting flippantly,
but it's what Wilder used
to call a classic "meet cute".
For instance, a couple
meet in a department store,
when the man only wants to buy
the bottom half of some pyjamas,
and the woman only wants the top.
That was the "meet cute" in
Lubitsch's "Bluebeard's Eighth Wife",
which was co-written by Billy Wilder.
Norma's make-over is made to look
exaggerated and ridiculous,
but these days plastic surgery is so
common among ageing Hollywood stars
that nobody bothers to hide
the surgery any more.
They still think they must look
young to be successful,
and maybe they do.
Remember that Norma Desmond
is really only in her fifties,
which makes her desire to look
younger all the more pathetic.
In this scene in Joe's bedroom,
Norma is acting the role of the
great silent actress she once was.
She performs most effectively
using her face and her hands.
She may seem exaggerated to
audiences unused to such gestures,
but it's great in terms
of silent screen performance.
"If only there weren't words, words..."
Given the already excessive
gestures she employs,
Norma herself creates
a rope of words.
The rope she referred to earlier,
and she's strangling herself with them.
Norma's melodrama only pushes Joe
to work at night with Betty.
Billy always worked
with a collaborator.
He liked the interplay.
But his collaborations with Bracket,
who co-wrote "Sunset Boulevard",
weren't always as happy as the one
Joe and Betty are about to enjoy.
They argued so much they
threw phone books at each other.
Their secretaries simply got used
to hearing the shouting and thudding.
"Mad about the boy,"
signed Norma. Well, she is.
They take a walk around
the studio late at night.
Betty's speech about being born
and growing up in Hollywood
was based on someone real: Mrs Billy
Wilder, the lovely Audrey Young,
whose mother had worked in the
Paramount wardrobe department.
Audrey wanted to be in the movies,
but because of her terrific voice,
she became a successful
big band singer before marrying Billy
and became Audrey Wilder.
They've come close
to a big clinch here,
but Joe cuts it short.
He's saving it for later.
Max's revelation here is a very
biting comment on Billy's part.
It's another harsh remark on what
happens to Hollywood has-beens.
But it's also a strikingly bitter reference
to Erich von Stroheim himself.
Stroheim never became
a star's masochistic slave,
but he let his career go to hell
after Gloria Swanson stopped working
with him after "Queen Kelly".
Notice how very dark this scene is,
there's barely any light at all.
As almost always, Norma plays
this scene, this time with Joe asleep,
as silent film melodrama.
Big gestures, big facial expressions...
This is really the only mode
of expression she knows.
"Untitled Love Story":
that's what she's afraid of.
We're back at the office working,
but Betty is preoccupied.
It's true, she's not romantically
impressed by Artie Green at all,
and instead has fallen
for the studly Joe Gillis.
In a way, we see this
even before she does.
When they finally kiss
on the balcony,
Wilder got what he wanted
on the first take,
but he called for a second
take just to make sure.
The second time, he let them kiss
and kiss
and kiss.
All without calling "Cut".
Finally, the crew started snickering,
then, one of the spectators watching
the filming yelled "Cut" herself.
It was Mrs William Holden,
who wasn't amused at Billy's joke.
Here's something younger audience
members may not recognise:
Norma is using the phone,
that's the sound of the dial turning.
This turns into one
of the creepiest scenes:
poor Norma, inflamed
and made mean by jealousy,
with those patches on her face,
whispering dirt into the mouthpiece.
She reveals through this dialogue,
which is directed at Betty Schaefer,
that she holds Joe
in contempt for what he is.
As she puts it,
men of his sort are,
in her view,
really worthy of derision.
She still plays everything
as silent melodrama,
but it turns to genuine emotion
when she's caught.
She's so flustered she
stops the performance
she thinks has been
to her own advantage.
When she says that line about
"Don't hate me, Joe",
it's neither funny nor grotesque.
It's quite real-sounding,
and as such, all the more touching.
When Betty arrives at the mansion,
Joe remains flippant as he
shows her around the house,
even, or perhaps because,
he's at the depth of his self-contempt.
After all, he's showing his young
girlfriend his old girlfriend's palace.
He goes on and on about the house
to explain why he lives there.
"A very simple set-up," he says.
Then Wilder gives him
a wonderful turn of phrase:
"An older woman who's well-to-do, a
younger man who's not doing too well."
All that stuff here appears
to mean something to him.
He's describing the decor
seemingly admiringly,
but his tough-talking manner only
makes us doubt him all the more.
His harshness shows he's getting rid
of Betty because he cares for her.
Does he love her?
That's another matter.
Real love may not be part
of Joe Gillis's emotional repertoire.
And so Betty leaves.
Wilder tilts his camera up to Norma.
As in her introductory scene,
she's got a very precise,
very intense light on her face.
She's still on top of him,
still controlling him.
As anyone before playing an important
scene, she checks her make-up.
This close-up of Norma on the line
"You're leaving me" is crucial.
It's sudden and scary
because it brings us close
to someone having
a nervous breakdown.
The intensity signals the end
of whatever rationality Norma has left.
At this point she's purely mad,
and she'll stay that way till the end.
Wilder has finally turned poor Norma
Desmond into a pure grotesque.
Not that she doesn't deserve it,
and not that Hollywood
isn't to blame in the end.
That's an inspired line:
"No one ever leaves a star.
That's what makes one a star."
Well, not exactly, Norma,
maybe it has to do with sustaining a
connection with an unseen audience,
something Norma
hasn't done for 20 years.
Note that she shoots
him in the back.
Wilder hated Westerns,
but even he would admit
that this violation
of the "Code of the West"
indicates cowardice
on the part of the bad guy,
in this case Norma.
So Wilder returns to the beginning,
and shows us who that
guy was in the pool.
Maybe some audience
members knew it all along.
Speaking for myself, I was shocked
when I saw this for the first time.
It seems like a tragedy, but Wilder
doesn't want to sustain that mood.
He needs a bizarre punchline,
so he cuts to Norma saying,
"The stars are ageless, aren't they?"
Yes they are, especially when they
turn into celebrity murderers.
Cut to Gillis in the pool surrounded
by policemen and photographers.
"Well," he says,
"this is where you came in."
He's grown comfortable
with being dead by now,
he's had the whole film
to get used to it.
And death hasn't diminished
his tough-talking sense of irony.
He says, "Funny how gentle people
get with you when you're dead."
Here come the newsreel
guys, from Paramount.
"Here's an item everybody
could have some fun with," he says.
He's cynical, but he's right. As the OJ
Simpson and Robert Blake trials prove,
Hollywood is still pretty heartless.
All those entertainment shows
focusing on human misery,
as long as it's about
somebody famous.
The rest of us are heartless too
in regard to famous people.
We're glued to our TV sets, after all.
They called Wilder cynical, but I think
he was just ahead of the curve.
Watch the cop try
to use the telephone.
Wilder cuts to Hedda Hopper
taking over the narration,
only her mode of expression is
classic, overblown gossip-speak.
Wilder and Bracket were friendlier
with the other major gossip-columnist,
Luella Parsons, but Hedda Hopper
had been an actress first,
and they knew she'd be
much better on screen.
There's another key
close-up of Norma coming,
to capture the moment when she
hears the word "cameras".
As I said, Wilder doesn't overuse
close-ups, here or in other films.
He saves them for key
expressive moments like this,
when Norma realises her dream
of appearing in pictures again.
In "Sunset Boulevard", Gillis
gets his swimming pool in the end,
Norma gets her big scene,
not a comeback, but a return.
Even Max gets to direct again.
It's perverse but true:
the three main characters
all get what they want.
Only Betty Schaefer gets
left out of the big payout.
Max is particularly lucky.
He directs one of the greatest scenes
ever recorded on celluloid,
Norma Desmond, descending the stairs,
at the end of "Sunset Boulevard".
Even with her ghastly make-up
and outrageous outfit,
one can't help feel sympathy
with Norma here,
when she doesn't know what scene
she's expected to perform.
It's like a nightmare,
when you can't remember your lines,
and despite the hideousness
and humour of it all,
it's also rather touching.
Gillis's lines here are telling.
He describes Norma's dream
as having "enfolded" her.
Even though she's killed him,
Joe still shows her a little mercy.
"Enfolding." It suggests that
Norma Desmond's dementia
is actually one of self-protection.
Maybe you need that in Hollywood.
More comedy here, when Norma
asks DeMille, really Max,
if she can speak,
and not waiting for an answer,
she just plunges on ahead
into her speech.
Even though she's
completely mad now,
she still finds a beautiful description
of the love of making movies,
a love Billy Wilder maintained
until his death, in Spring 2002.
"There's nothing else, just us"
"and the cameras and those
wonderful people out there in the dark."
Of course, Wilder can't help himself,
he has her gesture to us
with that creepy claw,
as she says that lovely line:
"All right, Mr DeMille,
I'm ready for my close-up."
An often misquoted line,
but as the film ends,
Norma doesn't really get
the close-up she craves.
Wilder pulls out of focus
before she achieves it.
He's right, she is out
of focus, thoroughly,
and so is the industry
that made her what she became.
This is Ed Sikov, and I certainly
hope you enjoyed the picture.