Men are haunted by the vastness
of eternity.
And so we ask ourselves...
...will our actions echo
across the centuries?
Will strangers hear our names
long after we're gone...
...and wonder who we were...
...how bravely we fought...
...how fiercely we loved?
Good day for the crows.
Remove your army from my land.
I like your land.
I think we'll stay. I like your soldiers too.
They won't fight for you.
That's what the Messenians said.
And the Arcadians and the Epeians.
Now they all fight for me.
You can't have the whole world,
Agamemnon.
It's too big, even for you.
I don't want to watch another massacre.
Let's settle this war in the old manner.
Your best fighter against my best.
And if my man wins?
We'll leave Thessaly for good.
Boagrius!
Achilles!
Boagrius has this effect on many heroes.
Careful who you insult, old king.
My king, Achilles is not with the army.
- Where is he?
- I sent a boy to look for him.
I was having a good dream.
Very good dream.
King Agamemnon sent me.
He needs to...
I'll speak to your king in the morning.
But my lord, it is morning.
They're waiting for you.
Are the stories about you true?
They say your mother is
an immortal goddess.
They say you can't be killed.
I wouldn't be bothering
with the shield then, would I?
The Thessalonian you're fighting...
...he's the biggest man I've ever seen.
I wouldn't want to fight him.
That's why no one will remember
your name.
Perhaps we should have our war tomorrow,
when you're better rested.
I should have you whipped
for your impudence!
Perhaps you should fight him.
Achilles.
Look at the men's faces.
You can save hundreds of them.
You can end this war
with a swing of your sword.
Let them go home to their wives.
Imagine a king who fights his
own battles. Wouldn't that be a sight.
Of all the warlords loved by the gods,
I hate him the most.
Is there no one else?
Who are you, soldier?
Achilles. Son of Peleus.
Achilles?
I'll remember the name.
The ruler of Thessaly carries this scepter.
Give it to your king.
He's not my king.
Brothers in arms!
- Friendship!
Princes of Troy,
on our last night together...
...Queen Helen and I salute you.
We've had our conflicts before, it's true.
We fought many battles,
Sparta and Troy. And fought well!
But I have always respected your father.
Priam is a good king, a good man.
I respected him as an adversary.
I respect him now as my ally.
Hector, Paris,
young princes, come. Stand.
Drink with me.
Let us drink to peace.
To peace between Troy and Sparta.
May the gods keep the wolves
in the hills and the women in our beds.
- For the gods.
You shouldn't be here.
That's what you said last night.
Last night was a mistake.
And the night before?
I've made many mistakes this week.
Do you want me to go?
Pearls from the Sea of Propontis.
They're beautiful.
But I can't wear them.
Menelaus would kill us both.
Don't be afraid of him.
I'm not afraid of dying.
I'm afraid of tomorrow.
I'm afraid of watching you sail away
and knowing you'll never come back.
Before you came to Sparta,
I was a ghost.
I walked, and I ate,
and I swam in the sea...
...but I was just a ghost.
You don't have to fear tomorrow.
Come with me.
Don't play with me. Don't play.
If you come, we'll never be safe.
Men will hunt us, the gods will curse us.
But I'll love you.
Till the day they burn my body...
...I will love you.
A beautiful morning.
Poseidon has blessed our voyage.
Sometimes the gods bless you in the
morning and curse you in the afternoon.
Drop sail!
Do you love me, brother?
Would you protect me
against any enemy?
The last time you spoke to me like this...
...you were 10 years old,
and you'd just stolen Father's horse.
What have you done now?
I must show you something.
Where is she?
I swear by the father of the gods,
I will gut you here if you don't tell me!
My king!
She left.
With the Trojans.
The fisherman here saw her
board their ship.
The Trojans?
With the young prince, Paris. She...
Get my ship ready.
Turn us round. Back to Sparta.
High on the sail!
- Wait, wait.
- You fool!
- Listen to me.
- Do you know what you've done?
Do you know how many years our father
worked for peace?
I love her.
It's all a game to you, isn't it?
You roam from town to town,
bedding merchants' wives and temple maids.
You think you know
something about love.
What about your father's love?
You spat on him when you
brought her on this ship!
What about the love for your country?
You'd let Troy burn for this woman?
I won't let you start a war for her.
May I speak?
What you're saying is true. I've wronged you.
I've wronged our father.
If you want to take Helen
back to Sparta, so be it.
But I go with her.
To Sparta? They'll kill you.
Then I'll die fighting.
Oh, and that sounds heroic to you,
doesn't it? To die fighting.
- Tell me, little brother, have you ever killed a man?
- No.
- Ever seen a man die in combat?
I've killed men, and I've heard them dying.
And I've watched them dying.
And there's nothing glorious about it.
Nothing poetic.
You say you want to die for love.
But you know nothing about dying.
And you know nothing about love!
All the same, I go with her.
I won't ask you to fight my war.
You already have.
To Troy!
About ship! Set sail!
- I want her back.
- Well, of course you do.
She's a beautiful woman.
I want her back so I can kill her
with my own two hands.
I won't rest till I've burned Troy
to the ground.
I thought you wanted peace with Troy.
I should have listened to you.
Peace is for the women...
...and the weak.
Empires are forged by war.
All my life, I've stood by your side,
fought your enemies.
You're the elder, you reap the glory.
This is the way of the world.
But have I ever complained, brother?
Have I ever asked you for anything?
Never. You're a man of honor.
Will you go to war with me, brother?
I always thought my brother's wife
was a foolish woman...
...but she's proved to be very useful.
The Trojans have never been conquered.
Some say they can't be conquered.
Old King Priam thinks he's untouchable
behind his high walls.
He thinks the sun god will protect him.
But the gods protect only...
...the strong!
If Troy falls...
...I control the Aegean.
Hector commands the finest army
in the east.
I'll attack them with the greatest force
the world has ever seen.
I want all the kings of Greece
and their armies.
Send emissaries in the morning.
One last thing.
We need Achilles and his Myrmidons.
Achilles.
He can't be controlled.
He's as likely to fight us as the Trojans.
We don't need to control him,
we need to unleash him.
That man was born to end lives.
Yes, he's a gifted killer.
But he threatens everything I've built.
Before me, Greece was nothing.
I brought all the
Greek kingdoms together.
I created a nation out of fire worshipers
and snake eaters!
I build the future, Nestor. Me!
Achilles is the past.
A man who fights for no flag.
A man loyal to no country.
How many battles have we won
off the edge of his sword?
This will be the greatest war
the world has ever seen.
We need the greatest warrior.
There's only one man he'll listen to.
Never hesitate.
Nervous?
Petrified.
You told me never
to change sword hands.
Yes. When you know how to use it,
you won't be taking my orders.
Your reputation for hospitality
is fast becoming legend.
Patroclus, my cousin.
Odysseus, king of lthaca.
Patroclus. I knew your parents well.
I miss them.
Now you have this one
watching over you, eh?
Learning from Achilles himself.
Kings would kill for the honor.
Are you here at Agamemnon's bidding?
We need to talk.
I will not fight for him.
I'm not asking you to fight for him.
I'm asking you to fight for the Greeks.
Why?
Are the Greeks tired of fighting each other?
- For now.
- The Trojans never harmed me.
They insulted Greece.
They insulted one greek. A man who couldn't hold
on to his wife. What business is that of mine?
Your business is war, my friend.
Is it? The man has no honor.
Let Achilles fight for honor.
Let Agamemnon fight for power.
And let the gods decide
which man to glorify.
- For the Greeks!
- Forget Agamemnon.
Fight for me.
My wife will feel much better
if she knows you're by my side.
I'll feel much better.
We're sending the largest fleet
that ever sailed.
A thousand ships.
Prince Hector.
Is he as good a warrior as they say?
The best of all the Trojans.
Some say he's better
than all the Greeks too.
Even if your cousin doesn't come...
...I hope you'll join us, Patroclus.
We could use a strong arm like yours.
Play your tricks on me,
but not my cousin.
You have your swords. I have my tricks.
We play with the toys the gods give us.
We sail for Troy in three days.
This war will never be forgotten.
Nor will the heroes who fight in it.
I knew they would come for you.
Long before you were born...
...I knew they would come.
They want you to fight in Troy.
I'm making you
another seashell necklace.
Like the ones I made you
when you were a boy.
Do you remember?
Mother...
...tonight, I decide.
If you stay in Lárisa...
...you will find peace.
You will find a wonderful woman.
You will have sons and daughters,
and they will have children.
And they will love you.
When you are gone,
they will remember you.
But when your children are dead
and their children after them...
...your name will be lost.
If you go to Troy...
...glory will be yours.
They will write stories about your
victories for thousands of years.
The world will remember your name.
But if you go to Troy...
...you will never come home.
For your glory walks hand in hand
with your doom.
And I shall never see you again.
- My son.
- Father.
Paris.
Father.
- This is Helen.
- Helen?
Helen of Sparta?
Helen of Troy.
I've heard rumors of your beauty.
For once...
...the gossips were right.
Welcome.
Come, you must be tired.
Look.
He's grown.
He is strong.
- Briseis!
- Paris!
Beloved cousin, your beauty grows
with each new moon.
Briseis.
A servant of Apollo now.
The young men of Troy were devastated
when Briseis chose the virgin robes.
Father...
...I know this is the last thing we need.
It is the will of the gods.
Everything is in their hands.
- But I'm surprised you let him bring her.
- If I'd let him fight Menelaus for her...
...you'd be burning a son's body,
instead of welcoming a daughter.
We could send peace envoys
to Menelaus.
You know Menelaus.
He'd spear their heads to his gate.
What would you have me do?
Put her on a ship and send her home.
Women have always loved Paris,
and he has loved them back.
But this is different.
Something has changed in him.
If we send her home to Menelaus,
he will follow her.
This is my country,
and these are my countrymen.
I don't want to see them suffer
so my brother can have his prize.
It's not just the Spartans
coming after her.
By now, Menelaus has gone
to Agamemnon.
And Agamemnon has wanted
to destroy us for years.
Enemies have been attacking us
for centuries. Our walls still stand.
Father, we can't win this war.
Apollo watches over us.
Even Agamemnon
is no match for the gods.
And how many battalions
does the sun god command?
Do not mock the gods.
They're coming for me.
The wind is bringing them closer.
What if we left?
Tonight. Right now.
What if we went down to the stables,
took two horses and left?
Ride east, keep riding.
- And go where?
- Away from here.
I could hunt deer, rabbit. I could feed us.
But this is your home.
You left your home for me.
Sparta was never my home.
My parents sent my there when I was 16
to marry Menelaus.
But it was never my home.
We'll live off the land.
No more palaces for us. No more
servants. We don't need any of that.
And your family?
We'd be protecting my family. If we're
not here, what's the need for war?
Menelaus won't give up.
He'll track us to the end of the world.
He doesn't know these lands. I do.
We can lose ourselves in a day.
You don't know Menelaus.
You don't know his brother.
They'll burn every house in Troy
to find us.
They'll never believe we've left.
And even if they do,
they'll burn it for spite.
Then I'll make it easy for him to find me.
I'll walk right up to him
and tell him you're mine.
You're very young, my love.
Look at that.
Take up your positions!
My lord?
Should we wait for the others?
- They brought us here for war, didn't they?
- Yes, but Agamemnon's orders...
You fight for me, Eudorus,
or Agamemnon?
For you, my lord.
Then fight for me. And let the servants
of Agamemnon fight for him.
Black sail.
It's Achilles.
What's the fool doing?
He's going to take the beach of Troy
with 50 men?
Make way there! Make way!
Tecton, is the Apollonian Guard ready?
- Waiting at the city gates.
- Good. I'll be right there.
Lysander, how long
before the army is ready?
Half of our men are still coming in
from the countryside. We have to arm them...
- How long?
- Noon.
Make it sooner.
Patroclus!
Put down your spear.
- But I'm fighting the Trojans, cousin.
- Not today.
But I'm ready.
You taught me how to fight.
And you're a good student.
But you're not a Myrmidon yet.
Look at these men.
They are the fiercest soldiers in all
of Greece. Each of them has bled for me.
- You'll guard the ship.
- But this is a war.
Cousin, I can't fight the Trojans if I'm
concerned for you. Guard the ship.
Trojans!
All my life, I've lived by a code.
And the code is simple:
Honor the gods, love your woman...
...and defend your country.
Troy is mother to us all.
Fight for her!
Myrmidons...
...my brothers of the sword.
I'd rather fight beside you
than any army of thousands.
Let no man forget how menacing we are.
We are lions!
Do you know what's there, waiting,
beyond that beach?
Immortality! Take it! It's yours!
Fight positions!
Archers!
Forward!
The man wants to die.
On my command!
Break off! Break off!
Look at him.
Look.
Row, you lazy whores, row!
Greeks are dying! Row!
Those men down there need help. Now!
Tecton, with me.
Flank! To the flank!
Achilles! Achilles!
Back to the city! Back to the city!
The sun god is a patron of Troy,
our enemy.
Take whatever treasure you can find.
With your permission, my lord.
- Speak.
- Apollo sees everything.
Perhaps...
Perhaps it is not wise to offend him.
Warn the men.
Wait.
You are very brave or very stupid
to come after me alone.
You must be Hector.
Do you know who I am?
These priests weren't armed.
Fight me!
Why kill you now, prince of Troy...
...with no one here to see you fall?
Why did you come here?
They'll be talking about this war
for 1000 years.
In 1000 years, the dust
from our bones will be gone.
Yes, prince. But our names will remain.
Go home, prince. Drink some wine,
make love to your wife.
Tomorrow, we'll have our war.
You speak of war as if it's a game.
But how many wives wait at Troy's gates
for husbands they'll never see again?
Perhaps your brother can comfort them.
I hear he's good at charming
other men's wives.
My lord, you let him go?
It's too early in the day
for killing princes.
Achilles! Achilles!
- Achilles.
- Ajax.
You're as fearless as the gods.
I'm honored to go to war with you.
As am I.
If you sailed any slower,
the war would be over.
I'll miss the start as long as I'm here
at the end.
I've got something to show you.
The men found her
hiding in the temple.
They thought she'd...
...amuse you.
What's your name?
Did you not hear me?
You killed Apollo's priests.
I've killed men in five countries,
never a priest.
Well, then your men did.
The sun god will have his vengeance.
What's he waiting for?
The right time to strike.
His priests are dead,
and his acolyte's a captive.
- I think your god is afraid of me.
- Afraid?
Apollo is master of the sun.
He fears nothing.
- Where is he?
- You're nothing but a killer!
You wouldn't know anything
about the gods.
I know more about the gods
than your priests.
I've seen them.
You're royalty, aren't you?
Spent years talking down to men.
You must be royalty.
What's your name?
Even the servants of Apollo
have names.
Briseis.
Are you afraid, Briseis?
Should I be?
My lord.
Agamemnon requests your presence.
The kings are gathering
to celebrate the victory.
You fought well today.
My lord.
What do you want here in Troy?
You didn't come
for the Spartan queen.
I want what all men want.
I just want it more.
You don't need to fear me, girl.
You're the only Trojan
who can say that.
You have won a great victory,
my king of kings.
No one thought the Trojan beach
could be captured so easily.
A beautiful gift, Triopas.
You will be among the first to walk
in the streets of Troy tomorrow.
My father, Neleus, had this urn made to
commemorate his victory at Cyparisseis.
I present it to you...
...in honor of an even more
memorable victory.
Thank you, old friend.
Tomorrow, we'll eat supper
in the gardens of Troy.
Leave us.
War is young men dying
and old men talking. You know this.
Ignore the politics.
Apparently,
you won some great victory.
Oh, perhaps you didn't notice.
The Trojan beach belonged to Priam in the morning.
It belongs to Agamemnon
in the afternoon.
Have the beach.
I didn't come here for sand.
No.
You came here because you want
your name to last through the ages.
A great victory was won today.
But that victory is not yours.
Kings did not kneel to Achilles.
Kings did not pay homage to Achilles.
Perhaps the kings were too far behind to see.
Soldiers won the battle.
History remembers kings!
Not soldiers.
Tomorrow, we'll batter down
the gates of Troy.
I'll build monuments to victory
on every island of Greece.
I'll carve "Agamemnon" in the stone.
Be careful, king of kings.
First, you need the victory.
Your men sacked the temple
of Apollo, yes?
You want gold? Take it.
It's my gift to honor your courage.
Take what you wish.
I already have.
Aphareus!
Haemon!
The spoils of war.
No argument with you, but if you don't
release her, you'll never see home again.
- Decide.
- Guards!
Stop!
Too many men have died today.
If killing is your only talent,
that's your curse.
I don't want anyone dying for me.
Mighty Achilles,
silenced by a slave girl.
Tonight, I'll have her give me a bath.
And then...
- ...who knows?
- You sack of wine!
Before my time is done, I will look
down on your corpse and smile.
If they want a war,
we will give them a war.
I would match the best of Troy
against the best of Greece any day.
The best of Greece outnumber
the best of Troy two to one.
Glaucus.
You have fought with me for 40 years.
Can we win this war?
Our walls have never been breached.
We have the finest archers
in the world.
And we have Hector.
Yes, we can win.
I spoke to two farmers today.
They saw an eagle flying
with a serpent clutched in its talons.
This is a sign from Apollo.
We will win a great victory tomorrow.
Bird signs.
You want to plan a strategy
based on bird signs.
Hector, show respect.
The high priest
is a servant of the gods.
And I am a servant of Troy.
I've always honored the gods, Father.
You know that.
But today I fought a Greek
who desecrated the statue of Apollo.
Apollo didn't strike the man down.
The gods won't fight this war for us.
There won't be a war.
This is not a conflict of nations.
It is a dispute between two men.
And I don't want to see another Trojan die
because of me.
Paris.
Tomorrow morning, I will challenge
Menelaus for the right to Helen.
The winner will take her home.
The loser will burn before nightfall.
Father...
...I'm sorry for the pain
I've caused you.
Do you love her?
You are a great king because you love
your country so much.
Every blade of grass.
Every grain of sand.
Every rock in the river.
You love all of Troy.
That is the way I love Helen.
I've fought many wars in my time.
Some were fought for land,
some for power, some for glory.
I suppose fighting for love makes
more sense than all the rest.
But I won't be the one fighting.
The sword of Troy.
My father carried this sword,
and his father before him...
...all the way back
to the founding of Troy.
The history of our people
was written with this sword.
Carry it with you tomorrow.
The spirit of Troy is in that sword.
So long as a Trojan carries it...
...our people have a future.
The man who killed Tecton
outside Apollo's temple...
...I've never seen a spear
thrown like that.
An impossible throw.
Don't go tomorrow.
- Please don't go.
- Paris fights tomorrow, not me.
Fifty thousand Greeks didn't cross
the sea to watch your brother fight.
You know this.
You'd make a fine general, my love.
You've been fighting your whole life.
Let other men do battle this time.
You know I don't want to fight.
I want to see my son grow tall.
I want to see the girls chasing after him.
I can't lose you.
I won't survive.
I must see Paris.
Wait.
Wait!
Helen, what are you doing?
- Let me go.
- No.
I saw them burn.
I saw them burning on the pyres.
That's my fault.
It is. You know it is.
All those widows.
I still hear them screaming.
Their husbands died because I'm here.
I'm going down to the ships.
No, you're not.
- I'm giving myself back to Menelaus.
- It's too late for that.
Do you think Agamemnon cares
about his brother's marriage?
This is about power. Not love.
Paris is going to fight in the morning.
- Yes.
- Menelaus will kill him.
I won't let that happen.
- It's his decision.
- No.
I can't ask anyone to fight for me.
I'm no longer queen of Sparta.
You're a princess of Troy now...
...and my brother needs you tonight.
My lord.
My lord, the army is marching.
- Let them march. We stay.
- But the men are ready.
We stay till Agamemnon groans
to have Achilles back.
As you wish.
Are you ready to fight?
Are you ready to kill? To take life?
I am.
At night, I see their faces,
all the men I've killed.
They're standing there on the far bank
of the River Styx.
They're waiting for me.
They say, "Welcome, brother."
We men are wretched things.
I taught you how to fight,
but I never taught you why to fight.
I fight for you.
Who will you fight for when I'm gone?
Soldiers, they fight for kings
they've never even met.
They do what they're told,
they die when they're told to die.
Soldiers obey.
Don't waste your life following
some fool's orders.
Go.
Are you sure you want to do this?
I started this war.
Helen...
...sit with me.
Prepare to halt!
Halt!
Move.
I see you're not hiding behind
your high walls. Valiant of you.
ill-advised, but valiant.
You come here uninvited.
Go back to your ships and go home.
We've come too far, Prince Hector.
Prince? What prince?
What son of a king would accept
a man's hospitality...
...eat his food, drink his wine, then steal
his wife in the middle of the night?
The sun was shining
when your wife left you.
She's up there, watching, isn't she?
Good.
I want her to watch you die.
Not yet, brother.
Look around you, Hector.
I brought all the warriors of Greece
to your shores.
You can still save Troy, young prince.
I have two wishes.
If you grant them,
no more of your people need die.
First, you must give Helen
back to my brother.
Second, Troy must submit
to my command...
...to fight for me whenever I call.
You want me to look upon your army
and tremble?
Well, I see them.
I see 50,000 men brought here
to fight for one man's greed.
Careful, boy.
My mercy has limits.
And I've seen the limits of your mercy.
And I tell you now, no son of Troy
will ever submit to a foreign ruler.
Then every son of Troy shall die.
There is another way.
I love Helen. I won't give her up
and neither will you.
So let us fight our own battle.
The winner takes Helen home.
And let that be the end of it.
A brave offer, but not enough.
Let me kill this little peacock.
I didn't come here for your pretty wife.
I came here for Troy.
I came for my honor.
His every breath insults me.
Let me kill him. When he's lying
in the dust, give the signal to attack.
You'll have your city.
I'll have my revenge.
So be it.
I accept your challenge. And tonight,
I'll drink to your bones.
- My lord.
- Back to the line!
Make him swing and miss. He'll tire.
Brother...
...if I fall, tell Helen... Tell her...
I will.
Don't let Menelaus hurt her. If he...
You think of your sword and his sword
and nothing else.
Get up.
Come on.