If our gods and our hopes
are nothing but scientific phenomena,
then it must be said that our love
is scientific as well -“L'Eve Future"
[sirens, city sounds]
[helicopter approaching]
[over radio] Repo 202 to Control.
Arrived at target airspace.
Commencing data relay.
[background radio chatter]
[people shouting]
[loud crashing]
[Batou] Fill me in.
The perp killed the owner 52 minutes
ago, at crime scene #1, then took off.
Ambushed and murdered two cops
at crime scene #2, an unmapped alley.
All access points are blocked.
We storm it in 2 minutes.
That's the cyborg cop
from Section 9.
Keep your distance. I hear his bum luck
catches like the plague.
E-police want to horn in on us.
They're asking for a data link.
First it's Public Safety,
now the E-Police.
Decline their request respectfully.
[faint footsteps]
[electronic beeping]
[crash]
[woman] Help me.
Help me.
[stretching, tearing]
[explosion]
[singing in Japanese]
[recorded voice] We've had eight cases
of gynoids murdering their masters.
After each killing, they self-destruct,
electronic brains reformatted.
In each case, the model in question
is Locus Solus #2052, “Hadaly” type.
A prototype developed for testing,
they were provided free of charge
to contractors.
Now, they've recalled
all the prototypes.
According to their most recent report,
they've identiﬁed no defects
in either software or hardware.
You get all that?
Manufacturer's latest gynoids
go berserk, attacking their owners,
company panics
and recalls every one.
They can expect lawsuits
by bereaved families,
inevitable liability trials
and mammoth damage awards.
I get it all
except why Section 9 is involved.
You get it?
What you call getting it
may be just wishful thinking.
Right now, Section 9's involved
for two reasons.
First, not one single family
has filed a lawsuit.
In every case they've settled
with Locus Solus out of court.
Second, the victims
included a politician
and a retired Public Safety official.
Because terrorism's a possible motive,
it's our job to consider
if it's a matter for Section 9.
lshikawa and Azuma
are getting background on the victims.
You two check out the gynoids.
[Aramaki] No questions. Go.
Just for the record,
I didn't volunteer for this.
There's no way
I'll measure up to the Major.
That's beside the point.
I hear she's still listed as missing.
[Batou] The Major could only call
her brain and her ghost her own.
Although even she doubted
whether they were real.
Her brains and hardware
were government property
and her entire memory,
including the classified information,
were part of the deal.
The top brass only cares about
recovering that memory.
Her life is not an issue for them.
So, where do we start?
[Batou] Locus Solus is located
in the northern frontier.
The first step is to check in
with local Forensics.
POLICE
[background chatter]
[female voice on loudspeaker]
You guys...
About the gynoid
this guy wasted yesterday...
She cost us two young officers.
Don't tell me you want her back?
That's part of what
we've come to determine.
Forensics is up on 19,
a right at the end of the hall.
- Need a guide?
- No thanks, we'll skip the tour.
“Birds never peck
at green persimmons,
they wait until the fruit is ripe."
[metallic crash]
[elevator creaking]
you would've had a choice word or two
for guys like us
swooping down
to horn in on your case.
[Togusa] That's why it's so irritating.
It's like watching my old self.
[chuckling]
“It is no use to blame the looking glass
if your face is askew.
The mirror is not an instrument
of enlightenment but of illusion."
Well, neither of us has looks
worth staring at in the mirror.
[door opens]
[bubbling]
[electronic whirring]
[Haraway] You can come all you want,
I'm not sharing this investigation.
And if you're too persistent,
I'll have you detained.
l'm Togusa, Public Safety Section 9.
This scary-looking fellow...
Blew her apart with double-O buckshot.
A 50 caliber hollow point
would've left her easier to reconstruct.
She wasted 3 people,
two of 'em cops.
She was trying to commit suicide
before you shot her. Isn't that right?
- "Commit suicide" meaning... Miss...
- [Haraway] Haraway.
Miss Haraway, how exactly
would a robot kill itself?
By intentionally malfunctioning,
these gynoids are capable of
self-authorizing attacks against humans.
This liberates them from Moral Code #3.
[Togusa] Which stipulates, “Maintain
existence without injuring humans."
lsn't “self-destruction” more accurate?
[exhaling]
If you assume differences between
humans and machines are obvious.
[Togusa] Are such “suicides”
confined to a particular model?
[Haraway] Not necessarily.
In recent years we've seen a surge
of robot related problems,
especially among the “pets”.
[Togusa] The cause?
[Haraway] E-brain contamination
from microbes and viruses,
human production errors,
functional defects from wear-and-tear.
- Take your pick, but...
- [Togusa] But?
[Haraway] I say it's because humans
discard robots once they're redundant.
When owners trade up to newer models,
some of those abandoned
become vagrants, and degenerate.
Perhaps it’s a protest
against their own obsolescence.
Absurd.
[Haraway] Humans are different
from robots.
That’s an article of faith,
like black isn't white.
It’s no more helpful than the basic fact
that humans aren’t machines.
Unlike industrial robots, the androids
and gynoids designed as“pets,"
weren't designed along utilitarian
or practical models.
Instead, we model them
on a human image,
an idealized one at that.
Why are humans so obsessed
with recreating themselves?
- [Haraway] Do you have children?
- A daughter.
[Haraway] Children have been excluded
from the customary standards
of human behavior,
if you define humans as beings
who possess a conventional identity
and act out of free will.
Then what are children who endure
in the chaos preceding maturity?
They differ profoundly from “humans,”
but they obviously have human form.
The dolls that little girls mother,
are not surrogates for real babies.
Little girls aren't so much
imitating child rearing,
as they are experiencing something
deeply akin to child rearing.
What on earth are you talking about?
[Haraway] Raising children
is the simplest way
to achieve the ancient dream
of artificial life.
At least, that’s my hypothesis.
Children aren't dolls!
Descartes didn't differentiate man
from machine, animate from inanimate.
He lost his beloved
five-year-old daughter
and then named a doll after her,
Francine. He doted on her.
At least that's what they say.
[whirring]
Can we get back to reality here?
I'd like your observations
with respect to the Hadaly robot,
model #2052,
manufactured by Locus Solus.
Right.
It's very well designed.
I understand it's a prototype, but
it's intended for particular functions.
[Togusa] Particular functions?
lt's equipped with organs
unnecessary in service robots.
[Togusa] Meaning?
[exhales]
[Haraway] It's a sexaroid.
Nothing to brag about to your neighbors,
but hardly illegal.
I get it. Scandal. No wonder
those families settled out of court.
When its systems shut down,
the electronic brain reformats.
That’s standard protection for
manufacturer's proprietary software.
- But...
- [Togusa] But, what?
We found a file in the audio buffer.
Care to hear it?
[recorded voice] Help me.
[repeating] Help me. Help me.
[recording repeating, beeping]
[recording stops]
[whirring winds down]
[Batou] Thanks for your help.
Uh, one last question.
lt’s none of my business, but...
No, I've never raised a child.
Nothing registered
at the ovum bank.
Thank you, Miss...
Haraway.
No need for Miss or Mrs.
[door opens]
[Togusa] She's not really the type
for technical work.
[Batou] Her reports are doubtless full
of unsolicited opinions, just like mine.
[Togusa] Which held you back
from promotion.
[Batou] We secure that gynoid's brain
for the labs at Section 9.
[Togusa] That's the last
we'll see of her.
- [Batou] She your type?
- [Togusa] Actually, I like older women.
- [Togusa] Next?
- [Batou] Follow procedure.
- Investigate the Hadaly inspector?
- [over radio] 09 calling 907.
There's been a 602
in the District 201 boathouse.
Victim is inspector for Locus Solus.
Scene secured two minutes
prior to local police.
- [Batou] Roger, 907.
- [Togusa] Unbelievable timing.
[Batou] “A fine spring day.
A carriage sprints between
this world and the next."
- [car starts]
- [brakes screeching]
You're all alone here?
Koga got reacquainted with his dinner
and went back with the corpse.
[Batou] What a wimp.
The scene, 22 minutes ago.
You made a rookie
deal with this mess?
[lshikawa] Life's a learning curve.
Here's what we've got.
Analysis of victim's brain yields...
Jack Volkerson, age 54.
Consignment inspector for Locus Solus.
He applied for leave five days ago
and vanished.
Three days ago,
he rented this boathouse.
The murder weapon,
kitchen utensils.
Inspection of the area
turned up a vehicle license
linked to organized crime.
We’re checking it out.
Seven credit cards found in jacket,
presumably the victim's.
Investigating transaction history.
38 caliber SW Model 2602.
Looks like he ran out of time.
Doubt it would've done him much good.
“An illegally powerful cyborg,"
or maybe a professional faking a psycho.
[over radio] 969 calling 906, 20 seconds
away from the scene, don 't touch.
Not a thing.
[Togusa] Let's leave this to Forensics.
[lshikawa] 907 calling 09.
We're handing the scene over to 969.
- [over radio] 09, Roger.
- [Togusa sighs]
It's my daughter's birthday.
- [lshikawa] Family man, huh?
- I'll drop you off.
- Wrong direction. lshikawa?
- [lshikawa] Not headed his way, either.
Okay.
Daughter's birthday takes priority.
You're a cheerful bunch.
The chief showing up at a scene?
The corpse is missing parts, that's why.
The place is all yours.
Take your time.
What’s the big deal
over a local case?
The boss has taken an interest.
[cop] Found it! Divided up in jars
in the refrigerator.
Heart, liver, kidneys,
even the pancreas.
Conscientious bastard.
[footsteps]
Fresh dog food, huh?
Stick to dry food and he'll last longer.
I can't feed him that.
You're teamed up with Togusa?
Beats being paired off with
a rookie fresh out of training.
For an ex-detective, he's got his uses.
I've got no complaints.
Except that the only one
up to your standards was the Major.
Cut the chatter, lshikawa.
J‘ But everything still holds me
J‘ In my heart
J‘ Hidden deep in my mind
J‘ The pictures are still on the wall J‘
- Later.
- Batou...
- What now?
- Stick to the dry food.
For nutritional balance,
it’s better for the dog.
J‘ And I am still here
J‘ Dreaming hopelessly
Holding in my heart
[car starts]
J‘ All the flowers you gave
J‘ Broken melodies
J‘ No more singing
J‘ No more laughing
J‘ In the sun
J‘ River of moonshine
J‘ I hear your voice
J‘ And it's calling
J‘ But I'm still alone
- J‘ I'm alone
- [dog growls]
[dog whines]
J‘ Alone J‘
[dog panting, whining]
[dog grunts]
[music box plays]
[dog whining]
[yeIpSI
[grunts, exhales]
[man #1] He died from a blow
that severed his cervical vertebrae.
The kitchen utensils
were for evisceration, not murder.
[man #2] Someone took their time
dismembering the corpse?
[man #1] So it appears.
We've confirmed the organs
in the refrigerator were the victim's.
They reveal gastritis and cirrhosis
of the liver. Apparently an alcoholic.
[man #2] Why'd the perp bother
with the organs?
[man #1] Maybe to create the impression
he was a psycho or a freak.
Or to underscore an element
of retribution or revenge.
[man #2] So we’re not looking for
an assassin posing as a thrill-seeker.
What's with the warped doorknob?
[man #1] Analysis indicates a Chinese
prosthetic limb, model NR26.
Known as the Crab Claw.
Strictly military.
Available on the black market,
defective ones, anyway.
The Claw jives with that stiff's
mutilated neck, too.
[man #2] Did you track down the license
on those yakuza wheels?
[man #1] They've covered their tracks
with a lot of illegal modifications.
[man #2] Stick to the facts.
[man #1] We tracked down records
from a nearby parking lot.
The vehicle in question's registered
to a crime group called Kojinkai.
Car's bulletproofed, with a
reinforced chassis and rear shocks.
It's been linked to a number
of assault scenes.
[man #2] Custom wheels for a cyborg.
An illegally powerful bodyguard at that.
- [man #2] So this was yakuza payback?
- But where's the motive?
The Kojinkai's an entrenched
Japanese crime syndicate.
[man #2] Drugs, hookers,
gambling, scams,
an anything-goes yakuza operation.
And a Hadaly gynoid yanked off
the big boss, Inoue's head 3 days ago.
A young turk, Wakabayashi,
took over the show.
[man #1] It’s a no-brainer.
[man #2] Avenge the boss' death
and his throne is yours.
Hold on.
If Volkerson knew
they had it in for him,
why'd he take the trouble
of hiding out on their turf?
[man #2] We don’t know.
His e-brain's wiped clean,
so the car's our only lead.
Let's leave this one to the locals.
The terrorists-masquerading-
as-deranged-robots scenario?
There's no political link
between the victims,
so I think that's a dead end.
But I'm putting Batou and Togusa on
all our berserk Hadaly cases full-time,
this one included.
The rest of you, get back
to your regular shifts. That's it.
Togusa.
See me before you go.
Talkto me.
We'll check out any links between
the Kojinkai mob and Locus Solus.
[Aramaki] I mean Batou.
Yourjob includes monitoring
your partner's emotional state.
[Togusa] I know, but I'm not a cyborg
or an electronic neurologist.
“One need not be Caesar in order
to understand Caesar."
You're a family man, right?
Do you consider yourself to be happy?
[Togusa] Well, sure.
Most of us are neither so happy
nor so miserable as we think.
The key is to stay engaged
with your life and your hopes.
[Togusa] I don’t understand.
Lately, Batou's reminding me
of the Major before she disappeared.
[Aramaki] You know,“Let one walk alone,
committing no sin,
with few wishes,
like an elephant in the forest."
[footsteps]
Chief, why did you pick me
for this job?
[Aramaki] Because it was the Major
who plucked you off your local beat.
[mechanical whirring]
[Batou] What'd he want?
Apparently you don't need to be Caesar
in order to understand him.
That goes without saying.
“The world cannot live
at the level of its great men."
You planning on starting a war?
[Batou] No need to be a yakuza to pay
them a visit, but we'll need weapons.
- I want to get something straight.
- What?
We're just going to chat
with these guys, right?
You dislike yakuza?
- Sure. Detest them.
- Same here.
But we're just going to chat, right?
Like I said, you don't need
to be a yakuza...
I know. To pay them a visit.
But you also said we need weapons.
I'm a family man.
I can always go alone.
No. I'll go with you,
I am your partner.
But I want your word.
Okay. We're just going to chat.
Avoid shooting as best you can.
- Happy now?
- Just fine.
Let's go then, pal.
[fish tank bubbling]
Who the fuck are you?
Here to chat with Wakabayashi.
Go get him.
What about, “Avoid shooting?"
I did as best I could.
[yelling]
[cat yowls]
Images!
That son of a bitch
infiltrated our vision!
[Batou] Blame your own
cheap shit electronics.
[gurgling]
[Batou] What's up?
[Togusa] Narrow, dark stairs.
What's the program?
- We take turns, I'll lead.
- No, I'll lead.
You're so damned big,
I can't cover you.
[QaSpSI
[grunting]
[gunshots]
[laughing, panting]
[Batou] Your little gifts exploded
above my head.
Even presuming they went off
at their most lethal range,
you think two grenades
are going to off an armored cyborg?
You insult me.
[gasping, whimpering]
Start by telling me about
the dead consignment inspector,
then spill your connections
to Locus Solus.
[explosion, garbled voice]
Well, look who's here.
[grunting]
Bring it on, Crab Man. You and that
claw look nasty, but I'm ready.
[mumbling]
[pained shout]
Betting on that obvious a move? Moron.
[heavy breathing]
...so we whacked him.
I'm fresh out of 3 years in the pen.
I knowjack shit about what the boss
was up to with that outfit.
Still with me, pal?
[Togusa] All I could see...
were my wife and daughter's faces.
That wasn’t your wife or daughter.
It was the grim reaper.
[Aramaki] I ordered you
to conduct an investigation.
I never said skip the paperwork
and act like vigilantes.
I certainly don't recall ordering you
to barge into any yakuza office.
This isn't the jungle and you're not
Special Forces hit men.
- [Batou] You still pissed off?
- [Togusa] I am not pissed.
And I hate to sound ungrateful
to the man who saved my life...
[brakes screeching]
But being your partner is definitely
gonna take atoll on me.
Look, it's only the two of us
on this case.
A half-assed approach
just won't cut it.
If Locus Solus has anything to hide,
they'll come after us.
So that's why you put on
that yakuza gun show.
Yeah, and if the chief was really
pissed, he'd have suspended us.
Pull over, will you?
[Batou] Later.
[bell rings]
[hushed voices]
[woman] You're in the kill zone.
[woman gasps]
[growling]
[rain falling]
Don't tamper with the settings
on that new arm of yours.
The operating system upgrades
can conflict with the weapon-control,
rendering it entirely useless.
[Batou] Then you'll have to
reformat the thing.
Hey, where are the remains
of my old arm?
Don't even think about it.
Not much left.
The organic components
in this new one match your DNA.
I suppose that, with enough use,
it'll feel like my own.
[dog whimpering]
Ouch. Hey, just hold on.
The fact that you carried him here
means that...
[lshikawa] Yeah.
I broke into your love nest.
I just couldn't stomach the thought
of him moaning with hunger,
covered in shit,
waiting for you.
Believe it or not, I'm a dog lover.
But I'm the one
that took him in for the night.
My daughter's in heaven and my wife's
fuming over her dirty carpets.
When did you start tailing me?
It's no big deal, man.
Yes, it is a big deal.
You used me as a smokescreen.
[lshikawa] With experience,
you would've caught on.
Blame it on the boss.
Is this pooch a clone?
Aren't originals
outrageously expensive?
[Batou] His was the first line
bred by artificial insemination.
It's hardly your style to let them
hack into your brain.
And any daily routine
just makes you vulnerable to traps.
I told you to stick to dry food.
But he likes the fresh stuff and that’s
the only store that carries it.
They had you going berserk,
shooting five bullets
into your own arm,
and nearly blowing away
the store owner.
He may be nuts, but it's a rare bird
that can hack into this guy.
[lshikawa] Except for the Major.
And why didn't they make me
blow my own head off?
[lshikawa] I think, because they want
to disgrace you, not wipe you out.
First, you barge into a yakuza office,
send a dozen men
to heaven or the hospital,
and that very same day,
unload your weapon in a grocery store.
So we think either you've gone mad
or your e-brain's shot.
[Togusa] But this was a planned attack.
It proves that our case wasn't random.
We can't pull out.
We'd jeopardize
the whole point of Section 9.
That's what the Major’d say.
And I’ve got a message
from the boss, too.
Stay on it,
but no more official Section support
until you come up with material proof.
We'll go to the source then,
Locus Solus.
[lshikawa] Nothing preserves
secrecy like speed.
You’re going to the northern frontier
immediately.
- Far north?
- You two can't handle it?
Sure, but what about the basset?
[lshikawa] A single man in this line of
work keeping a dog is preposterous!
And of all dogs, you choose
a high-maintenance hound.
It’s not my problem.
You guys figure it out!
[dog whimpers]
[aircraft approaches]
[Batou] This area was once intended
as the Far East's most important
information center,
a Special Economic Zone
in its heyday.
These towers survive as a shadow
of the city’s former glory.
Its dubious sovereignty
has made it the ideal haven
for multi-nationals and the criminal
elements that feed off their spoils.
It's a lawless zone,
beyond the reach of UN or E-police.
Reminds me of the line,
“What the body creates,
is as much an expression of DNA
as the body itself."
But the same applies
to beaver dams and spiderwebs.
I'll take the coral reefs
as my metaphor.
Though hardly so beautiful.
[Batou] If the essence of life
is information carried in DNA,
then society and civilization
are just colossal memory systems
and a metropolis like this one,
simply a sprawling external memory.
“How great is the sum of thy thoughts.
If I should count them, they are
more in number than the sand."
Psalms 139, Old Testament.
The way you spout these
spontaneous exotic references,
I'd say your own external memory's
pretty twisted.
Look who's talking!
[over radio] Sorry to interrupt, but
we 're about to fly over Locus Solus.
This pass is for you,
so take a good look.
[over radio] So much for the free tour.
Prepare for landing.
“His legions, angel forms,
who lay entranced.
Thick as autumnal leaves
that strow the brooks."
Now you're quoting Milton,
but we are not Satan.
[birds crying]
[singing in Japanese]
[howling]
[children shouting in distance]
[gasping] Batou!
[Batou] You sure have gotten informal,
Lin. Since when do you skip the “Sir"?
[Lin] I haven't forgotten
the debt I owe you.
[Batou] “The less one forgets
the less one can remember?"
[Lin] Oh, c'mon, Batou... Sir.
[Batou] Now you want
to butter me up with “Sir".
[Lin] Please, forgive me, I beg you.
I beseech you.
- Know a guy called Kim?
- Never heard of him.
Actually, they're a dime a dozen
up this way.
I'm just looking for a particular one.
[Lin] We got loyalty even in my line.
“There's loyalty that protects secrets
and loyalty that protects the truth. "
You cannot serve both masters,
so which loyalty is yours?
[Lin] They say there's no truth
without secrets.
[Batou] I'll ask you again,
do you know a guy called Kim?
[Lin] Never heard of him.
Actually, they're a dime a dozen...
[Batou] “Life and death come and go
like marionettes dancing on a table.
Once their strings are cut,
they easily crumble."
He used to be a long-range
military scout.
“Unfit as a commander,
unfit to be commanded,
fit only to languish by the wayside."
He bounced around between
Special Forces and Electronics,
and got into black market weapons.
His reputation turned to shit.
Wound up your garden-variety hacker.
Sounds like quite a story.
Yeah, but no matter how far a jackass
travels, it won't come back a horse.
His downfall came
when his reach exceeded his grasp.
Let’s go.
[Togusa] Batou,
the study on the top floor.
I guess we were a little late.
Pro-active firewalls must have
zapped him hacking in somewhere.
In any case, doesn't look like
he would've been of much use.
“The deceased firmly declines
offerings of fresh or artificial flowers
or birds released in his honor."
[grunts]
“Sleep not you of the dead."
Even Confucius says you should never
pretend to sleep like a corpse.
I haven't got time
for your stupid little jokes, Kim.
[laughing]
[Kim] Haven't seen you since
that landing operation in Nemuro.
[Batou] I'm here on a job.
[Kim] Meaning Locus Solus?
They came late to the robot racket,
but expanded rapidly once they focused
on high-end gynoids.
There are whispers of links
to politicians, bureaucrats,
even crime syndicates.
Wary of local regulators
for these “specialized” mannequins,
they shifted all production
to a multi-national factory ship
anchored in international waters.
They turn out
some mighty fine dolls.
Fine enough to commit suicide
after murdering humans?
[Kim] If that's true,
it's pretty unseemly.
[dishes rattling]
That would mean replicating humans
by breathing souls into dolls.
Who’d want to do that?
The definition of a truly beautiful doll
is a living, breathing body
devoid of a soul.
“An unyielding corpse,
tiptoeing on the brink of collapse."
Or reduced to a ravaged body
with an e-brain... like you.
The human is no match for a doll,
in its form, its elegance in motion,
its very being.
The inadequacies of human awareness
become the inadequacies
of life’s reality.
[Kim] Perfection is possible
only for those without consciousness,
or perhaps endowed
with infinite consciousness.
In other words,
for dolls and for gods.
Shouldn't we get back to business?
[Kim] Actually, there's one more
mode of existence
commensurate with dolls and deities.
[Togusa] Animals?
[Kim] Shelley's skylarks are suffused
with a profound, instinctive joy.
Joy we humans, driven by
self-consciousness, can never know.
For those of us
who lust after knowledge,
it is a condition more elusive
than godhood.
And this conundrum compelled you
to inhabit a doll and play dead?
Is that your reason?
[Kim] That's what Confucius says.
[Kim] It is a rare human
who knows death.
Most meet death unprepared,
armed only with ignorant familiarity.
In other words, people die
simply because it is inevitable.
[Batou] But death is a precondition
of life for a doll.
Kim chose to become a complete cyborg.
That was his reason.
and got into black market weapons.
His reputation turned to shit.
Wound up your garden-variety hacker.
Sounds like quite a story.
No matter how far a jackass travels,
it won't come back a horse.
What's wrong? Lets go.
[Togusa] Batou!
“The deceased hereby proclaims,
that on this day of this month,
“I have attained
my own celebrated death."
[grunts]
[mechanical gasping]
[Kim] Truly disturbing, isn't it?
I really understand.
The doubt is whether a creature
that certainly appears to be alive,
really is.
Alternatively, the doubt that
a lifeless object might actually live.
That’s why dolls haunt us.
They are modeled on humans.
They are, in fact,
nothing but human.
They make us face the terror
of being reduced to simple
mechanisms and matter.
In other words,
the fear that, fundamentally,
all humans belong to the void.
Enough. Let's get down to business.
[Kim] Further, science,
seeking to unlock the secret of life,
brought about this terror.
The notion that nature is calculable
inevitably leads to the conclusion
that humans too,
are reducible
to basic, mechanical parts.
“The human body is a machine
which winds its own springs.
In this age, the twin technologies
of robotics and electronic neurology
resurrected the 18th century theory
of man as machine.
And now that computers have
enabled externalized memory,
humans have pursued
self-mechanization aggressively,
to expand the limits
of their own functions.
Determined to leave behind
Darwinian natural selection,
this human determination
to beat evolutionary odds
also reveals the desire to transcend
the very quest for perfection
that gave it birth.
The mirage of life equipped
with perfect hardware
engendered this nightmare.
“God's everlasting geometry.”
[clicking]
[QaSpingi
[gunshot]
Here goes!
[Togusa] Batou!
[aircraft overhead]
[groaning in pain]
How do you feel?
How did I...
Looks like a tangle of virtual
experience hacked into your e-brain.
Just as luck appears in threes,
misfortune also arrives three times.
A gaze averted in discomfort,
a realization unspoken, advice unbidden.
Without noticing,
we welcome catastrophe.
But our world cannot afford to ignore
the first sign, let alone all three.
Itold you, Kim, I don't have time
for your stupid jokes!
When did you catch on?
[Batou] No one's easier to trick
than the trickster.
You may be
an electronic warfare specialist,
but you forget my line's intelligence.
And besides...
I come complete with a guardian angel.
Try digging up the hall image
in your external memory database.
[Batou] Jacob Grimm wrote that by
inscribing “aemaeth” upon Golem's brow,
the clay man lived by drawing energy
from the word for “truth”.
But simply removing “ae”
to form “maeth” or “death,”
returned the Golem back
to inanimate clay.
That prophecy told me that no truth
would be found within these walls.
[Kim] Someone broke through
the firewalls I devised?
Preposterous. Who on earth could!
[Batou] Like I told you,
my guardian angel.
Game's over, Kim.
It's time you started talking...
[gunshot]
That's just a doll.
You don't know when to quit, Kim.
I won't fall for another diversion.
Batou, how can you disprove
this reality is genuine
or an extension of false illusions
generated by virtual signals?
My ghost is whispering to me.
Humans are nothing but the thread
from which the dream of life is woven.
If dreams, consciousness,
even ghosts are no more than rifts
and warps in the uniform weave
of the matrix.
We are both but worthless humans,
though we walk very different paths.
Of course,
if you don't believe in ghosts,
you'll never know madness
or schizophrenia, either.
The little that's left of your body
will not rot, Kim,
but continue to function
until you meet a suitable death.
[QaSpingi
Are we actually back
in physical reality?
There is no way to distinguish
reminiscence from true memory.
Whatever they are, they can
only be analyzed after the fact.
The passage of time itself
can't be stored, so it's tough.
And inevitable, now that our e-brains
share external memories.
Do your wife and daughter,
waiting for you at home, really exist?
Or are you, in reality, still single,
living in some cheap rented room,
only dreaming of that family.
Don't you want to verify
what actually happened back there?
And if you knew
almost from the start, why?
I had to ascertain his motives.
Kim set his trap
knowing I'd come calling,
inserting the virtual reality
to shake us off.
That's about the gist of it.
Maybe he was the hacker who
planted something in my e-brain,
making me dance to his tune
and blow away my right arm.
Just as lshikawa surmised, not
many could have pulled that off.
Locus Solus suspects as much.
So you anticipated all of this.
Pretended to fall into his trap,
then beat him at his own game...
...that was my plan.
But Kim was pretty sophisticated.
I only made it out
because of the hallway clue.
The guardian angel you spoke of...
She's gone.
Somewhere beyond that “rift
in the uniform weave of the matrix."
She's definitely alive.
Merging somewhere on the vast net,
or with the entire domain.
Though that's not for me.
There are as many paths to proving
your existence as there are ghosts.
And you've got your daughter.
I thought Kim knew other paths too,
back when he and I
were in the jungle together.
- At least I've figured one thing out.
- What's that?
That I'll never cut it
as your partner.
Lost your nerve?
No, but to quote you,
I've got a daughter to go home to.
That may be, but you'll still need
to pay your way out of here.
Don’t you have enough?
We can nail Locus Solus
with the data from Kim’s e-brain.
We can only prove he interfered with an
investigation plus the ethics violation.
Besides, our investigation's
officially off the record.
So, if we're going to make charges
in those gynoid serial murders stick,
- we need material evidence.
- And Kim's a dead end.
No, he's not.
His ghost may be beyond reach, but
his e-brain's still tied to Locus Solus.
We've got to settle this case
before they clean out their operation.
There's an old saying,
“When you're neither right nor wrong,
it's time to beat the drums and attack.”
In other words, when dialogue fails,
it's time for violence.
Hey, this isn't like
barging into some yakuza office!
Then I won't count on
your Mateba revolver for cover.
“Birds seek refuge in the heavens,
fish dive deep into the sea."
[birds crying]
[Batou] I've made contact
with the escort.
[Togusa] Roger.
[man] Diving's risky
for a heavy cyborg physique.
It's so deep here, if you sank,
we'd never retrieve you.
[Batou] I used to know a cyborg
whose hobby was diving.
Don't know what got into her.
[man] I'm helping out because
you're Lin's friend,
but they say no one's
come back from that ship alive.
Then I don't know what's got into you.
- [Batou] Exactly. Let's go.
- [man] Hold on!
[bird cries]
[typing]
[Togusa] In 12 seconds,
we'll trip their sensors.
I'll send two seconds
of camouflage signal.
[Batou] Roger.
I’ve routed this thing
into the chief of security's e-brain.
[Togusa] Initiating synchronization.
[rumbling]
[breathing]
I'm in.
Forward the vessel data.
[Batou] Download complete.
Got my vision in your sites?
[Togusa] Recording now.
Wouldn't miss my mentor's assault.
You're a real smart ass.
Inﬁltra tor detected.
Rebooting security.
Review status of all onboard e-brains.
Scan for matches in memory usage
and virus size.
It may be a latent virus.
Cross monitor.
Logical contact
with the chief's e-brain denied.
Just go ahead and reformat!
Rebooting of level 2
security system complete.
Create a detour,
divert the inﬁltrator.
Rebuild the logic ﬁrewall.
Load antibodies.
Scanning viruses.
Response team,
prepare decoys for ambush.
Deploy all latent viruses
along ﬁrewalls.
Security wall 014 breached.
Error type 280 in security wall 032.
Rebuilding level 1
external security wall.
Fluctuation in enemy's proactive
ﬁrewall pattern detected.
Transmitting virus.
Pull out, Togusa. You're in danger.
They’re onto you.
They'll fry your brains!
- [Togusa] Not yet, a little further.
- You idiot! Don't be crazy.
[air hissing, gasping]
[grunting]
Illegal access
at gynoid production area.
Suspect an unconﬁrmed
latent virus attack.
Release all vaccines to thwart.
Too late, all systems activated.
Cannot establish logical contact.
Currently loading
combat robotics control software.
[loudspeaker] Warning.
Abnormality on the THO7 Line.
Security team,
arm and head for the line, I repeat.
[man whimpering]
“Veni sancto spiritus."
Been a while, Major.
How shall I address you now?
To be precise, it's just a fragment
of me downloaded via satellite.
This gynoid's e-brain lacks capacity.
It can only handle the combat
robotics control system.
This is the best I can do
for facial and vocal expression.
There should be an emergency access
terminal 50 meters down this passage.
If we can infiltrate that,
we’ll take over the whole system.
You haven't changed.
Move out. You're on point.
I'll cover the rear.
Just like the old days.
“Who can gaze into the mirror
without becoming evil?
A mirror does not reflect evil,
but creates it."
Poetics, now?
We're running low on ammo.
“Thus, a mirror bears a glimpse,
but not scrutiny."
[creaking]
[Batou] Hey, isn't that risky?
[Major] It's just until I shut down
the operating system.
Plug into the auxiliary inputs
in the floor.
I have to gain system control
or this gynoid's nonfunctional.
I'm counting on your 30-caliber arm.
[Batou] My brain can control firing,
but I've only got one clip left.
And I have my doubts about going
hand-to-hand with them.
Here goes!
Illegal onboard breach
of main system.
Onboard? Isolate access point,
erect proactive ﬁrewall.
Multiple camouflage signals identiﬁed.
No fluctuation in any terminal.
It may be an outside access.
Terminate all external network links.
Physically disengage external inputs.
Emergency control system
not responding.
Diffused viruses coalescing.
Breach in system area ﬁrewalls.
Prepare for system reset.
Isolate level 1 data.
Multiple illegal access in core system.
Our countermeasures can't keep up.
[silence]
[Major] We're in control.
All external links severed.
The ship is totally isolated now.
- We're moving?
- We're heading south,
leaving international waters
for sovereign territory.
This entire ship will be the material
evidence that proves Locus Solus' crime.
They'll come after us.
Before they do,
we'll have an escort vessel.
There. It's already done.
And we have the time to examine
the Locus Solus technique
that infused dolls with souls.
Haven't you cracked it?
You've got a hunch, too. Right?
It's absolutely silent.
They must have sealed it off.
[Major] Ghost dubbing.
In past animal experiments, scientists
mass replicated inferior copies,
but had to abandon the practice
as it destroyed the original being.
[Batou] But Locus Solus brainwashed
girls supplied by the Kojinkai mob,
dubbing their ghosts onto gynoids.
[Batou] It was the ghost that made
Locus Solus gynoids so desirable.
[faint girl's voice] Help me...
Help me...
[whimpering]
You came to help me.
Mr. Volkerson promised...
The police would come and rescue me.
I was stage four, but my friend Soana,
is already stage five.
She can't hear anything
and never answers anymore.
[Major] Volkerson, the murdered
inspector revised their ethics code.
Exposed, the yakuza served him up
to avenge the crime boss.
But Volkerson was right.
If the robots made trouble,
someone would notice.
Someone would come to save us.
[Batou] Didn't he consider the victims?
Not the humans.
What about the dolls
endowed with souls?
But... but...
I didn't want to become a doll!
[girl crying]
[Major] “We weep for the bird's cry,
but not for the blood of a fish.
Blessed are those who have voice."
If the dolls could speak,
no doubt they'd scream,
“I didn't want to become human."
Let me ask you this,
do you consider yourself happy?
[Major] A nostalgic value, I suppose.
At least I am free of qualms.
“Let one walk alone, committing no sin,
with few wishes."
[Batou] "Like an elephant
in the forest."
[Major] Always remember, Batou...
Whenever you enter the Net,
I'll be by your side.
I'm going.
[panting, barking]
She showed up on that boat,
didn’t she? Your guardian angel.
[Togusa] Clamming up again, eh? Why?
You think I'd report you?
I'll pick you up at 8:00.
I owe you for looking after him.
Why don't you come in?
Hanging out with someone else's
family just isn't my thing.
[little girl] My present, my present!
- [Togusa] I remembered, see?
- [girl shouts]
[Togusa laughs]
[dog whimpers]
English subtitles: Linda Hoaglund
with Judith Aley.