Presented by Cinema Service
Produced by Hanmac Films
57 B.C.
As the tribal age of darkness
and incantation was coming to its end
with the birth of new kingdoms
the kingdom of Shilla, founded by
PARK Hyokkose began to annex
nearby tribes with its military
power Auta The Leader of Moon
Tribe PARK Hyokkose
The First Emperor of Shilla
Why do you bear such hatred
to kill my people?
How can I forgive those who disgrace
my land with wicked spells
Your land?
We have resided here as long as
that Great Tree had been!
How dare you to claim
this land as yours?
I had given you a chance to
become a servant of my kingdom
but you've refused!
I'll grind your skin and
bones into ashes!
As long as this sword is here, you
will not trouble the world again!
THE LEGEND OF THE EVIL LAKE
896 A.D. - The 9th year under the
reign of Queen Chinsong of Shilla
The rebels are everywhere and our
people are crossing the border...
Our country is in distress
They say a hero is born
in troubled times
If you could help us to...
CHUNG Jun-ho
I never heard of a subject choosing
it's own monarch KIM Hyo-jin
Do not misunderstand
KIM Hae-ri CHOI Won-seok
I meant people suffer because of
monarch's wrongdoing
Then, you must faithfully
serve Her Majesty
One only sees
what he wishes to see
I'm helpless to protect Shilla
alone from all the rebels
The Great Emperor of Shilla
please grant me the strength to defend
the 1000 year sovereignty of Shilla.
Attack!
Executive Producer
KANG Woo-suk Thomas LEONG
Screenplay HONG Joo-ri
Adaptation
LEE Seung-moo LEE Kwang-hoon
Cinematography
KIM Yoon-soo LU Yue
Lighting LEE Seung-ku HAO Feng
I have alerted the rear guards
Sound KIM Bum-su JIANG Biao
Martial Arts Director YUEN Tak
Talwi!
Editing LEE Hyun-mi
Music LEE Dong-joon
Sound Supervisor LEE Kyu-seok
Even after a victory, they look
like bunch of stragglers
Hold your tongue.
You haven't even engaged in a
decent battle, General BANG.
Your Majesty, my duty is to guard you. So no chance
was ever given to me. Assistant Director LEE Jin-gu
Co-producers
CHOI Hee-il DOH Seong-hee
Producer Jonathan KIM
Director LEE Kwang-hoon
How will we control the overwhelming
power of the rebels?
We have to make sure our people
do not sympathize with them
Your Majesty, we should send an envoy
to China and await for their reply.
I'm afraid China will attack Shilla
under the pretext of reinforcements.
You must abolish the aristocratic
system and find men of ability.
I believe your duty is in National
Defense, not in domestic affairs.
You should mind your own duties.
Quiet.
The country is filled with thieves and
the palace is filled with conspiracies
to over throw the throne.
Biharang!
Will you stay and protect
me till the end?
Your Majesty, I'll do my best
as your royal servant.
Biharang.
Your Majesty.
Jaunbie was the name?
Don't get caught up with
a peasant like her.
Master, how have you been?
Your wound seems severe. It
must've been a fierce battle.
I'll be ok. Please don't be
worried about me.
General!
Will you marry me?
About Biharang's girl...
Her father was executed
for helping the rebels.
Your Majesty, how can you trust a
man who refuses marriage proposals
from royal families for
a peasant girl?
I have killed too many to
save my country.
That is your fate.
If you hold on to a passing fate,
it becomes yours.
Your Majesty! The rebels have
invaded Mujinju.
Their force is too strong. We
must send Gen. Biharang.
The Capital was recently attacked
by the revolting peasants.
Send Gen. KIM instead to
Mujinju for the back up!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, the rebels have
captured Mujinju!
What happened to
the governor of Mujinju?
He was killed mercilessly.
Your Majesty, only Gen. Biharang
can save us from the rebels.
Your Majesty, losing Daeya Fortress
will put Shilla in a great danger.
Allow me to defend Shilla
from the rebels.
I've put you back out in the
battlefield, again.
That is my duty.
Already 9 years have passed.
If there weren't so many battles,
you and I could've been together.
Back then...
I needed Prime Minister Wihong to
protect the throne.
However,
the only one I ever cherished in
my heart was...
Your Majesty.
I heard he was concerned about you
even on his death bed.
Yes, he was.
Biharang,
if the battle becomes too critical,
spare yourself and return to me.
General!
It will protect you.
You must be strong. Love turns
into hatred when it's broken.
- General BANG,
- Yes, sir.
Her Majesty shows too much
affection to Gen. Biharang...
General has been seriously
wounded. Come with me now.
Don't blame me for killing you.
I'm only carrying out an order.
Talwi!
Let's get a little taste
before we kill her.
I must be off. Take care of
the rest thoroughly.
There might be an ambush.
You shouldn't go alone.
The sword has vanished.
This place gives me creeps.
Let's get out of here quick.
Jaunbie!
Let's split up and look for her.
Be careful!
Jaunbie!
- Jaunbie!
- General!
Jaunbie!
General!
Get off me!
- General! It's no use!
- Jaunbie! Jaunbie!
Though she wanted to be my wife...
she never asked me of anything.
And she never said anything
for she feared she might
hinder my future.
The seal set by Emperor Hyokkose
1000 years ago has been broken.
And, now the evil spirit
of Auta is free again.
Auta! Who is he?
Before the time of Shilla, there were
many tribes who shared this land.
Auta was a leader
of one of the tribes.
My ancestors were commissioned by
Emperor Hyokkose to guard the seal.
The duty was passed down
to me for thousand years.
And Jaunbie was to succeed me...
General,
on my way home, I saw
officers dressed in black.
One of them had a large
scar on his face.
Aren't they the Royal Guards?
Who dare stops us?
Kill them!
General!
Bitch!
You're not aware of what your
officers have done?
How dare you to treat me, the Chief
of the Royal Guards, like a soldier?
Besides, this affair is
none of your concern.
Do you mean Her Majesty
ordered Jaunbie to be killed?
- I did not say that!
- Then, did you?
I know Jaunbie's father was a rebel.
You might fool Her Majesty
with your fake loyalty
but I know your dark intentions.
It terribly worries me that you're
in Her Majesty's good graces.
General!
Did you order Jaunbie to be killed?
What are you talking about?
One of your Royal Guards
tried to kill her.
I don't understand.
Your Majesty, you have no
connection with this incident?
Your anger soars to the skies.
- Put down your sword!
- You have or you have not?
How dare you to march in here
with a sword in your hand?
Throw away your sword!
Get her!
Close the gate!
That way!
Kill her!
Away with you.
So...
did you find out whose doing?
Please punish me for my disloyalty.
I could punish you for treason.
However, I could understand the
circumstances that you're under.
Keep your mind at ease and rise.
Your Majesty.
I've thought about you every moment.
Biharang.
Who are you?
Where is Biharang?
Biharang!
Guards!
Did you not hear me?
Your people do not change
even after 1000 years.
Trying to take away the only
thing that is left!
Starting with you, I'll eliminate
every living thing on this land.
The dead does not belong in a living
body! Come out of her at once!
Kill her!
Jaunbie...
She's no longer Jaunbie!
Talwi!
The Great Emperor of Shilla,
with this Sacred Sword, may
the evil spirit be defeated!
Biharang!
Talwi!
General!
Jaunbie!
- What are you doing?
- Put away your sword.
- General, she's the evil spirit!
- Talwi!
She's not Jaunbie.
If we don't kill her now, we
cannot destroy the evil spirit.
She's Jaunbie.
I can tell by the way
she looks at me.
- General!
- Believe me this once.
We don't have much time.
How can she possibly resist the
monstrous power of the evil spirit?
She's over there!
Talwi!
Get her!
Get him!
That deceitful peasant girl must've
approached Biharang
to get to you, Your Majesty.
We mustn't jump to conclusions.
However, since Biharang
protected her,
perhaps, they planned this together.
Then they are rebels! We must
order them be caught and be killed.
First, we must find their hideout.
What happened with Talwi?
He's not saying a word.
Your Majesty, since this is a critical
time, we should hold a trial.
A trial?
Why don't you talk? You shouldn't
be enduring all these sufferings.
It's not even your fault.
I did not fulfil my duty of
serving my general.
So, kill me.
Master!
I can't believe you sucked out the
poison from his wound.
It will protect you.
My promise of protecting
the 1000 year sovereignty
was a futile promise.
I couldn't even protect you...
Jaunbie.
General.
I've been having nightmares.
Do not be worried.
You'll feel better when you
get some sleep.
Drink.
I also hope for the safety
of Gen. Biharang.
I greatly honour your loyalty to your
general. However,
what if
Jaunbie truly is the evil spirit?
What if Biharang has been
bewitched by the evil spirit?
What if all was a devious
plan of the evil spirit?
It could've been its evil plan to
bewitch Biharang from the beginning.
It's sad.
Who would help him
in his time of troubles?
Talwi will lead us. Hurry.
Yes, Your Majesty.
She just fell asleep.
Tonight, a bloody moon that holds
the hatred of 1000 years, will rise.
When the darkness hides the moon,
the evil spirit will regain
its full strength.
Then, even the Sacred Sword
will be powerless.
Then what about Jaunbie?
If you could keep her away from the
moon, you might be able to save her.
Since her desire to be
with you is so great.
If I can't keep her away, then what
would happen to her?
She'll be nothing but an empty shell.
It would be Jaunbie outside, but
she'll be Auta inside.
We must sacrifice one life
to save millions.
Jaunbie!
I'm scared.
Jaunbie! Jaunbie!
It's too late for me. You must
go and save the General.
He's at the lake.
Hurry!
Let's go!
General Bang has left the palace
to kill the evil spirit.
- Did he bring any men with him?
- Only about 100 men.
And Her Majesty followed
him in secrecy.
Lead the way. I'll meet with
Biharang personally.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Jaunbie! Jaunbie!
You must fight it off!
Jaunbie!
Jaunbie! Jaunbie!
General...
If I can't be who I was again,
I want you to kill me yourself.
Jaunbie! Jaunbie! You must fight!
Jaunbie!
Jaunbie! Jaunbie! Please!
Jaunbie! Jaunbie!
Jaunbie!
Your Majesty, I'll go look first.
Jaunbie! Jaunbie!
Jaunbie! Jaunbie! Jaunbie!
Jaunbie!
General...
Master! Are you ok?
It's all over.
The evil spirit will take over
the Kingdom of Shilla.
- General!
- Biharang!
Here is the mighty general.
Where did you hide her?
I can defeat the evil spirit.
Just give me more time.
Draw!
I'll kill anyone
who gets in my way.
Stop!
General Bang! Whose order
were you following
when it was not I who ordered
you to shoot Biharang?
Withdraw!
Biharang!
Your Majesty, I cannot bear to
watch this with my own eyes.
Destroying your own country for
a shallow passion.
You're no different from
a bitch in heat.
How dare you to plot treason!
General Bang!
This is Her Majesty. Put down
your swords.
I pity your girl. She should've died
when she was supposed to.
It was YOU!
General Bang!
What are you waiting for?
Kill them all!
Your Majesty!
Is there any way we can destroy
the evil spirit?
It's hatred is too great
for us to bear.
So the 1000 year sovereign of
Shilla must end here?
How about the Sacred Sword?
The one that the Great Emperor used
to seal off the evil spirit.
It no longer has any power.
If not the Sacred Sword...
Then, can I do nothing but just
watch my kingdom fall apart?
Jaunbie.
Jaunbie!
It's me!
Please come back.
Please.
I do not know how great
your hatred is,
but I'll take the blame for all.
Let go of Jaunbi.
Take me instead! Take me!
General!
Talwi!
Talwi! Talwi!
It is not her.
Let her rest... in peace...
Talwi! Talwi!
Talwi!
If it was a sin for a queen of
one country to love a man,
then take me instead.
My people are innocent.
Stab her heart!
General.
Jaunbie.
Thank you.
Biharang!
6 month after Queen Chinsong left
the throne to her nephew Yoh,
she died in The North Palace.
38 years later,
the thousand year old
history of Shilla came to an end.