I told you on sleeping in class!
Expelled
JANG Hyuk
SHIN Min-ah
HUH Jun-ho
KIM Soo-roh
BYUN Hee-bong
Producer
TCHA Seung-jai
KIM Jae-won
Director
KIM Tae-gyun
Volcano High School
17 years of feuding, sparked
by the Great Teacher´s Battle,
have stripped the school
authorities of their power,
as self-indulgence, disguised as
self-control, grips the student body
The schools have
fallen into disarray
However, there is a legend
The one who acquires the
Secret Manuscript will end the chaos
It is a legend which disrupts the
Martial Court of Volcano High
In the 108th year of Volcano
Volcano High School
KIM Kyung-soo
This is your last chance
Today is a great day in the 5000
year history of the Martial Court
I, Ryang, Dark Ox anoint
this loyal fellow
as 2nd Ox of the Dark Oxen
Concho, the future of the Dark
Oxen rests on your shoulders
Sacrifice and broken bones will
lead you to great achievement
Dark Ox, Jang Ryang
Captain of the Weightlifting Team
You see that?
I´m sure you did, but I didn´t jump
cause someone told me to
I fell
Hey!
Doesn´t it hurt?
Yeah, it does
I have to go to
the nurse´s office fast
Did I do that?
Who else is there?
Uh, handkerchief
Volcano High´s greatest beauty
Icy Jade, YOO Chae-yi
Captain of the Kendo Team
Ryang, a loser like you can´t
have it just because you want it
Elegant Crane in a Pine Forest
SONG Hak-rim
Top fighter at Volcano High
Possessor of great supernatural power
Who the hell are you?
Nice to meet you
Kyung-soo, just transferred
Where´s the teacher´s office?
Over there?
- What´s your problem?
- Where´d you learn that technique?
Identify yourself!
The great SONG Hak-rim
hurt by a gust of wind?
Must´ve been strong
to knock down
Concho cleaning the windows
Are you badly hurt?
Well, I´m grateful
It´s been years
since I´ve used mercurochrome
That was a fearsome power
What?
Newly roasted tea leaves
Please share them
with the principal
Oh, yeah?
You know, that principal
should be a fortune teller
Excuse me?
Yesterday, while playing paduk,
he said a storm was coming
And that his shoulder ached
- And?/- And what?
I massaged his shoulder
two hours because of
that excuse
Is this good tea?
Expelled
Vandalism, assault of a principal,
harassing a female teacher?
So this school is already
your ninth?
Do you know my nickname?
A deadly snake, once
it bites, never lets go
"Cold-blooded Venom"
If you have the resolve
to keep out of trouble,
then stay
If not, you´d better start looking
for your tenth school
Why? Because I don´t forgive
even a single mistake
Do you understand me,
KIM Kyung-soo?
I will do my best
That´s what everyone says
Well, we´ll have to put you
in a class Which homeroom?
Oh, hot!
Don´t sleep in front of
the students
Right!
Put your jacket on my desk
I´ll have it cleaned
No, thank you
That´s alright
Never mind then
Looks normal enough
Introduce yourself!
KIM! Kyung! Soo!
Kyung-soo´s shy, so
he´s not good at greetings
By the way, is that brat
Concho playing hooky again?
The world´s a better place now
When I was young,
we didn´t even dream
of playing hooky
Oh, but look at the time
It´s too bad but I´ll have to
tell you that another time
Kyung-soo, take the empty
seat next to Concho´s
A little much
for your first day
Yo, transfer!
You sure took it well
They were just joking
so I couldn´t get angry
Just joking, you say?
Fine Shall I, Dark Ox,
JANG Ryang
test your endurance?
JANG Ryang, right?
You´re okay, man!
What does Dark Ox mean,
anyway?
Exercise restraint three times
to avoid even murder
Self-restraint!
You´ve got some
strength there, transfer
But no one yet has survived
a contest with Ryang
Get up
I´m not finished joking
Hey, transfer, you´re lucky
It´s too sacred a day
to spill more blood
I don´t know where
you crawled in from,
you´ll be in hot water, if you
look down on Volcano High
A brilliant scout
Shimma
Rugby team captain
My grandma brought it
from the country yesterday
Fermented bean paste soup!
Dal-chun, I´m sorry
Ryang´s real name
JANG Dal-chun
This cafeteria is not
for fighting, Ryang
When you have no appetite,
bean paste soup is the best
Writing 100 letters
she´ll never send
Single-hearted SOH Yo-sun
Kendo team asst coptain
SONG Hak-rim Today
was the last time
You did the right thing,
transfer
Restraining yourself
in front of such trash
I was very impressed
You´ll find out soon enough,
but Ryang, no,
Dal-chun is a dumbass
You don´t get it yet
Join our rugby team
Or we´ll crush your bones
so you can´t join
any other team
Transfer, beware
This is only the beginning
You don´t cage a bird
if it doesn´t fly
I´m just doing
what you told me
So you do
whatever people say?
I helped you because
you´re blind
but I´m going now
Sit down here
See, you do
whatever you´re told
Mr Principal,
I brought the paduk
book you asked for
Oh, I´m practicing
a new technique
Cross-eyed technique
Strategy most widely
used by teachers
to avoid hard questions
from students
One who can beat deadly
heat and lightening bolts
I can´t lose the Secret Manuscript,
not when it´s almost in my hands
SONG Hak-rim is
a panting puppy
in front of
the Secret Manuscript
The principal is
a blind Buddha without it
SONG Hak-rim!
Your joking days
at the top are over now
That´s an excellent move
It´s almost as
if you read my mind
Is that so?
You seem to
know my mind better
Mr Principal, as soon as you
master the Secret Manuscript
you´ll be able to see through
all the things in this world
You´re a step away from
mastering the truth
Oh, the Manuscript again?
Who´s been spreading
such rumors?
Instead,
I´ll show you an incredible
technique I´ve been practicing
The Cross-eyed Technique
Quite difficult!
You are more difficult, sir
Open a window
Open the left one, right?
I almost lost the King Horse
My head automatically bows
down to you, nurse, in respect
Principal JANG Oh-ja
Avoided the Great Teachers´
Battle Lived in seclusion
Spiritually awakened
by crowing rooster
Returned as a member
of the Non-intervention Group
Vice Principal JANG Hak-sa
Struggled in the
Great Teachers´ Battle
Bitterly regretted being
slapped by a minor
A member of the
Cram and Rote Group
What are you doing?
All your horses are dying
Oh, Learn something
new every day
Be content with any place
you can avoid wind and rain
So what if it´s a dog house?
Still, I know it´s not easy
to find a home to your liking
Looks as if you
like your cage, too
Whew, it´s not easy
The bell has rung
Brat
At 7 a.m.,
the nurse came to the Training
Hall after the forest spells dispersed
He found deadly pus-fermented
grass and the principal in
a Debacle Trance Grass soaked
in pus from nose disease
due to solving
10,000 math problems
When exposed, a red spot forms
Use your powers, and you fall into
the Debacle Trance,
very dangerous
Be brief
Yes, The nurse deduced
the culprit
was very interested
in the Manuscript
So the 1 suspect is SONG Hak-rim
The 2 suspect, the Vice Principal
Who wrote this?
- The nurse did
- Homicide!
- Louder!
- Yes!
He´s saying "homicide"
right now
He´s trying to indicate
the criminal
- h, h, h
- See,
he´s saying "h" for homicide
You sure it´s not "h" for help?
You´re also in the first stage
of exposure
You must not expend
your energy
Hurry and bring out
the Secret Manuscript!
From today, the
Training Hall is closed
While the principal is indisposed,
I´ll cast five spells to protect
the Manuscript around the clock
Let everyone know
What are you doing?
Hurry up and bring me
Hak-rim!
That´s right "H"
for Hak-rim
Conspiracy to harm a teacher,
attempted murder
Come on in
Sir?
Here
I gave it wings but it only flies
into the chicken coop
Where did you hide it? Where?
You tiresome old fart!
Where is it?
This is a conspiracy
Somebody´s conspiracy
It´s no use
This is a conspiracy
Stop,
it We all know it´s a conspiracy
without you saying it
JANG Dal-chun
I said my name is
JANG Ryang!
Strength in numbers is not
always enough, Shimma
War Breaks Out!
Come here!
You come here
Sure, I´ll take on any munchkin
I, Ryang,
give you two days
If anybody else
wants to take me on,
come find me
It´s been a while, Chae-yi
Wait just two days
Why?
You scared to fight now?
That´s right!
Now is not the time
I´ve waited this long
I can wait two more days
Our only chance is to form
an alliance led by
the rugby team
Why the rugby team?
You were beaten
just like us
So what?
Are you challenging me?
Stop it!
Both of you I didn´t
call you here for a fight
I was caught off guard
so Ryang might´ve won
But next time,
he has no chance
So all of you follow
my orders
No one here can beat Ryang
We have to combine
our strength
Right First, we beat Ryang
And then we save Hak-rim
Ha, Ryang´s easier
than Hak-rim!
What are you saying?
Hak-rim was always
the one to beat
Now, it´s just a bit
easier, that´s all
That´s right! The Manuscript is
passed down to the best anyway
With Hak-rim gone,
we can´t let the likes
of Ryang get it
Now it´s mine
Crazy asshole,
I´ll beat Ryang
You arrogant pig
Are you looking
down on the judo team?
Fine! You want a piece of me?
All of you, come on!
Meeting Adjourned
What the hell is going on?
With Hak-rim gone,
the students are more rowdy
Why do you worry so much?
Let the kids try to line up
They didn´t dare a peep
when Hak-rim was
around It´s odd
Don´t worry about
getting them under control
It´ll all end once
I get the Secret Manuscript
Right?
Just be patient
We have to keep up
appearances
I´ll expect the good
news soon
Arrogant brat
Soon that jerk will be after
the principal´s seat!
What are you looking at?
Cunning old man
Brain-wave lightening?
That´s just a myth
It´s not humanly possible
If a person is born with
natural power,
it´s possible
At any rate, a guy like Ryang
will never get the Manuscript
The problem is KIM Kyung-soo
If he decides to step up,
it becomes more serious
What are you talking about?
I´m not here about
the Manuscript
In the end,
he´ll want it too
We have to stop him
before then
What a stonehead
I´m talking about the school
- What´s the matter with you?
- YOO Chae-yi
No one can take the
Secret Manuscript from me
You never ended the chaos
You just weakened it a bit
Hurry back!
The school is full of guys
dying to fight you
Wow, did you really drench
Chae-yi with water?
That´s not it It was a mistake
Lancelot merely protected a lake
- before meeting King Arthur
- Judo?
Wake up!
Since you´re my seatmate,
I´ll give you some advice
Approach her the wrong way
and you´re doomed
You know what happened
to Shimma last Valentine´s?
He hit on her and ended
up with a chocolate wedgie
so bad he couldn´t come
to school for a week
She´s not Icy Jade for nothing
She can be cold
as ice Chilly
So cold!
Look here!
My friend, Kyung-soo!
It´s Orange Head Speak
of the devil
We still have a problem
to solve, don´t we?
- Nope
- Not so
If you and I combined forces,
our rugby team
I wasn´t ready Again!
That was so cool
Really something
Assaulting a fellow student
You know there´s no more
space on your school records
Here!
A Kendo team application
In these desperate times,
let´s help each other
I don´t usually join
delinquent clubs
We´re a little rough
but we´re not delinquent
Wait! Hold on!
Stop it
First, I apologize
The joke´s gone too far
You know that saying?
Frogs die because of child´s play
- The joke´s gone too far
- Hey!
Is rescuing Hak-rim a joke?
- Is it A joke that
he´s in jail?
- I don´t think Hak-rim Is
righteous/- Hey!
You think Ryang is?
It´s okay for him to
parade around like that?
Wherever you go,
there´s always a guy like that
Just ignore him
and let him be
Do what?
Not even fight back?
Just ignore him?
Coward
That´s right
I´m a coward
Let him go
We were wrong about him
It´s been two days,
Chae-yi
I, Ryang,
have never kneeled
before anyone
But Chae-yi,
I kneel before you,
to confess my heart to you
From the first moment
I saw you,
my feelings have
remained constant But
The best
I waited until I became master
the top man at Volcano High
Icy Jade, Chae-yi,
please accept my heart
This is a sign of our love
Your hand?
Ryang, are you ill?
No one can stop
my love
Chae-yi,
I´ll put the ring on
Stop
This is my business
Stand back
Now
Only the master of the court,
Volcano´s best is
worthy of you
That is me
Wait!
What is it?
I´m really curious
about something
Does the top guy
at Volcano High
get any girl he wants?
A man´s got to know when
to give up on a hopeless love
Begging and pestering
a girl is not manly
You know what kind
of day it is?
Do you think a pipsqueak
like you can stop me?
You need some
serious advice, man
You´ve got a long way to go
You!
Die in my hands today!
- Son! /- Brother!
- No!
You brought this on yourself
Stop it
Fine
I accept it now
You´re the best
Hey!
What are you doing?
No one will doubt
you anymore
We´ve seen enough of
your power
So let him go
Now it´s time to show
some generosity as the best
Thanks, Chae-yi
Your approval means
the most to me
Right!
When I get the Manuscript
I´ll return to you as the
true master of Volcano High
Till then
Don´t be a baby
Chae-yi
That´s my medicine
for athlete´s foot
Tonight
Let´s get wasted!
Dark!
Oxen!
What is this?
The people over there
want to buy you a drink
You think I can´t
succeed without it?
Now I´m going to
sweep them all away
Wait and see,
you old bastard
Welcome,
great cleaners!
Volcano High School
The School Five: Masters at
suppressing schools and wrongdoing
MA Bang-jin
means the secret,
logical order and
combination of numbers
We look at our
books only in this class
Are you okay?
Everyone who coughed,
step up
Can´t even do 2 octaves
You must smoke
3 packs a day
He´s a mind-reader
Smoker´s Wind-cut Technique
Terrifying technique that
blocks the windpipes
of heavy smokers
I just puff
It´s strange
I can´t feel any vibes
He must´ve hidden
it long ago
He´s a real pain in the ass
He must´ve buried
it somewhere
It´s exactly like I thought
What do you mean?
If you tell a tiger
who´s never seen
a mouse before
that it´s very scary
then the tiger may
not be able
to sleep because of fear
Of course, it´s
a weak mouse that
spread the rumor
Then it was always empty?
What the hell´s going on?
Don´t get so excited
The Manuscript does exist
Now what are you saying?
Mr. Ma, are you making
fun of me?
That´s strange
Isn´t the Vice Principal the only
one allowed in the Training Hall?
Could it be the new teachers
are after the Secret
Manuscript too?
Don´t be rash
In any case, the Vice Principal
and I are in the same boat
You still writing letters?
Arrogant brats
Give my regards to Hak-rim
- Get all The members together
- what?
Are you done?
- what?/- If The noodles
get soggy they´re no good
You eat it
Thanks
I´ve gone to a lot
of schools but
the noodles here
are the best
I can´t stand by any longer
Will you help me?
Here´s my share
I don´t have the strength
to help anyone
My help to you would be
talking you out of this
Chae-yi,
don´t do this
If you got a question,
ask it in school
What´s the meaning of this?
Would you answer me
if I asked in school?
Just look at your hair
- Don´t go out there!
- Let me go!
This is my business
Stay out of it!
Aw, you bring tears
to my eyes
It´s been a long time,
KIM Kyung-soo
Should I be thanking you?
Sure, you saved me
from being expelled
Happy?
I´m sorry about Yo- sun
I´m sorry about us
We were the cowards
I was scared
So scared I couldn´t move
If I had power like yours,
I wouldn´t let a friend
go like that
A guy, power makes him sad
The cruel days of youth
I didn´t want to fight
But guys always tried
to beat me
Kyung-soo
I beg you,
please transfer schools
If it weren´t for that accident,
that accident
Welcome
- Again?/- Mom, do We
have to transfer Again?
It´s alright
Let´s pack
I have to go now
Just tell them you were with me
I said that last time and I thought
the Math teacher was gonna kill me
You!
So you want me to kill you
or the Math teacher to?
This is the spot, right?
It´s very tense
Captain,
the Phys Ed teacher says
miss another class and we´re dead
Who´s gonna kill whom?
I´m Ryang JANG
Ryang Volcano´s best
Enticement Perfume: perfume
from the pheromone of a queen bee
I know, I wrote a lot today but
- Still, don´t kill yourself
- Kyung-soo!
Hey, move, move! What is this?
Get out of the way!
If you´re okay,
hurry back up
It´s
Here´s the Student Dean!
Hi, I´m Yoma
Yoma: Shimma´s fraternal twin
Attends Mystic Girls High School
I like guys and rugby
If a cool guy like you
played rugby too,
It´d be so heavenly
Will you play rugby for me?
Hmm, this feels so good
Have you kissed before?
Enough!
So this is how we meet,
Kyung - soo
They say she´s a nine-tailed
fox who eats the liver of boys
But she´s just a cat in heat
I transfer you and all you
do is make out with girls?
Your father would be proud
Is this the way to welcome
an old teacher?
Do my words sound
like nonsense to you?
Go, Kyung - soo!
She´s a funny one
You´re stronger, today!