In Ming Dynasty,
22nd year of Emperor Sun.
There was a civil war in Japan
among the generals.
One of the clan Toyotomi Hideyoshi.
United Japan.
Some generals planned for a rebel
and departed from their hometown.
They gathered by
the seashore of South China.
To wait for restoration
to the throne.
They communicated with
the local power.
And fought against the government.
- Announce my order.
- Yes.
I'm the in-charge of government.
The arms they grabbed is bought...
from Holland by the government.
If you return.
I can ask the emperor for mercy.
Or, everyone should be killed.
- Behead all of them.
- Yes, sir.
I'm sent by his Honour to tell you.
The arms you robbed
belong to the government.
You'll be exempted from
capital punishment if you return it.
If not, all of you will be killed.
Have you finished?
How can you talk to me like that?
How dare you?
I'll teach you a lesson
with my Holland battleship!
Who made the signal?
My Holland battleship!
Hong!
Who is it?
Invincible Dawn.
Invincible Dawn!
The men from the government.
Send them signal.
Master,
we've got signal from Hattori.
Chimp! I'll send you
to negotiate with them.
Leave if any of you
want to stay with me.
- What else...
- Chief!
- Kill all of them!
- Yes, Chief.
Chimp, let's see who is the first.
Brother...
Ling, watch out
You drink while you ride.
I'm afraid
you'll crash to hill one day.
Bull shit! Mind yourself.
After this hill,
we'll reach our destination.
You've repeated this twice.
Would you repeat it twice again?
I can't help! there're so many hills!
We'd better keep on ridding.
Flying stance!
Don't block my way!
Sword energy?
Fly! Little brother.
Brother.
Don't be afraid, just stay claim.
Oh God, my wine!
Brother! Wait for me!
Pay my wine back.
Or at least, apologize.
Go down and negotiate with him.
Leave him to me.
Yes, sir.
I can fight very well.
Do you dare to provoke me?
I've almost dead.
I've to save this bottle.
Tell me, which one I want?
Wine or life?
Such a drunk, you are lucky.
Just a waste of my time.
I think there is hope!
You just care your bottle.
Isn't it valuable than my life?
You know how to fly, but it can't.
You'd be understanding.
Oh my horse.
My poor little dead horse.
Never any complaint all your life.
Deserted and all alone in the end.
You call this justice?
It's not easy being a horse,
let alone a man.
Don't be a horse again
in your next life.
But it's even harder to be a man.
I know that.
I may end up like you one day...
or even worse.
- My body may be left in the open...
- Stop...
Well, who knows?
Don't talk about
something impossible.
What, no more wine.
How can I sleep without wine?
You still want to sleep?
Stop! Big brother,
pull yourself together.
The horse is an old friend of ours...
and we don't feel anything for him.
When do you guys become friends?
Your horse threw you down
a few days ago...
and you wanted to get rid of him.
You almost put him on sale.
That's in the past.
You have no empathy.
I understand. Men drink wine,
horses eat grass.
Instead of incense, let's burn grass
to feed him in heaven.
You mean it?
Sure! Horses don't drink wine.
Who wants a drunken horse?
Let's take the drier grass,
they burn faster.
They will reach heaven sooner.
Dinner time, brother.
Brother, you are cheating me again.
- Little brother.
- I'm not talking to you.
Well, just listen.
Our brethren and us
have been separated for a year.
We looked everywhere
for a place to retreat.
We lost contact with them.
Finally, we found Ox Mountain.
We can go into seclusion there.
Wind and snow, why forcing us?
Heroes do not last forever.
The outside world is so ugly.
We won't come back anymore.
Ever-lasting heroes?
Well, some music for you.
Tomorrow we'll hurry to the inn.
To meet with our brethren.
I wonder if they are asleep now.
Can you play some something else?
"Hero of Heroes."
Your mind is still
on the Highlander girl?
How do you know?
All you can think of
is wine and girls.
How can you seclude like this?
You must have a hard life.
I am not going to be a monk.
I don't have to live a quiet life.
"The seas laugh,
lashing on both shores."
"Canned in the waves,
we have only here and now."
"The heavens laugh
at the troubled world."
"Only they know,
who is to win or lose."
"The earth laughs,
no more solitude."
"The waves wash away
all the beauties in the world."
"The wind laughs, loneliness comes."
"Our aspiration overcomes the moon."
Chief!
Chief,
I can't hear anyone coming.
I think Ling won't come tonight.
Blue Phoenix.
I've got it, we'll keep on waiting.
That's good.
Wait!
One year over,
you play this song every day.
I'm dizzy!
When Ling reaches here,
I'll ask him to play too.
To make you all dizzy.
No matter how powerful you are.
You are always the weaker sex.
What?
Listen carefully, Chief...
A horse is coming our way.
Come up.
Good gracious!
Chief.
To make up,
shut up for the next three days.
If you speak...
You will lose your tongue.
Have some wine.
You like wine?
You'll speak up after a few drinks.
Then your tongue
will add body to my wine.
Why don't you drink up?
Show me your tongue.
Try out the good wine.
Your tongue should get used to
the wine before being cut off.
Put your tongue back into the wine.
I'm prepared to die, come on.
Chief, tell Ling that you like him.
Ask him to stay and drink with you.
I've finished my speech.
He wants to lead a secluded life.
But I'm still with the worldly mass.
He can give up, but not l.
A lot has happened
in the Sun Moon Sect lately.
My father has disappeared.
How can a Chief like me
just leave like that?
I smell danger.
Chief!
Alert everyone!
Sound the alarm.
Go up the roof.
- On guard, everybody.
- Right!
Come in at your own risk.
Attack!
Watch out!
- Disperse!
- Right!
Japanese ninjas!
Here they come, watch out!
They're coming our way.
Spread out,
we have to change our strategy.
You give me scorpions
and I give you snakes in return.
Come back.
Who are you?
Stop hiding.
Come back.
Good work.
"The Whirlwind Blow".
Energy from the sword.
"The Slaying Sword."
Watch out!
Super!
"The Slaying Sword."
"The Recoiling Whip."
Who are you?
What do you have against us?
Spit it out.
"Twin Swords."
"The Flying Bomb."
Chief.
- Blue Phoenix.
- Come this way.
You better walk fast.
"The Flying Bomb."
Looks like Ying's Whip.
She must be in trouble,
let's look for her.
Right, I'll go the other way.
Who is it?
Oh, it's you.
Why are you still with me?
Let's spread out.
I nearly go nicked.
I am going to show you.
We have no contact here.
Fighting our own people.
We better use a secret code
from now on.
In case anything happens...
We can avoid any mishap.
What's the code?
When anything comes up,
- say your own name.
- Good, that's too easy!
You're always too quick to agree.
Get away.
Why didn't you say your name?
That was our agreed code.
I panicked and forgot my name.
What did you say?
A few dead bodies over there.
Dead bodies?
Where's your sword?
It stayed with the dead horse.
Follow me.
It's over there.
Touch wood!
Inside may just be the same.
Scorpion!
One of a kind.
Perfect to be add body to the wine.
That should make a strong tonic wine.
Go in.
Fighting's still going on down there.
Take this, don't come down
unless I say the code.
Where are you heading?
The Wah Mountain Swordplay.
Watch out.
- "The Dragon in the Ocean".
- "The Seven-Star Rotation".
- The Wah Mountain Swordplay?
- Right.
Who are you?
I'm Ling.
Ling? The secret code!
"The Flight of the Star".
Wait a minute.
Right on!
Let's continue.
We're on the same side.
Get up, they are our brethren.
Good thing your technique
is not good enough...
Would have been
a few more dead bodies.
Buck-tooth, Scum Bag and Luke,
you're here.
Our own people fighting each other?
We say hello to
each other in this way.
You are quite
a few inches taller now.
She can't fit into our pants now.
Stop growing taller!
Shrink a bit!
- Taller...
- Shorter...
My turn now!
I can see that, it's not your turn.
Luke, the place was in shambles...
when you arrived?
Yes, but the smoke
was still smoldering.
Looks like the assault
was just before dawn.
Where is Chief Ying?
She must have been kidnapped.
Big brother, look at this.
This doesn't
belong to the Mainlanders.
It's not a knife or a sword.
There is a horde of Japanese gypsies
in the vicinity.
Do these belong to them?
Brother,
this belongs to the Sun Moon Sect.
Chief Ying must have been
kept hostage.
It's feud between the Sun Moon Sect
and the gypsies.
We can't be the mediator
all the time.
Chief Ying is our friend.
We should help as much as possible.
It's a never ending story
of our times.
OK... let me get something
to eat first.
There must be food in there.
- Let's cook a meal.
- Fine.
Kiddo... have you seen her?
She seems to be in the toilet.
She must be upstairs.
Always calling me Kiddo.
Don't I look like a girl?
Is it hard to be a lady?
A girl usually has extra hairpieces.
Where is Kiddo?
Kiddo, where are you?
I'm here.
Such a nuisance!
Hold on, don't fall over.
Have you seen Kiddo?
Are you blind?
Help!
My foot hurts.
Why you become crazy?
What wrong with you?
How come Kiddo's hair
look so different?
Jesus, Kiddo becomes woman!
You'd be in trouble!
What's up?
Look at me, talk to me.
Forget it, nothing.
My God!
She isn't like a female nor male.
She's wore our trousers too much.
She is poor!
Chilli pepper!
She used to lend her trousers...
to you.
Stop mentioning the past.
Too spicy?
Smells good.
Flowers?
Highlander flowers?
That's rouge for cosmetics.
It belongs to Kiddo.
All gone.
Hide it, quick!
All gone?
Use spicy powder to replace it.
- What's up?
- Nothing.
- Good.
- What's the matter?
Are you sure?
Really sure?
Really, are you alright?
Fine.
They are weird!
Two of them have gone hunting
in the nearby village.
They're not back yet?
There are bunnies and pheasants.
- Someone's coming.
- Let me see.
The scouts!
Sir, there is an inn ahead of us.
Brother...
What's the matter?
A bunch of scouts
are out in the woods.
What should we do?
Don't be afraid,
we haven't done anything.
How do you explain the dead bodies?
What's the explanation?
What should we say?
The soup is hot.
The soup is hot, and we've hot.
What should we do?
They're coming our way.
The scouts want to make contribution.
They'll think that
we've slaughterers.
Let's put on our veil
before we fight our way out.
I'm not fighting.
Are you kidding?
Didn't we decided
not to get involved?
Pack up and slip away in the back.
I know, bring more wine.
Fetch it, quick.
What about the soup?
Take it with us.
- Where is Scum Bag?
- He is washing himself.
What to do?
Such a nuisance, I'll fetch him.
Hurry up.
Master.
The smoke means
someone's still inside.
Please decide what to do.
We've been surrounded, Scum Bag.
Let's go.
- My pants!
- Forget them, run for your life.
They coming in,
should we wait for Scum Bag?
We can lie down
and pretend to be dead.
OK, hurry up.
Something's going on outside.
Maybe, there are enemies.
Let two men stay and check
if anyone's still alive.
- Yes sir, you guys follow me.
- Yes sir.
We've checked, they're all dead.
I double-checked.
Iet's go.
Catch him for the chief.
We found a horse.
I won't let them take him away.
My poor foot, delicious soup!
- Catch them...
- Yes.
Inform the troops to stop Ling.
Hurry up, he's ahead of us.
Catch them, hurry up.
Big brother.
The scouts are after him,
please help.
Get yourself armed.
Lend me a sword, anyone?
- Where's my sword?
- Hurry up.
- Take this one.
- It's mine.
A sword does not save two masters.
We'll take turns to use it.
What happened?
Ling must have gone to save Ying.
- Let's go.
- He likes wine and women!
What's up?
Strange weather!
Here they come again.
Alright, I'm at your service.
With the Sacred Volume in hand.
I'm on the top of the world.
"The Wavering Sword".
Hey, my wine.
What does that mean?
You're feeding the fish with my wine?
Good.
Excellent wine.
Perfect wine!
Good wine
deserve connoisseurs like us.
My name is Ling.
Would you mind telling me your name?
You have a problem with that?
Or else I'll give you a nickname.
Like...
Lady, are you trying to catch a fish?
Let's chat a bit more.
You babble too much, youngster.
You are trespassing my sphere.
I'll spare your life
you show your face and explain.
He can be heard without being seen.
It's too soon to tell
if he is friend or not.
He's after me, stay away from this.
When I come back
I'll give you a name.
I'm here at your disposal.
When I speak, I hope you are
on my same wavelength.
Can you hear me?
Can you?
1, 2, 3, looks it's not working.
Lady.
Must be one of her days at the beach.
How come you little thing...
Iook so plain all of a sudden.
Don't worry, I won't give you up.
Something pretty to keep you company.
You won't be alone from now on.
So many dead animals?
Let me roast one of them.
Who is it?
Brother!
We are here.
We meet in such place.
It's hard to find the way
if we get lost.
Take a seat, brother.
You should be waiting for us
in the inn.
Fortunately we are here.
I guess
there has just been a heavy shower.
The birds
have been washed down by the rain.
Big brother.
Close you eyes!
We have no clothes on.
No big deal!
I've seen nude bodies before.
Oh... your ass is no big deal!
Your ass is exposed
to the public now.
You bastard!
You are no woman, you are no man.
Are you a man or a woman?
Be asexual.
Why are you coming here?
Kiddo said
you'd save that Highlander.
She's always on your mind!
Since we're from the same school,
we are together.
But are we going into seclusion?
Then we don't have to fight
and kill all the time.
We may use violence to save people.
We can save people without violence.
How can we do that without violence?
If we are attacked, should we leave?
You'd counter attack if you can't go.
This is violence!
OK... You are forced to use violence.
Let's save Chief Ying.
But swear now,
this is your last mission.
Or, let's go back.
I swear!
No regrets!
Cross your heart and hope to die.
It's chilli pepper.
- It's hot!
- Let's see her make up.
I haven't eaten the food of my home
for long. I missed it.
We can't be defeated
by Chimp's troop.
Your general Kai was military genius.
But he wasn't appreciated
by that stupid emperor.
Instead, he was downgraded
and died of sickness.
There is no capable men
in the regime.
It's too stupid to
send small potatoes like you...
To fight against me!
I think, the reign of
the Mainlanders is over.
What a big mouth, bastard!
How dare you criticize
the government before his Honour?
How dare you call bastards?
Look up, bastards!
Can you see our flag?
It'll soon be hoisted in the capital.
You want to start a riot?
Yes, we do!
The six tribes of the Highlanders.
The Mainlanders
always bully us Highlanders.
Every regime
is result of a civil war.
Don't think that...
you befriend those Japanese Gypsies,
and you can rebel!
We've an agreement
with the Japanese General.
To suppress you.
The Japanese General?
He is busy fighting the Koreans.
He can't come on time to save you.
When he comes,
we'll be the new power.
Dawn is waiting for him all the time.
Shoot!
Help,
I don't want to be a Mainlander.
Even worse than a Highlander's dog.
You are still tough!
Say it follow me.
Long live the Highlanders.
Ridiculous.
Ridiculous?
It's useless!
Never mind! We have ample artillery.
- Fight for the right.
- Chief.
Sun Moon Sect.
Long live the Sun Moon Sect!
We are appointed by God!
Give us power.
Dawn from the East.
I'm the invincible.
- Master Hattori.
- Yes.
Eunuch Hong.
Gold?
Let's make it straight.
I would kill myself if you cheat me.
Hong's box was full of gold.
But he put his own head in it too.
Take half, come on.
Another half, take it to your Master.
Try to explain to the Central Court.
To take hold of arms.
Actually,
we've bribed most of your officials.
They help you secretly.
Go back and wait for my order.
If you don't.
Beware of the members
of the Sun Moon Sect.
Be prepared to be ambushed.
You don't have much choice.
You can kill yourself if you wish.
In fact you are going to a dead end.
Someone dares his guts.
Right on.
Your pulses are under my control.
One move and you'll be crippled.
Chimp, we've an agreement!
You'll help me to power.
And I'll help you
against Japanese General.
So that you can go back to Japan
to restore your reign.
I think you've been loyal.
Actually, this is a set up!
I know that you've got a book.
Called the Sacred Volume.
I want to learn about...
its secret.
Well, don't regret.
I won't.
Head Chief! Don't lose your temper.
No one knows
you have the Sacred Volume.
Who are you?
I come from the capital City.
Me too.
Really?
So we came from the same place.
What did he say.
Go and ask him.
Have you found Ying?
I can't understand them.
How can I find out more?
Watch out!
What have your discovered?
That's we've been discovered.
- What'll we do then?
- Let's go.
Where are my friends?
Anybody from the capital city?
Brother, he is tailing us.
What'll we do?
Take him somewhere and punish him of.
That fast?
Stop talking, let's go
The Japanese is gone.
Are we walking too fast?
Should I go back for him?
Ok, you go.
Go! Hurry up.
Wait for me! Wait!
Where are you from?
What next?
I came from the capital city.
Me too.
We came from the same place,
go ahead.
We came from the same place.
The sword position!
Sword of the Mainlanders.
"Rotation of the Stars".
Fantasy Land! Super Sword!
Sword energy!
Separating Sword.
Wonderful!
Dragon in the sky?
- What's it?
- Swaying sword.
Breaking sword.
Attacking sword!
Stop...
We're both using
the weapons of the Mainlanders.
You aren't Japanese Samarai.
Was that
the swordplay of Wah Mountain?
Don't tell him.
He is so evil looking.
Let's confuse him.
"The seas laugh."
"Lashing on both shores."
Why you know this song?
I'm from the Sun Moon Sect.
Are you?
Have you come for Ying?
She hasn't left the Highland,
follow me.
- Big brother, beware of lies.
- Let's play it by ear.
We've found it.
Ling?
- Ling?
- Blue Phoenix?
You are heavy.
Go and see the Chief now.
If you go yourself, she'd be happy.
Ying.
Ling?
I...
Ying, we haven't seen each other
for a year.
We miss you.
You look thin!
Kiddo
why are you so enthusiastic today?
It's the custom
of the Highlanders to embrace.
- Me!
- I am not her.
Just the same.
No.
what happen between Sun Moon Sect.
and the Ninjas?
Why are you risk staying
in the Ninjas place?
After my dad disappeared.
My uncle,
Dawn usurped to be the Head Chief.
Dawn is backed up by the Ninjas.
They robbed the artillery.
We're wanted by the government.
If my dad is caught by Dawn.
I think he'd be kept
with the gypsies.
The soldiers
discovered us in the lnn.
The mistook that
we were from the Sun Moon Sect.
If Dawn planned to seize power.
I'm afraid that
your father's life is in danger.
Not now.
My dad has lots of faithful fellows.
He'd control the fellows
with dad's life.
And kill them next.
Many members have disappeared
and committed suicide.
We'd have to find the Head Chief
as soon as possible.
Or else after Dawn killed
all the opponents.
He'll kill the Head Chief.
Another story of power struggle.
Listen.
Someone is coming. Sing...
In order to find Chief...
I disfigured my face
and joined the gypsies for months.
I've checked so many places.
But I could find no clue.
Maybe he is not there.
But I've found a well guarded place.
I can't get in.
He is hinting to seek your help.
Don't promise him anything.
Big mouth.
We can't help.
We'd better leave.
We once made our oath.
This is our last mission.
We're still in.
We'd retreat when in Ox Mountain.
Should we stay away from this?
No outsider
can interfere with our Sect.
One year ago,
you planned to meet again in our lnn.
Now that you have.
You can leave happily now.
No need to feel sorry for me.
Go.
Blue Phoenix. Get her back.
Brother, stay clam
Leave here first.
I'll go with Zen to look for Wu.
We can be easily discovered.
Big brother, you'll break your oath.
We swore, didn't we?
You did! I didn't!
- You fooled us!
- Brother.
I just go for investigation.
I must go to Ox Mountain tomorrow.
If I lie, I'll be punished.
Zen, let's go.
Sure you'll.
Dawn's men recognize you.
Zen and I will find out more.
We can disguise ourselves easier.
Ling!
You leave it in the inn
I'd wait for you to play it for me.
I've been waiting.
One can't prevent...
Great!
Head Chief.
After practicing the Sacred Volume.
Although you are a man.
Your skin is getting smooth and soft.
Why do you look at me so fiercely?
Don't mention
my metamorphosis anymore.
Highlanders are looked down
by the Mainlanders.
What we have done...
Is for the good of our Highlanders.
Forgive me, I'm short-sighted.
You haven't slept with me
for 6 months.
I think that you dislike me.
I think you've forgotten me Cici.
I worked very hard for our kingdom.
But how many people
will remember Dawn?
Who is heartless?
Everyone is heartless!
Why we'd keep on doing
for these heartless people?
The world is so beautiful,
many heroes are willing to sacrifice.
Do you think your Head Chief, Wu,
is locked inside or not?
The one inside may be Dawn.
Many guards around.
We'd act separately.
Let's risk our lives.
Sword, hammer, shield. Go ahead.
- Sword.
- Hammer.
Hammer wins.
- Shield.
- Hammer!
Shield wins. I'll go inside,
you'll guard outside.
Chinese are so cunning.
This is your choice.
Watch out!
A rare guest!
Retreat to the hiding place.