subtitles/timing: yuch
makotoyui@gmail.com
ADAPTED FROM:
"Calling You", "The Lost Story", by Otoichi
THEME SONG:
"Calling You" by DREAMS COME TRUE
NARUMI Riko
KOIDE Keisuke
KATASE Nana
NAKANO Hideo
KOTEGAWA Yuuko
SPECIAL APPEARANCE by IWAGI Kouichi
YACHIGUSA Kaoru
DIRECTED by OGISHIMA Tatsuya
CALLING YOU
"Only You Can Hear Me"
Who is it?
Excuse me.
I'm definitely
the only girl in this school
who doesn't have a cellphone.
Even though I'm like everyone else.
But,
I have no one to talk to.
There's nothing worse than
having a cellphone that doesn't ring.
Next person!
Aihara!
Are you there?
Yes.
Next.
It's your turn to read out loud.
Aihara.
Do you understand
the meaning of "read out loud"?
Forget it.
Next, Tanaka!
Continue where she left off.
I am...
Alone.
It's cute.
Ah, it's just a toy.
Listen to this, listen to this Dad!
I'm going to play the piano
in the school choir competiton!
Choir competiton?
Do you know
your Dad used to be a conductor?
Don't interrupt me...
Don't keep on talking
and eat your breakfast!
Ryou.
You're going now?
I'll be going now.
Have a safe journey.
Now, sit down and eat...
The first "him" is the object.
In the second sentence,
if you translate it the same way...
Um...
Do you hear a cellphone...?
Sorry, never mind.
Why?
Why doesn't everyone else hear it...?
Hmm... you don't have a fever.
But you seem a little pale.
For the time being,
just take a rest here.
Yes ma'am.
Hello?
It worked!
Yes?
Woah...
The line got connected...
Eh?
"Eh?" you say...
Can you hear me?
Yes.
Can you hear my words clearly?
Wow...
You can hear my voice...
Um...
What's this about?
Hello?
Can you hear me?
How? Why can you hear me?
I'm not sure myself.
How...? I'm not...
speaking!
Me neither.
I'm just speaking in my head.
In your head?
Yeah.
I called this number
using a spoilt cellphone.
And you picked up.
What?
What's with this person?
Me?
Yeah, you.
I can hear you.
The teacher's coming.
Teacher?
Are you a student?
Aihara-san, how are you feeling?
Yes.
I'm fine.
That's great.
You can rest till the next period.
Yes ma'am.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
I'm going to hang up now.
Hold on!
Can I call again?
This evening, at 5 p.m.
But...
By the way, my name's Shinya.
Nozaki Shinya.
What about you?
Aihara.
Aihara Ryou.
Then, Aihara-san.
Till next time.
Nozaki Shinya...
What the hell are you doing?
Stop fooling around!
That'll be a total of 800 yen.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Miki's playing the piano isn't she?
Ah, look at the time!
I'll have to make her stop.
You shouldn't play after 6.
But...!
You'll disturb the neighbours.
Ah, hello?
Aihara Ryou-san?
It's Nozaki.
Can you hear me?
Yup.
That's good.
I was thinking "what if she can't hear me...?"
But, sorry.
Even though I promised to call you at 5...
But I'm a little late.
But thankfully
I got to speak with you again.
I...
I don't really understand this...
You're not really there are you?
You're just part of my imagination.
That's our conversation isn't real.
When I think of it that way...
Well.
Let's confirm it.
Huh?
Have you reached?
Yes.
I'm at the magazine corner.
The magazines in front of you,
you've not read any of them before right?
Nope.
Me too.
In other words,
Both of us won't know
what are their contents.
Therefore,
If I tell you
what's inside these magazines,
You can't be someone from my imagination.
And we can prove you really exist.
Do you have "Gekkan Shounen Ace" over there?
Yes.
Could you pick a page from it?
Well then...
Page 12.
It's an ad.
It seems to be for a gym machine.
"Effective for training
the abdominal and back muscles."
Hold on a second.
"Effective for training
the abdominal and back muscles."
It's there...
Well,
It's your turn to pick a magazine.
Um,
Do you have "Da Vinci" over there?
Found it.
Well,
Page 32.
Ah.
What's written there?
Can't we use another page?
Huh? Why?
You can't find the page?
Um... it's not that...
A boy...
is thrusting his butt out... um.
Butt?
Ah...
Let's use another page then.
We're both real.
That's the proof.
But I...
can't really believe it...
Me too.
That I'm talking to someone else...
What a beautiful full moon.
Huh?
Full moon?
It's true.
It's still in the east sky.
Where do you stay, Nozaki-san?
Me?
I live in Nagano.
What about you, Aihara-san?
Yokohama.
Can you hear it?
What?
I can only hear your voice.
The church is ringing
the 7 p.m. bell.
7 p.m.?
Isn't it 6 p.m.?
Hold on...
On your side,
what's the date today?
11th June.
The year is 2007?
Yes.
The date is the same.
I see...
There's a time difference.
Time difference?
Between Nagano and Yokohama?
No, that's not it.
Between our mental cellphones.
There's a 1 hour time difference between us.
A 1 hour time difference?
That's the other time...
You were late the other time you called.
Yeah.
Ah, found something good.
Ah, it's nothing.
Ryou-san.
Yes?
You can call me Shinya.
Eh?
You don't have to be so formal.
Ryou-san, can you hear me?
Yes.
Then, Ryou-san, let's talk again.
Yup,
Nozaki-san...
I mean,
Shinya-san.
Welcome back.
You went there again?
Dinner is ready.
The neighbour's girl is getting married.
Let's eat, shall we?
Hello?
Shinya-san?
Huh?
Um... hello?
I got the wrong person! Sorry!
Hold on.
Don't hang up.
Eh?
It's been some time
since someone called on the mental cellphone.
I was a little surprised.
Since you went to the trouble of calling...
If it's okay, shall we talk?
Sure. But...
Ah, sorry!
I'm Harada.
I'm...
Aihara Ryou.
I see. Ryou-san, isn't it?
But...
I didn't think
there would be someone else like this.
"Someone else"?
It's another person called Nozaki Shinya.
He called me suddenly the other day.
By any chance, do you know about it?
Nozaki-san...
Ah, sorry!
Can you hold on for a while?
Next,
we'll be practising passing in pairs.
You don't have a partner?
Hey, you two! Practise with Aihara.
Ryou-san.
What happened?
Sorry.
I'm practising basketball for PE now.
Basketball?
Ah, I see.
You're a student.
Yes.
I'm a high school sophomore.
That'll make you 16 won't it?
That's nice...
You're 10 years younger than me.
Is it okay
to talk since you're playing basketball?
Harada-san?
Wow...
You work in a recycling shop?
That's right.
You might think it's strange,
when I look at things people throw away,
it feels like they're calling out to me.
They're calling out to you?
"Please pick me up.
I can still be used!"
The watch I'm wearing now
used to be trash.
It's really old, but I like it
because of it's antique-ness.
Ah, but you can't see it even if I say so.
Somehow I'm happy.
Everyone in school
uses their cellphone to tell the time.
I'm about the only one
who still uses a watch.
What does your watch look like?
It's red and round.
I've had it since I was young.
It's a bit childish.
It's a happy thing isn't it,
that red watch of yours?
Since you treasure it so much.
Eh?
I don't really...
Can't it be fixed?
Sorry, it can't be fixed.
Is my TV fixed yet?
Over here.
Hello?
Shinya-san?
Sorry, let's speak later.
"I'll fix it for you!"
Really?
You're not sleeping yet?
A music box?
Can you fix it?
Yes, of course.
"WORLD HISTORY TEST"
You can start writing now.
Hello?
You can depend on me.
It really got through?
Yup!
World history is my specialty.
Leave it up to me.
That's not what I meant...
I didn't mean I wanted you to help me...
Well, shall I hang up then?
No, hold on.
You'll be able to see a shooting star
soon in the sky in the east.
Eh?
I made a wish
when I saw it here an hour ago.
What did you wish for?
It's a secret!
I just
made a wish upon the shooting star.
What did you wish for?
It's a secret!
Hello?
Ryou?
What's up, Shinya-san?
I'm working on
something really hard now.
Something hard?
I don't have the required parts,
so it'll be tough fixing it.
But,
I want to fix it no matter what.
I see.
It'll be great if you can fix it.
After this is fixed,
After I fix this,
I thought I'd come see you.
Huh?
I want to see you.
Can't I?
I see, you rejected him?
Sorry!
There isn't anyone else
I can talk with about this.
I really enjoy talking with Shinya-san...
That's why,
if you met, you're afraid you won't like him.
Huh?
You're afraid,
so you're being pessimistic.
It's easier that way isn't it?
That way, you won't get hurt.
"Eh, isn't that guy a foreigner?"
Ryou-san.
Do you want to meet him?
Or don't you?
About that...
Um...
I...
want to meet him.
Then, the answer is easy.
It'll be fine if you meet him.
I want to meet him...
But,
now isn't the right time.
I see.
Don't push yourself then.
But,
there's no "right time"
for your feelings about meeting him.
If you want to meet him,
that's the "right time".
Hurry up, Dad!
Here, your handkerchief.
Ryou!
We're leaving now.
Remember to lock up.
We'll be back in the evening.
I'll be leaving now, big sis.
We'll be leaving!
"Will we meet? Or won't we?"
That's all I could think of...
Aihara!
Speak up more confidently!
Don't speak like a caterpillar!
What's wrong?
You sound down.
Today,
I was laughed at again.
Because my voice
was like a caterpillar.
That can't be...
That's not true.
No...
It's not just today.
It's always been like this.
Whenever I speak up,
I get nervous,
and start stammering,
and my voice turns inside out.
In the end I get laughed at.
It must be because
I don't want to talk to anyone
or get involved with anyone.
That's how I compensate
when I can't speak up.
That's why
I started making phone calls in my head.
That's not true.
I can hear your voice properly
when you talk with me.
That's because I'm talking in my head!
In real life I can't speak up like this.
You won't understand.
It doesn't matter
even if I disappear!
Even if I disappear,
nothing will change.
No one will even realise it!
That's why...
The wind...
Wow, that's cool!
The figurines are moving!
Hey, Ryou.
This weekend...
Will you go on a date with me?
Huh?
Alright, let's start off!
Just listen to my directions.
Go straight ahead,
and cross the red bridge.
I got it.
Somehow this is unbelievable...
Because it's a long-distance date?
But it feels
like you're just by my side.
Yup, I am.
Just think of it that way.
Have you been
to Kamakura [near Tokyo] before?
Actually, I lived there.
Till I was a sophomore in middle school.
Really?
Hey Ryou,
Can I ask you something?
What is it?
The bad experience you have,
when you speak to others.
But...
It's okay.
Don't worry about it, you can talk freely.
Okay.
It was when I was in my 2nd year
of elementary school.
I took part in a piano recital.
At first,
I wore a pretty doll-like dress,
I was all made up
and really excited about it.
"That dress is pretty!"
"And you're really great
at playing the piano!"
My friends praised me like so.
I was on top of the world.
But,
those were all lies.
Lies?
"Ryou really sucks!"
"Isn't that dress weird?"
I was laughed at
by my friends after the recital.
Since then,
I didn't know how to talk to others.
Of course,
I also stopped playing the piano.
I see.
It might just be that I'm timid.
But I'm slow,
so I can't
if people are being sarcastic.
So I take everything seriously.
That's why I'm scared.
Someone who's flawed like me,
has to be careful
so she doesn't get into accidents.
I understand.
It's tough to be laughed at by others.
But, Ryou,
You're wrong about one thing.
Hm?
You're not flawed.
You
consider other people's words seriously.
You consider each and every word,
and reflect on them
so you can answer meaningfully.
That's why,
you notice too many lies.
But it's alright.
It's proof that,
you're really
considering my feelings when we talk.
Shinya-san...
I really like it.
Your voice,
as well as your words.
From there, you should be able to see
a shop called "Toda Marine Services".
Yup, I see it!
I'd like you to go inside,
and get something for me.
It's something from me.
"Something?"
From here, you'll go alone.
See you.
Hold on...
Excuse me...
Excuse me!
What is it?
Sorry for coming suddenly...
I'm Aihara.
I came here to get something
that Nozaki Shinya-san left here.
It's you isn't it?
Hold on.
He used to live here a long time ago.
Here you go. Thank you!
Take care of it!
Um...
Shinya was a really weird guy.
Here you go.
He was always coming around,
saying "please fix this for me".
When I saw that face, I couldn't refuse.
He was happy just to come around.
And now he's fixing things for a living.
No matter
how many days it took to fix it,
even if it was something
he wanted he'd give it away.
Even after it was finally fixed?
Yup.
Isn't that sad?
If it was me,
I wouldn't want to give away
I tried so hard to fix.
He wasn't like that.
He would say: "Things I repaired
will always remember I repaired them."
Always remember?
Because he liked repairing things,
he got along okay as a kid.
I don't really understand though.
Shinya-san, I got it.
That's great.
Where should I go next?
It's a place I really like.
"To Ryou"
To Ryou.
The cassette recorder in the box
was something I picked up and repaired.
I'd like you to have it.
But, I have a request.
I'd like you to record your voice,
in this tape, and send it to me.
Speak loudly, and say anything you want.
Um,
I wonder if you can hear me...?
I'm Aihara Ryou.
I'm now at the beach at Kamakura.
As Shinya-san told me to,
I'm recording my voice now.
Even though I'm feeling
really embarrassed.
Can you hear me?
Shinya-san!
Is my voice carrying through?
It'll be summer soon!
Shinya-san,
When summer comes,
I want to meet you!
Thank you!
It's fixed!
Thank you so much!
How much is it?
But...
Thank you!
Bye bye, big brother!
Let's go shall we?
Mankind lives on a small sphere,
working and sleeping.
Sometimes they wish
they had fake friends.
I don't know what these fake people
do on this small sphere.
Possibly...
OK, that's enough.
You can sit down.
Hey, over there!
Keep quiet!
Aihara.
That was a really good recital.
Next, Kawanishi! The next line.
What's up, Shinya?
Let me go to Tokyo this time round.
You?
I'm supposed to be
the one who goes to Tokyo!
Don't you go around
doing these unnecessary things.
What's with those eyes?
Do whatever you want.
Kamigawa Prefecture, Yokohama City,
Naka District, Yamate Block
AIHARA RYOU
Hello?
Thank you, Ryou.
For the tape. I received it.
Really?
It already did huh.
Ah... it's embarrassing!
No, not at all.
Your voice is really cute.
Here it comes.
Thanks.
I'm always looking at it.
The tape recorder.
Really?
About that,
It was really tough
but I finally fixed it.
I didn't know
it was such an important thing...
That's why,
I gave it to you.
The way I think of it,
that tape recorder will probably
always remember me.
Actually I can...
read your mind.
No way!
Just joking!
Actually, I heard about it.
from the guy at Toda Marine Service.
Man,
that old dude didn't have to say that...
[Train Ticket: Nagano to Tokyo]
I'll leave it up to you then.
Shinya-san,
you must have used magic.
Magic?
A spell that can fix anything.
Hey Ryou,
there's something I want to tell you...
Or rather, a proposal.
What about?
Actually,
This weekend...
I'll be coming to Tokyo to get new supplies.
Whaaaat?
You're coming to Tokyo?
Yeah.
So I was thinking
whether I could meet you this time.
Will you see me?
Do you hear me?
Yup.
Will you meet me...?
I want to meet you.
Yes. I'll meet you.
I'll meet you.
Mum...
You're looking cute today!
Really?
It doesn't look weird?
Will it be all right?
No it isn't weird.
It really fits you.
Really?
Yup!
Hold on.
If you put this on,
it'll be even better.
As I expected!
Take a look in the mirror.
Ah, I'm going to be late!
I'll be going!
Have a safe trip!
Was that Ryou?
Yup.
What's with her?
It seems she's meeting her friend.
Ah I see!
That's nice.
Hello? Harada-san?
Ryou-san?
I called you a few times
because I wanted to talk with you.
Something you wanted to tell me?
Yes,
I decided that I'd meet Shinya-san.
"I really want to meet him!"
that's what I'm feeling now.
Thanks to your advice,
I gathered the courage to meet him.
When are you meeting him?
Today, now.
Now?
Where are you now?
There seems
to be interference with the reception.
Ryou-san, remember this:
You can do it!
No matter what happens.
What do you mean?
Miss, we're about to leave!
Since it's you, it'll be okay.
Eh?
Are you boarding the bus?
Sorry!
Harada-san?
What did you mean?
Ah, I got cut off...
Hello?
Ah, Ryou?
I'm on the way now.
It'll be another hour...
Ah,
but our times are different.
Don't get mixed up when you change lines.
I won't...
I checked online yesterday.
As promised, I'll meet you
at 3 at the ticket entrance.
If it's 1 hour earlier here...
somehow I'm really excited!
But sorry, I might be late.
There's a traffic jam.
It's okay.
I'll wait for you then.
Where will you be?
The roundabout at the western entrance.
I got it.
I was wondering
what you would be wearing?
It's nothing special...
Won't you tell me?
It's not really
I'd go to lengths to talk about...
All right.
Shinya-san,
Can you promise me something?
Promise?
After we meet, even if I'm not
what you imagined me to be,
don't hate me!
Don't be silly. I won't!
Rather,
I should be telling you that.
Actually...
there's something I'm keeping from you.
But I thought I'd definitely
explain it to you after I meet you.
Hm, what is it?
What happened?
Some driver
recklessly cut into the bus's lane.
Are you okay?
Yup.
Ah, sorry,
as expected I'll be late.
Even though
I should be the one waiting for you.
Don't worry about that.
It'll be fun looking for you
when you get off the bus.
Shinya-san, I've reached.
It's now 3.05 p.m.
Sorry for being late!
3.05 p.m., right.
Alright, I got it.
I'll be getting off now.
By the way,
we won't need
this phone call any longer, right?
Since we're about to meet.
The time and distance
between us will be closed.
Here's greetings from me,
1 hour earlier.
I got it.
Someone call an ambulance! Hurry!
Are you okay?
...What just happened?
He pushed you away and in your place...
Shinya-san?
Shinya-san!
There's still time.
If I call him now,
there's still time!
Please, pick up!
Please pick up the phone, Shinya-san!
Hello?
Shinya-san?
What's up?
Don't tell me
you're calling because you're troubled?
I'm not an imaginary person you know.
That's it.
I don't want to meet you.
Not someone like you.
You should go back now.
Please.
Why?
As expected, am I...?
Sorry. Please go back.
I don't want to meet you!
Someone like you... I hate you!
I hate your face,
your hair,
your fingers,
and your voice!
Voice?
You're lying.
You can't possibly hear my voice.
I'm not lying!
You're the worst.
I was disillusioned.
You weren't what I expected.
You're lying!
Because...
I can't speak.
I lost my hearing and speech
when I was 5.
That's why,
you couldn't
possibly have heard my voice.
That can't be...
Why did you lie?
Because...
Ryou?
What happened?
Why do you want me to go back?
Please!
I don't know
what happened after I met you.
But I will definitely meet you.
Why don't you understand?
If you come...
You'll die!
Die?
What do you mean?
You'll die after you meet me.
You'll die saving me.
Please go back!
I can't.
If what you're saying is true,
I have to go!
I'll definitely be saved... so...
I'll go!
Don't...
Don't come!
Don't cry, Ryou.
I'll be fine.
I won't die.
Do you rememer the time
you went to Kamakura?
You were humming a song for me.
It's been 15 years
since I last heard music.
You reminded me what it was like
to be able to hear music.
I was surprised
the first time you called me,
that someone wanted to talk to me.
When I heard your voice,
I was really excited
to be able
to finally tell someone my feelings.
And that someone was willing to listen.
It was such a wonderful thing.
That's why,
you should never
say something like that again!
That it would be fine
even if you disappeared.
I understand.
I won't say that again!
So stop! Please...
That's great...
But I'm still going...
I'll definitely save you.
I'll still make the same choice.
Just like what I did an hour earlier.
Where are you, Ryou?
A blue dress.
I'm wearing a blue dress today.
I got it.
A red and round watch...
I've been using it since I was young.
Shinya-san...
Please!
Please say something!
Ryou...
Shinya-san?
Hello? Hello?
Thank goodness...
Can you still hear me?
Shinya-san!
I can see you standing up.
You look okay, but are you?
Yes, I'm fine.
Thank goodness.
Ryou, so that's what you look like.
You're really cute.
You should have
more confidence in yourself.
Shinya-san?
You're calling my name.
I can hear you.
It's definitely a nice voice.
Shinya-san?
Why did you go to this length
to save me?
What are you talking about?
The one who's being saved,
is me.
Thank you, Ryou.
Shinya-san...
Because I met you...
We no longer...
Harada-san.
After Shinya-san passed away,
I came to Nagano.
I see.
Somehow it feels like,
I can still hear
Shinya-san's kind voice.
I wonder if I can become a strong adult
just like you, Harada-san.
Harada-san,
I wonder if I'll be able to.
Don't say that.
You will become one.
You will.
You'll change.
Hello? Harada-san?
God brought him back to Heaven...
But the order is wrong, isn't it?
He left before me.
It's just
a lot of odds and ends, isn't it?
But,
all of them can be used.
Is this all of it?
Yes.
To others it may just be rubbish,
but to him, it was different.
No matter what it was,
he would breathe life into it.
It was definitely magic.
Magic?
A magical spell that can fix anything.
It's magic, isn't it?
That's why when he was here,
somehow I always felt better.
But Ryou-san,
You may have some magic of your own.
Huh?
He listened to this tape countless times.
But...
Shinya-san couldn't hear, could he?
He couldn't hear, but
he kept on listening to it.
Actually
"Could you listen to this tape for me?"
he was asking me really earnestly.
"What did she say?
What's her voice like? Please tell me!"
Then, you heard the tape too...?
Yes.
I said it was a really cute voice.
He seemed really happy.
Especially
the last part.
The last part?
She says she wants to meet you.
"I want to meet you"
Again and again...
Such a happy smile of his...
it was really long
since I last saw it,
since he lost his parents
and his brother in an accident.
It must have been due to your magic.
Even though
it must have been tough on him,
he would sign like this.
What does that mean?
Please tell me.
You
aren't alone.
You... aren't... alone.
Shinya-san!
Can you hear
my voice?
Shinya-san!
It's going to be autumn soon!
I'll definitely live on strongly!
Because...
I'm no longer...
alone.
Can you hear me?
You're the only one
who can hear this voice.
Even now I can still hear
this voice.
I continue calling,
so it'll get through,
your name over and over again.
I'm calling you,
Calling your name.
Only you can hear this voice.
Every time
I call your name, it's as if
you were right by my side.
And my chest becomes warm.
I'm calling you,
Calling your name.
At that time,
If this voice hadn't reached you
I'd have given up,
without knowing
thinking about someone
would be something
I'd treasure so much.
I'm calling you,
Caling your name.
A heart can really be
touched,
"my beloved" and "pain"
are a little similar,
You gave me your voice and tears,
you told me about everyone.
You're the only one
who can hear this voice.
If it reaches someone, please look,
so it may join us,
I'll try and call out with you.
I'm still calling out even now.
I'm still continuing to call for you.
Your voice is being sent to someone,
Someone is replying to your voice,
Someone is remembering you.
Someone is remembering you,
replying to your voice.
subtitled by?
makotoyui@gmail.com [18th December 2007]
I'm Calling You
(Only you can hear me)
Thank you for watching (and reading)