"Peaceful and prosperous country"
"Return to us our country"
Protect His Majesty!
Yes!
Tonight our brothers of the
Red Flower Society will take our revenge.
Let's go!
Yes!
Chan Ka Lok?
You dare to kill the emperor?
You belong to the Han race.
Yet you have become a Manchu emperor.
I want to kill you
on behalf of Han people.
Your Majesty, take care!
Why can't I ever have a sound sleep?
I should be punished!
Send for Governor Oryeetor.
Did you come to buy a sword?
No!
What do you want?
My master is suffering...
from serious insomnia.
He should see a doctor.
I am only a blacksmith.
It's useless to see a doctor.
My master said,
only when the demon
of his dream is killed.
Then he can have sound sleep.
What's the name of your master?
Emperor Chien Lung.
5 days ago,
I killed a member of
the Red Flower Society.
What? You killed our Fourth Brother?
I found a letter from his pocket,
Saying there is a name list...
kept by a blacksmith.
Right, but I sent it away.
You will never get it.
Really?
I want to avenge Fourth Brother's death!
- Search!
- Yes!
Tiger Lui is so rich.
What business was he doing in Shantung?
He used to be a bandit.
This sports competition
is sponsored by him.
So what?
Cocky bastard!
Buying so much land that,
within these three months,
he has bought half the town.
He is in league...
with the governor.
That's why he is so cocky.
What can we poor people do?
Miss, you'd better go home now.
So dad is a bastard
in the eyes of these people.
Miss, you know it only now?
Will we be recognized?
No, no one knows us, we'd better leave.
This girl is pretty.
Let me see...
- Let's go...
- Come on!
Shall we stay and have a look?
No, or master will scold us.
Miss, are you alone?
What do you want?
Are you a stranger here?
So pretty!
Don't bully us, we know Cantonese.
That's fine! So we can communicate!
Don't touch my sister!
Your sister?
I know him, he is bull shitting.
He has no sister.
I know you too.
You are a pimp.
How dare you insult my boss?
Beat him!
Come on!
You dare fight with our boss?
Beat him!
Do you want to be put behind bars?
None of his business.
This is the first day I reported duty,
give me face.
Let's see if he gives face or not.
Damn it, how dare you fight here?
Do you want to go to jail?
I am sorry...
No fighting!
Yes...
We are not allowed to fight here,
let's compete in the playground,
if you have guts.
Let's go!
He was a sports champion
from St. Joseph College in Shanghai.
Sai Yuk, you are not used to
these foreign games.
Damn it,
but he is good at kung-fu.
Look, your "brother"
is beating a retreat.
Bullshit, he isn't.
Let's compete.
18 feet.
Next!
He achieved good record, the next one.
He's been the sports champions
of St. Joseph College for 3 years.
22 feet!
Break record! How wonderful!
Let's see the next one.
I don't have any record
or information about him.
Let's see.
Scared?
Jump!
You're so slow.
Let me give you a hand.
Why don't you jump?
He is jumping.
Wonderful!
He has broken a new record!
Bravo!
So smart!
Although you are a little ant.
I won't bully you.
Bastard, the next race
is 400 meters relay.
I won't lose this one.
There should be 4 people in a relay.
We have three only.
Miss, we need 4 people,
we're only three.
Are you willing to help?
- Can I?
- Yes!
But I run slowly!
Are you slower than an ant?
More or less the same.
That's good enough!
You run first!
How about me?
Bo, you run first!
Ready...
Go!
Hurry up!
"Young at heart, boundless world"
"Can climb every mountain"
"There seems many obstacles"
"Take the challenge,
reach the boundless world"
- I can't anymore.
- No problem!
"Practise kung-fu and show your talent"
"Take the challenge..."
Are you alright?
"Be happy, create a happy life"
Hurry up...
You'll lose!
"Young at heart, the world is yours"
"In this unlimited place"
It's my turn!
Hurry...
How amazing is the pig tail!
Yes! Straightened pig tail!
"Be happy, create a happy life"
"Proud of yourself and love yourself"
"Young at heart, the world is yours"
"In this unlimited place"
"let your dreams fly"
Oh! Flying stance.
Hey, young man,
you've gained 2 championships,
join us next year.
You, St. Joseph's student,
go back and eat shit!
Thank you, Miss!
You have a share of this medal.
For you!
How about you?
This is a present from Tiger Lui,
I don't want it.
May I know your name?
Chan!
Damn it!
What are you doing?
You make me lose face.
Beat him!
Yes!
I love fighting. Come on!
Come on!
You want some more?
No...
Thank you...
Thank you for sparing time
to fight with me.
What are you fighting for?
Who joined the fight?
They did, I arrested them for you.
You are most enthusiastic.
- Thank you.
- Take them away.
What?
You too!
Yes, go now!
Are you kidding?
Wait...
Go!
Don't push me!
Damn you! You son of a bitch!
Damn you! Why didn't he see me
the Central Primary School?
How dare he offend me?
Go tell the Governor.
Say he's been robbing.
And cut his head off.
Yes, Master!
Master,
I've heard many gossip about us.
So what?
Should I be scared?
Of course not, master.
But, there is an old Chinese saying that,
you should follow the rules
of the village which you have entered.
If we want to establish
our power in Canton.
We should mix with the people.
How?
I have an idea.
If we want to make a name,
and establish power here,
let's arrange for a kung-fu competition
to select a son-in-law for you.
It's not fair to Ting Ting.
Master, you should be decisive.
The daughter would marry anyway.
She will leave your family
and change her surname.
She won't remember her parents.
Please consider.
Did your father and mother-in-law...
gain any benefits from you?
Damn it, what you said
is just what I have in mind.
I was about to propose it.
It's very wise of you, master.
It's a deal!
Get Ting a husband
with a Kung-fu competition.
Sai Yuk,
we should never tell others that,
we've been caught.
Right, if you dad knows that,
that'd be troublesome!
Don't worry, I wrote us false names.
You are called Yuen Kwei.
You are called Lau Chun Wai.
How about you?
I am Wong...
Jing!
Well, I have to go home now.
Or my mom would teach me a lesson.
Come around if you have time. Bye-bye!
Yuk!
Her curly hair is cute!
His dark glasses are funny too!
Isn't it black now?
Shit!
Nothing can be seen, but it's smart!
She is blind!
Miss!
You scared me!
You look good!
Your voice is sexy!
Are you selling cloth?
Bull shit!
What kind of cloth...
would you like?
The one outside!
That one?
I won't give it a damn.
Right, this one.
This one?
Yes!
How many yards do you want?
I want...
That much!
No, less...
- So much?
- No, here...
- Here?
- No, just that much,
- Yes.
That little! For wrapping a dumpling?
How dare you steal?
You bastard...
Shut up!
No! Mom, that...
Be polite!
It hurts!
Mom, you are pretty.
Shut up, give me the weight-measure,
Yes, mom.
What for!
Our cloth is not measured by yards.
It's measured by weight.
Otherwise you won't take so much!
Aren't you blind?
You are blind.
You thought I hit you by chance?
That shows I'm not in your good grace.
I am leaving.
You wanna escape?
This is for you.
Mom, we're in trouble!
Don't worry, 2 cm to the mark.
Really?
No blood,
no blood please!
Mom, you're wrong!
It's 6 mm to the mark, look!
They have deep throat!
He deserves it!
I'm in a good mood,
let's take the afternoon off.
You took a day off yesterday
because you were in a bad mood.
You want to rest today
because of good mood?
Sure, your dad is coming back today.
I can't concentrate.
Make it a day-off.
Mom!
Mom, I met a very pretty girl today.
She has character.
Then, let's take an extra holiday
the day after tomorrow.
Another day off?
Young master.
Young master, bad news!
What's the matter?
The Governor has come.
He is talking with Master.
What is it?
If fought with someone today.
Don't panic, there's always your mom.
Your Excellency, death friends,
You can be sure
I will do the right thing.
Yes, Master Fong is such a righteous man.
I feel shame!
I assure you I will punish...
So many friends!
Hello everybody.
No matter what had happened,
I, Miu Tsui Fa will be responsible.
Of course you should be responsible.
You, you beat that foreigner up.
And the cloth you sold me...
last time was stinky.
She insulted my wife,
saying that she was fat.
And refused to sell her cloth.
She teased me!
Saying that I'm as stupid as a pig.
She is too much!
What's your explanation?
I would not have come back
if I knew I had to face this.
Macu, get the cane.
What? Not again!
Master, for my sake...
For you sake?
Never mind.
Dad, please forgive mom!
Please hit me instead.
Look at our son! He is nice.
Is it the Fong family?
Oh, you are Fong Sai Yuk,
not Wong Jing!
Why do you call yourself Wong Jing?
He was caught fighting this morning and,
in the police station
he claimed to be Wong Jing.
You little scoundrel!
Are you hurt?
Yes!
I shielded you from most of your blows,
so don't cry for pain.
Mom, since you are so good at Kung-fu!
But you just let dad beat you up.
I should give him some face
in front of other people.
The status of a man in a family
is very precious and important.
Yes, it's precious and important indeed.
Get some sleep now!
Yes, dad.
I don't know how you teach your son!
He's a grown-up,
but just loiters around
involving in fights.
Kids should be independent.
All you care about is your business.
If our son don't keep me company,
who would?
You listen to these gossiping fools.
And best me up in front of everybody.
You don't treat me as your wife at all.
Listen to me.
I won't.
No, I won't...
"The beauty put up the curtain."
Oh God! He is reciting poetry again.
"And sits moody with furrowed brows."
"We only see stains of her tears."
"No one knows who she is hating."
I can't stand it!
He is too smart! Too Romantic!
So great!
Every time he recites poetry
I'm so excited.
I feel dizzy!
Am I wrong to scold you like this?
No!
Now why don't you come to bed?
Yes!
"Our Fist conquers the whole of Canton."
"Our Kick subdues Soochow and Hangchau."
What kind of bluffing is it?
Master, how is my writing?
Once it is hung out,
See, so many people
are gathered around it.
Ting Ting...
I don't want to select my husband
through the kung-fu competition.
Stop bothering me.
If you force me,
I will run away.
Shut up, or I will beat you to death.
- Damn it!
- Maybe you should...
...deal with Ting Ting in gentler way.
When I am talking, you shut up.
I do this to impress the local people.
If I don't get better status here.
Do you understand?
Why are you laughing?
I am not play acting! Damn it!
Can you stand it?
Sure! I can still stand it.
Really?
- Alright. I'll try again.
- Sure.
Son, does it work?
What's wrong?
Isn't it alright?
It's like barbecue!
Sure, I saw foreigners do this.
Do this to my eyebrow later, alright?
Sure, anywhere can do.
It's awful!
Would your dad like
and recite poem to me?
He will love it!
May be he will recite an English poem.
English poem?
May be, I would be more excited.
How is English poem?
I know, say, "Wonderful..."
How do you know it?
I am taught by Josephine Siao.
Sai Yuk...
Hurry up, your dad is back.
Quick!
Shit! My hubby!
What are you doing?
Honey, don't come in.
I want to show you something nice.
Mom, sit down, don't move.
Sai Yuk!
Wait, don't come in.
I'll be pretty soon.
Shit...
What is it?
It's on fire. On fire!
What happened?
None of my business.
I'm going to study.
I am going to town,
what do you want to buy?
It's such a nice hairstyle! Damn it!
Friends, countrymen!
I, Tiger Lui is a new comer to this town.
I want to stay peacefully
and happily with all of you.
So, I arrange this competition
to recruit a son-in-law.
Who gets the ribbon, who is the winner.
About the regulations,
once you step on the floor, you lose.
If anybody can defeat my wife,
Lee Siu Wan,
he can marry my daughter, Lui Ting Ting.
If anyone is killed or hurt by my wife,
the Lu family won't be responsible.
Now, my wife, Lee Siu Wan...
She is pretty.
If she marries me,
I shall spend all my nights
not sleeping...
You think you are capable?
I can ask for your help!
Okay, it's a deal. Let's go.
Let's go.
They are real friends.
Bo, tell Fong Sai Yuk
to go for the competition.
Okay...
Sorry, excuse me, please give way...
Where is Sai Yuk?
He is studying inside.
I am going to the mill.
Come home soon.
"After the storm,
numberless blossoms... fall..."
One, two. So much!
Who is it?
Sai Yuk, come out...
Sai Yuk!
"The birds cried...
After the storm.
Numberless blossoms...". Dad!
Sai Yuk, sit down.
I have to leave for town today.
Dad, how long will you stay in the town?
I will miss you.
Work hard.
Yes!
Today is not suitable for studying.
What's up?
Tiger Lui arranged a competition
to recruit a son-in-law.
His daughter is very pretty.
- Really?
- He said he is the best kung-fu fighter...
in Canton and Soo Hang.
Damn, what a big mouth!
Sai Yuk, what should we do?
Well?
Keep on studying.
Are you kidding?
My dad is in. If he knows that,
He'll kill me.
Young Master, what are you doing?
Sai Yuk, should we just
let those bastards kick us around?
You'll defeat them easily.
Come down quick, master is coming.
Macu!
Take my place.
No way!
I'll be back soon.
Young Master... I can't,
I have to go to town with master.
Master, bad news!
- What?
- Ting Ting disappeared.
Gone!
Damn!
Come on.
Master,
it's not right...
Don't stare!
It's alright this way?
Sure!
You want to get a wife?
My heart longs for a pretty woman!
Well, what about your vacation?
Dear friends,
it seems it's difficult...
to find a true hero in Canton.
Rubbish!
Bravo...
The new comer's name?
I am well known,
One of the ten most-outstanding
youngsters of Canton.
The "Invincible Magic Fist" Fong Sai Yuk.
No bad-looking boy,
But first my wife must
put you to the test.
You're the trophy?
Not me! My daughter!
Just a peek!
Watch it, young man!
Lend me your head.
How dare you trick me?
My feet not yet on the ground.
Don't worry,
We'll play till one of us loses.
Now try our Cantonese
tournament on heads.
Oh, my head.
It's hurt! Oh my neck!
What a bad luck to be stepped by a woman.
Great! Beat her!
Sai Yuk, beat her.
Can you make it?
Sure, we can.
I can't!
Get her down!
Hey, steady!
Oh, my neck!
I feel dizzy!
Honey, be careful!
Yes! I'll be careful!
Lend me your pig-tail.
My hair!
Hands off!
Beat her.
Knock her down...
Special request by the audience.
Catch my wife.
They're coming to help!
- How is it?
- Don't panic, the more the merrier.
Be careful. I can stand no more.
I'll destroy your footholds.
Bo, come and help.
We support you.
You Cantonese are not united at all.
Are you okay?
Sure! I am alright.
Do you want to support yourself
with these 2 poles?
You don't have six poles to support you,
can you hold it?
Fight!
If you can win her,
you'll be my son-in-law.
Beat her!
Your men are getting tired.
Let's fight.
How dare you pull my hair!
I'll attack you eyes in return.
Watch my kick.
Go to hell.
Watch mine!
My eye is hurt.
- Are you alright?
- I am fine...
Come on!
Beat them.
I'll bite you to death.
Hold it!
Bo is beaten.
I'll help!
Grab your poles.
I can stand no more.
Young Master, don't disappoint us.
I have never disappointed you.
My head fist.
Help me get up.
Madam!
Don't fall down!
I am lucky to get hold of it.
Come, kick me.
I lost! I surrender!
Sai Yuk, how can you let us down?
But if I didn't do so,
I would have let myself down.
How come you lost?
I am sorry, I lost!
Miss, I am sorry, I lost.
Kid, we may talk...
Damn it!
The Outstanding Youth lost.
Anybody wants it?
Lost again!
Is there an Outstanding Youth in Canton?
I wonder!
You're exaggerating!
That's why I have some extra customers.
I want to make another bet.
Let's see who will be the final winner.
If you want to win,
get my son to fight.
It's useless, Fong Sai Yuk just lost.
How dare he claim himself
the Outstanding Youth in Canton.
I think you are
no longer number one here.
Really, that son of mine
should do better.
Heroes, gentlemen,
Any one else for a fight?
If not,
we'll continuous tomorrow morning.
Wait!
There is money on the ground!
Go and pick up the money!
Lend me your back!
I'm coming too.
Great!
May I know the name of this hero?
May I know the name of this beauty?
Don't feel shy.
I am Mrs. Lui,
the mother of Lui Ting Ting.
If you can defeat me,
I'll be your mother-in-law.
Why not marry the mother-in-law too?
What a big mouth!
Well? What do you think?
Stop, or you will fall down.
Who are you? How dare you?
Damn it!
Read my lips, it should be...
D-A-M-N l-T!
I am the invincible kung-fu Master,
The brother of Fong Sai Yuk.
My name is Fong Tai Yuk.
Both brothers are braggarts.
Is your Kung-fu powerful...
Leave the question to Madam,
she will answer you later.
Why such a big fuss
just to get hold of this?
I want it!
Good foot-work!
So is yours.
Madam, why did you hold my leg?
You have smooth face.
Madam, you needn't be so nervous!
Thank you!
Madam, you are heavy.
Don't panic, I am here.
Why don't you come up? I'm helping you.
Come up!
The ribbon!
Be careful!
A secret attack?
A heavy attack.
Madam!
We are on the ground now.
Are you alright?
I am fine!
But I am not!
She is my wife, do you know that?
Dear fellows,
Fong's family is the
No. 1 Kung-fu family in Canton.
And our Lui family.
Stop touching me.
We are relatives now.
Who is your relative?
I come only to fight,
but not for your daughter!
How about my daughter?
I don't want her.
Kid, repeat that if you dare!
Read my lips.
I DON'T WANT HER!
You joined the competition,
you must marry my daughter.
Or I will ask the governor to arrest you!
Damn!
Damn what?
Don't touch my face!
If you ruin my face...
I want you finger print.
So you won't deny the deal.
Press on it.
Who catches my staff?
Your mom, me...
Mom, you look handsome.
I just did this for you,
to gain face for you.
Get me a bag.
What for?
I won in the Kung-fu Competition.
Lui forced me to marry his daughter.
So we should leave at once.
Mom, you are great!
Lesbian?
What?
Shit, they are coming.
What now?
Let's fight them.
Yes!
Watch mine.
Fong Tai Yuk, I am coming...
Fong Tai Yuk...
Search!
Yes!
They are inside, search!
I told you to search,
what are you looking for?
Go search!
Yes!
Damn it!
Fong Tai Yuk.
Why are you crying?
Where is Fong Tai Yuk?
He is dead!
Dead? How come?
He died on the street!
What? At least there is corpse.
It's burnt.
I can recognise him, even in ashes.
Let me see.
Really? Are you still
interested in the ashes?
Mom...
Look. The ashes.
Mom, run.
Don't go!
You are a man.
Bullshit!
Aren't you a man?
Don't move.
Or I'll kill him.
Son, why are you holding a banana?
Banana?
Isn't it a knife?
Catch him...
Freeze! Don't go!
Come down, do you hear?
Mom!
Forget about me, run for your life.
No, I will be punished by God
if I leave like this.
I am coming.
So great!
I tell you, we can't get your elder son.
We will take your younger son
as substitute.
Master, we've found Miss Ting.
Thank God.
Hey,
wait for my husband
to celebrate the wedding.
Okay, the wedding ceremony later,
but the Bridal Chamber first.
Go!
Disperse...
Go home...
Hand the man out.
Listen, leave here at once.
If you stay, you'll be arrested.
Let him go!
Your Honour!
Brother Lui.
What's up?
The people outside are all furious.
I heard...
that the Governor of Kau Mun
will come soon.
Your Honour, you should help me.
Get your son-in-law...
to get married in front of the people,
saying that he is willing to do so.
Then, we won't have any problem
if the Governor comes.
Okay, I'll force him to say he's willing.
Impossible! We should not use force
but virtuous persuasion.
Then we won't get into trouble.
Right, virtuous persuasion.
I won't lose my virginity to you.
If he dares touch me, I will kill him.
She pretends to be lady!
Makes me puke!
I want to scare the hag.
He's coming.
I want to scare you to death.
What do you want?
Are you kidding? Do you want to kill me?
That's too much!
What do you want?
I tell you, you can have my body,
but not my heart.
I love someone else.
Me too. I won't marry you.
I won't marry you too.
Okay, swear! What if you marry me?
My family will all die.
- What is this?
- Give it back to me.
Why do you keep such rubbish with you?
Idiot!
Sleep by yourself.