Yourtrain...
Not my train anymore...
I'm planning to stop traveling by train...
Buy myself a new car...
A nice new blue car...
You like blue? I like blue...
Your life is empty...
I can see it in your eyes...
Do you remember when we
touched each other?
Held hands? Anything? Do you remember?
I leave you at the station everyday
but yourthoughts never leave me...
To embrace each other's happiness and
pain, one has to embrace each other...
And you have neverfelt that way about me...
Since both of us are married...
...what are we doing at the station
in the middle of the night?
You have to tell me today, Maya...
tell me the truth... Why did you marry me?
Sometimes friendship takes the place of love...
...and then there's no place left for love...
The truth is, that you never married me,
Maya... You compromised...
Listen to the answer, Maya...
I love you Maya...
And you love me too...
And what if I find my soul mate
after marriage?
Dev...
I like blue...
Do you know when we reached here...?
I am yours and you, mine...
I'm wonderstruck at this moment...
When moonlight has emerged in
the middle of the day...
It seems awake yet it's dreaming...
My lovelorn heart...
Do you know when we reached here...?
I am yours and you, mine...
Intoxicated souls... Musky bodies...
There's a pureness in the air...
In this moment that we are in...
there's so much colour...
Spilling out of our eyes...
The blue sky showers on us...
Soft, silky rays of light...
Do you know when we reached here...?
I am yours and you, mine...
I'm wonderstruck at this moment...
When moonlight has emerged in
the middle of the day...
I was blissfully ignorant...
Of this love that flows forth unbridled...
True is this feeling... true is this love...
All else is just an illusion...
My heart slowly hums the
melodious notes of love...
Do you know when we reached here...?
I am yours and you, mine...
I'm wonderstruck at this moment...
When moonlight has emerged
in the middle of the day...
It seems awake yet it's dreaming...
My lovelorn heart...
We were crazy... We were strange...
We were different...
Very different... Incomplete on our
own but so complete together...
We were not walking on the ground...
There, we had slipped long ago...
We were flying in the sky...
Talking to the clouds...
We didn't have a care in the world...
We had made our own world...
Our world... Maya and Dev's world...
The world of our dreams...
But then dreams always leave
when you wake up to reality...
come on, drink your milk fast...
I don't want to drink it... - Drink it!
Here... - It's ok...
It's ok, Dev... Thank you...
I don't know what to do, Sam...
I was going to ask you for
advice and I come to know...
...that it's the same situation
in your house too... God!
Every house seems to have the same story...
Will you stop this TV soap commentary?
Sam... be serious for once...
What's the point of being serious... Look...
Your son is mule headed...
He is not going to do anything...
Maya isn't at fault so she
isn't going to do anything...
So what do we do, Kamlu?
I know... You do have a point...
Whatever needs to be done has to
be done by Rhea and Rishi...
But they are both being so stubborn...
Who will convince them?
What if they convince each other?
And why will they do that?
They hardly know each other...
Precisely... two strangers...
same situation...
Then, friendship and problem solved...
remember?
But how will they meet each other?
Dad... What are we doing here?
I haven't bought you a present in a long time...
So I thought I'd do that today...
Dude, it's a toy store...
- Yeah... So?
It's for kids...
But to me you will always be a kid...
Mom... Should I take this for Arjun?
Yes... take it... It's very nice... It's fantastic...
You have very good taste...
It's a fabulous dog... take it...
Dad... What did you have for breakfast?
I don't know...
I don't remember her name...
Ok... I'll take this...
God! What an awful red dog... Just leave it...
Kamaljit... What a surprise!
Oh Samarjit... So nice to see you here...
Of all the places in New York
we had to meet here...
coincidence... coincidence...
Just a coincidence...
How are you?
By the way what are you doing here?
We had come here to buy a
soft toy for my grandson...
...which he can cuddle upto in the night...
Even I was looking for something like that...
And I saw you...
Neither am I soft nor am I a toy...
So please stay away...
Much as I am enjoying this conversation...
can we please move on?
Of course... of course... of course...
There are so many beautiful
things here... red... blue... green...
come on darling... help me get this one...
Don't you think that was weird behavior?
You think he was hitting on my mother-in-law?
Oh no... you don't need to worry about that...
...he pretty much hits on anything that moves...
Ok I'm getting late... I have to go...
Where are you heading?
- Work... 55th and 5th...
Oh great... I'll walk you... - Sure... - Alright...
Sam... I think it worked...
So... what did you say your name was?
Charlotte... - charlotte... You are gorgeous!
Why are people so happy in New York?
Because they are not married... That's why...
Right... They are single...
No tension in life... No problem...
No stress...
They go home... shower... freshen themselves...
Watch TV... then they go out and get lucky...
We... we go home and get unlucky...
True... We go home to a sourface...
That likes nothing... That likes no one...
Not even us... I mean look at us...
You are super sexy... I'm a super stud...
But have they ever complimented us?
- Never!
All the time whine... whine... whine...
Blah... blah... blah... blah...
On and on and on...
- And on and on and on...
My God, how they trouble us...
How they sadden us...
Mock us... - Hurt us...
Why did we marry?
I know... Our brains were not working...
You know what? We should be single...
Yeah... Single...
Singles rock!
Single's the way to be... - I wanna be single...
I wanna be single too!
Single... - Single...
And you know what? - What?
We... - Yes?
...are lying... - What?
I really love her...
I really love him, too!
I love you, Maya...
You have called me five times since morning...
What's the problem?
The problem is that my work is that kind...
I never have the time to express my feelings...
And I keep expressing my feelings all the time...
So what's stopping you today?
Nothing's stopping you either...
Do you like diamonds, Maya?
Diamonds?
Large, beautiful... expensive diamonds...
Yeah of course...
Good... tell your husband to buy them foryou...
Dev...
I have bought you flowers...
call Dev... call him now...
Ok... I'll call him if you speak to Maya...
Why should I speak any longer?
I'm meeting you in five minutes...
Then speak to me forfour and a half minutes...
Voicemail!
Maya... I'm sulking and you aren't
even trying to make up...
come on... Show me you care...
...say or do something which
shows that you are mine...
Only mine... Maya... Miss you!
Hey, Dev... Look we have to talk...
It's gone too far...
I don't want to fight anymore...
If you want the same then show me a sign...
Just a sign... come on let's make this work...
I love you...
See you later...
Bye...
Dev... You? Here?
Ljust got out of the station...
And these flowers?
Foryou...
That's sweet!
I'll see you later at home...
Yeah... Bye...
Flowers have their own language...
...they say so much silently... Right?
I asked for just one sign...
And got so many...
Missed you... - Yeah!
Where's Arjun?
Oh... he must have gone to
his violin class... Right?
He's quit the violin...
Quit violin? Why?
He thinks his violin is the
reason for ourfights...
What an idiot I have given birth to?
Sorry, Papa...
Shut up! There's no reason to say sorry...
There's no reason to quit violin...
...and there is absolutely
no reason to play football...
And that is the coach's order... Ok? Say ok...
Ok...
No more football...
Anyone can play the football...
Even I can... really...
But only cool dudes play the violin...
Right? And you are the coolest... ok?
You can play violin as much
as you want from today...
Play it day and night... Wheneveryou want...
I won't say anything... You know why?
Why?
I'll show you... because now I have this...
Go on play the violin... I don't hear nothing...
Papa... can I hug you?
What?
Can I hug you?
No... because I'm going to hug you...
And I have another idea...
We will make an eleven memberteam...
You play the violin in the forward position...
Violin doesn't have a forward...
What nonsense...
And our band will be called Manchester
United Philharmonic... Ok?
Rishi... all this... - May I?
I cleaned the entire house...
It took three hours... the food's ready...
really...
With these very hands I phoned
and called forfood...
But it's the thought that counts, right? - Right...
And that's not all... This whole weekend...
You and me... All day and all night... for hours...
we will... with each other...
Discuss things...
Whateveryou want we shall discuss...
I'm sorry, Maya...
Forthat night...
Sometimes you make mistakes in love...
Yeah...
Dev... Who are you talking to? Come in...
Ok come on... one more...
Sorry... I couldn't take your calls...
Rishi was with me the whole weekend...
Don't worry... It's alright... I tried just once...
But I got 15 missed calls...
The numbers get dialed accidentally...
How was the weekend?
Very good...
I spent a lot of time with Rhea and Arjun...
It was fun... After all family is family...
We even went shopping...
Rhea bought a lovely dress...
Quite sexy... Rhea looked very good in it...
Of course... Rhea is a beautiful woman...
She looks good in anything she wears...
So what did you do today?
Same as everyday...
I had lunch with George Bush and
now I'm off for coffee with Madonna...
Stupid bloody questions...
Look, I don't know what your problem is
but I don't want to fight with you...
Anyway, I'm going out with Rishi...
There seems to be a sudden
bout of love for Rishi...?
Yeah... After all family is family... Right?
So, Rishi is taking you to meet
the rest of his family at the zoo?
Rishi is taking me to the ballet...
Ballet? Where men dance without underwear?
Rishi likes all that stuff?
Not Rishi... I like ballet...
Ballet is music, dance, poetry... I love the ballet...
You like strange things...
Yeah... Nothing can be more strange than you...
Enjoy your ballet... ballet!
Dev... I hope you are well... - I am... Why?
First the flowers... Now the ballet...
You all right?
I'm alright, thank you...
Maybe you are falling in love...
with me all over again...
Will you excuse me for a moment...
I will join you...
Hey... isn't that... Dev? And... Rhea... yeah...
Hey, Rhea... Are you following me?
I don't know about you guys...
...but I'm following your wife for sure...
Hey... Hey...
Hi Rhea... - Hi...
So how are you guys?
Oh we are good... we are good...
So even you have come here
to appease your wife?
Ballet can be so boring...
Boring? Ballet is not boring...
Ballet is music, dance, poetry...
I love the ballet... Maya...
Do you love the ballet?
Yeah... Lovely dress, Rhea...
Thank you... It's Dev's choice...
You've got very good taste...
Thank you... You look beautiful too...
But a little less than Rhea...
Just the way you look a little
less handsome than Rishi...
Oh yes...
Wow Maya! A compliment afteryears!
Not bad... not bad...
Same here... Dev, you need to be
taken to the doctortomorrow for sure...
come on lets go...
I don't want to miss the ballet...
I wanna pee... Excuse me... Excuse me...
I love the ballet... come on move...
I'm sorry...
Ok... Told you he was on drugs...
What were we doing?
What were we doing last night?
We were playing with theirfeelings...
Forthe first time I felt hatred for myself...
How could I do this to Rishi?
Feeling bad for him?
You must have felt guilty last night too...
So what did you do to get rid of your guilt?
What did you do?
Did you allow him to touch you?
Where did he touch you? Here? Here? Here?
Did he touch you here?
Stop it, Dev... Just stop it...
You think I don't feel bad?
That my love spends nights with
someone else? But I bear it...
I can't bear it... I can't bear it...
You will have to...
because our relationship is a dream...
...that shatters every time we reach home...
And that's the truth...
I can't accept this truth... I can't bear it...
I can't bear it... I can't bearto see you with him...
You are mine... Just mine...
Then how come he has a greater right...
Your heart is mine but you have his name...
I can't bear it... You are mine...
Dev, what are you doing?
Buddy... On the eve of your wedding...
...ljust want to say that marriage is beautiful...
It gives you that special someone
who you trust more than yourself...
Trust me, dude... being married is the
world's greatest feeling...
To Diva... Finally the NO.1 magazine...
Ok girls, from now on we have a new policy...
No more late nights...
no more ignoring your husbands...
Trust me... what's most important is this...
Rishi... I don't know who's following whom here...
Oh who cares? I'm celebrating...
So am I...
But only you and me know the
real reason why we are celebrating...
So? Singles still rock?
Naaaaa...
Dance all night... Wanna dance all night?
Do you feel alright? Wanna dance all night...
Beautiful moments...
Pretty as peach...
Weaving these dreamy days...
And dreamy nights...
Melody of the heart echoes...
The breezy song of the soul...
And all the loved ones sway to the tune...
So let's dance all night...
Where's the party tonight?
Weaving these dreamy days...
And dreamy nights...
Where's the party tonight?
Dance all night... Wanna dance all night?
Do you feel alright? Wanna dance all night...
The one I dreamt of...
The one who drove me crazy...
Today he is mine...
Like the flowerthat I yearned for...
Like the fragrance that I craved for...
He has blossomed in my arms...
The path is filled with fragrance of love...
Intoxicated are all eyes around...
Dreams weave a web around all of us...
So let's dance all night...
Where's the party tonight?
Weaving these dreamy days...
And dreamy nights...
Where's the party tonight?
Dance all night...
Dance... Dance all night
My story goes like this...
The one who I yearn for...
Has fallen for me...
The queen of my heart...
Has my story on her lips...
Happy ending is in sight...
I have got a sign...
Life dances in mirth...
So let's dance all night...
Where's the party tonight?
Weaving these dreamy days...
And dreamy nights...
Where's the party tonight?
Weaving these dreamy days...
And dreamy nights...
Where's the party tonight?
Dad... Who's house is this?
You know Kamaljit...
It's her birthday today...
So I thought I'd invite herfor dinner...
If you are with me she will
take me more seriously...
Kamaljit?
Kamaljit... That... Dev... Dev...
Dev's mother...
Rhea... Who is it?
Many happy returns of the day...
Thank you, Sam...
Happy birthday, aunty...
- Thank you... What a surprise!
I'm full of surprises...
So how old is chandigarh?
Beauty has no age, Sam...
Really? Anyway let's get to the point... Kamal...
I'd like to throw a party foryou tonight...
No... I don't trust your parties...
...the next thing I know there'll be nude girls...
So you can join them too...
Just kidding... Just kidding...
Seriously, it will just be family... Ourfamilies...
No...
come on... Listen... hey, Rhea... come on...
Dad!
Our wedding pictures...
God, we were so drunk...
You know what I am saying to Dev here?
Now that the vows are made,
I'll kill you if you don't stick to them...
This one's my favourite...
When Arjun was born...
I have never seen Dev so happy...
Rhea... I'm leaving... I...
Hey, Dev... Look who's here...
Hi...
Hey...
Ok... All's settled...
Dinner at my place... Sharp 8...
Hi... And yes you are invited too...
But if you are busy we shall understand...
Sam...
Just kidding sweetheart... Bye... see you...
You seem to have settled down here...
Should we?
Bye...
Maya...
can I have Dev back please?
Photo, Maya...
Sorry... - That's ok...
Fill it up... Fill it up...
Dude... ease up on the wine...
Relax... Ladies and gentlemen...
Attention please...
I have an announcement to make...
I'm getting married...
To Kamal...
What?
That's the expression I wanted to see...
Sam... What are you doing?
Just joking...
You know we have to do something
about your son's sense of humour...
Smile my son... Smile...
You won't die if you do... And even
if you die, you will die with a smile...
Sam... it's a five course meal
with a preset menu...
Thank you... Are you on the menu?
No... but my grandmother is...
Well done... At last there's someone
who can shut you up...
Tell me Rishi, was he always like this or
is this change recent?
He behaves like a tiger now but
he was a mouse before my mother...
Rishi... behave...
His mother was a very strict woman...
She used to say, 'you can look...
but don't you dare touch!'
And these days there's no time to look...
Too busy touching...
Very bad...
Oh Mom... I really hope you are not listening...
Your Mom and her rules...
It's not about rules, Mr. Talwar...
It's about limits...
It's very easy to slip in a marriage...
It's difficult to keep control...
I personally feel every relationship
should have its boundaries...
And I believe more the boundaries...
...more the chances of them being crossed...
Well... I don't really agree with you...
Maya you tell me... What do you think?
Maya doesn't need to draw any boundaries...
...because her husband loves hertoo much...
Flattery... Flattery... When a man uses
flattery it only means two things...
Either he is lying or he is hiding something...
Really... These days Dev is flattering me a lot...
You think I need to worry...
Actually you should... Everyone's
been speaking a lot...
About relationships...
But relationships are not about words...
...they are about circumstances...
No one knows why one slips in a relationship...
Why one falls in love outside a relationship...
No one knows... Even I don't know
why it happened with me...
But it did... Rhea, I am in love
with someone else...
I'm sorry, Rhea but that's the truth...
And the woman I fell in love with is right here...
Right here.
It's Maya...
What happened, Mr. Talwar?
No sense of humour? I was just joking...
Dev... That really wasn't funny...
I was going to kill you...
I was going to kill him before you...
You are a bit crazy...
Good joke... Good joke...
What was wrong with you last night?
What were you saying?
You said whateveryou felt like...
Did you think of me even once
while saying all those things?
Now who will answer Rishi's questions?
You... Who else? Just tell him the truth...
I don't care...
Tell him the truth? Then what Dev?
Leave the house?
And come to you? Will you leave Rhea
and your son? Tell me...
No... I don't think so... - I thought so...
Dev, don't touch me... Dev... just leave me.
You were right, Dev...
You never know what you'll get to
see outside this station...
Let's go...
It's all so dirty... Not been cleaned
for so many days...
Will you have coffee? What were you saying?
Coffee? No... This Rishi...
he just keeps anything anywhere...
...he's moved everything around...
Dad, you'll have tea?
Oh... you never have tea... I'm crazy...
What am I saying? Just need to clean all this...
You are late?
Yes... Too late...
Dude...
Any message for Mom?
Rishi... - Maya...
I wanted to apologise, Dad...
But apologies are for mistakes...
What's the punishment for selfishness?
I'm a father...
I can't punish... I can only advise...
Leave Rishi...
You don't love him...
By being with him like this...
...you are keeping him away from his true love...
And yourself too...
These incomplete relationships will
bring happiness to no one...
Dad!
It's not yourfault, Maya...
Love and death... both come uninvited...
No one has any control overthem...
He's going away... He's not going to make it...
I don't want to lose my Dad, Maya...
Thank God I have you...
chandigarh...
We knew this was the end of our journey...
These were the last few
breaths of our love story...
We had to collect these moments...
...and breathe a new life into
our old relationships...
It was time to go home...
We had to tell Rishi and Rhea the truth...
Because happiness can never bloom
in the shadow of lies...
No one knew this betterthan us...
Rhea...
There's another woman in my life...
That's not funny anymore...
I'm not joking...
Forthe last six months...
But it's over now...
Maya...
Why it happened... I don't have any answers...
But I want to give our marriage
another chance...
Do you love her?
How does it matter?
It matters to me...
If I had to do what you did...
would you forgive me?
You wouldn't, Dev...
You would neverforgive me...
You will have to leave this house...
This marriage is over...
Rishi... Listen to me...
Listen to me... Rishi... Rishi...
Did you sleep with him?
You slept with him? Tell me, Maya...
How was it? Was it fun?
Did you have fun? Tell me...
Tell me...
How strange Maya, that you kept
cleaning this house all the time...
...and today you have brought in so much filth...
Don't say that, Rishi...
- Then what should I say?
What should I do?
Celebrate?
Should I celebrate that my wife is
sleeping with another man?
I'm sorry, Rishi... I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
Why did you do this...
Why did you do this to me, Maya?
I loved you so much...
More than my own self...
More than life...
But it wasn't enough foryou, right?
It's not like that, Rishi...
Then how is it, Maya?
Every morning I woke up
to look into your eyes...
To search for my face...
But now I will only see him...
And I will not be able to bearthat...
But that relationship is over, Rishi...
This relationship is over, Maya...
Then I'll leave...?
I won't stop you...
Try not to hate me, Arjun...
Rhea... I want to say something to you...
Dev didn't ask me before stepping
out of this marriage...
Neither did you ask me
before throwing him out...
But my grandson's eyes ask me
whether I'm going to leave him...
I can't do that, Rhea...
So if you have no objections...
I would like to stay with you...
can I?
Hello... hello...
Dev...
Maya...
Yeah... Got dialled by mistake...
Are you ok?
Did you... Tell Rishi... Rishi?
I told Rishi everything...
What did he say?
He was very angry at first...
But with time I know he will forgive me...
He's a good man...
And Rhea?
Even she will forgive me with time...
After all family is family...
Yeah... Family is family...
Yeah Rhea... I'm coming...
Even I am at home... with Rishi...
Be happy...
Goodbye...
All our relationships were
defined by this one word...
Both of us left our homes and
didn't even tell each other about it...
I had never seen the hope of meeting again...
...die such a silent death before...
Your heart knows...
And so does mine...
That our roads are meant to part...
Far apart though we will be...
Please don't go away from my memories...
Never say goodbye...
Hi, Good morning. - Hi Miss.
My name is Maya Tal... My name is Maya.
All the mirth in life has slipped away slowly...
It's the pain that refuses to go away...
Tried to wish it away...
tried to laugh it away...
But the heart fails to find peace...
...fails to find peace...
Are these tears? Or is it cinder?
No... Just fire that flows freely from my eyes...
Never say goodbye...
Seasons come... and seasons go...
But the season of pain is here to stay...
The shade of sorrow is so deep...
That it will take a while to pale...
Who knows what's to happen ahead...
Who knows what's in store for us to bear...
Never say goodbye...
Your heart knows...
And so does mine...
That our roads are meant to part...
Far apart though we will be...
Please don't go away from my memories...
Never say goodbye...
Thanks...
Do you know Maya, that in these three
years, I tried hard to hate you...
To forget you... but I couldn't...
...couldn't do it, Maya...
You gave up the house, but the house
could never give you up...
You were right... I was a child...
I could never understand you...
And that I realize today...
I have grown up, Maya...
I am in love again...
I'm getting married...
Won't you say anything?
I'm very happy foryou...
Her name is catherine...
And I want you to be the best man
at my wedding, Maya...
I don't have anyone besides you...
You are my family...
Always have been... always will be...
This is foryou.
Dad!
Wherever he is... he is with us...
...he is with you...
Jai... I'm not ready yet...
I am being a motherto my
son after many years...
At this point I'm happy with this
one relationship... And...
You don't have to say anything...
Ijust want you to know that
I'll be waiting... Ok?
I'm sorry... Ijust came to say 'Bye'...
Rhea... You just get ready...
I'll wait foryou outside...
And good luck with your job in canada...
What time is yourtrain?
In two hours...
Arjun...
I know... I met Mom...
He probably forgot that I was leaving today...
Rhea... I have lost my right to
ask you forforgiveness...
...but I don't want to lose the
right to bless you...
Have a good life...
You stay in touch...
God! Rhea... We are really late...
I'm so sorry, Jai...
Don't worry about it...
Jai... I'm going to kill you...
You missed the ceremony...
Not my fault, sweetheart... Blame it on Rhea...
congratulations...
Rhea... It's so nice to finally meet you...
Jai talks about you all the time...
Well I hope good things...
Of course... You haven't met
my husband... Sweetheart?
Come meet my oldest friend
in the world... This is...
Rhea... - Rishi?
Great... You know each other?
Yes... We do...
congratulations... You are a lucky man...
Thank you...
Jai you are never going to
believe who's in town...
Honey... we'll see you later... Rhea...
See you in a bit...
Rishi? Your wedding? What about Maya?
Maya and I separated three years ago...
And you here? With Jai?
Dev and I divorced three years ago...
But do Dev and Maya know this?
Maya... What's the matter Maya?
Can't look me in the eye... can't face me...
Because you broke my heart? My home?
How could you break something
that was already broken, Maya?
Maybe you shouldn't have filled
the void between Dev and me...
But what could you do?
Dev's love is like that...
Ask me... I know...
Don't be so large-hearted Rhea
that I feel even smaller...
I'm not that magnanimous...
When Dev told me about you I left him...
But I don't think you know that...
How strange!
The love that changed the destinies...
...of two homes today stands destitute...
I moved on... Rishi moved on...
The two of you got left behind...
Perhaps that's our punishment...
Such a small punishment?
Try living with Dev... Then you
will know what punishment is...
Ok... I had to fight fifty women forthis...
It's tradition...
...the girl who gets these flowers
gets a new life...
...new happiness... And I want
that girl to be you, Maya...
Your heart has been searching
for love for many years...
...and that love is Dev...
And if you don't hurry now your love
will move further away from you...
Dev is leaving for Toronto... His train
leaves in fifteen minutes...
Go, Maya... Go get your love
before it's too late...
Go...
Thank you...
And Rhea?
Even she will forgive me with time...
Maya!
Dev...
Aren't you a little overdressed forthe station?
Sorry... It's been a while hasn't it?
I don't live here anymore...
And I don't live here despite being here...
Watch where you are going!
Nothing's changed Dev...
You still get angry at everything...
Anger's my own... Doesn't leave me...
Love can always leave and go...
What will you do if you find your lost love?
What will I say now, Maya...
I'll just say 'go back'!
Dev... Only I know how I have
survived these three years...
There was not a moment in the
day when I didn't think of you...
But I used to convince myself
that you are alright...
...you are happy with yourfamily...
I used to think of your happiness...
...and it would reduce a bit
of my unhappiness...
But today I realized that you
have been as alone as I am...
Yes, Dev...
Even I have been alone forthree years...
Alone... Like you...
Why, Dev?
Why did all this happen? Why?
Why did we meet? And then part?
Why, Dev? Why?
Everyone shares happiness and sorrow...
I want to share my punishment with you...
My life may not be complete living with you...
...but at least it will be a life...
Will you share this incomplete
life with me, Maya...
Answer me, Maya... It's hurting...
Answer... I can't sit here the whole...
What do you want me to do?
Go down on my knees?
Shut up... Just shut up... Speak politely...
Ok... Hello... Thank you... Nice to meet you...
I love you... Dammit!
I love you too...
come on...
Now?
Now what? Fifteen days in jail...
What?
Yeah... I stopped the train by pulling the chain...
Why are you wearing this silly saree?
I'd gone for Rishi's wedding...
The foundation of a marriage
should only be love...
And nothing else...
because if the foundation
is wrong, relationships end...
Like it happened with us...
Years later, we found love... Happiness...
But we just wish that...
...the road to our destination didn't have
to be paved with broken hearts...