[Man Screams]
[Man Narrating] So where are you?
You're in some motel room.
You just-- You just wake up,
and you're in a motel room.
There's the key. It feels like maybe
it's the first time you've been there,
but... perhaps you've
been there for a week,
three months.
It's kind of hard to say.
I don't-- I don't know.
It's just an anonymous room.
- [Radio Sportscast, Indistinct]
- This guy.
He's here already.
Lenny!
It's Leonard...
Like I told you before.
Did you?
I must have forgot.
I guess I've already
told you about my condition.
Oh, well, only every time I see you.
[Clicks Tongue]
- My car.
- This is your car.
Oh, you're in a playful mood.
It's not good for you to make
fun of someone's handicap.
- [Car Alarm Chirps]
- Just trying to have a little fun.
- [Engine Starts]
- [Radio Newscast, Indistinct]
- Roll up your window.
- Hmm?
It's broken.
I can get that fixed for you.
So where to, Sherlock?
- I got a lead on a place.
- Oh, what the hell do you
wanna go there for?
- You know it?
- Yeah, it's just this
fucked-up building.
- Why Do you wanna go there?
- Don't remember.
Looks like somebody's home.
Ah, that thing's
been here for years.
[Door Closes,
Alarm Chirps]
What are you talking about?
These tracks are only a few days old.
Tracks?
What are you? Pocahontas?
Come on!
Let's take a look inside.
[Sighs]
[Thinking]
"Teddy."
"Don't believe his lies.
He is the one. Kill him."
I finally found him.
How long have I been looking?
Find anything?
Didn't think so.
Let's go, huh?
Oh, fuck this.
- [Teddy Grunts]
- You're gonna pay for what you did.
Beg forgiveness,
and then you pay.
[Panting]
You don't have a clue,
you freak.
Beg My wife's forgiveness
before I blow your brains out.
Leonard, you don't know
what's going on.
- You don't even know my name.
- Teddy.
That's 'cause you read it
off a fucking picture.
You don't know who you are.
I'm Leonard Shelby.
I'm from San Francisco.
That's who you were.
That's not what you've become.
- Shut your mouth.
- You want to know, Lenny?
Come on. Come on, let's
go down to the basement.
Let's go down,
you and me, together.
Then you'll know
who you really are.
- No!
- [Gunshot]
[Narrating]
it's just an anonymous room.
There's nothing in the drawers.
But you look anyway.
Nothing except the Gideon Bible,
which I, of course, read religiously.
[Chuckles, Sighs]
You know, you know who you are, and
you know kind of all about yourself.
But just for day-to-day stuff,,
notes are really useful.
Sammy Jankis
had the same problem,
but he really had no system.
He wrote himself
a ridiculous amount of notes,
but he 'he'd get them all mixed up.
You really do need a system if--
if you're gonna make it work.
[Bell Buzzes]
- Hi.
- I'm Mr. Shel by from 304.
- What can I do for you, Leonard?
- Um--
- Burt.
Burt. I'm not sure. I think I may have
asked you to hold my calls.
- You don't know?
- I'm not too good on the phone.
Right. You said you like to look people
in the eye when you talk to them.
- Yeah.
- You don't remember saying that?
- Well, that's the thing.
I have this condition.
- Condition?
- It's my memory.
- Amnesia?
No, no, no. It's different from that.
I have no short-term memory.
I know who I am.
I know all about myself.
Since my injury, I can't make
new memories. Everything fades.
If we talk for too long,
I'll forget how we started.
The next time I see you, I'm not
gonna remember this conversation.
[Laughs] I don't even know
if I've met you before.
So if I seem a little strange
or rude or something, uh--
I've told you this
before, haven't I?
Yeah. I mean, I don't mean
to mess with you, but it's so weird.
- You don't remember me at all?
- No.
- We've talked a bunch of times.
- I'm sure we have.
Well, what's the last thing
you remember?
My wife.
What's it like?
It's like waking.
It's like you just woke up.
That must suck.
I mean, it's all backwards.
Like, may be you get an idea about
what you want to do next,
but you don't remember
what You just did.
- I'm exactly the opposite--
- How long have I been staying here?
- A couple of days.
- And you're holding my calls?
- like you said.
- Okay, but this guy's an exception.
- Do you know this guy?
- Yeah, it's your friend, right?
What makes you think
he's my friend?
- I just saw you together, that's all.
- He's not my friend.
- Okay.
- if he calls or if he shows up here,
you give me a call
in my room, okay?
- What, his name's Teddy?
- Teddy, yeah.
All right.
Look, I hope my condition's
not gonna be a problem for you.
No, not as long as you
remember to pay the bill.
- Okay.
- Forty.
This guy--
He's here already.
Lenny!
[Narrating] You really needa system
if you're gonna make it work.
You kind of learn
to trust your own hand writing.
That becomes an important part
of your life. You write your self notes.
And where you put your notes--
That also becomes important.
You need a jacket that's got
like six pockets in it.
Particular pockets
for particular things.
You just kind of learn to know where
things go and how the system works.
You have to be wary of
other people writing stuff, for you,
that it's gonna lead you astray.
I mean, I don't know how these
people try and take advantage
of somebody with this condition.
If you have a piece
of information which is vital,
writing on your body instead of
on a piece of paper can be the answer.
It's just a permanent way
of keeping a note.
[Phone Ringing]
Who is this?
[Thinking]
"Remember Sam my Jankis."
[Door Opening]
[Quiet Chattering]
Excuse me, sir.
You left these at your table.
Thanks. Uh... Lincoln Street?
Oh, yeah, just go
straight out on Sixth Street.
I'm gonna write this down.
- It's easy.Just go--
- Trust me. I need to write this down.
[Thinking]
"The Discount Inn."
[Drops key]
[Thinking]
Discount Inn.
Natalie.
My car.
Teddy.
"John Edward Gammell."
This guy told me
his name was Teddy.
"Don't believe his lies."
[Dial Tone]
[Dialing]
[Line Ringing]
- [Man On Phone]
Yeah? Lenny, is that you?
- Mr. Gammell?
- John Gammell?
- Lenny, it's Teddy. Stay there.
- I'll be right over.
- Okay. I'll be waiting.
"White. Male"
"First name John."
"Last name 'G' for Gammell."
"Drugs. License plate."
"SG1 3...
7I U."
It's him.
I found you, you fuck.
You said we talked before.
I don't remember that.
Yeah, but it's not amnesia. I remember
everything up until my injury.
I just can't make new memories.
So I can't remember talking to you.
What did we talk about?
Oh, Sammy Jankis.
I tell people about Sammy
to help them understand.
Sammy's story helps me
understand my own situation.
Well, Sammy wrote himself endless
amounts of notes, but he got mixed up.
I have a more graceful
solution to the memory problem.
I'm disciplined and organized.
I use habit and routine
to make my life possible.
Sammy had no drive,
no reason to make it work.
Me? Yeah, I got a reason.
[Car Alarm Chirps]
[Thinking] "Today, 1:00 p.m.
Meet Natalie for info.
"She has also lost someone.
She will help you out of pity."
- Natalie?
- You don't remember me.
- I'm sorry. I should have
explained. I have this--
- You did explain, Lenny.
Please call me Leonard.
My wife called me Lenny.
- Yeah, I know. You told me.
- Then I probably told you
how much I hated it.
Yeah.
Do you mind taking your glasses off?
It's hard for me to--
Thanks. So you have
information for me?
- Is that what your little note says?
- Yeah.
Must be tough living your life according
to a couple of scraps of paper.
Mix your laundry list with your
grocery list, and you'll end up
eating your underwear.
I guess that's why you have
those freaky tattoos.
Yeah, it's tough.
It's almost impossible.
Look, I'm sorry I don't remember you.
It's nothing personal.
I do have information for you.
You gave me a license plate number.
Had my friend at D.M.V. trace it.
Guess what name came up.
John Edward Gammell.John G.
- Do you know him?
- No.
But his face on his driver's
license looked really familiar.
I think he's been
in the bar, maybe.
Here's a copy of his license,
his registration, photo and all.
are you sure you want this?
Have I told you
what this man did?
- Yeah.
- Then you shouldn't have to ask.
But even If you get revenge,
you're not gonna remember it.
You're not even gonna know
that it happened.
My wife deserves vengeance.
Doesn't make any difference
whether I know about it.
Just because there are things
I don't remember doesn't make
my actions meaningless.
The world doesn't just disappear
when you close your eyes, does it?
Anyway, maybe I'll take
a photograph to remind myself,
get another freaky tattoo.
Tell me about her again.
Why?
Because you
like to remember her.
She was beautiful.
To me, she was perfect.
No. Don't
just recite the words.
Close your eyes...
and remember her.
You can just feel the details.
The bits and pieces you never
bothered to put into words.
And you can feel
these extreme moments...
even If you don't want to.
You put these together, and
you get the feel ofa person.
Enough to know
how much you miss them...
and how much you hate
the person who took them away.
I, um-- I added
an address in here.
It might be useful. It's an abandoned
place outside of town.
A guy I knew used to do
bigger deals there.
It's isolated.
Sounds perfect.
Do I owe you any--
I wasn't helping you for money.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
"See, you have this condition."
[Laughs]
Oh, are you still staying
at the Discount Inn, room 304?
You left it at my place.
Yeah.
[Chuckles]
- They treating you okay?
- I don't remember.
[Laughs]
You know what we have in common?
We are both survivors.
You take care, Leonard.
[Door Opens, Closes]
[Thinking]
"Remember Sammy Jankis."
I met Sammy through work.
Insurance. I was an investigator.
I'd investigate the claims
to see which ones were phony.
I had to see through
people's bullshit.
It was useful experience,
'cause now it's my life.
When I meet someone, I don't
know if I've met them before.
I have to look in their eyes
and try and figure them out.
My job taught me the best way
to find out what someone knew
was just to let them talk...
and watch the eyes
and the body language.
If someone scratches their nose
while they're talking, experts
tell you it means they're lying.
It really means they're nervous.
People get nervous
for all sorts of reasons.
It's all about context.
Yeah, I was good.
Sam my was my first rst
real challenge lenge.
[Engine Starts]
Yo, Lenny! I thought
you split for good.
- Well I, things change.
- So I see.
- My name's Teddy.
- I guess I've told you
about my condition.
Only every time I see you.
Come on, I'll buy you lunch.
- Have I told you about Sammy Jankis?
- Mm. Yeah.
I'm sick of hearing about the guy.
What about John G?
- Who?
- Johnny G., the guy you're looking for.
- That's why you haven't
left town, am I right?
- Maybe.
- Leonard, look,
you have to be very careful.
- Why?
The other day you mentioned
that maybe somebody...
was trying to set you up,
get you to kill the wrong guy.
Well, I go on facts,
not recommendations, but thank you.
Lenny, you can't trust a man's life
to your little notes and pictures.
- Why not?
- Because your notes
could be unreliable.
- Memory's unreliable.
- Oh, please!
No, really. Memory's not perfect.
It's not even that good.
Ask the police.
Eyewitness testimony is unreliable.
- Cops don't catch a killer
by remembering stuff.
- Right--
They collect facts, they make notes,
and they draw conclusions.
Facts, not memories.
That's how you investigate.
It's what I used to do.
Look, memory can change
the shape of a room.
It can change the color of a car.
And memories can be distorted.
They're just an interpretation.
They're not a record.
They're irrelevant
If you have the facts.
You really want
to get this guy, don't you?
He killed My wife.
He took away my fucking memory.
He destroyed my ability to live.
- You're living.
- Only for revenge.
Well, then we'll get the bastard.
Where are you staying?
The Discount Inn.
I don't know what room.
I haven't got my key.
Probably left in your room.
[Bell Ringing]
Hi. I'm checked in here, but
I think I've misplaced my key.
How you doing, Leonard?
Probably in the room, right?
I don't see my key anywhere.
This is the wrong room.
You're in 304 now.
- I'm sorry. I fucked up.
- This is not my room?
- No. Come on, let's go.
- Why is this my hand writing?
Well... this was your room,
but now you're in 304.
- When was I in here?
- Last week.
- But then I rented you
another room on top ofit.
- Why?
Business is slow. I mean,
I told my boss about the--
your condition and stuff,, and he said
try and rent him another room.
So how many rooms am I checked
into in this shit-hole?
J Just two, so far.
Well, at least you're being
honest about ripping me off.
Well, you're not
gonna remember anyway.
You don't have to be
that honest, Burt.
Leonard, always get a receipt.
Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna write that down.
- Hey, what time is it?
- Quarter to one.
Excuse me.
Your room's--
- Natalie?
- You don't remember me.
I'd just become an investigator
when I came across Sammy.
Mr. Samuel R.Jankis.
Strangest case ever.
Now, the guy's a 58-year-old
semiretired accountant.
He and his wife had been in this
car accident. Nothing too serious.
But he's acting funny. He can't get
a handle on what's going on.
The doctors find some possible
damage to the hippocampus.
Nothing conclusive, but Sammy can't
remember anything for more than
a couple of minutes.
Can't work, can't do shit.
The medical bills pile up.
His wife calls the insurance
company, and I get sent in.
Now, this is my first
big claims investigation,
so I really check into it.
- Can I get you some coffee?
- Sammy can think just fine,
but he can't make
any new memories.
- He can only remember things
for a couple of minutes.
- This is Mr. Shelby.
He'd watch TV, but anything
longer than a couple of minutes
was too confusing.
He couldn't remember how it began.
He liked commercials.
- They were short.
- Sammy.
It's time for my shot.
The crazy part was
that this guy...
who couldn't even follow the plot of
Green Acres anymore...
could do the most
complicated things...
as long as he learned them
before the accident...
and as long as he kept his mind
on what he was doing.
- Be gentle.
- Now, the doctors assure me...
there's a real condition called
anterial-grade memory loss,
or short-term memory loss.
It's rare, but legit.
Every time I see him...
I catch this look,
this slight look
of recognition.
But he says
he can't remember me at all.
Sammy, it's okay.
I got it. I got it.
- H i, Mr. Shel by.
- H i, Mrs. J ankis.
- Now, I can read people,
and I'm thinking: bad actor.
- This is Mr. Shelby, Sammy.
So now I'm suspicious,
and I order more tests.
[Thinking]
Awake.
Oh, where am I?
Somebody's bedroom.
Ah, it must be her room.
But who is she?
[Moaning]
It's only me.
- Did you sleep okay?
- Yeah. You?
Yeah. Oh, shit. Shit!
I got to be some place.
- It's pretty weird.
- It's useful.
You never write a phone
number on your hand?
I, um-- I should be able
to talk to my friend today
about the license plate.
- Yeah, the license plate.
- John G.'s license plate.
You have it tattooed
on your thigh.
[Water Running]
[Thinking]
"Natalie."
"She has also lost someone.
She will help you out of pity."
[Footsteps]
Mm, if It's registered
in this state,
it should only take
a couple of seconds to pull up
his license and registration.
I'll call you
as soon as I talk to him.
Do you thi nk we could
just arrange a meeting now?
I'm not too good on the phone.
You know,
it's great that you--
well, that you're
helping me like this.
I'm helping you
because you helped me.
So next time you see me,
will you remember me?
[Whispering]
I think you will.
I'm sorry.
Lenny, before you go, could
I have my shirt back, please?
[Engine Starts]
Yo, Lenny! I thought
you split for good.
Sammy couldn't pick up
any new skills at all.
But I find something
in my research: conditioning.
Sammy should still be able
to learn through repetition.
It's how you learn stuff
like riding a bike. You just
get better through practice.
It's a completely
different part of the brain
from the short-term memory.
So I had the doctors test
Sammy's response to conditioning.
- Just pick up any three objects.
- That's a test?
Hey, where were you guys
when I did my C.P.A.?
[Laughs]
Sorry.
Ta-da!
- [Object Buzzes]
- Ow! What the fuck?
- It's a test, Sammy.
- Well, test this, you fucking quack.
[Leonard]
Some of the objects were electrify Ied.
They'd give him a small shock.
They kept repeating the test,
always with the same objects
electrify Ied.
The poi nt was to see if
Sam my could learn to avoid
the electrify Ied objects...
not by memory,
but by instinct.
[Car Alarm Chirps]
[Knocking]
Natalie, right?
Who the fuck is Dodd?
Guess I don't have to worry
about him anymore.
- What the fuck have
you got me into?
- Shh. Come inside.
- Who is he?
- Calm down. Okay?
This is my problem. It has nothing
to do with your investigation.
- How did you get me into this?
- You offered to help when you
saw what he did to my face.
- How do I know he did that?
- Because I came straight to you
after he did it.
- I showed you what he did,
and I asked you to help me.
- And I just take your word?
- Yeah.
- Something doesn't feel right.
I think someone's fucking with me,
trying to get me to kill the wrong guy.
- Did you? Kill him?
- What? Of course not!
Hey, what--
Sit down, okay? Sit.
This has nothing to do with you.
You helped me out,
and I'm grateful.
You have to burn them.
Leonard, you decided to help me.
trust yourself.
trust your own judgment.
You can question everything.
- You can never know anything for sure.
- There are things you know for sure.
Such as?
I know what that's gonna
sound like when I knock on it.
[Knocks On Wood]
I know what that's gonna
feel like when I pick it up.
See? Certainties. It's the kind
of memory you take for granted.
You know,
I can remember so much.
The feel of the world... and her.
[Sighing]
She's gone.
And the present is trivia, which
I scribble down as fucking notes!
Hey, hey, come on.
Try and relax. Come on.
It's not easy for me to relax,
you know? Shh.
Come on.
Take your jacket off.
Yeah. Come on.
Here.
Didn't think
you were the type.
It's backwards.
Come here. Come here!
What about here?
Maybe it's
for when I find him.
I've lost somebody too.
I'm sorry.
His name was Jimmy.
what happened to him?
He went to meet somebody.
He never came back.
Who did he go to meet?
A guy called Teddy.
What do the police think?
They don't look too hard
for guys like Jimmy.
When you find this guy,
this John G.,
what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna kill him.
Maybe I can help you
find him.
I don't even know
how long she's been gone.
It's like I've woken up
in bed and she's not here...
because she's gone to
the bathroom or something.
But somehow I just--
I just know she's never
gonna come back to bed.
if I could just reach over...
and touch her side of the bed...
I would know that it was cold.
But I can't.
I know I can't have her back.
But I don't want to wake up in
the morning thinking she's still here.
I lie here not knowing
how long I've been alone.
So how--
How can I heal?
How am I supposed to heal
if I can't... feel time?
[Thinking]
"She has also lost someone.
She will help you out of pity."
They kept testing Sammy
for months,
always with the same objects
carrying an electrical charge.
- [Object Buzzes]
- Ow! What the fuck?
- It's a test, Sammy.
- Test this, you quack!
Even with total
short-term memory loss,
Sammy should have learned
to instinctively stop picking up
the wrong objects.
All the previous cases
responded to conditioning.
Sammy didn't respond at all.
It was enough
to suggest that his condition
was psychological, not physical.
We turned down his clai m
on the grounds that he wasn't
covered for mental illness.
His wife got stuck with the bills,
and I got a big promotion.
Conditioning didn't work for Sammy,
so he became helpless.
But it works for me.
I live the way Sammy couldn't.
Habit and routine
make my life possible.
Conditioning.
Acting on instinct.
[Indistinct Screeching]
[Man Shouts]
- [Thinking] Awake.
- [Car Horn Honks]
Where am I?
Motel room.
[Groans]
Some anonymous motel room.
Nothing in the drawers,
but I'll take a look anyway.
Nothing except
the Gideon Bi-- Bible.
[knocking At Door]
Hey, open up!
- [Muffled Crying]
- Just a minute.
- Open the door.
- [Continues knocking]
Lenny!
Open the door!
Come on!
Hi, Teddy.
- Finished playing with yourself, Lenny?
- [Door Closes]
- [Groans]
- [Muffled Cries Continue]
[Sighs]
Oh, I get it.
Amorous neighbors.
- What are you doing here?
- [Laughs]
You called me.
You said you needed my help.
You know, I've had more rewarding
friendships than this one.
Although I do get to keep
telling the same jokes.
- [Muffled Crying Continues]
- What the fuck is that?
- Who the fuck is that?
- You don't know him?
No! Should I?
Wait a minute.
- Is that John G.?
- I don't think so.
- You don't think so?
You didn't write it down?
- I might've fallen asleep.
For Christ's sakes!
Ask him.
- What's your name? Your name!
- [Mutters]
- Dodd.
- And who did this to you?
- What?
- Who did this to you?
You did.
Look, I'm not gonna
help you kill that guy.
No, just let me
think for a minute.
[Muffled Crying Continues]
- Okay, Natalie.
- who's Natalie?
- Natalie who?
- Why?
Maybe I know her. Look, we gotta
get him out of here.
All right, all right,
all right, all right.
He's gotta have
a car, right?
So we take him down to his car,
we tell him to get out of town
or we're gonna kill him.
We can't just walk him
out of here tied up and bleeding.
- How the fuck
did you get him up here?
- I don't know!
You don't know.
Yes, I do.
This is not my room.
- It must be his room. Great! Let's go.
- No, no, no.
- We can't just leave him here.
- Why not?
The maid's gonna walk in.
She'll see him, call the cops.
He can I.D. us.
Okay. We untie him,
we clean him up...
and we march him out of here
with a gun in his back.
A gun.
Why would I have a gun?
- It must be his.
- I don't think they'd let
someone like me carry a gun.
Fucking hope not.
Which one?
We should probably steal his car.
You know, teach him a lesson.
- Shut up.
- That's all right for you to say.
You're the one with the Jag.
All right, get in.
I'm gonna ride with him.
You follow us.
Give me your keys.
Take your own car.
[Engine Starts]
[Tires Squealing]
- So was he scared?
- Yeah. I think it was
your sinister moustache.
Fuck you. You should have
stolen his car.
- What's wrong with this one?
- Nothing. You want to trade?
[Sighs]
So what Do you do now?
I'm going to find out what
the fuck that was all about.
[Knocking]
Natalie, right?
Who the fuck is Dodd?
Sammy's wife was crippled
by the cost of supporting him...
and fighting
the company's decision.
But it wasn't the money
that got to her.
- I never said
that Sammy was faking.
- Listen. I have an idea.
Sammy, I have an idea
I want you to do for me.
Just that his problem
was mental, not physical.
I want you to have
a pen in your pocket, okay?
- You're gonna have
a pen in your pocket.
- She couldn't understand.
- I did something wrong.
- You did something wrong!
We're gonna deal with it.
- We're gonna try harder--
- when she looks into his eyes
and sees the same person.
- You can't go anywhere!
- if It's not a physical problem,
he should just snap out ofit.
- Ellen called! [Crying]
- Ellen called?
- Ellen can't come today!
Ellen can't come!
- Okay. I'm sorry!
- I'm sorry. I'm trying. I'm sorry.
- Try harder!
So good old Leonard Shelby
from the insurance company
gives her the seed of doubt...
just like he gave it
to the doctors.
But I never said that he was faking.
I never said that.
[Thinking]
Hmm, I don't feel drunk.
[Door Closes]
[Clattering]
[Urinating]
[Toilet Flushing]
[Both Grunting]
- [woman knocking]
Hello? Housekeeping.
- Oh, shit.
- Not right now.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
Okay.
[Thinking]
"Dodd. Put him onto Teddy...
or just get rid of him
for Natalie."
Dodd.
Get rid of him.
Ask Natalie.
Teddy, Teddy.
[Dial Tone]
[Line Ringing]
[Teddy's voice On Machine]
Yeah, leave your number.
You know what to do.
Yeah. This is a message
for Teddy.
I'm at the Mount crest Inn
of Fifth Street, room six.
I need you to come over
as soon as you get this.
It's important.
Oh, this is Leonard.
Thanks. Bye.
Whew. Fuck.
[Sighing]
Mrs.Jankis didn't understand
that you can't bully someone
into remembering.
The more pressure you're under,
the harder it gets.
Uh, well, then call me--
call me back?
[Car Alarm Blaring]
[Thinking]
Okay, so what am I doing?
Oh, I'm chasing this guy.
No. He's chasing me.
[Alarm Continues Blaring]
[Alarm Chirps, Stops]
[Engine Starts]
[Tires Screeching]
[Groaning]
Fuck.
[Thinking]
"Dodd. White guy.
Mount crest I nn
on Fifth Street."
I'll get the jump on you,
you fucker.
[Man On Television]
$9995, $98 a month.
A '97 Toyota RAV-4,
$11,995, $110 a month.
- Oh, fuck.
- A '96 Dodge Caravan,
$8995, $95 a month.
- Sorry.
- A '97--
[Thinking]
I need a weapon.
This will do.
Hmm, I don't feel drunk.
[Car Alarm Chirps]
[Horn Honking]
[Thinking]
Do I know this guy?
- [Honking Continues]
- He seems to know me.
What the fuck?
- I like your car.
- Thank you.
- Where'd you get it?
- Are you interested in buying one?
What, I haven't made a strong enough
impression on you?
I wouldn't be
too hard on yourself.
[Thinking]
Okay, so what am I doing?
- [Phone Ringing]
- Who is this?
[Car Alarm Chirps]
Ouch. Cut it out.
- How can you read that again?
- It's good.
Yeah, but you've read it,
like, a thousand times.
I enjoy it.
I always thought
the pleasure of a book...
- was in wanting to know
what happens next.
- Look, don't be a prick.
I'm not reading it
to annoy you. I enjoy it.
J Just let me read, please.
[Thinking]
Probably tried this before.
Probably burned truckloads
of your stuff.
Can't remember
to forget you.
Yeah. Uh-huh.
Well, sir, that'd certainly be
in keeping with some of
my own discoveries.
I was hoping for a little more
on the drugs angle. Hang on a sec?
Now, the police report mentioned
the drugs found in the car
outside my house.
The carwas stolen.
Bloody prints were all over it.
I got friends in the department.
They gave me a copy ofit.
I dealt with the police a lot
in my insurance job.
With my condition, it's really tough.
I can't keep it all in mind at once.
I have to summarize
the different sections.
And there's pages missing.
I guess I've been trying
to log them all.
I don't know why
these are crossed out.
But they weren't even
looking for John G.
The stuff they found in the car
just fit in with what they
believed had happened,
so they didn't chase
any ofit up.
[Door Squeaks, Shuts]
Honey.
Honey, it's late.
Everything okay?
- [Muffled Cries]
- You okay in there?
Was it good for you?
What? Was I supposed
to lock the door?
No.
I'd like you to leave now.
[Car Alarm Chirps]
There's something about
the drugs stashed in the car
that doesn't ring true for me.
Because the police claim
the guy was an addict,
needing money to score,
which I think is bullshit,
'cause he's not gonna go
breaking into places while
he's still got a stash that big.
Well, I think John G. left it there
or planted it there.
How Do you know that?
Oh, shit, that's true. It fits.
So he's a dealer.
Hang on a sec.
Now we're getting somewhere.
"Discount Inn."
[Alarm Chirps]
Yeah, okay.
Blonde's fine.
[Chuckles]
Well, that's what they say.
The Discount Inn. 304.
Leonard.
Well, what then?
We just go to bed.
You wait for me to fall asleep.
You go into the bathroom
and you slam the door.
- Slam it?
- Yeah. Loud enough
to wake me up.
- And that's it?
- That's it.
Uh,
yeah, first I just need you to put
these things around the room.
Just pretend they're your things
and that this is your bedroom.
- Should I wear it?
- No, no, no. Uh, just like
you took it off or something.
I-I don't want you
to use it. I'm sorry.
Just-- I just mean put them
around the room, you know,
as if they were
your-- your things.
Whatever gets you off.
[Door Squeaks, Shuts]
I can't blame the cops
for not taking me seriously.
This is difficult to understand.
I mean, look at Sammy Jankis.
His own wife couldn't deal with it.
I told you about how she tried
to get him to snap out ofit.
Eventually she came
to see me at the office.
I found out all kinds of shit.
- She told me about life with
Sammy, how she treated him.
- Thank you for seeing me.
It got to the point where
she'd get Sammy to hide food
all around the house...
and then she'd stop feeding him
just to see if his hunger...
would make him remember
where he'd hidden the food.
She wasn't a cruel person.
She just wanted old Sammy back.
Mr. Shelby, you know all about Sammy
and you've decided that he's faking.
Mrs.Jankis, the company's position
isn't that Sammy is faking anything.
It's just that his condition
can't be shown to be--
I just wanna know what your
honest opinion about Sammy is.
We shouldn't even be talking like this
while the case is still open to appeal.
- I'm not appealing the decision.
- Then why are you here?
Try to understand.
when I look at Sammy,
I don't see some... vegetable.
I see my same old Sammy.
What do you think
that's like for me...
to suspect that he might be
imagining this whole problem?
And that if Just could
say the right thing,
he'd snap out of it
and go back to being normal.
If I --
If I knew that my old Sammy
were truly gone,
then I could say good-bye
and start loving this new Sammy.
As long as I have doubt,
I can't say good-bye and move on.
- What do you want from me?
- I want you to forget the company
you work for 30 seconds...
and tell me If you really believe that
Sammy's faking his condition.
I need to know...
what you honestly believe.
I bel ieve that Sam my
should be physically capable
of making new memories.
Thank you.
I thought I helped her. I thought
she just needed some kind of answer.
I didn't think it was important
what the answer was,
just that she had one
to believe.
- A car this nice you should lock.
- Who the fuck are you?
- Teddy, your buddy.
- Prove it.
Sammy. Remember Sammy?
You told me about Sammy!
- Jeez!
- What the fuck are you doing in my car?
What, your sense of humor
went with the memory?
- Do you even know
why you're here?
- Unfinished business.
Lenny, let me inform you.
Your business here
is very much finished.
- You're still here because of Natalie.
- Who's Natalie?
Schmuck, whose house do you think
you just walked out of?
Oh, that's right. Take a look at your
pictures. I bet you got one of her.
Oh, nice shot, Leibovitz.
You'll wanna make a note.
You can't trust her.
Oh, yeah? Why's that?
Because by now she's taken
a look at this suit and the car...
and she's starting to figure out ways of
turning the situation to her advantage.
She's already got you staying
with her, for Christ's sakes.
You can't go back in there.
Let me give you the name ofa motel.
- You're lucky I ran into you.
That broad's bad news.
- What do you mean, "bad news"?
She's involved with drugs.
All right, look. These. You see these?
This is the bar
where she works.
Her boyfriend's a drug dealer.
She takes orders for him,
arranges meets.
He writes messages
on the back of these.
Then she slips him the answers
when she serves him his drinks.
- Why should I care?
- Because when she gets jammed up,
- she's gonna use you to protect herself.
- From who?
Guys are gonna wanna know
what happened to her boyfriend.
Guys are gonna come after her.
Somebody's gotta pay, Lenny.
Somebody always pays.
Maybe she'll make it you.
Oh, yeah? Well, maybe
she'll make it you. Is that it?
You worried that she's gonna
use me against you?
- No.
- why not?
Because she doesn't know who I am.
- Why are you following me?
- Maybe I wanna help.
She doesn't know anything about your
investigation, okay, Einstein?
So write this down.
When she offers to help,
it'll be for her own reasons.
I'm not lying.
Take my pen. Write this down.
Do not trust her.
- There. You happy now?
- I won't be happy
until you leave town.
why not?
You ever wonder how long you
can hang around here before
people start asking questions?
- What sort of questions?
- The same sort of questions
you should be asking yourself.
- Like what?
- Like, how did you get
this suit, the car?
- I have money.
- From what?
My wife's death. I used to work
in insurance. We were well covered.
Oh!
So in your grief you wandered
into a Jaguar dealership.
You don't have a clue, Do you?
- You don't even know who you are.
- Yes, I do.
I don't have amnesia. I remember
everything right up until the incident.
I am Leonard Shelby.
I am from San Francisco--
That's who you were.
You do not know who you are,
what you've become
since... the incident.
You wander around
playing detective.
You don't even know
how long ago it was.
Let me put it this way.
Were you wearing designer suits
when you sold insurance?
- I didn't sell insurance.
I investigated it.
- Right. You're an investigator.
- Well, maybe you should
start investigating yourself.
- Thank you for the advice.
Look, do me a favor.
Don't go back in there.
Will you take
the motel out of town?
It's been fun, Lenny.
[Thinking]
"Do not trust her."
"Don't believe his lies."
Oh, fuck it.
I need my own place.
[keys Jangling, Engine Starts]
No. She shouldn't have
given me that responsibility.
I'm a claims investigator,
not a doctor.
Yeah, yeah. I guess.
But I've got all sorts
of other considerations.
Legal responsibility,
large financ--
- Who is this?
- [Receiver Clicks, Dial Tone]
Write this down.
Write down what happened.
Write it down. Write it down.
Come on. Concentrate.
Keep it in mind. Find a pen--
- What happened?
- What does it look like?
He beat the shit out of me.
- Who?
Fuck, Leonard. Dodd.
Dodd beat the shit out of me.
- Why?
- Why? Because of you.
- Because I did what you told me to do!
- Calm down.
- Tell him about Teddy!
- Great fucking idea!
Calm down. Take it easy.
You're safe. It's okay.
Come on.Just sit down.
Sit down.
Here. Sit down.
Okay. You're okay.
I'll just get some ice
for your face.
Here.
I did exactly
what you told me to do.
I went to Dodd...
and I told him that I--
I didn't have any of Jimmy's money...
or the drugs,
and that this Teddy
must have taken everything.
And what did he say?
He didn't believe me.
He said if I don't have the drugs
by tomorrow, he's gonna kill me.
And then he just--
he just started hitting me.
Where is he?
- Why?
- I'll go see him.
- And?
- I'll give him
some bruises of his own...
and tell him to look
for a guy called Teddy.
Ah, he'll kill you, Lenny.
My wife used
to call me Lenny.
Yeah?
Yeah. I hated it.
Oh, this guy--
this guy is so dangerous.
- Let's just think
of something else, okay?
- No, no.
You just tell me what he looks like...
and where I can find him.
- Have you got a pen?
- In my purse.
He'll, um--
He'll probably find you.
- What do you mean?
- I told him about your car.
Why?
He was beating the shit out of me.
I had to tell him something.
Just write it all down.
Be careful.
I'll be fine.
- A car this nice you should lock.
- Who the fuck are you?
[Ringing]
[Ringing Continues]
Front desk? Burt. Right.
This is Mr. Shelby in room 21.
Yeah, that's it.
I don't want any calls.
Nope. None at all.
- what's wrong?
- Somebody's come already.
- who?
- He calls himself Dodd.
- What does he want?
- He wants to know what happened
to Jimmy and his money.
- He thinks I have it.
He thinks I took it.
- Oh. Well, did you?
No.
- What's this all about?
- Fuck!
You don't have
a fucking clue, Do you?
You're just blissfully ignorant.
- Look, I have this condition.
- Yeah, I know all about your
fucking condition, Leonard!
Probably know more about it
than you do. You don't have
a clue about anything else.
- What happened?
- Jimmy went to meet
some guy named Teddy.
He took a lot of money
with him, and he never came back.
Jimmy's partners think I set him up.
I don't even know
If you know this, Teddy,
- or how well.
- Neither do I.
- Don't protect him! Help me.
- I'm not. How?
- Get rid of Dodd for me.
Kill him. I'll pay you.
- What?
What Do you think I am?
I'm not gonna kill someone for money.
What then? Love?
What would you kill for?
- You'd kill for your wife, wouldn't you?
- That's different.
- Not to me. I wasn't
fucking married to her.
- Hey, don't talk about My wife.
I can talk about
whoever the fuck I want!
I can say whatever I want
and you won't remember.
I could call
your wife a fucking whore.
- Calm down.
- Easy for you to say.
You can't get scared.
You don't know how, you fucking idiot!
- Take it easy.
This has nothing to do with me.
- Maybe it does.
How the fuck would you know?
You don't know a fucking thing!
- You can't get scared,
but can you get angry?
- Yes.
Ah, you pathetic piece of shit.
I can say whatever
the fuck I want...
and you won't have a fucking clue,
you fucking retard!
- Shut your mouth.
- You know what? I'm gonna use you.
I'm telling you now, because
I'm gonna enjoy it so much more...
if I know that you could stop me
If you weren't such a fucking freak.
Did you lose your pen?
Well, that's too bad, freak.
Otherwise, you could write
yourself a little note...
about how much Natalie hates
your retarded guts and that
I called your wife a whore.
- Don't say another fuckin' word.
- About your whore of a wife?
I read about your
condition, Leonard.
You know what one of the causes
of short-term memory loss is?
venereal disease.
Maybe your cunt of a fucking wife
sucked one too many diseased cocks...
and turned you
into a fucking retard!
You sad, sad...
freak.
I can say
whatever the fuck I want...
and you won't remember.
We'll still be best friends...
or maybe even lovers.
Fuck.
I'll see you soon.
[Thinking]
Stay focused. Find a pen.
Gotta write this down.
Gotta write it down.
Concentrate.
Concentrate. Concentrate.
Keep it in mind.
Come on. Find a pen.
I have to find a pen.
Write this down.
Write this down,
exactly what happened.
Gonna write down
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Find a pen.Jeez!
Come on.
Okay, focus. Keep focused.
Keep-- Keep it in mind.
Come on. Find a pen. Write this note.
Write down what happened.
Write it down. Write it down.
Come on. Concentrate.
Keep it in mind. Find a pen.
- What happened?
- What does it look like?
He beat the shit out of me.
- Who?
Fuck, Leonard. Dodd.
Dodd beat the shit out of me.
- [knocking At Door]
- [Man] Hello?
- It's Burt, from the front desk.
- [knocking]
- Yeah?
- Uh, I know you said
you didn't want any calls.
But this guy called.
He's on the phone now.
He says he's a cop.
- A cop?
- Yeah. And, uh,
he says you're really gonna wanna
know what he has to say, so--
I'm not too good on the phone.
I need to look people in the eye
when I talk to them.
Well, what--
You can, um--
You can crash on the couch.
It's comfortable.
Just have a seat.
Thanks.
- So how long Do you think
it's gonna take you?
- Hmm?
You told me you were looking
for the guy who killed your wife?
Oh, well, that depends on if he's
here in town or if he's moved on.
I have my file here.
Can I ask you something?
If you have all of that information,
then why haven't the police
found him for you?
- Well, they're not looking for him.
- Why not?
They don't think he exists. You see,
I told them what I remembered.
I was asleep.
- Something woke me up.
- [Glass Shatters]
Her side of the bed was cold.
She'd obviously been out
of bed for awhile.
[Clattering]
[Muffled Cries]
There had to be a second man.
Somebody hit me from behind.
I remember. It's about the last
thing that I do remember.
Look, the police did not believe me.
If we check the police--
How do they explain what
you do remember? The gun and stuff,.
John G. was clever.
He was clever.
See, he took the dead man's gun
and replaced it with the sap
that he hit me with.
He left my gun and he left
the getaway car. He gave
the police a complete package.
The found the sap with my blood on it
in the dead man's hand.
And they only found my gun.
They didn't need
to look for anybody else.
I was the only guy who disagreed with
the facts, and I had brain damage.
See, the cops are not gonna believe
someone in my condition.
Leonard, you can stay here for
a couple of days if It'll help you.
Well, thanks.
I have to go back to work.
So, um, just make
yourself at home.
You can watch Tv or you can have
some food, whatever you want, okay?
- Make yourself at home.
- One thing.
- Something to remember you by.
- My name is Natalie.
"Natalie."
[TV Playing]
[Door Opens]
- what's wrong?
- Somebody's come already.
[Phone Ringing]
[Ringing Continues]
[Ringing]
- On the house.
- Thanks.
[Laughing]
My, you really do have a problem.
- J Just like that cop said.
- Hmm?
- Your condition.
- Well, nobody's perfect.
What's the last thing
that you do remember?
- My wife.
- That's sweet.
Dying.
I remember My wife dying.
Let me, um,
get you another one.
I think this one's dusty.
Why are you calling me?
What Do you want?
I know you're a cop,
but what Do you want?
Have I done something wrong?
I don't know.
Something bad, maybe.
Why are you asking me?
I can't remember what I've done.
You wouldn't believe me anyway.
Because of my condition.
You don't believe someone
with this condition.
Nobody believed Sammy!
I didn't even fucking believe Sammy!
"Ferdy's Bar."
"Come by after. Natalie."
I'll have a beer, please.
- What Do you want?
- A beer, please.
You can't just waltz in here
dressed like that and ask for a beer.
- What, is there a dress code?
- Why are you here?
- I'm meeting someone called Natalie.
- Well, that's me.
Yeah.
We met before, right?
- Then why am I here?
- I don't know. Tell me.
I don't remember. I have no
short-term memory. It's not amnesia.
- Oh, you're the memory guy.
- How Do you know about me?
My boyfriend told me about you.
- Yeah? Who's your boyfriend?
- Jimmy Grants. Do you know him?
No.
Well, he knows you.
He told me about you.
He said you were staying
at the Discount.
In fact, a cop came by here
earlier looking for you.
Said he was looking for a guy
who can't remember anything,
wouldn't know how he got here...
or what he'd done.
Said I get a lot of guys
around here like that.
Well, you know, chronic alcoholism is
one cause of short-term memory loss.
- are you Teddy?
- No. My name is Leonard.
- Did Teddy send you?
- I don't know.
- What's happened to Jimmy?
- I don't know that either.
- Sorry.
- You don't remember anything?
You don't remember where
you've been or what you've just done.
No. I can't make new memories.
Everything just fades.
- Then why did you come here?
- I found this in my pocket.
Your pocket.
[Clearing Throat]
Bar bet.
Care to contribute?
- No, thanks.
- It's for a lot of money.
Come on. Proceeds are
going to charity. Help me out.
[Hawking]
Thank you.
- On the house.
- Thanks.
[Man Laughing]
It's completely fucked
because nobody believes you.
It's amazing what
a little brain damage
will do for your credibility.
I guess it's some kind of poetic
justice for not believing Sammy.
You know the truth
about my condition, officer?
You don't know anything.
You feel angry,
you don't know why.
You feel guilty,
you have no idea why.
You could do anything and not have
the faintest idea ten minutes later.
Like Sammy. I could have
done something like Sammy.
I didn't tell you-- what happened
to Sammy and his wife?
Well, she came
to see me at my office.
I thought she was just
trying to catch me off guard,
so I didn't tell her
what I really thought, but
I never said that he was faking,
just that his condition
was mental, not physical.
I found out later that she went home
and gave Sammy his final exam.
Sammy?
It's time for my shot.
She knew beyond a doubt
that he loved her.
So she found a way
to test him.
[Sighs]
Sam my.
I t's ti me for my shot.
H m m.
- She really thought
she'd call his bluff,.
- There you go.
Or she just didn't wanna
live with the things
she put him through.
Sammy.
I t's time for my shot.
I t won't hurt.
She went into a coma
and never recovered.
- Sammy couldn't understand
or explain what happened.
- Oh!
He's been in a home ever since.
He doesn't even know
that his wife's dead.
I was wrong about Sammy,
and I was wrong about his wife.
She wasn't interested in the money.
She just needed
to understand his problem.
His brain didn't respond to
conditioning. But he wasn't a con man.
And when she looked into his eyes, she
thought he could be the same person.
when I looked into his eyes,
I thought I saw recognition.
Now I know. You fake it.
I f you're supposed to recognize
somebody, you just pretend to.
You bluff, it to get a pat
on the head from the doctors.
You bluff, it
to seem less ofa freak.
What drug dealer?
[Tires Screeching]
- Hey, Lenny, how you doing?
- It's private back here.
- It's okay. We know
each other. Right, kid?
- How did you know I was here?
Oh, the Jag is out front.
You should have put it around back.
what are you still doing here? There's
plenty of tattoo parlors up north.
I just wanted to get something down
before it slipped my mind.
- Then give me the keys.
I'll move it for you.
- It'll be all right for a minute.
- Wait out there.
- Oh, for Christ--
Look, give me a minute.
I gotta get something for you.
Fact six.
Car license SG137IU.
Look. Wait a minute, will ya?
- All right, we gotta
get you out of here.
- Why?
Aw, man. Come on, Leonard.
How many times I gotta tell you?
- It's not safe for you
to hang around here anymore.
- Why not?
Because that cop's looking for you.
Now, I gotta get you
a new identity, some new clothes.
A different car would do for now.
So put these on.
Whoa, whoa.
What cop?
He's a bad cop. He's the one who
checked you into the Discount Inn.
He's been calling you for days,
telling you shit, slipping
envelopes under your door.
- How Do you know this?
- He told me. He thinks it's funny.
- He's been laughing at you.
- You're full of shit.
I'm not. He knows you're no good on
the phone, so he's been calling you up.
Sometimes you don't
answer the phone,
so he slips shit
under your door to scare you
into answering the phone again,
giving you a line of crap about John G.
being some local drug dealer.
- Jimmy Grants.
- Who's Jimmy Grants?
Leonard,
Jimmy's the drug dealer.
The cop wants to know
how his operation's run.
He's got some score in mind.
Somehow you're involved.
Uh-huh.
How Do you know him?
I'm a snitch.
He's a cop from out of town.
The local boys put us together.
if he knew I was helping you,
he'd fucking kill me.
So take these clothes, put them on
and get the fuck out of here.
Come on, Leonard.
Just go.
You are full of shit.
[Thinking]
"Come by after. Natalie."
"Ferdy's Bar."
- [Knocking On Window]
- Hey, Jimmy.
I'm sorry. I, uh, thought
you were somebody else.
Sorry.
That's okay.
So this Jimmy Grants deals drugs out
of the bar where his girlfriend works?
But he's not gonna bring her along.
He'll come by himself, right?
I always figured
the drugs angle would be
the best way to get him.
No, officer.
I'm as ready as I'll ever be.
You're in the lobby?
What Do you look like?
I'll be right there.
Lenny.
Officer Gammell.
Yeah. Come on.
- Hey, smile.
- Oh, don't-- Not here. Over here.
- Now, is it Officer
or Lieutenant Gammell?
- You know what?
Don't write Gammell, just Teddy.
- Why?
- I'm undercover.
This is the directions
where he's going.
- My number's on the bottom
If you need me.
- You're not coming?
No. It wouldn't be appropriate.
Nice picture. I look thin.
Hey, Lenny.
Make him beg.
[Vehicle Approaching]
[Man]
Teddy!
Hey, Teddy!
Jimmy.
What the fuck
are you doing here?
- You J immy Grants?
- Expecting any otherJ immys
out here, Memory Man?
- Do you remember me?
- Yeah, I remember you.
where the fuck's
Teddy? well?
Mother fuck--
What the fuck are you doing?
- Strip.
- You're making a big
fucking mistake, pal.
Strip!
- My associates are not the kind
of people you wanna piss off.
- Don't say anything else.
- I knew I couldn't trust that fuck!
- Take it off.
- Your pants too.
- Why?
I don't wanna
get blood on them.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait, wait, wait.
Did he tell you what I was bringing?
- Take your fuckin' pants off!
- I've got two hundred grand
stashed in the car!
- Just take it!
- You think you can
bargain with me?
- Just take the money and walk away!
- I don't want your money!
Then what?
- what Do you want from me?
- I want my fuckin' life back!
Sammy.
[Thinking] He said "Sammy."
How does he know about Sammy?
Oh, fuck.
[Thinking]
What have I done?
Hey, mister, I need help.
There's a guy in here, he's hurt bad.
- We gotta get him to a doctor.
- All right.
I don't know
what happened.
- I've got this memory thing.
Do I know you?
- No. Don't worry. I'm a cop.
- Is he still breathing?
- I don't know. Maybe.
What the hell were you guys
doing down here?
Well, I don't remember.
I have this condition.
well, I hope it's not as serious
as his, 'cause this guy's dead.
Ouch! Lenny!
That shit kills!
- So you remember me now, huh?
- You are a fuckin' cop.
Yeah. And I'm the guy
that helped you find him.
Get up. Get up.
Lenny, you got the wrong idea.
Who is that? He knew me.
Of course he did. He raped your wife.
He fucked up your brain.
Bullshit.
He's not the guy.
His name is James F. Grants.
John G. Check your tattoos.
- What was he bringing
the two hundred grand for?
- What?
- What was it for?
- A load of amphetamines
I told him I had.
- Is this a drug deal?
- No. Yeah, that and your thing.
Look, Leonard,
Jimmy's your guy.
- I just figured we'd make
a few dollars on the side.
- How did he know me?
The Discount Inn.
He dealt out of there.
The guy at the front desk let him know
if anybody came snooping around.
He called Jimmy the minute he saw you
taking a picture of the dump.
- You're fucking using me.
- No! You get half!
He knew about Sammy! Why would
I tell him about fuckin' Sammy?
You tell everybody about Sammy,
everybody who'll listen.
"Remember Sammy Jankis?"
Great story. It gets better
every time you tell it.
So you lie to yourself
to be happy.
There's nothing wrong with that.
We all do it.
Who cares if there's a few little
details you'd rather not remember?
- What the fuck are you talking about?
- I don't know.
Your wife's
surviving the assault.
Her not believing your condition.
The torment and pain and anguish...
tearing her up inside.
The insulin.
That's Sammy, not me.
I told you about Sammy.
Yeah, right. like you tell
yourself over and over again.
Conditioning yourself
to remember.
- Learning through repetition.
- Sammy let his wife kill herself.
- Sammy ended up in an institution.
- Sammy was a con man, a faker.
I never said
that Sammy was faking.
You exposed him
for what he was-- a fraud.
But I was wrong.
That's the whole point.
- See, Sammy's wife came to me.
- Sammy didn't have a wife.
It was your wife
who had diabetes.
Ouch.
My wife wasn't diabetic.
You sure?
- Ouch. Cut it out.
- She wasn't diabetic.
You think I don't know my own wife?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Well, I guess I can only make you
remember the things you wanna be true.
- Like old Jimmy down there.
- He's not the right guy.
He was to you.
Come on. You got your revenge.
Enjoy it while you still remember.
what difference does it make
whether he was your guy or not?
- I t makes al I the difference.
- Why? You're never gonna know.
- Yes, I will. I will.
- No, you won't.
- Somehow I'll know.
- You won't remember!
- When it's done, I will know.
It'll be different.
Well, I thought so too. In fact,
I was sure ofit, but you didn't!
That's right.
The real John G.
I helped you find him over
a year ago. He's already dead.
- Don't lie to me anymore.
- Look, Lenny.
I was the cop assigned
to your wife's case. I believed you.
I thought you deserved
a chance for revenge.
I'm the one that helped you
find the other guy in your
bathroom that night,
the guy that cracked your skull
and fucked your wife.
We found hi m.
You killed him.
But you didn't remember.
So I helped you start looking again,
looking for the guy
you already killed.
Oh, yeah. So who was he?
Just some guy. I mean,
does it even matter who?
No reason, Lenny. No conspiracy.
Just bad fucking luck.
Couple of junkies too strung out
to realize your wife didn't live alone.
But when you killed him, I was
so convinced that you'd remember.
But it didn't stick.
Like nothing ever sticks.
Like this won't stick.
I took that picture...
just when you did it.
Look how happy you are.
I wanted to see
that face again.
- Oh, gee, thanks.
- Fuck you.
I gave you a reason to live, and
you were more than happy to help.
You don't want the truth.
You make up your own truth.
Like your police file.
It was complete when I gave it to you.
Who took out the 12 pages?
- You, probably.
- No, it wasn't me. See, it was you.
- Why would I do that?
- To create a puzzle
you could never solve.
Do you know how many--
how many towns?
How many John G's
or James G's?
I mean, shit, Lenny,
I'm a fucking John G.
- Your name is Teddy.
- My mother calls me Teddy.
My name's
John Edward Gammell.
Cheerup.
There's plenty of John G's
for us to find.
All you do is moan.
I'm the one that has to live
with what you've done.
I'm the one that put it
all together.
You, you wander around, you're playing
detective. You live in a dream, kid.
A dead wife to pine for.
A sense of purpose to your life.
A romantic quest that
you wouldn't end even if
I wasn't in the picture.
- I should kill you.
- Quit it. Lenny, come on.
You're not a killer.
That's why you're so good at it.
Come on. What are you doing?
You know what time it is?
It's beer o'clock.
I'm buying.
Fuck.
[Thinking]
I'm not a killer.
I'm just someone who wanted
to make things right.
Can I just let myself forget
what you've told me?
what you made me do?
You think I just want
another puzzle to solve?
Another John G. to look for?
You're a John G.
So you can be my John G.
Do I lie to myself to be happy?
In your case, Teddy,
yes, I will.
Hey! Hey, that's not your car!
- It is now.
- Jesus Christ, you can't take it!
- Why not?
- Because the guy
you just killed owns it!
Somebody'll recognize it!
You know, I think I'd rather be
mistaken for a dead guy than a killer.
I might hang on
to this for a while.
- Lenny. Look, don't--
- Will you help me find the keys?
Help me find my keys.
Lenny!
[Thinking] I have to believe
in a world outside my own mind.
I have to believe that
my actions still have meaning,
even if I can't remember them.
I have to believe
that when my eyes are closed,
the world's still here.
Do I believe
the world's still here?
Is it still out there?
Yeah.
We all need mirrors
to remind ourselves who we are.
I'm no different.
Now, where was I?
# we layin each other's arms? #
# But the room
is just an empty space #
# I guess we lived it out #
# Something in the air #
# we smile too fast then can't
think ofa thing to say #
# Lived with the best times #
# Left with the worst #
# I've danced with you
too long #
# Nothing left to save #
# There's something
in the air #
# Something in my eye #
# I've danced with you
too long, yeah #
# Something in the air #
# Something in my eye #
# Abracadoo #
# I lose you #
# we can't avoid the clash #
# The big mistake #
# Now we're gonna pay and pay #
# I guess you know I never
wanted anyone more than you #
# Lived all our best times #
# Left with the worst #
# I've danced with you
too long #
# Say what you will #
# But there's something
in the air #
# Something in my eye #
# I've danced with you
too long #
# There's something
I have to say #
in the air #
# Danced with you too long? #