Last delivery's finally here.
Watch yourself!
X marks the spot.
Christophe here.
- What up?
- Delivery confirmed.
- We're in position.
- Good luck.
We got one shot of this.
If anybody fucked up and those stones
aren't there, it ain't my problem.
- The stones are there.
- Not for long. Later.
I got you.
Thank you.
- I'm here for the reception.
- Name, please?
Angie Rawlins.
You can go on up.
Front elevator to the mezzanine.
Thanks.
Where are the stones?
Who the fuck are you?
Who's getting them for you?
Fuck off!
I want a name and a number.
Okay.
- Okay, I'll tell you.
- I know.
I hate these things.
Don't you hate these things?
Just doing my job.
Then again, you never know
who you're gonna meet, right?
I bet you're a lot more fun
than any of those boring people upstairs.
Really, ma'am, I have a job to do.
Right, well, I suppose I should
go see what they're selling.
Tommy.
Change of plans, he's gay. You're up.
- No way.
- Yes, way.
Come on, man!
- All right, Tommy, your turn.
- Hell, no!
This is not a conversation.
Do it! And make it good.
Shit.
Keycard.
So why don't you hold onto my purse.
I shouldn't be too long.
Aloha.
Hi.
I hope you don't take
offense to this but...
...I have such a weakness
for a man in uniform.
- That's ok.
- Uniforms are my thing.
I mean, every time I see a sailor,
all I can think about is seafood.
I'm not actually supposed
to be talking on duty.
Who's talking?
Baby, this is flirting.
Unless you're one of those big handsome
men letting it all go to waste on a woman.
The world is full of fools.
Yahtzee!
- What's it looking like?
- About a six-second rotation.
Tommy.
But you can call me Rachel.
Douglas.
I just hope I'm not too...
...pretty for you.
- I'm hooked up.
- That bitch.
I like sunsets, puppy dogs...
I'm big in the pants.
I can almost tie it in a knot.
Let's get the table.
I guess, one day I'll have to come in here and
do a little shoplifting and let you catch me.
Resist arrest just so you can
wrestle me down and...
...cuff me.
I can be pretty rough.
Don't get me excited now.
Faith.
Holy shit!
Earthquake.
But I bet you can hit a 10
on the Richter scale anytime, Douglas.
Let's do it.
All right. Y'all know what to do.
Let's get it on.
- 911, what's your emergency?
- I want to report a robbery in progress.
Robbery in progress. What's the location?
Man, I love colored stones.
This one blue diamond
is at least $2.5 million dollars.
Oh, yeah? So whose stuff we stealing?
- Drug dealers, money launderers...
- Works for me.
This...
This I can use.
T.
Check this out.
This is what we came for.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Jackpot. The rest is ours.
Yeah.
Your employer betrayed you.
The police are on the way.
- Leave the stones.
- Who is this?
You know the ones I mean.
I'm not gonna be able to do that.
Wrap them up.
Let's go, boys.
Better go move my car.
Five-O at the door, gotta go.
- Move now!
- Time to bounce. Leave this shit.
- Is this your car?
- Yeah, it's my car, man!
- Get it out of here!
- Move your shit...
- I'll move that, you move this.
- All right.
Let's go. Out of here, right now.
They stopped the trains.
We don't have a lot of time.
Daria comes with me.
I can't tell you how to get there,
but you know where to be.
- Faith.
It's clear.
Hold it.
All clear.
Okay.
Nice.
- Train is secure.
- Ok, get this train out of here.
You got it.
The stones?
Watch out!
The bag!
Fuck.
Enjoying California?
Hope we're not here long.
I hate sunshine.
We may have a problem.
The stones?
The Exchange was just robbed.
Let's hope that was part of the plan.
Who's in charge?
Who wants to know?
Follow me.
Vanessa. What are you still doing up?
- Just a little longer?
Come on, sweetheart, you have school tomorrow.
Come on. Time for bed.
- Getting heavy!
- No, I'm not.
Wait a minute.
There's something behind your ear.
Oh please. That is so lame.
- What you mean?
- It's in your hand.
This hand? Or this hand?
Watch.
- How'd you do that?
- Magic.
- Is it for me?
- Of course it's for you.
A diamond for my princess.
It's beautiful.
- So are you.
- I love you, Daddy.
I love you too.
Let's say our prayers.
Angels east, angels west,
north and south, just do your best...
...to guard her and watch her
while she rests.
- Amen.
Give me some love.
Can I have another one?
Yeah, you can have another one.
Vanessa's in the bed now.
- She'll be asleep for the rest of the night. Ok?
- She won't listen to me lately. Only you.
I'll talk to her in the morning.
Go to sleep anytime. Ok?
- I'm watching TV if you need me.
- All right. Thank you.
Player, what the hell happened?
Should we be considering a long vacation in a
warm foreign climate where they have no extradition?
The cat that called was only interested
in the black stones.
- Christophe sold us out.
- Or something.
- Oh, God, you made it.
- By the skin of my black ass.
Man, some Chinese dude kicked my ass
all around that goddamn train track.
Asshole busted my earpiece too.
- And the worst part, he snagged the loot.
- Shit!
So you know, maybe it's time to rethink
this no-gun policy shit.
A little ass-whupping ain't shit.
At least you didn't have to play
all foxy with the rent-a-cop! All right?
- This all we got.
- So, what do we do now?
- Wait to hear from me.
- So where are you going?
I'm going to get some answers.
- Hold up, dog. I got your back.
- I got this one.
But if I need you, I'll call you.
- All right.
- All right?
Be careful.
So this is Mr. Christophe.
Apparently we're not his first visitors today.
Please, Senor Ling, have mercy.
Whatever you're going to say,
make it the truth.
You may not have another opportunity.
I'll tell you what you wanna know.
Bang!
You like it?
It's all right.
You want it? I'll make you
a deal on it, ammo included.
It's got reactive armor, Browning
.50-caliber, 7.62 M-60 machine gun.
And that cannon there, that's 90 mm, man.
It's good to get around the bad areas of town.
Keeps neighborhood kids in line.
- I'll pass.
- All right. How about this?
- A Marine Corps Assault Hovercraft?
- Actually, I'm here on other business.
Hey, Arch! We're out of room
in the storage.
All right, listen, put them in my office
and be careful with them, they're expensive.
Well, not expensive to me.
Hey, listen, you weren't by any chance
downtown today, were you, Tony?
Not at all.
I didn't think so.
- Ever see a black diamond?
- I've seen a white diamond, pink...
...yellow, blue ones. I've seen Neil Diamond.
Awesome in concert.
He's in town in two weeks...
Never seen a black diamond.
Not like this.
- Wow. You got me.
- Find out what they're worth.
- Is there a timetable on this?
- Yesterday.
- That's what I figured.
- I'll be back.
Gonna return a favor to a friend.
Looks dead to me.
- Guess you got to him first.
- Not me, not my style.
You're the one that called me.
The same one that bumped into Miles.
Who the fuck are you?
- My name is Su.
- All right, Su, I'm Sally.
- I want the black stones.
- Make me an offer.
- You can walk out of here alive.
- No deal.
Leave a message.
Mr. Fait, I know you're there.
Pick up the phone.
We need to talk, now.
Who the fuck is this?
The man for whom Christophe arranged
to have the black stones...
...brought into the country
and deposited at the Jewelry Exchange.
The man who wants them back.
- Now.
- All right, well, how much?
Maybe you didn't understand me.
The stones are already mine.
Yo, check this out?
I got them, I'm selling them,
put the money on the wood!
I don't have time for this.
That's your last offer?
I can be a very dangerous man, Mr. Fait.
I don't understand this shit.
Man, do I look like the Salvation Army?
I bust my ass all night and got nothing
to show for it. You know what, dog?
It don't even matter who the fuck you are.
I ain't got nothing for you.
Shit!
Give us the stones.
How many times I got to tell you people?
I'm a businessman.
Make me a fucking offer!
Here's your offer.
That shit ain't gonna work, homes,
because I don't have the stones!
Then you gotta tell us where they are.
Come on!
The car!
What is it with these fucking stones?
- Yeah.
- It's Archie.
Bad news. We got a problem.
I put word out on the street
to get some info on the stones.
Next thing I know,
the Wu-Tang Clan shows up here.
Three important elements here.
One, I'm outmanned...
...two, they're heavily armed,
and three, they're about to pound me.
- I can't watch anymore. I got a few licks in...
- Let's see the rest.
Did you see my new DVD players?
All right! Okay! Okay! Okay!
- Give me that!
- I forgot I had them. Sorry!
I could've resisted more. But they could've
beat me into a coma or killed me.
How could I tell Tony where the stones
are if I'm dead or on life support?
Right? So I threw in the towel,
reluctantly, for your sake.
- Okay, so you saved yourself to tell me something.
- Right
- So tell me.
- What?
- Who was it?
- I don't know.
- What did they say?
- Well, they said:
"Give me the stones,
you fat cracker motherfucker."
- You know. That sort of thing.
- That's it?
That's pretty bad.
Cracker is... you know, is kind of racist.
Thanks for keeping yourself alive
long enough to tell me nothing!
- Did you call the police?
- Did I call the police?
Look around here, are you crazy?
Only question now is,
who's behind this jack move?
I don't know, but they got some great guns
I can't even get. U.S. Special Forces only.
- Chambers.
- Jump Chambers?
I hope not.
Hey, who's Jump Chambers?
This guy's in on everything
that goes down in this town.
The only one I know that can get those
type of weapons. And he has a fucking army.
You're on your own,
I don't need the headache.
And since I'm totally fucked, who are you?
Yeah, you got an ID?
Buddy? Picture, preferably?
Yeah, all right.
- This means nothing to me.
- Let me see it.
It's Taiwan, Central Security Bureau.
- Taiwanese Intelligence.
- Read Chinese?
No, but I know "cop"
in every language.
What are you?
Some kind of kung fu James Bond?
- The stones belong to Taiwan.
- They belong to Chambers now.
- I'm starting to hate this fucking phone.
- I'll get you a new one.
- Yeah.
- I hope you've reconsidered.
Oh, it's bad-ass! What's up, homes?
You've made this difficult, Mr. Fait.
Let me make it easy.
I can't wait to hear this.
Daddy, Daddy, Daddy!
She's very pretty in her pink pajamas,
aren't you, Vanessa?
- Son of a...
- I want my stones, Mr. Fait.
Let me talk to the Chinese gentleman,
who is with you.
Don't you fucking touch her!
The Chinese gentleman, please.
He has my daughter.
He wants to talk to you.
Jesus, Tony.
What happened? What did you just do?
I said I have the stones,
and I won't negotiate for your daughter.
- What?
- That's stupid.
It will confuse him,
buy us time, keep her alive.
What the hell are you talking about?
This motherfucker has my baby!
Look, I know him.
I want the stones, you want your daughter.
We can help each other.
So I'm stuck with you.
Get in.
We gotta see Chambers.
Find a place to put her.
My daddy's gonna come and kick your butts!
Su says he has the stones.
But why cut me off?
Why not negotiate for the girl?
Doesn't make any sense.
Buyers fly in tomorrow.
Should we stop them?
We'll never regain their confidence.
We need information.
Find the right people, pay whatever it costs.
Something's not right.
Something's happening with the stones.
What about the girl?
We'll need her. She stays alive...
...for now.
Yeah, I'm on my way to see Chambers now.
No, I don't have a choice.
Get in touch with his people,
let him know I need to see him.
I'll call you back.
I'm sorry about your daughter.
- How old is she?
- Mind your business.
She's 8. She'll be 9 in September.
Mine is 15.
- Boyfriends?
- Never. I'd kill them.
You wish.
- About time you PMD.
- PMD?
Yeah, put me down.
What's this all about?
- The stones are not what you think they are.
- No shit.
- What about this guy who has Vanessa?
- He's exactly what you think he is.
A thief and a killer.
Great.
Fucking great.
I want my daddy!
Keys.
Where'd you get this piece of shit?
Let's just say Grandma and Grandpa have
a long walk back from the campground.
- You sure you cleaned it out?
- Oh, it's clean, all right.
- Shut up!
- You shut up!
Go to sleep!
Angels east, angels west...
...north and south, just do your best...
...to guard her and watch her
while she rests.
Amen.
Who rang that bell?
Here are your visitors, Mr. Chambers.
And the morning mail.
Hey, yo, Vogel.
My DVD's broke.
Get you a new one straight away,
Mr. Chambers.
Well, well, well. Tony Fait.
Come all this way to visit his
old pal Jump. Who's the gook?
Chinese guy.
Hey.
No shoes in my crib, man.
- How you doing, Jump?
- Don't waste my fucking time, nigga.
- Look, I got a problem.
- How's Daria?
- Good.
- Yeah, she always was good.
From the moment I saw her to the
moment you took her away from me.
- Problem?
- The black stones.
That bitch brought in too.
I made a lot of money with her,
but that's all stopped now. You stopped that.
You decided it was okay
to put an end to that.
- Black stones, what?
- I need them back.
You know, the only smart thing you did
was not pimping her yourself.
See, because then I'd have been real
heated and you'd have been real dead.
But you don't pimp, right?
You're just a thief in the night,
stealing shit that don't belong to you.
Hey.
- What? He don't talk?
- I don't speak Korean.
Yeah, well, I do.
Bought me a little Korean
spot right downtown.
Bringing in the soul brothers
24-7, 365.
Black man gouging Koreans.
Ain't that a switch, Chick?
Them motherfuckers got faces like walls,
but they love to drink and look at naked girls.
Place ain't no shitbox.
You should see my office.
Got that shit decked out
like a kabuki love palace.
You know what that is, right?
Why don't you roll by sometime?
Check out the poon.
My little girl is mixed up in this.
If I don't get those stones back,
she's dead.
What do you want, man? I mean...
- I'm begging.
- You know, I was thinking.
That was a big heist. Risky heist.
And I'm wondering, what would make a man go
through that kind of trouble, take that kind of heat?
Gotta be something good.
Something valuable.
Jump...
...it's my little girl.
Make another one.
You mother...
Drama.
I see the slope's no dope.
Got a lot of offspring running
around, brother.
Big score is once in a lifetime.
- Yo, let me at him.
- Go ahead. Shit.
Say hey to Daria for me.
Don't forget your fucking shoes.
Pussy.
I used to really look up to that guy.
Used to want to be just like him.
- In Taiwan, I can make him talk.
- Yeah, well, this ain't Taiwan.
Only thing we can do now is try to find
out where the stones are and get them.
- You make it sound easy.
- It won't be.
- What?
- They're at his club.
How do you know?
I know. I can just feel it.
It's never happened to you?
No.
- Thought you Chinese people were all mystical.
- We like to gamble. Not guess.
It's no guess, but I could be wrong.
I'll hit the club, you go see Archie.
Why?
- He has to remember something.
- What if he can't?
Pretend it's Taiwan.
Make him remember.
Hey. Get away from here.
What are you doing?
Relax. All right? I'm just seeing if I can
help with something.
Well, you can't. It's very delicate
equipment, so just stay away.
All right? Stay away from the truck.
- What?
- Stay away from my fucking truck!
Okay, stop it.
Backing away.
Someone give the geek his Ritalin.
At least he's doing his job...
...which is more than I can say
for some people. Tape her up and gag her.
I want my daddy! I want my daddy!
- I want my daddy!
- Let go of me!
- Shut up!
- I want my daddy!
- Waste of time.
I can think of a better way
of shutting you up.
Yes!
Shit! She's got the key!
- Precious Daria.
- What's up, Odion?
Long time, no see.
- So, what brings you around here?
- Sometimes you need to see old friends.
- What? You got trouble?
- With a capital T.
Tony Fait? Thought you two
were tight. Bonnie and Clyde.
Yeah, it used to be that way.
Not taking care of me these days.
Kid's all he cares about.
It's a shame, huh?
- So, what you want me to do?
- I don't know.
Probably nothing you can do.
I just thought...
...you know.
No, this is crazy. I don't even know what I was
thinking. I shouldn't be in here. Sorry.
No, hold up, hold up. Girls.
- Give us a minute. Champagne?
- Yes.
I got it.
- So, you looking for a job?
- I need something.
How about you work here?
How would Jump feel about me
coming back and all?
You let me worry about Jump Chambers.
In the meantime...
...how about we go to my office
and we talk about this a little bit more?
It's not exactly boxing matches,
it's a lot more dangerous.
No gloves or nothing, no rules, period.
It's huge money. It's very illegal.
They hold it during the day to fool cops.
The man you remember,
how do you know he'll be here?
I don't, but this is Chambers' operation,
so it's a damn good place to start.
Here we are.
- This is a private club. You can't come in here.
- It's me, Archie.
- Everybody likes me here.
- Hey, it's that asshole Archie again.
How can you recognize him?
Well, I didn't see his face,
but they all kind of look the same.
Of course so do you guys.
No offense. But I will remember
that pinky ring because it was awesome.
He's got, like, a 10-carat, round cut,
square setting, good color and clarity.
I remember thinking about the damage
it'd do to my face if he hit me with it.
I gotta make sure Mr. Pinky Ring doesn't
recognize me, so I got a disguise.
- How do we get in?
- Leave it to me. I'll take care of it.
Hey, buddy. How you doing?
How's that armor-plated Lincoln I sold you?
- Cops stopped me.
- They do that sometimes.
- Car was fucking hot, Archie.
- Hey.
I didn't steal it, but stop by the shop
tomorrow. I'll make it right.
- You know the rules. No guests.
- He's not.
He's a fighter. An unofficial entry.
- Him? Is he any good?
- Is he...?
He'll kick all those chumps' asses!
He'll go Chinese on them!
Teeth will fly.
Blood will splatter!
It'll be awesome! Step aside.
No way, Archie. No more favors.
What? You've got to be shitting me.
Somebody's getting a letter from
the Better Business Bureau. All right
Excuse us.
You're number 12.
Go get your ass kicked.
I didn't come here to fight.
You don't have to fight,
I just said that to get us in.
Come on!
Get up! Oh, yeah.
Get up!
Yeah! Yeah!
Tear his eye out!
- On a good day, over a million bucks will...
- Just find the ring.
- All right. Okay.
- Knock him out.
- You know...
- Bullshit.
...this could take a little while.
All right, come on. Let's go.
Sit down.
Why don't you put on some music?
Slower.
Just relax.
And watch.
This looks good.
Set it up, tie it at the bottom.
- Tommy, go.
- Here come the bug man.
Excuse me.
Oh hey, what's going on, player?
- Yo, what the hell are you doing?
- Oh, pest control, player.
- Don't tell me you didn't get the notice.
- What notice?
See!? That's what burn my ass right to the bone, man.
A brother just trying to make a living...
You know what?
That's beside the point.
If you had gotten your notice,
you'd realize that the city has this new ordinance...
...saying I gotta spray every businesses
that caters to foreigners.
How come?