Presented by Cinema Service
in association with
Choong Mu-Ro Fund
Produced by Fun & Happiness Film
People are so naive.
Training in the mountains?
All those instructors
chasing kids' pocket money,
saying they did mountain training.
It's all just crap.
Right.
Remember in '88 when I
went to Mt. Gyeryong?
You get up five or six
in the morning.
Let's see, what for breakfast?
Preparing and eating takes 2 hours.
And then maybe
train for 1-2 hours.
And then it's lunch time.
So go down to the village
to get some lunch.
That's another 3 hours.
So, eat lunch and meditate.
Then you start nodding off.
Next thing you know it's dinner.
So you got 3 hours of
training max in a day.
So where's the only place
to get proper training?
The temple.
Yeah, shave off your head and
your house becomes a temple!
Does all that training give
you the right to eat meat?
Look here, how can you do
martial arts without nutrition?
You need strength.
What exactly do you do
with all that strength?
I can't believe
this asinine nonsense!
Kids these days don't even
know the meaning of tao.
You guys know how
serious our situation is?
Don't be so serious,
we gotta make a living.
Let's use our brain
to think, for once!
Forget Maruchi (supreme master),
no one wants to learn the tao.
Lady Banya, making
a living is one thing,
Telephone fortune-telling
service is another!
Ooh, listen to him! You know how
much money 1-700 service makes?
1-700 is a sign of the times.
You don't know crap.
Besides, how else would you
pay rent for Mu-un Academy?
Yeah, Banya's right.
We gotta go with
the flow, you know?
Academy, my ass!
We ain't got no
kids to teach!
Well, I've been saying we
should pull some public stunt...
Like maybe appearing
on a TV show.
I'm tired of staring at
the wallpaper when I levitate.
I levitate only to change the light bulb.
RYOO Seung-bum YUN Soy
AHN Sung-ki JUNG Doo-hong
Executive Producer KANG Woo-suk
Producer KIM Mi-hee
Director RYOO Seung-wan
ARAHAN
Urban Martial Arts Action
One dollar, please.
What the heck?
Oh, sorry.
Eui-jin, snap out of it, will you?
Uh, can I go to the restroom?
Are you running off again?
What the hell is he doing?
Dumbass.
Excuse me.
What?
You ran a red light, sir.
So what?
Your license, please.
Huh?
Look, do you know who this is?
I don't recall.
You dumbass...
He's the congressman
of this district.
Oh, how are you, sir?
But he's not the one
who ran the light, is he?
You're the driver,
so give me your license.
Boy, which
station do you work at?
Why do you need to know that?
If you don't want a ticket,
then don't run red lights.
My purse! My purse!
Hold it! Stay right here,
I'll be back in a minute.
Hey!
Hey mister,
watch where you drive!
What's up with
Manager Lee these days?
Stop right there!
Gosh, we're late!
What the hell?
Hey!
Do I have to keep running
around after punks like you?
What the heck is your problem?
Watch it!
Hand over the purse, kiddo.
And who are you?
Stop fooling around!
Missed again...
Hey, where are you going?
Get back here!
Wait.
Where are you going, huh? Hey! Hey!
Where are you going?
I think it's this meridian point...
Aren't you going in too deep?
Let me concentrate!
If we don't do this right,
it could make him impotent.
The last one...
in the Main Meridian Point...
Great Tao!
He opened all the
meridian points himself!
My, this kid has
extraordinary chi.
Look at him!
What's all the fuss about?
Uh, Eui-jin.
What's wrong with him?
Oh, we unblocked
the flow of his chi.
Tell him to shut up.
Hey, where'd you find that kid?
Everybody calm down!
Okay, okay.
Don't move, mister! I'm a cop!
- Don't move!
- I'm a cop! I said...
Calm down.
Man, this kid is cute.
Hey, boy!
He's got a cute dong, too.
- Damn...
- Aunt!
Stop! I'm the police!
POLICE!
You've done it!
- Wait a minute.
- Damn, this sucks.
- It still works.
- Which point did you hit?
It may be hard to believe, but the
world has secret currents of chi.
We awaken this chi and guide
people toward righteousness.
So to speak.
So you gentlemen...
and this madam here,
Are called the Seven Masters, right?
But there are only five of you.
With only five, you should be...
Power Rangers?
Right, Power Rangers or...
Five Lucky Stars?
Yes, Five Lucky Stars!
Wouldn't that be
more appropriate?
It's already been 20 years...
...since Baek-pung left us.
In an era when the powerful
exploited the powerless,
Baek-pung gathered up all his chi
to block the force of evil...
...but he inhaled
too much tear gas...
- And as for the seventh...
- Um...
I think you may
have misunderstood...
Don't call me madam,
I'm still a virgin.
Shut your mouth...
Then, are all of you here...
...like, tao masters?
You know, like you see on TV?
Sure!
I'm having a hard time
believing this,
so could you show me some stuff?
Like, can you levitate?
Can you walk on walls?
Can you do a Palm Blast?
Dammit!
No Palm Blasts in
the house, I said!
Hold on!
But I got to work!
What you saw right now,
is only the beginning.
Why are you afraid of
your own ability?
What ability?
What are you talking about?
Please leave me alone.
You have the most powerful chi
of all the young men I have met.
The wounds you sustained today
would've felled ordinary people.
All right, fine.
If that's true,
I should be able to do a Palm Blast.
And walk on walls, like this?
And levitate, isn't that right?
Cripes, that was weird.
Pretty spooky stuff.
Ah, what a nice night!
It's downhill,
so I might as well run.
What a strange guy.
But did you see him levitate?
Sometimes chi just comes out
by itself after you unblock it.
Or was it his chi?
Actually, I did a
Palm Blast back there.
Why'd you shoot
at the window?
It's broken again!
I shot at the wall.
"Daily Report"
Hey, you!
You can't catch thieves,
but you ticket the congressman?
You think we're some kind
of citizens' group?
Yes!
Get him out of my sight. Go!
Courtesy!
Hey, does he really
plan on being a cop?
Nobody saw it.
Who will believe you were
knocked out for a full day?
- Oh, about that...
- Look here.
It's important to run,
but even more important,
is to run when people
are watching.
- But yesterday...
- I repeat.
- Hey, quiet.
- Fighting is reported at Jaru Karaoke.
Officers in the area,
report immediately.
If you don't know, I can show you.
Or you can bring your boss here.
Hey!
Look who's here!
It's Sheriff Choi.
Oh, Mr. Gang!
I was wondering who
was causing trouble again.
Why are you doing this to me?
Where have you been these days?
I've been busy too.
You think I play around all day?
And if something's up,
just call me directly.
Let's avoid the reports, okay?
- Sorry about that.
- Officer Choi...
Should we start our inspection?
No, no. Don't bother.
So Mr. Gang, are things
just about sorted out?
Yeah, sure.
And come visit our club
with your boys sometime.
You must have time for a drink?
Ah... well, I...
Anyway, I'll leave you in charge.
And Mr. Gang...
- Keep it down next time, ok?
- Okay, okay.
- See you later.
- Okay.
- Bye.
But Officer Choi,
how can we just leave?
Hey, if we stir things up here,
it'll just cause more trouble.
Come on.
Please show me your ID.
What the hell?
I said show me your ID.
Hey, what's with this guy?
You wanna get pounded?
Wait a second, Mr. Gang!
This guy here, he's new...
- I'm really disappointed in you.
- But he...
How are you training these kids?
What's going on here?
These dumb thugs scare you?
Why are you groveling?
What was that?
- Wait, let me talk to him.
- Get over here!
Mr. Gang!
What did you say now?
Wait a second.
"Why are you groveling?"
Before that!
"Do they scare you?"
- Before that!
- Wait, let me...
Dumb thugs!
I can't believe this.
- What are you...
- You bastard.
On your knees!
Hey, hey. Let me go.
On your knees, bastard!
On your knees!
Let go, let go!
Look, blockhead. You think
we're just neighborhood punks?
- Mr. Gang! Mr. Gang!
- You think we're pushovers?
Let go! Hey! Mr. Gang! Mr. Gang!
- Pick him up!
- Let go...
Why are you doing this?
Why am I doing this?
What are you looking at, huh?
What are you looking at!
You staring at me?
Go ahead, bastard. Go ahead!
Stare, you bastard!
Officer, son of a bitch?
Take this, asshole.
"Why are you doing this?"
Why are you doing this?
Bastard!
Asshole!
Wipe it clean.
Wipe it clean, I said!
Spit-shine... with your tongue.
What? Are they too dirty for you?
That's the way the world is.
If you push too hard, it breaks.
Let's have a drink tonight.
You...
...have the right to remain silent.
You have the right to
choose a lawyer...
The problem with me is that...
I can't fight.
They hit me.
That's the problem.
The fact that I can't fight...
that's the damn problem!
What the hell?
What the hell's your problem?
Are you drunk?
Officer Yoo,
you can do better, right?
Yes, sir!
Don't go around getting beat up.
Sorry, sir!
- Got it?
- Yes, sir!
Come in early tomorrow!
Goodnight, sir! Courtesy!
What?
Oh, don't you remember me?
Good morning!
Ah yes, this yogurt...
I'm sorry, suddenly
I was so thirsty...
I always hate it when people
steal yogurt from our front step.
I'm so sorry...
Last time, after the acupuncture,
I never got a chance
to say thanks,
so I thought, gosh, I better visit,
but then I never got the chance...
But today I happened
to be walking by,
and I thought... are they home?
So I stopped in.
So is everyone healthy,
wealthy, and happy?
Wow, what a cool place!
This is the altar of divinity.
If those seeking enlightenment
stand on this altar with a key,
the path to Nirvana opens.
Have you heard
about Yongsan?
Yongsan Electronics Market?
Have a seat.
Yongsan is where the chi of
dragon and mountain intertwine.
But people who coveted
the powerful chi of this place
began building
there indiscriminately,
until the very altar
was buried underground.
Fortunately, when Army Headquarters
were rebuilt as a war memorial,
the remains of the
altar were discovered.
Excavation has been
going on for years.
Do you follow?
Um, sure...
I didn't know tao masters
trained at Yongsan.
It's not a training camp,
it's an altar.
Sure, I got it.
Still...
You know... what I mean is...
My, the tea's hot.
If I learn all that,
will I be a good fighter?
Hey.
We don't teach you
how to brawl here.
What are you thinking, Dad?
What makes you think
this dork can become Maruchi?
Your daughter has a sharp tongue.
Uh, Master...
How much do you charge
for learning Palm Blast?
Well, it depends, I guess,
on the scale of the blast.
Don't you have anything else?
Suit yourself.
You see those people working up there?
They are using light-body skills.
Construction workers
often practice them.
You remember the woman who
caught an armed bank robber?
A lot of people
were stunned by that.
Where do you think
she got the strength?
She's just an ordinary person.
Many skilled people reach the
state of master without knowing.
There are countless masters today.
They've just adjusted
to a changing world.
But most are tao disciples
who fight against evil chi.
The Seven Masters seek a
leader among such people,
who can restore the flow
of pure chi to the world.
Then the Seven Masters
can't do a Palm Blast?
That's weird.
Is this the right place?
I think it's there.
Do I have to do
this every day?
It's leaking a lot.
What a mess...
We should talk to
whoever built this wall.
It's so damp here.
Hey, come check this out.
What is it?
There's a noise.
What the heck?
You hear it?
What's that?
Isn't this a little too much?
Couldn't we add
a fried egg or something?
I'm not a rabbit,
how can I live off these plants?
During Tao training,
one must eat vegetarian.
Isn't that common sense?
Okay, I'll give you that.
But my arms! They're all tied up!
Look at my arms!
Tao training is a form of study.
You can concentrate better on
an empty stomach.
This is all to teach you sincerity.
But why is it just me tied up
when you and this girl here...
Hey you!
You came here on your own to
learn, but you've got no respect.
Try behaving yourself.
Did you even
finish high school?
I graduated from
technical college, at least.
What?
The fire went out.
Damn, I can't take this any more.
It's too much!
You tell me to clean and I clean,
now I'm doing laundry.
I stood on my head
like you told me.
When are you going
to teach me Palm Blast?
Look, boy! Tao training
is a form of study.
Forget study, when
do I learn to fight?
If you want to learn to brawl,
go somewhere else!
Try boxing.
All right, all right.
But still, isn't there any way
I can learn how to do a Palm Blast?
"No Palm Blast Indoors"
We'll need to examine more later,
but it looks like it's from
the Koryo Dynasty at the latest.
And the shapes
made of iron spikes?
It looks like an indicator
of battle formations.
Battle formations?
During wars with Japan, General Lee
arranged troops in a wing shape.
I'm sure you've heard of them.
These spikes indicate the
formation of soldiers.
Inspector,
a phone call for you.
The old man found
at the site has disappeared.
We need to make a profit
before we go contributing money.
These days the goods
I was supposed to send to Japan
are being held at customs,
and I can't do anything.
So first, bring over the goods.
That's right.
Just a sec. Go away.
Go! It's nothing.
I'll call you back in a sec.
Are you crazy, old man?
What the hell?
Who the hell are you?
- How about some freebie?
- What more do you want?
- Can't you go any cheaper?
- Go somewhere else.
All confrontations begin
and end with the eyes.
Like in The Art of War.
It's the best way to win a
confrontation without fighting.
It's winning mastery
with the eyes.
Don't think you'll get a discount
staring at me like that!
You said you'd teach me, but you
haven't taught me anything.
Are you starving these days?
I'm not starving!
If it's too hard for you,
try another job.
You get beat up all the time,
and now you don't even eat?
How will you find a wife?
I told you I'm not starving!
- When a man does important things...
- Dad's asleep, be quiet.
Mom, you don't know anything!
- Good afternoon.
I'm Kim Su-chul of
"Find the Master!"
I'm Kim Hyo-seon.
We have a big
audience today, don't we?
- Yes.
- This is great.
- Hyo-seon.
- Yes?
Have you heard that lately,
because of our program
"Find the Master,"
many people visit
the ophthalmologist?
Why is that?
Their eyes popped out
in anticipation.
In general this type
of thing is prohibited.
But young people just
have no interest in tao...
We have two guests here.
Quite an unusual name, yes?
Brother Yuk-bong,
and Master Sul-woon.
We're glad to have you.
Please come out.
Wow, they look impressive.
- Don't they?
- Yeah.
It's a great honor
to have you here.
Yes, nice to meet you.
It must have been
difficult to come here.
Wait a sec.
This is so heavy,
are these rocks?
Oh, yes. On crowded sidewalks,
I walk so fast that
I often bump into people.
I'm fine, but I worry
that I'll hurt people,
so I walk with these stones.
Oh, you must be really fast.
You must've transported here by magic?
I took the #77 bus.
Ah, yes.
Well, yes, we heard about you,
and I'm quite curious,
and I'm sure our many guests
want to see it as well.
So let's see you perform.
A show of extraordinary force,
the very site of destruction!
After training in the mountains,
it may be intimidating on TV.
Let's give them
a show of support!
Let go!
Stop, now!
This can't be!
- Well... I mean, master,
- It's over.
Please calm down.
Oh, sorry, I...
Let me put this in perspective.
The technique we've shown you
is extremely difficult.
For an ordinary person,
this is really hard to split.
You wanna die?
Sorry.
Be on time.
God, she even reads
martial arts comics.
What, she has makeup?
Does she use this stuff?
What is this?
Beauty Academy
Huh?
She wasn't bad-Looking
in high school either...
A birthday photo.
Wait, it's on April 17?
Wait a second.
That's coming up soon.
Martial arts are for supressing
violence, for stopping conflict,
and for avoiding cruelty.
This is the truth
all martial arts aspire to.
Only the truly powerful can defend
by anticipating an opponent.
Let's see. Try to hit Eui-jin.
Urr... the, the best defense
is offense, of course.
Those who want self-control
must learn mind control.
To serve others, not to win,
is the true, unbreakable strength.
To achieve this
you must renounce yourself.
Hey.
Do it right.
Suppleness is
to follow force.
To use the enemy's force
to beat him.
One who follows force
has no fear.
Merit is earned by
training without fakery.
Fist-fighting is
refined and simple.
The changes are unpredictable,
so you must learn to move
your body as you wish.
The body and mind are one.
To control your mind,
you must control the body.
Shut up and do it.
Hey, wait!
I said wait... wait...
This is too much.
Swiftness means fast, got it?
The fist has a form,
but hitting has no form.
In other words, you gotta
learn the laws of nature.
If I'm faster than others,
it means others are slower than me.
Sang-hwan, are you crazy?
- Mom!
- What do you have against
the eggs, you do it?
Bravery is not to hesitate.
To move in when
you see an opportunity.
Time seems to flow
equally for everyone,
yet with concentration,
a fleeting moment can
stretch into eternity.
Slashing is to give damage
to others without mercy.
But if you can't
control your emotion,
you might end up staining yourself.
Wounds on the body
may easily be healed,
but emotional scars do not
go away so easily.
Finally, truthfulness is to strike
and defend without deception.
Having reached the point
of truthful selflessness,
you eventually gain enlightenment.
What happens
after enlightenment?
First learn what comes before, kid.
Hello?
Is this Seung-gu?
It's me, Sang-hwan.
Yeah, did all of you guys
get together tonight?
Hey, I'm done,
so I'll come over there now.
Oh, it's fine with me.
But, it's okay...
Oh, really?
Then I'll see you guys next time.
OK, and give me a ring.
Anytime. Yeah, sure, sure.
Hey mister!
What are you doing, mister?
How can you just
jaywalk like that,
It's not even 4 lanes,
it's an 8-lane road.
Mister, you may
be busy, but still...
Show me your ID, please.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Officer Yoo,
servant to the public.
So...
Show me your ID, please.
Hey, look here mister!
Hey, mister!
Gosh, mister. Stop there!
You over there!
You crazy idiot, what the hell?
You aren't hurt, are you?
Why's he running away like that?
Where is he running to?
Damn it.
What are you doing?
Well, I think I'm fine.
What an idiot.
What's this?
Hey you, stop!
Wait, I said stop!
I can't believe it.
Now everyone knows us.
Tell me about it, the manager was
in a rage over last week's show.
But I kept telling him, splitting
wood is not martial arts.
By the way, should we contact
another place?
I guess so.
Gosh, it makes me nervous.
We're not some kind
of traveling circus.
Huh? That's a fearsome chi.
It can't be...
How did he get out...
Who is carrying the key?
Ever since
we found them,
they have kept the
exact same position.
Have they ever shown
this kind of symptom before?
All 72 meridian points
have been blocked.
Yes?
Their chi has been corrupted.
I've been trying so hard,
why isn't there any big improvement?
This isn't a computer game,
this is for real.
Of course not, but...
That guy's light-body skills
were really fantastic.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
What?
When you really fight,
chi is what matters, not skills.
- I'm not talking about chi...
- You have to beat him with chi.
Yeah... I just don't
have any confidence.
When somebody says,
"Let's fight,"
then you say, 'OK, but I may
end up killing you."
Did you learn this
to kill somebody?
If you don't...
Forget it.
Hey!
What now?
Here.
What's this?
It's your birthday...
How did you know?
I know everything...
I go by the lunar calendar.
Thanks anyway.
She is so cold.
Hey Sang-hwan,
what the hell is this?
Student ID
Beauty Academy
What?
Do cops enjoy spying on people?
Who said to spy on me?
You're really overreacting.
I... I did this for you,
aren't you even thankful?
Just concentrate
on your own life, okay?
Eat up.
Hey, what's up?
Are you buying me dinner now?
Mu-un said you drag
your body around,
so he said to buy you
some meat for strength.
Oh!
Here.
What's this?
Master Mu-un said you've got nothing,
but you're full of pride.
He said to look at this
when your temper flares up.
Here.
Honestly, is it really from Master Mu-un?
What? You think it's from me?
Miss, our flame's out.
Can you change the fuel?
Don't bother her.
Can't you see she's busy?
Hey, you can't do that here...
It's okay.
Hey, can you do me a favor?
Is there any way you can
teach me this Palm Blast thing?
Get a grip, will you?
Welcome to the world
of fortune telling.
Curious about your future?
I'm not available to take your call.
So those in a hurry
please try the 1-700 number.
Banya isn't answering either.
Heug-un must
surely want the key?
What should we do?
Would you take it?
What are you talking about?
We should solve this together,
don't try to avoid it.
Our power is lacking.
To fight Heug-un, we
need at least three of us.
I've carried the key too long,
waiting for Maruchi.
But how's it any different
if I have the key?
Let's assume it's really Heug-un.
He doesn't have true chi.
I know he has strong power,
but since we have true chi,
he can't beat is, can he?
Yuk-bong and Sul-woon
fell without a fight.
If we can awaken Sang-hwan's
chi, matters might be different.
Honestly, in my opinion...
I don't think Sang-hwan
can become Maruchi.
I have no confidence in him.
Destiny can be made.
The thing is will.
That punk's will is...
Where is he?
Let's have some meat.