Keep away!
Keep away...!
Letting loose a dog to bite so early!
Keep away...
Master Pin
How's it, Master Pin!
You look swell walking the dog
Sure! I bought it from the USA
Keep away!
Bloody dog!
Go to hell!
Tsai!
Pin, what now?
Go and chase it!
What's it?
Are you alright?
Yes
I'm not alright!
What is it, Master Pin?
You scared away my dog!
At worst I'll make good to you the loss
Make good?
Master Pin, we couldn't catch it
Right, Master Pin!
You couldn't catch it?
Make way! Out of the way!
I'm a marine officer's son,
I won't bully you
Magistrate Hu, please come here!
What's it, Master Pin?
Let Magistrate Hu arbitrate...
to reconcile you
I'm reconciled now!
Good! Why not come to my home to
pick your favorite dog?
I've got over a dozen
What? My dad bought Tsai...
for 100 taels from the USA and
it's the only one...
in Canton
Cost 100 taels plus 2 years' feeding...
200 taels
The minimum compensation is 200 taels
200 taels?
My whole family...
can't spend it all in 10 years!
Magistrate Hu,
our Tsai eats beef every meal
He must pay a penalty of 300 taels!
300 taels!
No!
Too little...
Just imagine
It's not simple...
to import a dog
from the United States
The expenses are innumerous!
You must pay at least 500 taels!
Secretary Sung's right, 500 taels!
Fu!
Don't!
Fu! Fu!
How are your buttocks?
It bleeds and hurts with toothmarks
You've beaten away my Fu!
He bit my buttocks!
You asked for 500 taels
after your dog bit
Now our Fu bit your buttocks
Our Tsai is a dog!
You asked for 500 for beating away a dog
The penalty for beating away
a man should be at least 1000
Tsai is a dog king bought from the USA
My Fu is "dregs king" bought from France
He's the only one in town
I've supported him for 20 years
It's reasonable to ask for 1000 taels
Your Honor,
what do you think?
The way you figure it...
You're right!
Your Honor is sagacious!
King Dregs of France!
Now your Fu's back!
That's why I'm asking
for 1000 taels only
If he never returns,
10,000 taels is not enough!
You're OK
You frame me
What's wrong?
Trying to kill! Damn it!
Something exciting!
Someone got into the ox manure pit!
Let me make the introduction
This is Master Pin!
How do you do, Master Pin?
My wife
Madam
Master Pin's courteous
Master Pin, it's alright for my wife...
to have saved your life
It's alright!
We must visit the grave
Yes!
Your Honor, you know the case?
Yes
Please
Go away!
Pay him 1000 taels
Right, Master Pin
If your dog returns...
like Fu did,
repay him several hundred taels
O. K...
Be nice, Chieh, kowtow to your brother
We've lost a dozen sons altogether
Don't say it!
You make me sad
It was all your fault!
You've chosen to be a shyster
You stick at nothing for money!
You're too unethical
You knew it yourself
You cried your heart out after each case
It's fair to help others
after getting paid for it
When did I cry?
You didn't?
No
Darling, seal your brush!
If I do, no more gold bracelets, chains,
jade rings, gems, earrings for you
Look,
they're too heavy to carry
I don't care, I'd rather forsake them...
Maybe...
I won't ask for so much!
I only want my child safe and sound
Will you do me a favor?
One must adapt to circumstances
It's easier said than done
Switch to business, darling
Tom made a fortune last year-end
but Dick hung himself to death
You two, stop quarreling!
Mind I hit you!
Be nice and sleep
That master inside has been waiting
Who are you, please?
Ta Pao-ho!
Yes!
What a memory you have!
Nonsense! You've hired so many men here
How can I remember them all?
Oh, how big!
Our master is Chen Chiang-fu
He's the owner
of the largest exchange shop in Canton
He wants you to write a memorial for him
Here's the deposit
Once you fix it,
the sky can be the limit
Fu
Yes!
Do you agree or not?
What do you mean by that?
That's right
Good, a stick facing a stick
That's not the way to talk to me
Of course
How could a man talk to a stick?
Mr Sung is indeed out of the ordinary
You're unreservedly
a No. 1 counsel in town
Am I okay?
Fit as a fiddle
What can I do for you please?
The fact of the case is
My son's been learning kung fu
He had a fight yesterday
His opponent is opium
owner Chang Piao's son
He's fragile after two light blows only
he got knocked down
And he died this morning
I know Chang Piao has reported it
to the magistracy
Please try...
to get him off the hook
My husband has decided to seal his brush
Here is...
Sorry
Just have a look!
Retired?
I'll reconsider the retirement
Darling
See him out
This case of gold...
Sorry, please
It's all yours if you win
No!
Whose son was killed...
by whose son?
Your Honor!
My son was killed by his son
So you're the plaintiff
Your Honor! In fact, we're plaintiffs
Our memorial was here
before dawn
At that time
His son didn't die yet
What's your charge against him?
Chang Piao's son Chang Hsiao Szu
broke the nail of the small finger
of the left hand of Chen Chiang-fu's son
Chen Ta-wen
He's seriously hurt!
But my son's dead!
Right, his son's dead!
Your Honor,
everybody dies!
Right
He seriously wounded and
killed my son
Why didn't you say your son was no good?
I just rushed over to give him 2 punches
Several, punches?
Two punches! I got over to...
So hard?
You...
Should be so hard!
Secretary Sung...
You're not smart enough
May I ask
when was your son hit by his son?
Yesterday afternoon
When did he die?
This afternoon
What does it concern him then?
Just now I punched him more than twice
Your Honor,
can he sue me for murder
if he should die in 8-10 years?
No, no
Your Honor's brilliant! Long long live!
My son was well and
and he caused his death
Secretary Sung, do me a favor!
Your son died because he was short-lived
He didn't look short-lived!
May I ask what's the span of my life!
I can't tell
Since you can't,
how could you tell that
your son was not short-lived?
Let's come to the point
Any result, Your Honor?
Yes!
Would you give me some hint?
Plaintiff Chen Ta-wen was wounded
but the defendant died, cause unknown
He should've asked
for a penalty of 50 taels
We won't pursue any more!
You're smart!
Your Honor, any result?
Yes!
Give the verdict now!
Okay!
Chang Piao allowed
his son to commit crime
No prosecution,
considering it a first offence
Tell your son not to commit again!
Well...
Is this right?
His son won't commit again
Chieh!
Darling
Darling,
take the son to the rocking horse
I've newly bought
Chieh!
He got a crash and dropped into the well
He couldn't pass one year
It's tit for tat
It really is tit for tat
The brush-sealing ceremony begins!
Is today really a good day, sir?
Today's the best day in a year
Look at the calendar
It says offerings are unsuitable
except for the wei hour
It faces your horoscope and is best
You mustn't go too far
Hurry up!
After the hour it would be trouble!
Convulsion, take me home quick!
Are you alright?
Hurry up!
What's wrong, darling?
Put...
Better now?
Let me see
What a miracle!
It gets well suddenly!
Yes! Go over then!
Good!
Come
Come...!
You first
You first!
You please. Help yourself
Well...
Okay! Let me
Fu
Don't tarry, go now!
Go up!
Go up, not yet there!
I've brought something horrible
to help you
What's so horrible with a frog?
Keep away! Let me
OK now
How could you...
How could you've sawed the highest part?
To make it look real!
It's broken! What now?
Buy a new one
A new one?
An order for such a long ladder...
takes 9 days
It can only be arranged in 2 days then
There's no other way out
Go home, buy food and cook
Don't you want to get cursed?
No, but I must wait some time
I'll kill you!
Just the right hour!
Go now
Darling!
What's it again?
To show your will,
swear that
if you go against it
the child I'm now bearing
will come out without a chick
Are you pregnant again?
Are you sure?
Don't touch me!
What?
A mammy...
cursing her own child
Has she to be so wicked?
No
Yes! Yes!
OK, you win!
If I should write memorials again,
may your child come out without a chick
A child!
A child without chick, okay?
Why didn't you say so?
So just one touch and you got pregnant?
You're evil!
Congratulations...!
Thank you...!
I must sue Chang Piao's son Hsiao Szu
for breaking the nail
of the small finger
of Chen Chiang-fu's son Ta-wen
Badly hurt!
Your Honor, my son's dead!
Yes, his son is dead!
Everybody dies, Your Honor!
Still thinking of the lawsuit?
You're incorrigible!
I really don't understand you women
What do you mean...
by having stripes planted on your head?
That's a bun
Like sea-slugs, how silly?
Are they beautiful?
You call that beautiful?
Does it look okay now?
Damn ugly
You're right
Better...
This way!
What does this look like?
Don't like it? Change it...
Don't move!
What're you doing from behind?
Don't you like this?
Where?
Over here!
You creep!
Even now I'm still taller than you!
Did you ever study?
For two days
Can't you be a bit euphemistic?
That's hypocrisy!
You?
What a busybody!
Am I busy?
It's so boring!
This is it
I'm middle-aged now
People will laugh
if I stay idle all day long
Even my brush is sealed! What a pity!
You're now a boss!
Isn't it nice for you to move around?
I've moved around a lot
Stand here!
Stand!
Don't try to act busy!
I know you're free
Get the writing equipment for me
Fu, are you writing?
Keep away!
That's no way to write!
Let me show you
Cursed with a son with no chick
Shui, let me use it
Pass the bucket of water!
Put it over here!
The one writing is Sung Shih-chieh
You each...
take off one rib from him
Don't worry
That's the way to do it!
No way, it can't be hung
I've to rewrite it
I give you a chance to learn
Let me demonstrate to you once again
Why have you moistened my head?
Why have you torn off my dress?
When did I tear off your dress?
Don't deny!
It's now even!
What now?
Hit him
What's so funny?
What's wrong, Fu?
Master got beaten!
Help!
Are you alright?
Let go...! How ugly!
I kill you
Let me hit you once
Again?
Help!
What a shame being in a girl's arms!
He would've fallen to death!
Sonny, your sister's fantastic!
Get dressed now
Luckily, not many are around
It's hard but ventilated, not bad
Believe me
Good...
Make a pair like before then
Excellent! The sole's a bit hard
Put a cushion
Put a cushion?
What do you think of this?
Not bad
Excellent...
Make it like that
This cushion may get flat after long use
Use a wooden one, okay?
That's too hard
Never mind
Too heavy
Don't worry,
put 2 cushions above it
2 cushions above the wood?
Wait
Okay, I can manage!
2 layers of leather under the sole
make it more durable!
How about this?
At least 5-6 inches taller in them!
Right...
Well...
Why not this?
Take this
You're in the mood today
Have a good time
Okay?
Why not this way then?
Excuse me!
What's wrong with you now?
Are you scared?
You know the pain
of not being tall enough?
Darling
Being tall doesn't count
It's a tall ambition that counts
Do you know
you rate high to me?
Darling
I...
Say it!
In my eyes...
you're the biggest
Please excuse me!
Please have tea!
Thank you
It's true, madam
Fu often pawed over me
I'm serious
What a gossiper!
It's true!
Creep, what a waste!
I feel great!
Madam, he's smart,
tea can remove odor
Shut up!
What a lousy man...
for such a beauty
Your husband died a mysterious death
Your brother-in-law may suspect you
if you go away now
What a wicked woman murdering
her own husband!
My husband was murdered
by my brother-in-law
An internecine war!
Your sister-in-law's brother
is Chief Secretary, Shansi
Right!
Will she sue you?
No,
she's guilty herself
What she said makes sense
You're pregnant, you may get cheated
exposing yourself
I won't be pregnant any more
I didn't mean you
I'm her brother
Brother, what about the money I gave you
I want to have a bet...
Have you lost everything?
Shut up!
What am I to do now?
Don't worry...!
The one in front is my fellow clansman
Let me borrow some money from him
to meet the emergency
Wait for me here,
I'll be back right away
Yang Ching, what a coincidence
I'm out for buying
It's been a long time
Yes, how's your wife?
She died two years ago
What about your two sons then?
An elderly maid's taking care of them
Your brother must've fooled
that upright man
Yes, I'm sure he has
Your pregnant niece wants to get married
Yes, she's desperate
because her husband's dead
If you marry her,
she'll serve you well
and your two sons
A fair lady is the most ideal
She's a fair lady
Your niece? Of the same family name?
No, I won't give you one
with the same family name as yours
Is that right?
They're staring at us
Why's he staring at me?
I'm sure he's staring at me
Don't you feel ashamed?
Chen, come here
Clear up everything!
Would your niece regret...
50 taels only?
No...
Chen, this is Mr Yang
Excuse me
I need the manure pit
Yang...
Miss Chou, is your Uncle alright?
He's my 2nd brother, not Uncle
He took 50 taels from me
to arrange for your marriage
Then he sold you
after your husband got killed
Damn him
I'll try to get him back
Master,
it's town after this mountain top
See if you can get away!
Go down and have a look!
Yes!
Keep away!
Kid, how could you have done that?
You're a beast!
Keep away!
At worst I'll refund you the money
Get hold of my hand!
Yang, I'm sorry
Take care of my sister!
Yang
Go up first!
Master, one of them fell to death
You witnessed it, sir
Please testify at the nearby magistracy
He's too busy to testify
You...
Keep this fan from me
If someone accuses you at the Magistracy
show it to him, and he'll understand
Sir...
Why are they still not back?
It seems he couldn't keep up
with your brother
and wouldn't return...
to embarrass you
So he left without saying goodbye
I really am miserable
How am I going to live?
Don't cry!
Why not put up at my home?
Your brother will return
after getting away
Go...!
Go!
Have you broken away
from that pregnant woman?
Nonsense!
Next time don't talk so much nonsense!
Go now!
Madam's cruel
She hurts my vital part
Take care
It hurts!
This woman's husband was killed by...
this woman's husband's brother
and his wife
This woman's husband's brother
then framed this woman...
for the murder
of this woman's husband
Luckily...
this woman's maid told her of it
This woman then rushed...
to see her brother at night
This woman's brother,
an addicted gambler,
gambled away all her money
and sold her to his fellow clansman
as his wife
Then this woman's brother ran away
from her
So this woman came back...
with me
Fantastic...
Talk faster and I say you're fantastic
She has a heartrending background
There're too many others...
like her
And she's pregnant!
There're many other pregnant women too
Let her stay till her brother comes
to pick her up
Master...
Madam...
That woman's brother...
won't return to take her away!
Why?
He fell to death down a cliff
Her brother is now dead too
She's pregnant with no kin
You can't take care of her...
all your life
Let her give delivery first
Master, madam...
That woman's given birth
So soon?
The arrival of a child...
will be a burden
She can't work and
is hard to find a husband
She's finished!
Master, madam
What's up again?
That woman is hanging herself
Hanging herself!
It's the more horrible. She should...
She is hanging herself!
Finished!
Don't!
Look, she's hanging herself!
Do something!
After what she's suffered...
she has no other recourse!
Have you no feelings?
Have you any feelings?
I'm asking you!
Are you tired after holding her so long?
Logically...
should be
Let her go then!
Okay. Why are you shouting?
Mrs Sung, let me die!
You still want to die?
You're resourceful. Do something for her
Didn't you make it clearly?
She's finished
Mrs Sung, I put my son in your custody
Take him as your own
I was the mother of a dozen sons
I know how you feel
I'll be a mother to your child
How did you get into this trouble?
Death is the only way out for me now
Death? I'll bring you back to life
Don't talk big!
Who on earth...
can bring a life back?
Halt!
Close the door!
What are you doing?
Violence!
Come on!
Hit me in my parents' presence
if you dare
Come down and see if I'll beat you
Be smart and don't come down!
You're a no-good scholar
You told me to seal my brush!
Now you want me
to write a memorial again
I vowed to Heaven under curse
This time it's for justice
God will forgive you!
What if he doesn't?
Would you make good the "chicks" to me?
Don't turn me down any more!
If you stand by, you're not a man!
Say that again and I'll slap you
You're not a man
I forgive you only
because you're pregnant
Say that again if you dare!
You're not a man...
Okay!
I'm a female! Outrageous!
Don't come to my room to sleep tonight!
I'll sleep with you tonight, mom, dad!
Master
Why laugh? Are you mad?
Rinse, master
Crazy!
Who's this perfect fright?
It's you!
Me?
Oh, God,
who brought me this?
Madam!
She said you're mean and cowardly
It's better to be female than man
But when you're posed as a female...
You look more beautiful than madam
Keep your mouth shit!
Where's madam?
She went to the magistracy early
in the morning
because you refused to defend
for Miss Yang
Who does she think she is?
Master
Change! I know
The wet nurse wants rock candy
to decoct papayas
Go and do it then. Why bother me?
You must return them to me
Madam put the papayas with you
Give it to me!
No, I don't owe you anything!
Don't go away!
You watch me go in
I watch you go in
Secretary
What a relief!
What does the memorial say?
Your Honor, many XX and OO
Read to me as much as possible
I, Mrs Sung and Yang Hsiu-chen...
XX Your Honor
Yang Hsiu-chen OO was XX
What?
Mrs Sung, what does OO mean?
Her husband!
Go on!
Yang Hsiu-chen OO was XX
Yang Hsiu-chen is seeking XX
Hold it!
Seeking what?
Seeking redress, Your Honor!
I forgot how to write that
What do you want?
I'm looking for my wife!
Return home to find her
Brazen!
I Counsellor Sung Shih-chieh
used to move around here freely
Who dares to stand in my way?
You had a memorial then
What've you got now?
Please be considerate, brothers
I'll buy you snacks
Outsiders are not admitted
under the new rules
of the new magistrate
Wait here, if you prefer
Finally, XX Your Honor
and your family's OO
Outrageous...
Unintelligible...
Mrs Sung, can any of your family write?
Why not? Within a perimeter of 500 li
who doesn't know my husband
the famous counselor Sung Shih-chieh?
No wonder you're so cocky
So you're Sung Shih-chieh's wife!
Precisely!
Good!
Come on, serve her with Torture A!
Yes!
What is Torture A?
It means 30 slaps on your face!
Hold it!
I'm here to prosecute. Why slap me?
Your husband Sung Shih-chieh talks
black into white
You're his wife, a termagant
30 slaps only...
are a favor to your husband!
Execute!
Terrible!
Go out... Wait outside if you prefer
What do you want?
Move, and it will be all over your face!
Halt!
Do I look like...
Yes!
Like Monk Chi
Cry your heart out
Let me be cursed with sterility or
anything worse,
I must take the revenge
Revenge!
That won't work!
Absolutely not
Absolutely impossible!
It won't work!
Make an exception!
You made a vow!
I often make vows
Right, I made the vow
What has it to do with you?
But now you're moving the scrolls
written by Emp. Chien Lung
That's absolutely intolerable
The scrolls affect
the feng shui of our clan
Yes!
It's been peaceful
since it was hung nearly a century ago
Right!
It was moved when it was hung
and any effect would've been felt
Anyway, you must absolutely not
move this feng shui scroll
Right, right!
Don't...
Darling!
Shut up!
Darling, you go up!
You sealed it, you must get it yourself!
Come down...
Fu!
Come down quick!
Take care of me!
Go get it quick!
It's got!
Go down
Yes,
the people can seek redress
with the comeback of a good counsel
I said it myself! Why rush to say it?
Hold it!
Ladies and gentlemen, please listen to
my husband for my sake
Look over there!
Don't move it!
It's enough for you
to build dozens of arches
Otherwise, split it
Yes, let's split it!
Mr Sung
Lord Ho
Thank you
Have you eaten?
Yes, thank you
Mr Sung...
Thank you...
Lord Ho
Please!
Sung Shih-chieh
Come on!
I've long heard...
of your eloquent defence
Is that true?
You're that paunchy Lord Ho Yu-ta
that gases...
from top to bottom?
You're insulting me!
I didn't mean to
I've heard of it only
Heard of it only? You're illiterate
Yes,
as illiterate as you are
I'm entirely different
What difference?
We both speak according to hearsay only
We're in the same trade
How dare you?
Sometimes we may get it wrong
They say you're a nut...
but I don't...
Think so
She's a native of Shansi
Why prosecute in Canton?
Your Honor, you're a native of Hunan
Why have you become
a magistrate in Canton?
You claim that her brother-in-law
and his wife killer her husband
and framed her for the murder. Any proof
No
That's a false accusation then
Hold it!
What?
May I ask Your Honor
Am I male or female?
Male of course
Any concrete proof?
The fact is...
You took a wife
and have children
This is logic
You're smart
Thank you
Her brother-in-law and his wife
Lost a brother followed by her departure
Yet they don't care a damn
Aren't they logically under suspicion,
Your Honor?
Did you see them put the poison?
Yes!
No!
My maid Mei saw it
She saw them put the poison
into the soup
After taking it, my husband died
of bleeding from his nostrils
This idiot ran away...
only after Mei reminded her of it
You're garrulous!
It shows the heart,
and the heart shows concern
That's why Kuan (Mandarin) has 2 mouths
My husband told me that
How coquettish!
Any result, Your Honor?
Good, I'll handle it for the time being
Thin Hu, Fat Lung
Your Honor, any mandate?
You set out for Shansi and escort
her brother and
sister-in-law back for trial
together with their maid Mei
Your order is understood!
Adjourned!
Hold it!
Your Honor, please stay!
May I ask you another question,
Your Honor?
What is it?
What's the charge...
for one framing a goodie?
It depends on the one framed?
A gentleman
Almost as good-looking as you are
Is that so?
Libel for a serious case,
insult for a light one
What would be your verdict?
Not premeditated
It depends on
whether it is premeditated or not
Even for that
he must pay scores of taels
Your Honor is enlightened
Bravo...
Thank you
What is it?
Pay me
Do I owe you any money?
You called me
an eloquent defence counsel
As you're in charge of this case,
it shows I'm speaking the truth
and you're guilty of "insult"
No...
Either you can't tell right from wrong
or are muddle-headed
Admit to either of these charges
Sorry
Pay Mr Sung 50 taels
Hush! If this circulates,
it may affect your prestige
How exciting!
You again?
Please
What a magistrate!
Your Excellency!
Yang, why do you insist...
on seeing me tonight?
It's urgent!
Those 2 constables
1 tall, 1 thin
said they rushed 3 months
all the way from Canton with a writ
to summon your sister Mrs Yao...
and her husband to Canton for trial
Miss, master
What's it?
Two constables from Canton are
here to arrest you
You're sued for murder and seizure
Mother...
Murdering who?
My brother-in-law
My sister has really gone too far
Your Honor, please have some mercy
What mercy?
Please calm down, Your Honor
She's your sister
Do something
No way, life for life
I'm your only daughter,
do help me
But how am I to help you?
Mother, he's most filial to you
He never disobeys you
Help me, flute
Yes
Let me try
Oh, finished!
Hold it!
My mammy calls me
Why's he so obedient?
Mother...
Mother, are you alright?
Brother
You two are heartless
So you really did it!
Brother, help us
You asked for it, why come to me?
Mother, brother's right
I deserve penalty
Forget your daughter
Darling,
you're breaking my heart
Mother!
Blood!
Mother's emitting blood! Alas!
No!
Mother's emitting much blood!
Don't get mad!
You broke her heart because you stood by
seeing your sister taken away for trial
Why give me this?
Let me die of cold!
Lychee honey!
No!
Mother!
Break it!
The one ruling is Canton magistrate
Can't you a Chief Secretary...
fix it?
Let me die!
I die! I die! I...
Okay...
Let me try!
Yuan, Chuan
Coming...
Yes, madam?
Keep the constables from Canton...
by every means
Hurry up...
Yes!
Have Yuan and Chuan rush to Canton
Spend as much as...
you can on bribery
before your sister and
brother-in-law arrive
Want to borrow my wet nurse?
Yes! My grandson's got whooping cough
No medication has proved effective
They say human milk
is the most effective
Wet nurse, come here!
Yes, madam
Come with her...
to breast-feed her grandson
Oh, no, my grandson's over 20
Damn!
Breast-feeding an adult?
Well,
milk some for him when you can
Madam, you're taking me
for a milk cow
Mrs Sung, what now?
Darling, not so hard!
Okay!
Alas!
Darling, come on!
What?
No!
Come on, hurry up!
No, it's too big!
This time it's getting big too soon!
You shouldn't have cried so sexily
to have turned me on!
Go out...
I really can't hold on
I've boiled almond puree
Mrs Sung
I've fixed the human milk
maid Chang wants
We're both female. Don't be shy
Put it over there
I'll have the wet nurse bring it
Okay
Darling
Mr Sung
Mrs Sung will be back right away
Will she?
The almond puree is ready so soon
You want it? Take it first
No smell of almond
It has a strong smell of milk
Is this yours?
Yes
What is it?
Milk
Goat milk or cow milk?
Human milk, from me
Don't ever let anybody know of it
I'll go out first
There must be something between you two
No
You deny?
Even with snake-bite?
What a sexfriend
You tomcat while I'm pregnant
Yueh Lai Inn?
Seems to be Sung Shih-chieh's
Don't you know
it's Sung Shih-chieh's?
Sung Shih-chieh? He is dead
Bitch!
Sung Shih-chieh doesn't die
at right time
What do you mean, gentlemen?
Who are you?
I'm the manager here
If he died earlier, we wouldn't have to
travel from Shansi to Canton in vain
You came from Shansi?
Only Shansi could have such elite
Are you on an official mission?
Yes, the Chief Secretary of Shansi
is our boss
We're to bring an important letter...
to the magistrate here
Why talk so much to this nobody?
Okay
You two really are...
smart
Did your Lord send you here to...
Shut up! Is the Inn full?
No, it was a mistake
Please be seated, gentlemen
Don't touch him
I'll come right away
after fixing the room
Madam...
What is it, Mr Sung?
Madam, don't cry
2 men on a mission...
from your brother-in-law
I suspect they're up to something
Madam... let me finish first
Vacate your room for me to
let it to them
So we may have a chance to test them out
OK, you're doing it for my own good!
Mr Sung, you want to drink?
No... it's for your son
Take it if you like
No, thanks, you milked it so hard
Ground!
Ground?
It's almond puree!
You can grind almond puree?
Madam
Don't crease my dress
It's late. Don't yell!
What a creep! He really entered her room
You creep!
Who's calling my name?
Did you?
You, a family woman, sneak into
a men's room at this late hour
You're acting like a whore
What do you want?
Give me a logical explanation
Speak up!
Come on!
I've come to borrow a urinal,
OK?
Is it a logical explanation?
No!
Darling! In fact, I didn't come for this
I know. You went to see Yang Hsiu-chen
because you thought she was there
Yes, how smart you are, darling!
Of course,
would I suspect you of anything?
Would I be so unethical
as to suspect you?
Would you suspect me of anything?
No, of course not
Outrageous! He's stolen a march!
So what? I enjoy doing it
I was only joking!
Are you resenting?
No
What does this letter say?
Judging from its contents,
Yang indeed...
is innocent
It's a letter...
from the couple to
Ho Yu-ta,
using the pull of the Chief Sec
They offer a bribe to him...
to frame Yang
So cocky? Let's hit him!
Don't act on impulse!
This letter can be a strong evidence
Let's put it back
after copying it
Right, you indeed are resourceful
You didn't know before now
I did, but I didn't say it
Now I want you to say it thrice daily
And don't dress a bun
And don't raise hell and hit me
Always take my advice
Only on important issues
Oh, no, you're too stupid to distinguish
between important or not
Alternatively,
you must follow my advice
whenever I say "maltose"
I'm the handsomest in the world!
Say "yes"
Don't!
Maltose
You're the handsomest
whether you want me to say it or not
Do I have to do it?
Maltose
Couldn't care less!
So it's like this
Even the Shansi magistrate...
didn't try it
No, but our Lord wants
Your Excellency...
to cover it up
You've said it all
Your Excellency!
Our mistress and husband...
are rushing in
with the constables. Please be lenient
Please take these 5,000 taels
I've been an honest mandarin,
open and aboveboard
Please convey the message
to the Chief Sec
I'll do my best...
in this case
But I can't accept the money
That's it
Please return...!
Please stay, gentlemen
Put the money here!
Yes, Mrs Ho?
Please convey my husband's...
thanks to H.E.
Didn't Magistrate Ho say
he's honest and righteous
We have heavy expenses
And righteous?
It's not right to turn down a gift
She's terrific...
Let's go
Mr and Mrs Yao greeting Your Honor
Do you know...
that woman holding a baby?
Your Honor,
she's my sister-in-law Mrs Yao nee Yang
Yes...
Yang Hsiu-chen,
you murdered your husband
and framed Mr and Mrs Yao for it
Your Honor, I...
Shut up! Keep quiet now!
Your Honor,
is it the first time you see Mrs Yao?
What if it is?
You really are stupid then
Why?
Since it is the first time,
you should have acted more tactfully
Did I do it not brilliantly enough?
No!
You should've feigned
to take everyone's statements
You arbitrated...
even before Mr and Mrs Tien
said anything
It shows there was a tacit agreement
That's unworthy of you...
as a magistrate
You... I...
Without teaching you a lesson,
I will never be a mandarin again!
Come on, use torture!
Your Honor,
which torture? A, B or C?
C
Hold it! What is Torture C?
C is C
No torture!
You female have no right to speak
My husband is still a bachelor
You can't do anything
you please to him
Lord Ho knows better
You don't have to remind him
If you try tricks, I'll oblige
If you go too far, you can't hold on
Adjourned!
I play along on anything serious,
Your Honor!
You three think it over
Uncle, you haven't defecated for 10 days
And you haven't slept well for a month
Your sow aborted and
died last night
All this happened
because Sung Shih-chieh
spoiled the feng shui of the arch
You two are his elder
Sung Shih-chieh...
is not giving you any face
In my view...
Uncle...
Just say what you've in mind!
Come on!
Isn't it right to punish him?
Just go on
Okay...
Uncle and neighbors
They're so rude
They left without saying goodbye
To strip him of his bachelorhood?
Why've you got downstairs so soon?
Hit him!
Didn't I say you can't beat a bachelor?
You're a mere magistrate
If I became a master,
I might be your superior
Change the subject!
You're no longer a bachelor!
Royal tutor
Why're you here? Teacher
Sung Shih-chieh, I disqualified you
as a bachelor
because you spoiled the feng shui
Sorry for the trouble, sir
Don't mention it
Please...
They've conspired against me
That's no way to cope with me
Darling
Show me that letter
It's with you!
It's not with me. It's with you!
With me?
Wait, Your Honor
They can't testify without that letter
Excuse me...
Help! Keep away! Don't be in the way
What're you two up to?
Well, Your Honor!
I forgot to bring an important document
Would you give me two hours?
Outrageous! Come on!
Yes!
Slap him!
Hold it!
What?
Let me warn you first
I know all about your scandal
You'll regret lifting one hair from me
Slap him!
Hold it!
Scared now?
Now I'll strip you and slap you naked
Slap!
What?
Hit me harder if you have the nerve
The harder you hit, the harder I sue you
What have you got against me?
40 heavy slaps!
Hold it!
40 slaps? Too few!
Double it if you dare!
Good, I'll round it up to 100
Hold it!
What is it now?
Nothing. I'm yelling. Damn it!
Swear words! Slap!
Hold it!
What do you want now?
Fu, the letter is here
Secretary, read it loudly for me!
Yes!
Darling,
I XX with you till dawn last night
So I know your XX is powerful
Why?
Darling, I XX you
Oh, God, the wrong letter!
What letter is this, Sung Shih-chieh?
A love letter from my wife
It's unintelligible
XX till dawn
A letter!
What do you mean "XX is powerful"?
My brush
You didn't write it...
properly
Let me teach you again at home
Halt!
What's going on?
Have you had enough fun?
Come on, slap!
Don't! Who dares to slap my husband?
Slap!
Oh, no!
Brazen!
Brazen! There's order in Court
Go away!
Let him go
Maltose
You promised to obey me!
Take care of the baby you carry,
if not yourself
Maltose! Go now!
Good
Wait for me!
Fu, go home and get the letter
I'd be a beast
if I didn't take revenge!
Good, I'll give you a chance
After the torture, you'll be paraded
to arouse public attention
Wake me up when it comes to 100!
Yes, Your Honor!
Ho Yu-ta
Mind you may not live
to spend the 5000 taels
Crazy! When have I got the money?
If I had taken it, I'd have retired!
You've to go on if you did take it!
I don't have it, so I'm here
I took it
You did?
Darling, you took the money?
The money from the Chief Secretary?
How could you have taken it?
Hold it...!
How did he know about this?
Never mind, just let him go
No...
If I do, I'd be under more suspicion!
We must persist to the end!
Have you found that letter?
No, madam
I've searched the whole room
without finding it
Oh, bad, Madam!
Master's being put on parade!
Mrs Sung... forget it...
I'd better give up
Just say yes or no!
I...
Get going!
Master!
Why're you here? Run quick!
Wait for me!
And you've brought a group!
Withstand for me
Open attacks are resistible,
but not sniping
O-Mei swordplay?
Hell with you!
Hell with you, bastard!
You've broken the bag
I've kept for years!
Are you alright?
Darling!
Darling, is it coming?
Hell...
Help!
Take Sung Shih-chieh away!
Yang!
We can't win, run!
Darling, don't scare me
You're...?
Here
Delivering?
Yes!
Terrible!
Go over, quick!
Protect the prisoner
If he dies, you'll all suffer
Stand back...
Harder! Will be over soon...
Retreat!
Darling!
Darling
Out? Is it out?
Master, madam has given birth!
Wet nurse, has it got a bird?
No
Why're you here?
For a celebration drink
What? You visit prisoners or
get jailed here
Never mind him. He can't try tricks
Secretary Sung,
you've sacrificed too much
Sure
Now my only wish is...
for a child with a bird
A bird for a girl?
What? Say that again
My wife have given birth to a daughter?
Yes!
So God has given me a little favor
What can I do for you, please?
Break jail
I won't do anything against the law
Creep!
How did Yang Hsiu-chen's brother die?
An accident
The fan owner can prove it
Don't deceive yourself
as it's against Heaven
Don't fail the people
as it's failing yourself
There's hope for us now!
Who's he?
Also a creep
A mandarin's a creep, but he's honest
His wife left him
because he accepts no bribes
His dedication won him...
quick promotions
and he's now...
An Inspector General
A saviour! What are we to do now?
You, not we!
Intercept him and
petition to him on the way
It's alright for you...
to sacrifice for justice
Absolutely alright
Good
Thank you!
Hand it over to him in person
Take care!
You're now in a dangerous situation
No, it's closely guarded here
Outsiders can't enter freely
You must've braved many difficulties...
getting here
But...
I got in only
after saying something casual
Good! I know you're okay!
Don't be mushy!
Let's get down to important business
Go now!
Good, I'll take my leave
What's there to see?
To see somebody
See if you can stay alive!
Just his luck
He got pursued even in a parade
It will be disastrous if he dies
If he dies, you can't bear it,
Your Honor
I know
What are you doing?
What is it, Lord?
Go and give chase
No point in chasing now
It won't get us anywhere
Give chase!
He's passed out! Wake him up quick!
Sung Shih-chieh, are you alright?
Walk 2 steps to show me
What on earth are you up to?
You told me to do that!
Clap your hands now!
Clap your hands now
Why're you clapping? What's so exciting?
Your mom's pregnant?
Is he really mad?
Sung Shih-chieh is mad...
Sung Shih-chieh is mad in jail!
Really? Why has he suddenly got mad?
Halt!
Sit down!
What are you up to?
Do you recognize...
that woman holding a baby
No
Are you sure?
Hold it!
Good!
Idiot...!
Darling, they say you're mad
Is it true?
Are you up to something again?
Who are you speaking...
upside down?
Come on, take him out for torture
See how long you can hold on
So you can still hold on
Good! Let me give you another kick!
Give it back to me!
Why have you taken away my daughter?
Quiet! I know what to do
Sung, both women claim...
to be mother to the daughter?
How would you handle it?
Why ask me? Making fun of me?
I'm soliciting...
your personal view only
for my reference
Don't make fun...
of your own daughter
Chop it into two and
each gets a share
Are you mad?
She's your daughter too!
You've a share too
Have I? Cut it into three pieces
I'll take the middle portion
Moustachio, have you got a share?
Yes!
Secretary
Sung, split it into four portions
Be fair to make them equal
Good!
I'll chop...
Chop...
Darling, are you crazy?
It's your daughter!
What're you two up to?
You're mad!
Sung Shih-chieh, a wise man like you
has ended up this way
No point in jailing you any more
I order that
you and your family be expelled
and all your assets confiscated
Keep away...!
You'll get mad if you stay alive!
See if you can sue me any more!
Out of the way! Don't look!
Madam
Leave everything behind except
what you're wearing
You're cocky
Dropped!
We'll seize everything...
you drop
How come he's come to such a state?
Anyway, he's still my husband
Darling!
Quiet!
Let's go
Yes!
Madam, are you alright?
Yes
I was thinking
he never said "I love you"
since I married him over 10 years ago
Sorry!
I love you!
A relapse!
Let me knock him unconscious
Maniac!
He's only acting mad. Give a hand
Come on quick!
Where's my daughter?
Master
Show me my daughter
Come...
Look, she's plumper than her wet nurse
One nest for one bird
Look how cute she is
Master, you acted brilliantly
Even I got taken in!
If I couldn't even fool you,
I'd jump to the sea!
If I didn't act mad,
I couldn't stay alive
But now they've to die instead of me
Darling,
Look!
The letter!
How come it's with you?
It has been with me
Why didn't you hand it to the magistrate
He accepts bribes to pervert justice
He would've destroyed any evidence
I presented to him
In fact, I'm waiting for a chance
for the appearance
of the Inspector General
to punish all the corrupt officials
Innocence, Your Honor!
How dare you block the Lord?
Whatever your grievance, 30 slaps first
30 slaps for that?
So it's you!
Bureaucratic conspiracy!
He's notorious...
for his sharp practice
He even acted mad to deceive me
How could you a magistrate...
spoil a bachelor?
He won't take me...
a magistrate seriously
He even claimed that
even Your Excellency
I'll be straight, Your Excellency!
Combined with us,
are not his match
Bastard!
How can a bachelor outsmart us?
My Lord,
many bet heavily that
Sung Shih-chieh will win this case
Good!
Let me see how capable Sung is
Court!
Summon Sung Shih-chieh and
party concerned!
Make an autograph...
We must win by every means
Thank you
Make an autograph!
Thanks for your support
Thank you
Inspector General!
Listen,
you're no longer a bachelor
Kneel down before the Inspector General
It shows your contempt to Court
Since you Lords insist on superficiality
I don't mind kneeling down
Nonsense! It befits propriety
to respect Court officers
The respect comes...
from the heart only
Don't you agree, Lord?
Sung Shih-chieh!
You've my permission not to kneel
Thank you, My Lord!
How did the couple...
murder Yang's husband?
Lord Ho, how did her husband die?
Yang...
She made her husband die...
bleeding from nostrils
Inspector General, you hear that
Summon Chen Erh
Announce your occupation to the Lords
An undertaker of Shansi, My Lord!
The cause
of Hsiu-chen's husband's death, please?
Deadly poison, as the autopsy shows it
What? Say that again loudly!
Deadly poison
You're wicked, you murdered my husband!
Don't cry, don't just cry!
You could be the one doing it!
Yes!
You could've put the poison!
Yes...
If it's true, you'll suffer
Me?
Make way!
You!
Someone died tragically...
in your area of jurisdiction,
but you didn't care
Isn't that your responsibility?
Blast...!
Why're you scared like that?
You aren't the murderer, are you?
No, Mr and Mrs Yao
Innocence, Your Honor! Innocence!
No,
it's been proved Yao Erh died
of deadly poison
and you claimed his wife
caused his death
Why did you lie
if you were free from suspicion?
He died of blood-emitting
It could be poison or
mental stimulation
No more subterfuge
Please arbitrate, Your Honor
Even if Yao Erh did die of poisoning,
there's no proof...
the Yao couple did it
Right!
Right he is!
Summon Hsiao Mei!
Come on!
Hsiao Mei greeting the Lords!
Hsiao Mei
Are you Hsiao Mei?
Where were you when the murder occurred?
Since madam disappeared,
I returned to the country
You were on the spot. Tell the truth
No, I was not on the spot!
How could you go back on your words now?
You told me
they poisoned my husband to death
and to run away
Why're you backing out on your remark?
I didn't
Besides...
Enough!
You may go home and retire. Thank you
Your Honor!
Sung Shih-chieh
Not yet your turn
Hsiao Mei, you go on
I'm madam's personal maid
Normally she was tough...
to her husband
You...
Sometimes she brought in some hooligans
I wasn't on the spot
on the day of the accident
But the previous night I heard her
quarreling fiercely with master
The following day master died
What've you to say, Sung Shih-chieh?
Bad!
Your Honor, now the truth is out
Yang Hsiu-chen murdered her husband
Sung framed others for it
Counsel Sung, you've got more than that
Your Honor is superb!
Here's a letter
It was written...
by Shansi Chief Sec to Ho Yu-ta
I got it perchance and copied it
The contents?
Really exciting
To cover up...
his sister's murder,
he bribed Ho Yu-ta with 5000 taels
to turn a blind eye to it
Your Honor, the letter only illustrated
to me the case with the request
that I judged it fairly
Where's it now?
Already burnt up
Read this letter then
Hold it!
You claimed to have copied it
It could be false
The one I copied has been sent
to Lord Ho
The one I'm now holding is the original
There's no proof
whether it's true or false
Check the handwriting. Your Honor!
Right!
Hold it!
What do you want?
Peepers of an official document...
will have their eyes gouged out
Is that right, Your Honor?
Yes, there's such a clause
If you did peep at it,
have your eyes gouged out
If you do it yourself,
we'll believe you
Don't you agree,
Inspector General?
Yes
Gouge your eyes out!
Can this be done
to any other part of the body?
Brazen! Observe order in Court
Use the torture!
Are you going to do it or not?
No!
You're guilty of false accusation and
insult to Court officers then
What punishment according to law,
Your Honor?
Hook his tongue
Have the torture ready!
Sung, either you gouge your eyes or
hook your tongue
There's no other choice
Darling
Use torture!
Hold it!
Who said that?
Me!
What is it?
Someone defecates
Who?
Me!
My daughter defecates
Your Honor, please allow us
to change her diaper
Nonsense, how can this be done in Court?
You...
Lord Ho has been gassing
Why're officers allowed to gas
but the people banned from defecating?
What justice is that? Please comment
What justice is that?
And he gassed loudly
You may change
Thank you, Your Honor!
What now?
Be nice...
A daughter's a nuisance
She defecates more
Do more good then
All your sons are dead
Haven't I done any good?
Bitch, it was all your fault
No!
What? I haven't finished
You know nothing but crying
I've endured you long
You made my wife...
take up your case
and we're in a hell lot of trouble
Listen...
I really didn't...
Quiet! Now I'm the most innocent
Please...
which of you would care
to fling this for me?
I get no good return. Look, how pitiable
Please do me a favor by flinging it?
Anybody care to give a hand?
Observe order in Court!
Who is it now?
Who else could it be?
Me?
Lord Ho, you're a scholar
Behave in court
Forget it!
Be careful!
Be nice, don't cry!
Darling, come here!
How come there's one ingot of silver?
It's Lord Ho's
Why is my silver with you?
Why's Lord Ho's silver with you?
There's a reason. Don't ask me!
Tell us
I can't
Why not?
No, it's only between you and me
You...
You seduced my wife
Me?
You old dog,
you seduced his wife
I didn't
Don't deny!
Tramp, confess or
I'll drown you
OK. Ho bought a house and
I earned a commission as the middleman
When did I buy a house?
Why not?
Remember the female impersonator Huang
Female impersonator Huang, a womaniser?
How did Lord Ho know him?
No, it was Mrs Ho who bought it
When did you buy it from him?
I didn't, master
You women are heartless
Lord Ho works so hard
and doesn't earn much
But you spent his money on a man...
How much did you pay for it?
5,000 taels
You spent 5,000 taels on a man?
Don't listen to them
Where've I got 5,000 taels?
You don't have the money?
I dared not take it,
but you spent it on a man
I didn't spend any cent of it
You didn't?
You lie!
You didn't spend Chief Sec's money
How could it be with my wife?
Crazy!
The Chief Sec's money is still inside
His money is inside!
Mrs Ho, sorry for the trouble
You may go home and retire
Your Excellency must've heard it clearly
Sung, even if I did
give Magistrate Ho 5000 taels
you can't sue me for bribery
Isn't it OK for me to send him a gift?
The letter can show
whether it was a bribery
Dare you still mention that letter?
Just now you deliberately
changed the subject
I forgot to accuse you
of unauthorized reading
and the penalty
of eye-gouging and tongue-hooking
Come on, execute!
Bullshit!
It was not a document,
When did I read the document?
only a piece of white paper
He lies, Your Honor!
Brazen!
You lie in Court
For lying in Court, the penalty is
50 slaps according to the law of Ching
I'd be delighted to get the penalty
Even 2 more blows are OK with me
But...
here's the genuine document
I brought here
I didn't read it and deserve no penalty
And you're guilty of...
Keep cool...
Stealing the document?
100 spanks plus 5 years in exile,
according to law
Sung Shih-chieh!
I expected that and couldn't care less!
If you hadn't read that letter,
how could you have accused me of bribery
Come on, what have you to say?
We're winning...
Frankly, it was my hypothesis only
Your Honor, what is the penalty for
hypothesis in Court according to law?
Nil
Luck's with me
But I'm ready to bear the other crime
Isn't it appropriate for Lord Tien...
to clarify himself now?
Why not read out loudly
the contents of this letter?
If my hypothesis is wrong and
damaging to the Lords,
I'll be condemned and
my whole family and I are ready...
to be beheaded
Yes!
Lord Tien, please read it
Are you shy? Let me
Lord Ho, better you read it
I dropped something
Let me pick it up first
I'll wait
It takes some time. It dropped again...
Sit down
I shouldn't have made you read it
You must be illiterate
Since no one would read it,
please read it, Your Honor
You're justice
Don't pick any more! Time off!
Pick it once again
Shall I read it or not?
Read it later
OK, read it later, Your Honor!
Better not read it, okay?
Yes
Sung Shih-chieh, what do you want?
Spitting and prosecution
First, you Shansi Magistrate
for negligence
Someone died a tragic death...
in the area of your jurisdiction and
you ignored it
And you Chief Sec for covering up
your sister's murder
And you Canton Magistrate Ho Yu-ta
for accepting bribes to pervert justice
and for gassing wantonly
And you too
Me?
No? You as Inspector General are
muddle-headed and indulgent
to your subordinates
Though you're famous for your honesty,
you've aroused much complaint
If this is brought to the Court,
your whole family will be involved
Counsel Sung is superb!
Adjourned!
Mrs Sung, feeling good?
Okay
Here
Mr Sung, feeling good?
Let me...
Any other complaint, Mr Sung?
Your sister is a killer
She's no good to live
Chop her dead
Are you serious?
Yes
Mr Sung, what about us?
What about us?
Chop you all!
Mr Sung!
You stand so high
How can I hear you?
Mr Sung, you've been reinstated
And we don't deserve death, do we?
Right...
Why ask me? I don't know
Ask His Honor!
Your Honor!
Discharged pending investigation?
Yes...
Please
Thank you
As to myself...
Go on
Everything must proceed
according to rule
Here's an ideal position. Come...
What do you think I should do, Mr Sung?
You've fully observed the rules
So nice!
Yes!
I won't sue you
Let's go
Darling, who are they?
Mandarins!
Oh, mandarins!
Superb!
Darling,
you helped Yang solve the case
Now you needn't worry
about children without birds
Now I resent too many kids with birds
Come...
Come over...
Bow to the brothers!
Come!
Hurry up!
Be nice!
Hold it!
What's wrong?
The feng shui seems to have moved
Where?
Over there
Better...
Okay
Are you ready?
Yes
Turn!