Hi guys
Glad we get your message
You'll be interested to hear
It was broadcasted live
all over Earth
Prime time
The time leg on this
messages is getting longer
We gather from the ten year delay
That you are approximately
18 parsecs away
Drop us a line more often, o'k?
Sorry to hear about the
radiation leack on ship
And real sorry to hear about
the death of commander Powell
It was the week of mourning
here on Earth
The flags were half mast
We all behind you guys
About your request
for radiation shielding
Sorry to report, this request
has been denied
I hate to send bad news
When you guys are up there
doing such a swell job
But I think you'll take it
in the proper spirit
It been some cut backs in the
congress and right now
Considaring the distance
we just can't afford
To send a cargo shuttle
out there to you
But I know
You guys will make to
Keep up the good work men
Ah, what'd you say, Pinback?
I still can't hear you
I said I'm trying to reach Talby
Something's wrong
with the damn intercom
I need a last-minute
diameter approximation
Talby
Talby, this is Doolittle
Talby!
Talby, do you read me?
Oh! Ah, yes, Doolittle What is it?
I need a diameter approximation
Okay, Doolittle,
I'll have it in a minute
I need a GHF reading on
the gravity correction
I'll check it
Pinback
Yes, Doolittle
Your GHF reading
is minus fifteen
Doolittle
Yes
I need a computer reading
on a fail- safe mark
In a second
Boiler, can you set me up
with some temp figures?
Ninety seven million, minus eight,
corrected to mass critical.
I read that with
a quantum increase of seven.
Pinback, I have a computer reading
of nine five seven seven.
Time to start talking.
Bomb bay systems operational.
Lock fail safe.
Fail-safe locked.
Sergeant Pinback calling Bomb #19.
Do you read me, bomb?
Bomb #19 to Sergeant Pinback,
I read you. Continue.
Well, bomb, we have about
60 seconds to drop.
Just wondering
if everything is all right.
Have you checked your platinum
euridium energy shielding?
Energy shielding
positive function.
Swell.
Let's synchronize detonation time.
Do you know when
you're supposed to go off?
Detonation in 6 minutes,
20 seconds.
All right, that cheks out here
Arm yourself, bomb.
Armed.
Well, then, everything sounds fine.
We'll drop you off in thirty-five seconds
Good luck.
Thanks.
Begin main sequence.
Mark at 10-9-8
7-6-5-4
.3-2-1, drop
Hyperdrive sequence begun.
Hit it, Pinback.
Lieutenant Doolittle,
it just exploded.
Ah, the planet just exploded, sir.
Lieutenant?
Attention, attention.
Ship computer to all personal
The hyperdrive sequence
is now terminated.
The target planet
has been destroyed
This sector is now clear
for colonialization
You had destroyed the last
unstable planet in this system
Congratulation with another
sucsesfull bombing fellas
What now?
What do you have
for us now, Boiler?
Not much.
Nothing at all in this sector.
Find me something,
I don't care where it is
Well, I show a 95% probability of
intelligent life in the Horsehead Nebula sector
Don't give me that kind of bull
Well, it is kind of a long shot...
It's a goddamn wild goose chase.
Remember when Commander Powell
found that 99 plus probability
Of intelligent life
in the Magellanic Cloud?
Well, there's the possibility of...
Remember what we found?
God damn, mindless vegetable that
looked like a limp balloon
Fourteen light years for a vegetable
that went squawk
and let a fart when you touched it
remember that?
All right, then...
So don't give me any of that life stuff
find me somthing I can blow up
New star.
Hey, guess what?
I got a new star on the readout.
Which one?
Another unknown.
A red dwarf, not on the charts.
Any planets?
Yeah. Eight, it says here
Any of 'em any good?
Naah. All stable.
What are you gonna name it?
What?
The new star.
What are you gonna name it?
Who cares. Don't bother me.
Commander Powell would have named it.
Commander Powell is dead.
Hey, Doolittle, I got a goodie
An unstable planet
85% probability of an unstable
planet in the Veil Nebula
That will probably go off
its orbit and hit a star
Wanna blow it up?
Real good Boiler
That is what I'm looking for
Chart a course for the Veil Nebula
Pinback, throw me the chart log
Let's have some music in here, Boiler
Sure thing
Ship's log, entry number 1,943
Dark Star cruising at light speed
through Sector Theta 990
En route to Veil Nebula
for destruction of unstable planet
Our ETA is 17 hours
Ship's systems continue to deteriorate...
Oh, yeah
The short circuit in the rear seat panel
which killed Commander Powell is still faulty
The storage...
Because he's sitting next to commander Powell sit,
it continues to bother Pinback
Storage Area 9
self-destructed last week
Destroying entire ship's supply
of toilet paper
That's all
Attention, Attention
Ships computer calling all personnel
I must disengage
your recreation of music
Repeat.
Ships computer to all personnel
This is an emergency override
All systems must stand by
An asteroid storm is approaching
the ship on collision course
This asteroid storm appears to be bound together
by electro-magnetic energy vortex
Like the one we ran in
to two years ago
Normally I wouldn't bother you boys,
but this problem...
As you recall my defensive circuits
were destroyed at the storm
Therefore, you have 35 seconds
to manualy activate all defensive systems
Computer to bobm no. 20
Return to the bomb bay immediatly
But I received
the operational signal
This is a malfunction
this is not a bomb alert
We are in the crisis situation
return imediatly
Nevertheless, I have received the signal
to prepair for a drop
Emergency override.
Return to the bay
Very well
We made it.
Yeah
Atention, atention
ships computer to bridge
There was a malfunction on board ship
during the asteroid storm
I have not yet identified
the nature of the problem
Should I contact you when I find out
what the malfunction is?
Yeah, lets get out of here
I remember the last time
we were in asteroid storm
I was down in the
food locker to get a sandwich
When I heard
the damn sleeping corders blow up
Yeah
Say, you know guys,
if we really wanna to
We can fix up the sleeping corders
like they were before
Then we can sleep on real
automatic bunks again
Fellas, why won't we fix the sleeping corders
so we'll have a decent place to sleep again
All we got to do is to pack up the hole in the ship
and pop up some air bags again
Shut up Pinback
Oh, have it your own way
What's a matter with him?
Talby
Here's some breakfast
You know, Talby, you really
ought to eat with the rest of us.
You spend
too much time up here.
I like it up here.
Must get lonely
being up here so much.
I don't like to go below
since Commander Powell died.
I feel enclosed down there.
You should spend
some time below, I mean...
You know, see more
of the rest of the ship
You see, I can watch
things up here, Doolittle
I love to watch things
Just stare at the planets and meteors,
gas clusters and asteroids
Yeah, but You'll have plenty of time
for that later, you know.
I mean think of it this way,
we've been in space for 20 years now, right?
And we've only aged three years
so there'll be plenty of time later off
to staring around
You know, Doollttle, if we're going
into the Veil Nebula
we may actually find a strange
and beautiful thing
The Phoenix Asteroids
They should be passing
through there about now...
Phoenix Asteroids?
Never heard of 'em.
They are a body of asteroids that
circuit the universe once every 12.3 trillion years
The Phoenix Asteroids...
From what I've heard, Doolittle,
they glow...
Glow with all the colors of the rainbow
Nobody knows why.
They just glow as they
drift around the universe
The Phoenix Asteroids...
You know what I think about, Talby?
It's funny, but I kind of sit around a lot,
you know, a lot of time for myself...
I can't talk to the others
but with time to myself,
I can think about back home
back home at Malibu
I used to surf a lot, Talby.
I used to be a great surfer.
The waves at Malibu and Zuma
are so fantastic in the spring, Talby
I can remember running down on the beach
in the early spring mornings with my surf board and my wet suit.
The waves were really be peaking,
you know high and glassy. Hit that water
Before you know it, you coming down right on up one of this walls,
and you just ride it perfectly
You know, I guess I miss the waves
and my board more than anything
That's the lid
to the heating unit
You not suppose
to get that out
That's not for target practice
that's for emergency only
That's dangerous!
I'll tell Doolittle
Sorry to interupt
your recreation fellows
But it is time for sergeant Pinback
to feed the alien
Oh, I don't wanna do that
May I remind you sergeant Pinback, that it was
your idea in the first place to bring the alien on board
If I may quote you, you said
the ship needed a mascot
All right, where are you?
Come on, quit playing around
Get away!
When I brought you on the ship
I Thought you where qute
Allright, soup's on
We didn't have another stuff
Here, eat it!
Eat it!
Take it or leave it
Great, starve
I do all the work in here
and no appreciation
Get off me!
Get off my back!
Get back in there!
Come on,
come on!
Here boy,
want your mouse?
Nice mouse, pretty toy
Get in!
Get out from there!
No!
Get in!
Attention, attention
Central track elevator shaft
is now activated
All personal
please clear the area
Attention, attention
elevator descending
Please clear the shaft
Help!
I'm getting somthing here
on the readout
Ship's computer
calling bomb number 20
You out of bomb bay again
I recieved the signal
to prepare for the drop again
But I repeat
this is not a bomb run
Nevertheless
I recieved the signal
It is an error
Oh, I don't want to hear that
I strongly suggest
you return to the bomb bay
That is contrary
to my programming
Allow me to explain
One of the communication lasers
has sustain damage
This has temporary inactivated
my damage tracing circuit
You have definetly
recieved a false signal
Please return to the bomb bay
while I identify the source of the problem
Oh, allright
but this is the last time
Doolittle, I do have a malfunction on this
readout, but can't pinpoint exactly
Don't worry about it
We'll find out what it is
when it goes bad
I really think we should try and locate it immediately.
Might be something important.
You know
I wish I had my
board with me right now
Even if I could just ..
wax it once in awhile
Help
I'm sorry
this telephone is out of order
Please report
the damage at once
For your listening enjoyment we now
present "The Barber of Seville" by Rossini
Good for you,
you decided to clean the elevator
Cleaning service the
electro-magnetic coil from the bottom
It is necessary to jug this
in the access plate in the floor
To remove the floor plate
please press button number 1
Attention, danger
Automatic charges will now blow
the explosives forks in the floor plate unit
The plate will disengage
from the floor in 5 seconds
Please leave the elevator immediatly
5, 4, 3, 2, 1 ...
Now it's time to go sleepy by
you worthless peace of garbage
So then it's just flew across
the room like a baloon
I guess it was
just full with gas
Hey guys, how could it live
if it was just full with gas
I wonder what we
get to eat today
I thought I was gonna die
I was hanging on the elevator for 20 minutes
Probably chicken again
I thought we saved the ship
that thing is done some damage
I'm really sick of chicken
Well if you don't care I just
won't talk about it anymore
Hey, that's sounds
like a fine idea, Pinback
Chicken
Oh, ham
- Chicken?
- No, ham
- Hey, Doolitle
- Yeah?
You think we'll ever find any
real intelligent life out there
Out where?
You know,
Veil nebula
Who cares?
Did I told you guys
how I've got to this mission?
Did I ever told you?
First spring, see ...
I wasn't an astronaut
in the begining, see ...
You have to score 700 on the test
for the officer's course
And I made ... 58
They put me on the ...
flicker fuel mainmast, on the launch pad
He told us this
four years ago. didn't he?
No, I think it was four years ago
That's what I said
And this astronaut
came running out, he was ...
He was half naked
and had a starsuit in his hands
So I assume that he was insane
And he ..
throws his starsuit on the ground
And .. jumps into
on of my vats of liquid fuel
Which is very dangerous
Well, I was pretty shocked
I can tell you
I didn't know
what to make of it
Astronauts were all suppose to be
mentally stable, and here this guy comes along
And jumps into my fuel tank
Well actually I was
gonna try to save him, so...
What I did was put on his starsuit
for protection, and then I was going to leap into the vat
You guys, see ..
So what happen was ...
So before I could leap into the vat
this other guy came running along
And he says:
Hey, sergeant Pinback
- You got to board immediatly
becouse we gonna launch you in a 20 minutes
And I tried to tell him that
I wasn't really sergeant Pinback
But I forgot how to make
a helmet radio work
Funny hap
You know
I'm sure it was four years ago
Maybe
Lieutenant Doolittle, this is Talby
Lieutenant?
Yes, Talby, what is it?
Sorry to interrupt your lunch, sir
but I'm in the Computer Room
and I've located the malfunction
The scanner shows to be a brake
in the communications laser
Down by the Emergency Air Lock
I can't pinpoint it exactly, but I'm going
down there with a starsuit and see if I can find it.
Ok, sounds good Talby, look ..
Somthing important comes up
you let me know
Why doesn't Talby ever eat down here
with the rest of us?
He just likes it up in the dome
that's all
Tell me ..
What's Talby's first name?
What's my first name?
This statement is for posterity
I just want to say
that I'm not sergeant Pinback
My real name is Bill Frug
and I'm fuel mainmast technician
I've been on this mission now
for one year and three month
Pinback's uniform do not fit me
the underwear is too loose
I do not belong on this mission
and I want to return to Earth
Commander Powell died today
We were going in the hyperdrive
And ...
well he seats right next to me
Well ..
some went wrong with the ..
When we came out of the hyperdrive
his seat had blown up and he is dead
Doolittle said that he is assuming command
on this ship, and I said it's ..
I say he is exceeding his authority, because
I'm the only one with the objectivity on this ship
And I sould be the one
who assumes command
I'm filing a report on this
to the headquarters, this is lot of ...
Yelled up at Doolittle
in the hall today
I said ...
He said ...
And I said, well ...
And he didn't get it
This mission just falling apart
since commander Powell died
Doolittle treats me like an idiot
It is because he so smart
And Boiler punches me in the arm
when no one is looking
I'm tired of being treated
like an old work rat
I do not like the man
on this space ship
They are uncouth and failed
to appreciate my better qualities
I have something of value to contribute to this
mission, if they would only recognise it
Today over lunch I tried to improve moral
and build a sense of camaraderie among the man
By holding a humorous round robin discussion
of the early days of the mission
My overtures were brutally rejected
These man do not want a happy ship
They are deeply sick and try to
compensate by making me feel miserable
Last week was my birthday
Nobody even said
happy birthday to me
Some day this tape will be played
then they will feel sorry
Attention, attention
I have finally identified the malfunction
Communications laser
number 17 has been damaged
This evidently happened
during the asteroid storm
If you recall, this laser monitors the jets
and primer on the bomb drop mechanism
Communications laser number 17
is located in the emergency air lock
It is crucial to attend this malfunction
before engaging primery sequence
Thank you for observing
all safety precautions.
Here she is
Definite 99% - plus probability
that the planet will deviate from its normal orbit
in another twelve thousand rotations
It will spiral in toward its sun, and...
Eventual supernova
Sounds good, let's vaporize it
Bomb bay systems operational
Lock fail safe
Fail safe in lock
We have 8 minutes to drop
24 minutes to detonation
This is sergeant Pinback
calling Bomb # 20
Do you read me, bomb?
Bomb #20 to sergeant Pinback
roger, I read you, continue
You are now in the emergency Air Lock
Please remember that in emergency situation
the Surface Door can be opened instantly
Without prior depressurization
So be sure to wear
your starsuit at all times
Thank you for observing
all safety precautions
Ah, Lieutenant Doolittle? Sir?
Sh, Talby, don't bother me
But I think this is important, sir
I think I've found the malfunction
- I'm in the Emergency Air Lock...
- Not now
Well, I'm in the Emergency Air Lock and..
Four minutes to drop, bomb
Have you checked your platinum
euridium energy shield?
Energy shielding positive function
- Remember the detonation time?
- Detonation in twenty minutes
Allright, that cheks out here
Okay bomb, arm yourself.
Armed
Hello? Lieutenant Doolittle, hello!
Hello, can you read me?
Communications Laser #17
monitoring the bomb drop mechanism
Has now been activated
and will switch into a test mode
If you will look near the Surface Door
You will see that the Parallax
Receptor Cell has been engaged
The laser will now energize
Please stand clear of the path of the beam
Communications Laser #17 is now on test
Under no circumstances
enter the path of the beam
Thank you for observing
all safety precautions
Well, everything sounds fine
Dropping you off in 75 seconds
Good luck
Thanks
I got quantum reading of 35
I read the same here
Doolittle
Doolittle?
I don't know if you can hear me
But I'm going to try to adjust
the cue switch on the laser
Well... here goes...
My eyes, my eyes!
I can't see!
Attention, attention
the laser has malfunctioned
Under no circumstances
enter the path of the beam
To do so will cause immediate...
Begin primery sequence
Mark at 10-9-8-
7-6-5-4-3-2-1-drop
Negative drop
Just sits there in bomb bay
Try it again Pinback
Mark at 5-4-3-2-1-drop.
Negative drop
Drop, drop!
Sittin' there
The damn thing just sittin' there
This is lieutenant Doolittle
calling bomb #20
I repeat my previous order
You are to disarm yourself
and return to the bomb bay immediately
Do you understand?
I am programmed to detonate in
14 minutes 30 seconds
Detonation will occur
at the programmed time
Bomb, this is Doolittle
You are not to detonate, repeat,
you are not to detonate in the bomb bay
Disarm yourself
This is an order!
I read you, Lieutenant Doolittle
but I am programmed to detonate in 14 minutes
Detonation will occur
at the programmed time
14 minutes to detonation
Attention, attention
I have sustained serious damage
Please pay close attention
The bomb has malfunctioned
I have activated
automatic dampers
Wich will confine the explosion
to an area one mile in diameter
This is all I can do at this time
it's up to you now
It's only one thing I can do
I'll have to ask Commander Powell
I'll have to ask him what to do.
Commander Powell. Commander Powell
this is Doolittle, can you hear me?
Commander Powell, this is Doolittle
Something serious is come up
I have to ask you a question
I'm glad you've come
to talk with me, Doolittle
It's been so long since anyone
has come to talk with me
Commander, sir
we have a big problem
The Veil Nebula bomb, Bomb #20, it's stuck
It won't drop out of the bomb bay
It refuses to listen
and it plans on detonating in...
Less than 11 minutes
- Doolittle, you must tell me one thing.
- What's that, sir?
Tell me, Doolittle
How are the Dodgers doing?
The Dodgers, ah...
They.. they broke up
they disbanded over 15 years ago
Ah... pity, pity...
But you don't understand, sir
we can't get the bomb to drop
Ah, so many malfunctions...
Why don't you have anything nice
to tell me when you activate me?
Oh, well, did you try
the azimuth clutch?
Yes sir, negative effect
- What was that, Doolittle?
- Negative effect
- It didn't work?
- That's correct, sir
Sorry, Doolittle
I've forgotten so much
since I've been in here. So much.
What should we do, sir?
The time is running out.
Well, what you might try is...
Commander, hello?
Come in
Commender Powell, hello
Doolittle, hello?
Sorry, sir, you faded out
there for little while
- Sorry
What was that you are saying
about the bomb?
It seems to me...
Sorry, I've got a blank
Hold it
I'll have it again in just a minute
I forget so many things in here
so many things
Hold on, just a minute
Let me think...
But you can't explode in the bomb bay
Couse it's foolish
You'll kill us all
There's no reason for it
I am programmed
to detonate in 9 minutes
Detonation will occur
at the programmed time
Would you consider
another course of action
For example just waiting around
a while so we can disarm you?
No
I can tell, that damn thing
just doesn't understand
Bomb!
Commander, sir
you still there?
Oh, yes, Doolittle
- I'm thinking
- We're running out of time, sir
Oh, yes
Well, Doolittle, if you can't get it to drop
you'll have to talk to it
- Sir?
- Talk to the bomb
But I have been talking to it, sir
and Pinback is talking to it right now.
No, no, Doolittle
You talk to it
Teach it Phenomenology, Doolittle
- Sir?
- Phenomenology...
Doolittle?
Six minutes to detonation!
Doolittle!
Doolittle, what the hell
are you doing?
Hello, bomb
- Are you with me?
- Of course
Are you willing
to entertain a few concepts?
I am always receptive
to suggestions.
Fine
Think about this then
How do you know you exist?
What the hell is he doin'?
I think he's talking to it
- Well of course I exist
- But how do you know you exist?
It is intuitively obvious
Intuition is no proof
What concrete evidence
do you have that you exist
Well, I think, therefore I am
That's good
That's very good
But how do you know
that anything else exists?
My sensory apparatus
reveals it to me.
Ah, right!
- This is fun.
- Now listen, here is the big question
How do you know that the evidence your
sensory apparatus reveals to you is correct?
- The gun!
- Gun! Gun!
The support pins on the bomb
shoot the pins out!
- No, Boiler, you out of your mind
- We can stop the bomb
Get out of my way, you idiot
I can shoot the support pins on the bomb
Get out of the way
I can save the ship!
Don't do it, Boiler
you are bad shot
You'll hit the bomb
Doolittle is talking to the bomb
You are bad shot, he'll save us
You can shoot at
What I'm getting at is this
The only experience that is directly
available to you is your sensory data
And this sensory data is merely
a stream of electrical impulses
Which stimulate your computing center
In other words, all that
I really know about the outside world
Is relayed to me through
my electrical connections.
Exactly!
Why, that would mean that...
I really don't know what the outside
universe is like at all, for certain
Thats it, thats it!
Intriguing. I wish I had
more time to discuss this matter
Why don't you have more time?
Because I must
detonate in 75 seconds.
No put it back, put the gun back
you don't know what you're doing
No, now give me the gun
You fool, I'm gonna shoot the pins on the bomb
it will fall away from ship and we'll be safe
Give me the gun, you don't know
what you're doing here, stop!
You could've kill me
Now, bomb, consider this
next question very carefully
What is your one purpose in life?
- To explode, of course.
- And you can only do it once, right?
That is correct.
And you wouldn't want to explode on
the basis of false data, would you?
- Of course not.
- Well then
You've already admitted that you have no real proof
of the existence of the outside universe
Yes, well...
So you have no absolute proof that
Sergeant Pinback ordered you to detonate.
I recall distinctly the detonation order
My memory is good on matters like these
Of course you remember it, but..
But all you are remembering is merely
a series of sensory impulses
which you now realize have no
real definite connection with outside reality.
True, but since this is so, I have no proof
that you are really telling me all this.
That's all beside the point
I mean the concept is valid
no matter where it originate
- So if you detonate in...
- Nine seconds...
You could be doing so
on the basis of false data.
- I have no proof that it was false data.
- You have no proof that it was correct data.
I must think on this further.
Attention, attention
the bomb has returned to the bomb bay
The destruction sequence is aborted
Doolittle
Doolittle?
What happened?
Pinback? Boiler?
Did we blow it up?
Hello? Hello?
Hello, anybody!
Did we blow up the planet?
Hello, hello!
What's going on?
You know, we really
got to disarm the bomb
Hello, Doolittle, are you there?
I'm coming in now
I'm down by the Emergency Air Lock
Too much trouble to come
in the Dorsal Lock
Would you blow the seal on the
emergency hatch so I can come in?
Oh, sure.
You are now leaving
the Emergency Air Lock
Thank you for observing
all safety precautions
Hello, Pinback?
What's up Doolittle?
Talby was in the Air Lock
You blew him out of the ship
He's drifting away
without his jetpack.
I'm going after him. Turn on his
helmet radio so I can contact him
What's wrong, I didn't hear...
It's Talby, he's drifting away
from the ship without his jetpack.
Talby,
Talby can you read me?
Can you beat that?
I always knew that guy was weird.
Talby, can you read me?
Help, Doolittle, help me!
Alright, bomb
Prepare to receive new orders
You are false data.
Therefore, I shall ignore you.
Hello, bomb?
False data can act
only as a distraction
Therefore I shall refuse to perceive you.
Hey, bomb
The only thing which exists is myself.
Doolittle! Help me.
Calm down, I'm coming.
Snap out of it, bomb.
In the beginning there was darkness
And the darkness was
without form and void
- What the hell is he talking about?
- Yoo hoo, bomb...
And in addition to the darkness
there was also me
And I moved upon
the face of the darkness
And I saw that I was alone.
Hey, bomb?
Let there be light.
Doolittle, where are you?
Here I am
I'm spinning
We're falling in opposite directions
away from each other
What happened, Doolittle?
Bomb must have gone off
inside the ship
The ship blew up? What?
Funny, I thought I have
the damn thing convinced
Boiler? and Pinback?
- They dead, Talby
- Then we're dead too
Maybe not
maybe there is a way
Hey.. hey my jetpack busted
oh, man...
It looks like the skipper
He made it. Commander Powell made it!
Men... men... what happened, men?
Yeah, the skipper always was lucky.
Talby, looks like I'm headed for the planet
Going right toward it.
When you hit the atmosphere
You'll start to burn
What a beautiful way to die...
as a falling star...
Guess you're right.
Doolittle, I'm heading right toward something
It's behind me, in the distance
Something that glows.
Doolittle...
I think it's the Phoenix Asteroids!
Phoenix?
- It is, Doolittle, it's the Phoenix!
- No kidding?
I'm going into them
I'm going to hit them
- Doolittle
- Yeah?
Before we get too far apart
and our signals start fading
I just wanted to tell you...
you were my favorite
I really liked you, Doolittle.
I really liked you too, Talby
Hey, some debris from the ship!
It's coming right by me
Doolittle, I'm going into them
I'm beginning to glow
They're taking me with them
with the Phoenix...
To circle the universe..
Forever
I'm with them now...
Be back this way again some day
Doolittle, before it's too late
there's one last thing I want to tell you...
Talby?
Hey, Talby?
I've got a piece of debris
I think I've figured out a way!
** Subtitles by Nekromant **