Occupation: Politician
Jaran Jitthanya
Your Reverence, enter.
Please, wait here just a moment.
Tul, be careful!
Tul!
Tul! Tul!
You're awake!
Where am l?
Dr. Sruang's clinic.
What about Jaran?
He's dead.
Tul, how are you?
Don't get up yet!
OK, let me have a look
at your eyes, please.
When can I go home, doctor?
What are you in such a hurry for?
I don't like it here.
I don't like you being here either,
but you've been here
for nearly 3 months already.
You're really lucky.
In cases like this, only one
in a million survives.
The question is:
Will I be seeing everything
upside down forever,
or is it only temporary?
7 YEARS AND FlVE MONTHS EARLlER
You've got no girlfriend, so
keep these fish for now, Tul,
so you won't be lonely.
I copied this for you to read.
What's it about, Yut?
You'd better read it yourself.
It's weird as hell.
The author is a doctor,
but uses the pen name "Demon".
Gene-pools, Parasites
and Justice by Demon
This "Demon" is a total weirdo.
He says people
aren't born with any kindness
or any morals whatsoever
but are created from
evil as their foundation.
Selfishness...
There are evil genes in
control of the human body.
Therefore, in order to
take care of evil people,
one must take care of
the source of the evil.
That's why we must control
the evolution of human genes.
If we let the genes
evolve by themselves,
the strongest genes would
definitely be the winners.
However, those strongest genes
are likely to be the most evil ones.
Don't you think that's weird?
Hands up!
Freeze! Freeze!
This is the police!
Keep your hands on your head!
Don't move!
Get back towards the wall!
Turn your faces away!
Freeze!
Get your hands up on the wall!
Yut!
Excellent!
You're on your way
to the monkey house!
I had to train like a blind person
when I was a cop.
Yut told me I'd better train.
He said it had saved
his life many times
when he had to fight any
crooks in the dark.
Drop the gun!
Get up!
Tul,
may I have 15 minutes of your time?
Who are you?
I'm a lawyer for the owner
of the factory you raided.
What do you want?
Do you know who the
owner of the factory is?
The brother of a minister.
Whoever watched the news in
the entire country probably knows too.
Why?
In here is 5 million in cash.
Just drop the case and
all of this money is yours.
But the evidence was on national TV.
Oh, you mean that video clip?
Just tell them it was a fake
and it'll all be over.
I think you'd better go.
If 5 million isn't enough,
I'll make it 10.
Hey! You want go in with your boss?
Tul...
If you want to make a
simple issue into a complicated one,
that's fine.
"Demon" said...
Now our society is full of evil people.
Even if we had tougher laws or built
more jails it wouldn't be enough.
We've made enormous investments
in the criminal justice system,
only to realize that it
wasn't the answer.
Some experts say
education is the answer,
but we can already see
that the evil people
are all highly educated.
Taking care of evil with an eye for
an eye and a tooth for a tooth policy
could be the answer.
Justice doesn't exist in nature
but is something that humans developed.
This is the only true justice.
Miss!
Your keys.
Thank you!
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
Are you a cop?
Yes.
I like cops.
What's your name?
Yes?
Joy.
Hey, Dr. Sruang said you have to
finish all the medicine.
OK.
The woman's name is Joy.
I don't know.
OK, I'll wait.
Excuse me...
Where's the girl's body?
Not only do we have pictures,
we've got a video clip as well.
What do I have to do if I agree?
Make a statement that there isn't
enough evidence in this case.
We'll arrange the press
conference for you.
You only need to read the statement.
You don't need to give
interviews or anything.
However, my offer just changed.
You don't get any money.
OK?
Oh, there's one more thing you must do.
What?
You must apologize to the
minister's younger brother
at the press conference.
Dear Demon,
I used to believe that
humans were born with morals,
knowing what's right and
wrong and having compassion.
We've evolved much more than animals.
But now, I'm not so sure.
Perhaps, our world is really
full of evil people's genes.
Like you wrote in your
gene-pool article.
Day by day, the
fucking capitalist system
fosters the evil genes,
making them stronger
and able to propagate faster.
Until one day they'll destroy
everything like you said.
I've spent nearly two months in jail.
I've written many
letters to "The Demon",
but I never sent any of them.
I think I only wrote
them out of boredom,
but the last one I decided to send.
I really don't know anything.
They paid me 50000 to sleep with
you and wait till you were asleep.
Of course, I took it.
So how did you know
that I'd fall asleep?
- I spiked your drink.
- Yeah?
So then?
Then there were these two guys
who said they were your friends.
They wanted to pull a joke on
you before you got married.
I even wondered what kind
of sick joke is this?
They're heroin smugglers!
Cop killers!
Yet you helped them get away!
How could I have known?
I was just minding my own business.
At least you didn't actually die.
If you had, I'd feel
really bad about myself.
Chat, sir.
I'm sorry.
Tul, you've got visitors!
I'm "The Demon".
Yes.
Sruang Santiprasoert.
When I was in prison they
called me Dr. Sruang.
I got your letter a few days ago.
I didn't write in the letter
to ask you to visit me, did l?
Of course not,
but I have something
I'd like to discuss with you.
You'd better talk fast.
In fifteen minutes I have
to go clean the toilets.
OK.
I would like you to work with us.
You can see that
I'm in prison, right?
If you agree to work with us, then
I can get you out of
here within two weeks.
Do you know me?
You're the only cop who dared
to arrest the minister's brother.
I also know they tried
to shut your mouth,
but you wouldn't cooperate.
That's why you're here.
What kind of work do
you want me to do?
You don't have much time
let's make this quick.
I'm delighted to know
you've recovered.
Name, Art Dechawat, age 54.
He's the owner of a slaughterhouse.
His other businesses include
illegal liquor, human trafficking
and supplying girls to politicians.
Art Dechawat is the owner
of a slaughterhouse.
His primary business is illegal liquor.
His secondary business is
supplying girls to politicians.
He's been accused of contracting 3
murders, but got off each time
because of his influences within
the major political parties.
The slaughterhouse is only a front.
This is my first assignment after
I left Dr. Sruang's clinic.
I don't even know how I'll do it,
seeing everything upside down like this.
An expert assassin?
Yes.
We exterminate traitors,
drug dealers, pimps,
illegal loggers, stock
speculators, and tax evaders.
Most of them are either
politicians or businessmen.
But...
is it legitimate?
It depends on how you view legitimacy.
You're in jail because
you've been blackmailed.
Can you call that legitimate?
Are you the leader of
The Legion of Demons?
Oh... not at all.
No one knows who the leader is.
Even I don't know.
I don't even know if he's in Thailand.
So you're asking me
to become a hit-man?
We prefer the term "expert assassin".
I'm in jail because I didn't want to
cooperate with a gang of crooks.
What makes you think l'd
cooperate with another gang?
No!
Thin! Don't! Don't!
Let's go! Don't!
Go!
I'd like to resign.
What do you mean?
I don't know either.
Ever since I got shot,
I've had a bad feeling.
So what are you going to do?
I don't know.
Go upcountry and see my mother.
KLONG KWANG PRlSON
4YEARS AND 6 MONTHS AGO
What are you doing over here?
You got released today.
So I've come to pick you up.
To take me where?
Wherever you'd like to go...
I'll take you there.
I don't know.
Just a while ago I thought l
needed to find a toilet.
Would you mind drinking
whiskey from a coffee cup?
I haven't washed the glasses yet.
Who taught you to draw?
Nobody.
One day I saw a deaf person
drawing pictures to sell.
I thought it was beautiful
so I decided to draw some myself.
Did it take long to learn
to draw like this?
Not too long.
Don't tell me, this is you?
Yeah, that's me.
You look so sad in this one.
My name isn't really Joy.
Oh, what's your name then?
Tiwa.
The clients prefer a foreign name.
I'll just call you Tiwa.
I don't like foreign names.
How many years were you in prison?
Three.
If we just just kiss but don't have
sex, can you handle it?
Why?
Well...
We hardly know each other.
I don't want to rush.
No way...
Why did you ask if l'd
be able to handle it?
I don't know.
You've been in prison
for three years.
I don't know.
Well, let's try then.
Quit it, Tiwa.
If I quit, would you be
able to take care of me?
Yeah.
What would you do
to earn a living?
I don't know anything else
except shooting a gun.
So, should I become a hit-man?
Tiwa.
Let's get married.
But I'm not a good person.
I don't like good people.
They die fast.
Hello.
I'm glad you're home.
Who's this?
Hello.
I think you've got the wrong guy.
I don't think so.
Your name's Tul, right?
We know you've killed
lots of people,
but we want to know who ordered it.
I've never killed anyone.
There's no need for you
to deny it so quickly.
We found plenty of
evidence in your room.
You killed a member of
the Bamrungthai party.
A hit-man disguised as a monk,
assassinated in front of his house,
Jaran Jitthanya,
a famous M.P.
You savagely killed Sia Toi,
mafia boss of second hand cars.
You killed Sia Han, mafia boss of
the Loyfa gambling den in Wisuthkasat.
Hit-man of two savage assassinations.
Art Dechawat and his secretary
died in their room.
There... a picture of Art.
We found it under your sofa.
We know that you did everything.
Tell us, who ordered you to
kill all of those people?
That's it and we'll let you go.
Are you all cops or something?
Don't move!
Tul.
I'll ask you one more time, OK?
Who ordered you to
kill those people?
Who ordered it?
Tul.
I told you I didn't kill anybody!
Stop!
Drive!
Drive! Drive!
What are you looking at?
Keep driving!
Have you got anything to eat?
Got anything to eat?
I've got fried pork skin.
Where is it?
- Where is it?
- On the floor!
Where do you want me to drive to?
Where are you going?
Chumphon.
OK, let's go there.
Turn on the speakers
so I can hear it too.
Don't talk too long.
Hello?
Toh.
What's up?
Where are you?
I'm driving.
Oh yeah? Did you get the
pork skin I sent yet?
Yes, yes, I got it.
Was it good?
Hello?
Hello. It was delicious....
delicous.
Toh, I'm driving now.
I'll talk to you later.
OK.
Can I stop at a gas station?
I need to use the toilet.
Lunatic.
Comfortable, eh?
Please, I beg you...
Let go!
Is there a power failure?
Your boyfriend told
me to turn it off.
My boyfriend?
Uh... that guy.
Who said he's my boyfriend?
Well... I saw you came together.
Where's the power switch?
On the wall over there.
Usually, I'm not like this...
I just needed someone to drive for me.
I guess you usually ride a buffalo.
Is that why you can't drive?
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm not doing anything.
Stop the bleeding.
Thank you.
Where are we now?
Chumphon.
I'm sorry about hijacking you.
You can go now.
Aren't you afraid that
I'll turn you in?
I'm not afraid.
I'm sick and tired of a
life like this already.
So what's your name then?
Tul.
My name's Rin.
I haven't seen anything
like this for a long time.
My home's like this too.
So why don't you go home?
I can't go back.
Aren't you welcome there anymore?
Are you like this all the time?
Like what?
Snapping at anyone.
I only snap at crooks.
How come you think I'm a crook?
There's two kinds of people
who carry guns.
Cops and crooks.
You're not a cop,
so you must be a crook.
What's your name?
Tul.
Where are you from?
I've lost my way...
Your Reverence...
I was waiting for when
you'd get rid of it.
Do you know who I am?
I don't know and I don't want to know.
Wherever you've come from,
whatever you did, it doesn't matter.
You're in a temple, so you
should leave all your sins behind.
Leave your gun on the tray over
there and recite my prayers.
Yes, sir.
That's right, that's it.
I can't help being a bit jealous
of Tiwa on the day she left.
Jealous that she won't have to
live in this awful world anymore.
Jealous that she can rest,
while I still have to struggle on.
There's only one thing bothering me.
All that time I'd been with Tiwa,
I never knew she was on drugs.
I stayed with her
until the police arrived.
The police instantly
concluded it was an OD.
For days after I tried to inquire
about any progress in the case.
You know what the officer
in charge of the case told me?
He told me...
Hookers on drugs OD-ing
is quite common.
We see this daily.
I should've known it
would end like this.
Just because of that simple reason,
the case was closed.
Justice never existed in this world
since the beginning, Mr. Demon.
It's exactly like you said.
We have to make it ourselves.
Now I know
which direction my life will go.
Your Reverence, disrobe me please.
Why?
Someone's trying to kill me.
I'm wearing monk's robes and it'd
be a grave sin if I killed him.
Stop!
Go! Go! Go!
The pork skin's in the back.
You again?
What the hell are you talking about?
Did you leave the monk-hood already?
Fifteen minutes ago.
Why?
Someone's trying to kill me.
That's not unusual,
I'd like to kill you too.
So, now where would you like to go?
Back to Bangkok...
You'll have to find another car.
Don't worry, I won't hijack
you to Bangkok.
I can't go even if you hijack me.
Where's the jack?
What's a jack?
Is there a garage around here?
Yes, two kilometers from here.
Stay down! Stay down!
Don't go! Don't go! Rin!
Rin! Don't run!
Where are you going?
How come all of a sudden,
a cop became a crook?
How did you know?
I had a peek in your wallet.
I'm sorry.
Why? Wasn't the salary of a cop enough?
I didn't do it for the money.
I may have killed people,
but I'm not a crook.
If you don't believe
me, it doesn't matter.
I believe you.
The dead guy's name was Thin.
He was my assistant.
So why was he tracking
you down to kill you?
I think my boss sent him.
Maybe, you're of no use to them anymore.
That's why they'll
have to terminate you.
Right?
You think so?
I think it's worse than that.
Like what?
Perhaps I've got a bad
view of the world.
At first when you told me that...
you didn't want to work like this.
Then, when your girlfriend died,
the police weren't
interested in the case.
That's why you decided to do it...
because you wanted to get
revenge on the police.
It may have been a setup.
What does setup mean?
Is it possible that
your girlfriend was killed?
Is it possible
that whoever killed her,
was the person who wanted you
to get revenge on the cops?
Tul?
What are you doing here?
Did you send Thin to kill me?
What?
You sent Thin to kill me, right?
Why would I do that?
So what have you been doing?
Been a monk?
Tul,
how many years have
you been working with us?
You know we only kill people
whose names are on the list.
We don't kill randomly.
If it wasn't you, then who was it?
Don't move! Don't budge.
It's me.
We had to do it.
We wanted you to think the
doctor sent Thin to kill you.
Then you would bring us here.
You hired Thin?
We killed him.
Then we dumped the body there.
Who are you?
I'm Tohphong Jitthanya.
- You're...
- The son of Jaran Jitthanya.
The person you sent that guy to kill.
We caught and interrogated
him once already,
but he kept his mouth shut.
So, we deliberately let him escape.
Then when you became a monk
everything was in place.
How did you know
I became a monk?
How did we know
you were in the monk-hood?
Thanks for helping me.
I didn't intend to help you.
You were pointing a
gun at me, remember?
Don't kill anymore, OK?
Go back upcountry, trust me.
You don't understand.
I hope we'll never meet again.
I'm sorry for what I did.
Rin.
Erin!
Yes...
She's my sister.
Does anyone have any more questions?
If there aren't any more questions
then Tul can go home.
I have no more business with you.
However, the doctor must
stay a little while longer.
If you want to get revenge on
someone then it should be me, right?
I killed your father.
Please, don't try to be a hero.
You sent those people to kill me
even though your sister was there.
You knew there was a
chance she'd get shot.
One of them nearly killed her!
If that's what it took to find out
who ordered my father's death,
then I can sacrifice a sister.
Then you're a worse shit
than your father.
Bow at my feet right now!
I told you bow at my feet!
1...
2...
Where are you going?
Get in!
You'll get shot and killed!
Quick!
Why did you turn off
the power to help me?
Clean your face first.
Why did you think it was me?
I knew it was you.
I won't ask you how you
know where I live.
I know a lot about you,
but not everything.
Perhaps you don't know that
I see the rain falling towards the sky.
What does that mean?
That day...
I killed your father.
I was shot in the head.
I was in a coma for 3 months.
When I woke up,
everything I saw was upside down.
So right now you see
me upside down?
So how do you feel?
Even upside down, you're beautiful.
I mean...
how does it feel seeing
everything upside down?
At first, I was very annoyed,
but now I think it's the best
thing that happened to me
for many years.
What do you mean?
Before, I could see everything
like everyone else.
I'd recognize anything
with just a glance,
but now I must look at anything
or anyone thoroughly.
It's made me see everything clearer.
Is that why you stopped
being a hit-man?
I had to quit anyway.
I could never shoot anyone seeing
everything upside down like this.
That's not true!
I've seen a blind
person play ping pong.
Could he play well?
Being blind and able to play ping
pong, isn't that good enough?
Doctor...
I've got a question
I'd like to ask you.
What?
Doctor...
Doctor, did you kill Tiwa
so I'd come work with you?
Once again, I spent my
life as a prisoner.
This time I wasn't able to
remember for how many years.
The monotonous prison life didn't
make me bored or tormented.
In fact, it even made me peaceful,
sensible and steadfast.
I knew on the day I got my freedom back
what I'd do for the rest of my life.
Rin got married 5 years ago.
She has a daughter.
I saw her at the temple once.
On the fifth anniversary
of her father's death...
That day I just returned from
receiving my morning alms...
She greeted me.
But we didn't speak.
Everything seemed to ease up
and my consciousness
appeared to be more awake.
I started to hear the wind blowing...
the sounds of chickens and birds...
I heard water flowing in the stream.
For a long time I've been searching
for something lost,
and for a really long time
I've travelled everywhere
searching for something lost...
something lost.
Many people have told me
that my life was so perfect.
Who really knows
about
my life...
what it's really like?
My life isn't smooth
and not that perfect.
Like you and many people
have seen.
I may smile, I may laugh.
Who knows... who really knows?
Nowadays, I'm just
a traveler.
I'm traveling in search for
something lost...
something lost.
Don't ask me
when will you stop
traveling?
Sometimes, I even
question myself
about something lost.
I ask myself
about something lost...
something lost.