You're saying none of these people
are human?
But I'd never seen
anywhere so alive.
Trying to hold on
to their humanity.
Like eating food
although we don't need to.
10 years ago, just before
the whole isolation policy
an unknown disease spread out
from Tokyo.
Infection brought a raging fever
with a high mortality rate.
There was no information about
cause or transmission...
just a mandatory
immunization program.
That was the beginning
of our tragedy.
The disease
was a goverment creation.
And the vaccination we all received
was a Daiwa cyber-virus.
It invades every cell of the body
converting its molecular structure
into bio-metal
so that the human body
is replaced by machine from within.
What was worse, the virus
was still under development.
Meaning what?
We were a nation of guinea pigs.
Japan was their laboratory.
Finally the brain is owerwritten
the person becomes an android
and falls under Daiwa's control.
The speed of the process
differs between people.
Some of us still cling
to our human consciousness...
to the fragments of our humanity.
The technology is half-baked,
so most turn into junk.
At best
we become lumps of metal
with no memory.
In either case,
we're miserable specimens
awaiting death.
How long do you have?
Daiwa's not done.
The next target is America.
They've already planted
androids there.
That politician...
My buddy, Saga!
Let's go!
We call those, "Jags".
Failed experiments
from the android process.
They search around for any kind of
metal absorb it and grow.
The wasteland's crawling with them.
They throw up some neat stuff
sometimes, though.
We should get going.
Our base is underground.
Saito, what about that SWORD woman?
We lost her.
Failure's dogging you
since you let that informant
escape to America.
Maria is harboring the girl.
Leave them alone.
SWORD may have penetrated
the R.A.C.E. net.
Even so, America won't do a thing.
Relax, Saito.
Our decade-long experiment
nears fruition, at last.
That group, G32 Beta, in the slums
they alone are perfect specimens.
Maria is a part of that group.
Left alone they'll join us
in good time.
But, sir...
We need not fear any act of man.
Very well. Summon Itakura,
Chairman of the slum.
Hello.
Here.
A fresh piece of junk.
It should contain the part you need.
Thanks, it's just in time.
Where's Maria?
Everyone,
this is Vexille from SWORD.
Taro, is it ready?
Darn right it is.
My suit...
I fixed it up
and it's ready for action.
Looking for this?
- I sent out a beacon signal.
- For how long?
Longer than 3 minutes.
The R.A.C.E. net's down?
Daiwa already reconfigured
the diffusion pattern.
Darn.
SWORD only needs
a few minutes to act.
Another thing, there's one more
SWORD agent at Daiwa HQ.
Leon?
Yes, Leon Fayden, I believe.
Where exactly is he? Any injuries?
Sorry, that's all I know.
Taro, what's your source?
Daiwa's main stream. It's reliable.
Just Leon, no-one else?
No luck. No bio-signature
readings anywhere.
I found an additional signature.
There's just one other.
What's wrong?
The electro-magnetic diffusion
has changed.
Darn.
I'll re-run the analysis.
Have Minerva ready to rescue them.
Captain Borg, a call on the hotline.
The Defense Secretary already?
No... it's the President.
Borg, here.
Yes, Mr. President.
That's correct. 7 agents.
I understand, sir.
We must abort the mission.
Takashi, what on earth's going on?
There's going to be an earthquake.
There is?
Yes, it's our last chance.
We're going to smash Daiwa.
Me, Maria and the guys...
3 freight tunnels connect Daiwa
with the mainland.
Only the main one links to the city.
The others conect to the wasteland.
They're all ceramic?
Yes. A mid-size 'quake is forecast
for the next 24 hours.
All communication gates are open.
In case of the quake.
All communication gates are open?
Correct. And we found a weak point.
During the earthquake stand-by,
all tunnel gates
go to auxiliary power
which creates a 50% delay
between detection of an intruder
and the gates sealing in response.
How soon
do they close after detection?
- 18 seconds.
- How far between the gates?
2,500 meters.
That's pushing it
even in a fighter suit.
With our air-buggies, too.
But it's that or nothing.
And after you break in?
We drag this cable behind us.
The Jags.
They finish the job
if we get the cable inside.
This is enough metal to lure them
into the heart of Daiwa.
Chairman Itakura's called
an emergency council session.
- Is that all?
- Yes, it is.
Don't make me repeat myself.
We don't wish to obstruct
those who calmly
wait for the end.
But surely you know Daiwa
is planning to take America next?
There's so little time. Excuse me.
You're determined to go?
Suppose Daiwa responds
by opening the protective gates?
This is their precious laboratory.
They'd never do that.
In the end
we're all in the same boat...
trying to protect the same thing.
It's just that we choose to fight...
until the very moment
we become scrap metal.
As an outsider,
it's not my place to speak but...
your city seems to celebrate
the splendor of what you've lost.
But Maria...
she fights for
the sake of what's not yet gone.
Foreigners are to be expelled?
What on earth for?
Leon...
Maria, come to America with me.
What do you mean?
Your departure permit is invalid.
Lt. Commander L. Fayden
requested a pass for me.
No such request was filed.
That can't be right.
Check once more.
It comes up negative.
Come with us for questioning.
Get out.
What for? Let me call him.
Calls to the airport are forbidden.
I'm going with you.
Let me join your mission.
It's a Japanese domestic matter.
Surely it's gone beyond that?
You're a foreign guest, behave.
Americans never learn...
Leon chose to return here
because of you.
Maria, please take me into Daiwa.
Keep personal matters out of this.
I know you want to help Leon, too.
Takashi, what's wrong?
Takashi, hold on.
Takashi!
Call yourself human?
This is our rule.
Otherwise our plan would
be leaked to Daiwa.
Vexille.
We need someone to replace Takashi.
Once in the tunnel, floor it
or you won't have a chance.
Take a mid-line to reduce distance.
Touch the brakes and it's all over.
I'll lead Team Red
to the East tunnel.
Saga takes Team Black to the West.
We've never fielded this many units
so we don't know how many Jags
will turn up.
Even if you're the only one left,
don't give up.
We just need one cable
to reach Daiwa.
Though we are no more
than fragments...
we are still human.
As long as we have our pride
we can still take back our country!
Maria,
more Jags than we thought, huh?
Murata.
I'll double back and
get them off your tail.
Team Black to Red.
Red here.
Almost to the target gate.
Roger.
They're after you!
Murata!
We're through the gate.
Leave it to me.
2nd gate cleared!
3rd gate cleared
but we lost Masato's team.
Maria, we lured them away
from the gate.
Make another approach.
Roger.
The Jags are on the cable already.
They're too fast!
Maria!
Vexille.
One left.
Maria.
How come...
Bravo.
I guess you didn't expect the tunnel
to be separated from the island?
What a shame.
Jags can't jump that far.
Chairman Itakura
kept us well-informed.
Leon!
Nice to see you again, Maria.
We're friends from our student days.
The 10 years haven't changed you.
As beautiful
and as dangerous as ever.
Mr. Kisaragi...
Nobody move. You're in breach of
international law.
Nobody move...
Maria...
I warned you in vain.
The irony of fate.
Hardly imagined I'd see you again.
I can't let you do that!
"Insufficent evidence"?
We're public servants with no chance
against the might of Daiwa.
It's not just breach of a treaty,
their research
is a threat to mankind.
They were released this morning.
We are the peak of human evolution.
In fact human existence is nothing.
But a preparatory stage
in our creation.
There's nothing evolved about you.
This body, born of humankind
is perfection.
Matchless in level of intellect
and stability of emotion.
No need for sleep nor food.
Above all, we shall attain
immortality at last.
What more could be asked?
You will join me in immortality
soon enough.
Only the few
will attain this evolution
and be reborn as Japanese...
the world's strongest race.
I have done the work of god.
Maybe I was god all along.
He's insane.
But on the eve of completion,
Japan is empty of
workable specimens.
But your country abounds in them.
Healthy subjects
like your dear Leon.
Nothing divine about you...
Just another flawed human.
I had to protect myself for
your sakes against everything.
Of course I would have the injection
once the virus was safe.
Such suffering
for this sicko...
My research brought you
all eternal life...
Androids can't act compulsively.
It doesn't make sense...
Halt, Saito. Stop it, please.
The city gates are opening
onto the slums!
You have the citizens' full support.
This is Chairman Itakura.
The Council and I were misguided
and betrayed you all.
Now, thanks to your brave resolution
we can make amends for our mistake.
Thank you all very much.
Chairman Itakura...
Detach the central tunnel
from the island!
A transporter is en route.
Do not let it arrive.
Detach the tunnel.
Don't let it in!
Darn.
Piece of junk.
As long as I have my research
the world can still be mine.
The Jags will be here soon.
I'll get him, you look after Leon.
No, I'll go after him...
Not with that leg, you won't.
Look after Leon for me.
Maria...
Why didn't you come to the airport?
I hate machines
but humans like you
are far worse.
Vexille!
Vexille.
Where's Maria?
Stay back, you heap of junk!
The Jags will get you soon.
Maria.
Maria, run!
Now we'll be together forever.
Maria!
Jags across Japan came
to destroy Daiwa
then sank deep beneath the sea.
Maria and her kind died off.
But they left us something vital
we should carry with us.
It was Maria that taught us
as long as we communicate hope
to the next generation
we ourselves gain eternal existence.