Now, remember, if your loop is
large, your rug is loose.
Let's all repeat that, shall we?
If your loop is large, your rug is loose.
Good. Now let's give it a try.
Make a loop, pull it through,
cross over and pull it out.
Tighten those loops, Mr Lefkowitz.
This rest-home.
You wouldn't believe the place.
"Lights on!" "Lights off!"
Rules, rules, rules.
They don't even let you
keep a hotplate.
I shouldn't complain.
Today was an exciting day.
I learned how to hook a rug.
A man who, at one time, had the entire
garment district right here.
That's how I spend my days.
It isn't fair.
You work all your life, and you pay
taxes, you're a good citizen.
And what are you left with?
A tight rug.
I miss you, Rose.
My glass-bottom boat is about to give
you a treat, so hold on to your lanyards.
What you have before you, ladies and
gentlemen, is the climax of today's adventure.
The famous Lost Treasure of
the Florida Keys.
Amazing, isn't it?
Oh, good people, it's been here since the days
of Ponce de Leon and Vasco da Gama.
- Even Moby Dick.
- What a rip-off.
If there are no questions,
we'll head back to port,
where our gift kiosk carries an attractive line
of postcards, T-shirts and other treasures.
Full steam ahead, matey!
Shiver me timbers!
Stop! What the hell are you doin'?
Them's my French fries.
Oh, Mamma!
- Hi, honey. I'm home.
- Hi, Mom.
- How's the term paper coming?
- Fine.
David, I hope that's not the TV I hear.
No, Mom.
David?
- Who's there?
- It's your grandpa. I gotta talk to you.
- Grandpa!
- Your grandma and I are coming to see you.
- Really?
- Our friends have unfinished business to do.
It was a chance
for your grandma and I to grab a ride.
You have to talk to your mother
because she won't be ready for this.
What do I say? She's gonna freak.
Just tell her the truth. How about that?
- Look, I'll see you soon, son.
- Great!
I know how much you love Grandpa and
Grandma and wish they were here with us,
so it's only normal to fantasize.
- But it's important to know it's only a fantasy.
- But it's not a fantasy.
Maybe it would help
if you talked to somebody about this.
Mom, I don't need to see a shrink. They're
not dead. They really did go to another planet.
- David, your grandparents are not in space.
They're not in the television
and they're not coming back.
They were lost at sea. You know that.
They've been dead for five years.
Hello, darling.
Oh...
Just a minute!
Well, aren't you gonna invite us in?
Oh, for crying out loud!
Joe! Joe!
Alma!
Bess! How are ya?
Art! Come in, Art!
It's so wonderful to see you.
- It's great to see you, boy.
- What's to see?
I'm a broken-down old schlep with one foot
in the grave. If I was a horse, they'd shoot me.
The same old Bernie.
You haven't aged a day. You probably think
I'm ajerk for not going with you.
Oh, Bernie, we never thought that.
Good, because I never regretted it.
I never once regretted not going with you.
What's that? A little remodelling?
Oh, the maintenance here is...
You wouldn't believe it...
I ought to sue. I think it's...
By the way, you owe me rent.
It's all yours. All your things.
They tried to throw them out after you left,
but I told them "Over my dead body."
- I guess they figured that wouldn't be long.
- Bernie, you're a sentimental fool.
Well, I'm glad you got here in time because
I've been thinking about a garage sale.
How have you really been?
The truth? Not too good.
But now maybe things are looking up.
I think it's gonna be like old times.
I think.
Huh?
I feel terrible.
We let him think we were staying.
Do you want to be the one
to burst his bubble?
So what do we do?
Let him think we're staying here for good?
- We're gonna have to tell him sooner or later.
- Hold it.
I'll tell him. I'll tell him.
But not until I think he can handle it. Right?
Good morning, my little Antarean butterfly.
- Smells like I'll gain 5lbs this morning.
- At least.
- How you feel?
- Finer than frog hair.
- Where is everybody?
- The first group went through.
Here, have some coffee.
I made a fresh pot.
- How's Susie this morning?
- All things considered, holding up very well.
It's good to be back, isn't it?
Yeah.
- Still got the moves, don't I, kid?
- I didn't marry you for your money!
Well, I'll be goddamned.
- What is it?
- Here.
I'll be right back.
Look at this!
Is this beautiful?
You are beautiful.
- You have incredible eyes. You a collector?
- No.
Oh, a shrewd one at that.
Well, I will not insult you by haggling.
This Davy Jones treasure chest - a beauty,
isn't it? - I can give it to you for $19.95.
For that piece ofjunk?
You wife doesn't appreciate
fine antiques the way you do.
Listen, you take the box and I'll throw in
the barnacle salt-and-pepper shakers for free.
- Sold.
- Ha-ha!
Lovely.
Shaun, uh...
Take care of those folks, will you?
Hello, Jack.
I don't believe it.
What are you doin' here?
Don't tell me. You searched the entire galaxy,
couldn't find anyone as terrific as me?
The cocoons are in danger, Jack.
The sensors that we left on the bottom
of the ocean floor indicate seismic activity.
We've come to take our friends away.
We've got four days to rescue them
before our ship returns to take us home.
Seismic activity? That's heavy.
I was in an earthquake,
so I know it's very intense.
Well, aren't you glad to see me?
Isn't it a custom here to hug a friend
when you haven't seen her in a long time?
Yeah... Yeah, of course.
Hey, Romeo!
D'you think you could tear yourself away long
enough to ring up my clamshell castanets?
"O my luve is like a red, red rose
That's newly sprung in June:"
"O my luve is like a melodie
That is sweetly play'd in tune."
Oh, Arthur, darling, it's perfect.
- D'you want me to fix us breakfast?
- No time. Gotta meet the boys and get Bernie.
- Poor Bernie.
- Oh, nonsense.
We'll get him out of that hospital
and get his blood pumping again.
- That's Joe.
- Will you miss me?
- I already do.
Goodbye, Mrs Selwyn.
- How'd ya sleep?
- Best night's sleep I've had in years.
- How about Bess?
- She slept like a baby.
- What about you two?
- Alma didn't sleep a wink.
- You're kidding?
- No.
Neither did I.
Oh, you dog, you!
You smell that?
Yeah, incense.
Maybe a Hindu runs the place.
Back here.
Come on back, whoever you are.
Believe it or not, I'm open for business!
Hiya, fellas. What can I do for you?
- Mrs Feinberg?
- Call me Ruby.
Ever try this? It delivers oxygen-enriched
blood to the pleasure centres of the brain.
It's terrific. Will you give me a hand? I'm new
at this. It's tough getting out of this cookie.
Here we go, OK? Come on, don't be shy.
Now, put me right side up. Right side up.
Easy! Take it easy, fellas. Easy. Easy.
That is great. That's it. That's it.
OK, now, you grab an ankle
and you grab an ankle.
There's the left one. Terrific.
That is it.
Great.
Oh, boy, that's terrific.
I feel sensational. Thanks a lot.
Nice little place you got here... uh, Ruby.
D'you hear that, Sidney?
It's a nice little place I got here.
Sidney was my husband.
This dump was his dream.
Unfortunately, the son of a bitch died
and left me to live it.
- That's tough.
- Nah, it's not so bad. I just like to yak.
Now, tell me. You two on vacation or what?
- We, uh...
- Well...
...came down to see old friends.
- Oh.
Your night clerk told us to talk to you
about staying the week.
Sure thing. No problem.
This is not exactly my busy season.
- Great.
There's Ben. We better get cracking.
- See you round, Ruby.
- Count on it.
Oh, hey! Will you get a load of this sunshine?
I feel like a teenager.
- You do, huh?
- Yeah.
- Last one to the car buys dinner.
- Hey, yeah!
- Come on, slowpoke!
- You got a head start.
Where are you, boy?
Yahoo!
Hey, not bad, Superman!
We'll have to stop at a pharmacy.
If I don't have zinc oxide, I'll burn to a crisp.
So we'll stop at a pharmacy.
- Did you bring juice? I'll get dehydrated.
- We'll getjuice.
- Bernie, where you going?
- None of your business.
- You should be in your rug-hooking class.
- Take your hands off him.
- Or what?
- Or you'll be sorry.
- I said let him go!
- Out of my way, you old coot.
Easy, Rambo.
- What do you say we blow this joint?
- Yes.
After you.
Hey, hey!
- Look at that.
- Come on!
- Here we go.
- Last one in's a pantywaist!
Last one in ain't got a hair on his ass!
Here we go!
Where is everybody?
- How's the water?
- Great. It was just great.
A beautiful beach, a sunny day and
good friends... what more can a man ask for?
Can I have some of that, please?
Wonderful. Would you look at them move?
Gentlemen, I'd say all that those ladies
are lacking is a little mature male company.
- Yeah.
- How about that?
I think you're right.
Come on, Bernie. Come and dip your wick.
Come on!
Joe, I've gotta go. I've got an appointment.
An appointment?
We're playing a game here, Bernie.
It's important.
OK, Bernie. I'll get the guys.
Art. Ben.
- How's this feel?
- Perfect.
You're a good friend, Jack.
I knew we could count on you to help us out.
It's no sweat. You're my favourite Martian.
Well, I guess we're ready
and we'll be back in about an hour's time.
Yeah. OK.
- "My favourite Martian." That's good.
- See, he gets it.
"St Petersburg Oceanographic Institute."
They got a cocoon.
Holy shit.
OK, David, one more swing.
I know you can do it, buddy. Come on.
Hit it, man. Come on, David, one more time.
Oh, man, too bad.
- Next.
- That's OK, David. It's only batting practice.
Come on, Tom, you're up. Take a cut.
Screwed up again, guy.
No matter how many times I see that,
it's still impressive.
What's the mystery? You were analysing the
effects of quakes on fish and find a meteorite.
When a meteor enters the atmosphere, the
pressure will leave characteristic markings.
This baby doesn't have 'em.
Whatever it is, it didn't fall from the sky.
It's weird-looking.
It's kind of like a dinosaur egg.
What do you think, Sara?
You subscribe to the dinosaur-egg theory?
- Oh, my God.
- What is it?
It's a life form.
I'm gonna get a hot dog
and an ice-cold beer. How about you?
- Sure, I'll have a beer.
- You get a milk shake.
In you go.
- Hey, look, it's Wade Boggs.
- How's it hanging, doofus?
Yeah, that guy can't hit worth shit.
Wanna let me in on that?
I read somewhere, I don't know where,
maybe Ted Williams.
It said the hardest thing in sports to do
is hit a round ball with a round bat.
What you gotta do is learn how to hit the ball
with some degree of control.
You go over by the bucket
and I'm gonna hit some of these.
Now, watch. I'm gonna try
to see the ball hit the bat.
Boom. See? And you don't
have to swing hard. Give me a ball.
- OK.
- Now you. OK, come over here.
Now, think. Try and see the ball hit the bat.
All right, now you're cooking. All right.
Let's go, let's go, let's go. A little pep.
That's the one.
- You ought to have your head examined.
- It was just a little baseball... Here, over here.
Just a little ball game. No big deal.
This is Earth, Ben, not Antarea.
- As long as we're here, we keep getting older.
- I know.
But with this kind of fringe benefit,
maybe it's worth it.
Hey, what's going on?
Well, it's been so long since you needed me
for anything like this, I guess I missed it.
Yeah. I missed it, too.
I know.
It's not your fault.
How could you know an earthquake would
knock a cocoon out of its hiding place, huh?
I'm responsible for him. They're
counting on me to bring him back home.
And I'm going to need a blueprint
of the institute so I can plan his rescue.
Well, I'll help you. I'll do whatever you want.
But I got into trouble last time,
so you cannot steal any more old people.
- We're not doing that.
- All right, fine. Let's just go bust him out.
It's not that easy. We can't free him without
the risk of drawing attention to ourselves.
We'll go back in three days,
then rendezvous with the ship.
Three days!
You're crazy! Kitty, in three days they'll cut it
open and perform grotesque experiments...
I'm sorry... I didn't mean...
I'm sorry.
I'm... I'm...
We're going to get him back.
Look at this. Slick as a whistle.
You're not so bad yourself.
Joe, I'm in heaven. Isn't this wonderful?
You're the one who didn't wanna come back.
- You glad I twisted your arm?
- I think I was afraid it wouldn't be the same.
But it's better.
- Look. What are we gonna do about him?
- I asked him to dance.
- Forget it. Bernie hasn't cut a rug in 30 years.
Joe, maybe we should
go and keep him company.
I see something
that'll get his juices flowing.
One more of these
and I am no longer responsible.
- Waiter! Waiter!
- Oh!
You are my kind of group.
Most people our age are a pain in the ass.
Most people our age are dead.
Oh, Bernie.
Where did he get to be so funny?
- Yeah, Bernie, how'd you get to be so funny?
- I always thought Bernie was funny.
- Me, too.
- You have?
Oh, you don't think I'm funny, Joe?
Watch this. I'll show you funny.
Presenting Mr Laurel and Mr Hardy.
This is an eagle who just found out
his teenage daughter's pregnant.
You know what? You are adorable.
What's... Are you all right?
What's the matter? It was just a little kiss.
I'm a married man.
Oh, pardon me. I'm so sorry.
- Your friends told me you were available.
- What?!
- Bernie, we just thought...
- You just thought what, Joe?
That I've forgotten about Rose?
That her memory means nothing to me?
Well, I got news for you. It means everything.
Now, don't break up your little party
on my account. I'll get a cab.
He's a fun guy. A barrel of laughs.
Thanks for the intro.
- I'm sorry, Ruby.
- Yeah, forget it.
Like I said...
we had some laughs.
Ruby, underneath it all
he really is a wonderful guy.
Yeah, yeah.
Thanks for the drink.
Pay attention to the teacher.
Behave yourself.
Michael, stop pushing.
Kelly, why'd you fall from there?
I told you so many times.
Sh, it's not gonna hurt.
Hi. Is it bad?
I don't think so, but I'd like to have someone
look at it. She banged her head pretty hard.
Oh, poor little girl. Now, that's a bad bump.
Let me see if I can take it away.
I got it! Let's throw it away.
Wow. You've got the touch.
The first-aid station's over there. Would you
mind watching the kids for a few minutes?
- OK. You go take care of her.
- Oh, thanks.
Just blow this if they attack.
All right, children. Gather round.
Well, well, well, look what
the cat dragged in.
- Your pals said to tell you they'd be a bit late.
- Fine. I'll wait outside.
Don't be silly. Take the load off your feet.
I don't bite, you know.
- I'll just stand here, by the door.
- OK, suit yourself.
Listen, um...
I'm sorry about last night, OK?
- Forget about it.
- No, I don't think so.
I don't like loose ends.
Maybe we could, um, smooth things out.
Over a cocktail?
That's not necessary.
I accept your apology.
- You're afraid of me, aren't you?
- I certainly am not.
OK. Then there's no problem.
Pick you up at seven.
So finally, after the longest trip
you could ever imagine,
their spaceship landed and
it was time for them to see their new home.
The spaceship's door slowly opened
and there before them was the magic planet...
the most beautiful sight
any of them had ever seen.
The sky was gold, and shining down on them
were three pale, pale pink moons.
So they stepped outside, and guess what?
- What?
- They floated.
That's right!
They could fly like birds.
So they all joined hands and,
with their new friends leading the way,
they flew off to a silver city
shimmering in the distance.
- Can we go there?
- Hold on, now. It's very far.
And, besides, if you left here
think of all the things you'd miss.
- Do they have ice cream?
- No.
- Santa Claus go there?
- I'm afraid it's too far for Santa to make it.
Then how come the people went there?
Well, on that planet no one ever gets sick,
no one ever gets old and no one ever dies.
So if you're in love with someone,
you never have to lose them.
What happens if
you fall in love with ice cream?
You're in trouble!
- I like that one!
- You do?
Here we go, fellas. Stake your claim.
- Oh, boy. Oh, boy. Is that a hot dog, or what?
- State of the art.
- You know what they put in those things?
- I do. Thanks for reminding me.
Have a bite, Bernie.
They say the chilli kills the bugs.
Very funny. Give me gas for a week.
You know, Bernie? You'd fit in the Guinness
Book of World Records for complainers.
- Hey, come on!
- Sorry. You wanna throw our ball back?
- We look like your servants? Get it yourself.
- Hey, we said we're sorry.
- Don't give us any shit. Just give me the ball.
- Don't do it, Joe. Look at the mess they made.
- If I was you, I'd keep quiet, pops.
- Oh, yeah?
Hold it a minute!
Let's be gentlemen about this.
I say we settle this with a little four on four.
- Great idea.
- Get real.
- Are you nuts?
I'll tell you what I think. I bet $10 we can
make 11 baskets before you hotshots can.
- My money's on the table. Come on.
- Oh, right.
Like taking money from a dying man.
- You dudes got yourself a game.
- Good.
Whoo! In your face, grandpa.
- Ben, over here.
- Get him. Watch him, watch him.
Art! Art!
I got him. I got him.
Just like downtown.
OK, no more charity. Now we're gonna play.
- Over here, man.
- Defence. Watch the defence.
I got him. I got him.
Fellas, let's not give up.
- Joe, what's the score?
- 7-1, for God's sake.
Art, shoot!
8-2! We're catching up.
- Guard your man!
- Guard your... Where? What?
Guard who, Joe? Who?
Hey, hey, watch it. Here we go.
Hey, that's 9-2. You guys give up?
No! Do you?
- Time out. Time out. Come on.
- What's the matter? You pooped?
Fellas? Fellas?
OK, I think it's time
we showed 'em what we learned.
- You're damn right. Art?
- I couldn't agree more.
Let's go.
Now, boys. Now.
Watch him. Come on, man, cover.
Get him.
Go, Art. Go!
Come on, take him.
Oh!
Great, Joe! Great.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Go, Ben. Go!
- What's the score?
- 10-5. Guard your man.
Which one is my... I say, which one is my...
Watch it.
Cover him.
- Get him!
- Attaboy!
Are you my man?
9-10, your favour. Getting nervous?
Aaaargh-agh!
Art!
Hallelujah!
10-10. Next basket wins.
All right, all right.
I'm free. Over here, over here.
Bernie! Bernie!
Bernie, go for it!
In your face, junior.
Bernie, you're the greatest!
You're the greatest!
Oh... Oh...
That is to die.
- It sure is. The price tag alone'd kill you.
- Maybe you should try it on.
Are you kidding?
I've never shopped in a store like this.
Me either. Where would any of us
wear a get-up like that?
In our dreams.
That settles it.
Oh, it's terrific.
Ta-da!
It's gorgeous.
Aaargh!
I don't believe it!
Oh! Wow!
Bess, that's naughty.
Oh, that's so sexy. I think it suits you.
Oh, Bess? Oh.
- Jean, get some water.
- Are you all right?
How about some hot coffee?
I just can't understand what could be wrong.
She was in perfect health.
And the minute we get back... this happens.
There isn't any justice.
If there were, it'd be me in there, not her.
- Now, don't be ridiculous.
- No, I'm not.
You don't know her, Joe.
Not the way I do.
She's the most generous,
loving and giving person I've ever met.
She's the only one that's ever really loved me.
I'd trade places with her in a heartbeat...
if I could.
OK. Just a few more inches, Bob.
You're doing very well.
- All right. That's fine.
Doug, Ray, let's lift it off.
Carefully! Carefully.
Don't be afraid.
You guys OK?
What are we doing, gang?
They've opened the cocoon, Jack.
- Is he gonna be all right?
- For a short time.
But if he doesn't get an infusion
of life force soon, he'll weaken quickly.
Mr Selwyn?
- That's me, Doctor. How is she?
- She's fine, considering her age
and the fact that she's six weeks' pregnant.
- Well, you smutty old devil.
- Pregnant?
Very impressive, Mr Selwyn.
This one's definitely going in the books.
- Congratulations.
- Pregnant? Pregnant?
- Don't you go near him!
- She's pregnant. Pregnant?
Uh-huh.
- Safe.
- All right, all right, all right, all right.
Hold it a second. Let me clean the plate.
Right, here we go. Let's play ball.
- Strike!
- Come on, kid. Be a hitter.
Come on, Davy.
Davy, you can do it.
Strike two!
You can do it. Let's play ball.
Come on, Davy.
- Strike three! You're outta here.
Well...
How you doin'?
Fine, considering I'm the worst player
in the whole league.
That don't sound like the fella
I saw hit the ball yesterday.
I told you. It's different when I'm with you...
you want me to hit it.
And you think your pals
don't want you to hit it. Is that it?
I'm just no good at stuff. I always mess up.
You know, that could be true.
I don't know.
But I know you're not the only kid
that ever felt scared or anxious,
or couldn't hit a baseball.
You see, when I was a kid playing baseball,
a little younger than you,
they always sent me to right field...
that's where they send the duds.
Then when I got up to bat there was
no way in the world I could ever hit that ball.
- But you can do it now.
- Sure, but I've had a whole life to work on it.
You can hit too. I've seen you.
You see...
it looks to me like you're listening
to a lot of people tell you you can't do it,
when maybe what you should be doing
is listening to yourself say that you can.
And I want you to remember something.
I love you, and all I want for you
is the very best that life has to offer,
but, see, you're gonna
have to go get it yourself.
Yeah.
Now think about that, will you?
OK.
Thanks, Grandpa.
Mr Finley?
Won't you have a seat, Mr Finley?
We'll talk about this.
We don't really need to talk, Doctor.
Just tell me what's wrong.
You had leukaemia a few years back,
but it went into complete remission, right?
Right.
- I've got it again, haven't I?
- Yes.
I'd like to get you started on chemo.
How long have I got, Doctor?
The disease is unpredictable. It may spread
quickly or it may go into periodic remission.
Six months, six years.
I honestly don't know.
Great.
- I'll take over for a while.
- OK.
If only you could talk.
Did you do that?
- Is he doing what I think he's doing?
- I think so.
- Call Dr Baron.
- Right.
Relax.
Contraction ends.
Now take a deep, cleansing breath.
Oh, that's my little mommy.
Hi.
Thank goodness. I was just about
to organise a search party.
I have so much to tell you.
Me, too.
Sorry I'm late. The market was jammed.
This has been the most incredible day.
First Bess, and then guess what?
I met a woman who runs
a preschool for foster children.
She just called and offered me ajob.
Isn't that something?
In all my life no one's ever offered me ajob.
She said she was impressed
by the way I handled the children.
- So what did you tell her?
- I said I'd have to talk to you.
I'm going back tomorrow just to help out.
How can you take ajob
when we're leaving in two days' time?
Joe, for heaven's sake, I was just pleased
to get the offer. I didn't say I was taking it.
Then why didn't you
turn her down on the spot?
I don't know.
I suppose I just wanted
the fantasy to last a little longer.
I'll tell her tomorrow.
What's your news?
What?
Those groceries are a lot more expensive
than they used to be.
Thank you for coming.
We're going to start the demonstration now.
Sara, please?
- See?
All right!
You can't fool him, you see?
Oh... Yes.
We're gonna make arrangements
to move him to a secure location.
- I want to keep this very quiet.
- Fine.
- Good work. Job well done.
- Thank you.
Congratulations. I am very impressed
with you and your facility.
My reports to the Joint Chiefs
will reflect that.
All I'm saying is we've no idea how a drastic
change in environment might affect him.
He's losing his strength, and a dead alien
won't do you or the military any good.
Sara, I know you're fond of him, but don't let
emotions overrule your scientific judgment.
You're not giving him to MIT
or the Smithsonian, but to the Air Force!
To the government.
There's a national security issue.
There you are.
- Hello, Jack.
- Hey.
I got you a little something. Sort of
a "get your mind off your problems" present.
Thank you. I really love it.
Me, too. I can't understand why
we're not selling more of them though.
You're a good friend, Jack.
Friend? Friend, friend, friend, friend.
Kitty, we are more than friends.
We shared ourselves and everything.
Would you like it
if we shared ourselves again?
Like it? I would love it.
I've been dreaming about it for five years.
Then let's go back to your cabin.
Huh? Whoa, ho, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
You Antareans may have the market cornered
in sharing, but know nothing about romance.
Kitty, I'm the kind of guy,
I need to have a nice dinner, you know?
A little music, a little candlelight.
I charmingly convince you
to ask me back to your cabin for a nightcap.
And then...
we share our brains out.
Hop in.
How can you stand this racket?
What are you talking about?
This is a terrific joint.
I haven't heard a word of English
since we walked into the place.
You know something? When you want to,
you do a great impression of an old fart.
Oh, thanks!
Oh, thank you very much.
Oh, whoo-whoo!
I can't wait.
Mmm!
- What is this?
- It's Cuban punch. And it's delicious.
Go ahead, Bernie. You'll probably hate it,
but go ahead. Force yourself.
Uh-huh.
Bernie... Bernie... Oh, my God.
You are a real nutcase.
That's 151-proof rum!
Maybe I was thirsty.
Waitress! Oh, waitress!
This way.
I tell you, this place must be great...
I have no idea what we just ordered.
Is this a ritual commonly practised
before people share themselves?
Oh, yes, absolutely. Absolutely.
See, this is romantic.
You got champagne, ambience, you know.
Gets you in the mood.
Mm, mm-hm, mm-hm, mm-hm.
- Voila. Bon appetit.
- Gracias!
- What is this, Jack?
- Uh...
This is, um... Oh, this is bon appetit.
This is French food.
See, it's terrifique. See, they don't
say "terrific", they say "terrifique".
You OK?
- Jack?
- Hm?
I want to rub this bon appetit
over every inch of your body.
- Really?
- Yes.
Well, let's do it. Let's do it.
We'll get an order to go.
Uh, garcon? Uh, senor?
What did I say? I said something funny?
Oops. I guess that bite
got away from you, huh, honey?
- What's the big idea?
- I'm really enjoying this bon appetit, Jack.
You're having an extraterrestrial
reaction to this.
- Don't be silly. I feel wonderful.
- I think maybe the best thing would be...
- No, Jack.
- Kitty, please.
- No.
- Kitty, listen to me. You gotta trust me.
No. Jack! Jack!
Argh!
Honey, what's the rush?
Don't you want your entree?
Oh, my God!
No, Jack.
I want to share myself with you right now.
Oh... Oh...
Well, I don't know if that's such a good idea
in front of all these nice people.
Whoa, hold it, Kitty. Don't do it.
Not here. Not here.
Kitty, please! Heads up!
Kitty!
Must be something she ate. Huh.
Incoming!
Keep the change!
- I figured out something about you.
- Yeah? What?
Once a person gets past that tight-ass routine
of yours, you're not a bad guy.
No! And I'll tell you something else,
Lefkowitz,
you make me laugh.
Imitation of an owl.
I think you're very pretty.
You do?
Thanks.
- Rose!
- Bernie?
Rosie.
Hey, Bernie.
- What's the matter? You sick?
- This was a mistake. I shouldn't have come.
- Jesus Christ. What are you talking about?
- I can't do this to Rose.
- I think we better go now.
- Bullshit!
Bernie, bullshit!
Your wife is just an excuse, d'you know that?
An excuse so you don't have to go on living.
Well, guess what, buster?
Life goes on.
And if you had any,
if you'll pardon my French, balls,
you'd face up to the fact that she's dead.
Rose is dead, Bernie, and you're not!
Are you all right?
Um, I, uh...
I was going through
one of Susan's photo albums today,
and there were some photos of David on
his fourteenth birthday at a New Year's party.
It's five years of his growing up
that we've missed.
This is our family. My life doesn't have
any meaning without them.
Ben, I want us to stay here.
I want us all to be together.
Look, I know you're worried,
about the boy and his mother.
I'm worried, too.
Look around, honey. I mean, everybody
we know, except for Bernie, is sick or dying.
They're dropping like flies.
Honey, I don't wanna
watch that happen to you.
I don't want it to happen to me.
And we can beat it, you know?
But it's not right.
People shouldn't outlive their children.
D'you want the truth?
I'm scared to death.
Don't you think I know that?
I'm scared, too, but not of dying.
I'm scared of living without you.
But I don't want to leave here.
Morning.
- How's it going?
- Good.
We can get in and out of the institute
without being discovered.
Great. Great.
That was some date last night, huh?
How are you feeling?
Foolish.
I should have known better than to eat
something when I didn't know what it was.
But thank you for taking care of me.
- So where did you sleep?
- Are you kidding? Sleep?
I was up all night
waiting for the cops to show up.
Well, I guess we made a clean getaway.
I'm sorry, Jack. Is there any way
that I could make it up to you?
Come on, come on, Kitty.
Compared to some of my dates,
last night was a raging success.
I don't know. Sometimes I think
maybe I'll be one of those guys
who never finds anyone,
lives on TV dinners, talks to his dog,
which is OK cos I kind of like dogs.
Jack, I'd like to show you something, but in
order to see it you'll have to close your eyes.
- This isn't gonna be anything kinky, is it?
- No, I don't think so.
OK.
Oh, oh, wow.
Sh.
Vital signs are dropping fast.
Respiration rate's down. Looks bad.
I think that dog and pony show wore him out.
What do you think?
I think that in a couple of days
it'll be out of our hands.
That's what I think.
- How do you know it'll work?
- It has to work. He wasn't revived properly.
If we don't get him back now,
he won't survive.
We need your help.
I don't know... Thanks.
Breaking into that place sounds kind of risky,
especially now that the military's involved.
Joe's right. What if we get caught?
Will you listen to us?
We're back less than a week,
and already we sound like
a bunch of frightened old geezers.
Have we forgotten what they've given us?
We owe them everything, and if one of
their friends need help, I'll damn well give it.
You can count me in.
Well, we're in.
- OK. Count us in, too.
- Good.
Once we get our friend back,
we'll go to the rendezvous point.
The ship will meet us at midnight.
If you have unfinished business, do it today.
Joe.
- Why don't you tell me, Joe?
- Bernie...
- We were going to...
- Don't you "Bernie" me.
You can all go straight to hell.
Bernie!
Goddamn it, Bernie, wait a minute.
When were you going to tell me, Joe? Or were
you going to let me find out after you'd gone?
I didn't have the heart to tell you we were
only staying a while. I was trying to help you.
Help me! You just yanked the rug
right out from under me.
Do me a favour, go be a good
Samaritan somewhere else.
You know, Bernie, you're the most miserable,
self-centred complainer I've ever met.
Other people are in pain and afraid, and
if you'd open your eyes you might see that.
As far as I'm concerned, you can feel sorry
for yourself until hell freezes over.
You don't deserve to have friends like us.
Here, here it is.
Now you throw it. Throw it fast.
That's the way. That's the way.
Throw it to Mary.
That's a good throw.
Yeah, that's the way.
Catch it.
Anthony!
- Anthony!
- Oh, no.
Anthony!
- Oh, God, no!
Someone, please call an ambulance.
Joe.
Hello, Bernie.
I went looking for you at the motel.
Ruby told me. I couldn't find the others.
How is she?
Doesn't look good.
Really something the way things work out.
She was so happy to be back here,
and then this happens.
Did you ever tell her?
- Tell her what?
- That you're sick again.
I've known you over 30 years, Joe.
After you blew up this afternoon,
I figured it out.
Will you get better if you go back?
I got better before.
You don't get sick there.
- Mr Finley?
- That's me.
Your wife's vital signs are stable
at the moment, but she's comatose.
I don't expect her to last the night.
I'm sorry.
- Can I see her?
- Yes, of course.
Honey, can you hear me?
Joe.
Hello, my darling.
What happened? I can't remember...
You were in an accident.
But you're gonna be fine.
I dreamed I...
Something was pulling me
farther and farther away.
And then you came and held me
and wouldn't let me go.
My God, Joe.
What's happened?
- What have you done?
- I gave you a present.
Something you needed.
You know, a lot of my life
I've been a selfish son of a bitch.
Oh...
I haven't always taken care of you
the way I should have.
But I always loved you.
I know that, Joe.
I've always known that.
Joe...
I can't be without you.
Sure you can.
I want you to take thatjob.
And anyway...
my time's run out.
Oh, Joe.
I am so tired.
I am...
so damn tired.
Then rest, darling.
Go ahead and rest.
Well...
that's the end of an era.
Won't be the same now.
We never should've come back.
If we'd stayed put,
this never would have happened.
Aw, you can't second-guess fate.
You gotta take it the way it comes,
then try and figure out how to deal with it.
Joe would have liked this.
He loved the beach.
He didn't give a shit about the beach.
It's them smooth-legged girls in them
dental-floss bikinis... that's what he liked!
I'm gonna miss that old son of a bitch.
Yeah.
Me too, pal.
Me too.
She's finally asleep.
Ohh...
Art, honey, can you give me a hand?
I'll be right there.
I think we overdid this.
Half of these things won't fit.
I've been thinking.
Could we be making a mistake?
I mean, are we doing right... by our child?
Is it fair to take him that far away?
I know it won't matter when he's young, but...
what about when he grows up?
Think of what he'll be missing.
All those experiences we took for granted,
he won't have.
Art, do you really think
I hadn't thought about that?
For all the snowflakes and sunsets
and rainbows he won't see,
think of what he will have,
think of what he'll gain.
A world with no illness,
no poverty, no wars.
Besides, if we stay here,
our child might not be born.
We'd never live long enough
to see him grow up.
Well, it's time we head out.
Be a good boy.
- Take good care of your mother.
- Wait a minute, Grandpa.
Thanks.
- Have a safe trip.
- Bye-bye now.
Bye, Ruby.
Oh, we can'tjust leave you here like this.
Please, won't you come with us?
I belong here. I'm going to take thatjob
with the children. It's what I want.
- You'll be all alone.
- What am I, chopped liver? She'll be fine.
We're gonna miss you...
more than you know.
- Goodbye, Bernie.
- Bye, Art.
- I hate these long goodbyes, so bye, my girl.
- Bye-bye.
- Bernie, I'm glad I got to see you.
- Me too, Ben.
- Goodbye, dear.
- Goodbye, Mary.
Bye, Bernie. Bye.
- Goodbye, Alma.
- Bye.
Be careful, Jack.
- Goin' to get something to eat.
- Bring me back a burger.
I'm so sorry.
Down by six, right?
Come on.
You take the passenger side.
Good evening, Doc.
You're working kinda late.
Yeah, well, I had a couple of things
I had to finish up.
You have a good evening.
- Power failure!
- Rebecca, get Engineering.
- Right.
Damn!
That was weird.
- Oh, my God. Rebecca, get Dr Baron!
- Right.
- He's not in here.
- Phil!
- Where the hell would he go?
- This way.
- Yeah, let's check it out.
- Have you seen anything?
- This way, this way.
Phil.
- Don't run.
- Sara, make sure the building is sealed.
- Don't forget the sea door by the tanks.
- Right.
Be careful. Don't frighten him.
There's someone in the building.
Check out the west wing.
Let's go back to the lab.
- Nothing down that way, sir.
- All right... all right.
We split up here. Everyone takes a door and
stays put. Nothing gets out of this building.
Doug. Rebecca.
You, come with me. Come on.
I'll check the central core.
OK. OK. We better move.
Grandpa!
David? Good.
Come on, you can help me.
We're gonna have to do this, son.
Take a hold.
Let's get it open.
Lean in.
All right. Push, David. Push.
Aagh!
I got it, Gramps!
Stop!
What are you doing?
Well, you see, he's my friend.
And we're gonna take him home.
OK?
Here they come.
Did you see anyone, ma'am?
No.
- Ahoy!
- Hello. Welcome back.
There we go.
All right, sir. There you go.
- There you go, my boy.
- Hello, darling.
- David, what are you doing here?
- Grandma.
Are you all right? Are you both all right?
What happened?
Now, Mother, he was a lot of help to me
and without him, I wouldn't be here.
- Yeah. I did all right, didn't I, Grandpa?
- I'll say! Hitting a baseball'll be a cinch now.
I wish you'd be here to see it.
We will be.
What?
- Well, hell, that's what you want, isn't it?
- Oh, Ben!
Oh, thank you, my darling. Thank you.
Walter!
- Good to see you, Jack.
- You make one hell of an entrance.
Thank you.
- You've done well.
- He's weak, but he'll survive.
Well, I see the gang's all here.
- Not the whole gang.
- I know.
I'm sorry about Joe. He was a good man.
And a good friend to all of us.
Well, Ben, are you sure
you won't come with us?
Real sure.
I tell you.
See, Walter, a man's
not supposed to outlive his children.
And besides, I may see you
some other time, some other place.
That may be true, Ben.
Well, I think it's time to leave.
You've no idea how we'll miss you.
You'll make a wonderful mother.
You'll make a wonderful grandmother.
You won't forget us, will you?
Forget you? Ha!
No, we won't forget you.
Now, you better get goin'.
You'll miss your connection in Baltimore!
I thought you only cried
when somebody died.
Or when your friends are leaving.
Yeah!
I see what you mean.
Goodbye, Ben.
Well... Oh, hey, come here.
I got something here that means a lot to me.
I want you to have it, Kitty.
It's my high-school graduation photo.
I got it framed so you can
put it on the TV or something.
Thank you. I really love it, Jack.
I'll miss you, Kitty.
- I'll miss you too, Jack.
- I'm sorry. Kitty, it's time.
Excuse me?
Hi. I'm sorry to bother you, but
I ran out of gas and you were the only light.
Do you know a place nearby
where I can get gasoline?
I'll be right with you.
Yeah, there's an all-nighter
about a mile down the road.
I can give you a lift, if you want.
- Sure you wouldn't mind?
- Oh, no. No problem.
- Kinda late to be out, huh?
- Yeah. Well, I'm just on my way from work.
At this hour?!
I wouldn't want yourjob.
Neither would I. I just quit.
- Why are you looking at me that way?
- Honestly, this is no line, I swear,
but I think I know you from somewhere.
- No, I don't think so.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- You look so familiar.
No, I never forget a face.
I'm sure I'd remember yours.
- My name's Jack. Jack Bonner.
- Sara. Nice to meet you, Jack.
Pleasure.
- It's chilly, isn't it?
- Yeah. Well, you know, down... Oh!
Where's my manners?
- Here you go.
- Oh, thanks.
- Ever been in a glass-bottom boat?
- No.
- Wanna go on one?
- Yeah, I've always wanted to.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Well, I got one.
- Really?
Yeah. Well, the bank owns it, but you're
looking at a captain of a glass-bottom boat.