Stop!
Have mercy, sir! Take it back!
How dare you steal from me?
Damn you!
Go away!...
Stop! Stop!
Is it him?
Doesn't look like him! Get going!
Thank you!
Don't go!
If you're not a fugitive, step aside!
You're in my way, scram!
Stop!
Not him!
Tell him to leave!
Stop!
Stop!...
Don't run!
Over there!
Stop!
There's a fugitive there!
Did you ask me to stop?
Pilgrimage? How hilarious!
You're carrying money
Don't fish in troubled waters
Don't say that
I don't need this money
You may need it sooner or later!
Thank you!
Want a room, Sir?
Get the luggage for him
There's a nice room
Sorry, but I'm a collector
from Tsi Pao Zai
Collector?
That's too rude!
Why is it a different man each time?
The ex-collector was killed
on his way home
Why don't you just do me a favor?
Since you might get
killed for the money
Just don't collect
You're kidding
Can I see your books?
It's the new rule
New rule? Show me!
Sorry, no!
What kind of record is that?
It's a mess. How do you collect?
I can't return without the money
Help me out here
Since I'm not in your books
I don't owe you anything
Don't deny it or I'll take you to court
Where can I spend a night for free?
Go to the Orchid Temple!
Madam, I didn't lie to you
Where's Orchid Temple, please?
Orchid Temple?! 3-1/2 miles to the East
You'll see a spooky temple!
Thank you!
Sorry! Excuse me!
Madam, are you going to buy it or not?
Well done!
Master, you've good taste, make an offer!
I don't even have money
for travel expenses
Good taste, but no means, what's the use?
What are you doing?
I'm taking your measurement
for your coffin!
Thank you!
Remember
there are wolves in the woods
You may come upon them when it's dark
Don't go...
The fire must not go out
If it does, I can't get
out of the forest
Anybody in?
Have you finished?
Hsia-hou, we're fought for 7 years
and you're always lost
But you're quite persevering
You follow me wherever I go
You've been in the
Temple for a fortnight
And you've improved your swordsmanship!
But you've wasted your youth too
You're ambitious, but not aggressive
For the sake of the title
you've become corrupt
You're petulant but not focused enough
Your blows are violent but ineffective
You have to cool down
If you win, it's just luck
I'm here to duel with you
Not to listen to your sermon
You...
Right, he's right
You've already won
You shouldn't have
said that to disgrace him
He's right too
You shouldn't have followed him
Lay down your swords
Move him with sincerity
The universe is limitless
and love is eternal
Love conquers the world
Love is the most powerful weapon!
You speak too much
I'm not trying to follow you
Your clothing is torn
To hell with your love!
The kind of love you need
you should find in a whorehouse
I'm trying to find shelter
It's not convenient!
Why not?
Are you a brave man?
Yes!
Look over there!
When I shout
Hide behind me
If there's a real tiger
Where should you hide?
What? There's really a tiger?
No!
But we've something scarier then a tiger
Do you always keep
so close while talking?
I have bad breath, and this
will keep you away
Get out of here!
Your compassion can't save you
I know. I'm off!
Me too!
Hsia-hou, you were ambitious
but after death
you're still a nobody
I won't leave your body in the open
You never change, you fight
even when dead
Pao-Yeh-Pao-Lo-Mi!
That monster's out again!
Shit! Is he still here?
I meant no harm
I'll fling it away if you're afraid
What is it?
Where's my veil?
Veil? I'll find it for you!
Water's deep!
Come up quick!
Come up!
Thank you!
It's too dark, I can't see
I'll look for it early tomorrow
This water is both deep and cold!
Your hands are colder than mine
Because you're warmer
You're sick
you look so pale
Go see a doctor
I need your warmth
I shouldn't have pushed you
Otherwise, Iwould have
spurted all over you
It hurts!
I shouldn't have pushed you
It's cold!
I'm wet, you'll feel colder lying on me
Do you feel pain or cold?
Carry me inside!
Carry you?!
I can't, you're too heavy
I need some help...
You look nice, but you're
in the wrong place
Or else, you wouldn't die in vain
Why am I still in water?
Miss, you forgot your lute!
Why are you following me?
Why are you leaving?
A villain! I must run for my life!
Who? I can't see it
Don't be afraid!
Let me get rid of it
I'll stomp you to death
Still here?
Snake!
Where's the snake?
Don't shout!
The villain just passed by
Which one?
The bearded one from Orchid Temple
If he discovers us, we'll be killed!
The one living opposite me?
I can tell he's no good
It's too dangerous. I'll take you back
No, you can't!
My family won't allow this
They're very strict
I see, Miss
Let me lure him away then
Run when he tries to get hold of me!
Don't let him see you
Here's your lute, Miss!
What's your name?
Ning Tsai-shen!
What's yours?
Nieh Hsiao-tsing!
Tomorrow night...
Tomorrow night I'll come to see you
Stop running!
It's dangerous
Stop! You can't get away!
If you can scream; I can scream too!
Damn Taoist
Both of us want shelter here
Actually, all the men
I killed deserve it
Why have you been annoying me?
I am not
I'm hiding in this hellish place
to stay away from
the fighting in the world
Our common aim is to
rid the world of villains
for the good of mankind
We are fellowmen
Fellowmen? Nonsense!
You're hurting me too
One day, you'll be in big trouble
then I'll finish you off
You're a good man. Don't see me anymore
Hsiao-tsing!
Man of love
Did you come upon anything last night?
I've bumped into everything in the house
Did you see anything eerie?
Including you?
Idiot!
I'm serious. Why are you joking?
Who knows if you're serious or not?
When do Ijoke?
You're always joking
Get out of this place. It's haunted
Show me the ghost if you can!
Stupid fool!
If you can see it
then it can't be a ghost
They won't show up in the day!
Big beard, don't scare me!
If not in the day, then
tell them to come tonight
It'll be too late if you see them
Why don't you believe me?
If I see you at night
I'll throw you out
Come on, do that
No, I'll kill you
There's no better way to help him
than to scare him
Ghost? He must be kidding
Where's my lower torso?
Damn big beard!
Where have you put it?
Isn't it connected to your upper part?
Don't talk nonsense!
Take it!
He's incoherent. No point in helping him
It's illegible anyway
I'll fill it in myself
Have you really lived in Orchid Temple?
It clearly shows 70 taels
Pay up!
Take it!
Thank you!
Inn keeper!
You scared me. What do you want?
I was scared too
EXCUSE me, excuse me...
Hsiao-tsing!
Can you hear me?
Stop!
Did you hear me, stop!
Don't go!
Who said that? Who did?
Let me see who's a fugitive
I told you to stop!
That man of taste is here again
Boss!
Why are you here again?
Boss, where's that painting
"The girl washing hair"?
I'll get it
for you at once
Boss, what are you doing?
Why is it missing?
No one has ever asked for it
Well, come again tomorrow
I promise I'll find it for you
Well, I'll come again tomorrow
How could all 3 lanterns be out?
See howl deal with you
when the wolf comes
Can't you see the Yellow River flows
into the sea without returning?
Can't you see the sadness of those
with grey hair before the mirror?
Don't face the moonlight without a drink
Can't you see the Yellow River flows
into the sea without returning?
Can't you see the sadness of those
with grey hair before the mirror?
Don't face the moonlight without a drink
Give and spend and God will send
1234567
7654321
Know the scriptures, and you
have the sword for 10 years
This secret cannot be leaked
I can hardly breathe
Why is there no wolf?
The wolf's coming!
Nieh Hsiao-tsing
Hsiao-tsing...
Open the door, Hsiao-tsing!
Why are you here?
I came because I heard the lute
Come in quick!
You shouldn't come here
I'm leaving tomorrow
I must say goodbye!
Tomorrow?
Yes, but I'll try to
come back to see you
Don't!
Someone's coming!
Old Evil has a sharp nose
Hide in the water
she can't smell you
In the water again?
Sister Tsing!
I know the Old Evil's
waiting impatiently
As soon as I put on my make up
Tramp!
You're hiding a man!
I am not!
Don't deny it!
Here's the proof!
See for yourself
Why have you written such stuff?
You obviously do that to defy me
I must punish you
You bitch!
Don't forget the ordeal you suffered!
Do as I tell you or
I'll destroy your ashes
and you'll evaporate like thin air
Tonight, you must...
get me a human to increase my vitality
and prolong my life
You'll be forgiven for
this first offence
Tsing, bring medicine for your sister
Yes!
You've been betrothed to Lord Black
In three days you'll be his wife
He's a bit old
But he's not good-natured
When he flares up even we
can't control him
After you marry him, you'll never return
Hsiao-tsing!
Yes!
Try it on. Your bridal dress
Come and have a look
Seems there's some sort of smell
The smell of a living man
My dress is torn
Why are you so careless?
I must wash my hand!
Tsing, let me help you
Thank you!
You're welcome
Why are you doing that?
An oversight
Don't keep offending her
I didn't mean to
You haven't cleaned up yet
You did it on purpose, I give up
Take it off so I can mend it
Tsing, what are you doing?
I must take a bath before going out
If not
I can't get you a living man
Good girl
Learn from her
Old Evil, don't worry
I won't let you down tonight
Come!
Hurry up!
Why rush? After I get married
this room will be yours
Dress up! I won't look at you!
Come!
You...
Go!
I've a lot to tell you!
Go to the temple!
I'll wait for you there!
Yes!
Ning!
Why are you so speedy?
It's faster coming down!
Are you OK?
Do you like this picture? It's yours
The picture?
Why are you here?
My father commissioned it a year ago
Just found it 2 days ago
That's me!
See the picture and you see me
You sound like we'll never meet again
Yes! I'll marry the old monster
in 3 days
Unwillingly, I know
Go away if you want to
Let me go. It's dawn
It's better, then we can go
Let me go
I won't if you don't go with me
Release me!
Hsiao-tsing!
Don't dream on, you beggar
You want my money
I see so many of your kind
I won't be tricked
How dare you say this?
If you don't go, I'll get
someone to catch you
OK! I'll go!
Take care!
Mister!
I can't find the picture!
We'll change it to another
I saw the girl
Forget her. She died a year ago!
It's pouring, go and find shelter!
Don't curse her
Keep to my side
You are totally wet
Don't be superstitious!
Don't go away!
Who's shouting?
I'm not a fugitive!
Grab the shouting one
You won't get a reward
Get him
So cool
The bearded man is a killer
Is she dangerous?
Help me on my feet
Beware, don't let my new gown get wet
You can't effort it
I'm coming to save you
My mom will punish me; | wet my clothes