In order for you to hear me,
my words are soft
I ike a seagul I' s footpr int.
Wonton noodles.
Thank you.
Where' s the cute mute gi r I from last t ime?
What' s the use of cuteness when you' re mute?
Would you have let me marry a dea f gi r I?
What a pi ty. She was cute, but she was mute.
She i s not a mute.
She' s hear ing- impa i red.
We can hear.
She can' t.
She has a name, and her name i s Yang Yang.
Her s ign language name i s: Yang Yang.
Are you okay?
Eat something.
I don' t want to.
What' s wrong?
You don' t make those char i ty boxes anymore.
Rejected?
Reject ion.
I don' t even know i f our love ever started.
Has i t rea I I y started?
I don' t know.
I know.
Before I met your mother,
I' ve been rejected 23 t imes.
23 t imes?
Quiet down or your mom wi I I hear me.
Turn on the faucet.
Come.
Dad, I' m surpr i sed
you have such a r ich hi story.
I t was just tough luck,
not being able to meet your mother f i rst.
She' s a good woman.
Even though she' s loud and nagging,
but she st i I I takes care of
the household and us.
Just now,
she yel led at you outs ide,
then she came in and tel I s me to console you.
That' s how she i s.
She seems tough but she' s soft hearted.
What do you mean?
She' s got a kni fe for a mouth
and tofu for a heart.
0h.
Honest I y,
what k ind of gi r I s do you I ike?
When you' re in a stable relat ionship,
don' t forget to br ing her home
so we can meet her.
Dad,
would you let me date...
a gi r I who can' t hear?
Dear,
What' s up? Did he say anything?
I s he st i I I sad?
What k ind of a gi r I,
can sweep our Tian Kuo off hi s feet?
I would I ike to see i f she i s fat or sk inny.
She can' t hear.
Can' t hear?
You mean "can' t hear"
as in her ears don' t work?
Duh. What el se could i t be? Her nose?
Move the cha i rs.
Dear, you okay?
I' m f ine.
Tian Kuo sa id that a I though she can' t hear,
she i s a hard work ing,
opt imi st ic, cute, I i vel y,
f i I ia I, amicable, and k ind gi r I.
0h.
She i s nice to her s i ster,
and everyone around her.
Uh.
Tian Kuo sa id so.
There' s nothing wrong
wi th not being able to hear.
So long as you don' t say anything
no one wi I I know.
What i f you need to say something?
Then wr i te i t down.
Don' forget that Tian Kuo know s ign language.
Tian Kuo does, but we don' t.
No.
That' s true.
(March to Dea f I ympics- X iao Peng #1)
Tian Kuo.
Huang Tian Kuo.
Come down and go del i ver lunch boxes.
How many take outs?
Three.
Three take- outs.
Where i s he?
Doesn' t he know we' re busy?
What.
Your s ign language sucks.
Luck i I y I understand.
Go. Go. Go.
I don' t need you to tel I me.
I' m hi s mom.
What' s the hurry.
Tian Kuo.
Wi I I you come help mommy?
Mom. Dad.
Tian Kuo. Take thi s to the Hong Ta i Company.
The receipt i s on top.
- 0kay. - Ride careful I y.
Thank you.
Tian Kuo, your sa fety helmet.
- You must wear the helmet. - Thanks, mom.
Here.
Thi s i s $3000. Keep i t.
Don' t hurry back.
Go have fun wi th your fr iends.
Buy or eat something wi th thi s money.
0h, yeah, and...
Cheer up.
Ah?
Yes, yes, yes...
Cheer up i s the way to go.
Are you st i I I mad at me?
Sorry,
I didn' t mean to f ight wi th you last t ime.
Wi I I you forgi ve me, please?
Wi I I you stop being angry?
I' m love- s ick. Don' t hi t me.
Gi r I s should' nt be so narrow minded.
I a I ready sa id I didn' t look down
on sma I I money.
Wi I I you stop being unreasonable?
Who would be angry for cash or coins?
Don' t think you' re the onl y one wi th digni ty.
I have temper too.
I t' s f ini shed.
She' I I never ta lked to me aga in.
I sn' t an apology enough?
What' s up?
Are you okay?
I' m f ine.
We' re going to eat later.
You want to come?
Sure.
Just go back.
You?
I' I I wa i t for them.
I can wa i t wi th you.
There' s no need.
We' re going to eat later.
I can go wi th you guys.
I don' t want you to come.
(The end i s near. Start plant ing trees.)
(0ne tree.)
(Two trees.)
(Three trees make a beaut i ful forest.)
(0ne acre of ra in forest vani sh each second)
(which i s the s i ze of two footba I I f ields)
(137 spec ies of anima I s
become ext inct da i I y)
(I f the s i tuat ion cont inues,)
(The water bi rds may soon be ext inct.)
(So to prevent that from happening to you,)
(Take me and plant me in your home.)
Have you ever thought that
we might not get a long?
Not everyone can love water bi rds and trees.
Maybe someone wants me to di sappear.
And you...
become ext inct.
You drank a Icohol?
What were you think ing?
You' ve just recovered, you can' t dr ink.
What i f i t a ffects your tra ining?
Have you forgotten your dream?
You onl y care about my dreams.
What about yours?
What?
What i s your dream?
Doesn' t I i v ing for another person bother you?
What are you ta lk ing about?
Your dream i s my dream.
Why must you stea I my dream?
Stea I?
You are you, and I am I.
Why do you project my dream on yoursel f?
No one can I i ve for another person.
I may not be able to hear,
but I st i I I need my own I i fe.
I won' t get gold meda I s my ent i re I i fe.
You shouldn' t sacr i f ice your I i fe for me.
Can you tel I me what happened?
The coach told me,
My performance has regressed.
I t' s probabl y going to a ffect my el igibi I i ty.
You can' t compete anymore?
No I can' t.
I' ve lost the chance to compete thi s year,
the chance to show the wor Id
how hard I' ve worked,
and the chance for you
to wave that f lag for me.
Al I of the hard work i s wasted.
Sorry.
I t' s a I I my faul t.
Don' t you understand?
Al I thi s has nothing to do wi th you.
I' m not sorry that I cannot get a meda I,
i t' s because I can' t get the meda I for you!
For me?
You work so hard.
You never go out dat ing.
You sk ip mea I s.
You' ve sacr i f iced everything for me,
but I can' t win a gold meda I for you.
How can I face you?
How wi I I we pay the loan
wi thout the pr i ze money?
Don' t worry about the loan...
I' m your elder,
but I let you take care of me.
Who' s tak ing care of whom, does i t matter?
I don' t want to be your burden.
You are not my burden.
You are my s i ster.
I onl y need to stand st i I I when I perform.
But when you swim,
you' re compet ing in mi I I i-seconds.
To have you as an elder s i ster,
makes me so proud.
When we were k ids.
You ignored those who bul I ied you.
You never got angry.
Yet when someone bul I ied me,
you would go and beat them up.
Hav ing you as my elder s i ster,
I feel so proud.
You' ve never been a burden to me.
I f there i s a next I i fe,
Wi I I you st i I I be my s i ster?
(Happy Mea I Box Boy: How are you?)
(Me too. You need to rest.)
(March to Dea f I ympics- X iao Peng #1:)
(You have the wrong person.)
(You must have mi staken me for another gi r l)
(I am Yang Yang.)
(I know you are Yang Yang.)
(Since you never repl y to my messages,)
(and I can' t stop think ing of you,)
(I fantas i zed that you
wrote me many messages)
(Then I repl ied to them.)
(I can go to s leep now.)
(Are we that fami I iar?)
(Do you think that we won' t get a long)
(because of hear ing problems?)
(Do you have a dream?)
(Yes.)
(Marry a gi r I,)
(have two k ids.)
(0ne boy, one gi r I.)
(I s i t an imposs ible dream,)
(for a hear ing person to date someone)
(who i s hear ing impa i red?)
(I t' s eas ier than your s i ster winning a meda l)
Why i s she ignor ing me aga in?
Did I say something wrong aga in?
Yang Yang
I love you.
She' s gone aga in.
I t' s so beaut i ful here.
Do you remember catching crabs
when we were k ids?
I do.
We a lways returned home
a I I di rty and smel I y.
Mom used to yel I at us so angr i I y.
I laughed and sa id that
you ran I ike a water bi rd.
A boy once told me,
That I looked I ike a water bi rd.
He' s seen you run as wel I?
I s that boy Tian Kuo?
Yes.
He looks I ike a good guy.
You two are a good match.
I' m not going to date him.
Why?
He can' t hear ei ther.
Do you I ike him?
I' ve often thought of him.
How come you can' t just say you I ike him?
I s i t because of me?
Egrettas f I y according to seasons.
I hope you can be I ike an water bi rd,
and not be conf ined to one place.
I f you leave me one day,
and f I y freel y I ike a water bi rd.
I would be very happy.
You don' t want me to stay by your s ide?
No, I don' t mean that.
I want you to bel ieve that
I can be independent.
I didn' t say I don' t bel ieve you.
I f you bel ieve that I could be independent,
why would you reject a dea f person?
I t' s because you spend a I I your t ime on me.
You think you can' t take care of him.
You don' t think
the dea f can take care of others.
Dad a lways encouraged us,
and told us to never gi ve up.
I did not gi ve up swimming.
You should not gi ve up on him.
What' s up?
- For me? - Yeah.
When did i t arr i ve?
I don' t know.
I thought i t belonged to a customer,
but i t sa id Tian Kuo.
You are Huang Tian Kuo, so i t must be yours.
There' s money too.
Lots of i t.
Why did you come back?
She probabl y hasn' t gone too far...
So what i f I get her back.
Ah?
Even i f I get her back,
would you guys accept her?
That' s the gi r I who can' t hear?
The hard- work ing, opt imi st ic, cute,
I i vel y, energet ic, f i I ia I,
k ind, nice to her s i ster, and nice to everyone?
Yes.
Dear.
We should f ind t ime to learn s ign language.
Huh?
Ah what?
You know.
Mommy just loves to ta lk.
Somet imes my chin
gets sore because I ta lks too much.
I t' s good to let i t rest every once in a whi le.
That would be better, r ight?
Yes, then my ears can rest too.
You think I' m noi sy?
You' re the one that sa id i t, not me.
So you guys are okay?
Thank you mom, thank you dad.
I love you guys.
I love you guys to death.
Yang Yang
I want to inv i te you home for dinner.
Why?
I want to introduce you to my parents.
Because I I ike you.
I want to be your boyfr iend.
But I can' t hear.
They won' t accept me.
They wi I I see.
Bes ides, you told me before,
i f the dea f cannot see,
then they wi I I be uneasy.
I guarantee you,
I wi I I let you,
and them
see my love for you.
Can I inv i te you home for dinner?
Why?
I want to introduce you to my parents.
I want to gi ve you a job at our restaurant.
But I can' t hear.
Wi I I your parents agree?
They...
wi I I see
wi I I see my...
They wi I I see your effort and dedicat ion.
Dad Mom
Dear, they are here.
So pretty.
Thi s i s the gi r I I was ta lk ing about.
Yang Yang.
Hurry. Let her s i t.
They asked you to have a seat.
Tian Kuo' s Mom, I.
Move on.
(We welcome you.)
(Thank you for I ik ing Tian Kuo.)
(Tian Kuo i s just I ike you.)
(Hard- work ing.)
(0pt imi st ic.)
Hurry up.
(Cute.)
Next one.
(Li vel y.)
Hurry up.
(Fi I ia I.)
Very amicable.
Very k ind.
(Nice to hi s s i ster.)
Does Tian Kuo have a s i ster?
I don' t think so.
Why did you put down s i ster?
He made a mi stake.
Nice to hi s parents
Next one.
Nice to everybody. Hurry.
(So, wi I I you marry him?)
She never sa id she' s going to marry me.
How would you know i f you don' t ask?
She' s not even my gi r I fr iend.
Then what k ind of a fr iend i s she?
I do.
You can ta lk?
She can ta lk.
I thought you can' t hear.
I can hear.
Why didn' t you say anything?
You never asked.
That' s because... because...
I thought you couldn' t hear.
I didn' t think you could hear ei ther.
How i s that poss ible?
I sel I mea I boxes.
What does that have to do
wi th the abi I i ty to hear?
True.
How are they related?
Are they related?
I don' t think so.
I must have sa id something in front of you.
Yeah.
Yesterday.
Technica I I y,
you' ve sa id something behind me.
You heard a I I that?
Then why did you I ie to me?
You did' nt tel I me the truth ei ther.
I asked you why you' re inv i t ing me
to your house.
You sa id you were going to f ind me a job.
So
You didn' t come here to see my parents
because
I can hear, r ight?
0f course not.
I t' s because...
I I ike you.
Did you hear that.
She sa id she I ikes him.
I heard i t.
She I ikes him.
Wa i t.
Then how did you guys ta lk when you dated?
We didn' t ta lk.
We used s ign language.
Sign language?
I' ve actua I I y imagined your voice.
0h.
Yeah.
Who does i t sound I ike?
Just I ike
you.
How did you become
so sk i I led in s ign language?
When I was in col lege,
I met a s ign language teacher.
He asked me i f I was interested.
So I studied under him.
You must have been a di I igent student.
Honest I y, a fter I met you,
I spent a lot of work on my s ign language.
When I was young,
I did not I ike s ign langugage,
because I a lways have to trans late
for X iao Peng,
so I never have enough t ime for mysel f.
Unt i I one day,
X iao Peng asked me i f the piano sounds nice.
Then I started cry ing.
From that day on,
I studied s ign language di I igent I y.
I want her to understand a I I of the sounds.
I got i t.
I t' s I ike when I wanted you to hear the ra in.
Why?
I think i t sounds I ike longing.
When did the water bi rd
I gave you have s ibl ings?
Whenever I think of you,
I' I I throw in a dol lar.
Slowl y, each one f i I led to capac i ty.
So I had to buy a new one.
I know you love me,
but can you let me go f i rst?
Did you see X iao Peng?
X iao Peng?
Where?
Thanks.
Go. Go. Go.
Why didn' t you go to pract ice?
I qui t the compet i t ion.
What do you mean?
I can' t rega in my speed in t ime.
I' ve dec ided to look for a job f i rst,
and pract ice whi le I work.
When I' m ready
I' I I enter the next compet i t ion.
Don' t worry about the money.
I' I I handle i t.
Just focus on your tra ining.
I told you.
I cannot get gold meda I s my ent i re I i fe.
Even i f I do,
I st i I I have to work to support mysel f.
Whether I am a coach or a jani tor,
as long as I am ready,
I can st i I I enter the compet i t ion.
Awesome!
So touching
I support you!
Look at me.
Lin X iao Peng.
In my heart.
You are a I ready number one!
Number one.
Number one forever.
Thank you.
Number one.
(Four years later.)
(Love and dreams are mi raculous.)
(They don' t need to be heard, to be sa id,)
(or trans lated.)