It's you again, Nagara.
Get yourseIf together!
Damn!
You use your muscle to
swing your sword,
so you give in to
the weight of the sword.
Learn from Azumi. The strength comes
not from muscIe, but from speed!
Where is Azumi?
Oh yeah, she's not here.
She was just her e a while ago.
Yeah, she often disappears.
Azumi! Azumi!
AZUMI
I wonder how far this sky goes.
It'll be any day now when we cross that
mountain and enter the outside world.
That's right. We are going to
pursue our mission then.
Excellent...
Yes, we are always going
to stick together.
Can't wait to leave this
mountain and raise some heIl!
I can't see any stars.
Of course you can't.
It's still daytime.
Stars only come out at night.
Then where are they during the day?
Time to eat!
I'm starving.
We're starving!
Master, isn't this a bit overcooked?
Fresh water fish tastes better
when it's burnt like this.
- Nagara.
- Yes, Master.
You're soaking wet.
What happened to you?
We were training in
underwater combat.
Master, he lost again today.
- He fell into the river.
- He lost and fell into the river.
Skip your meal today.
No food, no mission,
you have no chance.
- What do you mean, fools?
- Hey, stop.
Let's get him.
Hey, let's eat.
- Come, hurry up.
- Ouch, that hurts.
Lately I'm beginning to see
who's the strongest.
Either Nachi or Azumi are
number 1 and 2...
Azumi is fast, and Nachi is strong.
Ukiha and Hyuga are an even 3;
the rest of us are more or less the same.
I think I am one of the strongest,
wouldn't you all agree?
Hey, is that your only response?
Nachi, that looks cool.
Good luck charm,
is it supposed to work?
Something like this only works
for someone who believes in it.
Then it won't work for me.
Yeah, welI, you're a monkey.
I don't want to hear that from a
frog-face like you.
He's a frog, a frog!
We are going to leave this mountain.
Leave? This Mountain?
Do you really mean it, Master?
At last, the time has come for us
to carry out our mission.
Yes.
Finaly, we'll all get to
carry out our mission.
Is this your son?
Our Lord Tokugawa won the war,
yet all this misery is left behind.
It's time we put an end to such wars.
We must try everything possible
to build a peaceful nation.
I doubt very much that the
Toyotomi Allies will retreat now.
Most likely this conflict and chaos
will continue for some time to come.
Unless we eradicate ambitious warlords
trying to take over the nation,
we will never see any peace here.
Gessai.
Assassins are the answer.
Train a group of master assassins
and have them exterminate
every single warlord who intends
to cause conflict.
Priest Tenkai, I, Gessai, swear on
my life to accomplish your wish.
Azumi, wake everyone up
and bring them to the clearing.
I had acknowledged your potential
when you were yet very young,
and have trained and brought up
all ten of you.
Your skills in the martial arts
already exceed
by far those of warriors
in the outside world.
The time has finally come for you
to go to the outside world,
unknown to you since you
were brought here,
and use your skills to
perform your duty.
You all grew up and trained together,
thus you all know one another truly
well and have strong bonds.
Now, make a team of two
with the one you like best.
Azumi.
Are you done?
Listen to me well.
The mission that will be given
to you from this moment on
will be most severe and rigorous.
An assassin is unable to
choose whom to kill.
Depending on your mission,
sometimes you must kill a child,
or a great and respected person.
The way of the assassin is to have a
mind of steel and to become inhuman:
thus, I give you this final test.
Slay each other.
Slay your teammate.
Kill!
The one who loses this fight
and loses his life has no aptitude
to pursue the mission that
lies ahead of us.
The weak-minded one who
can't kill his friend
will not be able to pursue
his mission either.
The winners of this fight
should terminate their counterpart
and come back to the hut.
Should you think of escaping
without fighting,
you must know that you
cannot survive.
Begin!
It's Master's order.
We have no choice.
Nagara! Come!
I want to pursue my mission.
I trust that you do, too.
Nachi.
One of us will be left alive
and pursue our mission.
Nachi.
Nachi, don't do it!
Azumi. This is our destiny.
Get ready!
Azumi...
You have become really strong.
Nachi.
Take this...
This is crazy!
Why?
I don't know why either.
But if we try as hard now as they would
have tried in pursuing our mission,
their deaths won't be in vain,
right, Master?
So this is a village.
Master.
Aren't we going to help?
- Master.
- Don't move, don't get involved!
How come? We can easily
get rid of them.
You have an important mission.
This is no time to be mixed up
in a trifling matter.
They will all be massacred.
Don't draw your sword unless
it is your mission to do so.
Isn't it our mission to slay those
kinds of bad guys?
Master!
Why, why not? Why, Master?
Why couldn't we kill them?
Merely kiling a hundred bandits
will not change this nation.
As always, well done.
These kids have grown up
to be pretty sharp.
What's going on?
I brought a letter from Priest Tenkai.
Guys, good luck.
Who was that?
He is a Ninja called Nagato.
Throughout this grave mission,
he will be in and out,
but always moving along with us.
What does it say?
"The following three warlords
Nagamasa Asano, Kiyomasa Kato"
"and Masayuki Sanada will not
regard the battle"
"of Sekigahara as the ultimate
defeat of the Toyotomi."
"They claim the young prince, Hideyori,"
"to be the true loyal successor
to the head of the nation."
"They press for the leadership
of the nation to be"
"returned to Toyotomi
once he becomes an adult."
"These three are dangerous rebels
who will harm Togugawa."
"They should be eliminated."
Hey, girl. What are you doing?
Stop right there.
It's a young girl on her own.
It's okay.
Yes, sir.
What a pretty girl she is, isn't she?
What are you doing?
Can't you see what I'm doing?
I'm fishing.
Fishing?
Haven't you ever fished?
Oh, I see, you have never gone fishing.
Fishing is fun.
And, when I am fishing like this,
I can for get about all of the terrible
things that go on in this country.
Moreover,
if you catch a big fish like this,
you can boast for the rest of your life.
Furthermore, a couple of fish from
this pond will make you full.
So you are hungry,
and you want to eat a fish.
This is how you catch a fish.
What the hell's she doing?
Kill him now!
That's enough. Let's go!
Well, you are very amusing.
What is your name?
Azumi.
What's yours?
Girl, you'd better watch
how you talk to our lord.
My name is Nagamasa.
Nagamasa Asano is my name.
You are the one that wants
to start another war.
Why?
Such a young girl.
What a pity.
I feel sorry for you...
Are you sure about that?
Yes, sir. Asano clan is concealing the
fact, but Nagamasa was assassinated.
All of the guards were killed.
How did they do that?
Who are these assassins?
They must be of the Ieyasu clan.
Lord...
If I may say so,
we do not have any proof
that they are of the Ieyasu clan.
Proof?
Ever since Ieyasu won the victory over
the Ishida Forces in Sekigahara,
Ieyasu has been acting as though he has
the whole nation under his thumb.
The regime belongs to
our prince Hideyori Toyotomi.
Nagamasa, Masayuki Sanada
and I had pressed him
to return the regime to prince Hideyori.
The result is Nagamasa's assassination.
I am next on the list.
I am quite aware of that.
Please remain cautious, my Lord.
What?
This talk of proof and caution, Kanbei,
what happened to your warrior's way?
Kanbei, it will be too late
once my head is cut off.
I, Kanbei, will not die after you,
my Lord.
I, Kiyomasa Kato, am not
intimidated by any enemy.
Ieyasu is a stupid fool.
If all the warlords of the Toyotomi side
unite to fight against Ieyasu,
he doesn't stand a chance.
I am troubled
with a temperamental boss.
- Saru.
- Yes, sir.
We'll let them kill our Lord.
Azumi!
It's a signal. They got Kiyomasa!
Okay, let's go.
They would be happy up in heaven for us.
But Master, they weren't tough at all.
Those slowpokes were no match for us.
It's not that they weren't tough,
it's that you are too strong.
That's why you can't easily show
your strength outside of our mission.
That Ninja who looked like a monkey,
he was funny, wasn't he?
Ninja? Has anyone received
any cut from their weapons?
Master, there's no way any
Ninja can get us.
Ninja or any other, no one will
be our match.
Right.
But be careful, Ninjas daub
poison on their weapons.
Poison?
Even if it's just a pinch of poison,
it may take your life.
Oh, man, that's scary
Hey, Azumi, are you alright?
What's the matter, Azumi?
I was wondering if that Nagamasa
we killed the other day,
and this guy today,
are they truly bad guys?
What are you talking about?
What's gotten into you?
But we don't know a thing about
the guy we killed.
He must have friends like we do.
No time for silly nonsense, Azumi.
They have to be bad guys, otherwise,
why would we have to kill them.
Right, Master?
No need to ask such a question.
Enough of this nonsense.
- Have a mind of steel.
- Be quiet!
Just eat!
We have completed our mission.
I'm going to take a piss, then.
Well done in finding a double
who looked exactly like me.
Can you kill those assassins next time?
Definitely, my Lord.
Kanbei...
It amuses me to see your failure,
but the fun is over now.
Saru...
Yes, sir.
We will start the attack this time.
It hurts
I made a hole.
That's cool!
Big brother,
you're very strong.
- You're not so bad yourself.
- I know.
Right everyone, right?
Hey old man...
Listen big brother, I think I should
open a hole in the left,
that would look awesome.
You dumb ass! If you keep
doing stupid things like that,
mom will get angry.
No, I am scared of our mom.
- She is scary!
- I'm scared of our mom.
Watch your step.
It's slippery with blood.
- I'm back you guys.
- You're back.
I brought a client.
He got a job for us.
Brother, he looks like a monkey.
- Oh, oh, he got mad.
- So, what's the job?
As a matter of principle,
I don't read letters.
These are horrible assassins.
As soon as you find them,
kill them without a word.
It reads like that.
This is the drawing.
Sorry, they're a bit slow.
This girl is cute.
So, one girl, one old man, guys,
one, two, three, four...
...that's it?
Don't underestimate them.
They are tough, very tough.
We, Sajiki brothers,
have nothing to complain about
if we can kil and make some money.
She is very beautiful.
Oh, look over there.
Master, can we go take a look?
Yes, go and have some fun.
That was great.
Yes, thank you, thank you.
My name is Hyuga.
I am Yae.
Great.
- You guys are better than us.
- Please, join our troupe.
Have you trained yourself
since you were little?
Yeah, you can call it training.
Hyuga, are you guys performers?
No, but we've been living
up in the mountain, so we are flexible.
I see. We've also been doing this
ever since we coud remember,
but we're not as good as you.
Since you could remember?
Yes.
That's just like us.
This is beautiful.
It's from a foreign country.
A foreign country?
Yes, beyond the ocean.
Come on, pack up quickly.
The sun will go down soon.
Yes, boss.
Are you leaving?
We are leaving tomorrow at noon.
We are traveling performers.
If we perform the same act in the
same place, we won't have an audience.
No, I'll come tomorrow,
and every day after that, to see you.
Thank you. But I have been living
like this since I was little.
Stay well.
I'll see you again someplace.
Come on.
Hyuga, let's go.
How are the Sajiki brothers?
The Sajiki brothers are
chasing the assassins.
They've confirmed the
whereabouts of the enemy.
I have little confidence in those dim
- witted brothers to kill the assassins.
I know. Those Sajiki brothers
are just meant to be the first attack.
Saru, go to the prison
in Nishikawa.
You mean to get that guy out?
Eye for an eye.
Poison for poison.
Amagi, Hyuga, time to wake up.
Get up.
Oh no, I slept in.
Master, can I go out for a while?
Where to?
I want to see the street
performers one more time.
Oh, that sweet one.
I think I can learn from her
movement for my technique.
Don't fall for a girl in a
traveling company.
Shut up!
Well, Master, may I go?
We're leaving at noon.
Come back by then.
- I'll go with you, too.
- Me, too.
Amagi, aren't you coming?
They are in a playful mood.
Are you sure it's okay, Master?
Hey, Amagi, wake up!
How long do you need to sleep?
I thought we were to meet
tomorrow evening.
Things don't look good.
What?
They killed Kiyomasa's double
and not Kiyomasa himself.
The enemy is onto us.
They've sent a party of pursuers.
Master, what's wrong?
We've been deceived.
What?
Kiyomasa is still alive.
We killed his double.
Go get everyone.
We are leaving at once.
Amagi, I've been
telling you to get up.
Amagi, what's wrong?
Why didn't you say anything?
- They are gone.
- Oh well.
Hyuga!
Yae was so sweet.
You're fond of Yae, aren't you?
I wanted to spend a little more
time with her.
I finally met someone I liked.
They may not be too far yet.
Let's go. Come
Oh that's it! Let's look for them.
Come on, let's go.
I'm sorry, Master.
I can still do it. Our mission...
Enough. Don't talk.
I messed up. I swore I would work...
as much as all of our dead comrades.
They were a lot of fun.
Yae, I know who you like.
Who? Azumi?
No, I am talking about the guy.
What are you talking about?
You can't hide it.
I know these things very well.
Even if you fall in love, he's a
traveler and so are we.
You'll never see him again.
Such romances don't stand a chance.
Are these them?
The ages are right on the mark.
And there is an old man too.
One, two, three, one two three, one...
Aren't there too many?
There are more girls,
and not enough boys.
A rough count will do.
By the way, do you see them?
These girls are incredible.
No two ways about it,
they are the assassins.
- They don't look like the drawing.
- A rough resemblance will do.
Excuse me, sirs.
What can we do for you?
Where are you going.
Where are you headed?
You're cute.
Come, I won't do anything.
You sure are pretty.
What's your name?
Tell me your name.
Let me touch you a little.
Get this out of the way.
Damn, brother.
What a waste.
Nisai, don't you go too far.
Don't waste your life.
Don't come near me.
Give it back.
You scared me.
Stay back.
They look like the assassins too.
That's them, brother.
She is cute.
Are you pursuing us?
Yes. You're getting the idea.
They have nothing to do with us!
We kill whoever we like...
Oh, I see.
Then you have no
complaints if you get killed.
You are gorgeous.
You fool!
Hyuga!
You are truly cute.
That hurts!
It's not over, yet!
Now you got me.
Saru.
I have a job for you.
If you accept my offer, then all of
your past crimes will be for gotten.
If you get me out of here,
that means many more people will die.
What have you been doing
at a time like this?
You killed someone?
Our swords are only for the mission!
You don't understand!
The performers were attacked
instead of us.
They had our drawing.
So Yae and-
We must leave here immediately.
Kiyomasa is still alive.
We killed his double.
What did you say?
Amagi, what's wrong?
Ninja's poison got him.
Say it isn't so.
Let's go. Quick!
Let's go?
Master, what about Amagi?
Amagi won't last.
Master, what are you talking about?
You are going to leave him behind?
We can't do that!
Why do you think we have
worked so hard until now?
Damn it, I am totally confused!
Have you for gotten that we live
only to carry out our mission?
We killed our dear friends, and stood by
when villagers were murdered.
Killing an enemy we don't hate is
one thing,
but not saving innocent people
from dying...
What is our mission, then?
After everything we've been through,
how can we leave Amagi here?
Master!!
Who are you aiming your sword at?
Withdraw your sword, Ukiha
Your sword can't even kill
an insect at this moment.
It's like swinging a mere stick.
You are no longer an assassin.
Amagi.
Sorry.
Go...
...please go.
Don't be silly, Amagi.
Amagi!
Why did you do that?
I'll walk you...
to the main road.
Good bye.