1
00:00:09,634 --> 00:00:14,054
What I'd like to do today is
get your version of what happened.

2
00:00:14,723 --> 00:00:17,641
- You mean the truth?
- Of course.

3
00:00:18,184 --> 00:00:21,854
First, just state your name and
your occupation for the record.

4
00:00:22,856 --> 00:00:24,940
Egg Shen, bus driver.

5
00:00:25,650 --> 00:00:29,695
Bus driver.
What kind of bus and where, please?

6
00:00:30,905 --> 00:00:36,577
Tour bus. Bus for tourists.
San Francisco Chinatown.

7
00:00:36,745 --> 00:00:42,708
Thank you. Now, before we get
to the meat of this thing,

8
00:00:42,876 --> 00:00:46,128
do you at the present time
have any knowledge

9
00:00:46,296 --> 00:00:48,964
of the whereabouts of
a Mr Jack Burton or his truck?

10
00:00:49,132 --> 00:00:52,760
- Oh, God. Will you leave him alone?
- Mr Shen, please.

11
00:00:52,927 --> 00:00:55,554
You could be in a great deal of trouble.

12
00:00:55,722 --> 00:00:59,141
Half a city block
explodes in a ball of green flame.

13
00:00:59,309 --> 00:01:02,269
Green flame! All hell is breaking loose here.

14
00:01:02,437 --> 00:01:04,938
And there are people
who say you're involved,

15
00:01:05,106 --> 00:01:10,069
that you might be responsible,
that you're a very dangerous man.

16
00:01:10,236 --> 00:01:14,990
- Now, if you're protecting Jack Burton...
- You leave Jack Burton alone!

17
00:01:16,117 --> 00:01:20,162
We are in his debt.
He showed great courage.

18
00:01:25,502 --> 00:01:28,253
OK.

19
00:01:28,421 --> 00:01:32,091
But if I'm gonna be your attorney,
there are a few things l have to know

20
00:01:32,258 --> 00:01:34,635
that still don't make any sense to me.

21
00:01:34,803 --> 00:01:36,845
Like...

22
00:01:37,597 --> 00:01:39,890
do you really believe in magic?

23
00:01:41,101 --> 00:01:43,602
You mean Chinese black magic?

24
00:01:43,770 --> 00:01:46,688
- Yes.
- Absolutely.

25
00:01:46,856 --> 00:01:52,319
Are you still serious about this? And
monsters and ghosts as well, l suppose?

26
00:01:52,487 --> 00:01:55,531
Sure. And sorcery.

27
00:01:56,783 --> 00:02:02,204
And l suppose that you expect me
to believe in sorcery as well?

28
00:02:02,372 --> 00:02:04,706
- Of course.
- Why?

29
00:02:04,874 --> 00:02:07,126
Because it's real.

30
00:02:07,293 --> 00:02:09,294
How can l know that, Mr Shen?

31
00:02:09,462 --> 00:02:13,507
- How?
- Yes, how? Help me out here.

32
00:02:14,217 --> 00:02:15,509
Please.

33
00:02:22,392 --> 00:02:25,102
See? That was nothing.

34
00:02:26,354 --> 00:02:29,356
But that's how it always begins.

35
00:02:29,524 --> 00:02:31,859
Very small.

36
00:02:55,425 --> 00:03:00,512
<i>This is Jack Burton at the Pork-Chop Express
and I'm talkin' to whoever's listenin'.</i>

37
00:03:00,680 --> 00:03:02,764
It's like l told my last wife.

38
00:03:02,932 --> 00:03:05,893
I says "Honey,
I never drive faster than l can see."

39
00:03:06,060 --> 00:03:09,980
"Besides that, it's all in the reflexes."

40
00:03:15,653 --> 00:03:21,074
You just listen to the Pork-Chop Express and
take his advice on a dark and stormy night.

41
00:03:21,242 --> 00:03:24,077
When some wild-eyed maniac
grabs your neck,

42
00:03:24,245 --> 00:03:27,080
taps the back of your head
up against a barroom wall,

43
00:03:27,248 --> 00:03:31,126
he looks you crooked in the eye
and asks you if you've paid your dues,

44
00:03:31,294 --> 00:03:33,587
you just stare that big sucker
back in the eye,

45
00:03:33,755 --> 00:03:37,216
and remember what Jack Burton
always says.

46
00:03:37,383 --> 00:03:42,346
"Have you paid your dues, Jack?"
"Yes, sir, the check is in the mail."

47
00:03:58,863 --> 00:04:04,785
Well, you see, I'm not sayin' that I've been
everywhere and I've done everything.

48
00:04:04,953 --> 00:04:08,872
But l do know it's a pretty
amazing planet we live on here,

49
00:04:09,040 --> 00:04:14,378
and a man would have to be some kinda
fool to think we're all alone in this universe.

50
00:05:34,834 --> 00:05:37,502
I can't believe you're stuck on even.
This is odd!

51
00:05:37,670 --> 00:05:40,380
All right, even! Another even! Come on!

52
00:05:40,548 --> 00:05:43,467
You want one more? All right!

53
00:05:48,306 --> 00:05:51,099
- What do we got? He can't count.
- Even!

54
00:05:51,267 --> 00:05:55,103
Learn how to play some fan-tan here,
buddy-boy!

55
00:05:55,271 --> 00:05:57,522
Three!

56
00:06:17,460 --> 00:06:20,504
Heaven and earth, boys. What can I tell ya?

57
00:06:23,257 --> 00:06:27,511
You like that one?
What did he say, Wang? l n English?

58
00:06:27,678 --> 00:06:31,306
Something about beginner's luck.
It doesn't translate. But he quits.

59
00:06:31,474 --> 00:06:37,479
He quits? What is this? It's a brand-new day
and he's still got 100 bucks in his pocket.

60
00:06:37,647 --> 00:06:42,442
I'm not gonna complain, because I'll bet I'd
have lost my shirt in the next 20 minutes.

61
00:06:42,610 --> 00:06:45,612
Breaks my heart to do this,
but the next time I'm down here,

62
00:06:45,780 --> 00:06:49,741
you'll gang up on Jack so fast
he won't know what the hell happened.

63
00:06:49,909 --> 00:06:52,285
- No.
- Ah, sure. Easy come, easy go, Wang.

64
00:06:52,453 --> 00:06:53,578
No!

65
00:06:55,456 --> 00:06:58,375
Not next time. Now.

66
00:07:00,586 --> 00:07:03,672
Is this gonna get ugly now? I hope not.

67
00:07:03,840 --> 00:07:07,008
I thought what we were here,
racial differences aside,

68
00:07:07,176 --> 00:07:10,679
was a coupla old friends,
both of us Californians.

69
00:07:10,847 --> 00:07:13,432
Shit, Wang. It's only a game.

70
00:07:16,978 --> 00:07:18,854
Nothin' or double.

71
00:07:19,021 --> 00:07:22,107
This knife cuts this bottle in half.

72
00:07:24,110 --> 00:07:25,360
- Nothin' or double.
- Bullshit.

73
00:07:25,528 --> 00:07:28,029
- Nothin' or double.
- Why, man? Don't be stupid.

74
00:07:28,197 --> 00:07:31,199
- I need the money.
- I got near a thousand bucks here, Wang.

75
00:07:31,367 --> 00:07:33,535
1, 148, Jack.

76
00:07:39,625 --> 00:07:42,461
OK. But not that bottle.

77
00:07:45,256 --> 00:07:46,715
This bottle.

78
00:07:51,596 --> 00:07:53,221
OK.

79
00:07:53,389 --> 00:07:56,266
You're outta your mind, Wang.
God bless ya!

80
00:08:08,070 --> 00:08:11,323
- It's all in the reflexes.
- It always works at home.

81
00:08:11,491 --> 00:08:14,367
Have me over for dinner some year
and prove it.

82
00:08:14,535 --> 00:08:17,162
In the meantime, pay up: $1, 148 times two.

83
00:08:17,330 --> 00:08:20,123
- I don't have that kind of money.
- I didn't hear that.

84
00:08:20,291 --> 00:08:22,667
I'm just a poor Chinese boy, you know?

85
00:08:22,835 --> 00:08:25,504
You own a restaurant. That's more than me.

86
00:08:25,671 --> 00:08:30,425
Yeah, right. What l meant was,
I don't got that kind of money on me.

87
00:08:30,593 --> 00:08:33,553
That's what l thought you meant.
Where's your truck?

88
00:08:33,763 --> 00:08:35,931
- I gotta go somewhere.
- No, you don't.

89
00:08:36,098 --> 00:08:39,434
I do. How about we meet in my restaurant
in a few hours? I pay then.

90
00:08:39,602 --> 00:08:42,103
- You pay now. Where you gotta go?
- The airport.

91
00:08:42,271 --> 00:08:45,565
- Yeah, right. Over my dead body.
- If need be.

92
00:08:47,068 --> 00:08:50,737
- I'll follow you.
- You don't trust me? That makes me sad.

93
00:08:50,905 --> 00:08:54,783
- It reminds me of an old Chinese joke.
- Save it. I'll give you a lift. Get in.

94
00:08:54,951 --> 00:08:59,371
- You were gonna follow me, Jack.
- I know, then l came to my senses.

95
00:08:59,997 --> 00:09:03,083
- So who are we pickin' up?
- A girl. l don't wanna talk about it.

96
00:09:03,251 --> 00:09:05,502
- A girl? Where from?
- Peking.

97
00:09:06,337 --> 00:09:10,257
This is a big day in my life. l should
have gone home and gotten 40 winks.

98
00:09:10,424 --> 00:09:13,134
A girl from China?
All right, l never done that.

99
00:09:13,302 --> 00:09:18,056
I picked up girls from everywhere else,
but never from China. Is she pretty?

100
00:09:19,475 --> 00:09:22,769
- I'm gonna marry her, Jack.
- Oh, God!

101
00:09:22,937 --> 00:09:27,107
I've known her since we were kids.
I haven't seen her in five years.

102
00:09:27,275 --> 00:09:29,943
I came here alone.
I worked my fingers till they bled.

103
00:09:30,111 --> 00:09:32,112
Before you knew me, l slept on the floor.

104
00:09:32,280 --> 00:09:35,490
I saved every nickel to bring her here
because l love her so much.

105
00:09:35,658 --> 00:09:38,785
I can't eat, sleep or think properly
without her any more.

106
00:09:38,953 --> 00:09:41,746
She'll put my whole life in order.

107
00:09:41,914 --> 00:09:44,499
Boy, listen to me. Real tough guy.

108
00:09:44,667 --> 00:09:47,669
You sound a little nervous, pal.

109
00:09:48,170 --> 00:09:53,800
That's why the bottle didn't slice. My mind
and my spirit are goin' north and south.

110
00:10:01,934 --> 00:10:06,605
<i>Flight number 26 has just arrived
at gate number seven.</i>

111
00:10:11,485 --> 00:10:14,195
Whoa. Who is that?

112
00:10:15,489 --> 00:10:18,283
She has green eyes.
You know how rare that is, Jack?

113
00:10:18,451 --> 00:10:23,204
- How can you tell from here?
- Not her. She's trouble. Miao Yin.

114
00:10:24,040 --> 00:10:26,875
Beautiful green eyes, like creamy jade.

115
00:10:27,501 --> 00:10:28,793
Trouble, huh?

116
00:10:41,807 --> 00:10:44,893
- Can l ask you a serious question?
- Absolutely not.

117
00:10:45,061 --> 00:10:46,936
Would you consider jumping right into...

118
00:10:47,104 --> 00:10:49,397
Sure, but not with a man in your condition.

119
00:10:49,565 --> 00:10:54,069
- What's wrong with my condition?
- Try standing downwind where l am.

120
00:10:54,236 --> 00:10:55,236
It's Miller time.

121
00:10:55,404 --> 00:10:57,614
You know what l say when it's Miller time?

122
00:10:59,659 --> 00:11:02,118
Wait a minute!

123
00:11:02,620 --> 00:11:04,537
- Don't!
- Don't what?

124
00:11:04,705 --> 00:11:10,293
The Lords of Death. Street gang. Punks
from Chinatown. What are they doing here?

125
00:11:44,370 --> 00:11:45,954
Tara!

126
00:11:49,625 --> 00:11:51,876
Miao Yin!

127
00:12:02,304 --> 00:12:03,304
Excuse me.

128
00:12:10,479 --> 00:12:13,273
Let's you and me have a little talk, friend.

129
00:12:13,441 --> 00:12:15,066
What?

130
00:12:15,234 --> 00:12:17,235
Where'd you get that?

131
00:12:25,202 --> 00:12:26,953
Wait a minute, pal.

132
00:12:29,039 --> 00:12:30,123
Get that one!

133
00:12:38,090 --> 00:12:40,425
Come on, Jack!

134
00:12:57,067 --> 00:12:58,777
Where?

135
00:13:00,029 --> 00:13:02,197
Call the cops!

136
00:13:24,220 --> 00:13:26,471
Son of a bitch must pay!

137
00:13:30,601 --> 00:13:33,394
What's goin' on, Wang?
Why'd they steal your girl?

138
00:13:33,562 --> 00:13:37,941
You tell me! How come it's not safe to walk
in Central Park or to give a stranger a lift?

139
00:13:38,108 --> 00:13:40,235
Because the world's full of crazy people.

140
00:13:40,402 --> 00:13:43,571
The American girl knew something was up.

141
00:13:43,739 --> 00:13:45,907
Stay away from her. She's a lawyer.

142
00:13:46,075 --> 00:13:48,993
She's a what? Oh, come on!

143
00:13:49,745 --> 00:13:53,248
- What the hell...?
- They got a clubhouse where they hang out.

144
00:13:53,415 --> 00:13:55,542
- To sharpen their knives?
- I can't ask you to...

145
00:13:55,709 --> 00:13:57,585
- Where is it?
- Thank you, Jack.

146
00:14:03,342 --> 00:14:08,596
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
I am Mr Egg Shen, with this wonderful tour.

147
00:14:08,764 --> 00:14:11,391
Sit back and enjoy yourselves, see?

148
00:14:11,559 --> 00:14:17,188
Long time ago, Chinese men with
gold-rush fever flooded into California.

149
00:14:17,356 --> 00:14:20,775
We call <i>Gum Shan</i> - Mountain of Gold, see?

150
00:14:20,943 --> 00:14:24,112
Leaving behind their wives and children.

151
00:14:24,613 --> 00:14:28,741
Working for years to complete
the transcontinental railroad,

152
00:14:28,909 --> 00:14:33,121
saving all their pennies.
And then they sent for their families

153
00:14:33,289 --> 00:14:37,292
to help build this beautiful Chinatown
you see outside your window

154
00:14:37,459 --> 00:14:40,461
this fine warm day.

155
00:15:10,618 --> 00:15:13,578
- Go right, down that alley. Lords of Death!
- What alley?

156
00:15:13,746 --> 00:15:15,580
Go right! Now!

157
00:15:36,810 --> 00:15:39,729
- Where the hell are we?
- Come on, Jack.

158
00:15:42,358 --> 00:15:45,985
Excuse me, ma'am.
I don't suppose you saw a...

159
00:15:50,240 --> 00:15:51,991
No.

160
00:15:52,159 --> 00:15:54,202
Keep moving.

161
00:16:21,689 --> 00:16:23,815
- What is it? A parade?
- A funeral.

162
00:16:23,983 --> 00:16:27,568
- A fighting tong. They're Chang Sings.
- A fighting tong?

163
00:16:27,736 --> 00:16:31,572
Don't panic, Jack.
They're OK. They're good guys.

164
00:16:32,491 --> 00:16:36,452
Maybe we should try a different alley.
What do you say?

165
00:16:42,334 --> 00:16:46,129
Wang, these guys, these Sing Dings.
They got enemies?

166
00:16:46,296 --> 00:16:48,756
- Wing Kong.
- Who wear red turbans?

167
00:16:48,924 --> 00:16:50,758
Holy shit!

168
00:16:50,926 --> 00:16:53,219
These guys are animals, Jack.

169
00:18:25,437 --> 00:18:27,855
- What's happening, Wang?
- Chinese standoff.

170
00:18:28,023 --> 00:18:29,857
A what?

171
00:18:30,025 --> 00:18:32,151
Don't make a sound.

172
00:20:40,948 --> 00:20:42,490
Who's that?

173
00:21:52,352 --> 00:21:55,271
No questions! Just get outta here, Jack!

174
00:22:12,789 --> 00:22:14,790
Jack!

175
00:22:19,629 --> 00:22:22,131
- I think it was Lo Pan.
- Who?

176
00:22:39,566 --> 00:22:41,776
- Don't look, Jack!
- I already did.

177
00:22:41,943 --> 00:22:43,944
- Who? l mean, what?
- Lo Pan. Come on!

178
00:22:44,112 --> 00:22:48,032
- I can't see!
- It's OK. It's only temporary. Over here.

179
00:22:49,451 --> 00:22:51,535
Bend over.

180
00:22:52,537 --> 00:22:54,997
Yeah, yeah.

181
00:22:55,165 --> 00:22:58,626
I ran straight through him, Wang.
How the hell did l do that?

182
00:22:58,794 --> 00:23:01,295
- You didn't. It only appeared that way.
- Right!

183
00:23:01,463 --> 00:23:06,425
- Lords of Death, Jack.
- OK, I'm goin' home. Keep your money.

184
00:23:06,593 --> 00:23:08,636
- Hey, Wang Chi!
- Lookin' for us?

185
00:23:08,804 --> 00:23:12,139
- They know your name.
- That's not good. Let's go!

186
00:23:15,143 --> 00:23:17,228
- My truck!
- Forget it!

187
00:23:38,125 --> 00:23:42,670
Lords of Death controlled by the Wing Kong,
Jack. Just errand boys for the Wing Kong.

188
00:23:42,838 --> 00:23:47,174
Great! Who wiped out all those
yellow turbans? Those guys were winning.

189
00:23:53,056 --> 00:23:55,433
He says it was the Storms.
The Three Storms.

190
00:23:55,600 --> 00:23:57,852
Three guys did all that? Listen.

191
00:23:58,019 --> 00:24:01,856
What about that...
whatever it was l ran straight through?

192
00:24:02,023 --> 00:24:03,274
Fast!

193
00:24:14,995 --> 00:24:17,371
Lucky us. We made it.

194
00:24:17,539 --> 00:24:19,832
All right, where's my truck? I'm outta here.

195
00:24:20,000 --> 00:24:21,375
Isn't your truck insured?

196
00:24:21,543 --> 00:24:24,003
- Of course it is.
- Then smart man gets it later.

197
00:24:24,171 --> 00:24:25,337
Smart man calls the cops.

198
00:24:25,505 --> 00:24:28,674
- Cops got better things to do than get killed.
- So do I!

199
00:24:32,345 --> 00:24:35,973
Mutual Fidelity Insurers of Sacramento.

200
00:24:36,141 --> 00:24:40,311
Well, there's gotta be a listing, honey.
I pay 'em six G's a year in premiums.

201
00:24:40,479 --> 00:24:46,484
China is here, Mr Burton.
The Chang Sing, the Wing Kong.

202
00:24:47,152 --> 00:24:51,155
- They've been fighting for centuries.
- What does that mean? "China is here"?

203
00:24:51,323 --> 00:24:53,782
I don't know what that means.
All I know is,

204
00:24:53,950 --> 00:24:56,202
this Lo Pan character comes out of thin air

205
00:24:56,369 --> 00:25:01,749
in the middle of an alley, while his buddies
fly around, cuttin' everybody to shreds,

206
00:25:01,917 --> 00:25:05,920
and he stands there, waiting for me
to drive my truck straight through him,

207
00:25:06,087 --> 00:25:09,548
- with light comin' out of his mouth!
- Jack, please.

208
00:25:12,052 --> 00:25:14,553
- When did this happen?
- It didn't, not like he says.

209
00:25:14,721 --> 00:25:20,518
Yeah, it did. Two hours ago. Tall guy, weird
clothes. First you see him, then you don't.

210
00:25:20,685 --> 00:25:23,229
Lo Pan appeared on the street?

211
00:25:24,189 --> 00:25:27,399
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I didn't want to alarm you, Uncle.

212
00:25:27,567 --> 00:25:31,904
I'm gonna tell you about an accident
and l don't wanna hear "act of God", OK?

213
00:25:32,072 --> 00:25:35,533
All right, look. What's your name?
Mine's Jack Burton.

214
00:25:35,700 --> 00:25:39,119
- Good afternoon, Mr Wong.
- Eddie Lee, meet my friend, Jack Burton.

215
00:25:39,287 --> 00:25:42,623
- Eddie's the new maître d' here.
- And a whole lot more.

216
00:25:42,791 --> 00:25:46,293
Well, l don't know my policy number.
It's in the glove compartment.

217
00:25:46,461 --> 00:25:49,213
Just look under B-U-R-T-O-N, will ya?

218
00:25:49,381 --> 00:25:51,966
- Jack Burton?
- Yeah.

219
00:25:52,342 --> 00:25:55,636
Boy. The guy you always told me about.

220
00:25:56,680 --> 00:26:00,391
- Then that was your abandoned truck.
- Abandoned, like hell!

221
00:26:00,559 --> 00:26:02,685
Hello. Hello?

222
00:26:02,852 --> 00:26:04,311
Oh, Christ!

223
00:26:04,479 --> 00:26:07,481
Bad news. The Lords of Death
stole it after you ran away.

224
00:26:07,649 --> 00:26:11,318
- They stole my truck?
- Take it easy, Jack. You're with friends.

225
00:26:11,486 --> 00:26:13,779
- We'll find it for you.
- Damn right you will.

226
00:26:13,947 --> 00:26:16,615
And my money. And time is money
to a guy like me.

227
00:26:16,783 --> 00:26:18,742
And your phone is dead, by the way.

228
00:26:18,910 --> 00:26:24,290
- How do you think l feel? l lost a whole girl!
- The Lords of Death were only on a joyride.

229
00:26:24,457 --> 00:26:26,500
Not acting on orders from the Wing Kong.

230
00:26:26,668 --> 00:26:30,254
They just wanted a girl to sell
and Miao Yin got in the way.

231
00:26:30,422 --> 00:26:32,840
Plus, the skirmish you guys stumbled into.

232
00:26:33,008 --> 00:26:37,428
Lo Pan, the word is, ordered the boss of
the Chang Sings, Mr Lem Lee, assassinated.

233
00:26:37,596 --> 00:26:39,847
- That was his funeral.
- It was a war, Eddie.

234
00:26:40,015 --> 00:26:44,476
- What are you doing here?
- Don't panic. It's only me, Gracie Law.

235
00:26:44,644 --> 00:26:45,728
Great.

236
00:26:45,895 --> 00:26:49,023
Just passing the neighborhood
on a dark and stormy night?

237
00:26:49,190 --> 00:26:52,192
- This is my neighborhood.
- Sure it was a war.

238
00:26:52,360 --> 00:26:53,569
And anybody that showed up

239
00:26:53,737 --> 00:26:56,614
was gonna join Lem Lee
in the hell of being cut to pieces.

240
00:26:56,781 --> 00:26:59,366
- Hell of being what?
- The Chinese have a lotta hells.

241
00:26:59,534 --> 00:27:01,785
And what the hell is Gracie Law doing here?

242
00:27:01,953 --> 00:27:03,871
She can't get enough of me.

243
00:27:04,039 --> 00:27:06,540
He wishes. Look, you know me.

244
00:27:06,708 --> 00:27:10,044
I'm always pokin' my nose where it
doesn't belong and, I admit it,

245
00:27:10,211 --> 00:27:12,463
this mix-up is my fault, sort of.

246
00:27:12,631 --> 00:27:16,383
But l have it on good advice that the punks
that jumped me and took his truck,

247
00:27:16,551 --> 00:27:20,679
they took the girl they kidnapped to the
White Tiger's for a quick sale. Who was she?

248
00:27:20,847 --> 00:27:25,267
- My fiancée. The White Tiger's?
- Oh, God. I'm sorry.

249
00:27:25,435 --> 00:27:28,979
If we go tonight, we can buy her back.
A warrant's too complicated,

250
00:27:29,147 --> 00:27:31,815
- violence out of the question...
- Hold it! Slow down.

251
00:27:31,983 --> 00:27:34,360
- I'm feelin' like an outsider here.
- You are!

252
00:27:34,527 --> 00:27:37,905
Jack, listen. I need more of your help.
I can't pay you today, OK?

253
00:27:38,073 --> 00:27:40,491
- Shit.
- How can I? l need the cash for Miao Yin.

254
00:27:40,659 --> 00:27:45,412
- And it's gonna cost. She's got green eyes.
- Seriously? That's an extra.

255
00:27:45,580 --> 00:27:48,165
It's like leather bucket seats:
double the price.

256
00:27:48,333 --> 00:27:53,087
- Look, this Lo Pan l ran over... through...
- Has spirit-medium powers.

257
00:27:53,254 --> 00:27:58,050
Like the immortals.
His flesh and his bones are atomized.

258
00:27:58,218 --> 00:28:00,886
He becomes the dream.

259
00:28:01,054 --> 00:28:03,764
- What?
- That's an exaggeration, Jack, l promise.

260
00:28:03,932 --> 00:28:05,265
Please, help me.

261
00:28:05,642 --> 00:28:07,726
I got a great idea.

262
00:28:20,573 --> 00:28:22,616
- Relax.
- I am relaxed.

263
00:28:22,784 --> 00:28:26,203
Look, this is as far as I go,
because I'm a dead giveaway, see?

264
00:28:26,371 --> 00:28:30,249
I'd go in there with you, but they know
my face and they'd wanna push it in.

265
00:28:30,417 --> 00:28:32,960
- Not while I'm around.
- It's all up to you now, Jack.

266
00:28:33,128 --> 00:28:35,254
My destiny rests in your capable hands.

267
00:28:35,422 --> 00:28:37,965
- I'll do my best.
- Make them drop their guard.

268
00:28:38,133 --> 00:28:39,633
- I'll try.
- Look stupid.

269
00:28:39,801 --> 00:28:41,635
He does.

270
00:28:43,012 --> 00:28:45,723
Boy, it sure is rainin' cats and dogs.

271
00:28:46,641 --> 00:28:49,643
The cab driver said...
He told me that I could...

272
00:28:49,811 --> 00:28:53,063
Well, that the White Tiger would...

273
00:28:54,232 --> 00:28:56,108
Just a minute, please.

274
00:29:02,240 --> 00:29:06,618
Excuse me for a second, guys.
I think I know that car.

275
00:29:11,291 --> 00:29:13,667
What's she doing now?

276
00:29:13,835 --> 00:29:15,669
Strange girl.

277
00:29:20,842 --> 00:29:23,343
That building there. The White Tiger.

278
00:29:23,511 --> 00:29:27,347
God, it's creepy. Do we have to go in?
Because I will, if we have to.

279
00:29:27,515 --> 00:29:30,768
I'll go anywhere or do anything
to get my story. It's my big break.

280
00:29:30,935 --> 00:29:35,355
Just sit tight. We've got one of our
best men inside right now, stirring the pot.

281
00:29:50,580 --> 00:29:55,876
How do you do, ma'am? Henry Swanson's
my name and excitement's my game.

282
00:29:56,044 --> 00:29:59,296
- Cash or charge?
- Gosh! Cash, I guess.

283
00:29:59,464 --> 00:30:01,548
I mean, it's not deductible, is it?

284
00:30:03,927 --> 00:30:06,845
Mrs O'Toole will take care of your needs.

285
00:30:07,013 --> 00:30:09,056
Boy, l wish these were in color.

286
00:30:09,224 --> 00:30:12,893
Because what l really am
in the mood for is a girl with green eyes.

287
00:30:13,061 --> 00:30:15,562
And price is no object, Mrs O'Toole.

288
00:30:15,730 --> 00:30:19,733
Fresh off the boat's the way l like 'em.
The more exotic the better.

289
00:30:19,901 --> 00:30:22,569
Chinese girls do not come with green eyes.

290
00:30:41,381 --> 00:30:43,882
- Too long. Let's go in.
- It's only been ten minutes.

291
00:30:44,050 --> 00:30:46,093
Give the guy a chance.

292
00:30:48,471 --> 00:30:51,265
- So how long you been in the US of A?
- Three months.

293
00:30:51,432 --> 00:30:54,268
- Where from?
- Hong Kong.

294
00:30:54,435 --> 00:30:59,439
What happens? You stay here a while?
Old girls leave, new girls come in?

295
00:30:59,607 --> 00:31:03,277
Maybe. Take your tie off, please.

296
00:31:03,444 --> 00:31:06,613
Yeah, l know what you mean.
My wife gave it to me for Christmas.

297
00:31:10,743 --> 00:31:12,119
Holy shit!

298
00:32:44,337 --> 00:32:49,633
Green explosions? People flyin' in and out?
That was not real. l wanna talk to the cops.

299
00:32:49,801 --> 00:32:52,678
I want my truck back.
Now where the hell am l?

300
00:32:52,845 --> 00:32:56,056
- My office. Sit down.
- You sleep in your office?

301
00:32:56,224 --> 00:33:01,019
What l need to get straight is...
These Storms, what are they? Magicians?

302
00:33:01,187 --> 00:33:04,898
- Yeah, sort of. It's hard to explain.
- Try real hard.

303
00:33:05,066 --> 00:33:07,901
If the Storms have Miao Yin,
there's one place they'd go.

304
00:33:08,069 --> 00:33:12,114
Lo Pan. The godfather of Little China,
Mr David Lo Pan.

305
00:33:12,281 --> 00:33:15,409
You mean the Lo Pan that's
chairman of the National Orient Bank

306
00:33:15,576 --> 00:33:17,744
and owns the Wing Kong Trading Company,

307
00:33:17,912 --> 00:33:21,415
but who's so reclusive
that no one has laid eyes on him in years?

308
00:33:21,582 --> 00:33:23,917
Who the hell are you, anyway?

309
00:33:24,085 --> 00:33:27,546
I'm Margo Litzenberger.
I'm with the <i>Berkeley People's Herald</I>.

310
00:33:27,714 --> 00:33:32,050
I've been trying to get somebody from
the press to listen to me about this, Burton.

311
00:33:32,218 --> 00:33:37,055
It's not possible that you saw David Lo Pan.
The bastard's afraid to show his face.

312
00:33:37,223 --> 00:33:40,058
- He's got more enemies...
- He's got Miao Yin. I'm going!

313
00:33:40,226 --> 00:33:42,436
- Are you nuts?
- Who's that?

314
00:33:42,603 --> 00:33:45,522
It's OK, Tara. You can go back to sleep.

315
00:33:45,690 --> 00:33:47,941
- From the airport.
- This morning, sure.

316
00:33:48,109 --> 00:33:52,571
That's why I was there. l was protecting her
civil rights, making sure she gets a chance.

317
00:33:52,739 --> 00:33:56,616
This is just so shocking. l mean,
I must just be so monumentally naive.

318
00:33:56,784 --> 00:33:59,453
- You are.
- Now we have to grab your fiancée...

319
00:33:59,620 --> 00:34:02,164
Wait a minute! I'm a reasonable guy,

320
00:34:02,331 --> 00:34:04,791
but I've experienced
some unreasonable things.

321
00:34:04,959 --> 00:34:08,712
- It depends on how you look at it.
- The hell it does! So somebody

322
00:34:08,880 --> 00:34:11,173
- tell me what is goin' on!
- The truth?

323
00:34:11,340 --> 00:34:13,467
- I can take it.
- We don't know.

324
00:34:16,679 --> 00:34:20,432
- I'm going now, alone if l have to!
- Where? It's pouring out.

325
00:34:20,600 --> 00:34:24,186
- Lo Pan's. The Wing Kong Exchange.
- The Wing Kong Exchange?

326
00:34:24,353 --> 00:34:28,065
The most dangerous den of madmen
in Chinatown? You can't waltz in like...

327
00:34:28,232 --> 00:34:32,778
Like the wind. Yes, l can, Miss Law.
My mind and my spirits are as one.

328
00:34:32,945 --> 00:34:35,781
- As two. l said l was comin'.
- I'd go with you...

329
00:34:35,948 --> 00:34:38,784
I know. There's a problem with your face.

330
00:34:38,951 --> 00:34:42,954
OK! You people sit tight, hold the fort
and keep the home fires burning.

331
00:34:43,122 --> 00:34:46,625
If we're not back by dawn,
call the president.

332
00:34:56,427 --> 00:35:01,973
- This is gonna take crackerjack timing.
- Total concentration. You ready, Jack?

333
00:35:02,141 --> 00:35:04,184
I was born ready.

334
00:35:08,272 --> 00:35:10,357
I love working nights.

335
00:35:10,525 --> 00:35:12,484
Don't get up. Phone company.

336
00:35:12,652 --> 00:35:16,071
All right, boys, where's the main panel?
Probably through here.

337
00:35:24,997 --> 00:35:26,873
Wang.

338
00:35:35,758 --> 00:35:39,302
Good work, Jack.
I think they actually fell for it.

339
00:35:41,722 --> 00:35:46,017
Well, last time we had this problem was
on account of squirrels chewin' the wires.

340
00:35:46,185 --> 00:35:50,230
- I'd better locate the central junction box.
- I think it's down there.

341
00:35:55,319 --> 00:35:56,820
What does that say?

342
00:35:56,988 --> 00:35:59,823
- Hell of boiling oil.
- You're kidding!

343
00:35:59,991 --> 00:36:02,159
Yeah, l am. lt says "Keep out."

344
00:36:06,664 --> 00:36:09,124
We've got to do something!

345
00:36:13,921 --> 00:36:18,842
Goat butts against a hedge
and its horns become entangled.

346
00:36:19,802 --> 00:36:24,097
- I don't think I've had the pleasure.
- Miss Gracie Law, Mr Egg Shen.

347
00:36:24,265 --> 00:36:26,766
Egg's kind of our local authority on Lo Pan.

348
00:36:26,934 --> 00:36:29,436
- He's helping us out.
- It has been almost two hours.

349
00:36:29,604 --> 00:36:32,856
- Let's go over there, beat down the door...
- No, Miss Law.

350
00:36:33,024 --> 00:36:38,111
We have to gather our strength,
because now there's clouds and thunder.

351
00:36:38,279 --> 00:36:41,615
The image of difficulty at the beginning.

352
00:36:41,782 --> 00:36:45,452
But finally we shall bring order out of chaos.

353
00:36:50,625 --> 00:36:53,210
- Look.
- Yeah.

354
00:36:53,377 --> 00:36:56,254
What you got here is two
people dragging a third.

355
00:36:56,422 --> 00:36:58,465
Miao Yin!

356
00:37:12,855 --> 00:37:16,483
- You did that, right?
- I guess so. l hope so.

357
00:37:22,198 --> 00:37:24,491
Jack, check this out.

358
00:37:25,785 --> 00:37:27,827
So what is this? Chinese or somethin'?

359
00:37:27,995 --> 00:37:30,580
- Countin' backwards?
- Not backwards. Downwards.

360
00:37:41,092 --> 00:37:46,012
Of course the Chinese mix everything up.
Look at what they have to work with.

361
00:37:46,180 --> 00:37:50,976
There's Buddhism, Confucianism
and Taoist alchemy and sorcery.

362
00:37:51,352 --> 00:37:55,522
We take what we want and leave the rest.
Just like your salad bar.

363
00:37:55,690 --> 00:37:59,651
But there is one thing
even David Lo Pan must acknowledge.

364
00:37:59,819 --> 00:38:03,321
All movement in the universe
is caused by tension

365
00:38:03,489 --> 00:38:06,199
between positive and negative furies.

366
00:38:06,367 --> 00:38:10,704
- So when the furies are out of balance...
- As they are in Lo Pan, who is cursed.

367
00:38:10,871 --> 00:38:13,999
Then the people
turn into demons and live for ever.

368
00:38:14,166 --> 00:38:18,420
Repulsive and evil,
existing only to plague the living.

369
00:38:18,587 --> 00:38:23,717
Well then, what you're saying is
this David Lo Pan... What is he? A ghost?

370
00:38:23,884 --> 00:38:29,848
Plays at being a man.
A creature of vast, dark, destructive power.

371
00:38:30,433 --> 00:38:35,478
All right, out this hatch and up the cable.
Does that sound like a brilliant idea or what?

372
00:38:35,646 --> 00:38:38,481
The cable is three stories high
and covered with grease.

373
00:38:38,649 --> 00:38:42,485
Exactly. It's real and we can touch it,
so at least we know where we stand.

374
00:38:42,653 --> 00:38:44,279
Yeah, in deep shit.

375
00:38:47,116 --> 00:38:49,701
- What?
- What the hell...?

376
00:38:51,579 --> 00:38:53,038
- Shit!
- See?

377
00:38:53,205 --> 00:38:56,041
You think they'd let us
walk in and out like the wind?

378
00:38:56,208 --> 00:38:58,835
Yes.
I thought that was your whole damn point!

379
00:38:59,003 --> 00:39:01,254
My point was to find Miao Yin at any cost!

380
00:39:01,422 --> 00:39:04,257
- This is salt water, Wang.
- And get your truck back!

381
00:39:04,425 --> 00:39:08,053
- I'll buy another one.
- But there's only one Miao Yin!

382
00:39:36,040 --> 00:39:38,083
Jesus Christ! Where are we?

383
00:39:38,250 --> 00:39:40,710
Hell of the upside-down sinners!

384
00:39:55,142 --> 00:39:59,270
Hey, you! Come on over here
and fight like a man!

385
00:40:38,519 --> 00:40:42,063
Shit, Jack. I don't like the looks of this.

386
00:40:44,733 --> 00:40:47,026
- Where are we, Wang?
- You are nowhere!

387
00:41:13,387 --> 00:41:15,221
Oh, boy.

388
00:41:15,389 --> 00:41:18,349
Look, we came here to see David Lo Pan,
all right?

389
00:41:19,059 --> 00:41:20,685
David Lo Pan?

390
00:41:20,853 --> 00:41:24,397
- Then you have succeeded, Mr Burton.
- What, you?

391
00:41:25,316 --> 00:41:28,401
- I don't get this at all. I thought...
- Shut up, Mr Burton!

392
00:41:28,569 --> 00:41:32,614
- You are not put upon this world to "get it".
- Come on! Lo Pan is like...

393
00:41:32,781 --> 00:41:34,574
Nothing you can understand.

394
00:41:34,742 --> 00:41:39,913
There are many mysteries and unanswerable
questions, even in a life as short as yours.

395
00:41:40,080 --> 00:41:43,666
The way l see it, it doesn't mean
we shouldn't ask. Where's my truck?

396
00:41:43,834 --> 00:41:48,129
You are not looking for a truck. You're
looking for a girl. A girl with green eyes.

397
00:41:48,297 --> 00:41:51,549
- Yes.
- She must be something extraordinary.

398
00:41:51,717 --> 00:41:54,260
Or I'm not about to waste
another 2,000 years.

399
00:41:54,428 --> 00:41:57,889
There can't be many Chinese girls
with green eyes these days.

400
00:41:58,057 --> 00:42:01,267
- There are not. Never were.
- So beggars can't be choosers.

401
00:42:01,435 --> 00:42:03,478
But l can!

402
00:42:04,271 --> 00:42:07,065
Tell me about Miao Yin.

403
00:42:07,233 --> 00:42:09,484
What province is she from? Hunan?

404
00:42:10,194 --> 00:42:14,280
Her mother? Her father?
He must be a holy man. l must know.

405
00:42:14,448 --> 00:42:17,951
You got a tongue, Dave. Ask her yourself.

406
00:42:23,082 --> 00:42:27,794
Mr Burton, if you have an influence over
your youthful friend, you better exert it now.

407
00:42:27,962 --> 00:42:31,965
Otherwise I will send both of you to
the hell where people are skinned alive.

408
00:42:32,132 --> 00:42:34,467
It's that simple. Understand?

409
00:42:35,511 --> 00:42:39,222
- Are you crazy? ls that your problem?
- No, he means it, Jack.

410
00:42:39,390 --> 00:42:44,435
My problem is this place.
This place is my tomb. I'm buried here.

411
00:42:44,603 --> 00:42:50,692
A young man, a king, a warrior,
is entombed in this old man's crippled body.

412
00:42:52,361 --> 00:42:54,821
And all l need is a woman, Mr Burton,

413
00:42:54,989 --> 00:42:58,199
a special kind of woman
with dragon-green eyes,

414
00:42:58,367 --> 00:43:00,326
to make me whole and young again,

415
00:43:00,494 --> 00:43:03,705
so that l may
rule the universe from beyond the grave.

416
00:43:03,872 --> 00:43:07,125
- Ch'ing-ti. The God of the East.
- Who, him? This guy?

417
00:43:07,293 --> 00:43:09,252
No, not me, Mr Burton.

418
00:43:10,629 --> 00:43:15,174
My demon. The god l must appease
in order to regain my heart, my blood.

419
00:43:15,801 --> 00:43:19,470
A girl with green eyes to satisfy Ch'ing-ti,

420
00:43:19,638 --> 00:43:22,432
a girl brave enough
to embrace the naked blade.

421
00:43:22,600 --> 00:43:24,726
- When l find her, I will marry her.
- Never!

422
00:43:24,893 --> 00:43:27,228
Ch'ing-ti will be happy and my curse lifted.

423
00:43:27,396 --> 00:43:30,148
You can rule the universe
from beyond the grave.

424
00:43:30,316 --> 00:43:32,650
- Indeed!
- Or check into a psycho ward.

425
00:43:32,818 --> 00:43:35,153
Whichever comes first.

426
00:43:35,321 --> 00:43:36,988
What, I'm supposed to buy this shit?

427
00:43:37,156 --> 00:43:40,116
2,000 years
and he can't find a broad to fit the bill?

428
00:43:40,284 --> 00:43:43,328
Come on, Dave, you must be doin'
somethin' seriously wrong.

429
00:43:43,495 --> 00:43:49,125
There have been others, to be sure.
There are always others, are there not?

430
00:43:49,293 --> 00:43:53,379
You seem to be one who knows
the difficulties between men and women,

431
00:43:53,547 --> 00:43:55,882
how seldom it works out.

432
00:43:56,425 --> 00:43:59,802
And yet we all keep trying, like fools.

433
00:44:01,889 --> 00:44:07,644
Who are these people? Friends of yours?
Now this really pisses me off to no end!

434
00:44:07,811 --> 00:44:11,314
- Come on, stick around!
- Where's Miao Yin? l n this building?

435
00:44:11,482 --> 00:44:13,024
- Safe.
- Where is she?

436
00:44:13,192 --> 00:44:16,694
Safe.
Safer with me than any creature on earth!

437
00:44:18,197 --> 00:44:21,157
Go ahead. You want bad publicity?
Give us the run-around.

438
00:44:21,325 --> 00:44:25,411
But this woman has a deadline,
and her pen is mightier than your sword.

439
00:44:25,579 --> 00:44:28,331
- Yeah.
- No visitors.

440
00:44:28,499 --> 00:44:32,752
- I don't make the policy around here.
- Come on, man! Give 'em a tour.

441
00:44:32,920 --> 00:44:35,254
What's it gonna hurt?

442
00:44:36,340 --> 00:44:38,591
I can help you.

443
00:45:07,579 --> 00:45:10,081
- Are you OK, Jack?
- Yeah.

444
00:45:12,334 --> 00:45:16,337
We're in a room.
No windows, a few skeletons.

445
00:45:16,505 --> 00:45:19,590
- Where's the light coming from?
- The floor.

446
00:45:35,023 --> 00:45:38,568
With the easing of trade restrictions,

447
00:45:38,736 --> 00:45:43,573
next year we'll start importing
a lot of strange things from Peking.

448
00:45:43,741 --> 00:45:46,659
What sort of strange things?

449
00:45:46,827 --> 00:45:49,162
Are we going up or down?

450
00:45:49,329 --> 00:45:51,414
It feels like down.

451
00:46:11,143 --> 00:46:13,603
Great. Thank you, Jack.

452
00:46:13,771 --> 00:46:18,733
I think we've come up. First we went down.
Now they've brought us up.

453
00:46:19,818 --> 00:46:24,697
Two, three feet thick, I'll bet. Probably
welded shut and covered with brick by now.

454
00:46:24,865 --> 00:46:28,701
- Don't give up, Jack.
- OK. Let's just chew our way outta here!

455
00:46:28,869 --> 00:46:31,412
Lo Pan has plans for us,
or we'd be dead doornails.

456
00:46:31,580 --> 00:46:36,626
Which Lo Pan? Little old basket case
on wheels, or the ten-foot-tall roadblock?

457
00:46:36,794 --> 00:46:41,672
- One and the same person, Jack.
- You know something you're not tellin' me.

458
00:46:41,840 --> 00:46:44,217
Myths and legends.

459
00:46:44,968 --> 00:46:48,262
- I don't wanna insult you.
- No, no. Go ahead.

460
00:46:49,097 --> 00:46:50,681
Insult me.

461
00:46:52,643 --> 00:46:56,062
It's about all sorts of scary things:
an ancient army of the dead,

462
00:46:56,230 --> 00:46:59,732
the Spirit City and monkey sacrifices.

463
00:46:59,900 --> 00:47:01,984
The First Sovereign Emperor of China,

464
00:47:02,152 --> 00:47:06,072
that mad monarch who federated our
seven warring states, defeated Lo Pan

465
00:47:06,240 --> 00:47:11,452
and imposed upon him
that horrible curse of no flesh in 272 BC.

466
00:47:12,371 --> 00:47:16,749
A lot of Chinese hear these things
when we're kids, then we grow up,

467
00:47:17,709 --> 00:47:19,836
and pretend not to believe them.

468
00:47:20,420 --> 00:47:23,256
- No horseshit, Wang.
- No horseshit, Jack.

469
00:47:23,423 --> 00:47:28,761
I don't blame you. I'm Chinese and l don't
even wanna believe it, but it's for real.

470
00:47:28,929 --> 00:47:31,389
Sorcery, the Chinese black magic.

471
00:47:36,770 --> 00:47:38,855
Blindfolds!

472
00:47:57,958 --> 00:48:00,084
You make one move...

473
00:48:06,258 --> 00:48:10,136
Now, let's try that again.
Don't make me kill you, tough guy.

474
00:48:11,972 --> 00:48:13,931
Come on, Jack!

475
00:48:14,391 --> 00:48:16,475
- Come on!
- How?

476
00:49:10,989 --> 00:49:12,949
- Great work, Jack.
- Yeah.

477
00:49:13,116 --> 00:49:15,034
We're all in: me, Gracie and Margo.

478
00:49:15,202 --> 00:49:18,287
Uncle Chu and Egg
are in Egg's bus, ready to get us out.

479
00:49:18,455 --> 00:49:19,872
- Right.
- Here, Jack.

480
00:49:20,040 --> 00:49:22,083
I'll trade ya.

481
00:49:23,293 --> 00:49:25,795
All right, which way?
Fast, before they wake up.

482
00:49:25,963 --> 00:49:28,547
There, l think. Down there.

483
00:49:34,888 --> 00:49:36,973
No pathetic excuses.

484
00:49:37,975 --> 00:49:44,063
I smell the blood of human beings. Find
them. Boil them until their flesh falls off.

485
00:49:44,356 --> 00:49:46,107
You heard me!

486
00:50:42,831 --> 00:50:44,915
Empty.

487
00:50:47,252 --> 00:50:49,920
I need you, Miao Yin.

488
00:50:50,338 --> 00:50:54,800
You, whose eyes flash
like emerald lightning.

489
00:50:55,969 --> 00:50:59,930
Ch'ing-ti, make me flesh again soon.

490
00:51:02,017 --> 00:51:03,476
Please.

491
00:51:05,270 --> 00:51:07,146
Let's go. It's clear.

492
00:51:12,986 --> 00:51:15,071
Safety!

493
00:51:18,950 --> 00:51:20,534
Wang!

494
00:51:26,458 --> 00:51:29,168
First time you ever plugged somebody?

495
00:51:29,795 --> 00:51:31,754
- Course not.
- Come on!

496
00:51:33,590 --> 00:51:35,341
You wanna go up or down?

497
00:51:35,509 --> 00:51:37,593
- Up or down?
- Up.

498
00:52:00,283 --> 00:52:04,286
All has become strange.

499
00:52:05,247 --> 00:52:11,168
A world so unreal and yet,
at once, so frightening.

500
00:52:34,693 --> 00:52:37,653
Open up or I'll blow his head off!

501
00:52:40,824 --> 00:52:43,701
Open! Or he dies in the name of Ch'ing-ti

502
00:52:43,869 --> 00:52:47,705
and your souls speed with his
to the hell of the oily dragon!

503
00:53:14,900 --> 00:53:17,067
- You all right?
- Yeah.

504
00:53:21,781 --> 00:53:23,616
- Margo!
- Jack!

505
00:53:23,783 --> 00:53:27,453
- Where's Gracie?
- On the floor next door. She's a wildcat.

506
00:53:27,621 --> 00:53:31,290
- How are you gonna spring us?
- I have no idea.

507
00:54:08,828 --> 00:54:11,330
That way maybe.

508
00:54:14,918 --> 00:54:17,002
Wang, haul ass!

509
00:54:31,810 --> 00:54:33,727
Come on, keep movin'!

510
00:54:35,355 --> 00:54:36,897
Margo, jump in!

511
00:54:38,566 --> 00:54:40,859
- In there? Are you nuts?
- Go!

512
00:55:12,183 --> 00:55:14,685
- Where's Margo?
- I don't know.

513
00:55:18,064 --> 00:55:19,064
Where are we?

514
00:55:19,232 --> 00:55:21,400
- Where's Eddie?
- Beats me.

515
00:55:24,529 --> 00:55:26,613
Where's Jack?

516
00:55:28,450 --> 00:55:30,534
Jack!

517
00:55:32,495 --> 00:55:34,580
Jack?

518
00:55:36,583 --> 00:55:38,667
Jack!

519
00:55:41,880 --> 00:55:47,259
- Sorry, I'm just thrilled to be alive.
- Yeah, sure. Let's go.

520
00:55:54,100 --> 00:55:57,686
- It's like some giant garbage disposal.
- I think it is, sort of.

521
00:55:57,854 --> 00:56:01,774
Will you just stop rubbing
your body up against mine?

522
00:56:01,941 --> 00:56:03,984
I can't concentrate when you do that.

523
00:56:04,152 --> 00:56:08,113
What a pig you are, Burton! l mean, really!

524
00:56:10,658 --> 00:56:14,620
- Where's Jack?
- It's OK. Everybody relax. I'm here.

525
00:56:14,788 --> 00:56:18,123
Jack, I know where we are.
This is a central... what do you call it?

526
00:56:18,291 --> 00:56:20,959
- Sewer?
- Yeah. Water comes in up there.

527
00:56:21,127 --> 00:56:23,295
Seawater from the bay fills this room.

528
00:56:23,463 --> 00:56:25,798
They divert it
through pipes to different chambers.

529
00:56:25,965 --> 00:56:29,468
I bet up there's where
we first got on that elevator.

530
00:56:57,205 --> 00:57:00,666
All right, we're almost outta here.
From here on, it gets normal.

531
00:57:00,834 --> 00:57:02,960
Offices, storerooms: a nice false front.

532
00:57:03,128 --> 00:57:06,547
I count to three, open the door, and we go.

533
00:57:06,714 --> 00:57:08,590
- Everybody got that?
- Ready?

534
00:57:08,758 --> 00:57:11,218
Follow the leader. One, two, three.

535
00:57:15,223 --> 00:57:16,974
We may be trapped.

536
00:57:20,019 --> 00:57:22,312
Hide!

537
00:57:22,480 --> 00:57:26,191
- Hide?
- Hide! They only saw me!

538
00:57:30,071 --> 00:57:32,614
We fight together, Jack. Do or die.

539
00:58:23,541 --> 00:58:25,083
Time to go.

540
00:58:29,839 --> 00:58:32,966
The bus is right outside in the parking lot.

541
00:58:54,155 --> 00:58:58,951
Here's the deal. l run interference and
you bring up the rear. Can you handle that?

542
00:58:59,118 --> 00:59:00,118
Can you?

543
00:59:00,662 --> 00:59:04,081
Well, what a night's work!
You got a problem like that again,

544
00:59:04,249 --> 00:59:07,042
- you reach for the sky!
- Let's go!

545
00:59:09,295 --> 00:59:11,380
Come on, come on.

546
00:59:12,590 --> 00:59:15,717
- You're doin' real good, guys.
- Come on, Jack!

547
00:59:17,637 --> 00:59:20,347
Let's go! Open the doors!

548
00:59:23,768 --> 00:59:25,894
- Hurry!
- Move it, Egg!

549
00:59:27,522 --> 00:59:29,439
Duck!

550
00:59:45,498 --> 00:59:45,539
We made it. Holy shit, we made it!

551
00:59:45,540 --> 00:59:48,625
We made it. Holy shit, we made it!

552
00:59:49,294 --> 00:59:52,170
- Where's Miao Yin?
- Inside.

553
00:59:52,755 --> 00:59:54,464
Somewhere inside.

554
00:59:57,510 --> 00:59:59,136
Where's Gracie?

555
01:00:15,570 --> 01:00:18,739
Put me down, you overstuffed monster!

556
01:00:22,869 --> 01:00:25,704
Let me go! Let me go!

557
01:01:03,826 --> 01:01:05,911
What does it mean?

558
01:01:06,079 --> 01:01:08,705
Two girls with green eyes?

559
01:01:08,873 --> 01:01:10,916
After all these years.

560
01:01:11,084 --> 01:01:16,588
You bastards! Unchain me! You're not
gonna get away with this. Where's Lo Pan?

561
01:01:18,508 --> 01:01:20,717
This one has fire as well!

562
01:01:20,885 --> 01:01:24,721
Listen,
I've had it up to here with you maniacs.

563
01:01:24,889 --> 01:01:28,934
I wanna see that disgusting
flesh-peddler David Lo Pan in person.

564
01:01:29,102 --> 01:01:34,106
Unless the coward's afraid to see
an unarmed girl one-on-one!

565
01:01:34,649 --> 01:01:36,733
Where is he?

566
01:01:45,993 --> 01:01:50,831
You know what this is? This is like
some radical <i>Alice In Wonderland</i>.

567
01:01:50,998 --> 01:01:52,082
That's what this is.

568
01:01:52,250 --> 01:01:55,085
Then you've got a best seller on your hands.

569
01:01:55,253 --> 01:01:57,963
Call the police. You're not a one-man army.

570
01:01:58,131 --> 01:02:01,174
Cops got better things to do than get killed.

571
01:02:04,595 --> 01:02:06,304
Here he is, Jack.

572
01:02:06,472 --> 01:02:10,058
No, these are our friends.
These are the Chang Sings.

573
01:02:10,226 --> 01:02:13,437
- Any of 'em savvy English?
- Hey, man. Who is this guy?

574
01:02:13,604 --> 01:02:15,355
All right. You got any guns?

575
01:02:15,523 --> 01:02:20,902
Not against Lo Pan, but here's one for you
to make you feel better, like Dirty Harry.

576
01:02:21,070 --> 01:02:24,072
I'll stick with these.
You comin' with us, Egg?

577
01:02:24,240 --> 01:02:29,077
Of course, Jack. It's my destiny. Besides,
if l don't you'll never make it out alive.

578
01:02:29,245 --> 01:02:31,747
- I'm on board too then.
- Yeah, sure, kid.

579
01:02:31,914 --> 01:02:35,584
- You can't keep the press out. It's America.
- You're not going back there.

580
01:02:35,752 --> 01:02:38,253
You're stayin' here
with Eddie and Uncle Chu.

581
01:02:38,421 --> 01:02:41,423
- Eddie? But he's...
- He's got a crush on you.

582
01:02:41,841 --> 01:02:44,301
- You mean like you've got on Gracie?
- Are you kidding?

583
01:02:44,469 --> 01:02:46,094
I just want my truck back.

584
01:02:46,262 --> 01:02:49,514
What do I know?
She's not even your type. All brains.

585
01:02:49,682 --> 01:02:51,725
Come on, let's go!

586
01:03:00,443 --> 01:03:04,196
Play your cards right,
you live to talk about it.

587
01:03:27,136 --> 01:03:29,221
Oh, boy.

588
01:03:30,389 --> 01:03:33,433
Are you OK? Are you Miao Yin?

589
01:03:33,601 --> 01:03:36,853
Yes. Miao Yin.

590
01:03:37,188 --> 01:03:39,898
- Who are you?
- Lo Pan.

591
01:03:40,066 --> 01:03:43,527
You have come to seek me out
with your green eyes.

592
01:03:43,694 --> 01:03:45,654
Yes.

593
01:03:45,822 --> 01:03:47,739
- No, no.
- Yes.

594
01:03:49,617 --> 01:03:55,205
- What's going on here? Some kind of...?
- Magic. The darkest magic.

595
01:03:55,373 --> 01:04:01,628
My soul swims in it, scattered across time,
trapped in the world of formlessness.

596
01:04:02,046 --> 01:04:06,007
Until I find her and marry her.

597
01:04:06,175 --> 01:04:07,467
Marry her?

598
01:04:07,635 --> 01:04:12,806
The girl with green eyes.
The girl who can tame the burning blade.

599
01:04:14,892 --> 01:04:19,312
Miao Yin or Grace Law.

600
01:04:29,740 --> 01:04:33,952
- Great start. It's the other way.
- The front door will get you nowhere.

601
01:04:34,120 --> 01:04:35,203
Here, let me hold that.

602
01:04:35,371 --> 01:04:37,622
A brave man likes to feel nature on his face.

603
01:04:37,790 --> 01:04:41,042
And a wise man has enough sense
to get in out of the rain.

604
01:04:53,139 --> 01:04:55,807
- He lives here?
- He owns the block. He's a rich guy.

605
01:04:55,975 --> 01:04:59,227
- Rich? This place is a dump, Wang.
- To Western eyes.

606
01:04:59,395 --> 01:05:02,272
The stuff in these bottles is priceless.

607
01:05:03,608 --> 01:05:06,610
Well, all set?

608
01:05:07,612 --> 01:05:10,196
Yeah. Ready when you are, Egg.

609
01:05:29,508 --> 01:05:31,343
- Jack next.
- Where does it go?

610
01:05:31,510 --> 01:05:34,346
- Down. Lo Pan is down there.
- Down where?

611
01:05:34,513 --> 01:05:37,432
- Where is the universe?
- Come on, Jack. Don't be afraid.

612
01:05:37,600 --> 01:05:39,643
Afraid? Are you kidding?

613
01:05:53,866 --> 01:05:58,161
- Where in the hell are we?
- Underneath Chinatown.

614
01:06:58,764 --> 01:07:01,057
That is not water.

615
01:07:01,225 --> 01:07:03,601
Black blood of the earth.

616
01:07:03,769 --> 01:07:07,939
- Do you mean oil?
- I mean black blood of the earth.

617
01:07:08,107 --> 01:07:13,319
A thousand years ago, huge earthquakes
turned the world upside down.

618
01:07:15,573 --> 01:07:18,074
Many normal people were killed.

619
01:07:20,327 --> 01:07:24,372
Many unnatural people roam free

620
01:07:24,540 --> 01:07:29,085
to commit great offenses against the gods.

621
01:09:15,442 --> 01:09:20,446
They have survived the burning blade,
tamed the savage heart.

622
01:09:23,284 --> 01:09:25,577
I will marry both women.

623
01:09:27,538 --> 01:09:30,123
Prepare them.

624
01:09:44,722 --> 01:09:46,806
What is that?

625
01:09:48,517 --> 01:09:52,437
- It sounds like...
- Something breathing underwater?

626
01:09:52,605 --> 01:09:54,272
Yeah.

627
01:10:04,074 --> 01:10:06,117
You will come out no more!

628
01:10:06,285 --> 01:10:09,871
What? What'll come out no more?

629
01:10:10,039 --> 01:10:12,207
Come on.

630
01:10:12,374 --> 01:10:14,417
Dammit!

631
01:10:27,223 --> 01:10:29,307
Miao Yin?

632
01:11:07,888 --> 01:11:09,973
Hey, Wang!

633
01:11:10,140 --> 01:11:12,684
- Egg!
- Jack, come on!

634
01:11:27,491 --> 01:11:30,868
It's OK, Jack. Wing Kong storeroom.
Emergency provisions.

635
01:11:31,036 --> 01:11:33,913
We're inside Lo Pan's domain.

636
01:11:34,081 --> 01:11:35,957
Christ!

637
01:11:38,752 --> 01:11:39,836
Later.

638
01:11:40,004 --> 01:11:44,632
We're getting close. Real close.
And now for some more bad news. Ready?

639
01:11:44,800 --> 01:11:49,137
- This gets worse? Come on!
- 2,258 years ago

640
01:11:49,305 --> 01:11:51,764
the First Sovereign Emperor...

641
01:11:53,225 --> 01:11:56,853
He subjugated Lo Pan,
made him of no flesh.

642
01:11:57,896 --> 01:12:01,733
- Only an evil dream.
- Get to the goddamn point, Egg.

643
01:12:01,900 --> 01:12:06,988
In order to be whole again, he had to find
this certain girl of his prophecy,

644
01:12:07,156 --> 01:12:09,741
and marry her to appease
the God of the East.

645
01:12:09,992 --> 01:12:12,952
But to appease the emperor,
he had to kill her.

646
01:12:13,120 --> 01:12:14,871
Kill her? No!

647
01:12:15,039 --> 01:12:19,083
Well, let's go. What are we talkin'
Chinese history for when we gotta get...

648
01:12:19,251 --> 01:12:22,670
We are getting ready
to strike the final blow.

649
01:12:22,838 --> 01:12:26,424
- If we reach Lo Pan...
- When we reach Lo Pan.

650
01:12:26,592 --> 01:12:29,260
..then the power in this flask
will be our only hope

651
01:12:29,428 --> 01:12:34,349
against the Bodhisattva of the underworld,
the ultimate evil spirit.

652
01:12:35,434 --> 01:12:39,437
Yes. Only a dream can kill a dream.

653
01:12:39,813 --> 01:12:42,690
I've waited for this for a long time, Jack.

654
01:12:43,901 --> 01:12:46,527
The evil dream will die.

655
01:12:52,951 --> 01:12:54,118
Wing Kong outside.

656
01:13:20,938 --> 01:13:24,440
- Were they real?
- Yeah. Dressed for Lo Pan's wedding.

657
01:13:24,608 --> 01:13:26,609
What's in the flask? Magic potion?

658
01:13:26,777 --> 01:13:29,153
- Yeah.
- Thought so. Good. Do we drink it?

659
01:13:29,321 --> 01:13:31,030
- Yeah.
- Good. Thought so.

660
01:14:07,443 --> 01:14:11,863
I am the past,
come back to haunt you, Lo Pan!

661
01:14:14,158 --> 01:14:18,536
My God, no! Please!
What is that? Don't tell me.

662
01:14:18,704 --> 01:14:22,999
A guardian. What it sees, Lo Pan knows.

663
01:14:23,167 --> 01:14:25,460
They have returned.

664
01:14:25,627 --> 01:14:29,714
And this time they are not alone.
Egg Shen is with them.

665
01:14:29,882 --> 01:14:35,470
Little bastard sorcerer has brought them
through the Bog of the Dead Trees.

666
01:14:35,637 --> 01:14:37,221
Egg Shen?

667
01:14:37,389 --> 01:14:42,310
Egg Shen! You have come
a long ways to find me, but it is too late.

668
01:14:42,478 --> 01:14:46,731
There are two girls with green eyes,
and l will marry them both.

669
01:14:46,899 --> 01:14:50,151
And then I will sacrifice Gracie Law
to appease my emperor,

670
01:14:50,319 --> 01:14:54,530
and live out my earthly pleasures
with Miao Yin.

671
01:14:57,159 --> 01:15:00,411
That's right, Egg Shen.
The best of two worlds.

672
01:15:07,294 --> 01:15:09,837
You never know till you try.

673
01:15:10,005 --> 01:15:12,048
Let's get outta here.

674
01:15:22,518 --> 01:15:25,353
You know what l don't like?
Where is everybody?

675
01:15:25,521 --> 01:15:27,772
Preparing for Lo Pan's wedding.

676
01:15:38,325 --> 01:15:42,078
We should not be in here, not this easily.
It's a setup, I'm tellin' ya.

677
01:15:42,246 --> 01:15:45,623
Lo Pan is about to take his queen.
He's too busy to care.

678
01:15:45,791 --> 01:15:48,501
So where is he, Egg? Where?

679
01:16:20,075 --> 01:16:22,159
- Jack, here!
- What?

680
01:16:25,747 --> 01:16:27,832
- Hollow.
- Fuck it.

681
01:16:32,462 --> 01:16:36,132
- I know. It's an elevator. lt only goes down.
- Yeah, look.

682
01:16:36,300 --> 01:16:40,177
- Hey, all right!
- Time for the medicine!

683
01:16:47,936 --> 01:16:51,522
- Cheers!
- This does what again, exactly?

684
01:16:51,690 --> 01:16:54,275
Huge buzz.

685
01:16:55,193 --> 01:16:57,028
Good!

686
01:16:57,195 --> 01:17:01,365
You can see things no one else can see,
do things no one else can do.

687
01:17:01,533 --> 01:17:03,784
- Real things?
- As real as Lo Pan.

688
01:17:03,952 --> 01:17:07,955
- What more can a guy ask for?
- The six-demon bag!

689
01:17:08,123 --> 01:17:11,792
Terrific. A six-demon bag.
Sensational. What's in it, Egg?

690
01:17:11,960 --> 01:17:14,670
Wind! Fire! All that kind of thing.

691
01:17:14,838 --> 01:17:17,256
Here's to the army and navy
and the battles they have won.

692
01:17:17,424 --> 01:17:20,051
Here's to America's colors,
the colors that never run.

693
01:17:20,218 --> 01:17:22,887
May the wings of liberty
never lose a feather.

694
01:17:37,944 --> 01:17:41,322
I feel pretty good. You know, I'm not...

695
01:17:41,490 --> 01:17:44,450
I'm not scared at all. l just feel kind of...

696
01:17:45,452 --> 01:17:48,162
- I feel kind of invincible.
- Me too.

697
01:17:48,330 --> 01:17:52,249
- I got a very positive attitude about this.
- Good. Me too.

698
01:17:58,090 --> 01:18:00,633
Is it gettin' hot in here, or is it just me?

699
01:18:00,926 --> 01:18:03,844
Ch'ing-ti! Ch'ing-ti!

700
01:18:04,680 --> 01:18:08,349
Great Ch'ing-ti, equal with heaven,

701
01:18:08,517 --> 01:18:14,438
come into our presence
and witness this holy matrimony.

702
01:18:14,606 --> 01:18:18,234
- Miao Yin.
- And the ultimate evil spirit.

703
01:18:23,532 --> 01:18:26,909
And now, my beloved disciples,

704
01:18:27,077 --> 01:18:29,412
the moment of truth.

705
01:18:29,579 --> 01:18:32,081
The needle of love.

706
01:18:35,585 --> 01:18:38,546
- I'd like to shoot that bastard.
- Not until he's married.

707
01:18:38,714 --> 01:18:41,257
- Then he's flesh.
- Then it's too late.

708
01:18:41,425 --> 01:18:43,592
Ch'ing-ti!

709
01:18:43,760 --> 01:18:48,472
You, who shake the heavens
and descend from the east,

710
01:18:48,640 --> 01:18:52,268
all I ask in order to conquer this universe

711
01:18:52,436 --> 01:18:56,772
is that you grant me flesh and blood.

712
01:18:58,567 --> 01:19:01,694
Yes! Guide my hand

713
01:19:02,487 --> 01:19:06,657
as l insert this needle into Miao Yin.

714
01:19:07,534 --> 01:19:11,328
Let him complete the ceremony.
Then he is ours for certain!

715
01:19:11,496 --> 01:19:14,039
Come, my love. Give it to me.

716
01:19:27,220 --> 01:19:29,138
It's working!

717
01:19:30,766 --> 01:19:32,850
I'm mortal!

718
01:19:41,276 --> 01:19:43,277
Look out, guys!

719
01:19:58,877 --> 01:20:00,544
No way!

720
01:21:04,067 --> 01:21:06,360
Come, Miao Yin, it won't hurt.

721
01:22:07,213 --> 01:22:08,672
Shit!

722
01:22:16,932 --> 01:22:18,223
Take her.

723
01:22:41,247 --> 01:22:43,540
Peasant magic!

724
01:23:18,910 --> 01:23:20,995
You never could beat me, Egg Shen.

725
01:24:27,270 --> 01:24:28,687
- It's me.
- Are you all right?

726
01:24:28,855 --> 01:24:31,940
- Never mind me. We gotta get Lo Pan.
- Where is he?

727
01:24:32,108 --> 01:24:33,400
Wang!

728
01:24:33,568 --> 01:24:35,319
Come on.

729
01:24:37,322 --> 01:24:39,406
Pull it apart. Come on!

730
01:25:06,601 --> 01:25:10,854
- Where does this go?
- Up. To Lo Pan's office. It's cooler up there.

731
01:25:11,022 --> 01:25:14,024
- From there we can...
- Do you have a gun, l hope?

732
01:25:14,192 --> 01:25:17,528
- I have a knife.
- A knife? He's 12 feet tall!

733
01:25:17,695 --> 01:25:20,948
Seven. Don't worry.
I can handle him. l took something.

734
01:25:21,116 --> 01:25:23,742
I can see things no one else can see.

735
01:25:24,994 --> 01:25:28,539
- Why are you dressed like that?
- I was getting married.

736
01:25:28,706 --> 01:25:33,836
He was marrying both of us,
just because my eyes are green too.

737
01:25:43,096 --> 01:25:45,681
Oh, God. ls this really happening?

738
01:25:52,939 --> 01:25:56,191
- Look into my eyes.
- No! Never!

739
01:25:56,359 --> 01:26:00,195
I have suffered so much pain and agony.
Look at me!

740
01:26:00,363 --> 01:26:04,074
No! I don't understand.
I don't belong to you!

741
01:26:04,242 --> 01:26:07,995
No, you don't. You belong to Ch'ing-ti.

742
01:26:08,163 --> 01:26:10,914
I must sacrifice you,
but I love you and l need you.

743
01:26:11,082 --> 01:26:13,208
No!

744
01:26:13,376 --> 01:26:15,502
Here, take her! Take the bitch!

745
01:26:15,670 --> 01:26:18,463
- Master, you are flesh!
- I am?

746
01:26:19,090 --> 01:26:22,050
I am! lt worked!

747
01:26:22,218 --> 01:26:24,970
Ch'ing-ti is appeased.

748
01:26:25,346 --> 01:26:30,601
Now we must satisfy the First
Sovereign Emperor by destroying this!

749
01:26:30,768 --> 01:26:32,936
Not so fast, gentlemen.

750
01:26:33,104 --> 01:26:36,690
Is it too much to ask, Thunder?
Kill him! For me!

751
01:26:36,858 --> 01:26:41,612
It won't solve anything, Dave. Too many
people have been droppin' like flies already

752
01:26:41,779 --> 01:26:45,324
and where's that gettin' us? Nowhere, fast.

753
01:26:45,491 --> 01:26:48,827
Nah, you know what Jack Burton
always says at a time like this?

754
01:26:48,995 --> 01:26:51,955
- Who?
- Jack Burton. Me!

755
01:27:00,298 --> 01:27:02,466
Old Jack always says

756
01:27:02,967 --> 01:27:05,093
"What the hell?"

757
01:27:30,870 --> 01:27:32,329
It's a good knife.

758
01:27:34,749 --> 01:27:36,625
Goodbye, Mr Burton.

759
01:28:00,858 --> 01:28:03,360
It's all in the reflexes.

760
01:28:06,489 --> 01:28:08,198
Wang!

761
01:28:15,873 --> 01:28:18,000
You all right?

762
01:28:18,167 --> 01:28:20,294
- Hey, thanks.
- Wait a minute.

763
01:28:56,039 --> 01:28:58,123
I don't think he's gonna stop!

764
01:29:02,462 --> 01:29:03,962
Come on!

765
01:29:23,816 --> 01:29:26,276
- We got a problem.
- There!

766
01:29:58,017 --> 01:30:00,435
Come on, Jack!

767
01:30:02,355 --> 01:30:04,439
Jump, Jack!

768
01:30:14,575 --> 01:30:17,452
- This whole place is melting!
- Hello! Hello!

769
01:30:18,329 --> 01:30:22,457
- How'd you get up there?
- It wasn't easy! Stand aside!

770
01:30:27,171 --> 01:30:29,381
Take it away!

771
01:30:48,985 --> 01:30:50,902
Hang onto this.

772
01:30:53,114 --> 01:30:55,115
Watch out, Wang Chi!

773
01:31:04,584 --> 01:31:06,668
Go for it, Wang!

774
01:31:27,398 --> 01:31:30,275
- Go!
- Come on, Jack, hurry!

775
01:31:32,278 --> 01:31:34,821
There's my truck... My truck!

776
01:31:34,989 --> 01:31:37,407
Get in.

777
01:31:58,971 --> 01:32:01,056
- They took the key.
- Do you have a spare?

778
01:32:01,224 --> 01:32:04,100
Course l do, but it's underneath the...

779
01:32:06,687 --> 01:32:10,482
- What was that?
- 6.9 on the Richter scale. Hang on!

780
01:32:18,950 --> 01:32:21,451
- Sorry.
- Don't you know how to drive this thing?

781
01:32:21,619 --> 01:32:23,161
Relax.

782
01:32:37,176 --> 01:32:39,469
Stop! Red light!

783
01:32:43,641 --> 01:32:46,101
Take it easy. OK, we made it.

784
01:32:47,645 --> 01:32:48,728
Yeah.

785
01:32:48,896 --> 01:32:52,941
Look at that.
Doesn't that make you feel good?

786
01:32:53,109 --> 01:32:55,151
Terrific.

787
01:32:56,445 --> 01:32:58,738
The light's green. You can go.

788
01:33:17,341 --> 01:33:20,427
- What are you doin', Jack?
- I'll be right back.

789
01:33:20,595 --> 01:33:23,054
Where are you goin', Egg?

790
01:33:23,764 --> 01:33:25,849
My work's done.

791
01:33:26,559 --> 01:33:30,520
Lo Pan is dead
and the evil spell's been lifted.

792
01:33:31,647 --> 01:33:35,025
Years ago l promised myself
a long vacation.

793
01:33:35,192 --> 01:33:37,152
It is time to collect.

794
01:33:37,320 --> 01:33:40,447
Well, why don't you go on over to China?
Visit the motherland?

795
01:33:40,615 --> 01:33:45,285
Well, China's in the heart, Jack.
Wherever l go, she's with me.

796
01:33:47,788 --> 01:33:52,042
- So what are you gonna call it?
- I don't know.

797
01:33:52,209 --> 01:33:57,339
Maybe you can come over to my place later
and help me find a title?

798
01:33:59,425 --> 01:34:02,636
- Here, Jack. Nothin' or triple.
- Nothin' or double.

799
01:34:02,803 --> 01:34:05,513
Triple. You earned it.

800
01:34:05,848 --> 01:34:08,558
You're right, l did. Thanks, Wang.

801
01:34:11,771 --> 01:34:14,314
Well, last chance. I'm a rich man now.

802
01:34:14,482 --> 01:34:18,276
I can give up the open road,
sell my truck, settle down.

803
01:34:18,778 --> 01:34:21,321
Couldn't have that on my conscience.

804
01:34:21,489 --> 01:34:24,240
The only way it might work
is if you buy a bigger truck

805
01:34:24,408 --> 01:34:27,827
with a cozy little apartment
in back, just big enough for two.

806
01:34:27,995 --> 01:34:33,333
That sounds pretty great. But sooner or later
I rub everybody the wrong way.

807
01:34:35,336 --> 01:34:37,629
Well, let me think about it.

808
01:34:41,342 --> 01:34:45,178
God, aren't you even
gonna kiss her goodbye?

809
01:34:48,974 --> 01:34:50,517
No.

810
01:34:52,728 --> 01:34:55,855
- See you around, Burton.
- Never can tell.

811
01:35:00,903 --> 01:35:02,987
Bye, Jack.

812
01:35:06,450 --> 01:35:09,786
We really shook the pillars of heaven,
didn't we, Wang?

813
01:35:09,954 --> 01:35:12,622
- No horseshit, Jack.
- No horseshit.

814
01:35:34,687 --> 01:35:38,273
You just listen to the Pork-Chop Express
and take his advice

815
01:35:38,441 --> 01:35:42,318
on a stormy night, when the lightning's
crashin', the thunder's roarin',

816
01:35:42,486 --> 01:35:46,156
and the rain's comin' down
in sheets thick as lead.

817
01:35:46,323 --> 01:35:49,242
Remember what old Jack Burton does
when the earth quakes

818
01:35:49,410 --> 01:35:54,247
and the poison arrows fall from the sky
and the pillars of heaven shake.

819
01:35:54,415 --> 01:35:59,169
Yeah, Jack Burton just looks that big old
storm right square in the eye and he says

820
01:35:59,336 --> 01:36:03,006
"Gimme your best shot, pal. I can take it."
