"The itsy bitsy spider
"Climbed up the water spout
"Down came the rain
"And washed the spider out
"Up came the sun
"And it dried up all the rain
"And the itsy bitsy spider
"Went up the spout again"
Come on, Laurie Ann. It´s going to storm.
Hi.
Laurie Ann?
Honey? Don´t scare Momma.
Excuse me. Move along.
Chief´s going to have a cow
when he sees you nosing around.
I won´t tell him if you don´t.
What have you got?
There´s not much left.
Just like the last time.
- Did anyone see anything?
- The mother said she saw...
I told you to stay out of this.
l´m just a concerned citizen, Chief.
I call six kids missing or dead
a major cause for alarm.
It may be a rash of runaways.
Kids get itchy feet.
Right. A five-year-old in a toy car
gets itchy feet.
A seven-year-old goes to Acapulco
for a wild weekend?
The boy´s father took him.
The other one...
Chief, there´s something terribly wrong
here in Derry. And you know it.
l´m the cop. You´re the librarian.
Okay?
Georgie.
May 28th.
Another killing today.
But this time there was something more.
Something that makes my skin crawl.
A picture that shouldn´t...
That couldn´t have been there.
It´s time to tell the others
what´s happening.
I can´t put it off any longer.
But I hope l´m wrong.
I hope to God l´m wrong.
Taggert steps onto the moors as the
fog curls around his ankles.
He shivers, buttons his coat,
and walks on into the mist.
A shadowy figure lurches into frame,
dripping with foul water and dark mud.
Yeah.
Bill, for the last time...
In a minute!
You said that half an hour ago.
- And a half an hour before that.
- Okay!
- It´s cold.
- Sorry.
I like the changes. They´re wonderful.
- I wish you´d tell that idiot, Greco.
- I do. Every day.
You didn´t have to take this job.
We don´t need the money.
In case you´ve forgotten,
I took the job to be with you.
If someone
is going to mangle my books...
...it may as well be me.
The idea of taking a vacation
didn´t even occur...
So I could hang around the set?
That´s not what I do. Writing is what I do.
At least when you´re doing a novel,
you´re in a good mood.
Audra, could we...
l´m asleep unless it´s Greco.
Greco.
Yeah?
- Bill, is that you?
- Do I know you?
This is Mike Hanlon, from Derry.
Swear to me.
Swear to me that if it isn´t dead...
...we´ll all come back.
- Sorry, Mike, for a minute there...
- You didn´t know who I was.
For a minute, I didn´t.
Bill...
...it´s back.
You sure?
Yeah. I found a photograph of George.
George?
What is it?
Who was on the phone?
Nobody. Wrong number.
Bill?
I have to go back to work.
Georgie.
Please, Bill. Tell me a story.
Maybe later.
The magic stone story.
Please, Bill. Please.
Go bug somebody else, you little cootie.
I don´t feel so hot.
Georgie?
For me? You made it for me?
Can I go sail it?
You have to seal it first with paraffin.
- What´s that? Where is it?
- In the cellar.
I wish you could come, too.
She´s your boat, really.
Thanks, Bill.
You got cooties all over me.
Georgie.
Don´t stay out too long
or Mom will have a bird.
- I won´t.
- Georgie!
Be careful.
Sure. I will.
S. S. Georgie!
Come on!
S. S. Georgie, out of the way!
No, please, no!
Hi, Georgie.
Aren´t you going to say hello?
Come on, bucko.
Don´t you want a balloon?
l´m not supposed to take stuff
from strangers.
My dad said so.
Very wise of your dad. Very wise indeed.
I am Pennywise, the Dancing Clown.
You are Georgie.
Now we know each other.
Correct?
I guess so.
- l´ve got to go.
- Go?
Without this?
- My boat!
- Exactly.
Go on, kiddo. Take it.
You want it, don´t you, Georgie?
Of course you do.
There´s cotton candy and rides
and all sorts of surprises down here.
And balloons, too. In all colors.
- Do they float?
- Yes.
They float, Georgie.
They float.
And when you´re here with me...
...you float, too.
"Fear no evil for thou art with me,
thy rod and thy staff, they comfort me.
"Thou preparest a table before me in
the presence of mine enemies.
"Thou annointest my head with oil,
my cup runneth over.
"Goodness and mercy shall follow me
all the days of my life.
"I will dwell
in the house of the Lord forever."
Georgie.
Billy?
- Are you all right?
- What is it?
The picture. Georgie´s picture.
Mom, don´t you see?
- What were you doing in Georgie´s room?
- Nothing.
- Dad, listen!
- Never come in here again. Understand?
I mean it, Bill.
I forgot.
How could I forget?
Leave? Have you lost your mind?
We´re in the middle of making a movie.
They can replace me.
This is something I have to do.
Who was on the phone?
The call was from a guy
named Mike Hanlon.
I haven´t heard from him in 30 years.
Not since we were kids.
- Audra. My brother, who died...
- Yes, George.
He didn´t just die.
He was murdered.
- Why didn´t you ever...
- Tell you?
Because I forgot. As if it never happened.
I know it doesn´t make sense,
but I have to go.
For God´s sake, why?
Because we made a promise.
- Why are you stuttering?
- I used to stutter when I was a kid.
What happened? Tell me.
Damn it, Bill, talk to me! Let me help.
- lf you´re going back, l´m going too.
- Don´t even think that!
- Why not? You´re scaring me.
- Promise me you´ll stay here.
- Promise me!
- You´re crazy.
This is crazy.
I love you.
Oh no, Ben.
Your architect award.
And you just received it. It´s a tragedy.
Yeah, honey.
We´ve got ourselves a real tragedy here.
This is an American tragedy.
Look at this. Would you hang on to this?
I got this and this.
Here you are, my good man. Recycle.
Come on.
Go on, honey.
Limbo! How low can you go?
You don´t have to be quiet.
- Is all this yours?
- Yes. Come on in.
Let me see what I can do with this.
Come here, beautiful. Come on.
- I love your body.
- I like yours, too.
- Would you believe I used to be fat?
- I bet you were real cute.
Not just fat, a regular butterball.
You bet your fern I was.
We used to say that as kids.
You bet your fern, but I was F-A-T.
- No.
- Yeah.
I hear bells. l´ll be right back.
Hello?
Haystack, it´s me, Mike.
It´s payback time, piggy.
Hey, fat boy!
Ben?
Are you there?
- Mike?
- Yeah, buddy. Listen:
It´s come back.
How much do you remember?
Very little. Almost nothing.
Will you come?
l´ll come.
Are you okay?
I don´t think I am, sweetheart.
Not tonight. Not at all.
Are you going to kill yourself?
I don´t think so.
But it might be better if I did.
My name is Ben Hanscom.
Until last week,
I lived with my mom in Houston, Texas.
We moved here to live with my cousins.
Look at that gut.
Go on, Ben.
Do you have any hobbies?
I read a lot.
Especially about old civilizations,
like the Egyptians and Indians.
We have a wonderful library here.
Welcome to Derry.
Thank you, Miss Douglas.
What a porker.
Henry Bowers...
...you will stay for one hour after school
every day this week.
My father will tan my hide.
You should´ve thought of that
before you picked on Ben.
Report to the principal´s office.
You´re dead, fat boy.
It´s going to be some funeral, friend.
Now, class...
...as you know, the Sheriff has instituted
a 7:00 pm curfew.
We live in dangerous times, boys and girls.
I want you to be careful.
Do you like the school so well
that you´re going to stand there all day?
School´s over, you know.
- Excuse us, please.
- Can we get through?
- Some people have no class.
- Some people have janitors for parents.
So long, Ben Hanscom.
l´m Beverly Marsh.
See you tomorrow, Beverly Marsh.
- Look, it´s the fat boy.
- Top of the day, fat boy.
- What do you want?
- I want to teach you something, porky.
You like to learn new things, don´t you?
I want to make sure
you remember my name.
l´ll remember. Henry.
How can I be sure?
Don´t really cut him.
Cut him?
Let´s see, first comes...
Oh, God!
You´re going to die! l´ll bury you!
You´re going to die!
- Nobody kicks me! Nobody!
- You better run, boy.
You´re going to die, man!
Get him! You´re dead, you fat pig!
- What´s this?
- Looks like a geek wading pool to me.
What are you two girls doing here?
Look at the stupid little baby dam.
You don´t have to do that.
Why did you do that?
I felt like it. Give me that.
- That´s for my asthma.
- Is that a fact? Sissy.
- Leave him alone.
- Shut up, creep.
Stop that or l´ll pull your ears down
and tie them underneath your chin.
Did you see a fat kid run by here?
- Big, fat kid, all messed up.
- No.
You sure, mush-mouth?
You better be sure.
l´m sure.
Let´s go.
Ta-ta, girls.
It´s empty.
I can´t breathe.
Are they gone?
Yes. Can you stay here with my friend
while I get his medicine?
Yeah.
Let me take this.
Take it easy, kid. You´ll be okay.
- You´ll be okay.
- Yeah?
What will we do if they come back?
Want some?
- My dad died of the big "C".
- Big "C"?
Cancer. I was just a little kid.
My dad died, too.
He was shot down in Korea.
- Do you remember him much?
- Sort of, I think.
- Who´s the other guy?
- Bill?
Bill´s my best friend. He´s a great guy.
Hey!
l´m...
...back.
- Does he always stutter so much?
- It´s worse since his brother died.
Some guy killed George.
His arm was pulled off like a wing off a fly.
- That´s awful.
- I told you because...
...lf you want Bill to be your friend,
don´t talk to him about George.
- He´s all messed up about it.
- I would be, too.
- Would be too, what?
- Nothing. Thanks.
Thanks for staying.
He´s really got it bad. l´m scared he´s
going into a coma like on Dr. Kildare.
- Me, too. You´re Ben.
- And you´re Bill.
- This is...
- Eddie. He knows.
I hate it when you stutter my name.
You sound like Elmer Fudd.
No, Elmer Fudd has a lisp.
Porky Pig stutters.
Okay.
Why don´t you come back tomorrow?
Me and Eddie, we´re trying to make a dam.
You´ve got to have some boards,
and put them in a row, facing each other.
Like the bread of a sandwich...
- But we do it.
- Yeah, we.
- What are you doing?
- Something for school.
- A poem.
- That´s private.
"Your hair is winter fire.
"January embers."
Hey, Mom, Benny´s in love!
Give this back.
- Mom! Mom!
- Stop that! Benjamin!
Stop that immediately, you ruffian.
I hate you!
You´re only here because
Mom says it´s our Christian duty.
Nobody´s ever going to say
a sister of mine is on welfare.
So you´re welcome
as long as you need to stay.
But you´re spoiling the boy, Arlene.
He needs a firm hand, discipline.
We´ll have our own home one day.
I promise.
I know, Mama.
As long as we´re guests,
I need you to help me.
They wouldn´t treat us like this
if Daddy were still alive.
Come on inside and apologize.
But he was...
- You must!
- No! I hate it here.
Come on, Benny.
Benny!
Ben! Benny! Up here, Ben.
Daddy?
Ben!
Hi, Ben.
Daddy?
That´s my home now, son.
Do you want a balloon?
They float.
They all float.
Come here, son. You´ll like it down there.
You never have to grow up.
They float.
They all float.
When you´re down here with me...
...fat boy, you´ll float, too.
Please, stop.
Beverly By Hand. One moment please.
Miss Marsh´s office.
Hold a moment, please.
Someone calling from Maine,
says it´s important.
Maine?
- Pam, I said no calls until...
- We´ve got a minute. l´ll take it.
No. Get their number and close the door.
Your hands are shaking.
l´m scared to death.
That stuff spreads like cancer.
I won´t have it around.
There. That´s perfect. Don´t touch it.
Listen to me, Bevy.
We have some well-heeled
Japanese gentlemen waiting downstairs.
We´ll show them around. You´ll play
the charming flamboyant designer.
We´ll make a deal, l´ll play hardball,
and when it´s over, we´ll be rich.
If you get a hold of yourself right now.
Do you understand?
A kiss for good luck?
Okay, let´s go.
And don´t ever contradict me
in front of Pam again.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
l´m Beverly Marsh.
This is my partner, Tom Grogan.
- Hello?
- Beverly, it´s Mike Hanlon.
- Who?
- Mike Hanlon. Remember me?
Mike Hanlon. Of course. How are you?
Fine. Are you sitting down?
There you are.
Who was on the phone?
You may think this is crazy,
I certainly think it´s crazy...
...but I have to go to Maine.
It´s hard to explain.
That was Mike Hanlon on the phone.
Remember he called at work today?
He´s an old, dear friend. I have to...
Shut up! You have to shut up!
I make the deal of a lifetime and
you run off to an old boyfriend in Maine?
What do you take me for?
l´ve seen this coming.
You´ve forgotten your manners, little girl.
Contradicting me,
smarting off, and now this.
You´ve forgotten your lessons.
It´s been too long since last time.
Put that thing down.
I have to get to O´Hare as fast as I can.
There´s some very bad trouble.
It´s come back, Beverly.
Remember your promise.
Put these clothes back.
- Get into bed!
- No!
Then maybe you can leave this house
in two days, instead of two weeks.
Not ever again!
If you ever come near me again,
l´ll kill you.
Do you understand? I will kill you.
Bev, you need me!
Bev!
O´Hare, please.
What airline, miss?
I need to go to Maine.
We´ll find one that goes to Maine.
What´s in Maine, your family?
Friends.
The best l´ve ever had.
Daddy, breakfast is ready.
l´ll get it.
"Your hair is winter fire.
"January embers.
"My heart burns there, too."
Who was at the door?
- What do you got there?
- Nothing.
Let me see that.
You been doing something you shouldn´t?
Are you fooling around with some boy?
Poetry from some boy?
I worry a lot about you.
- Sometimes, I worry a lot.
- Daddy, please.
Not even 12 years old
and already seeing some boy.
Let me alone!
Come here!
Don´t make me come and collect you.
Come to me.
No.
- What did you say?
- I said, "No! "
You get the hell back in here!
l´ll whip the skin off of you!
Sorry if I scared you. Are you okay?
Yeah.
Don´t you have anything better to do
than sneak up on people?
- Sorry.
- You should be.
I was thinking, it being Saturday and all...
...if you didn´t have anything to do,
you could come with me to the barrens.
The barrens?
This is Eddie...
...and this is Bill.
Hi.
Do you guys know each other already?
Bev wants to help.
I hope that´s okay. She´s a girl.
Sure.
What´s this? By George, Martha...
...it´s the river Nile.
And four, count them, four sphinxes.
Richie.
You were expecting Gunga Din?
Richie´s okay,
but he can drive you to the bughouse.
- I heard that, you skirt.
- Hi, Eddie Spaghetti.
I hate it when you do that.
Don´t call me "Eddie Spaghetti."
You love it.
It makes you so chuck-a-licious.
Richie Tozier´s my name.
And doing voices is my game.
This is Stan the Man Uris.
Stanley´s a Jew, which means
he´s really smart and says oy a lot.
Richie has a high metabolism,
which tends to make him hyperactive.
So you, Haystack,
are you building a dam or something?
- Ever built one before?
- No.
How do you know it´ll work?
- Why wouldn´t it?
- How do you know?
I just know.
Yeah, he just knows.
Well, okay.
- You´re a genius, Haystack.
- It´s nothing.
It´s great. We stopped it. That´s so cool.
We could flood out
the whole barrens if we wanted to.
We did it! We!
Yeah!
l´ll go this way.
- See you later, alligator.
- After a while, crocodile.
- See you, Ben.
- Yeah, see you, Bill.
Hi yo, Silver. Away!
See you, Beverly.
See you.
"My heart burns there, too."
77 Sunset Strip will continue
following station identification.
Help me.
Help me, please.
- Help me, Beverly.
- Hello?
Is someone there?
The clown brought us down here.
We all float.
Who are you?
- l´m Vickie Burrows.
- l´m Matthew O´Connor.
We´re all the dead kids.
Come closer, Beverly.
We all want to meet you. We float.
Daddy!
- What in the name of heaven?
- The bathroom!
- Was someone peeping in at you, girl?
- In the sink!
What do you think you saw?
Speak up, girl.
I worry about you, Bevy.
I worry a lot.
Explain yourself.
There was this spider. A big, fat spider.
He crawled out of the drain,
and I guess, it crawled back down.
These buildings are old,
with drains the size of the Holland tunnel.
There´s nothing there now.
Get to bed.
Say hello to your friends, Beverly.
You´ll die if you try to fight us.
You´ll die, if you try.
You´ll die if you try to fight us, Beverly.
Eddie, where are you?
Eddie?
- Eddie, where are you?
- l´m in here, Ma.
Where are you going?
I have to go away for awhile.
Away? Where?
This isn´t like you.
Tell me where you´re going.
Eddie, stop!
You´re in trouble, aren´t you?
Eddie?
Tell me who was on the phone.
Answer me.
Mom, please don´t cry.
You´re scaring me so bad,
you´ve got to tell me.
- Where are you going?
- I have to go back to Derry.
Why would you want to go back
to that dirty little town?
There´s nothing for you there.
There never was, Eddie.
Please, Ma. Please.
Eddie!
Let´s get out of here.
- What´s going on?
- Nothing.
- You look like you saw a ghost.
- Move it!
Eddie!
l´m sorry to leave you holding the bag.
- Do we have enough drivers for next week?
- It´s covered.
I want you to do the Pacino job.
He likes the Lincoln stretch.
I know, Eddie.
The business is under control.
- It´s you l´m worried about.
- l´m fine.
Where are we going?
Penn Station. The 1 1:30 pm to Boston.
They saw me.
- We better go.
- l´m a dead man.
If I were you,
I wouldn´t pay to see a monster movie...
...l´d just look in a mirror.
Let´s get out of here!
Yeah, let´s go!
- Did you see those guys?
- I saw you make it worse.
Come on, Eddie Spaghetti.
- It was just a joke.
- Sometimes you joke too much.
You have to or you´ll die of boredom.
- Are we men or are we mice?
- We´re mice!
Then let´s act like mice.
Look.
That place scares me green.
I think it´s haunted.
Honestly, Eddie,
such things aren´t empirically possible.
In English, it ain´t no such thing.
You´re a pretty swift guy for a girl,
my little chickadee.
Was that a compliment?
On our very first date?
Why is Richie so special?
The date wasn´t just with him, Eddie.
I love you, too.
Hey, don´t trip!
- Eddie, it´s been great.
- See you later.
- ´Bye, Eddie.
I wish this summer would never end.
It´s the best summer of my whole life.
Eddie Kaspbrak...
...I was worried sick.
I almost called the police.
- Eddie was with us.
- Go away.
Go home.
Ma, these are my friends.
- See you tomorrow.
- Eddie has to rest tomorrow.
I don´t want you to play with them again.
No good will come of it.
- But they´re my friends.
- You don´t need any, except for your ma.
- You feel warm.
- l´m fine.
No showers with the other boys.
I don´t want you catching their germs.
Guys, quit that running,
this is a hallway not a track! Come on!
- Did you take a shower?
- No, sir.
l´ll explain this only one more time:
You take phys ed, you sweat,
you take a shower. Got it?
It´s okay, Eddie.
Hi. I just wanted to say hello.
Hot enough for you up there, is it?
This is a little inconvenient.
l´ll have to make a few adjustments.
Here I am, wheezy.
You´ll like it down here.
Won´t do any good to run, girly boy.
See you in your dreams.
Oh, come back anytime.
Bring your friends.
So I say, ´´Go ahead, make my day. ´´
The next thing you know
l´m feeling my way to the toilet.
How much power
does the electric company have?
Remember Godzilla?
A plane couldn´t stop him,
the atom bomb couldn´t...
...even Nancy Reagan couldn´t stop him.
But you get him in front of
one high power line...
Look! The creature is attacking the city.
You guys are great. Good night.
Hey, guys!
- You´re beautiful!
- That political material is getting old.
Who knows Betty Ford?
We´ve got to work on this.
Hold on, hold on!
There she is. How´s my favorite niece?
l´m so glad you made it. I want to see
Miller first thing Monday.
l´ve got it arranged.
If l´m hosting next week. I have to have
that new material. l´ve got...
l´ve got somebody you should meet.
- I can´t tell you...
- Hold on!
Buona sera. This is Richie Tozier.
Who´s this, Elvis?
Who?
Mike Hanlon, from Derry.
Do you remember?
Yeah. Sure I remember you, pal.
What about subbing for Carson
on Monday night?
Who´s going to sit behind the desk
and be funny?
- Let Leno do it, I don´t care.
- Richie!
- What am I going to tell them?
- Whatever you have to!
I need a couple of days.
For what?
The reunion of your Cub Scout pack
at Grover´s Corners?
Come on, what is it?
A broad? The mob?
I don´t know what it is.
Don´t insult my intelligence.
I made a promise.
We´ve been through a lot together.
You´re fine. You can handle this.
No. This can´t be happening.
Help!
Help! Help!
They felt its hot and horrible breath
against their faces.
But at that moment, they released
the stones and ran out of the cave.
Now they were home,
but nothing could change the way they felt.
They learned to be strong together.
They beat the dragon with the magic
stones, and nothing would be the same.
Write that one down, Bill.
That´s my favorite.
- Really excellent.
- Beautiful.
Yeah, Bill´s going to leave
this one horse town, meet Sandra Dee...
...and the other babes in Hollywood.
Dream on, Richie.
I don´t want to grow up at all.
I do. I want to be a train conductor
and see the world.
If your mom will let you cross the street.
I want to be the first rock ´n´ roll singer
from Derry.
Or an impressionist.
- Your voices all sound the same.
- Thanks a bunch, professor.
- How about you, Bev?
- A painter, maybe.
My dad´s teaching me to draw.
Fighter pilot. When l´m old enough,
l´ll join the Air Force.
An ornithologist. I like cataloguing things,
and finding their logical order.
Can I tell you guys something?
- lf you laugh, l´ll never...
- We won´t, will we?
The other night, in Georgie´s room...
What on earth? For the love of Mike!
Look at this mess. The saints preserve us.
Officer Nell.
You´re fixing to back flood
all the drains in town.
- Whose brainstorm was this?
- I showed them how, it´s my fault.
It was my idea.
- Me, too.
- I was in on it, too.
- I suppose it was your idea too, lass?
- Yes.
Listen to me, all of you.
There´s been another murder.
- Little Velma Daniels.
- Velma Daniels?
Her body was found down by the canal.
If you come down here to play,
come together. Understand?
That means together, all the time.
Your hands on it?
So what did you think
Bill was going to tell us?
I don´t know. He´s been moody lately.
They all have.
With this food, who could blame them?
Well, hey.
- Larry, Curly and Moe.
- Richie!
All right, twerp. Who threw it?
You? It was you, wasn´t it?
Tell me. And you might live
through this, four-eyes.
In the Paramount theater, who did it?
Way to go, banana-heels.
Tozier!
Bowers!
Go downstairs and get a mop
from Mr. Marsh and clean this up!
Go on!
Mr. Marsh?
Just great.
Mr. Marsh, you down here?
Probably drunk as a skunk.
Mr. Marsh?
Mr. Marsh...
...I had a little accident in the cafeteria.
No, this isn´t happening.
No!
Help!
Beep, beep, Richie!
Come back, anytime!
l´ll show you how to float down here.
They all float down here.
You´ve got to help me. Somebody, please.
In the basement, there´s a werewolf.
Stop him.
The day I took that photo
was one of the best days of my life.
We were lucky that summer
that we didn´t get ourselves killed.
Maybe it was something more than luck.
If so, I hope it returns when they do.
Lucky seven.
I brought this old photo album from home.
My dad was stationed in Derry
during World War II.
He collected these old photos
from the olden days.
Who´d want a history of this toilet?
How many years
will you be in here with me?
Continue, Michael.
This is the old ironworks.
One Sunday, back in 1930,
there was an Easter egg hunt here.
The ironworks exploded,
and all these people got killed.
This is the Derry Standpipe.
It supplied all the water to the town...
...until a big disaster in 1900.
The biggest mystery is how 253 settlers
disappeared without a trace.
Thank you for that illuminating,
if somewhat morbid, history.
Who´s next?
Howdy, partner.
Give it here!
Or what, boy? Or what?
This nigger lives down the street
from me and my dad.
Give it here.
You´ve been giving me
and my daddy grief for a long time.
You like fireworks?
What do you say
to a rocket in your pocket?
Hey, you!
Stop that right now.
Get him!
l´m glad l´m not the only one
who saw something.
It wasn´t a clown at first.
It was a werewolf.
I didn´t see a werewolf. Just a clown.
Don´t you see...
...it was a werewolf for Richie
because he saw that dumb movie.
But it was a clown underneath.
Maybe it´s an evil being
that can read our minds...
...and take the shape
of stuff we´re afraid of.
- That´s what happened to the kids here?
- Get serious.
Why didn´t any of us say anything?
Personally, I thought
you guys would think I was nuts.
Me, too. I thought it was just me.
- You´re not alone.
- Such a thing isn´t empirically possible.
It was so real.
- It almost had my guts for garters.
- It´s just the influence of the movie.
Could it be a crazy guy
dressed up in a clown suit?
No.
It´s some kind of monster,
right here in Derry.
l´m going to bury you.
God, Henry Bowers.
We better get out of here.
- Dummy up. All of you. Rocks.
- Rocks?
Rocks. Ammo.
Please, help me.
You´re dead!
What do you know?
It´s the fat boy, the Jew and the sissy.
Four-eyes and the patch girl, too.
Nigger, you know how to pick them.
The loser´s club.
Yeah, the loser´s club.
I got bones to pick with you.
l´m willing to let that go for today.
Today, I want him. So buzz off.
Get out of here.
- Who´s going to make me?
- We are.
- What did you say, chubs?
- Dig the wax out of your ears.
You´re through, Bowers. Get out!
You stuttering freak.
You´re going to get a surprise.
You´ll get such a surprise!
Run, Henry!
Come on!
Get out.
What if I won´t?
The six of us could put you in the hospital.
Seven.
l´ll kill you all.
Get some new material, champ.
Thanks.
Anytime.
Who are you guys anyway?
We´re sort of a club.
Yeah, the loser´s club.
Yeah.
You want in?
Yes, I do.
We´re seven now.
Lucky seven.
Wait a second.
There´s no way to date this one.
He says it´s probably from the early 1 700s,
when Derry was a logging town.
Hold it.
- Pennywise the Clown?
- That´s him.
That´s him!
Two hundred years ago?
He was here then?
Come on! lt´s just a drawing.
Look.
Here he is again.
The same man.
It´s not a man.
It.
It!
That´s what happened
back in Georgie´s room.
Look!
l´ll kill you all!
l´ll drive you crazy, and l´ll kill you all.
l´m every nightmare you´ve ever had,
your worst dream come true.
l´m everything you ever were afraid of.
- No!
- Yes! Yes!
- Yes.
- No!
Yes. Yes.
- You saw it, too.
- I didn´t want to.
But you did.
Yes. If that´s what you want.
Yes.
That´s what I wanted, you turkey.
- What are we going to do?
- What do you mean "do"?
I just want to forget about it.
It´s not just us.
It´s all the other kids, too.
Like Velma Daniels from my class.
Who´s going to be next?
Bev´s right. We have to do something.
- We should tell somebody.
- They don´t see what we see.
When you grow up, you stop believing.
They´ll laugh and put us in a nuthouse.
- It kills kids, damn it.
- We have to do something.
Help me.
You killed my brother, you bastard.
Let´s see you now.
It´s scared of us, you know?
I can feel that. I swear to God I can.
I want to kill lt.
Help me.
We got a letter from Mom today.
She asked when
we´re going to make her a grandma.
She´s uncanny.
I was just thinking the same thing.
I was, really.
Does she know l´m a sex maniac
and that you prefer Perfect Strangers?
You want to pay attention to me.
Don´t move.
Uris residence. Stan speaking.
This better be good.
Hello, Stan. It´s Mike Hanlon.
- Who did you say?
- Mike Hanlon.
- Mike Hanlon?
- Yeah.
l´ll be damned.
Stan, it´s come back.
- Are you sure?
- l´m sure.
- Do you understand? l´m sure.
- I understand.
- You know how hard it is to call...
- I get the picture.
Can you make it, Stan? Please.
- I can´t promise that, but l´ll consider it.
- Don´t you remember, Stan?
- Don´t you remember your promise?
- Yes, Mike.
- You promised.
- Yes, I remember.
I hope you come.
- Goodbye.
- ´Bye, Stan.
Who was it, honey?
Stan?
No one.
No one, really.
I think l´ll take a bath.
Now?
A scout is trustworthy, loyal, helpful,
friendly, courteous, kind...
...obedient, cheerful, thrifty...
...brave, clean and reverent.
- Are you okay?
- I think this is crazy.
One out of 10. You´re worse than I am.
We might as well let that damn clown
take us one by one.
Beep, beep, Richie.
Who´s left? Ben? Bev?
One of them better be good.
You´re in the lead
with a pathetic three out of 10.
Will you please shut up?
- You don´t stutter all the time.
- Ladies first.
Ten out of 10. I don´t think I need to shoot.
It´s like it´s supposed to be Bev.
Yeah.
This is still crazy.
- No, it´s not.
- l´m with Stan.
So what if I can shoot good?
- You think a handful of stones are going...
- Show them, Richie.
My mother´s earrings. Solid silver.
That´s just stuff in movies.
What good is it going to do...
They´re silver. They can kill it.
We have to believe that.
On my honor, I will do my best
to do my duty to God and my country...
...to help other people at all times,
keep myself physically strong...
...mentally awake and morally...
- Maybe this isn´t such a good idea.
- What are you mumbling about?
Now, listen up.
You guys don´t have to do this.
My dad says you have to know
when to take a stand.
Lucky seven, Stan.
I said I was in.
You think we´re going
to let you have all the fun, Billy-boy?
Eddie?
l´m with my friends. Right?
Give me that.
It tastes like battery acid.
- Where are they going?
- Down in the sewer, stupid.
Guess what?
They´re not coming back out.
You mean we have to go down there?
Stan, if you don´t want to go,
now´s the time to turn back.
Great choice. Let´s go.
They´re going down into the pipes
where we chased that dog.
You go how we went. Go ahead of them
and chase them back towards us.
Me and Belch will catch them.
Hurry or there will be nothing left for you.
- Go by myself?
- Yeah, go by yourself.
What are you afraid of? The boogeyman?
Hardy, har-har.
At least we know we´re on its trail.
Maybe this is where it wants us to be.
Eddie, which way is Derry?
Bev, get up front
where you can get a clear shot.
Stay together. No stragglers.
Hi, kid.
I guess you´re the first.
- Who´s missing?
- Stan.
Oh, no!
Now, before you die, I want you
to think of every rock you threw...
...and everything you said.
Think about that before you die.
What was that?
God, he´s not in there anymore.
Belch!
Help!
Stan!
It´s coming!
Hands, quick!
Is that it? Did we do it?
Look!
Quick! Take hands
before we get lost in this stuff.
Grab hold.
Is everybody here?
- l´m here. Stannie?
- Yeah.
Richie?
Yeah. Mike?
Here.
- Whose hand is this?
- Mine.
That you, Ben?
Yeah.
Whatever happens, hang on.
It´s not as strong as it thought it was,
or it would´ve killed us then.
We have to resist.
Bill! Bill!
Georgie?
No, Bill.
That´s not George. Don´t break the circle.
Bevy!
What are you doing down here
with these boys. Now, get home.
Daddy? Daddy, l´m...
Wake up, hot stuff. That ain´t Daddy.
There ain´t nothing there.
I said, "There ain´t nothing there."
On my honor, I will do my best
to do my duty to God and my country.
Stan.
Stanley, boy.
Stanley, resist!
Let go! Be afraid!
Bev, the stones!
You all taste so much better
when you´re afraid.
Hurry, Bev, kill it!
Kill!
Me!
You are priceless, brat.
I am eternal, child.
I am the eater of worlds...
...and of children.
And you are next.
This is battery acid, you slime!
Kill it! Kill it, Bev!
Kill it!
Die!
Help me! Help me!
- Is it dead?
- I don´t think so.
- We have to get out.
- We have to go after it.
- No, it´s dead.
- We have to make sure.
- It sounded like it was dying.
- What if it didn´t?
Swear to me...
...that if it isn´t dead...
...you´ll all come back.
I swear.
I swear it.
Yeah, I swear.
I swear, too.
I swear.
Stannie?
l´m coming upstairs to scrub your back...
...and your chest.
And...
Stanley?
Stan?