He wants to go to college.
Really?
He's really something.
Son!
If you get into college,
the tuition is on me.
Go, Taesik!
Come eat some melon.
Give me a minute.
Come on now. Eat some.
Pretty good.
Wait for your brother!
Put it down.
What?
Hold still.
Come on, it's my favorite.
'Princess can't sleep.‘
- Princess what?
- Listen to it.
She's officially crazy.
Look into the camera.
Here we go.
- I'm going home.
- Okay, good job today.
- See you tomorrow.
- Good night.
Yes.
You live with Sunflower Lady?
I'm sorry about your leg.
No point talking about the past.
Forget about it.
Mr. Cho Pansu...
He wants to build a big mall.
He's bought the field of sunflowers...
...except that restaurant
standing in the middle of it.
That made him very upset.
You know what?
I hope you leave town with her.
Otherwise,
your family will be in trouble.
Cho is a ruthless bastard.
I hope to not see you again
around here.
Tocopherol,
unsaturated fatty acid...
It's good for the system.
Drink it.
Drink it now!
Gulp it down.
Changmu!
I never thought the day would come
for you to visit me here.
We got ourselves a problem.
'We'?
Since when?
But it wasn't Cho who met him.
Who's Byungjin?
Use your head.
That's for thinking.
I do a lot of thinking, too.
Forget it.
I think Cho made him an offer.
What would that be?
It can't be anything small.
- Oracle?
- You got it.
What about us?
Changmu.
Stop calling me like that.
Take care of the restaurant.
I'll deal with Taesik.
I'll kill you
if you ever come back.
Okay.
You look so unique.
Sure.
Doesn't it hurt?
I bet it does.
I don't understand
why you want it erased.
It's cool, isn't it?
Like an iguana with skin trouble.
Come on.
Send her out.
She's too noisy for me.
Don't you smell meat burning?
What's wrong with you?
Be quiet!
I'm sorry.
Study hard, okay?
What?
Study hard.
I hate repeating myself.
Why?
You don't know?
I'm going to a good college.
It'd be good
if we went to school together.
You can be my bodyguard.
It's a dangerous world
for pretty girls.
You know I'm pretty.
What, you don't think so?
How much is it?
Going to the same college
with Huiju
Why don't you leave?
We're not thugs.
We don't want any trouble.
Cooperate with us.
To my eyes,
you're nothing but thugs.
So save it and get out.
- God damn it!
- What?
I'm Lee Changmu.
And I'm about to lose it.
Don't you get it?
Get out, asshole.
- Get out of here.
- Fuck it.
Okay, boys.
We'll do it my way.
Get out!
- Trash it.
- Okay.
Let go, asshole!
What are you doing?
You crazy bitch!
Call the cops, please!
Call the cops!
Bitch!
Changmu, are you okay?
What are you doing?
It's our restaurant!
- Leave us alone!
- What?
What should we do?
I saw it coming.
Let's go.
We have to stop them.
God, I hate this situation!
Wait a little longer.
Hold your horses!
I said wait, didn't I?
Damn, it hurts.
That was your daughter, right?
She hit me with a weapon.
A weapon?
What was it then?
She almost killed me with it.
Stop staring at me.
Look, we'll call it even today.
Or I'll have her arrested.
I'm very well aware of that area.
A lot of witnesses.
I'm not bluffing.
You're nothing but trash!
Look here.
This car is 14 years old.
It's been quite well maintained.
Look, it's in good shape.
Come on, let's go!
HuUu?
Mom... Mom...
I gotta go.
What'd you bring him for?
It's nothing.
This is nothing?
I'm sorry.
It's totally broken.
I'll buy you another one.
No, I don't need it now.
Buy me one
when I get into college.
Okay.
The pictures are good, though.
Bastards...
Let's see who laughs last.
It's Cho Pansu, isn't it?
How do you know that scumbag?
Cheers!
Good job today.
That's how we get things done.
Let's drink.
Hey, Taesik.
I have no business with you.
Let me talk to Mr. Cho.
You're the Oh Taesik, huh?
I've heard about you.
I have a favor to ask of you.
I promised to myself
that I'd never fight again.
Help me keep that promise.
I force you to fight?
What makes you think that?
I was going to ask you help me
with my business.
I have a job.
You should have bigger goals in life.
I'm satisfied now.
My business is legitimate.
Thank you.
But no thanks.
That's a shame.
Do me this favor.
It's a favor?
More like a threat to me.
What's so difficult?
We're helping each other.
It's very easy.
We'll set the table.
You arrest him afterwards.
He's on parole.
It'll put him back in jail.
Can you do it?
No problem.
You know I'm good.
What's up?
You don't need to know.
- Let's go eat.
- Okay.
Hi.
I hear you guys are good.
You got that right.
What's wrong with it?
I want something special.
Like a flying car in the movie.
Cool, isn't it?
Put wings on my car.
You're kidding.
I am?
I had a burger for lunch.
You think I ate that to joke
with you?
Come on, put wings on my car.
We don't do that here.
Go to a different garage.
A different one?
Where?
You should be able to tell us
where I can have it done.
Where?
Please, don't.
Asshole!
I'm sorry if! offended you.
You're sorry?
This guy is so arrogant.
What are you doing?
Beat him.
I'm sorry.
Sorry my ass!
Taesik!
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Taesik!
Why are you doing this?
Stop it!
I'm okay.
Why are you doing this?
I'm okay. I'm okay.
What are you doing?
- What are you looking at?
- I'll poke your eyes out.
That's enough.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
Sir.
I'm glad you didn't lose it.
You did well.
Look!
They're leaving?
Who's that stupid ass?
He couldn't get him upset?
Anyway, Taesik has changed a lot.
He would've knocked them out
10 years ago.
5 big ones, and...
Are these all you have?
That's right.
I need more.
Can I order them in sets?
You didn't know them?
Never seen them before.
No reason?
Right.
It is true.
You did get beat up.
When I heard you got beat
by petty thugs...
I didn't believe it, but it's true.
You know him?
He's just a kid.
A kid?
You call me a kid?
Watch it.
Get out of here.
Don't bother my son again.
Your son my ass.
I know the whole story.
What a fucked-up family.
How can you adopt a guy
who whacked your own son?
You call that a family?
Shut up.
You whacked her son, right?
Choi Dopil.
What? What?
It's late.
Go to your room.
He really killed my brother?
Did he?
How could you do that?
How could you adopt a man
who killed your son?
Things happen in life.
It was an accident.
Still, it was him who killed
my brother.
After the funeral...
I went to see him in jail.
I wanted to ask him...
...what he did to deserve that.
Then what?
He started crying,
saying he was sorry.
I'd never seen anybody
cry like that.
Seeing him cry...
I realized
he'd just made a mistake.
And that he wasn't a bad person.
So I visited him a few more times.
I watched him for 10 years.
He was a good kid.
So I decided to make him my son.
I must be crazy.
I thought you had quit.
I want to, but it isn't easy.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't thinking right.
I'll leave.
Take care of your mom.
What about us?
Mom and I were happy
to have you with us.
Now you're leaving?
You're so funny.
You come and go as you like?
Huiju...
I'm thankful.
I came to thank you,
and you tell me you're leaving?
My brother was her son.
But he was a piece of shit.
He would beat her for money.
I was very young
when I heard that he died.
But I was very happy.
That mom would never be
beaten up by her own son.
Don't go.
I don't care what others say.
And mom is happy with you.
I've never seen her that happy.
Live with us.
I'm going down.
Smoke another cigarette.
I'll call you brother
from now on.
Brother...
God, it feels awkward.
So you're saying...
I ordered Dopil to hit Taesik.
So one died,
and the other ended up in jail?
And I cheated Dopil
out of the field of sunflowers?
If you leave Taesik and us alone,
I'll keep quiet.
You must be going senile.
Let's say that's true.
Why make an issue out of it now,
not 10 years ago?
If even you gave an order,
it was my son who did it.
It's my son's diary.
I couldn't care less
if you become a Congressmen.
But if this diary gets out...
You're going down.
It's Dopil's?
Yes, it's his.
What are you gonna do?
What do you think?
Nothing gets done
without me stepping in.
We should take care of this.
This is impossible.
Taesik, open this for me.
Okay.
Damn.
Hi, Wellbeing Garage.
Taesik, it's me.
Sunflower Lady is in danger.
What?
She blackmailed Mr. Cho.
- He won't leave her alone.
- What do you mean?
What happened 10 years ago...
It was Cho's work.
He gave Dopil the order.
What she knows is true.
I'm telling you
Cho won't let this slide.
Taesik, be careful.
I called to warn you.
You missed class.
Where'd you go?
How will you go to college
if you play hooky?
She's been drinking all day.
Mother, I'm home.
Nobody can touch us now.
I fixed the problem.
Give me a minute.
Let me finish the song.
J'Fall, this lonely night
IBugs are crying
Doing your best isn't enough.
The winner sleeps with a beauty.
And the loser sleeps alone.
- Understood?
- Yes.
Let's go, boys.
One, two, three.
Let's go!
Nice serve!
Far, further!
Guard! Guard!
She got hurt because of me.
No, don't be saying that.
Ifl had sold the restaurant,
it wouldn't have happened.
I didn't think
I wanted that much out of life.
Taesik, she's family.
Okay?
Yes.
Nothing's more important
than family in life, okay?
Yes, mother.
Okay, we'll sell the place
and leave.
We'll start all over.
Take it.
It's for her surgery.
It should be enough.
I saved it for her wedding later.
But we need it now.
Byungjin, it's me.
I need to see Mr. Cho.
Where should I go?
I need to talkto him.
- Or...
- It's Oracle.
- What does it mean?
- A prophet.
Crazy bastards!
A prophet at a night club?
What can he predict?
Who knows?
I hope to see them go down
before I die.
But I don't see it happening.
- Let's go eat.
- Okay.
Want a shot?
No thanks.
What'd you wanna see me for?
My family will leave town.
Oh, okay.
Nobody's stopping you.
Thank you.
We'll leave in a few days.
Well...
If you commit a sin,
you get punished for it.
Give me one of your arms,
and I'll let you go.
What do you say?
No?
Go ahead.
You'll be able to hold a spoon.
Taesik, your arm is fine.
Don't worry.
You know what! mean?
Have a good life somewhere else.
Consider it as a last gift from me.
It's okay.
Everything will be fine.
I'll protect you with my life.
We'll be happy again.
My dear son...
Only if! could see you again.
Ifl have to pick the most
difficult time of my life...
It's when we built the restaurant.
After your father died suddenly...
We were so poor then.
I wasn't eating well
so I couldn't breastfeed Huiju.
But what kept me going was you.
You were mean to me later.
Butl believed
you'd come around one day.
Looking back...
It was the toughest time
of my life.
But at the same time...
I couldn't be happier then,
building the restaurant together.
I wanted to keep the restaurant.
But those bastards are forcing us out.
I'm sorry.
Mom's so sorry.
The living has to keep on living.
Yes, we'll leave.
I'll be fine somewhere else.
Mother, it's me.
Mother!
Mother, open your eyes.
Mother?
Mother! Mother!
Mom, open your eyes.
Open your eyes!
Mom! I
Mom...
Open your eyes!
Mom? I
Mom... Mom...
Mother...
Mom, open your eyes.
Mom? Mom!
She was such a good person.
Being rich isn't everything
in life.
It's about living a healthy life,
respecting others.
I don't understand
why she did it.
She was such a nice person.
She should've listened to us.
She got too greedy.
Anybody?
It's me, Taesik.
Taesik?
Oh, I said I'd call you brother.
Brother...
Sounds weird?
No.
Where's mom?
Mom?
She's at the restaurant.
She'll be back soon.
Brother...
Do me a favor.
Hello?
Everybody, focus.
Let's rehearse again.
Attention. Bow.
Sir!
Nothing's impossible
if you push it.
How nice of you
to work together.
It's all thanks to you.
Get along from now on.
Run the club well.
What's this?
What?
Can't you hear it?
Who the fuck is crying?
It's me, fucker.
Oh Taesik.
You know what?
For 10 years, I regretted
and promised to myself.
Did you have to do it?
You shouldn't have.
Did you have to take it all?
Motherfuckers!
Are you out of your mind?
Taesik, you're back.
Welcome.
What can you do with
that hand?
I heard about that lady.
And her daughter.
It's so sad.
I'll make it sadder for you.
I was looking for it.
You had it.
Who messed up Huiju's face?
I did, asshole.
Got a problem?
Byungjin, leave.
Unless you wanna die.
That moron!
I'm sorry.
Thanks for letting me live.
If you commit a sin,
you get punished for it.
Understood?
Consider it my punishment.
Hey, do something.
This is quite embarrassing.
Give me a chance.
I'll take care of him.
Yeah? Go ahead.
This is my break
to leave a good impression.
I can do this.
He's a joke.
Should I make it worse?
Fuck! Put out the fire!
Get away from me!
Motherfucker!
I saw this coming.
I should've dealt
with you myself.
Trash is trash.
Did you drink?
No.
I didn't drink.
Did you ﬁght?
No.
I didn't ﬁght.
Then you won't be crying.
Forever!
Mom...
Huiju...
I'm sorry.
Here's the definition
of Laplace transform.
Either F (s) or L (f) are used
as notation.
Laplace transform of F (t) is...
0 to infinity.
2 and -s (t), f (t), dt.
And this inverse
Laplace transform is F (t).
Next, this is example of
Laplace transform.
When t is bigger than 0 and
F (t) is 1...
Laplace transform
of this is...
By the definition L (f) is L (1)
and integral 0 to infinity,
2 and -s (t), dt so,
if you integral calculus
- 1Is, 1 and -s (t)...
0 to infinity
so the answer is 1Is.
That's it for today.
You had a hard time
staying awake.
I'll make sure those who dozed off
will get a F.
Hand in your papers to Huiju.
Everybody's impressed
with your thesis, Huiju.
See you.
Passing a thesis examination
Let me ask you something.
What is it?
Were you in love with Taesik?
Love?
I don't know.
What do you think love is?
What's love?
It's simple.
It's about happy moments
and good memories.
If you remember,
love doesn't change.
It doesn't?