Let's go!
- Wang!
- Chon, for God's sakes.
- Now he shows up.
- I found it.
Wait. Do you want to hear?
The seal's gone.
Lin.
Roy!
Are we gonna come back?
Must you keep doing that?
I was taught
not to be seen or heard.
The seal.
I am a man of my word.
I remember watching
my brother play with this
like a baby rattle.
When I'd try to touch it,
the dowager empress beat me.
No doubt your deprived childhood
made you into the man you are today.
Wu Chow.
Wu who?
He is the emperor's bastard brother.
He was banished
from the Forbidden City
for trying to steal the Imperial Seal.
Our father caught him.
He vowed to return to claim
the emperor's throne.
This guy?
I'll assume everything
has been arranged as discussed.
You have nothing to worry about.
It's all in place.
That diamond is as big
as a damn monkey's paw.
- Look at that.
- Roy.
Don't even think about it.
I'm just admiring
the craftsmanship, Chon.
So for now,
our business is completed.
Where's Lin?!
Hey! Hey!
Gotcha!
Just looking out for number one.
No!
The kid got the seal!
Chon!
It's stuck.
Lin!
Go! You can do it!
She's got it.
She's got it!
Roy! Come on!
Chon, what in our history together
makes you think I'm capable
of something like that?
- Roy!
- I can't do that!
Hurry up!
Wait.
There's a better way.
Slow down!
I'm a bat out of hell!
Yee-haw!
Besides, I don't know
where the brake is.
What?!
Look out!
So, what now, buddy?
Relax, relax.
Smooth sailing from here.
Yes, these are the men
who attacked me.
I'm afraid the assailants have
temporarily eluded us, my Lord.
Perhaps you could explain to me
how Loony Lin managed to escape
from the confines of
Scotland Yard under the watch
of the most respected
police force in the world.
Yes, of course.
It's absolutely fascinating.
She picked the lock
using a deck of rather
risque playing cards.
Then scaled the walls
with a mop, a fork...
and various pilfered undergarments.
You've got to hand it to the Chinese.
They're awfully ingenious,
Lord, aren't they?
Does your incompetence know
no bounds?!
Where am I?
Lin!
I don't even know these women.
Lin, what are you doing here?
Oh, Lord.
Do you want to try
the position on page 37?
Come here, you little minx.
What?
- You okay?
- No, I'm not okay.
I've just been violated
by a barnyard animal.
Who would leave a pile of stones
in the middle of the field?
I don't know, Chon.
These people are nuts.
Come on.
- Can I tell you something?
- What?
This is a hell
of a damn adventure we're on.
I'm having
an absolute ball with you.
Me too.
Here we go.
Get your thumb out, maharaja.
- Why?
- Get over here.
Excuse me!
- Lin!
My shoulder's getting
a little tight.
This is your first time
in England, isn't it?
How do you know your way around?
It's incredible.
I always had a good sense
of direction.
You can say that again.
I wish we could say the same
about you-know-who.
I once sent him over a mountain range.
He was lost forever.
One time, I sent him
over the Great Wall.
- He was lost for three days.
- Three days?!
Oh, gosh, we got a lot in common.
I've never met
anybody like you, Roy.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Hey, can I tell you something
without you getting offended?
What?
You have a great body.
There. I said it.
It's out in the open.
- You must work out.
- Me?
Excuse me.
Chon, what are you doing?
I don't like the backseat.
Makes me sick. Dizzy.
Whitechapel.
This looks like
a nice enough neighborhood.
- What is Puss 'n' Boots?
- It's a boardinghouse.
Some of the sailors on the ship
coming over recommended it.
Come on. Come on!
I won't let my sister stay here.
What are we supposed to do?
Check in to the Savoy?
We'll get arrested
before we get to our room.
I don't mind this place.
See?
She's a little open-minded.
I know this sounds crazy
'cause I just met her...
but I think I'm falling for her.
I think she's the one.
Roy, she's my baby sister.
I know she is.
Thank God!
That's the only chance
I've got.
Look, I'm getting ready
to launch a little thing
called "Operation:
Sweep Her Off Her Feet."
You're in a position to talk me up.
Can I count on you?
Please, buddy, I've never
asked you for anything.
Sure, Roy.
I'll tell her the truth.
Don't get hung up on the truth.
Feel free to smooth out
your old pal's rough edges.
I love you, buddy.
Lin. Come.
Sit.
Hello, love.
Fancy a tumble?
Oh!
Where were you two days ago?
I would have bedded you
in a second.
Now you're looking
at a changed man.
I'm sort of saving myself
for someone special.
I'll give you a discount.
That's the most romantic thing
any woman's ever said to me.
You better go.
You better go
before we lose control. Go!
If you change your mind...
Roy!
Lin. Our father would talk about
the right man for you.
He must be strong, courageous...
and a good father.
- Like Roy.
- We got her, Chon.
Not like Roy.
You don't know him like I do.
He has many bad habits.
Such as?
He drinks, smokes, and he gambles.
Chon, where are you going with this?
He sleeps with women for money.
What are you...
Roy don't do that.
I can see inside him.
He has a good heart.
That's right.
His salmon don't swim upstream.
He shoots blanks.
Lin, he cannot be trusted.
How could you say that?
You're his friend.
Yeah, sort of.
Roy is the type of a friend
you'd never introduce
to your other friends
or bring home to your family.
He never speak the truth.
You know what I call him?
Not Roy O'Bannon.
Roy O'Baloney.
I don't care.
Lin, I forbid it.
You are not my father.
Roy, there you are.
- Hi.
- Mm-hmm.
You need anything, buddy?
A whole lot of
"leave me alone."
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I woke up
on the wrong side of the bed.
I feel a little pain in my back
like someone put a knife there.
I'm okay.
Don't worry about me.
Roy!
Ta-da!
That actually reminds me of a trick.
You ever seen this one?!
Or this one?!
You think you're so cool
with your karate
and your childlike reflexes.
Roy, you okay?
Look at you.
Do you really call me Roy Baloney?
Roy, you don't understand.
You just smashed my puzzle box.
I'll never figure out my message.
- Roy...
- Go.
You're dead to me.
I don't know a Chon Wang.
What?
Hi, Roy.
Who loves you, baby?
- Nice try, Chon.
- Roy...
I'm sorry.
You do that again,
and you're a dead man.
Pillow fight!
I am Roy Baloney!
Yes!
I'm full of it!
You are!
Roy?
Lin!
It was his idea.
- Chon!
- Clothes!
Nice night for a walk.
Lin!
- Lin!
- There you are!
What are you doing?
Don't you know there's
a serial killer on the loose?
Forget it.
Who the hell are these guys?
Boxers.
What do they want with us?
They're with me.
I think we need to have a little chat.
Chon Wang...
the man who can fight an emperor.
The emperor should never have
his burial knife.
I see.
You're still my brother's lapdog.
I'm here not for him.
I'm here for my father.
Of course you are.
It was my dagger
that plunged into his heart.
It's still crusted with his blood.
I know the boy has the seal.
Where is he?
We don't know.
That's the truth...
we don't know.
Mmm...
What are you...
What are you doing?
Stop! Put her down!
Put her down!
Or what, Mr. O'Bannon?
Are you gonna kick my ass?
I've read all about
your ridiculous exploits.
I mean, just...
how does it feel to kill
a mummy with your bare hands?
Only a nation
of uneducated rednecks
would be amused by such cowboy drivel.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Easy.
What's with the personal attacks?
You don't see me
making any comments
about your pasty complexion
or your snotty accent
or even your filthy, smutty sex books.
Yeah, I saw your book.
It disgusted me.
Oh, why is it always the head
with you people?!
Hold it! Stop! Hold it!
Just hold it!
What are we doing here?
Guys, look at this.
We're acting like animals...
over what?
Some seal?
The seal represents imperial power.
I will use it to unite
the emperor's enemies
and storm the Forbidden City.
What's in it for you?
You're looking
at the future king of England.
You're, like, 20th in line to the throne.
10th.
But my friend is about to change all that
by simple...
process of elimination.
It's called a machine gun.
The first of its kind...
it fires 200 rounds a minute.
Testament to British ingenuity.
Oh, so you steal the seal,
and then you knock off nine royals?
You got the short end
of that stick, my friend.
Dump them in the river.
Where are you taking her?
To make history.
I can already see the headlines...
"Nation mourns as Loony Lin
massacres royal family."
I need your assurance
that you will find the seal.
Don't concern yourself.
My men are scouring the city.
You better pray they find it...
or our agreement is over,
and you will never get the crown.
Chon, I got a confession to make.
You are in love with my sister.
Well, that, but...
I didn't lose all the money
on the zeppelins.
No?
Nah. I blew most of it
on the Roy O'Bannon novels.
I wrote them.
No, Sage McCallister wrote them.
That's what I'm saying, buddy.
I'm Sage McCallister.
You wrote those lies?!
I've always had low self-esteem.
How many books did you print?
I self-published probably a million copies.
We were actually second
to the Bible that year.
Oh, you...
I guess I'm just about
the worst friend
a guy could ask for.
No, you're a good friend.
Thank you.
If you really love Lin,
I won't stand in the way.
Really?
But if you break her heart...
I'll break your legs.
That's fair.
Well,
friends to the end, Chon...
and this is the end.
Chon, you got a plan?
You wouldn't happen to have
a plan, would you?
Yes.
- Anything I can do?
- No.
Good. I'll let you do
the heavy lifting, then.
Chon, hurry.
Chon!
Chon! Chon, hurry!
Hurry!
Hurry! Chon, hurry!
Roy!
Coming!
Chon!
Oh!
The water's so dirty!
No! No! It's dirty! No!
Just go ahead and drown me.
I don't care anymore.
Roy!
You look ridiculous.
I think we look good.
I really must protest
this intrusion.
Every bobby in London is out
scouring the streets
for you two.
Have you been drinking?
I always drink when my
employment's been terminated.
They fired you?
Lord Rathbone saw to that.
I'm sorry.
It's of no consequence.
I never wanted to be
an inspector in the first place.
It was my father's idea.
I always wanted to be a writer.
Yeah.
Artie, we need your help.
Rathbone has taken Lin.
He's gonna kill the royal family
and he's gonna assume the throne.
Do you have any evidence
to support these
preposterous allegations?
We have this.
It's the boy's.
Use your technique.
Tell us where he is.
Paraffin wax...
most interesting.
He's at a church.
The little punk's hiding
in a church.
No, no, no.
It's not candle wax.
I have it.
- Don't worry. You'll get it.
- What are you doing?
- He's picking the lock.
- Well, hurry up!
Chon, please! Please.
It's a very meticulous process.
Let Artie do his job.
It's almost an art form.
It takes the precision
of a surgeon.
You have to be so precise.
Maybe if we jam
another one in there.
That works, too.
Lacks a certain finesse.
All right, all right.
Let's split up.
What the...
I am gonna break your neck.
Come here.
Looky here.
- Come on, where is it?
- What?
You know
what I'm talking about.
Don't give me that "what."
What do we got here?
Oh, yes.
You don't mind
if I take this back, do you?
Go on.
Get out of here.
Go!
Roy?
I got it.
Give me the seal.
Give me the seal!
All right, spread out!
Through there!
Let's go.
The gig's up.
So, what are we gonna do?
Come on, think!
I'm not going
to an English prison.
With my feathery blond hair
and Chon's athletic build,
they'll try to make us
the belle of the ball.
Forget it.
I'm not going back.
Well, at least we'll get
a good view of the fireworks
from Scotland Yard.
- Fireworks?
- Yeah.
At midnight, they're launching
this huge display
from a flotilla of barges
on the Thames.
It's the official kickoff
to the Queen's Jubilee.
Is the royal family gonna be there?
They're gonna be viewing
the spectacle from a balcony
overlooking the river.
He's got a machine gun on the barge.
Yes.
You gents lost your way?
Kid, tell me
you got a way out.
Nice move, kid.
So why did you come back?
Why did you give up the seal?
'Cause I'm a fool.
Guess I'm a fool, too.
Well, put her there, fool.
I never got your name.
Name's Chaplin...
Charlie Chaplin.
- Excuse me.
Excuse me, please!
You warn the royal family.
I'll save Lin.
How on earth are you gonna do that?
You okay?
I just saved you!
You were late!
What?!
Nelson?
Why are you hiding yourself
back there?
I shouldn't like to impede
your view, Your Highness.
Nonsense.
You arranged all this.
You should have a front-row view.
I regret that, uh,
respectfully I must decline.
I need to keep a good eye
on proceedings.
Whoo!
Nelson,
you've outdone yourself.
Wait till you see the finale.
Hey!
Oh!
This is hopeless.
We're not gonna get past the guards.
Well, not with that attitude we won't.
Come on, Artie.
There's got to be a way.
There's always...
Lin!
Yee-haw! Yeah!
Yee-haw!
We got to jump it!
Wu Chow!
Hold it right there,
Rathboner.
I'm guessing
by your hasty retreat
that you're still
20th in line for the throne.
10th.
Inspector Doyle, arrest this man.
He's got a gun!
Oh!
Come on!
- Oh!
- You okay?
What happened?
Rathbone nailed Artie
with a little sissy gun.
I'll look after him.
You two go.
Go!
For Father.
For Old Man Wang.
Oh, my lucky playing cards.
Be careful.
Tell Rathbone to be careful.
Roy, let's go.
You're gonna need a bigger gun!
You see him?
No.
Show your face, Rathbone!
I'm gonna tear this guy apart.
Roy, you go this way.
I'll go that way.
Split up? I don't know
if that's a good idea.
It's okay.
He's not up here.
Roy, keep going.
Aw, come on, Roy.
Hey, uh, Rathbone...
I was just thinking
of a title for my new book...
"Roy O'Bannon vs. Little Lord Sissy."
But what about "Roy O'Bannon vs.
The Man Who Would Be Queen"?
No sign of him, Chon.
The coast is clear up here.
Roy! Look out!
Roy!
Oops.
Come on up.
I'll show you how your father died.
Lord, help me.
Just let me know you're there.
Love me. Hate me.
But let me know you're up there!
Hey, I can see our hotel from here.
Wow.
Come along.
I'm waiting.
Come on, Roy. Okay.
Roy O'Bannon will not go quietly.
You hear that, England?!
Throw whatever you want at me...
your terrible weather,
your perverted killers,
your Spotted Dick!
Roy, you're about to die.
You're on the minute hand of a clock.
My life is flashing before my eyes.
Wait a minute.
I don't remember her.
One more.
Oh!
How disappointing.
One more.
You killed my friend.
You killed my father!
Roy!
I thought you were dead!
Oh!
You think some tea-drinking psycho
can take out Roy O'Bannon?
Whoa.
Easy there, cowboy.
Huh?
You got any ideas?
- We jump!
- Jump?!
You mean fall?!
Aim for the flag!
Aw, shit.
I got to tell you something.
What?
You're the best sidekick
I could ever ask for.
Thank you, Roy.
I feel the same about you.
On three.
One...
Two...
- Three!
Roy. Roy!
Howdy.
In recognition of outstanding bravery,
I dub you Sir Chon Wang.
For uncommon valor,
I dub you Sir Roy O'Bannon.
And for steadfast dedication to justice,
I dub you Sir Arthur Conan Doyle.
Arise.
Who loves you, baby?
Madam.
Artie, I bet Scotland Yard's
dying to get you back now.
My official
crime-fighting days are over.
The queen has asked me
to accompany the Imperial Seal
back to China.
What a week.
Unbelievable.
She couldn't have picked
a better man, right, Chon?
Yeah.
And the voyage is gonna give me
time to work on my new novel.
It features a new kind of detective,
and he's gonna solve crimes
using deductive reasoning.
Give me a name.
What's his name?
Actually, Roy,
I was rather hoping
to call him Sherlock Holmes,
if that's all right with you.
I'd be insulted if you didn't use it.
- Ta.
- See you, Artie.
That was very nice of you, Roy.
I would've kept the name
if I thought it was any good.
It's a horrible name
for a detective...
Sherlock Holmes. Holmes?
Will you stop playing with that?
I'm gonna smash it.
I just want to see it for a second.
- Just let me see it.
- No, you're gonna break it.
It's just a rock
with some gibberish on it.
That's Chinese.
"Family is forever, my son.
I'm proud
you cast your own stone."
Wow.
That's a good message.
I'd like to cast my own stone, Chon.
- Hi.
I told you... the house
of O'Bannon will prevail.
Chon, I got a business
proposition for you.
No more zeppelins.
No, no, this is much better
than zeppelins...
a new thing they're starting
out in California
called moving pictures.
Pass.
Hold it. Hold it.
Hear me out.
I really think these movies
could play to your strength.
There's no sound,
so we don't have to worry
about the language problem.
And I think the kung fu stuff
could be huge.
People are dying
for a good action picture.
What do you think?
Chon Wang, movie star?
It could work.
I feel bad about ditching
that Chaplin kid,
but we're gonna be running
and gunning in Hollywood,
and he'd just cramp our style.
It's such a tough town.
Bloody tourists!
Action!
You have to say "cut."
You just keep looking!
Ouch.
Come here, you little minx.
Cut.
That was good.
That was a good one, huh?
Maybe on this one
I should lick you... you think?
Like, after you lick me...
that could be kind of good.
And, Jackie...
Jackie?
Thank you. Hi, Owen.
Hello. How are you?
Okay, and I'm not
Roy O'Bannon.
Who are you?
Damn it, Chon,
I think she's the one.
I know it's crazy.
We just met, but she's the one.
No, Roy,
she's my babysitter.
Your babys...
What?
Baby what?
Baby sister.
Baby sister?
Not babysitter.
Baby sister.
You okay?
Action!
What happened?
Roy is the type of a friend
you never introduce
to your other friends
or bring into your family.
He's... Look at his eyes.
They're brown... full of shit.
Always...
Just bullshit all the time.
Yeah, have you ever heard of those?
They're parents.
We have parents that love us.
You don't,
'cause you're a little orphan.
You don't...
We've got par... Yeah, parents.
Have you ever heard of those?
We've got parents that love us.
But you don't,
'cause you're a little orphan.
Oh, go on.
So mean.
Chon Wang, movie star?
It could work.
You could do your own stunts.
What? My own stunts?
Ow!
Whoa! Whoa!
Stay here and be a good horsey
for the new sheriff.
Ouch! Oh!
Ow. That hurt.
Ow! Ooh!
Ow!
Oh!
You're supposed to catch me!
Roy, catch.
- Jesus.
- That's my fault.
Wait a second.
This nut is killing
your street women?
Who did that?
Jackie Chan.
Me?
That's right.
- That was the...
- First time.
- The best take.
- I'm sorry.
Hurry up!
Are you crazy?!
I can't do that!
This isn't Chinatown!
I can't sail through the air!
- I'm not gonna break my neck!
- Roy!
What in our history together
makes you think I'm capable
of something like that?
It's getting bigger!
There's got to be
a better way.
Roy!
My ass is on fire.