Is it true that there are some
Han Chinese staying at our inn?
They're all from the Hua Mountain Sect.
I heard they're here to harvest herbs.
While travelling,
I discovered many scouts from the
Eastern Imperial Secretariat following us.
Maybe it's due to the success of our Sun
Moon Sect's trade in smuggled salt.
They want a share of the pie,
so that's why they attacked us.
Blue Phoenix!
Your bad habits are showing again!
Like a cat thinking of fish,
you think of men all the time.
Right now, the Han Chinese are outside,
wanting to take advantage of us.
If you don't behave, I'll punish you
severely according to our rules.
I, Blue Phoenix, understand.
I wonder where Skinny Boy went?
Hey, Skinny Boy!
What do you think you're doing?
Brother, I like you.
Little Brother, I haven't seen you before.
Where are you from?
What's going on?
You're a woman!
Who asked you to enter?
Leave now!
Did you understand what I said?
Leave!
You're Han Chinese!
A snake!
Get out!
- Elder Brother?
Hua Mountain Sect is a renowned
sect in the martial arts world.
We have 333 rules.
We adhere to them strictly.
If anyone breaches a rule,
then I won't let him get away with it!
You're a student of the Hua Mountain
Sect. You have to beware of your sifu.
He's not as righteous as he seems.
Blue Phoenix.
I told you
not to mingle with men outside,
yet you've lost us face
to the Han Chinese.
If you don't change,
I'll lock you up.
But he was a woman.
Chief!
Our men have discovered
the scouts have surrounded our inn.
It appears that they've come for us.
Tell everyone
to be prepared and alert.
Steal all the weapons
from the Han Chinese.
Drug their wine.
When they've passed out,
tie them up.
If the scouts dare to approach,
kill them.
We understand.
This is a chance for you
to redeem yourself.
I understand.
Your punishment is to return to
Hua Mountain for three years.
Yes.
I understand.
A symbol of our sacred Sect?
- Get out.
- Yes, sifu.
Did Uncle Lam say anything
before he passed away?
Yes. He asked me to do
something very important.
What was it?
Sit down.
Tell me
the details of what happened.
Sifu, Hua Mountain teachers
and students aren't equals.
Then stand and tell me.
You can tell me now.
I still can't tell you.
Why not? Not telling your sifu is disloyalty,
a serious violation of the rules.
I know, but I swore to Mr. Lam on my life
that I would only tell his son, Lam Ping Ji.
If I violate an oath,
I would be breaking rule 58.
I would be lying to the heavens,
and would have to unlearn my martial arts.
Rule 58?
You're right, but if this message is critical
to Hua Mountain Sect's existence,
then we must make an exception.
That won't work either.
I'll be in violation of rule 79.
If I break my promise to save myself,
I'll be excommunicated by the Sect.
But rule 26 states that if one repents and
is willing to change, forgiveness is granted.
A gentleman may be forced
to be acquiescent to the situation.
Then, if one repents and is willing to
change, forgiveness is still granted. You...
That's even more serious.
I would be lying to my sifu.
It violates rule 83.
Deceiving a teacher means
condemnation and heavenly annihilation.
Good! Good!
You are indeed a top student.
I tested you on purpose to see
if you did adhere to our rules.
Had you told me, you'd have
violated his trust and your faith.
Sifu would have been
the first to destroy you.
That was a close call.
Your test is over.
You can go to see Lam Ping Ji now.
Where am I supposed to find him?
He's just next door.
The next room?
- Quickly tell him the secret.
- So much for a long journey.
The Elder Kuk's qin.
Why does he have it?
Blue Phoenix. You need to first deduce
if this person is a friend or foe.
- Put the qin back where it was.
- I understand.
Don't alert him.
Tell the kitchen not to use
the 7-day sleeping draught yet.
When we know the whereabouts of
the Elder Kuk, we'll make a decision then.
We understand.
You're...
I'm Lam Ping Ji.
- And you are...?
- Ling Wu Chung.
The walls have ears.
Come here a moment.
Before he died, your father
told me to tell you a secret.
He said there's a Lam family treasure
hidden under your family's waterwheel.
Brother Ling Wu, allow me
to bow to you in thanks.
Don't mention it.
Brother Ling Wu, I know you like
drinking wine. Wait a moment.
With a Miao wedding taking place,
I'll use this occasion to gift you this wine.
How did you know
I liked drinking wine?
It smells so good.
Sifu would like you to dine
with him downstairs
when our brother
has finished talking to you.
Okay.
But our brother and sister must remain
in their rooms as punishment.
- I'll deliver dinner to you later.
- Even better! I can savour this wine alone.
- Smells great.
- Bullshit.
The moonlight shines
in front of my bed
I raise my head
to look at the moon
I bow my head and
think of home, think of home...
Nephew...
Where are you rushing off to?
In two days, it will be one week
since my father's death.
I want to rush back
to arrange his funeral.
Such filial piety.
But it should be arranged
by an elder like me.
There's an Uncle Lam managing
the funeral arrangements at home.
Uncle?
You have an uncle?
I have to speak with him.
I'll take you home.
- Sifu.
I can pass on your message. If! bring him
the message, it will save you a trip.
It's no bother, no bother.
Sit. All of you, sit.
- Take a seat.
Uncle Ngok, you don't know my uncle.
And my uncle doesn't know you.
What's so important that you must
discuss with him and not with me?
For example,
wedding arrangements.
I must discuss these with your elder.
Why would I discuss it
with you? Right?
A wedding?
I plan to arrange a marriage between
my daughter Ling San and you.
Uncle, I'm in mourning. It would be
unwise for me to discuss marriage.
Why don't we discuss this
in a year or so?
No, it can't wait.
You can't get out of it that easily.
I'll stand in for your father and take care
of you. I'll help make the right decisions.
You can't object. Be obedient
and do what I say, or I'll get angry!
- Let's dine.
- Dad! I don't want to get married!
- Nonsense!
- I won't...
You cannot speak out!
Without me, you wouldn't exist.
This doesn't concern you.
Upstairs!
This is for your own good!
- Lam Ping Ji eats dog shit!
- Nonsense! See if! don't kill you!
She's so spoiled.
Uncle Ngok, thankfully you're here,
or there would've been a scene.
Without a doubt!
One's guard must not be dropped!
Who is it?
- Open up, it's me.
- Okay.
There's no need to hide any more.
My sister's here.
If you knew I was there,
why didn't you say something?
If you knew I was sitting on you,
why did you let me?
Leave now!
Hurry! Hurry!
- Don't tell my Chief.
- Okay. Leave!
Look me up when you're free
and I'll sing for you again.
- Coming!
- Brother!
Brother, sifu is planning to arrange for
our sister to marry Lam Ping Ji.
Hurry up
and think of something!
Even a tomboy can get married?!
Who's the unlucky guy?
I don't know him.
If! have to marry, I'd rather marry you.
I've always treated you as a brother.
I don't see you as a woman.
How can you marry me?
Even though I don't act like a woman,
I can learn.
I can learn to be more feminine.
So what? I've never fantasised
about you in that way.
We've been brothers for so long!
What about loyalty?
Look how fierce you can be! You're lucky
if someone wants to marry you.
Will you two stop arguing!
When dawn breaks,
we have to go to the Lam family's home.
If you don't think of something soon,
then it really will be too late!
You're still drinking? Once you get drunk,
Lam Ping Ji can carry you away!
If we go,
we'll have to wander forever.
Have you considered we'd never
be able to return to Hua Mountain?
Never go back?
Yeah. Make up your mind soon.
Run away or get married.
Don't delay.
Run now, plan later.
By the time you've come to a decision,
it'll be dawn!
You're still drinking?
Hurry up and pack your bags!
Be at the big forest before dawn.
Whoever doesn't turn up
will be a nincompoop!
Why are you not drinking the wine?
I don't know how to appreciate wine.
I'm giving it back to you.
Blue Phoenix.
Who told you to drug him?
I didn't.
Chief, he's not been given a sleeping
draught, but a very strong poison.
And it's spread to all the different
meridian points already.
If we don't do anything to save him
in the next four hours,
he may lose
all his martial arts skills.
Damn! Why did you sit on my head
and play music?
What did you say about a head?
Nothing. I said the poison
has gone to his head.
He's been seriously poisoned.
- Bring him back round.
- Yes.
Show me later how to play
the qin with your head!
Do you still want to drink
some more?
I can't. I can't drink anymore.
You drunk almost all the wine
available here.
Keep an eye on him.
Don't let him make trouble in his state.
- Yes, sifu.
The Han Chinese are leaving.
Detain them!
The Han Chinese!
Wait, Chief! If you kill him,
no-one will be able to tell us what
happened to venerable elder Kuk.
Feed him the poisonous worm so that
he'll tell us about our venerable elder Kuk.
Chief, if we feed him
the poisonous worm,
he may become physically handicapped
for the rest of his life.
You're still asking
for mercy on his behalf?!
I dare not, Chief.
These Han Chinese
are working against us.
Cut him up after you
finish questioning him.
Bury him with our dead brothers.
The blue seas laugh
Surging against both shores
We are carried by the waves
We are only concerned with
the here and now
The azure skies laugh
LAUGHING PROUD
WORLD OF MARTIAL ARTS
At the disorder in the world
Only the heavens know
Who will win
and who will lose
The rivers
and mountains laugh
The clouds and rain
are far away
After the billowing waves
are spent
How beautiful the vulgar world
of mortals seems
The clear breezes laugh
And they provoke
feelings of solitude
Noble sentiments
even leave us melancholic
Like a long stretch
of moonlit nights
The green earth laughs
Solitude is no more
Noble sentiments
still make us laugh like we don't care
Mr. Kuk!
Chief!
This man turned out to be
a good friend of our venerable elder Kuk.
Give him the antidote!
If we don't first balance
his inner constitution,
and give him the antidote now,
he won't be able to handle it, and will die.
Quickly render him conscious,
or else I'll kill you all!
One minute she says kill him,
the next save him.
Pay close attention
to Chief's orders.
Otherwise,
if you can't save him,
she'll blame you
for the rest of your life.
The Sect's rules
will be relaxed from now on.
The brave heroes from the Five Mountain
Ranges are indestructible!
Those from the Five Mountain Ranges
are condemned by heaven and earth!
Keep your inner chi steady.
Listen to my calming music.
Chief! Your playing
is less steady than his inner chi.
You talk about being indestructible,
but you're dead afterjust one move.
One arm
in exchange for your life!
Evil... cult!
"Venomous snake rattles his tail."
You have an iron claw!
You have similar weaponry.
We must force out the poisonous worm.
You witch, you're shameless!
Imperial dog!
You're in my way!
- Leave Ling Wu Chung here!
- Leave this place!
- Still trying to escape?!
- Get lost!
- Take this blow!
- Get down!
Now it's my turn to play! Come on!
You still dare to laugh?!
"Cold ice that takes lives!"
Poisonous bees?!
You witch! You cultists!
Call off the poisonous bees!
I, Jo Lang Sim,
will definitely kill all Miao people!
Jo Lang Sim, on behalf of our venerable
Elder Kuk, I'm sending you to hell!
Your Eminence.
Official Au Yeung has arrived,
accompanied by
the Hua Mountain people.
Tell the imperial soldiers
outside to hide immediately!
Have all imperial guards
change into servants' clothing.
- Yes!
- Hurry up!
- Cheung Biu! Li Yee!
- Present!
Find me civilian clothes!
- Yes!
- Hurry!
- Uncle!
- Uncle?!
It's been four or five years!
I appreciate you coming
to arrange the funeral of my father.
Ngok Bat Kwan
from Hua Mountain Sect,
insisted on coming with me
to meet you.
He says he has urgent matters
to discuss with you, sir.
Why haven't you set up
a mourning hall? How strange!
We of the Lam family want
to keep a low profile.
We're afraid that if our enemies find out,
they'll come to exterminate us.
That's why we haven't set up a mourning
hall, but we mourn in our hearts.
Then you're really under duress.
Let us all pray to
Brother Jan Nam in heaven.
We'll all knee! and swear an oath.
To the heavens above.
We swear to revenge the Lam family's
loss by shedding their enemies' blood.
We must tear their enemies to pieces,
so their corpses remain unburied.
Brother Jan Nam,
you who art in heaven,
bless us so that we may find
your murderers and revenge you.
Bow to the heavens three times.
First bow.
Another bow.
Third bow.
We will bow three times in the direction of
Brother Jan Nam's bedchamber.
First bow.
Another bow.
Third bow.
Doesn't Lam family tradition include
bowing to the guests in gratitude?
Family... bow to them in thanks.
First bow.
Another bow.
Third bow.
Your Eminence!
What games are you up to?
This wily old fox wants to arrange
a marriage between his daughter and I.
Even I ran out of ideas!
Then what about Ling Wu Chung?
I eliminated him with a poisoned wine.
What about the whereabouts of
the Prized Sunflower Volume?
I still haven't found out where it is.
The treasure
is under the water wheel.
Damned thief!
Where do you think you're going?
Take this blow!
There's a thief! There's a thief!
Still trying to get away?!
Take this!
Don't try to escape!
The sword energy?
Are you from the Hua Mountain Sect?
"Lower-the-sword manoeuvre."
PRIZED SUNFLOWER
VOLUME
What kind of manoeuvre is that?
Sifu?
Ling Wu Chung,
Hua Mountain Sect's survival
depends on this. You have not seen me.
Where did it go?
PRIZED SUNFLOWER
VOLUME
- Thief? Where's the thief?
- Where's the thief? Where's the thief?
Elder Brother!
Careful! There are many
imperial soldiers outside.
Some may be impersonating
Lam family members.
Everyone, be on alert!
- Who is it?
- Sifu, it's Luk Dai Yau.
- There's something going on downstairs.
- Come in and swear an oath.
Take this scroll
and prepare to leave at once.
This mission
affects the fate of Hua Mountain.
If you have to sacrifice yourself,
do not reveal this secret.
Yes, sifu!
Skinny Boy!
I hope you've been okay.
What are you doing?
What is it?
This is the Prized Sunflower Volume.
Hide it and don't tell anyone.
Why are you mad?
What, you nincompoop!
Nincompoop?
You said whoever didn't show up at
the forest would be a nincompoop!
Didn't he say he'd poisoned
Ling Wu Chung to death?
Arrest him!
Lam Ping Ji! You're mistaken! I'm not
the thief! It was I who called out "thief!"
You'll see the Lam family
treasure is still there.
Stop bullshitting! I know you're
involved with the Sun Moon Sect.
You're the main culprit
who murdered our family!
Didn't you just mention some treasure
of our Lam family?
What do you mean?
- Arrest him!
- Yes!
He's the last descendant of the Lam family.
Why do you want to arrest him?
He's the last descendant
of the Lam family?
There are a lot of people in the Lam family
before him. He'd have to wait his turn.
Do you know where the Lam family
treasure is hidden?
I promised his father I could only tell him.
After doing that, I've forgotten it all.
If you want to know,
ask him yourself.
Uncle, don't let him divide us!
Have mercy!
Uncle, your rules are strict.
We as outsiders don't want to get involved.
Why don't you teach him
a good lesson?
A river doesn't
interfere with a well, right?
Let's help sifu pack
and leave for Hua Mountain.
We take our leave.
Allow me to return this.
- No need to see us off.
- Ling Wu Chung!
Did you yell out
there was a thief?
Yes, uncle.
Then why didn't you grab him?
I wasn't a good enough
martial artist, uncle.
If you, a senior pupil of the Hua Mountain
Sect, weren't a match for him,
who's better at martial arts,
except for your sifu?!
What nonsense!
How dare you! Rubbish!
Why are you all kneeling?
What are you up to?
Inner chi is like bubbling,
flowing water.
Inner peace
is like an immobile mountain.
We sit and meditate
to gather our chi.
So much shouting,
yet Grand Master Ngok,
you're a skilled martial artist,
you should have heard the commotion.
Why were you so late in reacting?
Uncle, why would there be a thief?
Don't listen to Ling Wu Chung's chatter.
He's very fond of lying and deceit,
causing confusion all over the place.
Ling Wu Chung! You've broken
the rules of Hua Mountain Sect.
I'm expelling you immediately!
Leave now!
- Father!
- Sifu! Sifu!
Stop!
No-one here tonight may leave!
Each country has its laws,
each family its rules.
This is a matter for Hua Mountain Sect,
and not the Lam family.
You want to talk about laws of a country?
Fine, then I'll discuss law with you!
- Cheung Biu! Li Yee!
- Present!
Put on your uniforms
and prepare for a formal edict!
- Understood!
Traitor!
The Grand Master of Hua Mountain Sect,
Ngok Bat Kwan!
Knee! to receive an imperial edict!
Ngok Bat Kwan
accepts the imperial edict!
The imperial court needs able men.
I appoint you as my personal security
official, to assist with my activities.
From now on, you will obey my wishes
and carry out my actions.
I, Ngok Bat Kwan, am a country peasant.
I'm afraid I won't be up to the task.
Nonsense!
If you won't accept, it means you're
discontented with the Imperial Court.
That means you want to rebel.
Is your inner chi like
bubbling, flowing water,
or is your inner peace
like an immobile mountain?
I know in my heart
who's loyal and who's not.
Official Ngok,
from now on, you're my man.
If you don't do as I say,
then you're being disloyal.
The punishment is to have
your head chopped off!
We, in the Imperial Court,
have our rules.
You must kowtow to me 1000 times.
Commence to kowtow!
Ngok Bat Kwan!
Commence your 1000 kowtows!
- Kowtow!
- Kowtow! Kowtow!
One.
Two.
Three.
FouL
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Reporting! We caught a beggar who's
actually a Hua Mountain Sect student.
It's Luk Dai Yau?
Your Eminence.
Official Ngok, let me see
how you handle this matter.
Traitor!
Stealing from the Lam family
means stealing from the Imperial Court.
I'm going to destroy
your ability to do martial arts.
Bring me a sword!
Move!
This book doesn't belong to
the Imperial Court.
It's a music score
given to me by an elder.
It's called The Laughing Proud
World of Martial Arts.
If you don't believe me, I can play it
according to the music score.
If you're interested,
you can sing along with me.
The blue seas laugh
Surging against both shores
We are carried by the waves
We are only concerned
with the here and now
The azure skies laugh
At the disorder in the world
Only the heavens know
Who will win
and who will lose
The rivers and mountains laugh
The clouds and rain are far away
After the billowing waves are spent
- How beautiful the...
- Stop singing!
Ling Wu Chung! Luk Dai Yau!
You're working with the Sun Moon Sect
and have betrayed us.
According to Hua Mountain Sect rules,
your martial arts must be destroyed.
You have to be expelled to appease
our Hua Mountain ancestors!
Execute the rules of our Sect!
My brothers, take action!
Sacrificing myself
for the Hua Mountain Sect,
I, Luk Dai Yau,
will receive glory in death!
Don't sacrifice yourself for nothing!
Sit down!
Is this a mutiny? Do you want me
to destroy all your martial arts?
- "Hua Mountain Sword Trap", en garde!
- Yes!
Elder brother, be careful!
Brother, be careful!
You be careful too!
"Seven swords joining together!"
Is everyone all right?
Kill him!
- Kill him!
Here we come!
Let's go!
Our sister is down there!
Dai Yau, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Father!
- Sifu!
Destroy all our martial arts abilities
and let them go!
You make me lose face
in front of outsiders!
There are so many other Hua Mountain
Sect students. I shall destroy all of you!
Father! Please let them go!
I have my brother's stuff!
Grab our sister!
Oops! I lost my hold on her!
You're...
Don't worry. We came to
check on your brother's health.
You dare disobey me! Die!
Die!
You can't die!
Dai Yau, it's dangerous!
Come over here!
Save your lives!
Protect the Hua Mountain!
Hide behind me!
Father!
A two-headed snake!
Ngok Bat Kwan! You hypocrite!
You're just like this snake!
You're double-faced!
You're my official,
yet you work against me?
You mandarins, you're always
considered to be in the right!
Think whatever you like!
Your sifu won't let you go free.
He's already sold out
all your brothers!
If you want to live,
you have to fight your way out!
Brothers, protect our sister,
and leave here first!
Hurry up!
Give up the Prized Sunflower Volume!
I'm such a powerful mandarin!
How do you expect to fight me?
I'm taking the scroll
to see the Emperor!
"Two columns supporting the sky!"
Quickly untie me!
Hurry up!
Untie me!
THE PRIZED SUNFLOWER VOLUME
Who are you people?
Why are you fighting against me?
You don't know?
We are of the Sun Moon Sect!
Skinny Boy! Go up there!
You ignorant youngsters!
You overestimate your own abilities!
If you manage to
get away from me today,
I'll let you write my name,
Gu Gam Fok, backwards!
Fine.
I'll write it backwards for you!
Elder Brother!
Why are you still here?
Get away now!
Old eunuch!
How do you read
your name backwards?
Ifl don't kill you old eunuch, then I'll write
my name, Blue Phoenix, backwards!
The Prized Sunflower Scroll?
It's all right! It's all right!
So much bloodshed, yet the Prized
Sunflower Volume hasn't been sullied.
My position in the Imperial Court
is secure now!
- Don't move!
- Lam Ping Ji!
I'm not Lam Ping Ji!
I'm Au Yeung Chun.
Your Eminence! Kill them all!
Ling Wu Chung,
when you were singing that song,
you laughed at everything
under the sky.
Do you really think that everyone
has a right to laugh?
There are some things which
can't be laughed at.
If you laugh at the wrong thing,
you could lose your head!
So that's why I am eligible
to have the last laugh!
Remember.
Once under my command, if you're
disloyal, there's no second chance.
I will have your head chopped off!
The Prized Sunflower Volume?!
The person most worthy
of being laughed at is himself.
Are we going back
to the Hua Mountain?
Are we still allowed to go back?
We may end up as nomads
like the Miao people.
Elder Brother...
I found your scroll amongst the rubble.
I'm returning it to you now.
The Prized Sunflower Volume!
No, it's "The Laughing Proud
World of Martial Arts," you idiot!
You dare work against me!
Prepare to die!
A student fighting his teacher!
Despicable!
I am no longer part of
the Hua Mountain Sect. I'll fight you!
- I want to ask you a question!
- Keep quiet!
Who's Fung Ching Yeung?
Fung Ching Yeung is my great uncle
within my Hua Mountain Sect.
You shameless youngster,
on what basis do you dare to ask me about
matters concerning Hua Mountain Sect?
On what basis? We're sworn brothers.
That means I'm your step great uncle!
How dare you!
You dare discuss rank with me?
You're wrong to have
betrayed so many people!
Hua Mountain Sect cannot be
sacrificed for you!
You traitor!
I'll kill you as a warning to others!
You don't even have
a third of my sword chi!
If you have the ability to penetrate
10 feet of my sword chi, then fight me!
"Wave-like sword manoeuvre!"
Throw! Throw! Throw! Throw! Throw!
- What kind of swordplay is this?
- "The Nine Solitary Swordplays!"
Father!
Let him go!
You've already severed
the meridian points on his wrist.
Hua Mountain
doesn't belong to him.
He sacrificed so many innocent lives
to gain power, he's the real traitor.
The blue seas laugh
Surging against both shores
We are carried by the waves
We are only concerned with
the here and now
The azure skies laugh
At the disorder in the world
Only the heavens know
Who will win
and who will lose
The rivers and mountains laugh
The clouds and rain are far away
After the billowing waves are spent
THE LAUGHING PROUD WORLD
OF MARTIAL ARTS
The clear breezes laugh
And they provoke feelings of solitude
Noble sentiments leave us melancholic
like a stretch of moonlit nights
The green earth laughs
Solitude is no more
Noble sentiments still make
us laugh like we don't care