"Temple of the Goddess"
The King rules heaven
The devil rules hell
Between the two there is White Lotus
Keeping our country safe
White Lotus is divine!
Power to the people!
Welcome Priest Gao Kung
from the South Heaven Gate.
Green Dragon on the left.
White Tiger on the right.
On September the first, 1895,
I became a disciple
of the White Lotus Goddess.
I speak these words
before the heavens
to show my powers
and spread my word to the people.
Mystical powers protect me!
Impervious to water and fire!
Goddess, lend me your powers!
Welcome spiritual master, Gao Kung.
Goddess, make me as strong as iron -
fearless before blade or sword.
Stabbing and slicing have no effect.
I'm fearless before cannons
or gunshot!
49 levels of transformation!
Holy Army under my command!
My bones are like pillars
supporting the sky!
The fierce flames
are like dust to me!
Unlimited mystical powers
at my disposal!
The White Lotus Sect...
eradicates evil!
A thousand knives are deflected!
A million blades are deflected!
Regiment Commanders!
Mystical power protect me!
Cannon fire is as flying sand to me!
Bullets are mere raindrops!
White Lotus is divine!
Power to the people!
Bring out the objects of evil.
What's this animal? It's so ugly!
It's a Western dog, Master!
It has spots, so it is evil, kill it!
White Lotus is divine!
Power to the people!
Kill all foreigners
so we can live in peace!
"Protectyour homes
for the sake of your country!"
Starring: Jet Li, Rosamund Kwan,
Max Mok Siu-chung, Donnie Yen
Also starring: David Chiang, Xiong
Xinxin, Yam Sai-kwoon, William Ho
Screenplay: Lee Wei-mun
Created by: Chow Gin-mun
Script Writers: Tsui Hark,
Chan Tin-suen, Charcoal Cheung Tan
Action Director: Yuen Woo-ping
Wardrobe: Chao Kok-pui
Art Director: Eddie Ma Poon-chiu
Cinematographer: Arthur Wong Ngok-tai
Edited by: Muk Chi-sin
Sung by: Jackie Chan
Steady, Master.
'He doesn't spill a drop
to either side.'
'Good footwork.'
Aunt Yee, the train is rocking
so much, how will we eat?
You're not used to it.
Look, the foreigners are coping fine.
Come and sit here.
Now it's much better,
this journey used to take all day.
The trees look like they're flying.
- I feel ill.
- What's wrong, Foon? So much talk!
Nothing...
My stomach is churning.
You're trainsick!
Don't eat or you'll throw up.
But I must! There's Western food
to eat, right, Master?
Excuse me, waiter,
we haven't ordered yet.
You don't need to order your food
on the train.
- Miss, the soup.
- Thank you.
It's all been prepared.
You mean it's not fresh?
- Solar eclipse?
- Don't be so scared, idiot!
Aunt Yee, what's going on?
We're in a tunnel.
A tunnel? The train is strong enough
to go through a mountain?
Amazing!
Idiot!
Foon, we're all together now, but
don't run off when we get to town.
OK.
There will be a lot of foreigners
at the medical convention.
Don't embarrass us.
I understand, Master.
'So many hands!'
Fei-hung, eat the soup
while it's hot.
Foon, eat the soup
I don't know which hand is mine.
'I can do it that way.'
- Have you finished your soup, sir?
- I'll finish it later.
Only meat? Where's the rice?
Miss, have you finished your soup?
I don't want it.
Thank you.
Fei-hung, it's a steak,
use your knife and fork.
I've seen this before.
You're always doing this.
What a waste! Don't throw it away.
Waste not, want not.
Watch me.
- Are you OK?
- I'll clean your face.
Yes, I'm fine. Here's your steak.
Master, don't throw it away!
It's all your fault.
Forget it, let's eat.
Why are you so quiet?
No reason. Why are you so quiet?
Oh, no. I can't hold it any more!
I told you not to eat.
Hold on, we'll be in Canton soon.
- Really?
- Yes.
Riding on a train
is quite a challenge.
Waiter, can you pack this?
- What did you say?
- I just don't want to waste it.
Chicken buns!
Give me a pot of tea.
- Old man, you owe me money. Pay up!
- If I can't play, I can't pay.
Look, a crowd. What's on the banners?
- Support the scholar's proposal!
- We object to the cession of Taiwan!
Where is Taiwan?
We lost the war and gave it to Japan.
Taiwan must be near the sea...
or it wouldn't be called Tai-island.
I don't even know how big it is.
We can't even manage Canton,
forget it.
- Let's drink.
- Yes, let's drink.
Eat, we'll talk later.
We object to Li Hung-chang's
concession to Japan!
- We object to the cession of Taiwan!
Look at the clothes on that woman!
- Where?
- Over there.
The one in the rickshaw.
Come and have a look.
She's wearing Western clothes.
Sister?
Let's do the lottery.
Nine is my lucky number.
No, I don't want to.
Support the scholar's proposal!
We object to the treaty
of Shimonoseki!
We object to Li Hung-chang's
concession to Japan!
We object to the cession of Taiwan!
Support the scholar's proposal!
Money first, look after your tickets.
Get your ticket and move on.
The lottery!
Roast pork buns!
We're here, sir.
- Ten cents, please.
- Thank you.
Let's eat. Pulling this rickshaw
will be the death of me.
That's a pretty dress.
Can I take a picture?
You're not a foreigner. Get her!
Get her! Get her!
- Come with me.
- Go away, you pesky kids!
Throwing things at people!
No manners!
- Foon!
- Get lost...
Don't hit the children.
I'm bleeding!
Sister!
- Look, you've made trouble again.
- Master...
Let's go, we'll tell Uncle Gao.
Those kids are so naughty, throwing
things at people. Look at the mess.
Attention, please.
White Lotus are meeting
at Telegraph House. We should all go.
Don't leave! Don't forget to pay!
Master Wong,
I'm going to have a look.
Aunt Yee... Aunt Yee!
Foon! Foon!
Hurry! They're about to start!
Come on, hurry up!
In the name of the people's army
stand down!
Damned soldiers,
working for foreigners! Stone them!
Get out of the way.
Move!
Wind and fire come together to kill
the foreigners in one fell swoop!
White Lotus has come to save you
by driving evil away!
- Burn down Telegraph House!
Excuse me, please.
- Aunt, let's take the photo here.
- Help me set up the tripod.
Over there.
Wind and fire come together...
It's starting now.
- I can't see. I can't take pictures.
- Get on my shoulders.
Get on your shoulders?
OK, keep still.
White Lotus is divine!
Power to the people!
Protect your home
for the sake of the country!
Kill all foreigners
so we can live in peace!
Foon, this position is no good.
So good.
White Lotus has come to save you
by driving evil away!
What was that?
Thank you.
She can make lightning, run away!
Arrest that evil spirit!
The top one or the bottom one?
The foreigner on top.
Arrest her!
Calm down! She is Chinese,
she's not a foreigner! Have a look.
Look at the way you dress.
It proves you're evil. Arrest her!
Stay calm! Don't!
Aunt Yee, run! I'll protect you!
My camera!
Aunt Yee!
Aunt Yee! Where are you, Aunt Yee?
Foon! Help me, Foon!
Kill all foreigners
so we can live in peace.
Take her to the temple,
burn her to death!
Fei-hung!
Who the hell are you to stop me?
Tell me your name!
I'm Wong Fei-hung from Fushan.
- Fei-hung?!
- And Leung Foon too!
I hear his kung fu is deadly.
Kick you, kick you... to death!
Leave him alone, pick on
someone else. You'll hurt him.
- Who else? Where?
- Hit them, don't hurt them.
That's enough.
Ten-finger punch!
Thank you, thank you.
Master.
- Are you all right, Aunt Yee?
- You came just in time.
What is it? It smells sweet.
It's sleeping powder.
Foon! Take care of Aunt Yee.
Aunt Yee, Aunt Yee.
Mystical power...
All this trickery and mumbo jumbo and
you claim to be acting in God's name!
Aunt Yee, wake up! Aunt Yee!
Aunt Yee! Help her up.
Foon, take Aunt Yee back to the inn.
Foon, what are you waiting for?
He's one of Canton's Ten Tigers.
His kung fu is legendary.
Get back!
Master Wong, don't!
That thing is evil!
Stand back!
Master Wong, can I be
your apprentice?
Back! Don't follow me!
- Fei-hung.
- You're awake.
They covered you in sleeping powder.
- Did you carry me back here?
- No, Foon did.
Why did he carry me back?
Foon is preparing your medicine.
Take it and rest for two days
and you'll be fine.
- Master Wong.
- Come in.
Don't go out alone,
this town is in turmoil.
Rest a while, don't worry.
Fei-hung, I'm all right.
I can still be your interpreter
at the convention tomorrow.
Let's talk about that later.
Take your medicine now.
- Master Wong, sorry to disturb you.
- It's OK.
Oh, you're awake. Did you know...
You carried me back.
Yes, I did.
The medicine is very hot, be careful.
Mr Mak, what can I do for you?
I sent my servant
to buy these clothes.
Please ask her to wear them.
- That's very kind of you.
- Don't mention it.
Mystical kung fu is very popular now.
Foreigners make them mad.
Master Wong, I've known you for
a long time, I'll be frank with you.
If Miss wears her own clothes,
she'll definitely get into trouble.
I understand. How much were they?
- There'll be no charge.
- Thank you.
Thanks for your help, Master Wong.
'lf I'd known it'd be so boring,
I'd have asked So to come.'
'There's another one!'
'lt's not any of them.
Another foreigner.'
- Dr Wong, it's your turn.
- Foon, it's our turn.
- I'll let you out.
- We'll go together.
Thank you. Thank you.
My topic of discussion
for today is Chinese acupuncture.
Louder.
There are 360 pressure points...
Do you want him to speak louder?
That's not what he means.
Dr Wong, may I interpret for you?
- May I know your name?
- My name is Sun Yat-sen.
- Mr Sun, I'm most grateful to you.
- Don't mention it.
Thank you.
The five elements are gold,
wood, water, fire and earth.
They form a network.
Acupuncture regulates
the nervous system.
Dr Wong, Dr Thompson
doesn't quite understand.
His demonstration shows the Western
understanding of the nervous system.
That's quite simple -
I can use needles to close two nerves
so that he can't move his leg.
Master, are you going to stick
those in me?
Dr Sun, ask them
to test his reflexes now.
Join White Lotus
and save your country!
Foreigners out, leave us in peace!
Master!
The White Lotus Sect again!
Master! I can't move!
I'll be shot! I'm a goner!
Master, I've only been stabbed
by you, not them.
- Mr Sun, your bag.
- Leave it.
We're finished here.
Back to the Temple!
- Are you OK?
- I'm fine.
Mr Sun, here's your bag.
If we get the opportunity,
let's exchange ideas, shall we?
China needs more men like you.
You flatter me.
See you soon.
The White Lotus Sect is
always making trouble.
Master, Aunt Yee must still be
at the inn.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
The White Lotus Sect?
Come out!
Fei-hung!
Master, what's the matter?
Nothing, come on, out.
Master, you look pale,
something must have happened.
It's just a woman changing.
Mind your own business!
But you saw it.
- What a terrible noise!
- Tell him to stop.
Here!
Thank you, thank you...
Sir.
Telegraph House is our only contact
with the outside world. Protect it.
Yes, sir.
Sir.
There are a lot of bystanders,
take care not to hit them.
Drive the White Lotus
towards the gate.
Yes, sir.
Sir, if this continues,
we will be outnumbered.
Master!
Dinner time!
I got a nice treat
to help Aunt Yee get well.
- Is it game?
- Yes, it is.
What is it?
Foon, haven't you told Aunt Yee
what this is?
Don't you know?
Aunt Yee, do you like dogs?
They're man's best friend.
I like them more than cats, anyway.
- What's the matter?
- Nothing. Let's eat.
People like dogs in different ways.
They went that way.
Canton is in chaos.
Foon, pack our things after dinner.
We'll go to the station
early tomorrow.
- Take Aunt Yee back to Fushan.
- OK.
You'd better eat well tonight, you
don't want to be sick on the train.
Come outside when you've finished
the dog meat, I'd like a word.
You'd like a word with me?
What did you say? This is dog meat?
- Is it really?
- Yes.
Yes, Master loves dogs.
- Aunt Yee.
- Yes.
- I want to teach you kung fu.
- Me? Why?
These are troubled times.
You could use it for self-defence.
The basic technique has 36 stances.
The advanced has 72 stances.
- There are 108 pressure points...
- Fei-hung...
Do I need to remember all this?
No, just listen
and try to get the basics.
Remember, for punches,
attack from the side.
For kicks, come from below.
What if someone has a knife?
I'll teach you that another time.
Look, this is the single,
this is the double.
- Such effort! Why don't I use a gun?
- Shut up!
I was a bit rude.
That's how I speak to my students.
I'm fine, let's continue.
OK.
The first move.
Go for my head.
Pay attention.
Grab the hand,
crouch down, then twist.
Grab the hand, crouch down...
- then twist.
- Then twist.
Let's try again.
Grab the hand,
crouch down, then twist.
The second move, throat lock.
Come on, attack my throat, harder.
Grab the hand, crouch down, elbow up.
Aunt Yee?
Be careful!
Why aren't you concentrating?
I was practising in my head.
Try it once more.
The first move, grab the head.
What's next?
Then punch!
Are you OK?
I'm OK, it's better to be your friend
than your enemy.
Sir, we've received a telegram
from Hong Kong.
We've no time for that now.
It says someone's planning
a rebellion here.
Here's the message.
Sir, it's another telegram
from Hong Kong.
This is serious,
guard Telegraph House well.
- I'll inform the Governor.
- Yes, sir.
Your Excellency.
The British consul invited me here,
can't this wait?
Our spies in Hong Kong
cabled us twice today.
The Chiu Chow Society are planning
to smuggle weapons to Canton.
- They want to start a revolution.
- A revolution?
- Is it the White Lotus Sect?
- No.
Their leader is called Sun Yat-sen.
Sun Yat-sen?
Officer, who is this Sun Yat-sen?
He's the one who started
the Agricultural Society.
He's a doctor,
he's always giving speeches
and criticising the Government.
He encourages democracy too.
He says China should be a republic.
How can a doctor rebel?
Do we not have enough men?
White Lotus has been causing trouble
recently, so we're under-manned.
The Government is having trouble
with the French in the north.
I think there'll be war soon.
It won't be easy
to get reinforcements.
The British are our allies,
they'll help keep the other
foreigners at bay.
Put the army and navy on alert
and extra men at ports and stations
till we find Sun Yat-sen.
- What was that society?
- The Agricultural Society.
Who else is involved with
Sun Yat-sen?
Someone called Luke Ho-dung
is the money man.
Sir, should we bring him in
for questioning?
- Yes, let's bring him in.
- Yes, sir.
- Sir?
- I'm not going.
Sir.
Chow, tell Snake to get up,
it's not his day off!
Did you spend all night
at the brothel? Get up!
Be careful, Aunt Yee. Take it easy.
Foon, what are you doing?
She twisted her ankle.
How come? I only showed you
hand movements. What happened?
I don't know,
it was just hurting when I got up.
Foon insisted on carrying me
when he found out.
Foon...
I don't mind, Master.
Well, let me carry her,
you take the luggage.
OK.
It hurts.
I always do the carrying.
Now you want to get involved.
Waiter!
May I help you?
We'd like to check out.
- Leave me alone!
- Get up.
You're too much!
- Mr Mak.
- Master Wong?
- We are leaving now.
- Oh, thank God!
No, no, I mean have a safe journey.
Sorry for the trouble.
If you're ever...
Fei-hung, look, what's going on?
Hey, what's going on?
The White Lotus have burned down
Friendship Hall.
What's Friendship Hall?
It's where they teach foreign
languages. It's full of students.
- Mr Mak, where's the school?
- Near the fruit market.
Don't go there!
- Aunt Yee!
- Master, where's she going?
Foon, you lied to me, she's OK.
It was her idea, Master.
Wait for me.
"Friendship Hall"
Is this it?
Master! Wait for me!
- What is it?
- Skin.
It's human skin.
Master.
It's the younger students.
It's lucky they were hiding.
What's happening?
Let's go and have a look.
What's going on in there?
They've gone now.
Don't worry. Be good.
Are you hungry? Eat something.
It's so gloomy in here.
Mr Mak is here!
Master Wong!
Why are you still here?
Are these children with you?
They're students.
We just needed a rest.
They can't stay here!
If White Lotus comes, I'm finished!
I don't know them, even worse,
they study foreign languages.
Take them to the courthouse.
Can't we rest for a moment?
I don't know how to fight.
This inn is all I have.
If it's burnt down, I'll...
- Mr Mak!
Have you got some salts?
You've made him faint.
Who do you think you are?
If he dies, I'll call the police.
Then I'll back off.
Foon, Aunt Yee, let's go.
Let's send them home.
Where do you live?
I'm from Kwangsi Province.
I'm also from Kwangsi.
I'm from Fukien Province.
He's from Chuijao,
they're from Kwangsi.
I guess the rest
are not from here either.
Do any of you live here?
Miss, I live by the north gate,
so does he.
I live in Sha Min.
I think I live near the east gate.
I live in Shu Zhao!
Anybody else?
I came here on the train,
I don't know where I come from.
We'll take these two home.
The rest come with us.
I'll carry you.
Foon! Order some chicken rice
for our journey.
Waiter, 20 portions of chicken rice!
Come on, you, too.
Sir...
what can I do for you?
I'd like to know if the children from
Friendship Hall came here earlier?
Students? No, no, you've come
to the wrong place.
Have any of you seen the students?
There are no students here, you fool!
Maybe the boogie man's got them.
The King rules heaven
The devil rules hell...
It's lucky the students are gone.
Between the two there is White Lotus
Keeping our country safe
- Lucky tokens!
- I want one.
The hanging lantern
will keep you safe.
Lucky tokens
will protect your family!
- Light the lanterns.
- Here's the offering.
Lucky tokens
will protect your family!
- This will keep you safe.
- Of course, of course.
Give more offerings
to ensure your safety.
Finish up in there. We have to leave.
- I'm scared.
- Be quiet.
- What happened to your hands?
- It's not my blood, it's his.
It's everywhere.
He's badly injured.
We can't stay here.
I'll go to the courthouse to see
if they'll take them. Stay here.
- Foon.
- Yes.
- Help me bandage the poor kid.
- I haven't finished yet.
Don't be naughty. Come back here.
I just wanted to know
where he was going.
Foon, you stink.
- You peed on me!
- I told you I wasn't done yet.
"Only the truly brave reach the top"
Sir, Wong Fei-hung
is here to see you.
Master Wong, come in.
Sir!
Sir.
Master Wong, now I see why
you're so famous.
- Sorry, sorry.
- It was nothing, sir.
I just wanted to spar
with you a little.
Master Wong, your Shaolin
staff is excellent.
Maybe you can teach me
some other time.
Have some wine.
Thank you.
His Shaolin staff isn't that good.
He hit that pole, but it didn't
even move. Wong is full of himself.
All our troops are busy
protecting foreigners.
It may not be that safe here either.
If the students come here,
the White Lotus will come
to cause trouble.
Sir...
I know it's my job
to protect the people.
The trouble is
even though I can fight,
I don't have the men to support me.
I'm deeply ashamed.
Foon, come over here.
Stay out of the way.
He is still bleeding.
Master isn't back yet.
What shall we do?
- He's not moving.
- Why isn't he moving?
- It's Mozart.
- What do you mean?
Listen. Can't you hear
the foreign music?
There must be
a foreign consulate nearby.
A consulate?
Beware of fire!
Beware of thieves!
Aunt Yee, Foon!
- I need to pee.
- Wait until you're home.
It's bad for my kidneys.
So? They're rotten anyway.
Don't move!
Stay there!
Where has the sect taken
the woman and children?
We aren't with White Lotus.
My children are in bed now.
My woman has run off...
Foon, where did you go?
Aunt Yee took the children
to a safe place.
Really?
Why are you holding
a White Lotus lantern?
To bring us good luck.
But it doesn't seem to have worked.
- May I go now?
- Yes!
Come on, hurry.
Foon, let's go.
Don't you remember me?
I came with the children...
and a beautiful lady.
I only left to find my master.
I don't understand you.
Foon, did Aunt Yee bring
the children here?
Yes, he let us in before,
but now he won't.
Aunt Yee! Aunt Yee!
I've come with Master!
- Did he ask us to stand up straight?
- That's what I heard.
Aunt Yee, we are waiting
at the entrance.
Master, they're opening the gate.
- How dare you!
- Foon, stay calm.
Don't hit me!
- Tell them why we're here.
- I have!
- Put your guns down.
- They don't understand.
- Stop pointing that at me!
- Stop!
Pardon me.
My name is Luke Ho-dung, and yours?
I'm Wong Fei-hung from Fushan.
Wong Fei-hung?
You saved the children!
Yes, they're all inside,
but the soldiers won't let us in.
Allow me.
I don't understand...
Why do foreigners believe in a god
whose face has so much suffering?
Everyone has a god in their heart.
When we're young
we believe in one god,
when we're older
we believe in another.
Finally we realise all beliefs
are just lies.
Why are you always looking at your
watch? Are you expecting someone?
A bad habit I picked up
from a friend.
He says time is valuable.
We Chinese waste a lot of time.
I still can't read foreign numbers!
I'll never keep good time.
Stay where you are.
Don't be afraid.
Foon, take them upstairs.
They're foreign merchants
and their families.
They've been attacked by White Lotus
and have come to seek refuge.
They need a doctor.
Master is the one they need. Master!
They're looking for a doctor.
They don't want Chinese doctors.
Mr Sun.
Mr Wong.
This is...
No need to introduce me. He's the one
who's always looking at his watch.
White Lotus will free the poor!
Kill the foreigners
so we can live in peace!
Burn the foreigners' belongings!
Aunt Yee.
Burn it down!
White Lotus will free the poor!
Kill the foreigners
so we can live in peace!
White Lotus are making trouble again.
Mr Luke.
Which one tells the right time?
Your watch is fast, Sun.
Mine can't keep up with yours.
Enough of this,
let's check the injured.
Foon, I never thought
time was so important.
I didn't think you'd understand.
Burn the foreign devils!
Chase them out!
Aunt Yee.
Oh, no, they must have
taken her soul!
If they're so clever,
they would have won by now.
They're just trying to scare us.
Don't worry, just relax.
What if she vomits?
We're not on the train now.
Mr Luke.