- Ola.
Wait. I want to talk to you.
Come with me!
What are you doing? What do you want?
Can you listen to me?
I'm not after you for my wallet.
I just wanted to
take you to see someone.
I think this meeting
will be beneficial to you.
Will you come?
Help!
Why do you cry for help?
I mean you no harm.
I'm actually a private investigator.
My job will be done if you'd only
go see this man with me.
Can you do me just this one small favor?
Please trust me and don't cry for help.
Then I'll let you go. Okay?
I practically grew up on the streets.
You think I'm that easily conned?
Don't waste your time.
- Where?
- Over there.
Miss.
Don't come near me! I mean it!
Thank you.
Don't say I didn't warn you!
Sylvia is delivering an order
to a very dangerous place.
You'll live to regret it
if you don't believe me.
Let me borrow your bench.
- Where?
- Over there.
What do we do now?
Just pack up and go rescue her.
Don't run!
- Let me go!
- Let her go!
Don't come any closer!
Come on.
Get in, quick!
Use the cars!
That's my car! That's my car!
Faster! They're right behind us!
I can't take this anymore.
- Then sit on my lap.
- You wish!
Go sit in the back! Go!
Back up! Back up!
Driving like a maniac!
Good thing mine is a race car.
Otherwise I'd be in big trouble.
Drive more carefully next time!
It's a dead end!
Let's do it!
Sit tight!
You were great!
They're not following us anymore!
I know that! But they're in front of us!
We'll see if you have the guts
to hit me head on!
Excuse me.
Let's try out my newest weapon.
Ready, aim, shoot!
I'll give it a shot too!
Ready for some olive oil?
Try this on for size!
Let's make it a little more interesting.
How's it going out there?
The enemy has been defeated!
So many of you and the girl
still managed to get away.
The only explanation is that
you are incompetent!
Morons, what use are you to me?
You've wasted six days.
Now I only have eight days left.
God made the world in six days.
Eight days is more than enough
to get a girl...
Then whether I can become the Count's
successor is all up to you.
Who do you think...
You first.
Who do you think those people were?
Now its your turn.
You've already said it!
This was not the first time
they tried to kidnap me.
That's right.
Moby?
Why didn't you say something? If I had
a gun, you would have been dead!
You don't think I would duck?
Those people will
keep coming after Sylvia
until they have her.
- Who are those people?
- Bad guys.
How do you know?
Because I'm a good guy.
Please tell me what this is all about.
Actually, it was quite simple.
Although it is now getting complicated.
There are 2 groups of people. The first
group consists of those we've just met.
The second group consists of
only one person me.
I'm officially looking for Sylvia.
Those guys want to kidnap her
by any illegal means.
My reason for wanting Sylvia is
I need to deliver her to my client.
About those other guys? I don't know.
I'm even more confused than before.
It's like you've said nothing.
You should know why your client
is looking for me.
You're right. I should.
However, my client did not wish
to tell me his reasons.
As such, what I should know...
I don't know.
So Moby, Private Eye.
Can you tell us one thing
that you do know?
I can tell you two things.
First, it's very dangerous here.
Why? Do you smell gas?
You don't believe me.
There's nothing I can do.
Second, if Sylvia wants to find out
what this is about,
then she should come with me
to see my client.
- I know one thing too.
- What?
I have a dimwitted
private investigator in my apartment.
You don't have to believe me,
but you can't insult me.
It's not that
we don't want to believe you.
Please tell us. How long have you been
a private investigator?
Six days.
That's not even a full week yet.
We'd be insulting our
IQ if we believe you.
Just forget it.
You've not only insulted me,
you've hurt my feelings.
Moby, you hold down the fort.
We'll take off!
Let's go from the balcony.
Moby, we're going!
Moby, hang in there!
Four Eyes, you go down first.
Come on!
Moby, come on!
Hurry!
Go!
Why are we running?
They want to kidnap Sylvia!
So they do!
And there's nothing we can do?
Can't we fight back?
They have five or six guys.
David and I are used to fighting
more than 10 guys.
Including spectators?
Let Four Eyes and I demonstrate for you.
You stay with Sylvia.
- They're tough!
- They're more than tough!
Then what are we waiting for?
Come on.
Where the heck is this?
This is the headquarters of filth.
This is a dead end. Turn back!
What do we do now?
Find a place to hide first.
- Who has a flashlight?
- I do.
Turn it off and save your batteries.
Look at each one carefully.
This place stinks.
I know. Be patient.
Hey, I don't see them over here.
I know I saw them coming in here.
Let's look again.
Oh... What a relief!
I can't stand it anymore.
We have to or we'll be in big trouble.
I can't take this anymore!!
That Fatso!
Leave it up to him to give us away!
Run! What are you waiting for?
Free money here! Come and get it!
Move aside! Move aside!
They can't be far away! Go!
What do you want?
I love to help people.
I'm glad to hear that.
How can I help you?
Someone has paid us to push you off.
Why don't you jump off yourself?
Hey... You have the wrong guy!
Don't think so.
- Who hired you then?
- I did.
You?
You hired someone to kidnap me.
Now I've also hired them to make
Superman out of you. Push him off!
No... Help!
Help! Please listen to me.
- I'm your father...
- He's you father?
You're my father?
No, no. I'm your father's butler.
You better tell me the whole story.
Your father is Count Lobas.
20 years ago, Gloria worked for him.
One night while the Countess was away...
The Count raped her.
Gloria got pregnant. The Count was afraid
his wife might find out.
So he quietly sent Gloria away.
Son of a bitch!
But he's your father!
I hate him. I never want to see him.
He already passed away.
Before he died,
he begged the Countess
to find you and your mother,
so his evil brother Mondale would not
inherit his fortunes.
For your own safety,
I did not want to tell
my reasons for looking for you.
For that same reason,
I even hired the worst P.I.
- Fortunately, Moby's not here.
- Who says I'm not here?
I'm not that fortunate.
What I wanted to find out,
no one would tell me.
What I don't want to hear... Well.
But it turned out
I'd come to the right guy.
According to the Lobas family tradition,
Sylvia and her mother
have to appear within 14 days.
Otherwise, his evil brother Mondale
will inherit his entire fortune.
Those men after Sylvia must
have something to do with Mondale.
There are still three days left.
Hey, where are you two going?
We wanted to help Sylvia because
we thought she was helpless.
But now it turns out
she is the Count's daughter.
She has no use for us anymore.
You're saying...
that you'll only hang out with Sylvia
if she's poor and helpless?
Now that you've found out that she's
the Count's daughter,
you don't want to be friends
with her anymore?
We really did want to help her.
Do you know then that this is
when she needs help the most.
Don't you want her and her mother
to have a better life?
Of course.
But you can take care of that!
But I'm just one man.
You've seen Mondale's men.
There are still a few days left.
He won't give up now.
If you still consider
yourselves Sylvia's friends,
you wouldn't abandon her now.
Enough already.
We almost feel bad
enough to jump off from here.
Let's devise a plan to get
Sylvia's mother out.
What? What are you looking at?
Want me to try this knife on you?
Don't come any closer or I'll kill you!
Don't run, friend!
Let me go! What?
Let me go...
Relax, Calm down.
Untie me, let me go
All done.
Untie me.
That's too risky.
We don't want to be found out. Lie down.
Turn off the siren.
I saw my mother and Mr. Chan
dancing over there.
What's going on?
Your father and her mother are dancing
over there.
There's a nut case.
His mouth is moving.
Is he talking or eating?
I hate to guess.
I'm not crazy, pal. I'm sane.
Please untie me.
Are you really as sane as us?
Yes.
Why don't you test his intelligence?
Now listen closely. 3 worms line up
in one straight line, moving forward.
The first worm says,
"there are two worms behind me."
The last worm says,
"there are two worms ahead of me."
But the worm in the middle says,
"there are no worms
ahead of or behind me."
Why is that?
- The middle worm is blind.
- No.
Then I don't know.
You shouldn't have given him
such a difficult question.
- Was the question too difficult?
- Way too difficult.
Why did the middle worm say
"there were no worms
ahead of or behind him?"
Because the middle worm was lying.
Worms don't know how to lie!
Never mind him.
Why were you tied up here?
This is a secret.
I can't tell just anyone.
Come closer and I'll whisper it to you.
Don't tell anyone else. That's it.
So you see, I had to fake
being crazy to get in here.
What did he tell you?
He said, "Don't tell anyone else."
Am I anyone else? What did he say?
You're not going to tell me?
You bully me all day long.
I'm going to let you have it!
Hey... Now I am really stuck.
Friend, what did you tell him?
Why should I tell you?
I'll untie you if you do.
You? I don't trust you.
Wait. You were going to tell me.
I said, "Don't tell anyone else." Okay?
Hm... What was it that I was not to
tell anyone else?
Why would they ask us to leave?
It's so nice in here.
What are you all waiting for? Let's go.
We can't.
My mother doesn't want to go without
Mr. Chan and Mr. Chan doesn't want to go.
Just tell your father you and Sylvia
are getting married.
And you need him
out to attend the wedding.
You can't lie to your parents like that!
Not if we can show him some proof.
Just get them out first.
I'll go tell him.
Mr. Chan, you're so in love with Gloria.
Why don't you take her out
and marry her?
Good idea! Why didn't I think of that?
Why did you say that?
What? Do you object to the idea?
No.
So no one objects.
Gloria, will you marry me?
What took you so long?
Congratulations, Mr. Chan.
That makes you two brother and sister.
Are you happy?
Why don't you say something?
Are you unhappy?
You should call him brother now.
That's right, Brother.
No need to be so frustrated.
I have an idea.
Just cut off your ties with your father
as soon as we get out!
Is this a good idea?
Finally...
What is that big thing doing there?
Yeah, what is it doing there?
So do you want me to let up the gas,
step on the brake,
turn off the car, take out the key,
get out of the car to find out
and then report to you?
You could have just asked me nicely!
What is it?
You Fatso. Can't even do
one little thing without any hassle.
Moby.
How are you doing?
Not very well.
Why are you hitting my son?
Let go of me!
Get that bulldozer out of the way!
What are you waiting for??
I don't have the keys!
Then get down and push!
Why don't you show me how to push?
The butler was right. It's not that
difficult to get inside this castle.
But to get inside unnoticed is.
Come on.
I have at least seven ways
to get inside.
Seven? Why not six or eight ways?
Seven is my lucky number.
If it works, one way is enough.
Unfortunately,
that is not one of my seven ways.
Let's get in from the back.
There're many guards in the front.
But even tigers snooze sometimes.
I'm going to get in from the front.
The front is too dangerous.
Who are you going to go with?
I don't like either one of your ideas.
Three people, three ideas.
We're no better than
a pail of loose sand.
There is a difference.
We are only three pails of loose sand.
You're terrible!
Get down now if you have guts, pal!
You guessed it. I don't have guts.
How do you plan to get in?
Through the front door.
It's guarded.
I'll wait for an opportunity.
Wait? It'll be morning then.
Let's climb up the trees.
Have you ever seen an elephant
climb trees?
Then have fun waiting.
Stop playing. Be on your toes.
Come in for dinner.
Don't argue.
Last ball I threw is a top spin,
even if you hit it would've been
gone out of bound.
Hide the bodies first.
I have good news for you.
Someone has come to rescue you.
But I also have bad news for you.
We have already captured him.
How are you?
Don't be rude to my guest.
Give him your seat.
Thank you.
Cheers.
- What do we do now?
- Go home and go to bed.
Bed? Have you lost your mind?
We must find a way to save them!
If you knew, why did you ask?
Come on up.
Are you crazy?
You think I'm you?
Then think of a way yourself.
It's me!
I know.
Then why did you kick me?
I only knew it was you
after I kicked you
and you didn't scream.
For my own safety, we better split up.
What are you doing up there?
Are you guests of the party?
Yes.
I told you not to follow me!
You almost ruined everything.
Take care of the guy first!
Let's go to the party.
The dress and your movements
are a perfect match.
Do you mean I look very classical?
Mother, just sit down.
That's right. I'm a bit hungry.
Set an extra plate.
We have one more guest.
Since you're here,
why not show yourself and join us?
Sorry I'm late, everyone.
What's the main course for tonight?
Roast lamb.
Wouldn't you know!
I was born in the Year of the Lamb.
It's an omen! That explains why I've
made a complete fool of myself tonight.
I am very much honored to have
the pleasure of
so many guests here tonight.
This is a very important night to me.
To the Lobas family,
this is a night of disgrace.
It is you and your mother
who brought disgrace to this family.
Don't upset yourself.
Count Mondale.
If people ever find out
that you kidnapped the two of them,
your reputation will be ruined.
Thank you for reminding me.
Now I know what to do.
I don't see a problem because...
Cardi, take care of my guests for me.
Yes!
Put the ladies in the dungeon.
I haven't finished my soup yet.
Where are you taking me?
What are you looking at?
Reinforcements are here!
You hang in there.
He's really not that tough.
You take care of him
and I'll go help over there.
Come...
I stay with him.
You go rescue the ladies.
- Are you sure?
- No.
You better do it. Go!
I block... block... block...
You can't poke me on the back!
This guy is something else.
No need to panic. Just relax.
Treat this as a training session.
Round 2!
Wait!
1-2-3-4, 2-2-3-4, 3-2-3-4.
You're good!
Come on...
This is getting to be no fun.
Wow, that was a good one!
If you have guts,
pull me up and we'll go another round!
Pal, don't let go. Please pull me up.
What's taking you so long?
I was waiting for the two of you.
The Three Musketeers.
All for one and one for all.
Attack the top.
Attack the bottom.
Divide and conquer.
We're invincible.
Ola. How are you?
What can I get for you, Miss?
A hamburger and a Coke.
Please have a seat while you wait.
Pal, smile a little.
I know you miss her.
Just do the order.
David. Come out.
- What's going on?
- Look.
How nice of you to visit us.
I'm looking for work.
Are you hiring for the summer?
Definitely.
You must wish this summer never ends.
Hello, everyone!
What's up, our phony private eye?
Hey, don't give me a bad name!
Just got my membership card from Intl.
Association of Private Investigators.
I'm now perfectly legitimate.
Congratulations!
Do you guys want to expand
your business?
If you come on an assignment
with me one more time,
you could easily
add 20 more catering vans.
Another castle?
No. It's a hut this time.
That easy? Who are you rescuing?
It's a Black president.
He's been kidnapped
by an African cannibal tribe.
Cannibals!
Hey, someone is looking for you.