Welcome to Zee News.
A look at the top story of the day.
The Mumbai police are on
the horns of a dilemma...
because of an unusual bank robbery.
An internet hacker has succeeded...
in siphoning off 5.5 billion
rupees from two bank accounts
According to our sources,
both companies belong...
to the underworld don
of Mumbai, Babu Anna...
who uses the companies as a front
for his illegal activities
What remains to be seen
is whether the police..
..get the internet
mastermind first..
..or the don who finds himself
swindled out of his savings
Damn it!
What happened to Anna?
A match... a match!
Light it up! Set me
on fire! Light it up!
No, Anna...
- Finish me!
I'm a dog! A mad dog! A cur!
Babu Anna's money gets robbed!
Babu Anna's!
All right if he's robbed it. But
where's he going to spend it?
On his family, Anna.
- Family...?
No way! Who could he
have in his family?
His father, his mother...
- Carve his father out
Burn his mother alive! And hack
his brother to tiny pieces!
As for his sister...
set Yeda Yadav after her! Look
at how I hit out at him!
When I hit him, forget
touching my money...
that swine won't even
be able to sniff at it!
I want that dog here!
Girish! Your responsibility.
You get that?
- Right on, Anna
Yes sir. Six computer experts have
been busy tracing him all night, sir
Can't say for sure... yes, I'll
report first to you, sir
Chavan, what's happening on
the internet robbery case?
It's taking a bit of time,
sir. The systems...
Don't give me excuses.
The pressure's mounting
every minute
Find out who he is and
where he is holed up!
'My eyes...'
'seek her...'
'everywhere I look'
'One day, she will
come right upto me'
'Her charms have made
a romantic out of me'
'She's the one who appears in my
dreams and makes them rosier'
'She hasn't a clue,
she's ignorant...'
'how bowled over
I am by her charms'
'Never before have
I experienced this'
'I have no idea how it all happened'
'My obsession is nothing but the
effect of your love, sweetheart'
'She must've never have
seen someone as crazy'
'It's this fancyfree nature of mine
that shall win her over some day'
'I've never seen such a romance, nor
have I seen someone as crazy'
'In your heart is now my dwelling'
'Somewhere, some day...'
'I will find my heart-throb'
How much?
- 3 rupees
Keep the change.
Let me go.
- Let you go?
After you give me your licence
That girl ahead will go away.
- Girl?
Had heard about the
wife and the other one.
But first time I am hearing about
the ahead one and the behind one.
You have a bike. So why
do you need a babe?
You youngsters are real flirts
She is the one. I am telling you,
it is absolutely amazing.
And that cop sprang there!
The girl I could only dream
of was actually there!
Right there in front
of me! I mean...
I mean.. - What the heck.
- You know Sonia..
I'm sure she'd have recognised
me too, if she had seen me
She'd have felt just as I felt! I'm
telling you, I can't believe it!
That I have found her.
She is the one!
I want to meet her, talk to her...
- Stupid!
You haven't told me about the
car deal. What happened..
..about the BMW and Mercedes?
Oh yes, that was finalised
last night.
That too in 2.5 million.. cash!
Forget all that! You're
not listening, Sonia!
I have found her.
She's in this very city! I
saw her in flesh and blood!
I want to meet her. Talk to her.
But these cops are
really too much.
Hey, just listen to me.
My wait has actually come to an end.
How I wish I could meet her once
Guess what, Jai? Dad asked
me to marry that guy..
..again and I turned him down
Only because I happen
to be waiting...
for this stupid boy
to propose to me!
You did right. Excellent!
You.. - Hey.. ok, relax.
Shut up and listen
carefully, you stupid.
There's no one else in your
life. There's only me
Sonia is my best friend.
But my heart's bowled over by her
I love you, Jai!
Hang on!
Jai... what happened?
Hello, brother.
- Hello, son. How're you doing?
Very well. Tell me, sir..
Which Gurudwara is this
procession coming from?
The Singh Sabha Gurudwara.
- Sat Sri Akal
Lord, my pledge of 40 days'
fast comes to an end today
Heed my prayer, Lord.
Please grant me my wish
Please wear them.
- But...
Go on. I'm doing service.
- Service?
Yes. I'm doing service
with a wish...
that I find the one I love
How sweet!
You will surely find her
Because the wish you seek with
a true heart, is always granted
Wear your footwear
Are you Neha?
- Yes
Neha madam...?
Who's been sending this...?
- I don't know
Oh God!
Now look...
You? Is it from the Gurudwara?
Oh no! Not from the Gurudwara!
- So then...?
Believe me, I've never done
a thing like this ever before
But I'm not afraid to do it
They fear, who have
malicious intentions
I love you, Neha.
That's exactly how I reacted when
I saw you in person 3 days ago
And I fell in love with you
And then I saw you in a
salwar-kameez for the first time...
See..? I still can't control myself
Look, you aren't...?
- I know, I know
It isn't easy for a girl to
make a decision so quickly
You need time, isn't it?
No problem, I'll wait
But just two hours, okay? Because
I can't wait any longer
See you two hours later then
China Love!
You will come and put
your arms around me...
and say that you love me.
Ok, bye! You are so beautiful! Bye.
Have a really good time tonight.
Keep this party going at China Love.
She is coming.
- Who?
Neha
Today, I professed my love to her.
- Then?
I gave her time to think.
All of two hours
Two hours! Wow!
I know it's too short a notice,
but I can't help it
I can't live more than two
hours without her. Sonia...
I'm sure she'll come
She will give me a hug and
say that she loves me
Whatever!
'I...'
'you...'
'love...'
'and the rising desires'
'And love starts now!'
'Come to me, my love'
'That's right.'
'I, you, romance, love...'
'and the rising desires!
Come to me, my love'
'Sweetheart...'
'what have you done?'
'I've given my heart to you'
'With those gazes and sweet words
you've stolen my heart away'
'Come my love, let's shake a leg.'
'I am...'
'lost...'
'in your love'
'So lost...'
'that I care...'
'for none else'
'When my anklets chime, he
pines... it's inebriating'
'Come my love, let's shake a leg.'
'My heart...'
'throbs...'
'as desires...'
'well up'
'I'd die for you...'
'my love'
'You are the girl of my
dreams, you invade..
..my heart... love is a delight'
'Come my love, let's shake a leg.'
'I...'
'you...'
'love...'
'and the rising...
- desires'
'Love..'
'..starts now.'
'Come to me, my love'
'Sweetheart...'
'what have you done?'
'I've given my heart to you'
'With those gazes and sweet words
you've stolen my heart away'
You thought she'd come,
give you a hug...
and tell you that she loves you
Only a stupid girl would
do that with you
That's me
Now, c'mon. Let's go.
C'mon, Jai.
You...?
- You didn't come...?
I kept waiting for you since nine,
but you didn't turn up
Are you insane?
I've been insane ever since
I saw you, never before
Neha, I've decided...
I really love you, Neha.
- O God! Please.
O my God! Then..
Then?
What else? He kept on raving, and
I slammed the door in his face
What a crazy guy!
Whatever you say, he seems
to be very interesting
Do such lovers exist in real life?
I've never...
Is it him? He is so cute!
You may think I'm crazy,
and I really am
I know, I've been quite a pest
And, last night I even
came to your house...
I shouldn't have done that.
I am sorry for that.
But I can't help it. When it comes
to you, I've no control over myself
Excuse me, bill please.
Look probably.. - Thank you.
Probably...
I'm bad at displaying it,
but my love for you is true
And I can do anything to prove it
Now you will say that..
you can down the moon and the
stars for me...
Will jump off the highest cliff...
Will even give up your life for me.
If that would convince
you, I'll do it
Very good.
What are you waiting for?
All right! I was madly
in love with you...
now I'm going to die for you
Ok, best of luck.
Greetings! Welcome to our viewers.
Here are the headlines.
Neha Mehra? - Yes.
Who do you think you are?
- Excuse me.
Your good looks...
don't give you the right to
play with someone's life
I've never seen Jai like this
His parents passed away when
he was nine. Do you know?
Yet, he worked his way up on his
own, From the age of nine years.
And now...
he's paying a heavy price
for not understanding you
Meaning? - Jai took an overdose
of sedatives...
and tried to kill himself - What?
If something happens to
him.. Its your fault.
Govind kaka, did you
get the medicines?
Excuse me, you can relax now.
We've removed even the last
traces of the pills
He is out of danger.
Can I see him?
- Not now
I don't think he'll come
around before morning
Ok, thank you so much, doctor.
You are really crazy
I don't believe, for my sake,
someone would...
I feel as if I've
got a new identity
Someone loves me so much
If I turn him down, no one will be
more insane than me in this world.
I love you, Jai.
I have never said that before
But I felt no fear in saying
it for the first time today
They fear, who have
malicious intentions
Such decisions aren't
taken in haste, I know
I'm not in a hurry
I will wait.
I'll give you...
two seconds
I love you, Jai!
'O heart of mine...'
'wait no more'
'If you are in love...'
'express it'
'O heart of mine...'
'wait no more'
'If you are in love...'
'I love you.. love you, like crazy.'
'I want you.. want you, like crazy.'
'I won't let you...'
'belong to another'
'You mean the very life to me'
'You are the story...'
'I read all night, all day'
'I believe you'
'Let me give you the comfort
of my arms...'
'come to me'
'Dear Life wants me to give
up my life for Her'
'If you are in love...'
'express it'
'I love you.. love you, like crazy.'
'I want you.. want you, like crazy.'
'There's none crazier than you'
'I've given in to your obstinacy'
'My love...'
'I know...'
'I make you restless'
'In my thoughts, in my dreams,
you shall dwell'
'I shall hold you in my eyes'
'Come to me'
'My love...'
'trust me'
'If you are in love...'
'express it'
Jai, I need to tell you something
Go on
You know Sonia, it's amazing.
Ever since I met Neha, I've
cared least for time
At times I feel it flies,
at times I feel it stops
See, I have to meet her in an hour,
but the clock just won't tick away
What's going to happen of you?
- Nothing
I'll work hard for a few
years, earn enough...
and then I'll marry her and
have seven or eight kids
Seven or eight? Is that all?
- Yes, don't I need to work?
But I'll send them over
to you for stories
Okay, so I'll be their nanny?
- Right
Forget it, Jai.
It's going to prove you costly.
- Why?
Because I'm going to London, Jai
I've decided to marry
Why London? You could
get suitors here too
I'll talk to your parents...
- No Jai
I relate every place, every
thing in this city with you
I may stay away from you, but I
can't tear myself apart from you
I must go now... else I'll
miss my flight, too
You are...
leaving right now?
And you tell me now?
- Had I told you earlier...
I might've given in
to your reasoning
I know, you think I'm selfish
But today... please
let me be selfish
Let me escort you to the airport.
- No
I'll go alone
You are not going alone that far.
- No, Jai
Please don't make it
more difficult for me
I will miss you.
I love you.
Bye. - Stupid.
Neha...?
What are you doing?
Neha, what are you..
Have you gone mad, Neha?
What's happening here?
What's the matter?
- I...
What is it?
How would you know that you're in
love with a criminal's daughter?
A criminal?
- Yes
Daddy's no more. But he left
making life difficult for me.
What does that mean?
Daddy had borrowed money
from the underworld...
and now, they're following me
Till now, they only kept
threatening me. But now...
they say that if I don't return
their money within 3 days, they will...
they will kidnap me.
- Who do they think they are?
They're like the wolves,
Jai. I don't..
..want to fall in their
hands. So I...
Didn't you consider for
a moment what would..
..happen of me if you were harmed?
Don't worry. Just tell me
where I will find them
They're very dangerous, Jai. I did
all I could to repay them, but...
Don't worry, I can really help. I
have the money. 2.5 million in cash
It isn't so little.
I owe them 60 million.
Neha, everything is going to be fine.
I'll deal with everything.
You don't worry
It's five years old,
but thank God...
you've maintained it rather well.
You also have a 24-hour water supply
Got to sell immediately, right?
So, thank God...
it'll fetch at least 8 million.
Is that okay?
Don't worry.
Nice, nice... looks solid
Facing the West. Also
has a nice sea-view?
Can we get a glimpse of
the sea from here? - No
No? From the terrace?
No harm in saying you can
Since it's the ground floor,
security is good enough
This is a weak lock, I say. But
that's okay. I'll handle it
Actually, I have a buyer.
And cash won't be a problem
I'm sure it'll get sold at 5 million
You want me to negotiate?
60 million? You can't be serious!
You say 60 millions as if you
were borrowing my car for 6 days
60 million. Only
one way of raising that..
..type of money in
such a short time
Go and rob a bank!
Stop joking.
- Sorry, sorry.... but 60 million?!
Are you mad? You will rob a bank...?
What else can we do? We
have no other choice
Your house and mine and our belongings
won't fetch more than 20 million.
I know what I'll do. I'll go to
the bank tomorrow morning and...
Really...? By the way, which
bank do you propose to rob?
Standard Chartered Bank, Bandra.
Now listen to me, Neha
I know what I'm doing is wrong.
But we have no other choice
To raise 60 million in just
two days... think about it
We've tried everything, we...
- Rather I die than do this, Jai
Listen to me, Neha
Neha, just stop.
Promise me, you won't even joke
about such a thing again
If something happens to you... -
Okay. The bank robbery's off. Okay?
Five guards during the day. Must
at least be 3 during the night
Looks pretty difficult
Mr. Vikram, it's great pleasure
to be of service to you.
What urgency makes you withdraw
70 million in one go?
No problem. The bank is
yours. So are we...
and most important, the
money's yours too!
Thank you for using our services.
This is the first time we're handling
such a big wire-transfer for you
I hope you will give us
the opportunity to..
..do many more wire-transfers
for you
Thank you very much.
Seems I won't be required to
break the promise made to Neha.
Now not the bank but
he is going to get robbed.
You look well-bred. Why
did you come here?
To steal
I see
I went to rob the bank and saw
you withdrawing the money
Thought I'd rob it from you
Robbing the bank was much
easier, wasn't it?
Please, come in.
What if you had got killed?
That's okay
I don't care for my life
I'd at least have got 60 million.
Why do you need the money?
I don't consider it
necessary to tell you
That's my problem.
All right, you can tell
the cops when they arrive
Have some juice. - No thanks.
Have it. It's said
to be good for health
Sit down
It was six months ago that I
saw Neha for the first time..
Interesting.. very very interesting.
Let's say I give it to you.
I give you 60 million
But what can I give you in return?
Your life
Something you don't care for, right?
Which means...?
Now look, Jai. There's
no going back after..
..I tell you what I
am about to tell you.
So think it over and...
- I'm prepared to do anything
But I need the money. In 24 hours
Are you sure? - Yeah.
So listen. Maybe you've heard
of the internet robbery case?
Yes, in which someone
stole 5.5 billion..
..from Babu Anna's account, right?
For 60 million, you must claim
to be the computer hacker...
and turn yourself over to
the police. - But what..
..will you gain out of it?
Gain?
I'll be rid of the fear of getting
caught or dying at Babu Anna's hands
Because I am the computer
hacker, Jai
I've committed a crime in
my lust for wealth...
but I've lost my sleep
and peace of mind
You were willing to lose your
life for 60 million, Jai
Now you've only got
to serve a sentence
What are you thinking about, Jai?
Okay, not 60 million. I'll
give you 70 million...
to spend the rest of your life,
after your imprisonment
I agree
Good boy.
But I need just 60
million and not 70.
All right. suit yourself
When are you going to surrender?
- When are you going to pay me?
Surrender. And you
will have the money
Give me the money.
And I'll surrender
Ok, fair enough.
I think I can trust you
Where will you go anyway?
Let's go inside. It takes a hell of
a lot of time to count 60 million.
Throw this money in their face
So much of money...? How?
I've mortgaged my life to someone
You think your boyfriend
is worth nothing!
Been dealing in imported
cars for 3 years now..
..I command respect too, no?
All in one night...?
One moment. You haven't really
robbed the bank...?
Swear it on you!
I didn't rob the bank
You've sworn on me.
- Sworn on you
I didn't rob the bank. Okay?
How we will we repay
such a huge debt?
This is nothing. I'd give my
life for you, if I had to
For as long as I live, it's
my duty to look after you
Why must you talk about dying?
Our lives have only just begun
What's that?
Keep it with you forever.
And whatever happens...
remember, I'm always with you
I love you, Jai.
I'm very scared, Jai
I feel as if you're hiding
something from me
Silly girl. Have I
ever lied to you?