Jo, are you ready?
Hey, baby. No, no - um...
Yes, I'm all set.
Why don't you get something to eat?
Jo, we're already late.
Did you grab a bottle of wine?
If we get hitten, you could lose an eye.
Not todayÉ
How was your day?
My day was fine.
Thank you.
Michael where's the wine?
What?
Wine.
Shit!
Wait, wait, wait...
Hello!
You look nice baby.
Thanks.
Come.
I love you.
Oh, you didn't bring Sarah?
You didn't tell her?
See you in hour.
You should be finished by then.
Oh well, thank you for that!
Barbara! Hello!
Thanks for having us.
Come see me upstairs.
I will.
How long were you two together?
Three months.
Three months?
Three months already?
Talking to Monroe, I think we should schedule
another meeting for Monday.
Okay, let's just see how tomorrow goes.
I bet you didn't like Sarah either, did you?
I did! I said I did!
Yeah, but I don't think that you meant it.
Thanks.
Welcome.
Why's it so hard for me, Jo?
It isn't. I mean it can't be.
You haven't gone to the hard bit yet.
What it gets harder than this?
- Joanna?
Hello!
Hi, so good to see you.
Thank you for having us.
Andy...
Stuart...
Michael says you're working on a new book.
Michael always says that.
He's probably right.
I just don't know it?
Well, I got to go and talk to somebody.
Eat, I'll be here.
He hates me.
He's gonna fire me. I know.
You say that every week.
Yeah well, it's true.
But it hasn't been in the last two years.
Well maybe he's just waiting for the right time.
Hey do you want me to walk Lucy,
while you guys are away?
Yeah, that'd be great.
Where is Michael anyway?
Here he is.
Here he is, let's go!
Joanna?
Um yes no I'm going to go to the ladies.
I'll catch you up.
Okay.
I'm starving.
Hey, where have you guys been?
I got totally ambushed by Stuart.
The guy's hasn't talked to me in two weeks -
- and sees me with your wife,
and just lit up.
Laura, this is my Joanna.
Hello! Nice to meet you.
Joanna, this is Laura. She's our new designer,
who has worked for us.
Nice to finally meet you.
So Michael tells me you're a writer.
Yes, I am.
I've been meaning to order your book.
That's nice.
Oh! Look, look! Oh my god!
Neal he's trying with Cynthia again.
She's not going to go for it.
I know. It just won't work.
Why not?
He's a good looking guy.
Why did you turn him down?
Speak of the devil...
Hey, Neal!
Had any luck with Cynthia?
Hi Joanna!
Hello.
Had any luck?
What?
You didn't really go to
"The Yogo" with her, did you?
She told you that?
She told me about that!
Still with Cynthia huh?
What? You're getting jealous?
So what's Laura's story ?
Stuart recruited her.
She seems to be good.
She's working the Monroe project with us.
Of course she is...
Try to get me some wine?
That's not funny.
There you go.
Hi. Would you like a drink?
Yeah, white wine please.
Sure.
Thanks.
Is she going to Philadelphia with you guys tomorrow?
Yeah.
And she was in LA with
Michael last month?
Taxi!
Have you been smoking?
You really going to attempt to give me
a grief about that?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Have I done something wrong?
She is pretty.
Who?
You never mentioned that.
Laura?
Yeah, Laura.
I think you described her as "whatever".
I don't remember.
I bet.
You didn't tell me that she was in LA with you.
She's wasn't in LA with me.
We were just there at the same time.
Michael, face me!
You didn't tell me anything about her, before tonight,
but then I think you know that.
What's that supposed to mean?
What did you think could happen tonight?
And seriously, did you think I just wouldn't notice?
Why would I think anything would make you notice her?
You're a terrible liar!
Might be because
I don't l lie.
She likes you,
and you like her.
Of course you don't want to talk to me
about it.
Where is this come from?
My eyes, Michael!
She's she the only one you talked to,
all night.
How many glasses of wine did you have
tonight, Jo?
Two and two sips.
Is that really your response?
You had more than that.
What are you?
The drink patrol?
Well remind me when we go out,
and I ask you not to have another.
You ask me why.
This is why.
You're kidding me, right?
Because it makes you like this, baby.
Michael without wine we would be in a
much shittier place.
Eleven hours a day.
Five, sometimes six days a week.
That's sixty hours a week with her,
three months now.
What is it you think I have done?
Check my phone, Jo.
And check my e-mails, check receipts, go on.
Not everyone gets caught, Michael.
Has she told you she's attracted to you?
Maybe, Joanna.
I don't let the conversation go there.
But she tried to, hasn't she?
But she tried to when you were
in LA together?
You do hours I do not know about,
with the people that you work with.
You go away -
- doing articles, all the time!
Have I ever given you a reason to stand here
feeling the way that I am right now?
I looked through a window tonight and I
saw something that I didn't need to see.
Couldn't you just have watched yourself
and spared me?
What the fuck are you doing!?
I want to charge the phone.
Why do you always have to use this one?
Why did you build a Berlin wall of freakin' magazines!?
I haven't done anything wrong,
and you try to pick a fight.
I spare you.
I would.
What's that supposed to mean?
Is she going to Philadelphia with you and Andy tomorrow?
Uh-huh, cause she's been working on
the Monroe properly with us.
Why? What does that look?
That looks sad, Michael.
There's nothing going on,  Jo.
Laura is just someone I work with.
It's not that I'm blaming you for being
attracted to her. She's... -
- attractive.
And it's natural to crave newness.
So what are you blaming me for?
For going out of your way not to admit it.
Thought I just did.
Don't do that face, Jo...
You know what I meant.
You corner me, and you order me
to admit something -
and then you're pouncing me the second I came,
and now you're going to sleep on the couch?
Fucking fantastic!
I did not do anything wrong, Jo.
I'm sorry.
What for?
I'm not sure but,
I love you.
Come to bed.
I don't want to.
Come to the kitchen.
Food isn't going to fix this.
Soon you'll have a full stomach.
Come on.
We got any tomatoes?
No.
How was your day?
Oh, but...
What?
Nothing,  I just remembered I'm mad at you.
I hate it when that happens.
Danny proposed!
Yeah!
What Pia said?
What did you think she said? Yes!
Was she surprised at all?
Yes, she thought that he was going to tell her
he was moving out.
My mum called.
Yeah, I know. I spoked to her.
Second week of December.
I' ve already said yes.
Can we go via London?
Yeah, sure.
What time is your train?
At 8:00.
You shouldn't be up this late.
I'll sleep on the train.
It's an hours ride.
I'll sleep in the meeting.
What are you doing tomorrow or today?
I got to finish up the accessories piece.
Yeah, with pearls?
Yeah, I'll dig up another hundred words.
It's good. And then you can work on the book,
without me here to distract you.
Joanna, I'm sorry.
I would have said something about her,
if I thought there was something to say.
Michael, did something happen in LA?
No.
I swear.
Eggs are good.
Yeah.
What about the orange juice?
Come on.
What kind of cafe is this?
Do you think we got married too soon?
What?
Why can't you make yourself consider that?
Because I don't have to.
I don't think we got married too soon -
- because we married after four years.
Yeah, with a break up in the middle.
And anyway, it's not about the amount of time
but the when of time -
- and our when included college.
You know, that was before we were even us, you know.
Do you think it's even the same
between us?
It got better...
Can you hear yourself right now?
What?
Just because I disagree with you,
means I'm not aware of what I'm saying?
You can't really think that.
I do think that.
How?
Sunday night.
The last two weekends.
Breakfast yesterday.
Dinner last night.
There's no bullshit between us.
With the possible exception of this evening.
Come here, Jo.
I'm cold.
Got your orange juice?
No. Thank you!
You're gonna try to get some writing done?
"Try" is a big word.
No, it's not.
Alright, I got to go.
See you later.
Bye.
Hello.
A cup of coffee, please.
Joanna!
Alex! What are you doing here?
I have some work here.
I can't believe this!
Yeah, it's been a while.
How are you?
I'm fine, I just can't believe you're here.
How did you know I'd be here?
I keep tabs on you.
I'm serious.
So am I.
Your Christmas cards.
They gave the return address on them.
What if I' d moved?
You haven' t.
How long are you in New York for?
I leave tomorrow. Actually, I'm late for a meeting.
Do you have time for me now?
Yeah, yeah. Sure.
Good.
Then I call you later with the time.
Wait, wait, do you need my number?
Has it changed?
No...
Then I call you later?
Wait!
Cause I've never been able to sleep -
- think that by the time I sleep I won't wake up
for about four years.
Be like, ...
I need to use the men's room.
Okay.
Michael, we have to wait for Andy.
It's funny, because I could actually.. I could sleep anywhere.
Is that right?
Yes, I could probably fall sleep right here.
Right here?
Six, four, seven, two, two.
Operator! Operator!
Operator!
Good morning!
How can I help you?
I need to check in.
Name please?
Michael Reed.
Hello.
Yeah?
About noon, I thought I hallucinated
the whole thing.
Yeah, Yeah, No, No.
That sounds good.
Okay, No...
I'll meet you there.
Alright, see you there.
Bye.
Wow, you look beautiful!
Thank you.
You caught me off guard this morning.
You looked just as beautiful then.
Shall we sit?
Okay.
So do I look different?
No.
I feel older.
You look the same.
You smell the same.
You do too.
Okay...
Let's get you a drink.
Yeah!
Can I have two vodka-martinis on ice,
with olives? Thank you.
Can't be that kind of a night.
I know.
The last time we saw each other.
Claridge's.
For drinks.
That was almost...
Two years ago.
That's right. So how's work?
How's the book?
I don't know. But it's finished.
It is?
That's great!
Can I read it?
Of course!
Do you speak french?
No, good.
Okay...
We 're starting early.
Excellent!
The translation is almost finished.
You'll read it.
How's Paris?
How are you?
I'm good.
How's your work?
I'm doing freelance.
Fashion stuff mainly. It's good. It's ok.
Where are you staying?
Here.
Oh, right.
You're still afraid of this object being you
for too long, right?
Come on this is strange.
Us having a drink?
You in New York.
Why?
Because you don't belong here.
Thank you.
So...
Tell me something that counts.
It's been too long since I've seen you.
I meant something personal.
That is something very personal.
Are you seeing someone at the moment?
Tell me about her.
We are... -
- happily under-committed.
How long?
Few months.
That's long.
"For you" .
I wasn't gonna say that!
It was good seeing you...
Bless the Martini!
Obviously you guys won't keep
the hotel open -
-as long as possible while we're doing work.
It's definitely something you need to think about
as far as how we run phases -
Because now it's becoming very important -
- thinking about maybe solar panels -
- double paint glass in all the rooms.
It's actually something that Michael has invested
a lot of his time and making sure.
It's actually something -
- for people who stay at your hotel, because you have these options -
- and we think this is really something.
It's a lot of money upfront, you then you get a payoff.
Absolutely!
So Stuart tells me that you guys could probably
bring in about three months.
Do you agree with that?
There's no problem.
Is it alright?
Yeah.
It's all about the timing.
Start paying next week and we could be done
by the end of this year.
Alright.
You know yout timing is nuts.
Why? Are you getting a divorce?
No!
And then?
I think it's possible that I will you into being
in my life.
It's like if I think about you too long
you pick up on it.
Were you thinking about me?
I always think about you when thinks
aren't going well.
What wasn't going well?
We should get going.
Where?
My room...
I'm kidding!
I'm having dinner with -
- you know the man who bought the permission house
and who is in France?
You're coming with me?
No, I am not.
Why not?
It's your work dinner!
No no - not at all!
I've known him for a long time.
He's a friend.
You'll like him, and his wife.
I wouldn't fell comfortable.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
I can't cancel.
Come on! It's been two years.
Michael won't let you out one night?
Michael is out of town.
I'll get the check.
Still a little early for
grabbing a drink?
Not so much.
We have an early day tomorrow.
All the more reason to relax
a little tonight.
I don't think that'd be relaxing.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
So if there's anything you'd like to
add to the presentation -
- we should probably meet a little earlier.
Absolutely.
How long? 30 minutes?
Yes, 30 minutes.
How's the view?
It's good.
Thanks for dinner.
See you tomorrow.
Thanks, goodnight.
Goodnight.
I'm exhausted.
I swear meeting conversations are
right there with working out.
Not that I work out, though...
God, I feel like a drink!
No, no. Not me.
Plus I thought that it didn't sound relaxing?
Well it didn't. Not with Zach.
You up for it?
Sure, I'll have one.
Really? Because I think you didn't
get much sleep last night.
I'm ok. Call you in the morning,
go for the run.
How is your mum?
She's better, thanks.
Hello.
How are you?
Your friends are there.
Hey, Alex!
Hey!
Hey! How are you?
Great!
Good to see you!
Alex!
So, Joanna, this is Sandra.
Hello.
Hi.
Joanna, Truman. Truman, Joanna.
How are you?
Excellent! Good to see you!
God, you're good looking!
Thank you!
She is!
Look at her!
I had no idea you were seeing
someone in New York.
No, no. We're just good friends.
Who sleep together!?
Oh come on! I was joking.
I was wondering but you know -
- it's way too early in the evening -
- to answer a question like that.
Well, she's not answering and neither am I.
- And no.
Thank you!
So, where do you two know each other from?
Go ahead.
Paris!
I was writing a story and -
- a mutual friend had a dinner.
When was that?
That was about 4 years ago?
What kind of wine guys?
We'll have the Brunello we had last week.
So, Joanna.
What do you write?
Articles.
Freelance mainly.
She writes books.
She's written one very good one already.
What's your last name?
Read.
Was the first book not received well?
Wasn't really received at all.
She went with the wrong publisher.
I think, if it had been received,
it wouldn't have been received well.
You're being modest.
No!
Yes!
I wish!
Alright, I got ten more questions.
Do you want me to bring the specials?
Yeah.
Would you like another?
That guy with the green sweater, if he leaves,
I'll have another.
Why?
I spent 12 and 13 doing things
on the basis -
- of other things happening
or not happening.
Like...
If my mother wore her navy skirt to work -
- instead of her navy pants -
- then I wouldn't talk to anybody on the bus -
- but if she wore pants, then I'd have to.
Afraid to be responsible for what you did.
Exactly...
And now?
I'm obviously experiencing a relapse.
I'd love another drink.
Okay.
Just not here...
Okay...
This thing in my life with the most random unrandom things -
- happen to me all the time,
does that make sense?
Yes!
No!
I mean it makes sense to me,
because I know you.
Joanna?
Maggie!
I thought that was you.
What are you doing here?
We're just having dinner.
Where's Michael?
He's out of town at the moment.
Okay...
Well, call me.
Yeah, okay.
Enjoy your dinner.
Thank you, bye bye.
Your best friend?
I'm so sorry I didn't introduce you.
Don't be.
Unless you couldn't remember our names.
Because I do that.
Me too, actually.
No worries.
Who's Michael?
He's my husband.
God, it tastes good.
I didn't know you ordered this.
Of course you can have mine?
So tell me about your wife.
Where's that come from?
I don't know.
It just came.
She's great.
What does she do,
when you're out of town?
Same things she does
when I'm in town.
What she's doing tonight?
I don't know.
I thought you called her.
Yeah I did.
I just couldn't get through.
How long have you been married?
Three years.
Yeah?
And you guys dated a while before?
Yeah, we met in college.
You met young.
Yeah, we did.
I got to find the men's room.
I'll meet you at the bar.
If it's a mingy cat -
- that really means that it's a bad sign.
In dream world, a mingy cat...
Who's phone is that?
Sorry it's me..,
Michael is out of town, excuse me.
Hello, hello!
Hey!
Where are you?
Well, I'm grabbing a bite, I just stepped out.
How's your day?
Is it my phone or is it yours?
It's got to be yours, I hear you fine.
What?
I said I hear you fine.
How was your day?
It's good. I got some work down.
This isn't a very good connection.
No, it's not that good.
Are you out?
I'm in a men's room -
- we're still with the clients.
Okay.
Why don't you give me a call tomorrow morning?
Love you.
I love you.
Bye.
I love it, when you come back at the table,
and your food is there!
How long have you been married?
Three years.
Have any kids?
No, no. You?
No.
None.
I never wanted any.
In fact, that's why my first wife and I
broke up.
That didn't came up
before you got married?
Yes, of course it did, but
I think she thought that -
- I would change after we got married.
But people don't change.
I mean, at most your weight fluctuates and
you start dressing differently.
I realize for a host of reasons I -
- I probably shouldn't be going here,
but I'm going to.
That night in LA, when we all
went to that bar -
- we sat on those low couches -
- and Jeff wanted to sit next to us,
so you had to move over.
Your hand sort of rested against my leg.
Was that on purpose?
I had to be careful not to really
let it rest there.
Cause you moved.
I didn't move.
I wouldn't have.
I'm married.
I know.
Still it felt nice.
That is so embarrassing!
Thank you.
Usually she's doing it better.
No, the point was that I love Italy.
I love it there.
We have a place, we go there -
- one month a year.
It's so wonderful.
Wait! This is who you went to Italy with?
When?
When I got to Paris early, and -
- your little cousin was staying in the apartment,
till you got back -
- and you were away with Patrick and his friends.
Yeah, exactly!
This is them.
That's really so weird!
And you seemed familiar!
How funny.
What if you were married?
Hypotheticals don't do much for me, but...
Probably nothing different.
Are you happy?
With what?
With your marriage.
Yeah.
Very.
You can be happy and still be tempted.
I know.
Just surprised you do.
Have you ever been with someone else
since you've been married?
No.
Have you wanted to be?
What happened?
Think of Joanna.
You regret not doing it?
I'd regret more if I did.
You ever cheated on anybody?
Cheated?
Have you?
No.
Not necessarily on principle,
I just -
- I never wanted to.
Alex, I know you want them.
I need one yeah.
And I know you want one.
No, no, no.
She wants to keep me company.
I do. I do.
You do? I do.
Okay.
So have a good night.
It's a trap.
I know.
You'll never change.
When was the last time you saw Alex?
Two years ago.
So you know Helen?
Helen?
Alex's girlfriend from Paris.
Well, we are not very good at keeping touch with -
- the dailies.
We talk when we talk.
She's nice. I don't think he's going
to settle down with her anytime soon.
But I don't know that Alex would ever settle down,
with anyone.
He seems more whole,
on his own.
So where is your husband?
He's in Philidelphia on a business trip.
What's he do?
Commercial real estate development -
- but, I don't think this was the question
you wanted to ask.
No, it wasn't.
Go ahead.
I usually tend to go too far.
Okay, warning heard.
Does your husband know Alex?
No.
Does he know of him?
Have I gone too far?
Yeah, maybe, but it's fun!
Why haven't you told him?
I think when you know something like that,
you can't unlearn it.
So there is a something like that.
Are you faithful?
Yes.
Will he forgive you,
if you were not?
He's always said
that he wouldn't.
Does that stop you?
Yeah, probably.
How long were you with Alex together?
We were never really together.
We were more kind of on and off.
You think you'll tell your husband
about tonight?
I don't know.
Tonight is not finished yet.
Remember the last time we were here,
and we got in the wrong car?
When was that?
Remember how far we went before you remembered?
Ten blocks. Hey guys, come on.
Why don't you just drive with us?
Oh shit, Lucy!
Who?
A friend's dog.
I said I'd walk her.
Where is she?
She's on our friend's apartment.
Are you just saying that to get out of
going to the party?
No, No! I know! I swear!
When were you last in New York?
Nine months ago.
Why didn't you get in touch?
I wasn't alone...
Can't get the key out!
Andy cooks?
No, I bought that for him last year
I doubt he's ever used it.
I do that when we're over.
So why aren't you writing?
I am writing!
No, why aren't you writing?
You mean...
Your book, Joanna.
My editor says that I just need to get over
my doubt.
What do you doubt?
Everything, Alex.
I go to write -
- and every word, every thought, every choice
that I make leads to another and -
- I doubt every single one I make.
It wasn't like this last time.
You live with your first book
all your life -
- it comes out on its own.
After that though, it's just different.
You can suddenly write -
- anything and you second-guess everything.
Doubts will kill your work.
Who me? I don't know.
What's the matter with doubt?
I think the world could use
a little more doubt.
So I doubt...
For the good of the world?
Exactly.
No, thank you.
Your first book was good, Joanna.
You know I think you might just have ruined
this kitchen for me.
How?
By being in it.
I come here all the time,
and now you've been here.
Remind me why it didn't work?
Geography.
People live between two cities.
I don't, and neither do you.
And timing.
You were broken up!
Temporarily. Technically, whateverly...
We got back together -
- after we'd already been together
for a really long time.
You came after.
So you're with him,
because he came first?
He did, and I love him -
- and I love you too, and I love
being able to tell you the truth.
And I love...
Faith, loyalty and all that shit, even now.
And this?
This?
I don't know that this would be
what it is on its own.
This is only what it is, because it's something that's between -
- me, my marriage to Michael,
you and your set of things.
Does Andy have anything to drink?
What are my things?
Nothing, I'm criticizing.
I'm just...
I know that if we went for it,
we'd lose it.
That's hard to lose,
because we never wear out.
We were just getting to know,
that we weren't right for each other.
You didn't want to!
No.
No?
I came to Paris for two months!
You do hold that against me.
I don't hold anything against you!
I was finishing a book.
I was too tired to figure out -
- what you being there even meant.
It should have meant that you wanted
to spend some time with me.
It doesn't matter.
No, it matter to me.
Because I'm the one who has to see you here.
I'm the one who has to look around Andy's
- to see these pictures of you in this life.
What?
I was what you needed to be sure of Michael?
No. No.
It doesn't work like that.
I think...
Maybe I've wanted this to change.
Everything...
Everything changes, but this,
this still hasn't.
Not for me.
That's a lesson.
I saw you this morning...
And... in the middle of most nights, when I can't sleep -
- I still replay you.
I'm going to take her out for a walk.
Keys, Alex!
I thought you took them with you.
No.
Oh merde!
Did you leave them upstairs?
Yeah, can we call someone?
We can call Caroline, but...
Shit!
Give me that, I'll give it back to you tomorrow.
Let's go.
You weren't lying about the dog!
No!
Come with me.
Let us find Fred.
Okay.
Her husband's best friend's dog.
She's the one Chris told me about?
I don't know.
At Phillips wedding, after you just broken off
with Lauren.
I asked him, what the hell was
wrong with you.
I liked Lauren.
But I like this one much more.
She's smart.
Yeah.
She's funny.
She's gorgeous!
I know.
And she's honest.
Well I mean, besides the fact she's out with you,
and her husband is out of town.
But she's married.
I know.
No, you don't. No, you've never been married.
I mean fuck the vows.
It's the years you can't undo.
You will never be able to take her away
the years with her husband.
And the moment you try, this,
this will be gone.
Trust me.
That would be a shame.
I bet you've had less than a hundred days
together, am I right?
It's the best.
Be smart.
Keep it as it is.
I'm in!
Your turn.
Here.
Oh, come on.
I'm not going to be the only one in here,
in my underwear.
You're uncomfortable.
I am uncomfortable.
You don't hold back much, do you?
We're here in our underwear. I think
it's a late for that, no?
Do you remember that first night?
Do you ever think about it?
Of course I do.
I did not want to go home,
and you put me in a taxi.
And do you remember that night -
- when we met the photographer you were interviewing?
And he was drunk!
He was drunk.
And you danced on that top of yours with no back.
Come.
Let's go.
So, have you ever been cheated on?
No.
Well, I have.
The worst part with her I found out.
We shared a photo account -
- and I went on the website to order
some pictures -
- and I saw the album she decided to
share with him.
I think they were together for the weekend,
or something.
I could have done without the visuals.
There was this one, they were laughing so much...
What happened?
We fucked like animals for about a month.
I was angry...
Maybe because I thought I had to be.
Or maybe because I was sad.
But he still wanted to be with me,
I still wanted to be with him.
So what happened?
We stayed together -
- had the best year of our relationship.
And then?
He died.
I'm sorry.
Do you want anything to drink?
No, I'm fine.
Do you think you still would have been with him?
Yeah, definitely.
And I think I'd still be here, attracted to you.
You'd never guess what I was upset about
this morning.
Michael had a work think last night
that we went to -
- and I was accusing him of being
attracted to this woman he's working with.
Was he?
I think so.
You think there's something going on?
It could be.
I think he'd want that to be.
He's in Philadelphia with her right now.
Are you worried?
I think I make too big a deal out of it.
Why?
It's 2:00 in the morning and
I'm here with you.
So when you think you could get up and have
absolutely no idea what a day will go?
Eighty...
Ninery, a thousand years back
without incident -
- and then all of a sudden...
Hello!
What if I hadn't come up for coffee
this morning?
I would have called.
If my number changed?
I would have come upstairs.
What about Michael?
Why did you stop e-mailing me?
Because it wasn't enough...
Do you know how often I have to make a choice,
not to write.
"Hello, Alex. How are you?".
"Where are you? What are you doing?".
"Do you want to meet me?
Whatever".
"This Friday for dinner?"
"Just to catch up".
You really touch me whenever you feel like,
don't you?
No, I don't.
I touch you a fraction of how
often I'd like to.
Why?
Because I like you.
I can't.
I can't do anymore,
and look him in the eye.
You just told me he's away with a woman
you got upset about.
Michael isn't doing anything...
I never told him about us.
Even when -
- I found the need to confess something.
Which is when?
When I'm drunk, or happy -
- or after a fight, or in the middle of one -
- when things slip out, this never does.
Why?
Would he be angry?
He'd have no right to be.
I gave you up.
So what's Helen like?
We have another couple of hours -
- I don't want to spend them talking
about Helen.
Come...
Jo...
Come here...
What time is it?
Six thirty.
Laura...
Michael, I don't need us to talk about it.
Last night...
Michael, please.
Just don't.
I didn't think that would happen.
Not even a second time?
Well there's so much going on
right now, isn't it?
What I wouldn't give to have tired
of you.
Let me drop you off.
No, I'd rather walk.
Are you sure?
Yes, it would be good for her.
It would be good for me.
Let's not do this in a big way, ok?
Please.
See ya!
It's possible I overreacted.
I know that. I know you.
And I love you.
Jo.
Hey Andy, it's me.
I need you to cover for me.
Hey.
Are you ready?
Yeah. Where's Michael?
He had to go back to New York.
Is everything ok?
Yeah, he left me a voicemail.
I guess, Stuart needed him
to go back.
Okay...
I'll see you out front.
Joey...
What are you doing back?
What's Lucy doing here?
We got locked out of Andy's.
Who?
Me and Lucy.
When?
Last night, when I went out to walk her.
You've been crying, Jo?
A bit.
What are you doing back?
We finished up early.
Thought the presentation was today?
No, we finished up early.
I'm sorry about our fight.
Yeah, so am I.
Let's not talk about it, okay?
Let's have a great lunch, let's walk.
Let's make a day of it.
Okay.
Does she want to go out?
Probably.
I'll take her.
Come on.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I love you.
- English subtitles by -
- spyk & marilita -