- Come on.
- Central Security Agency.
This is Wallace.
Operation Big Drip
is cresting Level Two.
I need Devlin.
I need him now.
Hold, please.
No, no, don't put me on hold!
Mother...
Hello, Agent Wallace.
I need your nine-digit
security code, please.
Hello? Agent Wallace?
Agent Wallace?
Agua la vista... baby.
Hello, my name's Jimmy Tong
and I was wondering
if there's anything I could say
that would convince you
to have lunch with me.
Oh, Jimmy, you're so cute.
Let's go back to your apartment
and make like... donkey.
You got me nervous again.
It's just a salesgirl.
To you... but to me...
I dream of her
before I ever saw her.
No, that there! That!
Shh.
That is the line.
Go tell her that. That line.
Listen.
Hi.
My name is Jimmy Tong.
When I see you,
I have a wet dream.
Is that what I say?
No, no, you know...
just ask her out to lunch now
and later,
we work out that line.
But hurry up, man.
We be wasting time, man.
Come on. We have to drive.
And whatever you do,
do not be yourself.
Just joking.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome. Good-bye.
I can do it.
Hi. My name's Jimmy Tong.
Okay...
Hi.
Pretty colors.
Will you excuse me
for just one moment?
Okay.
Ah...
Just between us guys...
you don't come around
here for the art, do you?
Who would?
Heh. Yeah.
Uh... let me,
as owner of this gallery
give you a little bit
of friendly advice.
Don't waste any time.
You go over there and
you ask Jennifer out.
You think so?
Yes. That way, she can say no
and we can get on
with our little lives.
Thank you for your advice.
Yeah.
Hello. My name Jimmy Tong.
What can I say to convince you
to have lunch with me?
Oh!
I'm sorry. Are you hurt?
I'm terr... I didn't...
Come here, you little runt.
Hi. Hello.
Get back here! Come here!
Where'd you go?
Where are you?
Sauer... sauerkraut
or sauercrop?
Sauerkraut?
Hey... hey, hey!
Hey! I just washed that car.
What the hell
wrong with you, boy?
Want I jam this in your ass
and break it?
You want a go? Come down here.
Whoa, whoa, wait, oh.
Not too fast.
Hey, I just want to talk.
Eh, eh, you do that
there, man. You do that.
Oh, you're scared now.
Just-just go
and get yourself
some training wheels!
Go get a tattoo of a chicken!
- Go!
- I thought all your people know karate.
Not everybody Chinese
is Bruce Lee.
Just calm yourself, eh,
Jimmy, calm yourself.
Just not my day.
Whoo! Wow.
Do you think you can get me
to 70 Fleming Street?
Of course. Wait a second.
You Jimmy Tong?
That's who I am.
Who are you?
The name is Steena.
So, how come you drive so fast?
More fares.
Mmm. Is that why
you had your license
suspended nine times
for speeding?
But no accidents.
Do you remember where I'm going?
70 Fleming.
Get me there before
I finish putting on my makeup
and I'll, uh, double the meter.
You serious?
Do I look like
I have a sense of humor?
Okay.
Hurry, open the gate!
Hey, Jimmy... ho, ho, ho, ho!
LAZY ASS! OPEN THE GATES!
I'M ON MY COFFEE BREAK.
SHUT UP, OLD MAN!
IT'S JIMMY, YOU FOOL!
DON'T RUN OVER THE CHICKENS!
You drive too fast!
Yeah, I got mascara
and eyeliner left.
You got five blocks.
Don't tell me
you're slowing down.
You know, you drive like
an old woman.
Hmm.
You're not scared, are you?
Hey, you!
What do you think you're doing?
Back off, buddy.
She's mine.
Oh, it's you, miss.
Well, you lived up
to your reputation.
The job is yours.
I have a job. A good one.
Oh, yeah? How much do you
make at this "good job"?
$475 a week, plus tips.
So how would you like to make
$2,000 a week
plus room and board?
When do I show up?
Tomorrow morning, 7:00 a.m.
You'll be driving
Clark Devlin, Mr. Tong.
Good day, miss.
Now, you!
Out of here!
Good morning, Mr. Tong.
Huh.
You put your face on
without me, huh?
Please have a seat.
Those are the house rules.
Memorize them.
Especially number one.
"Never talk directly
to Mr. Devlin."
If you have any questions
you'll find
all the answers in there.
And, if I were you, I'd get rid
of the mildew on the chin.
My soul patch?
Uh, yeah.
You like working
for this Devlin guy?
I don't work for him.
I'm not a professional driver,
but I'd always believed
that thing you're staring
into is designed
for the monitoring of traffic,
not passengers.
Am I wrong?
While I'm really enjoying
our time together
shall we try moving?
Wallace has been my partner for years.
Something's happened to him.
He wouldn't just disappear.
Now, you get your job done
and find my partner.
So tell me how.
You're the head
of an intelligence agency.
Why don't you be intelligent?
I don't understand
what you're talking about.
Well, why don't you call me back
when you do understand
what I'm talking about.
Did we just take
the Balsam Road exit?
Of course.
You have to take
the surface street.
Sorry.
Did you get a copy
of the rules?
Did you read them?
Jimmy, let me tell you
something, my friend...
I hate the rules.
Take Grant Boulevard
all the way.
The lights are timed.
Thank you.
And, Jimmy...
crank the music up.
Yes, sir.
C.S.A. HEADQUARTERS
Deputy Director Chalmers,
ladies, gentlemen
I present to you
Special Agent Wallace.
Deceased two days, 14 hours,
five minutes... approximately.
Pretty interesting.
Now, why don't you, uh,
tell me a little about him?
Well, in simplest terms,
he drowned in his bathtub.
Contusion here suggests
he hit his head
fell prone, unconscious.
The man infiltrated
a Serbian death squad
with not even a scratch.
He goes down in a bathtub?
Life's a bitch.
You want to put him
back in the fridge?
He didn't drown, sir.
He was murdered.
Does that make life
a little less bitchy?
And-and you would be?
That's Del Blaine, sir.
She's having a filter installed
between her brain and mouth
next week.
So you don't think he drowned?
Well, sir, there was water
in his lungs
but the pulmonary vein
was filled with
collapsed platelets
indicative of dehydration.
He died of thirst.
Thirst.
And it wasn't just
city tap water.
The mineral profile fit
a high-end bottled water
but what was really weird
is that
it contained a strain
of bacteria that I, so far
haven't been able to culture.
Anyway, uh... didn't
mean to interrupt.
Ooh, the woman seems to know
a lot about water.
Yeah. She thinks she knows
a lot about a lot of things.
You know, we have a special
situation in the field.
I think we could use
your talents.
You interested?
When do I start?
You ever hear of Clark Devlin?
Rumors and innuendo.
Del, I could tell you
a thing or two
about Clark Devlin.
Uh, you think we
could keep our minds
out of the gutter
for about a second?
Meet me upstairs
in an hour.
You might just become
Clark Devlin's next partner.
I'm going to need
that Gerris marginalis
as soon as possible.
Yes. My contacts in Guatemala
have what you're looking for,
I'm sure.
Good.
And, meanwhile...
I'll take one of these
beautiful Uticella marginalis.
Just gorgeous.
Now, you're going to call me?
Is your phone number on file?
I'm having a bit of trouble
with the phones at the moment.
It might be better
if you dropped it off yourself.
It may take a while.
Well, why don't you
familiarize yourself
with the route?
There's a little gathering
at my house tonight...
a fund-raiser for
the Natural History Museum.
I would so love to have you.
Should I send a car?
I drive myself.
Admirable.
Eight o'clock.
And, uh, be sure
not to wear anything
too distracting, or no one
will get their checkbooks out.
How did you learn
to be so smooth?
I've seen the way you drive.
And the same instincts I do.
You lack confidence.
The girl in the art gallery's
not beyond you, you know.
You know about her?
Every time we leave the house
we go by the art gallery
and slow down.
You just need a little polish.
I'll never be a Clark Devlin.
Don't tell anyone this, Jimmy,
but there's a lot less
to Clark Devlin
than meets the eye.
I've got a couple of good lines
and a couple of
very expensive suits.
Apart from that,
we're exactly the same.
How about
a couple hundred million?
Trust me...
90% of it is clothes.
The other ten percent?
The other ten percent's
in there.
You've got plenty of it.
Oh, Mr. Devlin,
can I ask you a big favor?
Yeah?
Can I stop wearing my hat?
All right.
Thank you.
No, just stay smooth.
Remember... smooth.
Thank you.
Steena, Devlin.
This driver, this Jimmy,
I like him.
Let's get him a proper suit.
Something sexy. You pick it out.
All right.
Always a delight
talking to you, too, darling.
Home, James.
Absolutely, Mr. Devlin.
Oh!
Oops.
Watch your step.
Thank you, sir.
Oh...
This definitely not a rental.
Hello.
My name's Clark Devlin.
Would you like to dance?
Admirable.
There is just one rule.
Never touch my tuxedo.
I didn't.
Good.
Don't.
Yes, sir.
Jimmy.
Get the car.
Let's go for dinner.
Yes, sir.
What'll you have? It's my treat.
Anything.
All right.
Two Whoppers,
hold the onion, extra ketchup.
Toast the bottom bun only,
medium well-done.
Two large fries,
extra well-done.
Two chocolate milkshakes,
however the chef likes.
That's it.
Your order's ready.
Pull forward.
That's pretty quick.
It's fast food. Anything else?
Yeah.
I'll have a personal pizza,
crispy crust.
He doesn't eat out much.
They don't serve pizza
at Burger...
New item, huh?
Do you have chicken chow mein?
Thank you.
- Jimmy?
- Yes?
It's a drive-through.
Let's drive.
Watch out!
Watch it, man!
Sorry, pal.
Let's go.
Why are we running away
from a skateboard?
I think it's probably a bomb.
I thought you said a bomb.
What do you mean, a bomb?
No good. Out!
Mr. Dev...
Move!
Jimmy, you okay?
I'm fine.
You okay, boss?
Yeah.
Yeah, all in a day's work, eh?
Look.
Oh, damn.
Mr. Devlin.
You got any aspirin?
Who did this to you?
Water stri...
Walter Strider... he's the one?
Wat... er... stri...
Walter... Walter Strider.
No... no police.
Okay. Uh...
I need an ambulance right now.
His name is...
Trust nobody.
Uh... his name is...
Brad Dillford.
Wear it.
Wear...
Boss! Boss!
Hold on, boss. You'll be fine.
Give me the clipboard.
I'll take care of you.
Wa...
stri...
- Huh?
- Sir!
Oh!
Please wait in the waiting room.
Okay.
I will find Walter Strider.
Hey! Hey!
Huh? I'm sorry.
I promise.
What do you want
my mother's maiden name for?
Last time she was
in here, I was born.
I'm sure my dad had something
to do with it
at least I hope so.
Dr. Angela.
Where is Dr. Angelo?
Dr. Angelo.
Are you Dr. Angela?
Dr. Angela.
Dr. Ang... ela.
Hey!
There's no smoking
in a hospital.
I was nervous. How is he?
He might be here a while.
You might want to get him
some things from home
in case he comes to.
Oh.
He had this clutched
in his hand.
I don't know
if it means anything.
"Orderly with wheels
to the front desk."
I do need Dr. Angelo.
Dr. Angelo.
Dr. Angelo is on holiday today.
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah.
BANNING, INC.,
FLOATING HEADQUARTERS
I'll tell you,
I'm pretty excited.
I mean, nervous,
but I'm excited.
I'm pumped, you know.
I knew I was doing good work
for Banning International
but I didn't know Mr. Banning
would be taking so much notice
of me so soon.
I'll say this, though,
when I'm CEO of this place
I won't be having
my headquarters
in the bottom of a boat,
you know what I mean?
Why did you choose Mr. Lundeen?
He questioned my growth projections.
No, that's not it.
I don't like his hair.
Mr. Banning.
So, word filtered
down to me
that you don't share my optimism
about our company's future.
Oh, no.
Actually, I just...
Drink?
Oh, yes, thank you.
I just felt that to meet
your projections, pretty much
every person on Earth
would have to drink
only Banning Springs water.
Yes, indeed.
Water, Mr. Lundeen,
comprises 60% of your body.
Don't you find it incredible
that two hydrogen atoms
and an oxygen atom can combine
to create something
so beautiful
so useful, so essential?
I find water to be
miraculous.
Do you think I'm silly?
Not at all.
Feeling thirsty?
Yes.
You're helping me out
by being a guinea pig
for a new product.
Oh, I see.
What a brilliant idea.
Water that makes you thirsty.
What's in it?
Salt?
There's no profundity in salt.
Bacteria.
Once ingested
its DNA will instruct
your cells' cytoplasm
to spill electrolytes
into your bloodstream
causing dehydration.
It's virulent
but, unfortunately,
it's too fast.
Way too fast.
As we speak, your internal
organs are shriveling.
You're becoming as dry as...
Well, as dry
as your limited imagination.
Gentlemen,
fetch the vacuum, won't you?
Thank you.
Schiffer, Schwartzkopf,
Sondheim, Springsteen...
No Strider.
Wow.
Welcome to the Tactical Uniform
Experiment.
Tuxedo recognizing new user.
Mapping user's
neurological structure.
Activate wristwatch
for desired function.
Demo...
Okay, show me.
Uh-oh.
Caution... demolition mode.
The Tuxedo will consider
any object a target
and act to destroy it.
Oh, what's happening?
Exit the demolition mode
immediately.
Mr. Devlin, is everything
all right?
This is Jimmy.
I think Mr. Devlin wants you
to clean his room tomorrow.
It's a little bit messy.
I think he threw the party.
Should I send someone up now?
No. Maybe after he leaves.
Very good.
Hmm?
Hello?
Are we on?
Are we on what?
C.S.A. OPERATIONS
I take my work seriously,
Mr. Devlin, so please
stop using
that ridiculous accent.
What?
What accent?
All right.
You're the senior officer.
I'll play it however you want.
Deitrich Banning is holding
a meeting with water CEOs.
The Agency wants us to find out
what he's planning.
Wh-What about Walter Strider?
Who is he?
I don't know. You tell me.
Okay.
So, we will meet tomorrow.
V-15, 10:00.
I'll be wearing a gray suit.
Your code is "nice rack."
I'll respond
"I forgot my bra."
That passes
for humor around here.
10:00, V-15.
What's the cross street?
Very funny.
May I join you?
Uh, yeah.
Nice rack.
Hello.
Mr. Devlin, there's been
a change of plans.
But I'm here already.
Where are you?
Don't get all pissy about it.
They just told me,
so I'm telling you.
We'll meet tonight
8:00, Pier 17,
base of the silo and...
forget the password.
Oh, now you tell me.
Oh, hey, there he is.
Oh, my God, that's him.
I got to go.
Guy in the raincoat. Get him!
I see you tonight. Sorry.
Stop!
Get back here, you creep!
So, we've got five minutes
to get into position.
I secured the rooftop.
The equipment's good to go
and I just have to say
it is such an honor to be
working with the legendary...
Clark Devlin?
I'm Del Blaine.
Have we met before?
No.
Good.
Okay, Del Blaine, let's do
what we've come here to do.
I'll follow you.
Ladies first.
Okay.
A couple of details changed
from what was in the file.
You read it?
The files are crap.
Give me the
short version.
Deitrich Banning's
holding a meeting
of international
water company CEOs.
We think he's trying
to force them
into selling
their companies to him.
Where are you going?
Huh?
I'm thinking.
We had Agent Wallace
working undercover
at his bottled water factory.
That is, until last week.
Wallace calls us
on his cell phone
to tell us that the operation
had reached critical mass
and, suddenly, wham! Dead.
As you requested, a Klineholtz
bolt-action nine-millimeter
titanium folding stock with
20-time infrared sniper-scope
and counterweighted
micro-rifled barrel.
My favorite gun.
But I don't kill
people anymore.
Killing?
You're planting a bug.
It was all in that "crap" file.
Go look through your binoculars.
They're arriving.
Ready?
It's critical we get
a listening device
in Banning's meeting.
Range... 962 feet.
Aim for the briefcase.
Should be a piece
of cake for you, sir.
You kind of missed.
In the year 2001
$35 billion worth of bottled
water was consumed worldwide.
Today, bottled water costs more
per gallon than gasoline.
We, my friends,
are the new oil barons.
We at Banning Springs
have developed
a new filtration process
that would protect your assets
against the biological holocaust
that's coming.
Looks like we got company.
CSA would be my bet.
You've heard what I have to say.
Now I'd like to hear you.
How much is this plan
going to cost us?
It won't cost you a penny,
out of pocket.
All I ask is to become
your slightly-more-
than-equal partner.
Banning says he's got
the only process
to make their water safe.
But to use it,
they've got to give him
half of their companies?
He's trying to muscle
these guys
into selling
their companies to him.
Banning says that their
water sources are in danger.
Something about everyone
being defenseless
against more deadly
forms of bacteria.
I can barely make out
what he's saying.
Do you want to listen to this?
What do you think
that means, sir?
Del Blaine!
Yeah, I'll be there
in a minute.
Yeah, I'd really like
some help up here, sir.
Del Blaine!
Do you hear me, sir?
I know this is not
near as exciting
as most of your missions,
but could you humor me
with just a little
professionalism?
I would really
love some help...
What are you doing?
What's with the jumpy-jumpy?
Take off your headphones!
- What?
- Your headphones!
Okay, Chapter Six
of the training manual.
Unarmed assailant...
frontal attack.
Begin!
Stomach, head! Stomach, head!
God!
What's my name?!
Yeah!
You okay?
Oh! Where the hell
have you been?!
Stop pushing!
Aah, my hand!
Whoa!
Yeah! Not bad.
Sir?!
Sir, are you okay, sir?
Don't let go! Don't!
No, no, no, let go!
You're-you're-you're ripping...
my sl-sleeve! You-you...
No, no. No, not, not my...
Sir!
My ring.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my... Oh!
This was not...
part of the plan.
Del Blaine?
Del...
Confidence.
Nice of you, moron.
Not in the manual.
Creep!
Del Blaine! Stop!
Get off of me!
Why didn't you stop?
God, what the hell
is wrong with you?!
How do you...
fall off a building
and end up... uh...
You okay?
Would you stop that?
It's okay.
I am in the car
with a psychopath.
We are not safe.
Are you upset?
Why would I be upset?
I've always wanted
to begin and end my career
with a big fat failure!
Thank you very much, Mr. Devlin.
It's my first time.
I mean... every mission
is like my first time.
It's so difficult
being Clark Devlin.
Oh.
Sorry.
Aah!
I didn't do that.
What...
i-is wrong with you?!
I'm not who you think I am.
Stay away!
I'm a little over-amped
myself right now.
Let's just call it a day.
Get some rest and medication.
What?
We'll be in communication.
Oh.
I don't have your phone number!
C.S.A. TARGET RANGE
Who am I kidding?
I have no idea what I'm doing
or why I'm doing it.
I felt the same way
when I took my first
field assignment.
Then I met Clark Devlin
and life just got
a whole lot better...
and a little more complicated.
Let's, uh, can we get
a close... can we...?
How do we pan down...
Yeah. Just hit the
second button there.
DEL:
Everybody warned me,
he was unorthodox
but he's way irrational,
bordering on nutso.
We'll just get, uh... That's it.
There, yeah. That's it, there.
Look at that.
Move it over, over just a bit.
He's getting under your skin,
isn't he?
He got under my skin once
and I'm still feeling it.
Yeah, you told me.
What about his English?
Oh, I can never understand
half of what he says
but don't you just love
his accent?
She can't hear
anything from here...?
No, I don't think... Whoa!
God, I wish I was
still back in the field.
How do you like me now?
She's got issues, man.
Holy...
Can your, uh, can your
girlfriend shoot, uh...
A groin out of a target?
Let's go.
Let's get our nails done.
Okay.
Have a nice day, boys.
"Dr. Angelo, Dr. Angelo..."
They ran out of "Get well soon."
You said to wear this,
but I don't know.
Being Clark Devlin is not easy.
Hello.
So, Mr. Devlin
how are you feeling today?
Not so good, I'm afraid.
Well, you've got a few hours
to pull yourself together.
What do you mean?
After the fiasco
of planting the bug
I'd say we have
only one choice:
Level One surveillance.
In other words...
Infiltration.
Banning's going to be at
the Lanford Hotel tonight
entertaining three
of his new partners.
Chalmers has agreed to...
get us at the next table.
Is this a black-tie event?
No. But I'm sure you'll
wear whatever you want.
Maybe we can find
Walter Strider.
Meet you there at 8:00.
Water... strider...
What?
Water...
Mr. Clark Devlin.
Stri... der...
What are you doing?
Huh?
Uh, he needs help.
Security! Security!
Del Blaine.
Hey.
I know how partial you are
to that monkey suit of yours
so I got gussied up.
Good job. You gussy very well.
Oh, and here's a little
something for you.
Hmm?
Oh.
Thank you.
Sorry, I don't have
anything for you.
It's a video camera.
Shh. Act normal.
We don't want everybody to know.
Sorry.
Good evening.
Uh, name, please.
Name?
Um...
Lincoln.
Washington.
You're a billionaire
and you try to grease
the guy with seven bucks?
You think I have money
to throw away?
You on the list?
Perfect.
Let me talk to him.
No. You know what,
we'll do this my way.
I've got a T-135
disorientation module.
You just stand there.
Hi. Could you...
hold this for me?
Aw, thanks.
Now, where did I put
those tickets?
What's happening, Snowman?
What's happening?
Hey... what's happening?
Oh, hey.
I can't believe it.
James Brown.
The Godfather of Soul.
- What's happening?
- Hello.
Mr. Brown.
Forgive us for bothering you.
We came to see your show and...
Yeah, she forgot
to make reservations.
Don't worry about it.
I can get tickets
for the front row for you.
Oh, thank you very much,
Mr. Brown.
See? The things work out.
There's one more thing
I'd like to say, um...
It's not the in thing today
to give compliments
to a young lady
but I just got
to let you know that...
you got a nice rack.
Oh, thank you, Mr. Brown.
Enjoy the show.
What...
is wrong with you?!
He f-fell down by himself.
You killed James Brown.
No, he's fine.
He's not fine.
And Banning is going to leave.
Don't panic.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Are you... praying?
Miss Cleo told me
this would happen.
$4.99-a-minute Miss Cleo?
Just go out and tell them
Mr. Brown is not here.
There will be another act.
Nice to meet you.
And right about now,
it is style time!
If you will,
ladies and gentlemen
introducing the hardest-working
man in show business
ladies and gentlemen,
Mr. Dynamite...
James Brown!
Uh, l-ladies and gentleman...
What's going on?!
Mr. James Brown will not be
appearing tonight...
due to unforeseen circumstances
but stay right where you are
because the Lanford Hotel is
really proud to present
the Last Emperor of Soul.
And, um, well, here he is.
Hi.
Hi, everybody. Good evening.
How are you tonight?!
Go home!
Who wants to get funky tonight?!
Go ahead and make it funky.
Yeah.