And by the way, honey,
with all this décolletage
you should be getting
a lot more dickoletage
than what he has to offer.
And as I can recall it,
you were the one that told me
that when he came,
it was as thin
as coconut water.
Honey, that's
a dealbreaker for me.
It was that thin.
Well, I see we 're settling
for less nowadays.
That's beyond.
Mrs. Morrow,
a package arrived for you.
I found it in the mailbox
this morning.
May I ask you who you'd like
on duty this weekend?
Um, actually, why don't
you give everybody
the weekend off?
Are you sure?
Yeah, yeah.
We might go to
the beach house and, uh,
if not, it might be nice
to have a weekend alone.
I'll let everyone know.
Thank you.
Oh, damn it.
- Christopher?
- Yes?
I'm sorry. Can you
help me open this?
I just got a paper cut.
Yeah, of course.
Here, let me do it.
Thank you.
Yeah, yeah.
I just... A paper cut.
There's a note.
You can read it.
"Dear Susan, I've written
a novel that will be
published in the spring.
"It's different from
the kind of things
that I was writing
"when we were together."
Go ahead.
"In the end you left me
with the inspiration
thatlneeded
"to write from the heart.
"I wanted you to be
the first to read it,
so I'm sending along a proof.
"I will be in LA until
Wednesday on business
"and it would be good
to see you after so long.
"My cell number
and email address
are below. Edward."
Thanks.
Morning.
Good morning.
What's that?
It's a manuscript
Edward sent me.
He wrote a novel.
Edward who?
Edward, my first husband.
You remember him.
I didn't know he could write.
Yes, you did.
He was writing a novel
when you and I got together.
You just don't remember.
Have you guys even talked
in 20 years?
19.
No. I tried calling him
a couple of years back,
but he hung up on me.
I think he's teaching English
at some prep school in Dallas.
It's sad, really.
He never remarried.
Where were you
last night? You didn't
come by the gallery.
I'm sorry. Really, I...
By the time I left
the office, I was late
for my dinner and...
It would have
taken you 15 minutes.
Fifteen minutes, and it would
have meant a lot to me.
Never mind.
You didn't come
to bed last night.
I didn't wanna wake you.
Yeah.
Well, I wasn't asleep.
I was too wound up
from the opening.
It went well, by the way.
Apparently.
Good.
Yeah.
Look, why don't you and I
go to the beach?
We can go tonight
and come back on Monday.
Maybe if we
just spent some time,
just the two of us?
Why are you wearing
this blazer on a Saturday?
Because I gotta
go back to the office,
and then I gotta go
to the airport, and then
I gotta go back to New York.
You just came from there.
Yes, I know.
But I have to go again
if I wanna get this deal done,
and I don't wanna have to sell
anything else.
Shit.
It's okay.
You know,
the strange thing is is,
I don't really care
about all this art.
That doesn't sound like you.
I know, but it's true.
I care.
It pisses me off.
I know you do.
Don't worry,
I can fill the walls
with some new LA artists
and people will think
we're ahead of the curve
instead of going broke.
You won't have
to be embarrassed.
Are things a little better?
He's just having a hard time
with his business right now.
Carlos told me.
I'm surprised. I thought
we were hiding it pretty well.
Hutton would be very upset
to find out anybody knew.
He just hates not to win.
Are you sleeping?
Did you call my
psychopharmacologist?
Did you call him?
You should call him,
because he's a genius.
I'm worried
about you, seriously.
Just look at me for a second.
Look at me.
You scared me
the last time we talked.
I'm fine.
I am fine. lam...
lam. I just can't believe
that I told you
all of those things.
I'm just kind of
embarrassed, you know.
Because what right
do I have to not be happy?
I have everything.
I feel ungrateful
not to be happy.
As much right
as anyone, Susan,
as much right as anyone,
because it's all relative.
You're just awfully hard
on yourself.
How do you do it?
You mean with Carlos?
I just... It's...
I'm totally cool with it.
And having a gay husband
is not such a bad thing,
you know?
We're best friends.
We love each other completely.
I'm certainly
the only woman in his life.
And that lasts
longer than lust, doesn't it?
It's forever, really.
Hutton and I don't have that.
Did you ever?
I think we just
want different things,
or I want different things.
Do you still love him?
I'm being summoned. Pardon me.
He has to catch a plane.
I'm gonna say goodbye.
I hope this deal
works out for you.
I really do.
I know you need it.
We need this.
No. You need this.
Bye.
So I said,
"Well, my mother
always told me
"if you massage your pussy
with Pam cooking spray
"a month before
the baby comes,
"you don't need
vaginal rejuvenation."
I've gotta get some Pam.
And she is going to get
a nomination this year.
A nomination? She's gonna win.
Let's talk about your opening.
My favorite subject.
Not mine.
The opening was
spectacular last night.
Really?
That's what you thought?
What, you didn't?
No.
I thought the work
was incredibly strong.
So perfect with
all this junk culture
that we live in.
It'sjunk. It isjunk.
Total junk.
Darling, you are
a big success.
No one really likes
what they do.
Then why do we do it?
Because we're driven.
Maybe a bit insecure.
We get into things
when we're young
and because we think
they mean something.
And then
we find out that they don't.
Oh, Susan, enjoy
the absurdity of our world.
It's a lot less painful.
And believe me, our world
is a lot less painful
than the real world.
Yeah, why are we driving
this old thing to Marfa?
Becauseljusthadit
completely rebuilt.
It's a classic.
It has a terrible
sound system.
Well, you're gonna have
to suffer through that.
You have two sets
of boots, India?
Do we really
have to stop tonight?
I'd rather just get there.
All right, ask your mother.
She's the boss.
I set the alarm.
India, you've been
on that thing for hours.
I thought you were
the one who wanted
to drive all night.
I did, but what are we
supposed to do, sing
campfire songs or something?
- How much longer?
- I don't know.
Like three,
three and a half hours.
Well, Dad,
you're gonna get your wish.
My cell service just went out.
Jesus, can you believe
there's no service here?
How is that even possible?
Two of the things
I love most about west Texas,
no phones and no people.
Oh, come on.
Total jerks.
Are we rid of them?
India, don't do that.
What?
What? What'd she do?
She just gave 'em the finger.
Mom. Mom, I'm scared.
Tony.
Speed up.
It's all right,
it's all right.
No, I don't like this.
It's all right.
Speed up. Tony.
Shit. Oh, good.
Just let 'em go. Let 'em go.
India, don't look at them.
But, they're...
Just don't give
them any reason.
Why is he smiling like that?
I don't know,
sweetheart. It's all right.
It's all right.
Wh00!
He's crazy.
- Oh, my God.
Shit.
Hey, motherfucker, pull over.
Pull the fuck over!
Oh, God, Tony.
India. ls your phone
working yet, India?
No, no, but I took down
the license number.
No.
Oh, n0.
Pull over.
Pull the fuck over!
Dad. Dad.
Hey, asshole, pull over.
Pull over.
Oh, no.
What do you
want from us?
Easy, easy. Easy, easy!
Stop it!
Shit.
Hey, come on!
Don't worry, honey. It's okay.
They probably
have a gun.
Please, Tony, pull out.
I can't move.
He's blocked the car.
What's he doing?
It's okay.
Don't get out the car.
I'm not getting
out of the car, sweetheart.
Good evening.
You know you're supposed
to stop when there's
an accident, right?
Yeah, I know that.
Why didn't you stop, then?
That won't work.
No signal here.
You're not supposed to leave
the scene cf an accident.
It's a crime.
After the way
you were driving...
I'm sorry, what'd you say?
Just the way you were
driving was crazy.
Hey, Turk.
Don't come any closer.
All right, sweetheart.
It's all right.
You know, pleasejust
get back in your car now
and leave us alone.
Calm down. We got
an accident to report,
that's all.
Calm down.
Hey, lady, lady, lady.
It's a flashlight, sweetheart.
It's just a flashlight.
It's all right.
Jesus Christ.
Okay, so let's
exchange information.
Information?
Yeah.
Let's exchange information.
Get it out of
the glove compartment.
Okay, I'm a Gemini.
My favorite c:olor's
pale pink.
I like long walks and kittens.
We should... You know what?
We should call the police.
Oh, oh? Really?
Yeah. Yeah.
That's a great idea.
It was your
fucking fault, right?
What?
It doesn't matter
whose fault it was.
Let's get going.
Hey, Ray, these guys
have got a flat tire.
They sure do.
Well, what do you know?
What'd he say?
Don't believe it, Dad.
- He said we had a flat tire.
- What did he say?
Don't believe him.
We don't have a flat.
What?
Yep, your left tire's flat.
It sure is.
Must have bust it when
you were shoving us
off the road.
We did not shove you
You shoved us off the road.
It's a lie.
You think I'm a liar?
It's okay. It's okay.
She'sjust a child.
You think I'm a liar?
No, she's not
saying that, man.
She's just a child.
You don't got a flat,
go on, drive.
Start the engine and drive.
Please drive. Just drive.
Just drive on it,
asshole. Nobody's
stopping you. Drive away.
Go. Fuck off.
Stupid motherfucker.
- Shit. God damn it!
- Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, God.
It's okay. It's all right.
It's not okay.
We're in the middle
of nowhere.
What are we gonna do, Tony?
What are we gonna do?
I tell you what.
We'll fix it for you,
won't we, guys?
Yeah, sure.
Really?
Yeah.
Just to show you we're okay,
we'll fix it for you.
You won't have to do a thing.
Then we'll go
to the cops together, right?
You and me,
report your accident.
All right.
Thank you.
Sound good?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
- You got tools, mister?
- Um, lactually, I...
No need. Use ours.
Come on, let's get going.
No, it's fine,
it's just fine.
I can't fix a tire,
so I can't...
I need their help.
Please don't make
eye contact with them.
You got a spare tire, man?
Can't change a tire
without a spare.
You wanna give me
the keys to the trunk?
No,don1.
Vvhothefuck
do you think you are'?
Just pop the trunk, honey.
I got it.
That's all right, I got that.
That's fine.
It's right underneath here.
There you go.
Just right under there.
Just got a lot
of things in here.
It's just right under there.
Sorry.
Get the women
out of the car.
Come on, get 'em out.
Come on, man.
Gotta lift your car up
on the jack, so get 'em out.
Dude. Has he gotta lift
your wife and your child
and the car?
Right, right.
Get your women out the car.
It's all right, honey.
Just get out of the car.
They need to fix the car.
They're fine.
They're just fixing the tire.
Come over here.
Come on, here.
Have you seen
what you did to my car?
You think you're fucking
hotshH,don%you?
What are you talking about?
They definitely think
they're fucking hot shit.
Who?
Are you serious?
Your bitches, man.
Who else?
TCDNYI LOOK...
No, you think you're
so special, you can just
bump another guy's oar...
No, we were just trying
to get... You were playing
some kind of crazy game.
Hey!
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, God.
Oh, my...
There goes your cops.
You should have tried harder
to stop 'em.
That's okay. It's okay.
We'll take good care of you.
Fucking bitch.
Uppity rich bitch.
I'll teach you
a fucking thing or two.
It's okay.
What? What you looking at?
Hotshot.
What do you mean?
What are you trying
to do there on the road, huh?
What? I...
What are you talking about?
Look, look, look...
We... We are... We are
just trying to get where...
Where we are going.
Where's that?
I said where you going?
To Marfa.
What exactly is in Marfa?
Hey, motherfucker...
Hey!
Leave my
dad alone, asshole!
Leave me alone, man.
Fuck you, baby.
She didn't mean that.
She's just a kid.
Your daddy won't tell me,
so why don't you?
Let me go!
What's it to you anyway?
Look, we're nice guys.
Don't touch my daughter!
We're just trying to get
to where we're going.
You wanna dance? Wanna dance?
Oh, is that it? That all?
Baby, look at your daddy.
He thinks he's so much
better than me, huh?
What do you think?
Well, he is.
I mean, seriously,
look at him.
Let her go!
You're scum, you know!
No! No!
Hey! Hey, get off.
Hey, watch it,
you fucking assholes.
You got no fucking right
talking to me like that.
Christ's sake!
Fixing your goddamn tire.
Let's go and get
the fuck out of here, y'all.
India.
Don't cry, sweetie.
It's fine.
You all right over there?
Need a tissue?
God damn, that looks bad.
You might need...
I'm fine.
Hey, honey, you got a tampon?
Your nose looks like shit.
All right, I'm fine.
I mean it looks like shit.
I'm fine.
This is bad news. We good?
We're good. We're set.
- We're good to go.
- Let's go.
All right.
We're good.
Yeah.
How far up the road
till we can get a signal?
Why do you wanna get
further up the road?
So you can leave the scene
of an accident again?
Leave him alone.
There's service up by Bailey.
All right.
How do you think
we're gonna get there, though?
In our cars.
Which car?
In both cars.
Mister, don't try no fucking
shit with me.
What?
You heard me.
I know what you're doing.
I know what your plan is.
What is the matter?
Don't try no fucking
shit with me.
No, what is the matter, man?
What the fuck
is wrong with you?
How do I know you ain't
just gonna floor the gas
and leave me in the dust?
You get in your oar
and we'll get in ours
and we'll follow you there.
Fuck you! No way.
You go in my car.
What?
You come with us.
Lou can drive your car.
No, I'm not gonna do that. No.
Okay, fine, you drive your car
and the girl comes with us.
- What? No!
- You come with us, baby.
Listen, honey, I ain't
after your fucking ass.
No, don't touch me.
You are not doing that.
Yeah, baby.
You like it like that, huh?
Let me go!
No. Hey, wait!
What are you doing?
Stop!
Get off her, please!
Go over there.
Get your hands off her!
India.
Bye-bye, sweetheart.
I love you.
India...
- Let go of me, please.
- Get your hands off her.
Shit.
India...
Look what
you gone and did.
Hey, hey.
It's okay.
She the boss?
Is she the boss
of your family?
Laura?
Have you got a vagina?
Have you got
a fucking vagina there?
Hey!
- Laura!
- Vagina boy!
Just get her in the car.
Get her in the car.
Vagina boy!
Stay away!
You want fucking
something, boy?
- Tony.
- You want something?
- Laura.
- Get in the car.
- Okay, here we go.
We're goin' in both cars.
Hey, Lou.
No.
Dad.Dad.
Hey!
Hey! Wait! No.
No! Please, no!
No! No! Please...
Susan?
Why didn't you call me
and let me know
you got in safely?
'Cause it's 4:00
in the morning.
I didn't wanna wake you.
If you can't sleep,
why don't you take
one of your pills?
Where are you?
I'm just walking
in the door of the hotel.
What floor, sir?
31, please.
That's not our usual floor.
No, our regular room
wasn't available.
You should have seen
the scene I caused
in the lobby.
I hope you got some sleep
on the plane.
I do worry about you.
Even though you think
that I don't, I do.
You must be exhausted.
I hate that flight.
It's really not...
31, madam.
I'm at my floor.
I gotta run. I'll call you
later, okay? Susan?
Susan, can you hear me?
Yes. Yes, I heard you.
Get some sleep.
You're driving.
Is this the exit?
Exit for what?
Well, for Bailey.
Keep going.
Keep going. Speed up.
What the fuck
are you doing to us?
Here. Turn down here.
No, fuck you.
lam not going down that road.
Listen, mister, you wanna
see your wife and kid?
Then turn down the road.
You gonna cry now?
That's my car we just passed.
It ain't your car, man.
Keep going.
I don't think you need
to worry about
your wife and kid.
Like I say, you don't
need to worry about them.
What do you mean, I don't
need to worry about them?
What the fuck does that mean?
Calm down.
He ain't never killed nobody
yet, that's all I mean.
Least as far
as I know he ain't.
Killed? What are you
talking about, killing?
I said he ain't
killed nobody yet.
If you'd listen to me,
you'd hear what I was saying.
Well, looks like
we've run out of road
and they ain't here.
I wonder if I made a mistake.
It's time for you
to get out now, okay?
Get out!
What are you...
What are you doing?
You'll get killed
if you don't watch it.
Wait.
Wait!
No, wait. Wait, wait, wait!
No! No!
What did you fucking
leave him out here for?
Hey, mister!
Your wife wants you!
Get in the fucking car.
Hey, mister! Your wife!
Mister!
Shit.
Hey.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Hey.
May I use your phone?
Mr. Hastings,
there's no town
near here called Bailey.
I was afraid of that.
There's a motel
across the street.
You got money?
Ihave“.
I have credit cards.
It's still early,
Mr. Hastings.
But we'll call
if we get anything.
All right, thank you.
Hello?
This is Lieutenant Graves.
They found your car
over in a dried-out arroyo
at Topping.
What about my wife
and daughter?
Still no news.
They weren't in the car.
We're turning the case
over to Lieutenant Andes.
He wants to know if he can
pick you up in a few minutes.
Yeah, I'm ready now.
Morning.
Oh, glad to meet you.
I'm Bobby Andes.
I look into things
around here.
You found my car?
They found it in a creek bed.
Tell you what, we take you
back to the house
we picked you up at,
you think you could backtrack
from there?
I could try.
Okay, then, you try. Let's go.
It's my understanding
these fellas didn't have
any guns.
No.
All right.
So let me get this straight,
you say some fella named Lou
just drove you out
into the brush
and left you there?
No, he made me drive.
He made you drive.
And then when you
started to walk out,
you saw 'em coming in again.
Yes.
Hmm. Whose car were they in?
I think itwas mine.
You think?
What makes you think that?
By the look of it
and the sound of it.
It sounded like my oar.
Could you see 'em in the dark?
Not very well.
Did they say anything?
They said,
"Mister, your wife wants you."
You didn't go to 'em.
Why didn't you go to 'em?
I don't know
why I didn't go. I was...
Okay.
Can you take it from here?
Yeah, I came down the highway
and I walked for a long time,
'cause no one stopped for me.
Sergeant, back up slowly
down the shoulder.
Put your signal lights on.
Stop the car.
Stop the car!
I came out of that barbwire
fence right there.
Right by the reflector.
I remember that.
Let's get out and walk.
You said you walked out,
right?
I came up...
I came up right here,
'cause I walked along
that arroyo over there.
This is part
of the old Valdes place.
There's an old cattle station
down that way a bit
next to where
they burn their garbage.
This road leads to it.
Is she all right?
Mom? Is that you?
Is everything all right?
Yeah, yeah,
it's fine. I just wanted
to hear your voice.
I miss you.
You woke me up.
I'm still in bed.
It's Sunday morning, Mom.
Can I call you later?
Yeah. Yeah, call me later.
Go back to bed, sweetheart.
You sound weird. Are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Go back to bed.
I love you.
Me too.
I'll call you later.
Okay.
Edward? Edward?
Hi.
Susan.
Hi. God.
How are you?
It's good to see
someone I know.
It's good to see you.
You look beautiful, as always.
What are you doing
in New York City?
I'm here for an interview
for a scholarship at Columbia.
Columbia?
I thought that you were at
the University of Texas
becoming a great writer.
A great writer? I mean,
I don't... I don't think so.
Well, lam...
But aren't you at Yale
becoming a great artist?
Graduated Yale,
but I'm at Columbia
getting my master's degree.
Oh, wow.
Yeah, art history.
That's great.
Yeah.
Listen, do you know
anybody else in New York?
Just you.
Just me.
Okay, well, would you like
to go to dinner?
Absolutely.
Okay.
Okay, great. Just let me...
Just let me drop off
my packages at my apartment.
All right, do you want me
to grab them for you?
I can hold that.
Yeah, great. Thank you.
Oh... I miss Texas men.
You don't have blizzards
like this in Texas.
No, you don't.
You know that you
were my first crush
when we were at Hastings?
I only spent so muoh time
around your brother
just to be around you.
Well, you were
his first crush.
What?
Yeah.
Well, I had no idea
Cooper was gay.
I don't think
he knew back then,
but he was obsessed with you.
Mmm.
Wow.
Yeah.
If I hadn't caught you
staring at me so much,
I would have thought
you were sleeping with him.
I, actually...
I feel terrible.
I haven't called him
in a few years.
IfeelHke
I've been a bad friend.
I hope I didn't hurt him.
You're good, you know that?
No, you are. Most guys
would have freaked out
if they found out
their best friend
was in love with them.
You're very sweet.
You should call him.
He would like that.
My parents have basically
disowned him.
They're not really
talking anymore.
Why?
Why? Are you serious?
Well, you know
my parents, right?
They're religious,
conservative, sexist, racist,
Republican, materialistic,
narcissistic, racist.
I could keep going...
I'm just wondering
what you really think, Susan.
It's true, I know.
But they just see us
as a reflection of themselves,
so they can't accept Cooper
for who he is.
I'm not sure
how I'm gonna fare.
Aren't you being
a little hard on them?
No.
They have an antiquated idea
of how I should live my life.
Especially my mother.
I understand.
I've always loved your mom.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
She was great with me
when my dad died.
Mmm.
You both have the same kind
of sadness in your eyes.
What?
You and your mother.
That is a weird thing
to say, Edward.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't mean to offend you.
I just... She just
always seemed sad to me.
She has sad eyes.
And I've thought that
since I was a little boy.
You have the same eyes.
They're beautiful.
Just don't say
I'm like my mom, okay?
I don't wanna be like her.
It's funny, 'cause
I always envied your family.
I felt like
such an impostor at school.
You did? I thought
I was the only one
who felt like that.
You?
Yeah.
I was so busy
trying to be perfect and...
And you don't feel that way?
No.
That's exactly
what makes you so perfect.
You are gonna be
a great novelist,
'cause you have created
a fictitious character
in your head about...
No.
Yes.
I don't believe that.
Why'd you give up
on becoming an artist?
Because I'm too cynical
to be an artist.
I think that to be
really, really good,
you have to come
from someplace inside
that I'm just not sure I have.
You underestimate yourself.
Do you know that?
Edward, um,
will you come home with me?
Well, that's a bit forward.
Yeah.
It's not what I'd expect
from a Texas debutante.
Well, you know
all debutantes
are sluts, so...
Hmm.
And you were
my first crush too.
I know.
We got a report
from Ozona.
Someone else harassed
on the highway last night
just like you.
If you don't mind,
we could use
your fingerprints.
Mine?
There's just a bunch of prints
on the trunk of the car.
It could help us
sort 'em out.
There's something else.
Yeah?
We have the cause of death.
Your wife had
a fractured skull.
She was probably struck
with a hammer
or a baseball bat,
probably just once
or twice, so...
Your daughter had
a much more difficult time.
She was suffocated.
She also had
a broken arm.
And they had
both been raped.
It turns out you were right
about that trailer, too.
H ow?
Those fellas,
they took your folks
in there,
just like you thought.
How do you know that?
We found your wife's
fingerprints on the bedpost.
Whose trailer is it?
It's clear.
Guy doesn't even live here.
He's in El Paso.
Trailer's been broken into.
Somebody's been living in it.
There's prints
all over the place.
We're gonna have to check 'em
against the owner's,
see if we can
separate 'em out.
Right.
I'm hopeful, though.
The owner hasn't been there
since last fall, so...
Looks promising.
Prom...
Promising?
Why didn't
you tell me this before?
You're actually gonna
leave New York,
move to Austin and go
to the goddamn
University of Texas?
Why are you doing this?
I mean,
where is this gonna go?
What do you mean,
where is this going to go?
I'm going to marry Edward.
That's where this
is going to go.
This is a ridiculous
conversation.
You're too young
to get married.
Really?
Mom, last summer you tried
to convince me that I had
to marry Bass.
That is different.
Bass is your equal.
Oh, my God.
Did you just say that?
You really just said that.
That came out
of your mouth.
Thafsu.
Why do you always think
the worst of me?
That is not what I meant.
What I meant
is that you are very
strong-willed,
and Edward,
as sweet as he is,
he's too weak for you.
Weak is not a word
that I would use
to describe Edward.
Sensitive is a word
that I would use,
which isn't a word I would use
to describe anyone else
in this family,
except maybe Cooper.
Don't bring Cooper
into this.
Sorry.
Come on, Susan.
I know you think
that we don't care
about the same things,
but you're wrong.
In a few years,
all these bourgeois things,
as you so like to oall them,
are gonna be
very important to you,
and Edward's not gonna be able
to give them to you.
He has no money.
He's not driven.
He's not ambitious.
And I can promise you,
if you marry Edward,
your father's not gonna
give them to you either.
No, you're right.
He's not driven
the way that you
would like him to be.
But he is strong.
He's stronger than I am
in a lot of ways.
Just... He just has
a different kind
of strength is all.
"A different kind
of strength."
And what kind
of strength is that?
He has the strength
to believe in himself
and believe in me.
Susan,
keep seeing him
if you have to,
live with him,
I don't care,
but do not marry him.
I understand
what you see in Edward.
I get it.
No.
No, wait, I do.
No, you don't.
Yes, I do.
He is a romantic.
But he is also
very fragile.
I saw that
when his father died.
Don't...
Don't do this.
You'll regret it.
And you'll only hurt Edward
in the end.
The things you love
about him now are
the things you'll hate
in a few years.
You may not realize it,
but you and I
are a lot more alike
than you think.
No. You're wrong.
You and I are nothing alike.
Really?
Just wait.
We all eventually
turn into our mothers.
Yeah?
Tony Hastings?
Yes. Who is this?
Roberto Andes.
I've sent you an email.
You get it?
Yes.
Well, you recognize the guy?
No.
Shit.
God damn it.
You sure?
Yeah. The whole thing's
just a blur.
Well, his prints
are all over your car.
They found 'em
at the trailer too.
His name's Steve Adams.
He's got a record
in California.
A stolen car,
acquittal on a rape charge.
I put out an APB on him.
He's the only lead
we got, Tony,
and I sure as hell don't have
any other witnesses.
You sure
you don't recognize him?
No.
Fuck. What's wrong
with you, man?
Don't you wanna put
these guys away?
Yeah, of course I do.
The whole thing
is just some...
Just a blank.
I know itwas him.
Well, that may be,
but nobody's seen him
around here lately.
Listen, I gotta be
honest with you.
Right now
it's not looking good.
Sometimes these cases
go months or even years
without a break.
You need to prepare
yourself for that.
Why are you
so driven to write?
I guess it's a way
of keeping things alive.
You know, saving things
that will eventually die.
And if I write
it down, then,
it'll last forever.
Afternoon.
Hey, there.
Sorry I'm late.
There was traffic:
on the interstate.
That's all right.
You look different.
No beard.
You look...
You look different too.
Yeah. So I'll tell you
what we got.
We had an attempted hold-up
at the supermarket
in the mall last night
just before closing.
We caught one
of the guys,
one got killed
and one got away.
What do you,
what do you want me to do?
See if you recognize
the guy we caught.
You can look
at the dead one too,
although I don't really
think it's necessary.
We know who he is.
Who?
Steve Adams.
The one you called Turk
that I emailed you
about last year?
Come on in.
Are you afraid to look
this fella in the eye?
Let him see you?
No.
That's good.
I think it will
help him talk.
That's him,
that guy on the left.
On the far left.
That's him.
No,
no,no,no,no,
no. Hold up, son.
You ain't that lucky.
Get over here.
This fella?
Yes.
I see. Right.
I don't think
he understands.
Lou. Lou. Hey, you.
Your name Lou?
You know my name.
I told you.
Yeah?
Yeah. What's going on?
Well, I guess I want you
to tell me if you've ever
seen this man before.
Think carefully.
You ever seen him?
No, I don't know him.
Hmm?
Who is he?
Why don't you tell him, Tony?
Tell him who he is.
Last summer, this man,
Lou, and his friends,
they forced us off the road
on the interstate
and two of them
forced their way into my car
with my wife and my daughter.
And then this man...
This man? This man Lou?
Yes. Lou, he made me
drive his car,
he took me to the middle
of the desert
and he left me there.
And later my wife
and daughter
were found dead
near the same place.
Well, that ain't right.
What you got to say
about this man's
wife and daughter?
I don't know
nothing about that.
I've never seen him
before in my life.
What you gonna tell me
about Ray and Turk?
Who?
What, are you an owl?
You an owl, Lou?
I never heard of 'em.
You never heard of 'em?
No, sir.
Hmm.
Mmm-hmm.
All right.
Officer.
Put him up.
Are you sure
this is the man?
Absolutely, yes.
You'll swear in a court of law
under penalty of perjury?
Yes.
Good.
Well, we got Lou.
I'm gonna charge him
with murder.
What, do you have
enough evidence?
Oh, you bet,
between you and the prints
in the car and the trailer.
What, he went back
to the trailer
after he left me?
Yeah, looks like it.
Uh, he probably just went back
to tell 'em where you were.
That's why they came back
with the bodies.
They were,
they were gonna kill you.
You see? Yeah.
I bet your friend Ray's
the third fella
in the hold-up.
What HOW?
Well, you're gonna
wait for trial.
And I'm gonna go find Ray.
Don't forget you have
a board meeting
at the museum at 3:00.
I'm sorry. What was that?
You didn't sleep again,
did you?
You know me.
I never sleep.
My ex-husband
used to call me
a nocturnal animal.
What ex-husband?
I didn't know
you had an ex-husband.
Since when?
A couple of years
in graduate school.
It's weird,
I've been thinking
about him a lot lately,
and then recently
he sent me this book
that he's written
and it's
violent and it's sad,
and he entitled it
Nocturnal Animals
and he dedicated it to me.
Did you love him?
Yeah, I loved him.
He was a writer and, uh,
I didn't have faith in him.
I panicked
and I did something
horrible to him.
Something unforgivable,
really.
You left him?
I left him.
I left him in a brutal way,
for the handsome
and dashing Hutton.
Who is very handsome
and dashing.
...and dashing. Yes.
Do you ever feel like
your life has turned
into something
you never intended?
No.
Of course not.
You just started
living your life.
You really didn't get
any sleep, did you?
No.
Where did
this painting come from?
What do you mean,
where did it come from?
You bought it for us,
remember?
It was part of the series
like eight years ago.
It's great, isn't it?
Yeah.
What is that?
Oh, my God,
it's so cool.
It's this app
that lets me watch Willow
while she's in her crib.
Really? Do you not
trust your nanny?
No,no,ldo.
I just hate her, so...
And I would like
to be more involved
with Willow
throughout the day, so...
Look. There she is.
And the sound's incredible.
You can actually hear
her breathing.
And I can talk to her
if I want to.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry. I'm...
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I just...
I thought I saw someone.
Well, you did see someone.
That's Willow
and she's in her crib.
She's sleeping.
I'm really sorry
aboutyourphone.
I can, um...
It's fine. A new one comes out
next week anyway, so...
Thanks.
Shall we?
They're all
waiting for us.
We're under
no contractual obligations.
Which is good.
I know we all have different,
you know, opinions about this,
but as far as I'm concerned...
Anyways,
I think we should
out her loose.
She isn't who she sold herself
to be when we hired her.
I disagree.
I think we should keep her
for now.
Why is that?
Because she's great
and we all like her.
She just needs our support
and a little bit of time,
that's all.
- But it's not working.
- We need to fire her.
There's an awesome candidate
that we could steal
from the Hammer
if we move fast.
I agree with Linda.
We hired her.
We should support her.
New doctor?
No. New haircut.
But, Susan, you were the one
who brought it up last meeting
that you were
looking for a change.
I know, but now I think
we should keep her.
Sometimes it's...
Sometimes maybe
it's not such a good idea
to change things
quite so much.
I don't get it.
What are we doing here?
Shit.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Follow me.
That's Ray Marcus.
He's been named
as a frequent companion
of Lou Bates and Steve Adams.
Part-time electrician,
part-time plumber,
hence the clever
toilet facilities.
He's not a bad match
to your description
and the fella at the hold-up.
No fingerprints,
but we knew that before.
I wonder why there aren't
any fingerprints.
Well, his hands
were probably on your wife.
His record's clean,
except for a rape charge
that got dropped.
I heard from this barman
at this place, Line Camp Bar,
that Ray lives here
with a girl named Leila
but he also keeps another spot
to take girls
she don't know about,
probably your murder trailer
before it got notorious.
Does he look like
he could be the guy?
Yes, that's him.
Good.
Let's talk to him.
Hey, Ray.
What the fuck?
Who the hell are you?
Get off my property, man.
Shit, I'll call you back.
I wanna ask you
some questions.
Fuck you.
I'm occupied at the moment.
What's that?
Just a few
questions, that's all.
We need you to come with us.
What for?
I ain't done nothin'.
I ain't saying you did.
Well, ask me here.
No, we need you
to take a little drive
with us.
Come on, finish up
what you're doing
and let's go.
Do you mind turning round?
Believe me,
I wish I could, but...
Fucking unbelievable.
All right,
that's enough. Come on.
Come on, now.
All right, come on.
Get dressed. Come on.
- You questioning me?
- Yeah.
Yeah, that's what
we're doing, ain't it?
You ain't read rne my rights.
You know your rights, Ray.
You're supposed
to read 'em to me.
I read you your rights,
didn't I, Tony?
Uh-huh.
I read you your rights.
This ain't legal, man.
I'm supposed to have
a lawyer or something.
Calm down, sunshine.
This is just
informal questioning,
that's all.
You're helping rne out.
I ain't charged you
with nothing yet.
Now, if you want a lawyer,
I can take you down
to the station
and charge you with something.
Oh, come on, man, listen,
you ain't gotta take me in.
I'm answering
the questions, ain't I?
Come on.
Give me some questions.
I'll answer your questions.
I don't know any more
about this hold-up
than I did before I met you.
I tell you what,
I'm gonna ask you
a different question.
You recognize this car?
What car?
This one. The one
we're driving around in.
Why should I recognize
this fucking car?
It ain't familiar to you?
It don't remind you
of nothing,
take you back?
Why should it?
You don't remember driving it?
I think I'd know.
Yeah. How about the driver?
What?
This fella?
This fella sitting behind
the steering wheel.
My friend Tony?
You remember him?
I can't see him.
Make him turn around.
Stop the car, Tony.
Turn around and look
at this piece of shit.
Who is this guy?
You don't remember him?
Can't say I do.
You remember him, Tony?
Yes.
Well, refresh his memory.
Last summer on the interstate.
Tell him what you
remember he did.
You killed my wife
and my daughter.
That's crazy.
I never killed nobody.
ANDESI
Tell him the whole thing.
Mmm-mmm.
You and your buddies
on the interstate,
you foroed us off the road.
- Tell him who his buddies are.
- Lou and Turk.
You remember that, Ray?
You remember horsing around
on the interstate
with your buddies,
playing chicken
with the other cars?
You're crazy. That's crazy.
You made us stop
and we had a flat tire
and Lou and Turk fixed it.
Then you and Turk
got in my car
with my wife and my daughter
and you forced me
in your oar with Lou.
ANDESI What then, Tony?
Lou took me out into the brush
and kicked me out.
And you came back in my car
and you called out for me,
trying to lure me
into your trap.
You came back
where Lou had left me
Oh, is that why
you went back there, Ray?
You're fucking crazy!
Tell him what
we found there, Tony.
TCDNYI YOU tell him.
Do I have to?
Don't you know, Ray?
Y'all are crazy. It's crazy.
The bodies
of my wife and child
which you took
back there and dumped.
You're the one. I know you.
What do you say, Ray?
You're crazy.
You're making
a big mistake.
Mmm.
I don't think so.
I don't think so, Ray.
Put your hands out
in front of you.
You got no right.
Got no right?
Rights, rights, rights.
You and your goddamn rights.
Speaking of rights,
I just wanna let you know
I'm recording
this entire conversation.
There. You clear?
Mmm-hmm.
All right, let's go, Tony.
Now, we're going
to a place you might remember,
and you can help yourself out
by telling me about it.
But if you don't remember,
Tony does, all right?
Hey, I'm sorry
you lost your folks, man.
It's a shame.
But I didn't have
nothin' to do with it.
What's this place?
You know this place.
Honest to God, I don't.
You wanna get out, Tony?
Shall we have
a look inside, Ray?
What for?
Come on,
let's take a look.
All right,
all right.
Oh, you raped them
on the bed, I suppose.
I never raped nobody.
Stop fucking around, Ray.
We seen your record.
We know about
that girl in Lubbock.
The charges were dropped.
I never raped nobody.
I wanna know, Ray.
I wanna know the exact story,
what you did to them.
You'll have to ask
somebody else.
I wanna know what they said.
I wanna know what my wife said
and I wanna know
what my daughter said.
I wanna know
how you killed them.
And I wanna know if they knew
it was happening to them.
I wanna know what they felt!
I wanna know if they hurt.
Answer me!
Answer me,
you fucking bastard!
Is it better?
You're gonna take this
the wrong way, but, um,
I think that you
should write about something
other than yourself.
Nobody writes about anything
but themselves.
I just, my mind started
to wander when
I was reading it,
and that's not good, right?
I don't know what to do.
Maybe, you know,
maybe I don't have
a book in me.
Maybe give yourself
some space.
Just do something else.
Can you not do that?
What?
Becauseitu
That makes me feel like
you don't believe in me.
Edward,
that's not what I said.
No, you didn't say that.
But you're saying it
with your face
and you're saying it
when you sigh.
Whatever, you're saying it
when you say you want me
to go baok to sohool.
Well, yeah, I do want you
to go back to school.
I don't see
what's wrong with that.
I mean,
I'm just being a realist.
I mean, you're gonna
work at a book store
and just write a novel,
like that's what
you wanna do
with your life?
I mean,
that's really romantic, but,
like, what? This is it?
This is it? This is what...
You sound like your mother.
Well, you always said
that I reminded you
so much of her, so...
You know, this is exactly why
I don't wanna read your work
because you always get
so fucking defensive.
Yeah, of course I'm defensive!
Do you know what it feels like
to put yourself out
on the line creatively
and then have someone
you love tell you that
they don't understand it?
No, I don't,
because I'm not creative...
That's because
you choose not to be.
I don't wanna fight.
I'm tired and I'm edgy.
I've been writing all night.
I just wanted you to like it,
all right?
Thanks.
I got some news
you're not gonna like.
They're letting Ray Marcus go.
What? What do you mean,
they're letting him go?
The D.A. says we don't have
enough hard evidence,
what we have
is circumstantial.
He needs corroboration.
I'm real sorry, Tony.
It's a goddamn shame.
At least you got to lay
a good belt on him.
No, that's not enough.
What else can we do?
I can think of something.
You'd better get
here quick, though.
He ain't gonna
stick around for long.
Okay, all right,
I'm leaving now.
What?
I told you,
I got lung cancer.
It's metastasized.
But you smoke all the time.
Yeah, well,
that's how it works.
What's the point
in quitting now?
I'll be dead in a year.
It's this fella named Jenks.
He's the lawyer
the court appointed for Ray.
He's a little smartass
from Dallas.
He and the D.A. made a deal
and Ray got off. Politics.
When did you tell me
you were sick?
See, they're trying
to force me out.
They already got another fella
lined up for the job.
I don't understand
what you're talking about.
They'd drop a murder case
to do that?
Oh, yeah.
Give 'em the reason,
ammunition.
They said my case
wasn't well-prepared,
was a sloppyjob, slapdash,
no evidence and evidence
improperly gathered,
won't stand up in court.
The D.A.'s too much
of a chickenshit
to take a case he might lose.
They're not dropping Lou.
Well, it's no fucking good
if we don't get Ray.
Good.
That's what I was
hoping you'd say.
They want me to retire
and enjoy the benefits
of my cancer somewhere else.
Fuckthat
Y%n1neverkMdrne
about the cancer.
The problem with Ray
is his alibi.
You have a family?
Ray claims he was with
that little...
Bobby.Bobby.
What?
Do you have anyone
in your life?
No. No wife or...
I have a daughter in Corpus.
Has she been a help?
She doesn't know.
What can she do about it?
Anyway, Ray claims
he was with that little girl,
Leila whatever her name is
and she backs him up.
Her aunt backs her up.
What are we gonna do?
It's a question
of how serious you are
about seeing justice done.
You get me?
I can't eat.
Gonna throw up.
How are you gonna get
anything done
if you can't eat?
Sometimes I can,
sometimes I can't.
This place is terrible.
I need you to eat something.
So let me ask you
a personal question.
Off the record,
between you and me.
What do you want me to do
with Ray Marcus?
Well, what can you do
with him?
Anything you goddamn like.
But I thought
you said that...
Listen,
I got nothin' to lose.
I'm not gonna let
this asshole D.A.
fuck up my last case.
I'm also not gonna stand by
and watch a murderer go free.
I've seen too many sick fucks
like Ray Marcus get off
over the years.
Now, are you willing
to go outside
of strict procedure on this?
Yes.
You sure?
Andes here.
You're kidding?
All right, thanks.
Rayjust showed up
at Line Camp.
I'm gonna let
that little idiot get nice
and liquored up
and then I'm gonna go grab
his ass and take him
to my camp.
And I want you
to come with me.
We're gonna keep him for
a little while,
work him over a bit,
get a little rough,
make him suffer.
And then we'll see
what he does.
Would you like that?
You have to realize
that this is not working.
We are not working.
We are too different.
We are not right
for each other.
Susan, stop.
We're not right
for each other?
No, we're not right
for each other.
We are perfect for each other.
No, we're not perfect
for each other, Edward.
We may be perfect
for each other
if we didn't live
in the real world,
but I live in the real world
and I need a life
that is more structured.
Hey.
I need a future
that is more structured.
I want to be the person
that you want me to be,
but I just can't.
You are. You are.
I can't be that.
Hey, no, stop.
I, I really wanted
to be this person
that you thought I was,
I really did,
but I'm just
not that person.
I'm, I'm cynical,
I'm pragmatic.
No, look...
No, lam. I'm a realist.
You're afraid. You're afraid.
No, I'm not afraid.
We've been through this
so many times before.
I'm not scared.
I'm unhappy.
All right.
I'm just really,
really unhappy.
You're so...
You really are so wonderful
and you're just so
sensitive and
romantic and...
Weak. That's right, yeah.
What? I did not say
you were weak.
You've said it
so many times before.
I did not call you weak.
You've said it before,
so why don't you say it again?
Weak.
I did not say
you were weak.
Do you love me?
That's not the point.
No, that is the point.
No, it is not the point.
That is the point!
That is not the point.
You didn't answer me.
Yes, I love you.
Well, when you love someone,
you work it out.
You don't just throw it away.
You have to be
careful with it.
You might never get it again.
I can't do this with you
anymore, Edward.
I just can't keep doing this.
Susan“.
You can't just
walk away from things
all the time.
- Come on. Come on.
- Oh, shit. Come on.
I told you,
I don't know nothin'
about this situation.
Why don't you go ask
in there, man?
I'll see you
in a minute, okay?
Okay, sweetie?
We're going to my camp.
It's in White Creek
near the trailer
where they took your folks.
You follow.
Sit up.
Oh, Jesus.
I'm gonna be sick.
Tony, get over here, quick.
Here, you use this, right?
You shoot him
if he gets out of line.
Boo.
Hey, man, this ain't legal.
If this were legal,
you'd have taken me
to the station,
not this fucking place.
It's all the legal
we need, boy.
There ain't
no new evidence.
Oh, yeah?
Why don't you take me in
if you got new evidence? Huh?
I like it better here.
It's more relaxed.
It seems to me
you tried
this trick already.
If you think this guy's
gonna break me down,
you already seen
that don't work.
Oh, yeah,
but what would you say
if I told you
your friend Lou Bates
implicated you
in the Hastings murders?
If Lou had done that,
you would have taken me in.
Well, don't worry,
we'll get you to the station.
Don't worry. Oh, who's this?
Well, looky here.
You son of a bitch.
All right.
Okay, come on, boy.
Get over there.
Lou, what'd you
fucking tell this guy?
I didn't tell him nothin'.
No, he said you told him
I was the one who killed
this guy's wife and kid.
What? That's what
he told me about you.
You're supposed
to be the lawman.
What kind of bullshit is this?
Fuck off
both of you.
Now, do you two
have any last words
you wanna say to eaoh other?
I think what we
should do, Tony,
is we should just kill
them right now.
It's gonna be rough
for 'em out there,
not knowing
how it's gonna come.
Maybe Ray'll get killed
for resisting arrest, huh?
Coming home late at night,
he might get shot
by a burglar.
Oh, you feeling
uncomfortable, boy?
Ooh. Come on up here.
Yeah, you look
like you're feeling
uncomfortable.
What?
Sorry. I'm sorry.
What's that?
I ain't gonna kill you, son.
I'm a policeman.
What, you gonna cry?
Are you gonna cry?
Aw, okay. Well, since you're
feeling so uncomfortable...
Tony, get over here.
Take this.
Go on, right here, okay?
Please don't.
Fuck.
Right here, right here.
Right here, okay?
- Right.
- Hey, hey.
What about me?
I might be feeling
uncomfortable too.
Oh, yeah?
Okay, come on up.
There you go. Free as a bird.
Okay? How about it?
What do you say, Tony?
Now, what shall we do
with these two?
What you gonna do?
What you gonna do, son?
Come on.
Let's go...
He's got a gun.
Bobby?
Shoot 'em, Tony.
Shoot 'em.
Come back here,
you little fuckers!
No. No.
No, please.
Are you okay?
I'm gonna live to regret this.
I regret it now.
You know, I'm Catholic.
I don't even believe
in abortions.
I'm so sorry.
I feel so useless.
You're anything but useless.
You always know exactly
what to do.
Thank you.
I just don't think
I'm ever gonna be able
to look at Edward again
after what I did to his child.
He'll never find out.
What did I do?
I promise
it'll be okay.
I'll make it okay.
Oh, my God, no.
Edward.
Tony.
Mmm.
Hey.
You know I had
to shoot him, right?
I don't give a goddamn
fuck that you shot him!
I'm glad that you shot him!
I'm fucking glad
that he's dead!
I should have stopped it!
I should have protected them.
I should have seen it coming.
I should have stopped it.
Hey, now.
Shh.
It's okay.
I should have stopped it.
Hey.
You're okay.
I should have
stopped it, Bobby.
Look at me.
You're a good man.
Come on. We gotta get up.
Ray gets to the road,
he's gonna hitchhike.
We gotta catch him
before he gets a ride.
Now, listen to me.
When you get to
the fork in the road,
you veer to the left.
That's gonna take
you back towards
where he took your folks.
I suspect he's gonna
go for the highway.
I'll go that direction.
You take this.
I got another
one in the car.
Bobby...
What?
Are you in trouble
for all this?
Hell, I don't know.
I don't really give a shit.
I'm dying, remember?
Fuck.
You. Where's your pal?
He's on his way.
Your cop friends?
They're around.
They here?
It's just me for the moment.
Oh.
You and that fucking gun
you don't know how to use.
What happened to Lou?
He's dead.
What?
Fucking son of a bitch.
That's big trouble
for your friend,
you know that, right?
I don't think so.
You don't think so?
Well, then, what the
fuck do you want?
You and that silly gun.
I've seen how handy
you are with that thing.
Sit down. Sit down.
You sit down
or I'll fucking kill you.
Listen, man...
Why does a nice guy like you
hang out with a guy
like Andes who kills people?
You kill people.
They had it coming to 'em,
your fucking wife
and that kid, but you...
You got me wrong,
it was an accident.
It was an accident?
I got a certain pride
in how people talk to me.
There are certain things
I don't put up with.
When someone accuses
me of something,
that's a fucking insult.
It gives me the right.
If my woman accuses me
of fucking somebody else,
well, then,
I'll go fuck somebody else.
If your daughter
thinks I'm a rapist,
then she gets raped.
Nobody gets away
with what you did to us.
Nobody.
They don't?
Well, then, you should
just kill me, then.
Right?
You should fucking kill me.
Man, you know nothing.
It's fun to kill people.
You of all people
should try it sometime.
Fun?
It's fun to kill people?
Did you have fun
killing my wife and daughter?
Get up.
Get up. Go on, now.
Go on. Go on.
Go on.
I remember your fucking wife.
I remember
fucking your wife.
You're too weak.
Too fucking weak, you know.
You're too weak
to do anything about it.
Son of a bitch!
Edward.
Right this way, sir.