Mr Chow, have you fallen asleep?
I come to serve you
Jade, why do you come here
in the middle of the night?
Why do you come here then?
Stop bothering my business
This is my inn
Who'll responsible for it
if someone get killed here?
But there were many people got killed
in this inn before
I tell you, I know your story very well
Don't push me to make a dead set at you
What are you?
Officers and thieves have their own ways
And our own duties
But I'd ask your help
How?
Be frank, they are kidnappers
That's none of my business
$1000 taels, deal or not?
To kill him?
No, just delay them.
Make them stay one more night
And forget everything, what say you?
Guess
Fantastic
Promised?
If you can't sleep, get something to eat
Sister
Take care of the kids
Where is Uncle Chow?
It's fine
Yuk Bo
You went for a walk so late?
It's freezing
- Here is too hot
- Hot?
But I feel cold! Am I so sick?
The logner we stay
the more danger we'll have
We can't wait
Let's take a risk! Go!
Ho Hu, Iron
I'll stop the enemies with Mo-yan
Just take the kids away
We'll meet at the Dragon Gate
Wai-on, cover them
Leave the inn to me
Mo-yan
Who is it?
Chun
- Brother Ho
- Come in
Miss Yau
Chun, don't worry
We'll protect you
Mo-yan
Wai-on, take care of Yang's kids
Wait
Can I have this flute?
Don't waste time
The rabbit in the trap is always
anxious to escape
But it can never make it
Yes
We'd move this time!
My inn would be jacked up
Pack up now
No matter how, we'd move
Damn it
Why do you shut the door?
Don't you know the wind is killing me?
No business today?
Thank god! Our savior comes
Don't let them fish in the trouble water
Just tail them
Thank god
You bring us peace
Even fire has to go off
What peace?
There is sand-storm outside
You said there was a fire?
Here! Here!
Where is it?
Here
Where is the fire?
What were you doing?
You should smell it!
Damn it! Can you see the fire?
I want them to show up
What's wrong?
Who are you?
Why do you bring so many weapons?
For business
Trade with knives?
Sir, businessmen should be careful
In this troubled world
we've to protect ourselves
You look familiar
Who are you?
I'm talking to you
Sir
Watch the opera
we don't have to do anything
Just wait and see
Where are you from?
Are you the general guarding the border?
How dare you talk to me like this?
We are...
Secret agents from the East Chamber
This is our identity proof
It's confidential
Our identity proof
Damn it
We become thieves in return
Where are you going to?
Going out of the border
Don't you know the gate is closed?
No one can get out without the order
from the President of the East Chamber
I know
You look like
the wanted criminal Chow Wai-on
You look almost the same
You should be him...
I don't think so
Look! There is a mold on the man's face
But he hasn't
But I don't remember there's any mold
Look at that guy
he has a mold when he came
Now, only a scar is left
Look, they pretend to be calm
You can tell there is something wrong
with them
Take them to your camps for questioning
Maybe they're the people we want
If you get any merit from it
don't forget us
Sure
You, come over here
The one with a scar
Hey, I'm talking to you!
Why do you stare at me?
Not happy with it?
You are just like a thief
And you're a businessman?
You can never cheat me
Don't get angry, it's their trick
I don't like you since the first time
I saw you
Take them to the camp
Yes, sir
Drink with me
Go
You two get up
They are all here
Watch over the general.
I'll look for another exit
Three taels, give me wine
Sir, take care...
The reward from
the government is just $1000 taels
See, these cheques cost $1,000 taels each
I'm a reasonable man
Drop the knife
There is trouble in the frontier.
No one can go in or go out
You'd better stay few more days
When the order is cancelled
I'll let you go
Thank you, sir
You'll have a share too
Let's drink
Chow Wai-on disappeared
Lu Siu Chuen
Sir, he doesn't seem to be here
Dao, the stuff is here
It is the first time...
you stare at me like this
Boss
Go
He came from the secret passage
If you are willing to stare at me
because of the passage
How about I open all the passages...
So you can stare at me for
the rest of your life
You're in this business for
such a long time
You should know what I want
and I like most
I want to buy a road to leave the country
I'll offer $1,000 taels
$1,000 taels?
If I want $1,000 taels
I wouldn't have added the...
So you don't want money
No
I want $2,000 taels
and you
What? Scared?
Hero always goes with beauty
But I do want to try...
a special one like you
But on one condition
What is it?
I want a formal wedding
What? Scared?
Forget it!
I just want to have one night stand
I'm a righteous man
Sleeping with you...
may bring me a notorious name
OK, let's have formal wedding
I'll take this as present
Give it back to me
Come on, go ahead
Move your hand downward
then we'll save the wedding
Come on
I'll take it back on our wedding
Your Excellency,
we'll be at Dragon Gate soon
A wedding? Do you mean it?
Jade's secret tunnel is
the only way out
Only you believe her
I don't trust that bitch
You are a triad member too
We can be brothers
So why can't I trust her?
Dragon Inn is a place
only talks about interests
It has its own way to survive in a desert
The wedding is to confuse the East Chamber
I want Cha to be the master of
the wedding so as to hinder their act
Then I'll force Jade to tell me
where the tunnel is
When you see I put the candle on the sill
you all rush our from both sides
Mo-yan'll take the kids to Jade's room
Then we'll escort Jade to lead us
out of here
There is no righteousness in politics
Mo-yan, do you understand?
How can a man come out
after entering the bride's room?
Don't you think...
I'll give you all up for having sex?
Just follow his instruction
Even Miss Yau can't understand him
The more confused we are,
the easier it goes
Dragon Inn
I hope I won't see you here again
How is it going on outside?
The set has almost done
Did the geanny promise?
There won't be any problem!
Of course!
Just only you stay...
The granny will promise anything
How can I be the master of wedding?
If it's not your reminder
on the other day...
I can never marry Jade
You deserve it
Right, their parents are not here
and you are old enough...
You're the only choice
Okay, I'll do it
Congratulation
Thank you
Today is my wedding
Enjoy yourselves and let's get drunk!
Make yourselves at home
You men look sad
Give a speech
I've been a homeless
and lonely businessman before
I'm so glad to be a match maker
in a desert
I really feel honored
Why are you standing here?
Today is Jade's wedding
Why don't you congratulate them?
Smile
I know it's nosy of me...
but it's hard to find a good man
If you find one...
just keep him by any means
Perfect couple
They're made for each other
Great! Have my toast
Don't get drunk on this big day
But it's a big day! We should get drunk
Sir, don't drink any wine
that is not ours
It may be poisoned
Cheers
Fine
Great!
Go to the bride's room.
Don't let them delay us
What are you doing?
Going to bed so early?
It's good time
We want to play with the couples
If you can defeat me, I'll let you go in
OK! Come on
It's a big day, don't fight
Let's drink
Give us wine
Sir, it doesn't matter
We've more men! We are having advantage
Water is filled into these 2 pots
Don't worry, you won't get drunk
Let's make it five
Don't waste time.
Tell me where the tunnel is
Light the candle first
But in case you're fooling me...
Here it is
See if you are capable to go in
Mr Ngai, the 4th one
The last one
Tell me now
It's not funny to fool you
Do you have weapons on your wedding?
Where is my flute?
Search it
Baldy, cheers
Ok! Let's finish a pot each
Useless! Get lost
Come on
Be careful
I have brought some fruits for you
Thank you
Isn't it delicious?
The moon is beautiful tonight
Sister, tell me why...
it's not the same moon as in our hometown?
Mom said the moon
is always more beautiful in hometown
So this is less beautiful than
the one in our hometown
But, we have no home now!
We can see the moon here safely
it's the mercy of God indeed
How do you feel this place?
Good, cause you are so kind
to treat me fruit!
Come and eat together
There may be some changes
If anything goes wrong, I'll drop the cup
Once you get this signal, take action
Think some ways to send me out
Sure
But not tonight
This is the only chance, I must go
I tell you, once stepping in my room
you have to listen to me
I say yes, then yes
Jade, please help me
I'll marry you when I return
So we won't owe each other
Haven't you fooled me enough?
Sir, the President's army will
arrive soon
Miss Yau, this is water, not wine
Forget me, just watch out for the signal
They seem to be serious
I think so
Cut the crap! We've bet our lives on it
You're a man of the world
Inform me once you get any news
There is a secret passage in Jade's room
Chow'll leave through this tonight
He's smart
No one can leave here
How about going up there and check?
Will it help?
Check? Okay
Don't waste time
Yes! Time is running short! Come on
Mistress, open up
Who is it?
It's Cha Ting! Open up please
What's the matter?
My servant is hurt
Do you have any medicine?
What's up?
You're trouble
My servant's head is hurt
Please have a look
Today is my big day.
You should know what to do
Give me the medicine
Come over here, this way
Let's talk
What's up?
Don't you think you can go that easily?
Why do you act in such a hurry?
Let's take action after this night
Don't ruin my wedding
But I'm afraid you'd ruin my plan
What does that mean?
I know Chow is planning to leave
through your secret tunnel
He gives me much money
and accompanies me
What can you pay?
Give me a price
$100,000 taels
Money isn't a problem, we can talk about it
Give me the money, I'll give you the man
Be careful that you'll lost
both money and man
You're back
2 more injured?
I tell you, you've to pay for my medicine
Have you finished your business?
But our affair is not ended
You can't go
Mr Ho, where are you going to?
Come on! Have some more wine
Get lost! I want to piss
What a coincidence, I want to piss too
Then you go first
The candle is blown off
Bitch
Shall we wait for the signal?
He is enjoying himself
but forget about our lives
Broken cups
Nothing... this is for protection only
Let's keep on drinking
These bastards are well prepared
We've to fight anyway, let's start now!
I'll help you
Take the knife
You want to escape?
Go with the kids
Ok
Let Chung chase after them
Our target is Chow Wai-on
Shall we wait for Chow?
Stop waiting, let's get out of here
Get up, let's go
Where is Uncle Chow?
Don't ask, quick!
Let me go, what have you got from
the East Chamber?
They've given me much more than you have
Stop him!
I won't let you go
I can't believe you work for
the East Chamber
Damn you
Don't frame me
Chow, you're going to lose
Meaner
Who told you to take action?
We didn't, that old man...
The old bastard?
Meaner
Damn you
Jade, we've paid you
Take it back to buy your coffin
You're good
There is a sand-storm ahead
It isn't sand storm
Someone is riding a horse
The troop from East Chamber is coming
Let's go separately, we'll join later
Okay
It's Tsao's black Flag Arrow Troop
I'm your man
Iron, Ho Fu
Yuk Ying, Yuk Bo
Yuk Bo
Sister, I am here
Where is Yuk Bo?
Sister
Don't be afraid, I will take you away
Are you mad, Jade?
Siu Chuen
You two bastards, you are beasts
I'll take your skin off!
Sister
Mo-Yan
Hold it
Tsao is here
What? Tsao is here?
She fainted, it's useless
Take her to my room
Dao
Tell the general I'm in trouble, go!
The medicine
We've been through all adversities...
and we'd escaped from every danger
But it's an ever changing world
We can't be sure if we can escape this time
Mo-Yan
Wai-on, I should have faith in you
That flute
I didn't mean to give it to jade
I really don't know...
you'd be so upset
Luckily I can explain to you
People said: Love is not secured
in a messy world
Actually, love is more valuable in
such a troubled world
You can't get the flute back
It's nothing
Nothing is more important than our love
Damn it
Why don't you leave?
This is my inn, why should I leave?
I've nearly forgotten
You're as cool as a desert
You're so mean
The people in desert are always selfish
They only care about themselves
So you open this inn
You travellers
leave when you reach your aim
I just learn this from you
And I'm cool and mean?
Who is it?
Dao
Are the helpers coming?
He's not coming
Damn it, they're all heartless beasts
After killing those bastards
I'll come back and teach them
a good lesson
Why are you back?
It's out of my expectation that
the one who stays behind with me
is a barbarian
Watch out for the arrows
Dao, take the kids to the tunnel,
Hurry up
Damn it
Hold it
Hurry up
Your flute
I don't want anything that
is given out of pity
Your excellency, the inn is surrounded
Mo-yan, go down first
Hold my hand
There are many soldiers
Forget it
Go
There are people behind the hill
Still chasing?
Go to hell!
Go...
The desert is huge, I'll follow you
I will stop him
Jade, take the kids away
Wait for me at the Dragon Gate
Don't think about it now!
Wai-on, we'd live or die together
Me too
Why don't you leave?
Block his way
Are you okay?
Wai-on!
Get lost!
After killing you
my kingdom is as solid as steel
We'll fight you together
But you fight alone
Damn you, we can kill you any time
Come on, eunuch
Shit, we are trapped inside
the drift sand
What should we do?
We can't move
It's your end
Mo-Yan
Don't close your eyes
I'll help you to chop him
The Willow Strike
Destroying stance
Mo-Yan
Go to hell
It's useless
I will kill you
Stop
Be careful
Chow, you are a man
You have to take the kids out of here
I'm the most powerful man in the world
You choose the way to hell
Oh, my leg
My hand
Where else can you go?
Wonder sword
Push me over there, hurry up
Chow, can you hear me?
Mo-Yan
Will you come back to the Dragon Inn?
When other guests come
you may have already forgotten me
I can't face the desert as brave as you
I want to leave now
The Dragon Inn
Give me some wine
Let's leave this heartless place
to go after Chow