Next.
I'll kill anyone that beats us.
Don't risk your lives for a meal.
One! Two! Three! Four! Five!
Six! Seven! Eight! Nine!
The first three may enter.
Enter!
The rest of you,
you know the drill.
On your heads, you fuck.
I said, on your heads!
YOUN Min-jae, get up.
Eun-ji?
I'm really dirty right
now and I stink.
Min-jae.
I'm sorry, Eun-ji.
I really meant to keep
the promise this time.
Cute, huh?
Min-jae, it's okay.
It's okay.
Listen to me.
I met someone here.
He's Captain Hwang.
I told him that you were my cousin,
so act accordingly
Got that?
Okay.
You should be out in no time.
Allegiance!
If it's okay, I'd like to
take you out to dinner.
You must feel better about
seeing your cousin.
Yes.
YOUN Min-jae has a solid
record so far,
so I'll make sure he gets out after
the four-week training.
Thank you so much.
How's the food?
What? Oh, the food...
Are you okay?
My earring...
That's okay.
Come out here for a second.
You don't have to do this.
I'm really sorry.
I wanted to find it for you.
That's really okay.
You can't just have one though.
I'll just take one off like this.
Can I have that?
Excuse me?
I'll find the other piece for you.
Ummm...
Here.
Hey, get up.
- Balls!
- Ferocity!
- Ferocity! Balls!
Eat that, you animals.
Let's get moving, boys.
Allegiance!
The release trainee list
has been completed, sir.
How about YOUN Min-jae?
He's on the list as ordered.
Let me see.
Allegiance!
Colonel Hur's relative?
Are you crazy?
YOUN Min-jae's a former thug
slash philanderer that
took away Hae-mi from the colonel.
- Number 2322, KIM Bong-gun.
- Yes!
- 2351, HWANG Young-jae!
- Thank you!
- Number 2133, YOUN Won-suk.
- Yes!
- Number 2400 PYO Dong-jong.
- Yes. Halleluiah!
- Number 2281, HONG Suk-jun.
- Yes! Thank you, god.
- Number 2116, HWANG Gi-suk.
- Yes, sir. Thank you, sir.
That's all for the third
Samchung Revival Camp!
The rest will be transferred
to Samchung Volunteer Corps.
Those of you that had their
names called to your left.
Execute!
Fuck. What about me?
What about me?
What are you doing, you fuck.
Sir, one sec!
I think there's been a mistake.
My name wasn't called.
Number 2126, YOUN Min-jae.
There's no YOUN Min-jae.
Is that clear?
There definitely is.
That's impossible!
There definitely is!
You fuck.
I need to get out!
I need to get out, you fuckers!
Freeze!
This is where you boys will
be staying starting today.
There's no agenda for today.
After six months of volunteer
work, you'll be sent home.
It's been a while.
I have one little question
I wanted to ask you.
What is it?
Did you know that Samchung
Revival Camp was like this?
I didn't have a clue.
So you didn't know, huh?
You stinking bastard!
- What's with you?
- You got me into this.
Off of me.
What do we do now, huh?
What now?
Stop crying.
Leave him alone.
I feel him.
Shut the fuck up.
You are a living nightmare.
Whatever man... it's you that
got us on the bus here
What did you just say?
Hey.
WANG Do-chul, you.
Shut up.
Who the fuck is this now?
Okay, so you wanna test
my patience today, huh?
- Okay then, let's go.
- Come here you little punk
- What?
- I said, come here.
He doesn't understand that.
You need to call him
as if you would a dog.
You bitch. Do you wanna die?
Do you boys have a death wish?
I own a barbershop.
One day, this cop came in for
a hair cut and a hand job.
Then he would leave without paying.
So I said he should at least pay
the chick for the hand job.
Just for saying that,
he tried to arrest me.
So I beat the crap out of the cop,
and that's how I ended up here.
I may be a mere barber,
but I can never stand injustice.
During the Park administration,
I used to be a Navy Seal, you know.
Anyway, after Park's death,
things just got tangled up.
KIM Jae-kyu's an asshole for
assassinating President Park
That was just foul, you know.
Enough!
Sit!
Next.
Number 3202.
Load personal story!
Load!
Fire!
I'm a doctor.
And I chose to come here.
Bullshit.
Please listen to my story.
I used to roam around the
country practicing medicine
to help out the needy.
I worked gruelingly to serve
my patients with utmost care.
But one day,
I met this woman who
was suffering from a clogged artery.
Why is that a big deal?
Well, if you don't prevent the
artery from being clogged,
the artery will expand and
eventually result in death.
The good thing is,
I knew the proper cure for the disease
and so I slid my rod in her clam,
attempting to save her life.
But ignorant people thought that
I was trying to rape her,
which in turn got her husband furious.
So I decided to go into hiding.
The end.
Go into the cathedral.
It's freezing out there.
Man, I need to get out of here
before my son sees birth.
But guess that's not
happening anytime soon.
Son? He's just going to turn
into a thief like you anyway.
Shut up. His mother's smart, so he'll
probably get the brains from her.
Yeah, whatever.
Like father like son.
How smart do you think
he can possibly be?
Besides, your wife's probably
banging some guy left and right.
Shut up, you fuck!
If you talk about Mi-ja again,
I'm going to kill you.
Mi-ja...?
That's right. WANG Mi-ja.
Now that I come to thin of it,
she has the same last name as you.
She's really something though.
Did you say, WANG Mi-ja?
Yeah.
What does she do for a living?
She's a hair stylist.
So it's WANG Mi-ja that
cuts people's hair?
Yeah, man.
She has a mole here?
And how do you know this?
You stinking bastard...
that's my sister.
Oh, so you're the younger
brother that ran away after
getting expelled from school?
Holy mother lord.
Oh my god. This stinking bastard
and my sister...
How dare you... you stinking...
So you're my brother in law.
That's fantastic, brother.
You're my brother
in law for real.
Nice meeting you, man.
Please cut that out, will you?
That crazy motherfucker.
Why would you want to take
off his pants, you homos?
Are you out of your mind?
Fuckin' A.
Freeze!
What's going on here?
Cut out the crap.
I'll give you another chance.
Back to sleep.
No violence, gentlemen!
Thank you, Min-jae, Mr.
Be nice to our new boss now.
We'll call him Mr. Butterfly.
If you don't call him that,
I'll kick all your asses.
Good night, boss.
Can you tell me where Min-jae is?
Why didn't you tell me the
truth from the beginning?
Your relationship
with YOUN Min-jae.
I didn't mean to lie.
What good is it for you
if you know where he is?
Please help.
I just need to find him.
Please tell me.
He's not for you.
Why not?
Because he's a gangster?
It's not like I'm any better.
I'm just a mistress.
Don't degrade yourself like that.
I love Min-jae.
I don't buy that love.
I don't care what you think.
What I need is knowing
where he is right now.
Please.
Okay, fine.
But I'll closely be watching
the love you just talked about.
We searched everywhere
but couldn't find anything.
But I did issue a warrant.
We should be able
to find her soon.
Forget about it.
I know what a man like you wants.
And I have the power
to give that to you.
But the question is,
what can you give me?
Leave it up to me.
Should I?
I already swore my
patriotism to you, sir.
Give me a chance.
- That dude...
- Why the hell is he here?
Attention!
You were all given an opportunity
for revival at the Samchung Revival Camp.
But you were all sent here
because you didn't make it there.
You gentlemen must change.
If you don't get better here,
you won't have another chance.
And the entire unit will take
responsibility for one's action.
If one fucks up, the rest
will be disciplined.
And if one of you decides to betray
the group for personal benefit,
I'll teach you why
it was a bad choice.
Prepare yourselves.
The end.
He's changed completely.
He was nicer than that before.
From what I'm seeing,
I guess he fucked up.
Or else, he wouldn't
be here, right, brother?
Don't call me brother
before I kick your ass.
You need to accept
our relationship.
Shit.
Settle down, brother.
As long as I'm here,
there will be no more fighting.
I'll teach you discipline from now.
- Get started.
- Yes, sir.
Authorized personnel only, miss.
How about visits?
I said,
authorized personnel only, miss.
Do you know YOUN Min-jae?
Does anyone know YOUN Min-jae?
Anyone?
Anyone know YOUN Min-jae?
Hold on.
Hold on. Wait!
You can't go in.
It's the same butterfly tattoo as this.
You know YOUN Min-jae?
YOUN Min-jae?
She was calling out
your name, boss.
And she had the same
butterfly tattoo as you.
Eun-ji?!
Eun-ji!
Stop!
Min-jae, be careful!
No, Min-jae!
Boss!
Eun-ji!
- Eun-ji!
- Min-jae!
Eun-ji, what are
you doing here?
Are you okay, Min-jae?
- I'm okay.
- You sure?
- Go back now. I'm okay.
- Min-jae...
Don't worry and just go, Eun-ji!
- Min-jae, I...
- I'm going to you later.
Min-jae...
Min-jae! Min-jae!
You dip shit!
Don't hit him!
Please stop!
Please just give me one second.
She came here to see me, okay?
Min-jae.
- Just a minute, please.
- Don't hit him!
I was hoping that
you wouldn't show up.
What are you doing here?
Did the colonel send you here?
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
So, can you please save him?
I'm begging you.
He didn't do anything wrong
It's all me. Let him go.
This is my last warning.
Don't ever come back here.
Will you let him go,
if I leave then?
You're going to kill him, aren't you?
Do you think I'm here to
kill YOUN Min-jae alone?
Hey, Sergeant, get her out of here.
Yes, sir.
If you see her again,
get rid of her.
Hey!
Do you think she's still here?
Of course man.
She's boss' woman.
She didn't look like she was
going to leave anytime soon.
What a kiss ass you are
What's Mr. Butterfly to you?
Are you talking shit about boss?
Well, if you think about it,
butterflies may look fancy
but in reality they're really a
Ionely and poor species.
You need to live as larva
for six years underground.
And for what? So that you can
fly for maybe a couple of weeks?
With bad luck, you can even get hit
by a rain shower on your first day.
They're some poor species.
So no larvas for snack when
you boys are out of here.
Got that?
What about the broth?
That you can. Larva broth with
a shot of Soju is the best.
Shut the fuck up.
How can you be talking about
Soju and larvas right now?
Hey, you little cold-blooded.
Eun-ji...
Eun-ji?
How did you get here?
How did you escape?
I knew that you would be here.
Min-jae, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I think all of this
happened because of me.
Stop saying that.
I'm so sorry.
It's all my fault.
It's dangerous here.
Let's go, okay? Let's go.
Min-jae! Min-jae!
No, no. Please don't shoot.
Don't shoot!
Please don't shoot!
Take him.
No! Please, no!
Let Eun-ji go, you fuckers!
Don't touch her! Eun-ji!
Min-jae... Min-jae...
Let her go.
What about her, sir?
Put her in my car.
Off of me!
- Go back to the corps.
- Allegiance!
Out! Get out!
Off of me!
You're not even human!
That's right, I'm a soldier.
My duty is to kill all enemies.
Foreign and domestic.
And YOUN Min-jae is an enemy.
If he dies, so will I.
Wake up!
Why would you want to risk
your life for a scum like that?
I never disobeyed higher
order up until now.
But you smiled at me when
everyone was laughing.
You acknowledged me as a
soldier when no one did.
YOUN Min-jae would've been dead a
long time ago if it weren't for you.
I never asked you to sacrifice.
Where's Eun-ji?
Where's Eun-ji, you fuck?
Please don't shoot.
I'm back.
So don't shoot.
Hey, brother.
So you're back, huh?
So you ran and couldn't
go farther than a kilo?
Eun-ji had it in her hands.
Where was it, huh?
Heads!
CHO Gwang-pal!
You can't die!
Let's run away! If I'm going to die,
I want to die in style.
Mr. Butterfly! Mr. Butterfly!
Reload the magazine!
Sir, there's no more!
Out of my way!
Is it YOUN Min-jae?
I'll gather a search
team right away, sir.
Eagle, Eagle, Tiger.
We have a problem. Backup needed.
Inform the location,
and contain this mess.
Eun-ji.
Eun-ji!
Eun-ji! Eun-ji! Get up.
I'm here. It's me, Min-jae.
Come on, Eun-ji. I'm here.
Eun-ji, you can't die like this
Eun-ji, you can't die like this.
What happened to our promise
that we'd live on the beach with palm
trees and a hammock drinking juice.
I thought we were going to live
happily ever after just like that.
Eun-ji, this can't happen.
We need to live together in style, remember?
Wake up, Eun-ji!
Wake up. Come on!
Why did you kill her? Why?
You fucker!
Why did you kill her?
Did you have a wedding and
everything with my sister?
Of course. At this huge
wedding chapel in Namwon.
Did she look good?
Brother!
You know damn well
how good she looks.
You know damn well...
At least Mr. Butterfly's
with his woman.
Good thing he'll be with his love.
I mean, it's a long way.