What are you doing?
Who is your boss?
I belong to Mr Chan.
Go to hell!
Where's Yuk-Su?
Huh?
- Where is Yuk-Su?
- Oh, he's...
Where's he got to?
- That little punk!
- It's not ready. You must add sauce.
Okay.
It'll do.
Quick!
Beef noodles are here!
- That's disgusting! How's yours?
- It's horrible.
Shorty,
come here.
What? My name's Lofty.
Not Shorty.
- Shorty, eat it.
- Eat! Eat!
What was that for?
- What are you doing?
- Tell your boss to come out.
My... my... boss has gone
to Guangzhou.
Oh, no.
Mr Wong's men.
Tell Yat to come out!
Let's go.
- It's like sticky goo.
- How can they serve this stuff?
Let's go.
Siu-Yu. Come on out,
quickly.
Stop!
Mister, what did we do
that made you tear down the sign?
What's it to you? Get lost.
Who are you?
Well,
I'm the boss here.
The boss?
"No.1 Beef noodles"?
More like the worst.
Calm down,
mister.
I opened this shop
to make a living.
Smash the board
and we'll be out of business.
What is this?
- They're beef noodles.
- Beef noodles?
- Yes.
- It's manure.
Maybe this one's not good.
I'll go and make you some more.
Stay right there.
- I make good ones.
- You said "good", huh?
Yes.
So eat it all.
Eat it.
Lick it off the floor.
You don't have the right to say
you're number one.
You are a dog so
crawl like a dog.
Crawl.
- Lofty, clean this up.
- Yes.
Hey, Siu-Yu.
Doesn't that look great?
What happened?
What's the matter?
Father, I told you not to work.
What about your leg?
You little punk!
I'll kill you!
You're useless.
I'll kill you.
- Don't hit him.
- Don't try to stop me. I'll kill him.
- Why are you hitting me?
- How can you face your Uncle?
Uncle Chai! Uncle Chai!
Calm down. It wasn't his fault.
Will you listen to me?
- Master Yat, I'm so sorry.
- Don't be like this. Get up.
Your poor mother.
She'd turn in her grave.
He doesn't know himself.
He's unfit and weak,
yet he's always picking fights
and even wants to be a hero.
The poor
can't fight the rich
and the rich
can't fight the government.
I work my guts out
to get him into the very best school
just so he'll be able to
rise above all this
and become a good
medical student.
And now it's all over.
It's lucky you took him in, but he
can't even learn to cook noodles
and now he's brought you
all this trouble.
- I'm so very sorry.
- Don't be like that.
As soon as everything's cleared up
we can start again.
If Yuk-Su doesn't like cooking
he can always continue drawing.
Everybody's good at something,
you know.
He actually can draw well.
Drawing?
What good is drawing?
When I was 20,
I won an award at
the Salone in Paris.
You have a great talent.
What good was this talent
when my wife starved to death?
That was just money problems.
What's so good
about drawing well?
When I was in Beijing,
I was so poor I had to sell my quilt.
And when my wife was in labour,
I couldn't send her to the hospital.
As a result,
she died giving birth to Yuk-Su.
I vowed that day I would never
draw again for the rest of my life.
Don't, Chai.
Please don't.
That little punk -
of all the things he learns,
why does he learn the worst
from me?
Look. This is what he draws.
They're worthless. Throw them away.
It's all right.
He's still very young.
He'll change as he grows up.
Don't let it get to you.
- Try and get some rest.
- Dear mother of Yuk-Su...
I'm so sorry.
Yuk-Su!
Why are you burning
your drawings?
Siu-Yu tells me you sneak off
to practise kung fu.
Do you think you can solve
all problems with force?
Yes, I can.
If I'd known kung fu
they couldn't have hurt my father.
And those men today wouldn't have
smashed your restaurant.
That is true.
With a personality like yours,
if you don't learn kung fu
somebody's going to kill you.
But why do you go out to learn?
Don't you know
I've already been teaching you?
Yeah. Washing the wok
and tossing the noodles.
Washing and tossing
are the basics of kung fu.
" One - guts. Two - strength.
Three - kung fu." Yours is kung fu?
Try it if you dare.
- Easy if you've done it for years.
- What about your strength?
Can cooking noodles
give you a 500lb punch?
Come here.
Use your new 500lb punch.
Punch.
Come on.
Yuk-Su, controlled strength -
that's what you need to learn.
Chinese kung fu is being able to
have control when you want.
I put my strength into my four fingers.
Therefore the egg didn't break.
Still not convinced?
Let's try it again.
- Wow! Washing the wok!
- Tossing the wok!
Want to learn my kind of
beef noodle kung fu?
Yes.
- Serious?
- Yes.
Then remember, if you learn my kung fu,
you can only use it in defence.
- Yes.
- No attacking.
I understand.
There'll be time for that later.
Go and take a bath.
Yes, Teacher.
Dice the tomatoes.
Slice the onion.
Slice the tomatoes.
Dice the onion.
Catch it.
Keep up with me.
Slice the pepper.
Slice the onion.
Flatten the ginger.
Dice this.
Catch this tomato.
Your hands are quick
but your eyes are far too slow.
To learn kung fu
your reflexes must be fast.
How would you stop this?
By hand?
- By ducking?
- Of course! Now, remember.
Teacher. Why do we only use
our hands and not our feet as well?
- Using feet is hard.
- That's not so.
I know a man who can kick birds
right out of the sky.
Show me your kick.
I'll try.
Left foot.
You knew which one
before I even started.
Now,
kick again.
One...!
Now, before you moved your foot
your shoulder moved.
How could you move your foot without
your shoulder moving?
Use your foot
without casting a shadow.
Now, there's one more
type of shadowless kick.
Hold on, Teacher.
Wait. Let me draw it first.
I'll be quick.
Great.
Got it.
Hold on tight.
You moved your left shoulder.
Got hold of it?
That's great!
It didn't move.
I need to draw it.
Be my model.
What?
You want to draw me?
More or less.
Now, copy the kicking pose I was in.
- Come on. Lift up your foot.
- I can't.
Yes, you can.
I'll get some paper.
Don't move.
- I'm falling.
- Good, good.
That's great.
This is great.
Wash the wok.
Wash them with both hands.
Wash, wash...
- Teacher.
- Watch it! What are you doing?
- The shadowless kick.
- The shadowless kick?
- Practising it all night?
- Yeah.
You're overdoing it. You're bruising
yourself even before you perfect it.
- You use this to practise with?
- Yeah.
But this doesn't move. When you're
fighting, your opponent will move.
Why are you hanging these woks up
at this hour of the morning?
- Washing the wok in the air.
- Think your opponent will stay still?
Left.
Right.
Left...
right...
- Don't starve me. I won't do it again.
- Go back to sleep.
Remember, while fighting you must
be agile while using your feet.
Once you lift your feet he'll kick your
other one, so you must be balanced.
- Balanced.
- Remember what I say. Balance.
Balance. My centre of balance
must be lower.
Look at you.
Are you trying to be an eel?
Yuk-Su, those eels...
I need them to make my noodles with.
- What's all this?
- You said to keep low. I'm practising.
Have you gone mad?
I want those eels dead. Cut them up.
- Okay.
- You've made him angry.
- Yuk-Su, are those eels ready?
- Yes, nearly.
Teacher, I've made seven-colour
noodles for your birthday.
Really?
Master, you've got to make a wish
before you blow out the candles.
Don't be daft - the wish shouldn't just
be mine. We should all share in it.
- Blow!
- Now, let's all blow together.
- One, two, three!
- Happy birthday.
- Yuk-Su.
- Fatty Hing, what a coincidence.
Turn on the lights.
Come on in.
Happy birthday.
No, just carry on.
- You're tense. Why are you here?
- Siu-Laan's in trouble. Come on.
- What's the matter?
- Siu-Laan's been sold as a prostitute.
How could you do that to her?
- You sold her as a whore?
- It wasn't me.
- Was it your father?
- It wasn't him either.
- Her mother did it.
- Why'd she do that?
It's all your fault.
You told me not to keep a maid,
so I persuaded my dad.
And he agreed -
and set all the maids free.
But Siu-Laan's mother sold her again,
seeing as she's still young.
- What do we do?
- Isn't your kung fu good now?
Why don't you and Master Yat
go and save her?
- No way. My father will kill me.
- So what do we do?
Siu-Laan's in real trouble. It's your
fault. You told me not to have a maid.
One more drink...
Now he's getting drunk.
Master. Here's some more wine.
It's from France. Good stuff.
- Have another one.
- Don't mind if I do...
Thank you...
Need to sleep...
- Come back soon.
- Okay.
"NO.1 BEEF NOODLES"
That's the girl.
I supply girls for the Chinatowns in
London, Korea and San Francisco.
I supply them all.
You've come to the right man.
- Have you considered the price?
- Oh, the price is no problem.
We just need to see the samples.
Not here.
These ones aren't suitable for France.
Do you have any more?
Move it.
Come on.
- Go in.
- Walk!
I'm not going.
Let go of me. No!
- I'm not going!
- Move!
Master.
- Master!
- Siu-Laan!
Let me go!
Master,
please take me home!
Don't come any closer!
- Don't! Don't!
- Get out of here.
Let's go.
Stay back!
Sonny...!
Look at that.
He didn't have to duck.
Wow! 500lb.
Keep away.
Wasn't that something,
Fatty Hing?
- He even broke the door.
- Even the wall's dented.
The "Scorpion Tactic".
The "Windblown Grass".
The meat isn't working.
- Honourable Sir!
- Get away!
- "Two Dragons At Sea".
- That's 1,000lb.
"Seeking A Failure Strategy".
"Crouching Dragon".
Honourable Sir!
Come on!
"Heaven's Knife
Whirlwind Kick".
Come on, let's go.
Let's go, quick!
Quick, quick,
let's go!
Siu-Yu!
They set fire to the restaurant.
Go save your father.
- We've got to go now!
- Siu-Yu!
Quickly! Go back and save them.
Don't worry about me.
Here...
Take him to hospital.
Quick!
Father!
Teacher!
Fire! Fire!
How tragic!
- Father!
- Pour water!
- Don't go in!
- Where's my teacher?
- He's gone to help your dad.
Teacher!
Come back out!
Father!
Teacher!
I'm going to save Siu-Yu.
Don't go in there.
Teacher...
I dragged you into this.
You're right.
Forbearance is useless.
For more than ten years
I've been concealing myself here.
Hoping to forget the underworld,
all the hate.
In the past, I was knifed and suffered
humiliation in silence.
I hoped that grinning and bearing it
would bring peace.
Teacher!
Do you know who I really am?
I'm the assassin from
the Green Dragon Triad,
called the Dragon Severer, the most
feared killer in the underworld.
You punk!
You dare to come back?
Get the weapons.
No need.
- Teacher, why did you throw it away?
- Together.
You stupid old fool,
let's see if you can beat nine of us.
Give me the stick.
- Quick.
- Yes.
Teacher, catch!
This is the real
three-section stick.
You've hit me,
Yuk-Su!
- Come bathe with me.
- No!
Don't!
- Don't? Then you'll have to starve!
- Let me go!
Help!
Catch!
Let me go.
Siu-Yu!
Sonny!
- Sonny.
- Teacher!
Sonny!
- Free the maids first.
- Okay.
You stupid old man.
Have you forgotten your humiliation?
Strange. How does he know
which foot I use before I use it?
I see.
He's watching my shoulders.
Okay, I won't move.
Let's see what he does.
"Southern shadowless kick".
Watch.
Watch, watch!
Watch!
Even if you can predict my moves,
I can still kick you to death, old man.
Don't just lie there!
Get up.
Fatty.
Let's get out of here.
Come on.
- Quick, quick, quick!
- Quickly, let's go!
Quick! Quick!
- Siu-Yu, I have to go. Fatty!
- What?
Take Siu-Yu home.
I must help my Teacher.
- Be careful.
- Go now.
Wow! Teacher,
you're the best.
Watch out,
"Crouching Dragon"!
Teacher!
How are you?
- Father?
- Sonny. Slaughter them!
You hit my father.
I'm going to take your life.
Sonny!
You hit my Teacher,
I'll hit your father.
Watch his shoulders.
Right foot.
Left foot.
Watch it!
Right foot.
- Watch carefully.
- I did, but he was too quick.
Do the "Shadowless Kick".
You want me?
Come and get me.
How can you do it on a table?
Grab his foot.
Wash the Wok.
- Teacher, I did it.
- Watch out.
Wash, wash.
Yuk-Su!
Wash.
The "Scorpion Tactic".
That hurts!
Yuk-Su,
what are you doing?
The "Eel Tactic",
Teacher.
The boy's mad. I've fought
everywhere and never seen this.
100 eels going up the beach.
I'll flatten you! I'll flatten you!
I'll flatten you!
"Heaven's Knife
Whirlwind Kick"!
Watch.
Toss the wok!
Wash the wok,
Yuk-Su!
Stand firm,
extend all limbs!
"Southern Shadowless Kick".
I did it, Teacher!
I beat him!
"To be or not to be"
is from William Shakespeare.
This is an important speech in Hamlet
when the prince takes his revenge.
Hamlet was alone in the castle,
and his feelings...
Well,
you could say...
Get up.
That slap came from Lincoln.
This one's from Shakespeare.
Drawing comics in
the classroom...!
Fai Yuk-Su used
to draw in class.
You compare yourself to him?
He is a genius. He's got an MBE.
Think you can get one?