[BEEP BEEP BEEP BEEP]
THE TIME IS 7:35.
PLEASE WAKE UP.
[BEEP BEEP BEEP]
WAKE UP. WAKE UP.
[BUZZ BUZZ BUZZ BUZZ BUZZ]
LAZY BOY,
PLEASE WAKE UP.
[BEEP BEEP]
UNH!
LAZY BOY.
[CLICK]
...CUTTING EDGE PROJECT
BY RESEARCHERS
IN PARTICLE PHYSICS
HAS BEEN SHUT DOWN BY
GOVERNMENT ORDER. HOSEA?
MARY, BIG NEWS
AT UTREL CORPORATION.
RESEARCHERS HERE WORKING
ON PARTICLE PHYSICS
BELIEVE THEY'VE
DISCOVERED A WAY
TO ACCELERATE
A SUBATOMIC PARTICLE
FASTER THAN
THE SPEED OF LIGHT.
THEY'RE USING
A GROUNDBREAKING DEVICE
CALLED A SUPERACCELERATOR.
BUT PUBLIC OUTCRY
HAS BEEN SO GREAT,
THE GOVERNMENT TODAY FINALLY
ORDERED A COMPLETE SHUTDOWN
OF THE PROJECT.
THIS TOOL WILL HELP US
TO FINALLY DEFINE THE
NATURE OF THE UNIVERSE
AND HARNESS ITS ENERGY.
IMAGINE A FACILITY
THIS SIZE
POWERING HALF THE STATE
OF CALIFOR--
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
HELLO!
HI...MOM. I'M LATE.
HOW ARE YOU?
YEAH, I--I KNOW.
I KNOW WE HAVEN'T
TALKED IN A WHILE...
BECAUSE YOU'RE GOING
TO ASK ME IF I'M DATING.
YES, MOM. I'M DATING.
A LOT OF
REALLY NICE GIRLS.
I CAN'T EVEN KEEP TRACK
OF THEIR NAMES.
YOU WANT TO KNOW
ONE OF THEIR NAMES?
UH...
BRIL...
LETTE.
BRILLETTE. YES.
SHE'S FRENCH.
SHE'S SMALL,
BUT SHE'S WIRY.
SHE LOVES TO CLEAN UP
AROUND THE KITCHEN.
MOM...LOOK.
I'M REALLY L--
BUT, MOM, MOM,
MOM, MOM...
I WILL CALL YOU LATER.
I PROMISE. GOODBYE.
PATHETIC. THAT'S NOT
HOW YOU THROW THE BALL.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU?
GOOD MORNING, KYLE.
HOW YOU DOING?
ANY WORK?
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE ALL
CLEAN UP THE PLANET TOGETHER?
CAN'T DO IT BY MYSELF.
[TIRES SCREECH]
WHOA!
BE CAREFUL. I DON'T WANT
TO SEE YOU GET RUN OVER.
UP YOURS, MY MAN.
NICE.
THAT MAY VERY WELL BE
OUR PRESIDENT SOMEDAY.
OH, MAN.
[HORN HONKS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[CRASH]
WHERE ARE
THE QUARTERLIES?
JACKSON'S READY TO CUT YOUR THROAT.
GOOD, THANKS.
HOW ARE YOU?
TED, DO YOU REALIZE YOUR HAIR
SPRAY MAY BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE OZONE HOLE?
JACK.
HOW'S IT GO?
YOU KNOW...IT'S
BEEN A BAD MORNING--
OH! OH! JACK!
OH, JACK,
I'M SO SORRY.
THANKS
FOR THE COFFEE.
ROOK TO QUEEN'S BISHOP.
WELL, LOOK WHO DECIDED TO SHOW UP.
ANN, I'M SORRY
I'M LATE.
I'M DOING YOU A FAVOR,
KEEPING YOU ON
WITH A WORK PERFORMANCE
LIKE YOURS.
SO FINISH THE PERSONNEL REPORTS,
COMPLETE THE MONTHLY BILLING,
AND CLEAN UP THE DESK
BY QUITTING TIME.
YOU KNOW,
I WAS WORKING ON--
IF YOU WANTED TO SHOW UP
ON TIME, YOU WOULD, RIGHT?
THERE WAS
A CAR ACCIDENT.
BARRY, BARRY, BARRY, I
DON'T WANT TO FIGHT WITH YOU
OR BE YOUR FRIEND EITHER,
SO DO THE WORK, HMM?
I'D HATE
TO KICK YOU OUT.
YOU'RE ONE
OF THE CUTE ONES.
YOU KNOW, SHE HAD SEX ONCE IN 1983,
BUT SHE DIDN'T
LIKE IT.
WHAT DID WE DO
LAST NIGHT?
I WOKE UP TASTING
PAVEMENT IN MY MOUTH.
WELL, WE DRANK,
AND YOU LEFT.
THEN I PICKED UP
THE BLONDE.
NO, YOU DID NOT. SHE
WASN'T INTERESTED IN YOU.
YOU LEFT, SHE GOT INTERESTED, O.K.?
YOU OWE ME 20 BUCKS
FOR YOUR DRINKS.
HERE. FILING
SYSTEM UPDATE.
AAH!
IT'S A SHOCKING
COMPUTER DISK.
PRESS THAT, AND WITHIN
THREE SECONDS IT SHOCKS YOU.
CURE FOR THE COMMON
HANGOVER. IS IT WORKING?
ARE YOUR PARENTS
RELATED?
NO.
NO? WELL,
I THINK THEY...
ARE.
MORNING, LISA.
MORNING.
OUT OF YOUR LEAGUE, MAN.
DID YOU READ THE PROFILE?
Ph.D. AT 25. THE CHICK'S
GOT NO SOCIAL LIFE.
LOOK AT THAT. SHE DOESN'T
EVEN SMOKE. HE KNOWS THAT.
HE'S OFFERED HER A CIGARETTE
BEFORE. WHAT A JERK.
LOOK. WHENEVER
SHE'S NERVOUS,
SHE BRUSHES HER HAIR
BACK OVER HER RIGHT EAR.
YOU SEE THAT? RIGHT OVER THE RIGHT EAR.
THIS HAS GONE ON FOR SIX
MONTHS. GO TALK TO HER.
WHAT, AND SPOIL
OUR RELATIONSHIP? NO.
RIGHT. YOUR PEEPING TOM THING
IS REALLY MUCH HEALTHIER.
TIME TO LEAVE
MY CUBICLE.
IF I HAD A DOOR,
I'D OPEN IT.
EXCUSE ME.
BARRY THOMAS?
YES, BUT YOU PROBABLY
WANT TO SPEAK TO MY BOSS.
I'M JUST
A SMALL GNAT--
YOU SIGNED THIS.
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU.
DR. MOXLEY,
YOU LOOK GREAT ON TV.
ANN JACKSON,
HEAD OF PERSONNEL.
TWO OF MY ASSISTANTS
HAVE BEEN REMOVED
BY SOME PAPERWORK
MR. THOMAS SIGNED.
I'VE ALREADY SENT TWO MEMOS
TO HIM REGARDING THE SUBJECT
AND GOTTEN NO RESPONSE.
I DIDN'T
GET THOSE.
LET ME HELP YOU
PERSONALLY, DOCTOR.
COME INTO MY OFFICE--
THAT WON'T BE NECESSARY, MISS JACKSON.
JUST PUT THEM BACK
IN THE SYSTEM.
LOIS HOPE,
THOMAS PLUME.
DONE.
MISS JACKSON,
WE ALL MAKE MISTAKES.
JUST CORRECT IT.
YES, SIR.
THANK YOU.
GOOD DAY.
ANN, WE--
YOU MADE ME LOOK
LIKE AN IDIOT!
YOU'RE OFF OF
TECHNICAL STAFF. OFF.
YOU'LL TAKE AND FILE
RéSUMéS, AND THAT'S IT.
HOWARD IS NOW IN CHARGE
OF TECHNICAL STAFF!
YOU--YOU BOUNCED THE HEAD
OF THE PROGRAM' ASSISTANTS!
I--I--ONE MORE.
ONE MORE SLIP-UP,
AND YOU'RE BOUNCED,
YOU GOT IT?
YEAH.
GOOD DAY.
RATTLED!
THE WHOLE OFFICE,
YOU SLOW DOWN THE WORK, AND
WE ALL SUFFER YOU KNOW THAT.
LET'S HUG.
JUST ONCE.
IT'LL BREAK
THE TENSION.
JUST SLOP ME ON
SOME OF THAT MACARONI.
YES, SIR.
OH...
THAT IS JUST
TERRIFYING.
EXCUSE ME?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU DON'T SMOKE.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
I'D OFFER YOU A CIGARETTE,
BUT YOU DON'T SMOKE,
SO WHY BOTHER EVEN?
RICO, SOME STRING BEANS,
PLEASE.
I DON'T SMOKE
EITHER.
AND SOME RICE, TOO.
SO EVEN IF
YOU DID SMOKE,
I COULDN'T OFFER YOU A
CIGARETTE. I JUST DON'T SMOKE,
SO SORRY
TO BOTHER YOU.
WHERE ARE YOU
USUALLY LOCKED UP?
OH, I'M JUST AN EXPERIMENT
GONE HORRIBLY AWRY
IN THE PERSONNEL
DEPARTMENT.
I SEE.
I'M LISA FREDERICKS.
I'M BARRY THOMAS.
WHAT IS IT
THAT YOU DO?
OH...NOTHING. I JUST
SORT OF BOOST MORALE
IN BETWEEN THREATS
OF BEING FIRED.
AH. WELL, YOU SEEM
TO HAVE A MIND.
THAT DOESN'T USUALLY
FIT IN THE SYSTEM.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
NICE MEETING
YOU, TOO.
BYE-BYE.
GOODBYE.
AND GOOD LUCK.
I'M NOT SHIPPING
OFF THE CONTINENT.
I'M JUST
HAVING LUNCH.
RIGHT, RIGHT.
OHHH...
SO, UH, SHE LIKES ME...
A LOT.
WOULDN'T YOU AGREE?
I'D SAY YOU AND AN ICE CREAM
HEADACHE ARE NECK AND NECK.
DO I ALWAYS SOUND
LIKE SUCH AN IDIOT,
OR DO I SAVE IT FOR
THOSE I WANT TO IMPRESS?
YOU'RE THINKING WRONG. WHAT IF
THE ICE QUEEN THING'S AN ACT,
A DEFENSE?
O.K.
WHAT IF SHE'S
THE LONELY ONE?
HUH? SHE'D BE THANKFUL
TO THE FIRST GUY THAT CAME
OVER TO HER AND SAID ANYTHING.
[BEEP BEEP]
I KNOW THESE THINGS,
MAN.
I PICKED UP A BLONDE
LAST NIGHT, RIGHT?
RIGHT.
UM, RIGHT.
SHE'S DYING
TO BE TALKED TO.
I GOT AN AIR CONDITIONING
REPAIR FOR...DR. SPECTER?
SURE.
UH...AHEM.
YEAH, GO AHEAD.
YES?
BARRY THOMAS. I'M HERE
TO SEE DR. FREDERICKS.
THERE'S A SLIGHT PROBLEM
IN PERSONNEL.
YOU GOING TO ERASE HER
FROM THE COMPUTER, TOO?
IT'S REGARDING
HER PAYCHECK.
WE'RE UPDATING
OUR FILING SYSTEM,
AND I HAVE TO VERIFY SOME PERSONAL
INFORMATION, MISS..."ZEBO."
OTHERWISE, HER CHECK
MAY BE DELAYED.
WELL, THAT'S THE TYPE OF CONFUSION
WE ALWAYS EXPECT
FROM PERSONNEL.
THANK YOU.
WELL, YOU DON'T SEEM TO
BE DOING VERY WELL TODAY!
[INDISTINCT]
GET OUT
OF MY OFFICE!
NOW!
GOODBYE.
WHO ARE YOU?
ARE YOU AUTHORIZED
TO BE BACK HERE?
IT'S O.K. COME IN AND SHUT THE DOOR.
I'LL JUST COME IN
AND SHUT THE DOOR.
I WAS JUST TAKING CARE
OF DR. MOXLEY,
HELPING OUT
WITH ONE OF--HEY!
I HAVE A GERANIUM
PLANT AT HOME.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
NOTHING. I WAS JUST
IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD,
SO I THOUGHT
I'D SAY HELLO.
HELLO.
YOU CAME BACK IN THE
MIDDLE OF A RESTRICTED AREA
TO FLIRT WITH ME?
IS THIS...A BAD TIME?
WE SPOKE FOR 10 SECONDS
ON A FOOD LINE.
THAT GIVES YOU THE
RIGHT TO COME HIT ON ME?
NO. NO. NO--
I DON'T CONSIDER PLAYFUL BANTER
OVER STEAMING STRING BEANS
GROUNDS FOR ROMANTIC
TRYSTS, SEXUAL ADVANCES,
OR EVEN--CAN YOU GET OUT
FROM BEHIND THERE?
EVEN A LONG-DISTANCE
FRIENDSHIP.
IT WAS GREAT
SEEING YOU, TOO.
I'M SORRY. TIMING'S EVERYTHING,
AND THIS JUST ISN'T THE TIME.
IT'S NOT THE TIME,
RIGHT? IT'S NOT THE TIME.
[DOOR SLAMS]
HOW'D IT GO?
OH, GOOD, THANKS. I'LL BE
ALONE FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE.
THANKS, PAL.
DRINKS TONIGHT?
YES, HOWARD. LET'S JUST
DRINK OUR LIVES AWAY,
SHALL WE?
O.K.
OHHH...
BARRY, WHAT'S UP?
YOU WITH ME? LET'S DO IT!
COMING.
HI, REYNALDO.
SEñORITA.
AH. I WANT
A DOZEN, PLEASE.
OH?
OH, THOSE
ARE QUITE BEAUTIFUL.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
POR NADA, SEñORITA.
[TIRES SCREECH]
YOU SAY THIS HAPPENED JUST AFTER WORK?
YEAH.
WHAT TIME
WAS THAT?
6:15.
DID YOU KNOW
MISS FREDERICKS?
NO.
NO, I DIDN'T
KNOW HER AT ALL.
I'M SORRY, BARRY. I KNOW
HOW MUCH YOU CARED ABOUT HER.
I'M QUITTING TOMORROW.
WHAT?
GETTING ON
WITH MY LIFE.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT? WHAT ABOUT ME?
IF I STAY ONE MORE DAY, WHAT DO I HAVE?
I HAVE MY PANTS BEHIND A
DESK, THAT'S WHAT I HAVE.
WE NEED TWO MORE
OF THESE, PLEASE.
MY DAD SAID I'D NEVER AMOUNT TO MUCH.
I DON'T WANT
TO DISAPPOINT HIM.
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
WHATEVER HAPPENED
TODAY WAS HORRIBLE,
BUT WE DON'T STOP.
WE KEEP GOING.
ARE YOU GOING
TO TURN BACK?
MAYBE.
NO.
[POTTERY CLATTERS]
[THUNDER]
TIME?
THE TIME IS 12:00.
I WONDER WHAT
SHE WAS THINKING ABOUT.
NOT ABOUT ME,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
LAZY BOY.
[THUNDER]
[LIGHT BULB CRACKLES]
[CRACKLING]
I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR THIS.
THE TIME IS 12:01.
[BEEP BEEP]
THE TIME IS 7:35.
PLEASE WAKE UP.
[BEEP BEEP]
WAKE UP. WAKE UP.
[BUZZ BUZZ BUZZ
BUZZ BUZZ BUZZ]
OH, PLEASE.
I HAVE A HANGOVER.
LAZY BOY,
PLEASE WAKE UP.
[BEEP BEEP]
NO, I DON'T.
...THIS CUTTING
EDGE PROJECT
BY RESEARCHERS
IN PARTICLE PHYSICS
HAS BEEN SHUT DOWN BY
GOVERNMENT ORDER. HOSEA?
MARY, BIG NEWS
AT UTREL CORPORATION.
RESEARCHERS HERE WORKING
ON PARTICLE PHYSICS
BELIEVE THEY'VE
DISCOVERED A WAY
TO ACCELERATE
A SUBATOMIC PARTICLE
FASTER THAN
THE SPEED OF LIGHT.
THEY ARE USING
A GROUNDBREAKING DEVICE
CALLED A SUPERACCELERATOR.
COME ON, HOSEA,
THAT'S OLD NEWS.
WHAT ABOUT
LISA'S MURDER?
...FINALLY ORDERED A COMPLETE
SHUTDOWN OF THE PROJECT.
THIS TOOL WILL HELP US
TO FINALLY DEFINE THE
NATURE OF THE UNIVERSE
AND HARNESS ITS ENERGY.
NOW, IMAGINE
A FACILITY THIS SIZE
POWERING HALF THE STATE OF
CALIFORNIA. IT'S REMARKABLE.
IF WE COULD ACTUALLY
POWER A PARTICLE
FASTER THAN THE SPEED
OF LIGHT,
THE ENERGY RELEASED
WOULD BE CATASTROPHIC.
TIME AND SPACE
WOULD BE SHATTERED.
WE'D BE PUNCHED
BACKWARDS IN TIME
AND THEN MOVE FORWARD
UNTIL THE ACCELERATOR IS FIRED
AGAIN, AND WE'LL PUNCH BACK AGAIN
IN AN ENDLESS LOOP,
LIKE A SKIPPING RECORD.
THIS CIRCULAR TIME BOUNCE
WOULD BECOME OUR PRISON,
AND WE'D BE PRISONERS
WITHOUT MEMORY
IN A CELL
WITHOUT A KEY.
WHICH THEORY IS TRUE?
ANOTHER TUNE GOING OUT OVER
THE KBRY LOVERS' REQUEST...
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH. SCIENTIST
KILLED AT WORK. COME ON.
...AND TEMPERATURES WILL
DIMINISH BY EARLY NEXT WEEK.
WE MAY S--
ONE OF US FELL DOWN
LAST NIGHT.
OH, MAN, I'M GOING
TO BE LATE AGAIN.
O.K., I WAS DRUNK.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[RING]
HELLO.
HI...MOM, I--
I'M RUNNING LATE AGAIN.
HOW ARE YOU?
YEAH, RIGHT. IT'S BEEN A REAL
LONG TIME SINCE WE TALKED.
I DID.
I DID MEET A GIRL.
NO, I DON'T THINK
YOU'RE GOING TO MEET HER.
BECAUSE SHE WAS SHOT.
NO, NOT-- NOT WITH
CAMERAS, WITH BULLETS.
MOM, I--I GOT TO GO.
I'LL CALL YOU LATER.
O.K...I WAS REALLY DRUNK.
THAT'S NOT HOW
YOU THROW THE BALL.
PATHETIC. WHAT'S
WRONG WITH YOU?
TALK ABOUT PATHETIC.
[TIRES SCREECH]
HO! WHOA! WHOA! WHOA!
DIDN'T I TELL YOU
TO BE MORE CAREFUL?
UP YOURS, MY MAN.
ALL RIGHT! NOW WE'RE
GETTING SOMEWHERE!
[HORN HONKS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[CRASH]
WHERE ARE
THE QUARTERLIES?
JACKSON'S READY TO CUT YOUR THROAT.
ON HER DESK.
CALM DOWN.
COMB YOUR HAIR.
IRON YOUR PANTS.
JACK, WOULD YOU BELIEVE
NOTHING WAS IN THE PAPER
ABOUT LISA FREDERICKS?
SHE WIN AN AWARD
OR SOMETHING?
AAH!
OH!
OH, JACK, I'M SO SORRY.
CAN I HELP? I'LL--
NO! NO!
THANKS.
HOWARD...
DAMN IT!
THIS ISN'T FUNNY.
WELL, LOOK WHO DECIDED
TO SHOW UP.
I CLEANED OFF THIS WHOLE
DESK YESTERDAY BEFORE I LEFT.
I'M DOING YOU A FAVOR KEEPING
YOU ON WITH YOUR WORK PERFORMANCE.
SO FINISH
THE PERSONNEL REPORTS,
COMPLETE THE MONTHLY
BILLING,
AND CLEAN UP THE DESK
BY QUITTING TIME.
I DID THIS WORK.
I CAN SEE THAT.
IF YOU WANTED TO BE ON TIME, YOU WOULD.
THERE WAS
A CAR ACCIDENT...AGAIN.
I DON'T WANT
TO FIGHT WITH YOU
OR BE YOUR FRIEND,
EITHER.
SO LET'S JUST
DO THE WORK.
I'D HATE
TO KICK YOU OUT.
YOU'RE ONE
OF THE CUTE ONES.
OW...
DID YOU SEE THAT?
SHE CAME IN HERE JUST
LIKE IT WAS YESTERDAY.
SHE HAD SEX ONCE IN 1983,
BUT SHE DIDN'T LIKE IT.
HERE'S THE UPDATE ON
THE NEW FILING SYSTEM.
YOU THINK I'M
A CRETINOUS MORON
WHO'D FALL FOR
THE SAME TRICK TWICE?
[ZAP]
TRICK?
THE SHOCKING DISK TRICK.
YOU GOT ME YESTERDAY.
HOW COME LISA FREDERICKS'
MURDER WASN'T ON TV,
WASN'T IN THE NEWSPAPERS, NOTHING?
LISA'S MURDER?
HOWARD, STAY WITH ME,
PLEASE.
YOU WERE STANDING
RIGHT NEXT TO ME
WHEN SHE WAS SHOT,
RIGHT?
WE TALKED TO THE POLICE
TOGETHER.
WE WENT DRINKING
LAST NIGHT.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO REMIND
ME I'M QUITTING TODAY.
HOMICIDE, PLEASE.
DETECTIVE, UH--UH--UH--
KRYLES.
WE DRANK. YOU LEFT.
I TRIED TO PICK UP THE
BLONDE, SHE BLEW ME OFF,
I WATCHED BATMAN AT HOME,
CALLED THE POWER LINE...
THE BLONDE WAS TWO NIGHTS
AGO. YOU SAID YOU SCORED.
DETECTIVE KRYLES?
YOU QUESTIONED ME LAST NIGHT
ABOUT LISA FREDERICKS' MURDER?
LISA FREDERICKS.
SHE WAS KILLED
LAST NIGHT.
I SAW IT. I WAS THERE.
YOU QUESTIONED ME.
HELLO?
HE HUNG UP
THE PHONE.
YOU CALLED HIM,
DIDN'T YOU?
YEAH.
YOU SET THIS
WHOLE GAG UP.
I'LL GO PRETTY FAR FOR A JOKE,
BUT I DON'T COVER UP HOMICIDES.
LISA?
IT'S FINE.
PLEASE GET THE OTHER
PAPERS TO ME BY NOON.
LISA.
YES?
BARRY FROM
THE LUNCH LINE.
YOU--
YOU KICKED ME--
I CAN'T GET OVER THIS.
SORRY. YOU MUST BE MISTAKEN.
I THOUGHT
YOU WERE DEAD.
NO, AND I HOPE MY CONDITION
CONTINUES. GOODBYE.
I'M JUST SO HAPPY
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
WHO IS HE?
I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW YOU.
CIGARETTE?
NO, THANKS. SHALL WE GET THIS OVER WITH?
MISS JACKSON,
WE ALL MAKE MISTAKES.
JUST CORRECT IT.
ABSOLUTELY.
GOOD DAY.
DR. MOXLEY,
REST ASSURED...
WHAT'S GOING ON?
TELL HIM
I'M NOT INVOLVED.
YOU MADE ME LOOK
LIKE AN IDIOT.
YOU'RE OFF
OF TECHNICAL STAFF.
YOU'LL TAKE AND FILE RéSUMéS. THAT'S IT.
HOWARD, YOU'LL HANDLE TECHNICAL STAFF.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M SAYING THAT.
YOU BOUNCED THE DEPARTMENT
HEAD'S TWO ASSISTANTS.
I HANDLED THAT YESTERDAY.
ONE MORE SLIP-UP LIKE
THIS, AND YOU'RE BOUNCED.
GOT IT?
MM-HMM.
BOUNCED.
HEY, COME ON, MAN.
COME ON,
THAT'S MY PAPER.
COME ON.
DR. MOXLEY.
I'M BARRY THOMAS.
WE MET YESTERDAY.
OH, YOU'RE THOMAS.
WE HAVEN'T MET.
ANYWAY, THAT MATTER'S TAKEN CARE OF.
I HEARD ON THE NEWS
ABOUT A TIME BOUNCE--
TIME STOPS, GOES BACK,
AND REPEATS.
THEY USED MY REMARKS OUT OF
CONTEXT. IT'S VERY COMPLICATED.
BUT I THINK THE TIME
BOUNCE HAS HAPPENED.
THIS DAY
IS REPEATING.
WHAT AN UNUSUAL THING
TO SAY.
I'VE SEEN IT-- THINGS
REPEATING EVERYWHERE.
IF THE BOUNCE
WERE TO HAPPEN,
EVERYTHING WOULD LOOP BACK
TO A STARTING POINT.
YOUR MEMORY
WOULD ALSO BE RESET
ALONG WITH THE REST
OF THE UNIVERSE.
THE FACT THAT YOU THINK
YOU REMEMBER IT
MEANS IT HASN'T HAPPENED.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
GOOD DAY.
BUT--
GREAT.
RATTLED.
THE WHOLE OFFICE,
YOU SLOW DOWN THE
WORK, AND WE ALL SUFFER.
YOU KNOW THAT.
RIGHT. RIGHT.
I'M SORRY
ABOUT THIS MORNING.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN
A SHOCK.
ARE YOU ASSUMING
WE'RE NOW FRIENDS
AND WILL HAVE
A CONVERSATION?
NO. THAT'S THE LAST
THING ON MY MIND.
STRING BEANS
AND RICE, PLEASE.
I JUST HATE MEETING NEW,
INTERESTING, AND ATTRACTIVE PEOPLE.
DON'T START A CONVERSATION
WITH ME. MACARONI, PLEASE.
YES, SIR.
THANK YOU.
SORRY. I DIDN'T
CATCH YOUR NAME.
ME? UH, BARRY.
BARRY THOMAS.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO HAVE
LUNCH WITH ME TODAY?
I'M SURE YOU'RE NICE,
BUT I DON'T THINK SO.
I'LL MAKE IT
WORTH YOUR WHILE.
HOW'S THAT?
I'LL PAY FOR
YOUR LUNCH.
I WON'T SPIT FOOD
IN YOUR FACE
OR MAKE SILLY NOISES
WITH MY LIPS.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
O.K.
THANK YOU.
Help!
I'M STRICTLY INTO THEORY.
NO GREASE STAINS.
THE PHYSICAL WORLD
IS JUST TOO DISAPPOINTING.
BUT TO USE YOUR MIND AND CREATE
THE THING-- THAT'S EXCITING.
THINGS DON'T ALWAYS
WORK OUT THE WAY YOU WANT.
YOU SHOULDN'T PICK UP MEN
AT LUNCH.
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHERE THEY'VE BEEN.
JOAN, BARRY. PLEASE EAT
SOMETHING. YOU'RE GETTING MEAN.
HE'S NOT WEARING
ANY RINGS.
YOU ARE.
RELAX. HER SISTER
GAVE IT TO HER.
SHE'S AVAILABLE.
ASIDE FROM DINNER WITH ME
TONIGHT, HER SCHEDULE'S OPEN.
ON THAT SUBTLE,
PRIVATE NOTE...
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO MAKE THAT DINNER.
JOAN WILL MURDER ME
IF I FLAKE OUT ON HER.
AGAIN.
ONLY TWICE.
NO. I MEAN YOU'RE NOT GOING TO MAKE
THAT DINNER TONIGHT.
WHY NOT?
[SIGHS]
THIS DAY IS REPEATING.
THE TIME BOUNCE
HAS HAPPENED.
RIGHT AFTER WORK
AT 6:15
YOU GO ACROSS THE STREET TO BUY FLOWERS,
AND YOU'RE...SHOT.
I'VE ALREADY
SEEN IT.
PEOPLE ARE SAYING THE SAME
THINGS THEY SAID YESTERDAY.
THEY'RE DOING
THE SAME THINGS.
THE NEWS HAS
THE SAME STORY.
IT'S ALL HAPPENING AGAIN THE SAME WAY.
PROVE IT.
POINT SOMETHING OUT.
O.K.
OH.
AH-CHOO!
I HAVEN'T BEEN
PAYING ATTENTION.
I'LL MAKE IT EASIER.
WHAT DO I DO NEXT?
[BEEPER SOUNDS]
YOUR BEEPER GOES OFF, AND YOU LEAVE.
I HOPE YOU'VE HAD FUN.
CALL ME WHEN YOU GROW UP.
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME.
YOU GET SHOT TWO TIMES.
UH, CAN I HELP YOU?
UH, PERSONNEL. GOING TO SEE DR. MOXLEY.
HE'S EXPECTING ME.
O.K. FINE.
GO AHEAD.
[LISA] LOOKS LIKE IT'S
CONTAINED. JUST IN THAT ONE SEAL.
[DR. MOXLEY]
JUST ONE SEAL...
[LISA] THIS MEANS WE CAN'T
SHUT THE ACCELERATOR DOWN TODAY.
[DENK]
WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
THE ACCELERATOR HAS
TO BE FULLY OPERATIONAL
UNTIL THIS IS
UNDER CONTROL.
IF ONE MORE SEAL
HAD BROKEN,
WE WOULD HAVE IRRADIATED
THE ENTIRE LAB.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT HAPPENED.
IT'S A TERRIBLE
EMBARRASSMENT.
WE TELL HIM IT'S SAFE,
AND NOW WE CAN'T DISMANTLE
THE CORE FOR TWO WEEKS.
I' GET
A CLEANUP CREW.
I'M SORRY, THADIUS.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT,
LISA.
FOR 40 YEARS
SOMETHING'S GONE WRONG
WITH EVERY PROJECT
I'VE WORKED ON.
WELL, YOU'RE BOUND
FOR A CHANGE, THEN.
MAYBE THE NEXT PROJECT
WILL HIT.
THIS IS THE LAST PROJECT I'LL SUPERVISE.
THE WAY THE PRESS
IS HANDLING THIS...
I CAN'T TAKE ANY
FURTHER DISAPPOINTMENTS.
YOU CHECK
THE OTHER SEALS.
NO CLEANUP
UNTIL 10 A.M. TOMORROW.
I'LL CHECK THOSE OTHER
SEALS AND STRUCTURES.
I'LL EXAMINE THEM. I'LL
DETERMINE WHAT HAPPENED.
SHE'LL DO IT.
THADIUS,
IT'S MY JOB.
ONE MORE SEAL BREAKS,
WE'LL BE READING AT NIGHT
BY OUR OWN GLOW.
THIS IS MY DEPARTMENT.
I WANT HER
TO DO IT!
I'VE BEEN WITH THIS PROJECT
SINCE THE BEGINNING.
YOU'VE CAUSED
ENOUGH PROBLEMS.
HOW DID YOU
GET IN HERE?
I WANT SECURITY
DOWN HERE IMMEDIATELY.
TAKE THOSE FILES
TO LEVEL THREE.
I NEED TO SPEAK
TO MR. STEVENS BY 4:00.
GET ME SOME COFFEE,
SOME FRESH...COFFEE.
SURPRISE.
EMPLOYEE OF THE MONTH.
YOU TRESPASS INTO THE
HIGHEST LEVEL SECURITY AREA.
YOU ACCOST THREE
HEADS OF THE PROJECT,
AND I'M SUPPOSED
TO EXPLAIN IT.
I LIKE YOU, BARRY.
I REALLY DO.
YOU'RE FIRED.
GIVE ME YOUR I.D. AND
CLEAN OUT YOUR OFFICE
BY THE END OF TODAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S FUNNY?
IF TODAY
WAS REALLY TODAY,
I WOULD HAVE QUIT
BY NOW.
HEY, SORRY, MAN.
YEAH, WELL,
STUFF HAPPENS.
WHAT'S UP?
THEY FIRE YOU?
WILL YOU BELIEVE ME
IF I TELL YOU SOMETHING
THAT SOUNDS IMPOSSIBLE?
WELL, YEAH.
LISA FREDERICKS WILL
BE MURDERED AT 6:15.
THIS WHOLE DAY
IS REPEATING.
WE'RE IN A TIME BOUNCE.
DID YOU TELL ANYONE?
YES.
THAT'S WHY
THEY FIRED YOU.
YOU'RE STRESSED OUT. YOU
HAVE DEJA VU OR VERTIGO.
THERE HAVE LAWS AGAINST
THIS. THEY CAN'T FIRE YOU.
HOWARD...UP YOURS.
SORRY, MAN.
DR. FREDERICKS, PLEASE.
WILL YOU HAVE HER CALL
BARRY THOMAS, EXTENSION 322?
IT'S URGENT.
LISA!
YOUR I.D., SIR.
I...
SIR, I CAN'T LET YOU
IN THERE WITHOUT I.D.
HI, REYNALDO.
AH, SEÑORITA.
¿COMO ESTA?
GOOD.
DO YOU HAVE MY ROSES?
HOLD IT. WHAT'S UP?
WHAT'S GOING ON, MAN?
TALK TO ME.
LISA!
GET DOWN!
OH, THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
UH...I GUESS I...
I CAME OUT BEFORE BARRY
WHEN I HEARD THE SHOOTING--
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
BARRY THOMAS?
DO YOU
BELIEVE ME NOW?
YOU'LL HAVE TO COME ALONG
TO ANSWER SOME QUESTIONS.
HE ALREADY
GAVE A STATEMENT.
HE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
HE CALLED ME
THIS MORNING
TO TELL ME
ABOUT HER MURDER.
DO YOU WANT TO GO
TO JAIL, TOO?
[THUNDER]
THIS DAY'S
ABOUT TO REPEAT.
NO KIDDING. THEY'RE ALL
ABOUT THE SAME AROUND HERE.
OH, MY GOD.
BUT WHAT IF IT DOESN'T?
I WANT ANOTHER CHANCE!
NO MORE CHANCES, MAN.
YOU'RE DOING TIME NOW.
THE TIME IS 7:35.
O.K.
TODAY I SAVE HER.
WELL, LOOK WHO DECIDED
TO SHOW UP.
YOU'RE RIGHT. IF I WANTED
TO BE ON TIME, I WOULD.
I'LL FINISH THE PERSONNEL REPORTS,
COMPLETE THE MONTHLY BILLING,
AND CLEAN OFF MY DESK
BY QUITTING TIME.
YOU DON'T WANT TO FIGHT
OR BE MY FRIEND.
SO WHY KICK ME OUT
WHEN I'M SO DAMN CUTE?
MM-HMM.
HOWARD.
WHAT?
GET RID OF
THAT STAIN.
THAT'S GOOD WORK,
MAN.
YOU ALMOST PREVENTED HER
FROM TALKING ENTIRELY.
YOU DON'T REMEMBER A THING
ABOUT YESTERDAY, DO YOU?
WE HAD SOME DRINKS.
I PICKED UP THE BLONDE
AFTER YOU LEFT.
SHE BLEW YOU OFF. YOU WENT
HOME. YOU WATCHED BATMAN.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE ME,
SO JUST TRUST ME.
I NEED TO TALK
TO DR. MOXLEY.
HE'LL BE HERE
IN 30 SECONDS.
FIRST I HAVE
TO TALK TO LISA.
WHEN MOXLEY GETS HERE,
KEEP HIM HERE. GOT IT?
DR. MOXLEY'S COMING HERE.
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
TRUST ME.
I KNOW.
[ZAP]
JACK!
LISA!
THE TIME BOUNCE...
YES?
IS A FASCINATING THEORY,
DON'T YOU THINK?
WHO ARE YOU?
I'M BARRY...THOMAS.
YOU SEEM TO KNOW BOTH
OUR NAMES VERY WELL.
I DON'T MEAN
TO SOUND FORWARD,
BUT I'M HAVING LUNCH
IN THE CAFETERIA AT 12:30.
I HATE MEETING NEW,
INTERESTING, ATTRACTIVE PEOPLE.
I'D RATHER EAT ALONE,
BUT IF WE HAVE TO,
ISN'T IT BETTER TO DISCUSS
HOW WONDERFUL THEORY IS
AND HOW DISAPPOINTING
THE PHYSICAL WORLD CAN BE?
THAT'S QUITE A QUALIFIED PICKUP LINE.
I'VE BEEN WORKING ON IT
FOR TWO DAYS NOW.
ENJOY YOUR
VERY NICE MORNING.
12:30. DON'T FORGET.
WHO'S THAT?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
CIGARETTE?
SHE DOESN'T SMOKE.
YOU'VE WORKED HERE, WHAT,
FOUR YEARS? PAY ATTENTION.
HOW'D YOU KNOW
ABOUT MOXLEY?
MOXLEY WAS
ALREADY HERE?
YOU MADE ME
LOOK LIKE AN IDIOT.
YOU'RE OFF
OF TECHNICAL STAFF.
I KNOW ALL ABOUT IT.
DR. MOXLEY?
JOAN, I NEED THE ISOTOPE
STUDIES FROM DR. MORGENRAU.
JOHN.
OH, YES.
HI.
IF WE'RE RIGHT,
WE DISPROVE EINSTEIN.
THAT'S PRETTY
GROUNDBREAKING WORK.
IT'S BEEN THREE YEARS
OF MY LIFE.
ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO BREAK THE LAW?
SOME PEOPLE WOULD.
THEY TOLD US TO PULL THE
PLUG, AND WE'RE PULLING IT.
DON'T MAKE THIS
MORE DIFFICULT.
O.K.
I SAW SOME COOLANT
STUDIES IN THE LAB.
THEY LOOK LIKE YOURS.
I THOUGHT I BROUGHT THEM ALL BACK.
I'M SORRY I SNAPPED.
IT'S NOT ABOUT YOU.
FORGET IT.
MARILYN, DO YOU HAVE
THOSE PAPERS?
THIS AFTERNOON
SOON ENOUGH?
YEAH, FINE.
THANK YOU.
[SCRAPING]
SHUT UP.
I BELIEVE YOU WANTED
THE STRING BEANS.
THEY'RE QUITE
EXCELLENT TODAY.
YOU ARE A VERY
UNUSUAL PERSON.
WHAT DO YOU DO AGAIN?
I USED TO WORK
IN PERSONNEL.
NOW I'M SORT OF TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT MY LIFE.
YOU'RE CHANGING JOBS?
NO. THE JOB IS THE SAME
EVERY MORNING.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU
SOMETHING.
LOOK AT
THE LUNCH LINE.
THOSE TWO PEOPLE ARE ABOUT
TO BUMP INTO EACH OTHER.
AND THAT WOMAN THERE
WILL SNEAK AN OLIVE
OFF THE SALAD BAR.
SEE THAT GUY...
RIGHT THERE?
HE'S GOING
TO SNEEZE.
AH-CHOO!
O.K., YOU'RE PSYCHIC.
NO. NO, I'M JUST LEARNING
TO APPRECIATE THE MOMENT.
IT SEEMS TO BE
ALL I HAVE ANYMORE.
DO YOU BELIEVE
IN SECOND CHANCES?
NO. UM, NO, I DON'T.
WHAT IF--
WHAT IF THE TIME BOUNCE
REALLY HAPPENED
AND YOU HAD A SECOND
CHANCE... TO KNOW SOMEONE,
SOMEONE YOU WATCHED
FROM A DISTANCE
AND THEN GOT CLOSER TO?
SOMEONE YOU TALKED TO ONCE
AND REALLY GOT TO KNOW.
LIKE WHAT THEIR
FAVORITE FLOWER WAS.
LIKE RED ROSES.
WELL, YOU COULD HAVE
SEEN ME BUY THEM.
YOUR RING?
YOUR SISTER GAVE YOU
THAT RING.
JOAN SAT THERE
YESTERDAY AND TOLD ME.
SHE'S SUPPOSED TO
BE HERE TODAY,
BUT SOMETHING HAPPENED.
SHE'S NOT HERE.
I TOLD HER
I HAD A LUNCH DATE.
THIS IS VERY WEIRD.
LOOK,
YOU'RE A SCIENTIST.
LET'S TALK THEORY.
THE TIME BOUNCE
MUST HAVE HAP--
OH, EXCUSE ME,
DR. FREDERICKS.
I'VE JUST HAD A COMPLAINT
THAT MR. THOMAS WAS SEEN
IN YOUR OFFICE THIS MORNING.
WHAT?
I WAS PASSING BY AND
SAW DENK IN YOUR OFFICE.
HE TOOK SOMETHING
WHILE YOU WERE--
IF I'D KNOWN ABOUT THIS, I'D
HAVE FIRED HIM IMMEDIATELY.
I MADE A TIME MAP--
WHAT WERE YOU DOING
IN WING B?
YOU GO ACROSS THE STREET
AND BUY FLOWERS AND--
YOU'RE KILLED. YOU'RE SHOT.
I'VE SEEN IT TWICE NOW.
YOU'RE FIRED. ONE HOUR
TO CLEAN OUT YOUR DESK.
YOU'RE FIRED. GET OUT.
GOODBYE.
YOUR BEEPER'S
ABOUT TO GO OFF.
OHH...
DR. FREDERICKS,
I AM SO SORRY.
OH.
WELL...
WHAT A DISAPPOINTMENT.
ACTUALLY, I DIDN'T
HIRE HIM.
HE WAS HERE
WHEN I CAME.
[BEEP BEEP BEEP]
HEY, SORRY.
THANKS, JACK.
WHAT HAPPENED?
DID SHE FIRE YOU?
I NEED A YELLOW
UTILITY WORKER BADGE.
WHY? LISTEN, MAN, I WANT
TO HAVE CHILDREN. O.K.?
JACKSON WILL
CASTRATE ME.
SHE DOESN'T COME BACK
UNTIL 1:20.
THAT'S WHEN SHE
FIRED ME YESTERDAY.
WE GOT FOUR MINUTES.
THE AIR-CONDITIONING REPAIR GUY
GOES INTO THE SCIENCE WING AT 1:40.
THAT'S 24 MINUTES
FROM NOW.
WHIP ME UP
A WORK REQUISITION ORDER.
I COULD FAKE MY WAY
THROUGH.
NO, I DON'T KNOW.
PEOPLE CAN DIE
OF STRESS, BARRY.
IT'S HAPPENING TO ME.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
REDECORATING?
I'LL HAVE TO BE CROSSING
GUARD AT A FEMINIST CAMP.
YES, MISS JACKSON.
WE'RE DONE.
AND CALL MR. STEVENS. I
NEED TO SPEAK TO HIM BY 4:00.
GET ME SOME COFFEE,
SOME FRESH COFFEE.
[CRASH]
OOH! OOH!
OOH!
OH, MISS JACKSON,
WHAT HAPPENED?
ANNETTE, WHAT DID YOU DO TO MY CHAIR?
PROMISE ME
YOU WON'T HAVE
A LARGE FURRY PUNGENT BEAR-CHILD
COMING OUT OF YOUR CHEST.
JUST PROMISE ME.
PROMISE.
HEY, HOW YA DOIN'?
I HAVE TO REPAIR AN
AIR-CONDITIONING UNIT
FOR DR. SPECTER.
WHERE'S YOUR UNIFORM?
THEY TOLD ME
TO CARRY A WINDOW.
THEY DIDN'T SAY
THE PAINT WAS WET.
I'LL GET
ANOTHER ONE.
GO AHEAD.
AHEM.
I HAVE AN AIR-CONDITIONING
REPAIR FOR A DR. MOXLEY.
THIS SAYS
DR. SPECTER'S OFFICE.
OH! MOXLEY, SPECTER.
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE?
ALL THESE OFFICES
ARE INTERCONNECTED.
IT COULD BE 100 DEGREES
IN THERE TOMORROW MORNING.
JUST SIGN THIS.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT HAPPENED.
THIS IS A TERRIBLE
EMBARRASSMENT FOR ME.
WE TELL THEM IT'S SAFE.
NOW WE CAN'T DISMANTLE
THE CORE FOR TWO WEEKS.
LET'S GO, DENK.
COME ON.
THIS IS ROBERT DENK.
WE BROKE AN ISOTOPE
SEAL IN THE CORE.
I NEED A CLEANUP CREW
IMMEDIATELY.
ALL RIGHT.
CLEAR A CLEANUP CREW
FOR TOMORROW AT 10 A.M.
AHH. COME ON, LISA.
GET YOUR BUTT
OUT HERE.
WHAT'S UP?
COME INTO
MY OFFICE.
STAY OFF OF HARDWARE.
THAT'S MY BUSINESS.
I'LL TAKE RESPONSIBILITY.
YOU WILL NOT
TAKE RESPONSIBILITY!
THADIUS ASKED ME
TO CHECK.
WE HAVE EQUAL STATUS.
DAMN IT!
DOCTOR...
LET ME DO WHAT I DO WELL.
WE WON'T HAVE PROBLEMS.
YOU'RE NOT DOING
VERY WELL TODAY.
DO NOT JEOPARDIZE
THE TIME I PUT IN HERE.
IS THAT CLEAR?
DON'T INTERFERE
WITH MY WORK.
I'M WARNING YOU.
DON'T YOU THREATEN ME.
GET OUT OF MY OFFICE!
NOW!
FINE.
[DOOR CLOSES]
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING IN MY OFFICE?
UH,
AIR-CONDITIONING REPAIR.
GOOD THING I WAS HERE.
YOUR OFFICE WOULD'VE BEEN
A SAUNA BY TOMORROW MORNING.
I'VE GOT AN AIR-CONDITIONING
REPAIR FOR, UH, DR. SPECTER.
YEAH. RIGHT.
SOMEBODY'S ALREADY HERE.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
THEY JUST CALLED ME
30 MINUTES AGO.
I JUST GOT HERE.
WE MIGHT HAVE
AN ILLEGAL ENTRY.
TWO MINUTES
OF YOUR TIME, PLEASE.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
SECURITY.
THE ACCELERATOR'S
GOING TO BE FIRED TONIGHT.
IMPOSSIBLE.
WE'RE DISMANTLING IT.
BECAUSE
THE SEAL'S BROKEN.
THAT'S
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION.
SOMEONE IS DELAYING YOU
ON PURPOSE.
THEY SABOTAGED IT SO
IT CAN'T BE DISMANTLED,
SO THEY CAN FIRE IT
TONIGHT.
PLEASE CHECK
THE COMPUTER.
IF I AM WRONG,
I WILL BE HAPPY TO THROW
MYSELF OUT OF YOUR OFFICE.
PLEASE.
O.K.
I SHOULD HAVE
CLEARANCE FOR THIS.
YOU SEE THAT?
THEY'RE TRYING TO KEEP
THE INFORMATION HIDDEN.
THERE'S A FILE I
DON'T USE ANYMORE--
MATHEMATICAL THEORY THAT'S
STILL LINKED TO THE ACCELERATOR.
OH, MY GOD.
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO TELL
YOU NOW FOR TWO DAYS.
ATTENTION, WE HAVE
A SECURITY ALERT
FOR ALL SCIENCE DIVISIONS.
PLEASE DETAIN A WORKER WITH
PAPERWORK FOR DR. SPECTER.
GUESS WHO.
I GOT TO GO.
I CAN EXPLAIN IT
TO THEM.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
SAY-- THE DAY'S REPEATING?
IT WON'T WORK.
I'VE TRIED IT.
MEET ME AT THE FRONT ENTRANCE AT 6:00.
DON'T TALK
TO ANYBODY. 6:00.
WE'VE GOT HIM.
CODE 4. SECTION "B."
HEADING INTO
THE MAINWAY!
HEY, YOU'RE
UNDER ARREST.
HEY, STOP!
HOLD IT, MISTER!
HOLD IT!
HOLD IT
RIGHT THERE!
HOLD IT! HOLD IT!
BUDDY! HE'S IN
A BROWN FOUR-DOOR.
CALL THE MAIN GATE.
[RING]
YES?
IT'S ME.
WE MAY HAVE
A PROBLEM.
FREDERICKS IS
WORKING WITH SOMEONE.
I DON'T KNOW!
I MAY NEED SOME HELP
IN THIS.
GOOD.
WHEN YOU FIND HIM,
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO.
ALL RIGHT.
O.K. UM...
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
STAY THERE.
STAY THERE, LISA.
NO.
THANK YOU.
OH...
[TIRES SQUEAL]
NO!
OH, MY GOD!
[CROWD SHOUTING]
I TOLD YOU
I'M NOT CRAZY.
LET'S GO!
CALL THE POLICE!
DON'T MOVE!
YOU ALL RIGHT?
I DON'T KNOW.
OH, GOD.
WHAT DID YOU DO
AFTER I LEFT?
WHAT?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
I COPIED THE EVIDENCE
AGAINST DENK.
ONTO A DISK?
YEAH.
HAVE YOU GOT IT?
NO. I LEFT
MY BRIEFCASE.
OH, GOD.
WATCH OUT!
[AIR HORN HONKS]
AAH!
[GUNSHOT]
HOLD ON!
MOVE IT!
BACK IT UP!
GET IT OUT OF THERE!
WE'D BETTER CALL
WASHINGTON OR THE POLICE
OR SOMEBODY.
THERE'S NO PHONE
IN THERE.
I'M SORRY?
MY MOM'S IDEA. THE OLD MAN
BRINGS HIS MOBILE ANYWAY.
WHAT?
THERE'S NO PHONE,
THERE'S NO DISK.
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO
DO, MAIL IN A COMPLAINT?
WE HAVE TIME.
WE'LL THINK OF SOMETHING.
AW, IT'S...
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
YOU KNOW, THE LAST TIME
I WAS IN THE WOODS,
I WAS 9 YEARS OLD.
I WAS BURYING
MY PET CANARY,
AND I MADE A GRAVESTONE
OUT OF A PAPER PLATE.
AND I WROTE ON IT--
"FLY TO HEAVEN."
HMM.
I HAVEN'T TOLD
ANYONE THAT IN...
20 YEARS.
WHY DO YOU REMEMBER?
WHAT MAKES YOU DIFFERENT
FROM THE REST OF US?
I DON'T KNOW.
MY MEMORY'S NOT
THAT GREAT ANYWAY.
I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETHING HAPPENED TO YOU,
OR YOU DID SOMETHING.
WHAT...
WHAT DID YOU DO
THAT FIRST NIGHT?
WELL, AFTER YOU GOT SHOT... I GOT DRUNK.
CAME HOME.
I KNOCKED A BUNCH
OF STUFF OVER.
I COLLAPSED IN BED.
I WOKE UP.
IT WAS THE SAME DAY.
YOU'RE MISSING SOMETHING.
YOU DROVE THROUGH
SOMETHING UNUSUAL.
YOU WERE NEAR METAL OR A
CHEMICAL OR HIT BY LIGHTNING.
I COLLAPSED IN BED,
MY CLOCK SAID 12:01,
AND I GOT A SHOCK.
MY LAMP WAS BROKEN.
THERE WERE LOOSE WIRES.
I TRIED TO FIX IT, BUT I
LIT UP LIKE A CHRISTMAS TREE.
AND THEN?
THEN...
IT WAS MORNING.
THERE'S A THEORY--
SCOTT'S THEORY
HAS A COROLLARY
THAT SAYS CONSCIOUSNESS EXISTS
SEPARATE FROM THE TIME BOUNCE.
YOU COULD'VE GOTTEN
THAT BAD SHOCK
WHEN THE FIRST
BOUNCE HAPPENED.
IT PUSHED YOU OUT OF
THE LOOP JUST ENOUGH
SO YOU CAN REMEMBER.
I BET THAT'S IT!
LUCKY ME.
BARRY,
I'M--I'M SORRY.
NO, NO. IT'S...
I MEAN,
YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
SELF-INTEREST.
I...
I'VE BEEN WATCHING YOU
OUT OF MY OFFICE
FOR SUCH A LONG TIME.
THE OTHER DAY,
I GATHERED UP THE NERVE
TO ACTUALLY SPEAK
TO YOU.
I MADE A FOOL
OUT OF MYSELF.
BUT I THOUGHT, HEY,
I'LL HAVE ANOTHER CHANCE
TO SPEAK TO YOU SOMEDAY.
BUT THEN YOU...WELL...
WE SPOKE?
YEAH.
YEAH, WE DID.
HOW WAS I?
GREAT.
YOU WERE VERY NICE.
YOU THREW ME OUT
OF YOUR OFFICE.
I'M SORRY.
I GUESS I WAS HAVING A BAD DAY.
THAT NEXT MORNING
WHEN I SAW YOU...
ALIVE...
I REALIZED
I HAD A SECOND CHANCE--
A CHANCE TO SAVE YOU.
I'M SORRY.
HEY, HEY.
I'M NOT GOING TO
LET YOU DIE AGAIN.
HI.
YOU KNOW, I'M USUALLY
NOT THIS TYPE OF GUY.
I'M SUPPOSED TO
SAY THAT.
WHAT TIME IS IT?
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S 12:00.
WE'VE GOT TO
DO SOMETHING.
THERE'S NO TIME.
QUICK. TELL ME WHAT
YOUR FAVORITE COLOR IS.
WHAT?
WHAT'S YOUR
FAVORITE COLOR?
GREEN.
FAVORITE FOOD.
SMOKED OYSTERS.
FAVORITE NUMBER.
37.1.
FAVORITE MUSIC.
THAT'S HARD.
TELL ME.
WHAT IS IT?
THE CARPENTERS.
YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING.
[THUNDER]
LISA...I LOVE YOU.
[BEEP BEEP]
THE TIME IS 7:35.
PLEASE WAKE UP.
[CLICK]
9:17--LISA'S IN CORRIDOR
WITH DENK.
LIGHTS CIGARETTE.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
9:25--DENK GOES
THROUGH LISA'S OFFICE.
12:30--LUNCH WITH LISA.
MOM, I'LL CALL YOU BACK.
THE DAY'S REPEATING.
1:00--LISA'S
BEEPER GOES OFF.
1:40--
YOU'RE PATHETIC. THAT'S
NOT HOW YOU THROW THE BALL.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
[TIRES SCREECH]
WELL, LOOK WHO
DECIDED TO SHOW UP.
DON'T GET YOUR
PANTIES IN A BUNCH.
IF YOU LEFT US ALONE,
THE WORK COULD GET DONE,
BUT YOU'RE SO INVASIVE
THAT NO ONE CAN CONCENTRATE.
STOP ASSUMING
WE'RE ALL IDIOTS
AND DON'T JUDGE PEOPLE
BY HOW CUTE THEY ARE.
WELL...
THIS IS WHAT I GET FOR COVERING
FOR YOU ALL THESE YEARS.
THANK YOU.
IT MIGHT BE TIME TO LOOK
INTO YOUR PERFORMANCE RECORD.
YOU DO THAT.
WELL, NICE KNOWING YOU,
BARRY.
EXCUSE ME. BARRY.
LISA.
I'M A LITTLE CONFUSED.
HOW DO YOU KNOW ME?
I KNOW YOU LIKE IT
COMPACT WITHOUT THE CRAP,
SO HERE WE GO.
IT'LL SOUND IMPOSSIBLE, BUT
I'LL SUPPORT IT WITH FACTS.
THE TIME BOUNCE
HAS HAPPENED.
WE'VE MET BEFORE--
THREE TIMES.
YOUR FAVORITE FOOD
IS OYSTERS.
YOUR FAVORITE NUMBER
IS 37.1.
YOUR FAVORITE MUSIC
IS THE CARPENTERS,
EVEN THOUGH YOU
COULD DO BETTER.
DENK HAS BEEN ILLEGALLY
FIRING THE ACCELERATOR.
YOU'LL TRANSFER THAT
PROOF ONTO A COMPUTER DISK.
HERE'S WHERE IT GETS
A LITTLE STICKY.
I'VE SEEN YOU SHOT,
TWICE NOW.
BUT YESTERDAY
I WAS ABLE TO SAVE YOU.
BUT THE TIME BOUNCE HAPPENS, AND
I WIND UP HERE, MEMORY INTACT.
I'M THE ONLY ONE WHO
REMEMBERS ANYTHING AROUND HERE.
I MADE YOU A TIME MAP.
SIT BACK AND WATCH
THE DAY UNFOLD.
IT'S 9:15 NOW.
LISA?
THADIUS.
BARRY THOMAS?
YES. I'VE GOTTEN
YOUR MEMOS.
YOU, TOO, LISA. ARE WE
ALL LOSING ASSISTANTS?
ACTUALLY, I--
YOU'RE TWO ASSISTANTS
ARE BACK ON THE COMPUTER.
THEY'LL HAVE THEIR PASSES
BACK BY LUNCHTIME.
DR. FREDERICKS EXPLAINED
THE WHOLE THING TO ME.
I APPRECIATE THAT,
LISA.
DR. MOXLEY, YOU
LOOK GREAT ON TV.
ANN, DR. MOXLEY'S
A VERY BUSY MAN.
HE DOESN'T HAVE THE TIME
TO LISTEN TO YOU SUCK UP.
IT'S SAD.
IF YOU EVER HAVE A PROBLEM,
COME TO ME PERSONALLY,
NOT TO MY
LOW-LEVEL STAFF.
EVERYTHING SEEMS TO BE
UNDER CONTROL.
THANK YOU, LISA.
I'LL SEE YOU AT THE 9:30.
GOOD DAY.
HOWARD!
LOOK. OVER THERE.
SEE THAT? HE'S ABOUT
TO LIGHT HIS CIGARETTE.
HE'S MET YOU IN THE HALLWAY
THESE PAST MORNINGS.
TODAY HE CAN'T BECAUSE
YOU'RE HERE WITH ME.
KEEP DENK FROM FINDING OUT
ABOUT THE COMPUTER DISK.
TODAY I'LL TAKE
ALL THE INFORMATION.
I...CAN'T JUST
ACCEPT THIS.
THE EPITAPH
ON YOUR CANARY'S GRAVE
YOU MADE WHEN YOU
WERE 9 YEARS OLD
WAS ON A PAPER PLATE,
AND IT SAID,
"FLY TO HEAVEN."
[BEEP BEEP]
OH, MY GOD.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
PERSONNEL.
OH, YES, SIR.
WHY, YES, THEY ARE.
EXCUSE ME?
O.K.
I DON'T THINK SO.
YOU TRUST ME.
YOU MAY NOT
REALIZE IT YET,
BUT YOU TRUST ME.
NOW, LET'S MEET OUT BY THE
FRONT ENTRANCE IN A HALF-HOUR.
O.K.
BIG DADDY,
THAT WAS GREAT.
HOW DID YOU DO THAT?
BARRY, I WANT YOU
IN MY OFFICE IMMEDIATELY.
RELAX, ANN. I'M QUITTING.
SOMETHING I SHOULD'VE
DONE A LONG TIME AGO.
NO, NO, NO, BARRY.
DR. MOXLEY JUST CALLED.
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST.
WELL, WHAT FOR?
FOR STEALING CLASSIFIED
COMPUTER INFORMATION.
COME THIS WAY,
PLEASE.
HEY. HOWARD--
MARITAL STATUS.
SINGLE.
AND OCCUPATION.
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT TIME IS IT?
JUST PUT DOWN
UNEMPLOYED.
AT LEAST IT'S NOT
MURDER THIS TIME, RIGHT?
SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER.
REALLY, YOU SHOULD
LEARN TO TYPE.
WE MAY BE DOING THIS
FOR YEARS.
WELL, I COULD ALWAYS
START AGAIN IN SIX HOURS.
HELLO. HOW ARE YOU?
THOMAS. YOU MADE BAIL.
YOU GUYS GOT
NOTHING ON ME.
IT'S A BUM BEEF.
HEY. THERE ARE
SECOND CHANCES.
YES, SIR.
THAT'LL BE FINE.
HOW DID YOU GET THE BAIL?
DON'T EVEN ASK
WHY I'M DOING THIS.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW HER.
YOU'RE NOT KILLED TODAY!
THAT'S GREAT NEWS!
BARRY, UM...
LOOK, WE...
YOU REALLY LIKE ME A LOT.
YOU JUST CAN'T
REMEMBER IT.
I'D LOVE TO STICK AROUND,
BUT THAT WOULD BE
A LIE.
BARRY, CALL ME WHEN
YOUR INSANITY CLEARS UP.
CLOSE THE DOOR.
GET IN.
I DON'T MEAN TO BE REALISTIC
ABOUT THIS OR ANYTHING,
BUT SHOULDN'T WE CALL
A PROFESSIONAL
TO TAKE CARE OF THIS?
HOWARD...LOOK, WE GOT TO
THINK OF SOMETHING.
HE'S GOING TO FIRE
THAT THING TONIGHT.
THE POLICE KEPT
THE COMPUTER DISK.
THEN THE POLICE WILL
TAKE CARE OF IT.
IT'S OUT OF
THEIR JURISDICTION,
AND WE DON'T HAVE
PROOF.
IS THERE ANY WAY TO GET BACK
INTO THAT BUILDING?
YEAH, I THINK SO.
YEAH.
THE ACCELERATOR NEEDS
A TWO-HOUR WARM-UP PERIOD
BEFORE IT CAN FIRE.
THAT MEANS HE'D START IT,
UH, IN THREE HOURS.
IF WE HAVE SECURITY TAPE THE LAB
THROUGH THEIR SURVEILLANCE CAMERAS,
WE COULD GET THE PROOF
WE NEED TO STOP THEM.
PAY THE LADY.
I DON'T HAVE
ANY MONEY.
WE HAD A LOT MORE FUN
LAST NIGHT.
WE DID?
WE TOOK A WALK
IN THE WOODS,
WE SAT BY A FIRE.
WE SAT BY A FIRE?
YEAH.
ARE YOU SAYING
THAT YOU--THAT WE--
I MEAN,
DID YOU GET LUCKY?
OH, MY GOD,
YOU GOT LUCKY.
YOU GOT LUCKY, TOO.
IT WASN'T JUST ME.
THIS IS SO STRANGE.
I KNOW, BUT IT WAS
ALSO TREMENDOUS.
THE EARTH MOVED.
OHH!
WANT TO STEP
IN THE ALLEY, PLEASE?
LET'S GO. YOU, TOO.
MOVE.
OVER THERE.
THESE ARE THE GUYS THAT
HAVE BEEN KILLING YOU.
WHERE ARE
THE OTHER DISKS?
WHO ARE YOU?
SHUT UP.
WHY DON'T YOU
JUST LEAVE--
LISTEN
TO THE QUESTION--
DID YOU MAKE
ANY MORE DISKS?
I'M NOT REALLY
A PART OF THIS.
SHUT UP.
THERE'S NO REASON
TO HAVE ME HERE.
SHUT UP!
THERE ARE
NO OTHER DISKS.
BARRY, TELL THEM I DON'T
HAVE ANYTHING TO DO WITH THIS.
ANY INFORMATION I HAVE
WOULD BE USELESS.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
OH, MY GOD!
HURRY UP!
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
HELP!
CHECK DOWN THERE.
I'm sorry about
your friend, Barry.
I know
you cared about him.
That's funny.
He said the same thing to me
when you were killed.
NOTHING.
WHAT?
I DIDN'T LEAVE
A LIGHT ON.
LISA...
THADIUS IS
IN THAT HOUSE.
WHAT?
SORRY I WASN'T ABLE
TO TELL YOU THIS BEFORE,
BUT SIX MONTHS AGO,
THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT ASKED ME
TO HELP THEM INVESTIGATE THADIUS.
WHY ARE YOU
INVESTIGATING THADIUS?
THEY SUSPECTED HE'D
BROKEN SAFETY REGULATIONS
TRYING TO GET THE ACCELERATOR
UP AND RUNNING ON BUDGET.
WHAT?
HE BROKE THOSE SEALS
TO STOP THE DISMANTLING.
MOXLEY BROKE
THOSE SEALS?
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE HE MIGHT DO.
WE BETTER
TALK TO HIM.
I DON'T THINK SO.
I'M GOING TO NEED YOU
AS MATERIAL WITNESSES.
SHALL WE?
O.K.
[DOOR OPENS]
THADIUS,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M SORRY, THADIUS.
IT'S OVER.
THANK GOD, LISA,
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
THADIUS.
ROBERT, YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
FIRE THAT ACCELERATOR TONIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
YOUR NAME IS
IN THE COMPUTERS
AUTHORIZING THE FIRING
SEQUENCE FOR TONIGHT.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
DR. MOXLEY,
WHY ARE YOU IN MY HOUSE?
I'D HOPED TO FIND
ANOTHER DISK
WITH THE PROOF
AGAINST HIM.
HE CRASHED
THE MAINFRAME COMPUTER
BEFORE I COULD
RETRIEVE ANYTHING.
HE'S LYING.
WHO WERE YOU WAITING FOR?
WHO WERE THOSE TWO MEN
IN THE TRUCK?
HELLO, TED?
WHERE THE HELL ARE YOUR MEN?
WHO ARE YOU
TALKING TO?
DON'T MOVE!
I'M JUST, UH, TAKING OFF
MY COAT, O.K.?
[GUNSHOT]
THANK GOD YOU MADE
THE RIGHT CHOICE.
HE SET ME UP.
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
THE ACCELERATOR IS GOING TO
BE A $50 BILLION INDUSTRY
IN FIVE YEARS.
HE DOESN'T CARE ABOUT YOU!
THADIUS, YOU SAID--
I SAID WHAT I HAD TO.
SOMETIMES YOU DO WHAT'S
WRONG TO DO WHAT'S RIGHT.
I'M SORRY.
NO!
OH!
I TRULY AM SORRY.
THE TIME IS 7:35.
PLEASE WAKE UP.
YOU BASTARD.
WHAT KIND OF MAN ARE YOU?
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
YOU SHOT HER AND HIM--
AND ME IN COLD BLOOD!
THAT'S IT, PAL.
YOU'RE FINISHED.
NO MORE HAMSTER WHEEL
FOR ME, YOU SLIMY...
[HONKING]
OHH!
THE TIME IS 7:35.
PLEASE WAKE UP.
[BEEP BEEP]
PLEASE WAKE--
THIS CUTTING EDGE PROJECT
BY RESEARCHERS
IN PARTICLE PHYSICS
HAS BEEN SHUT DOWN BY
GOVERNMENT ORDER. HOSEA?
MARY, BIG NEWS
AT UTREL CORPORATION.
RESEARCHERS HERE WORKING
ON PARTICLE PHYSICS
BELIEVE THEY'VE DISCOVERED
A WAY TO ACCELERATE--
[RING]
HI, MOM.
NO, WE HAVEN'T SPOKEN
IN A WHILE.
YES, I HAVE MET A GIRL.
I JUST DON'T THINK
IT'S GOING TO WORK OUT.
TELL ME, MOM. WHAT?
WHAT'S ALL THAT MATTERS?
YEAH? ALL THAT MATTERS
IS HOW IT FEELS?
IT DOES.
IT...IT FEELS RIGHT.
YEAH, YOU SAID IT.
NOTHING GOOD COMES EASY.
MOM, I'M--I'M RUNNING LATE,
BUT I PROMISE
I'LL CALL YOU LATER, O.K.?
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
BYE, MOM.
YOU'RE PATHETIC.
THAT'S NOT HOW
YOU THROW THE BALL.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
TREAT THEM WITH RESPECT.
THEY ARE HUMAN BEINGS.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE
NOT SUCH A BAD GUY
WHEN YOU GET TO KNOW YOU.
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING?
I KNOW WHO YOU ARE.
YOU'RE HELPING THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT CATCH MOXLEY.
I WANT TO BLOW HIM
OUT OF THE WATER.
YOU WANT TO HELP?
MORNING.
COME IN.
ROBERT, WHAT IS THIS?
I'VE GOT A REPORT.
YOU, UH...
YOU BETTER SIT DOWN.
BARRY HERE HAS
SOMETHING TO TELL YOU.
THE TIME BOUNCE
HAS HAPPENED.
EXCUSE ME?
THE TIME BOUNCE.
WE'RE IN IT.
THE EARTH HAS STOPPED
AS WE KNOW IT.
CHILDREN DON'T GROW UP,
PEOPLE DON'T STAY DEAD,
WE'LL NEVER HAVE
ANOTHER HOLIDAY,
AND YOU'LL NEVER SEE
ANOTHER FLOWER BLOOM.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
AND I'VE FALLEN IN LOVE
WITH A BEAUTIFUL YOUNG LADY,
AND, SO FAR, I COULD ONLY
SEE HER FOR A FEW HOURS,
AND IT BREAKS MY HEART
TO MEET HER EVERY MORNING
A STRANGER.
SEE, I WANT HER EVERY DAY.
I WANT HER
TO GROW OLD WITH ME.
THAT'S WHY LIFE
IS SO PRECIOUS--
BECAUSE TIME PASSES.
WHO IS THIS...
WHO'S THIS GIRL?
37.1...
OYSTERS.
GREEN.
THE CARPENTERS...
FLY TO HEAVEN.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
WE PLAY THE DAY
AS NORMAL.
WHEN HE GOES TO WARM UP
THE ACCELERATOR TONIGHT,
I'LL CALL FOR BACKUP,
YOU TWO WILL BE OUT.
IF I WAKE UP TOMORROW, AND
IT'S TODAY, I'LL KILL MYSELF.
LOOK WHO DECIDED
TO SHOW UP.
I AM ROBERT DENK.
THIS IS DR. FREDERICKS.
I KNEW THAT.
WHAT A PLEASURE IT IS--
WE NEED MORE MEN
LIKE BARRY.
HE'S AN
EXCELLENT WORKER.
TREAT HIM
ACCORDINGLY.
SORRY?
BARRY, I'D LIKE THAT EVALUATION
REPORT OF MISS JACKSON
ON MY DESK BY NOON.
EVALUATION?
WE ARE LIKE THIS.
HEY!
HOWARD, YOU'RE ALIVE.
I WASN'T IN THE BATHROOM
THAT LONG, WAS I?
OHH!
SORRY, SORRY.
CAREFUL, GUYS.
OH!
OHH!
OH, JACK, I'M SO SORRY.
THIS IS A TERRIBLE
EMBARRASSMENT FOR ME.
WE TOLD THEM
WE'RE SAFE,
AND NOW WE CAN'T DISMANTLE
THE CORE FOR TWO WEEKS.
NO ONE WAS HURT.
THE RADIATION'S CONTAINED
IN THE CORE.
I THINK
PEOPLE UNDERSTAND.
BETTER DOUBLE-CHECK
ON THOSE SEALS.
THANK YOU, LISA.
THADIUS, I TAKE
FULL RESPONSIBILITY.
I'LL GET A CLEANUP CREW,
AND I'LL DEAL WITH THE PRESS
IMMEDIATELY.
WELL...
I ADMIRE YOUR ATTITUDES.
DR. MOXLEY?
NO DISTURBANCES.
THANK YOU.
I KNOW AN INDIVIDUAL
WHO REALLY LOVES RED ROSES.
MAY I?
SEñORITA.
HI, REYNALDO.
I GOT IT.
REALLY?
YEAH.
IT'S MY PLEASURE.
[CAR DOOR OPENS]
HEY, WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU--
[MUFFLED GUNSHOT]
[MUSIC PLAYS ON RADIO]
THANK YOU.
ARE YOU AWARE
THAT COFFEE IS
ONE OF THE FIVE ALL-TIME
GREAT SMELLS IN THE WORLD?
NO.
WELL, IT IS.
THEN YOU HAVE
HOME-BAKED SOURDOUGH BREAD,
OPENING DAY
AT WRIGLEY FIELD...
NEW SHOES...
FRESH ROSES...
RAIN.
YOUR PERFUME.
UM, I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
HAPPENED THE OTHER DAYS,
BUT WE HAVE TO TAKE IT A
LITTLE SLOWER THIS TIME, O.K.?
IT'S TOO LATE FOR THAT.
I'VE DIED FOR YOU
ALREADY.
I GOT TO
GET USED TO THIS.
IT'LL WORK OUT,
YOU KNOW?
IT ALREADY HAS.
AND NOW
FOR THE LOCAL NEWS.
A MAN IDENTIFIED
AS ROBERT DENK,
A RESEARCH SCIENTIST
AT UTREL CORPORATION,
WAS FOUND
MURDERED THIS EVENING.
THE VICTIM
WAS DISCOVERED...
MOXLEY HASN'T
CHANGED THE CODES.
IS THAT GOOD OR BAD?
I DON'T KNOW.
DR. FREDERICKS?
YES.
YOU MUST BE BARRY THOMAS. HELLO.
I HAVE TO ASK YOU
TO STEP INSIDE.
YOU'RE WANTED IN CONNECTION
WITH DR. DENK'S MURDER.
DR. MOXLEY'S ORDERS.
LISTEN, FELLAS, IT HAS
BEEN A REALLY TOUGH WEEK.
IT HAS BEEN
ALL TUESDAYS.
SIR-- I'VE ALREADY
BEEN KILLED TODAY.
SIR, I UNDERSTAND.
STOP GIVING ME
A HARD TIME.
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
MAKE SURE YOU'RE FIRED.
DON'T THINK I CAN'T.
I'M IN PERSONNEL.
[ALARM SOUNDS]
PLEASE GIVE HER
THE GUN. PLEASE.
YOU GUYS DON'T SEEM
TO GET IT.
I WAKE UP EVERY MORNING
CLUTCHING THE PILLOW,
AND IT'S NOT LISA,
AND JACK STILL GETS HIT
WITH THE COFFEE.
SO I'M AFRAID YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO STEP INSIDE.
GO--NOW--MOVE IT--
1, 2, 3, LET'S GO.
SO MUCH
FOR THE SURPRISE VISIT.
[BEEPING]
HOW ABOUT A LITTLE
SOMETHING SPECIAL AT 11:59?
O.K.
HOLD IT.
GIVE ME THE GUN.
THADIUS, YOU CAN'T
FIRE THE ACCELERATOR.
WHY ARE YOU
TRYING TO STOP ME?
THE TIME BOUNCE
HAS HAPPENED.
WHAT THEY'RE ASKING ME TO DO IS WRONG.
THE TIME BOUNCE,
IT'S REAL.
GO AHEAD.
15 YEARS AGO, THEY STOPPED
WORK ON MY SUPERCONDUCTOR.
10 YEARS TO DESIGN A
PHASE-GRAVITATIONAL FIELD.
THE GERMANS BEAT ME
BY A MONTH.
NOW THEY'RE GOING TO
DISMANTLE MY ACCELERATOR
BEFORE IT HAS A CHANCE--
IT DOESN'T WORK!
I HAVE NO MORE TIME.
THADIUS,
IT DOESN'T WORK.
GET UP THERE.
GO ON.
IS THERE AN ABORT SWITCH
ON THAT THING?
THERE'S A YELLOW BUTTON.
PLEASE DON'T.
BARRY!
ARE YOU O.K.?
OH, MY GOD.
AHH!
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
HEY, DOC, TOMORROW
I MAY SHOOT YOU FIRST.
I'LL JUST
KEEP COMING BACK
TILL I GET IT RIGHT.
[ALARM SOUNDS]
GOT YOU
A LITTLE SURPRISE, DOC.
WARNING--POWER FLUCTUATION
NOW AT 30%.
DID IT ABORT?
NO.
ANY WAY
TO STOP IT?
NO. HE DISCONNECTED IT.
DAMN IT!
DAMN IT,
GET AWAY FROM THERE!
NO!
AAH!
I CAN'T GET IT!
I'LL GET IT.
THERE'S NOT ENOUGH TIME.
WE'LL NEVER MAKE IT.
WE'LL MAKE IT.
WE HAVE TO MAKE IT.
NO MORE
SECOND CHANCES.
OHH!
AAH!
NO!
MY GOD.
LISA, I LOVE YOU.
[BEEP]
IT'S WEDNESDAY.
DON'T MOVE!
YES, SIR.
THIS MAN'S BEEN SHOT.
CALL AN AMBULANCE.
WHO ARE YOU?
I'M DR. FREDERICKS.
DR. MOXLEY TRIED TO FIRE
THE ACCELERATOR ILLEGALLY.
HE TRIED TO KILL US.
THAT'S NOT
WHAT WE WERE TOLD.
YOU'RE UNDER ARREST.
WE HAVE PROOF!
PUT THE CUFFS ON THEM.
READ THEM THEIR RIGHTS.
WE'RE UNDER ARREST.
HOW ABOUT THAT?
EVERY MINUTE
WILL BE BRAND-NEW.
WE'LL NEVER KNOW
WHAT WILL HAPPEN NEXT.
I KNOW WHAT
WILL HAPPEN NEXT.
YOU DO?