The King rules heaven
The devil rules hell
Between the two there is White Lotus
Keeping our country safe
White Lotus is divine!
Power to the people!
Welcome Priest Gao Kung
from the South Heaven Gate.
Green Dragon on the left.
White Tiger on the right.
On September the first, 1895
I became a disciple
of the White Lotus Goddess.
I speak these words before the heavens
to show my powers
and spread my word to the people.
Mystical powers protect me!
Impervious to water and fire!
Goddess, lend me your powers!
Welcome spiritual master, Gao Kung.
Goddess, make me as strong as iron -
fearless before blade or sword.
Stabbing and slicing have no effect.
I'm fearless before cannons or gunshot!
49 levels of transformation!
Holy Army under my command!
My bones are like pillars
supporting the sky!
The fierce flames are like dust to me!
Unlimited mystical powers
at my disposal!
The White Lotus Sect...
eradicates evil!
A thousand knives are deflected.
Regiment Commanders!
Mystical power protect me!
Cannon fire is as flying sand to me!
Bullets are mere raindrops!
White Lotus is divine!
Power to the people!
Bring out the objects of evil.
What's this animal? It's so ugly!
It's a Western dog, Master!
It has spots, so it is evil
kill it!
White Lotus is divine!
Power to the people!
Kill all foreigners
so we can live in peace!
White Lotus is divine!
Power to the people!
Kill all foreigners
so we can live in peace!
White Lotus is divine!
Power to the people!
Kill all foreigners
so we can live in peace!
Steady, Master.
He doesn't spill a drop to either side.
Good footwork.
13th Aunt, the train is rocking so much
how will we eat?
You're not used to it.
Look, the foreigners are coping fine.
Come and sit here.
Now it's much better
this journey used to take all day.
The trees look like they're flying.
Whoops...
I feel ill.
What's wrong, Foon? So much talk!
Nothing...
My stomach is churning.
You're train sick!
Don't eat or you'll throw up.
But I must! There's Western food to eat
right, Master?
We haven't ordered yet.
You don't need to order
your food on the train.
Miss, the soup.
Thank you.
It's all been prepared.
You mean it's not fresh?
Solar eclipse?
Don't be so scared, idiot!
13th Aunt, what's going on?
We're in a tunnel.
A tunnel?
The train is strong enough
to go through a mountain?
Amazing!
Idiot!
Foon, we're all together now, but
don't run off when we get to town.
OK.
There will be a lot of foreigners
at the medical convention.
Don't embarrass us.
I understand, Master.
So many hands!
Fei-hung, eat the soup while it's hot.
Foon, eat the soup while it's hot.
Master, I don't know which hand is mine.
I can do it that way.
Have you finished your soup, sir?
I'll finish it later.
Only meat? Where's the rice?
Miss, have you finished your soup?
I don't want it.
Thank you.
Fei-hung, it's a steak,
use your knife and fork.
I've seen this before.
You're always doing this.
What a waste! Don't throw it away.
Sorry, Master.
Concentrate on what you are doing.
Watch me.
Are you OK?
I'll clean your face.
Yes, I'm fine. Here's your steak.
Master, don't throw it away!
It's all your fault.
Forget it, let's eat.
Why are you so quiet?
No reason. Why are you so quiet?
Oh, no, I can't hold it any more!
Foon!
I'm sorry.
I told you not to eat.
Hold on, we'll be in Canton soon.
Really?
Yes.
Riding in a train is quite a challenge.
Waiter, can you pack this?
What did you say?
I just don't want to waste it.
Chicken buns!
Give me a pot of tea.
Old man, you owe me money. Pay up!
If I can't play, I can't pay.
Look, a crowd.
What's on the banners?
Support the scholar's proposal!
We object to the cession of Taiwan!
Where is Taiwan?
We lost the war and gave it to Japan.
Taiwan must be near the sea...
or it wouldn't be called Tai-island.
I don't even know how big it is.
We can't even manage Canton, forget it.
Let's drink.
Eat, we'll talk later.
We object to Li Hung-chang's
concession to Japan!
We object to the cession of Taiwan!
Look at the clothes on that woman!
Where?
Over there. The one in the rickshaw.
Come and have a look.
She's wearing Western clothes.
Those Are Western clothes?
They're so ugly!
Sister?
We object to the cession of Taiwan!
Let's do the lottery.
Nine is my lucky number.
I don't know how to play.
Support the scholar's proposal!
We object to the cession of Taiwan!
We object to Li Hung-chang's
concession to Japan!
We object to the cession of Taiwan!
Support the scholar's proposal!
Money first, look after your tickets.
Get your ticket and move on.
The next draw will be at dinner time!
The lottery!
Roast pork buns!
We're here, sir.
Ten cents, please.
Thank you.
Let's eat. Pulling this rickshaw
will be the death of me.
That's a pretty dress.
Can I take a picture?
You're not a foreigner. Get her!
Get her! Get her!
Go away, you pesky kids!
Throwing things at people!
No manners!
Foon!
Get lost...
Don't hit the children.
I'm bleeding!
Sister?
Look, you've made trouble again.
Master...
Let's go, we'll tell Uncle Gao.
Those kids are so naughty,
throwing things at people.
Look at the mess.
Attention, please.
White Lotus are meeting
at Telegraph House.
We should all go.
Don't leave! Don't forget to pay!
Master Wong, I'm going to have a look.
13th Aunt... 13th Aunt!
Foon! Foon!
Hurry! They're about to start!
Come on, hurry up!
In the name of the people's army
stand down!
Damned soldiers, working for foreigners!
Stone them!
Get out of the way.
Move!
Wind and fire come together...
Kill all foreigners.
By driving evil away!
Eradicate all evil!
Burn down Telegraph House!
Excuse me, please.
Aunt, let's take the photo here.
Help me set up the tripod.
Over there.
Wind and fire come together...
It's starting now.
I can't see. I can't take pictures.
Get on my shoulders.
Get on your shoulders?
OK, keep still.
White Lotus is divine!
Power to the people!
Kill all foreigners
so we can live in peace!
White Lotus is divine!
Power to the people!
Foon, this position is no good.
So good.
Wind and fire come together.
Kill all foreigners.
White Lotus has come to save you
by driving evil away!
What was that?
Thank you.
She can make lightning, run away!
Arrest that evil spirit!
The top one or the bottom one?
The foreigner on top.
Arrest her!
Calm down!
She is Chinese,
she's not a foreigner!
Have a look.
Look at the way you dress.
It proves you're evil. Arrest her!
13th Aunt, run! I'll protect you!
My camera!
13th Aunt!
13th Aunt! Where are you, 13th Aunt?
Foon! Help me, Foon!
Kill all foreigners
so we can live in peace!
Take her to the temple,
burn her to death!
Put her down!
Fei-hung!
Who the hell are you
to stop me?
Tell me your name!
I'm Wong Fei-hung from Fushan.
Fei-hung?!
And Leung Foon too!
I hear his kung fu is deadly.
Kick you
kick you... to death!
Leave him alone, pick on someone else.
You'll hurt him.
Who else? Where?
Hit them, don't hurt them.
That's enough.
Ten-finger punch!
Thank you, thank you.
Master.
Are you all right, 13th Aunt?
You came just in time.
What is it? It smells sweet.
It's sleeping powder.
Foon! Take care of 13th Aunt.
Master
Take care of 13th Aunt.
13th Aunt!
Mystical power...
All this trickery and mumbo jumbo and
you claim to be acting in God's name!
13th Aunt, wake up! 13th Aunt!
13th Aunt! Help her up.
Foon, take 13th Aunt back to the inn.
Foon, what are you waiting for?
He's one of Canton's Ten Tigers.
His kung fu is legendary.
Get back!
What is he taking?
Master Wong, don't! That thing is evil!
Stand back!
Master Wong, can I be your apprentice?
Back! Don't follow me!
Fei-hung!
You're awake.
They covered you in sleeping powder.
Did you carry me back here?
No, Foon did.
Why did he carry me back?
Foon is preparing your medicine.
Take it and rest for two days
and you'll be fine.
Master Wong.
Come in.
Don't go out alone
this town is in turmoil.
Rest a while, don't worry.
Fei-hung, I'm all right.
I can still be your interpreter
at the convention tomorrow.
Let's talk about that later.
Take your medicine now.
Master Wong, sorry to disturb you.
It's OK.
Oh, you're awake.
Did you know...
You carried me back.
Yes, I did.
The medicine is very hot, be careful.
Mr. Mak, what can I do for you?
I sent my servant to buy these clothes.
Please ask her to wear them.
That's very kind of you.
Don't mention it. Mystical kung fu
is very popular now.
Foreigners make them mad.
Master Wong, I've known you
for a long time
I'll be frank with you.
If Miss wears her own clothes
she'll definitely get into trouble.
I understand.
How much were they?
There'll be no charge.
Thank you.
Thanks for your help, Master Wong.
Here you can see the 5 main regions
of the brain.
According to the result of
a medical study and research
we understand the function and the nervous
system of a human body are controlled by the brain...
If I knew it would be so boring
I'd have asked So to come.
Which believes those function comes from
the heart
This is a theory I of course
cannot subscribe to
and thus I'm afraid to conclude
my lecture
Thank you for your attention.
And now...
I'd like to introduce Dr. Wong Fei Hung,
from Fu Shan Region of Canton
There's another one!
It's not any of them.
Another foreigner.
Dr. Wong, it's your turn.
Foon, it's our turn.
I'll let you out.
We'll go together.
Please don't, master
Thank you. Thank you.
My topic of discussion
for today is Chinese acupuncture.
I beg your pardon, Dr. Wong.
I don't quite understand.
Louder.
There are 360 pressure points...
Dr. Wong, what do the lines represent?
Do you want him to speak louder?
That's not what he means.
Dr. Wong, may I interpret for you?
Gentlemen, allow me
to translate for Dr. Wong.
Very good!
May I know your name?
My name is Sun Yat-sen.
Dr. Sun, I'm most grateful to you.
Don't mention it.
Thank you.
The five elements are gold, wood,
water, fire and earth.
They form a network.
Acupuncture regulates the nervous system.
The human body consists of 5 major organs.
Heart, liver, spleen, lungs & kidneys.
These organs are all connected by nerves
and acupuncture can regulate
the human nervous system.
Dr. Wong, I'm not quite sure
what your chart exactly means.
But in western medical studies,
we call it the nervous system.
Allow me to give you
a demonstration of what I mean.
Reflex action.
Dr. Wong, Dr. Thompson
doesn't quite understand.
His demonstration shows the Western
understanding of the nervous system.
That's quite simple.
I can use needles to close two nerves
so that he can't move his leg.
Master, are you going to stick
those in me?
Dr. Sun, ask them
to test his reflexes now.
Please try again.
Really amazing!
White Lotus is divine!
Power to the people!
Foreigners out, leave us in peace!
Master!
The White Lotus sect again!
Master! I can't move!
I'll be shot!
I'm a goner!
Master, I've only been stabbed
by you, not them.
Mr. Sun, your bag.
Leave it.
We're finished here.
Back to the Temple!
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
Mr. Sun, here's your bag.
If we get the opportunity
let's exchange ideas, shall we?
China needs more men like you.
You flatter me.
See you soon.
The White Lotus Sect is
always making trouble.
Master, 13th Aunt must be
still at the inn.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
The White Lotus Sect?
Come out!
Fei-hung!
Master, what's the matter?
Nothing, come on, out.
Master, you look pale
something must have happened.
It's just a woman changing.
Mind your own business!
But you saw it.
Don't ask me about the past.
I'm so sad and lonely.
My future looks bleak and poor.
Tears flow when I think of the past.
I always wanted to be a soldier.
But I was raised in Confucianism.
So I lost my dream...
And missed my destiny.
I lost my idealism.
The winter wind blows...
Even the wild geese don't stop.
For I have no message
for them to take home.
My tears show the reflection of dawn.
We are hopelessly in love.
Worlds apart, the sky is near.
I'll spend the rest of my days alone.
Wandering from place to place till I die.
What a terrible noise!
Tell him to stop.
Here!
Thank you, thank you...
Sir.
Telegraph House is our only contact
with the outside world.
Protect it.
Yes, sir.
Sir.
There are a lot of bystanders
take care not to hit them.
Drive the White Lotus towards the gate.
Yes, sir.
Sir, if this continues
we will be outnumbered.
Burn down Telegraph House.
Master...
Dinner time!
I got a nice treat
to help 13th Aunt get well.
It is delicious.
Yes, it is.
What is it?
Foon, haven't you told 13th Aunt
what this is?
Don't you know?
13th Aunt, do you like dogs?
They're man's best friend.
I like them more than cats, anyway.
What's the matter?
Nothing. Let's eat.
People like dogs in different ways.
They went that way.
Let's go over there and take a look.
Canton is in chaos.
Foon, pack our things after dinner.
We'll go to the station early tomorrow.
Take 13th Aunt back to Fushan.
OK.
You'd better eat well tonight
you don't want to be sick on the train.
Come outside when you've finished
the dog meat
I'd like a word.
You'd like a word with me?
What did you say? This is dog meat?
Is it really?
Yes.
Yes, Master loves dogs.
13th Aunt, I want to teach you kung fu.
Me? Why?
These are troubled times.
You could use it for self-defence.
The basic technique has 36 stances.
The advanced has 72 stances.
There are 108 pressure points...
Fei-hung!
Do I need to remember all this?
No, just listen
and try to get the basics.
Remember, for punches,
attack from the side.
For kicks, come from below.
What if someone has a knife?
I'll teach you that another time.
Look, this is the single,
this is the double.
Such effort! Why don't I use a gun?
Shut up!
I was a bit rude.
That's how I speak to my students.
I'm fine, let's continue.
OK.
The first move.
Go for my head.
Pay attention.
Grab the hand, crouch down, then twist.
Grab the hand, crouch down...
then twist.
Then twist.
Let's try again.
Grab the hand, crouch down, then twist.
The second move, throat lock.
Come on, attack my throat, harder.
Grab the hand, crouch down, elbow up.
13th Aunt?
Be careful!
Why aren't you concentrating?
I was practising in my head.
Try it once more.
The first move, grab the head.
What's next?
Then punch!
Are you OK?
I'm OK, it's better to be your friend
than your enemy.
Sir, we've received a telegram
from Hong Kong.
We've no time for that now.
It says someone's planning
a rebellion here.
Here's the message.
Sir, it's another telegram
from Hong Kong.
This is serious,
guard Telegraph House well.
I'll inform the Governor.
Yes, sir.
This way please!
Please go inside.
Your Excellency.
The British consul invited me here
can't this wait?
Our spies in Hong Kong
cabled us twice today.
The Chiu Chow Society are planning
to smuggle weapons to Canton.
They want to start a revolution.
A revolution?
Is it the White Lotus Sect?
No.
Their leader is called Sun Yat-sen.
Sun Yat-sen?
Officer, who is this Sun Yat-sen?
Your Excellency
He's the one who started
the Agricultural Society.
He's a doctor,
he's always giving speeches
and criticising the Government.
He encourages democracy too.
He says China should be a republic.
How can a doctor rebel?
Do we not have enough men?
White Lotus has been
causing trouble recently
so we're under-manned.
The Government is having trouble
with the French in the north.
I think there'll be war soon.
It won't be easy to get reinforcements.
The British are our allies
they'll help keep the other
foreigners at bay.
Put the army and navy on alert
and extra men at ports and stations
till we find Sun Yat-sen.
What was That society?
The Agricultural Society.
Who else is involved with Sun Yat-sen?
Someone called Luke Ho-dung
is the money man.
Sir, should we bring him in
for questioning?
Yes, let's bring him in.
Yes, sir.
Sir?
I'm not going.
A busy night tonight.
Indeed.
Sir.
Chow, tell Snake to get up
it's not his day off!
Did you spend all night
at the brothel? Get up!
Hurry!
Be careful, 13th Aunt.
Take it easy.
Foon, what are you doing?
She twisted her ankle.
How come? I only showed you
hand movements. What happened?
I don't know,
it was just hurting when I got up.
Foon insisted on carrying me
when he found out.
Foon!
I don't mind, Master.
Well, let me carry her,
you take the luggage.
It hurts.
I always do the carrying.
Now you want to get involved.
Waiter!
May I help you?
We'd like to check out.
Boss.
Master Wong?
We Are leaving now.
Oh, thank God!
No, no, I mean have a safe journey.
Sorry for the trouble.
If you're ever...
Fei-hung, look
what's going on?
He is badly hurt.
Hey, what's going on?
The White Lotus have burned down
Friendship Hall.
Take him to see the doctor.
What's Friendship Hall?
It's where they teach foreign languages.
It's full of students.
Mr. Mak, where's the school?
Near the fruit market.
Don't go there!
13th Aunt!
Master, where's she going?
Foon, you lied to me
she's OK.
It was her idea, Master.
Wait for me.
Friendship Hall. Is this it?
Master! Wait for me!
What is it?
Skin.
It's human skin.
Master.
It's the younger students.
It's lucky they were hiding.
What's happening?
Let's go and have a look.
What's going on in there?
They've gone now.
Don't worry. Be good.
I'm scared.
They stormed in and kicked us.
Master Wong! Why are you still here?
Are these children with you?
They are students
from the Friendship Hall.
We just needed a rest.
They can't stay here!
If White Lotus comes
I'm finished!
I don't know them, even worse
they study foreign languages.
Take them to the courthouse.
Can't we rest for a moment?
I don't know how to fight.
This inn is all I have.
I have to support my family.
If it's burnt down, I'll...
I'll help!
Mr. Mak!
He's fainted...
Have you got some salts?
You've made him faint.
Who do you think you are?
If he dies, I'll call the police.
Then I'll back off.
Foon, 13th Aunt, let's go.
Let's send them home.
Where do you live?
I'm from Kwangsi Province.
I'm also from Kwangsi.
I'm from Fukien Province.
He's from Chuijao
they're from Kwangsi.
I guess the rest
are not from here, either.
Do any of you live here?
Miss, I live by the north gate,
so does he.
I live in Sha Min.
I think I live near the east gate.
Anybody else?
I came here on the train,
I've no idea where did I come from.
I stay at school all the time.
We'll take these two home.
The rest come with us.
I'll carry you.
Foon! Order some chicken rice
for our journey.
Waiter, 20 portions of chicken rice!
Come on, you too.
Sir... what can I do for you?
I'd like to know if the children from
Friendship Hall came here earlier?
Students? No, no, you've come
to the wrong place.
Boss
Have any of you seen the students?
There are no students here, you fool!
Maybe the boogie man's got them.
The King rules heaven
The devil rules hell...
It's lucky
the students are gone.
Between the two there is White Lotus
Keeping our country safe
Lucky tokens!
I want one.
The hanging lantern will keep you safe.
Lucky tokens will protect your family!
Light the lanterns.
Here's the offering.
Lucky tokens will protect your family!
This will keep you safe.
Of course, of course.
Give more offerings
to ensure your safety.
Finish up in there. We have to leave.
Be quiet.
What happened to your hands?
It's not my blood, it's his.
It's everywhere.
Will he die? He's badly injured.
We can't stay here.
I'll go to the courthouse to see
if they'll take them.
Stay here.
Foon!
Help me bandage the poor kid.
I haven't finished yet.
Don't be naughty. Come back here.
I just wanted to know
where he was going.
Foon, you stink.
You peed on me!
I told you I wasn't done yet.
Sir, Wong Fei-hung
would like to see you.
Sir!
Sir.
Master Wong, now I see why
you're so famous.
Thank you. Thank you.
It was nothing, sir.
I just wanted to spar with you a little.
Master Wong, your Shaolin staff
is excellent.
Maybe you can teach me some other time.
Have some wine.
Thank you.
His Shaolin staff isn't that good.
He hit that pole,
but it didn't even move.
People say he is the master of kung fu
I don't think it is true.
All our troops are busy
protecting foreigners.
It may not be that safe here either.
If the students come here
the White Lotus will come
to cause trouble.
Sir.
I know it's my job to protect the people.
The trouble is even though I can fight
I don't have the men to support me.
I'm deeply ashamed.
Foon!
Come over here.
Stay out of the way.
He is still bleeding.
Master isn't back yet.
What shall we do?
He's not moving.
Why isn't he moving?
It's Mozart.
What do you mean?
Listen. Can't you hear
the foreign music?
There must be a foreign consulate nearby.
A consulate?
Beware of fire!
Beware of thieves!
13th Aunt, Foon!
I need to pee.
Wait until you're home.
It's bad for my kidneys.
So? They're rotten anyway.
Don't move!
Stay there!
Where has the sect taken
the woman and children?
We aren't with White Lotus.
My children are in bed now.
My woman has run off...
What?
Master.
Foon, where did you go?
13th Aunt took the children
to a safe place.
Really?
Why are you holding
a White Lotus lantern?
To bring us good luck.
But it doesn't seem to have worked.
May I Go now?
Yes!
Come on, hurry.
Foon, let's go.
Don't you remember me?
I came with the children...
and a beautiful lady.
I only left to find my master.
I don't understand you.
Go away!
Nonsense!
Foon, did 13th Aunt bring
the children here?
Yes, he let us in before,
but now he won't.
13th Aunt... I've come with Master!
13th Aunt...
Shut up!
Did he ask us to stand up straight?
That's what I heard.
13th Aunt?
13th Aunt,
we are waiting at the entrance.
Open the gate, go away.
13th Aunt...
Master, they're opening the gate.
Go away now!
How dare you!
Foon, stay calm.
Hands up! Surrender now.
Don't hit me!
Tell them why we're here.
I have!
Put your guns down.
They don't understand.
Stop!
Stop pointing that at me!
Wait!
Allow me to clear up the confusion.
Alright.
Pardon me. My name is
Luke Ho-dung, and yours?
I'm Wong Fei-hung from Fushan.
Wong Fei-hung?
You saved the children!
Yes, they're all inside
but the soldiers won't let us in.
It's only a mistake.
What are you looking?
Stand back.
This Jesus is agony.
Luke.
Why do foreigners believe in a god
whose face has so much suffering?
Everyone has a god in their heart.
When we're young
we believe in one god
when we're older
we believe in another.
Finally we realise all beliefs
are just lies.
Why are you always
looking at your watch?
Are you expecting someone?
A bad habit I picked up from a friend.
He says time is valuable.
We Chinese waste a lot of time.
What a shame.
I still can't read foreign numbers!
I'll never keep good time.
What is happening?
Reporting Sir, the wounded
are flooding into the embassy.
Don't worry, let the wounded in first.
We will take care of everyone.
Stay where you are.
Don't be afraid.
Foon, take them upstairs.
They're foreign merchants
and their families.
They've been attacked by White Lotus
and have come to seek refuge.
Have they found the doctor yet?
He is on the way.
Go and get him now!
He is bleeding badly,
what'd we do then?
What to do now?
Stop the bleeding,
the doctor is on the way!
They need a doctor.
Master is the one they need.
Master.
Excuse me, Sir!
They're looking for a doctor.
They don't want Chinese doctors.
We prefer western medicine.
Dr. Sun, ask them
Mr. Wong.
This is...
No need to introduce me. He's the one
who's always looking at his watch.
Burn it down!
White Lotus are making trouble again.
Mr. Luke.
Which one tells the right time?
Your watch is fast, Sun.
Mine can't keep up with yours.
Enough of this,
let's check the injured.
OK.
Foon, I never thought
time was so important.
I didn't think you'd understand.
Burn the foreign devils!
Chase them out!
13th Aunt?
Oh, no, they must have taken her soul!
If they're so clever,
they would have won by now.
They're just trying to scare us.
Don't worry
just relax.
What if she vomits?
We're not on the train now.
Try to contact Dr. Lee.
Yes, sir!
I'm afraid
we don't have enough anaesthetic.
Then tell me, what do you suggest?
Mr. Luke, ask Wong to come in.
Feeling better?
Mr Wong, Dr. Sun would like you
to help him.
Where is he?
He's in the reception hall.
OK, lead the way.
He said thank you. He's never seen
anything like this. He's amazed.
I'm filled with the utmost admiration
and respect.
He said thank you.
He has never seen anything like this.
He said his view was broadened and
he admired and respected that so much.
Not at all, saving lives
is what matters.
Doctor Wong says nothing
is more important than saving lives.
Be calm! Keep clear of the window!
Call for reinforcements!
Yes, sir!
What's happening?
13th Aunt, don't, stay with me.
I won't leave you.
The children!
Watch out, Dr. Sun. Get down.
Urgent telegram.
The Consulate is under attack.
Deploy troops and prepare for evacuation.
The army have closed Telegraph House.
We've lost contact with Hong Kong.
Are we still going ahead with our plans?
It's too risky.
We'd better lay low for now.
Let's split up and tell the others.
The telex at the consulate
is the only way we can contact them.
Mr. Luke, you know how to send a telex.
Stay here and keep contact
with the outside world.
Sun, I...
I've taken care of your family.
I'll go back to the villa now
and then go on to the wedding.
If you don't get a message from me...
take the boat to Hong Kong
tomorrow morning.
Don't be late.
Take my watch with you.
If I fail...
carry on the fight.
I will.
Dr. Sun, Are you leaving?
I've got something to do.
I'll see you out.
Thank you.
Stay here.
Be careful, Fei-hung.
The White Lotus Sect will drive
the foreigners out!
Dr. Sun, ask them
how will you get out?
It's easier to save men
than their country.
It seems my medical case
and I can't save them all.
Move!
Get them out of here!
Get out of here! Go!
See you later, Master Wong.
Sir, we just want
to expel the foreigners.
We wouldn't
kill our own people.
I'm glad to hear it.
Leave the negotiating to us.
If you were so capable
we wouldn't have lost so much land.
If you continue to make trouble
I'll arrest you all.
Take the altar away.
Yes, sir. General Lan is here, make way.
Why have they all come in?
OK, get out of here!
You are not permitted to enter,
leave at once.
We suspect you are harbouring a criminal.
His name is Sun Yat Sen.
I have an order to arrest him
this is British Territory!
You are now in China! Not in Britain!
You shouldn't talk to me like that!
I'm sorry, but according to International
law, we are not under your jurisdiction
and you have no right to search
the British Consulate.
We do not intend to offend anybody.
Please leave!
I see Mr. Luke is hiding here as well.
Get off the premises! Commander,
you must leave now!
Mr. Luke.
Let's go!
Yes, sir.
Sam Fok, cut the wire pole down.
I want to stop all communications.
An army without information
is a dead army.
As soldiers we are men of the world.
We must do what is best.
Sir...
I know. Just follow my orders.
Yes, sir.
This way, Commander.
Carry out the General's instructions.
They protect the rebels
because they want to subjugate us.
Pull it up.
You may start now.
What is going on?
Gun fire!
Don't be distracted! Stay alert!
Yes!
If you are all up for this
let's practise some kung fu.
Once you have your stance, don't move.
This is the Hanging Horse.
One move and you're steady as a rock.
This stance brings unlimited power.
Perform the Unicorn Move.
Third move...
Hold the head, grab the hand, twist!
Watch carefully!
Return to your original position.
And again! Not bad.
Hold that stance for two hours.
Foon!
Hold the head, grab the hand, twist!
Grappling Hand?
Yes, I've learned it
but I don't know how to use it.
That's easy. I'll attack
and you counter attack.
Watch.
Is it this way?
It doesn't feel right.
Foon, what are you doing?
Why are you holding 13th Aunt?
I'm teaching her Grappling Hand.
You teach her?
Do you think I can't teach her?
It's not right for you to hold 13th Aunt.
Knee bends, now!
Master, I...
Now!
Stop looking at me.
Carry on!
I'm going, Master.
What are you doing?
The stance.
That's not the way!
Fei-hung, don't be angry with Foon
I asked him to teach me.
You did?
Why don't you ask him to come back?
Go on, then.
I'm punished for this?
What would happen if I
taught her the Bear Hug?
These foreigners are really lazy!
If White Lotus came, you'd be a goner.
Trying to scare me?
Wait for her to come down.
Mr. Luke.
Have you seen Foon?
The White Lotus Sect?
Help!
White Lotus is here!
Foreigner evil.
They're here!
Wind and fire come together...
Kill all foreigners.
By driving evil away!
Eradicate all evil!
Go and hide and don't come out.
I'll be right back.
Who is that?
Mr. Luke?
Yes.
Dr. Wong
Upstairs.
You Go first.
General...
Be quiet.
Now you'll die, you little brats!
The stance.
Master!
Foon, take care of these
I'll handle the horses.
Get off!
Where are you running to?
Foon, tie them up.
I'll see if there are any left.
Arrest them, go!
Yes, sir.
Arrest the White Lotus.
I have orders to protect the Consulate.
You must co-operate with us
let my men through to search
for the rest of the rebels.
Come on, hurry.
I saw what you did!
I saw you let the rebels go.
This is a conspiracy.
What are you looking at?
They are fighting.
This is China, not Britain.
Sir.
Fei-hung, General Lan killed the consul!
Don't move!
Search everywhere!
Yes, sir.
What are you doing?
Tell Sun to run for his life.
Fei-hung, I know you look on me
as your aunt...
but you're the one for me in my heart.
If we lose each other...
come and find me.
It's time to go.
Whatever happens,
we must survive this night...
so that future generations can see
a new dawn
do you understand?
Foon, you pretend to be Mr. Luke
and distract the soldiers. If you can,
find the name-book in the market for Mr. Luke.
I will.
Leung Foon, take this watch.
Meet me at the pier at seven am.
It's down to you now.
Siu-qun.
You said my name!
It's the first time you've done that.
Who are you?
I'm the interpreter
from the consulate, sir.
Go on, then.
Foon, go now.
Mr. Luke.
Mr. Luke?!
After him!
General.
Wong Fei-hung?
Sir, I want to destroy their leader.
That way I destroy the whole sect.
To destroy it from the root!
And who's that?
Foon! Take care of 13th Aunt.
Master
come and meet the General.
Sir.
He was injured by the White Lotus.
Sir, we can't predict what might happen.
Please take care of the children.
OK, I promise you.
Escort Master Wong to the temple.
Yes, sir.
White Lotus, I want to join you.
The White Lotus sect welcomes you,
our guests.
Master Wong, there are so many soldiers
how can we escape?
The temple is so big
we can just disappear.
I'm sure we can get out.
Under the incense,
long live the White Lotus sect.
Is it safe in there?
Don't worry, just relax.
Anyway, we can't go back now.
Let's go in, then.
The Goddess comes to save all people.
White Lotus is divine!
Power to the people!
Our sect brings peace to the world.
Prepare for our initiates.
Kneel!
Wong Fei-hung, Leung Foon,
come to the altar.
Come forward to be purified.
Let the ceremony begin.
Swallow the lucky token,
become a child of the sect.
We are all brothers.
We share a common bond -
for better or for worse,
for richer or for poorer -
all are equal.
Drink this
and you'll be a member forever.
May lightning strike down
all those who betray us.
Master!
Be loyal before God. Drink it!
Goddess, lend me your powers!
Protected by God,
nothing can harm me -
A thousand knives are deflected.
A million blades are deflected.
Protected by God,
nothing can harm me -
Nothing can penetrate!
Master Wong!
You're despicable.
Take back your evil water.
Mystical power protect me!
Wong Fei-hung,
how dare you make trouble here!
Priest Gao Kung's name is famous.
But I need to see him
before joining the sect.
I need to see him now!
We won't let you see his righteousness!
You won't?
I'll fight my way in, then!
White Lotus
How dare you!
Leave here.
Surround him!
You'll have to look out for yourself.
Sky, wind, earth, fire,
eight stances to challenge you!
Surround him!
You're all frauds!
That's enough.
God...
It's all a deception!
Mystical power protect me!
Gao Kung, why don't you come out?
This whole thing is a fraud.
I want to reveal the truth.
Protect the altar!
White Lotus brothers, kill him!
I'll fight you to the death.
Come and fight me if you dare!
God will protect us.
Go ahead...
Stop, or I'll shoot!
Can't you see this idol
cannot protect you?
You must stop believing in it.
You are the one who lies.
Yeah!
You...
Mr. Luke
Come this way
and we'll see who doesn't die.
Let me through!
God will protect me.
Your gun doesn't scare me!
God will protect you!
The body is as strong as iron!
Little girl, you will lose your life.
Get back!
Protected by God, nothing can harm us.
Between the two there is White Lotus
Keeping our country safe
Don't be afraid of him!
Come on, hurry.
I've shot the girl!
Don't worry about that now.
You first.
Stay there!
Look at these people.
They're giving up their lives
for this idol.
Mr. Luke, let's go!
If they're all like that
how will they ever change?
They know nothing else.
Surround him!
There's nowhere to run to.
We can't escape.
Don't let them get away!
Beloved God, take over my body.
God will protect my body giving me
power to exorcise the evil spirits.
With God in my body,
I'll teach you the true way.
How dare you wake me to come here
you fools!
Anger the gods and bring them to earth.
I'll teach you!
Come out, or I'll burn my own altar.
Gao Kung, the righteous, is here.
Welcome Priest Gao Kung
from the South Heaven Gate.
The invincible Gao Kung!
The universe is controlled by him!
I became a disciple
of the White Lotus Goddess.
The Goddess personally taught me.
She instructed me to set up an altar
to exorcise the evil spirits
and save us from this impure world.
Come spirit!
Come, spirit!
Here I come!
Protect the altar.
Stop.
Come down here!
Be gone!
Trap him! Come on!
Yes, sir!
Why do you need help?
I'll do what it takes!
Now!
Set up the altar.
Steady!
Yes, sir!
You set up a useless altar.
Come up here!
Supreme Being, come into my body!
I'll leave this broken altar for you.
Steady, steady!
How dare you!
How dare you wreck my altar!
Protect Priest Kung.
Use the cloth as an altar.
Do you want to die?
Supreme Being, four Guardians of Heaven
come to my aid.
Destroy my enemy.
Guardian of Anger!
Guardian of Mercy!
Little girl.
Guardian of Defiance! Come!
Gao Kung,
you've summoned all the guardians!
Are you ready yet?
If any guardian was of use,
one would be enough.
You have offended them all.
They will all punish you!
Death to you, the guardian's enemy!
Die now!
Wind somersault!
Mighty strike!
Evil being!
Priest Kung is invincible.
He will exorcise all evil!
Get down!
No Shadow Kick from Fushan!
Protect Gao Kung!
Killer Cloth!
I am not any sort of god.
I'm Wong Fei-hung!
Can't you tell gods from what is not?
Wong Fei-hung, prepare to die!
White Lotus opens up!
Put your feet on the ground.
It's all a deception.
Wong Fei-hung,
how dare you challenge the gods!
Gods don't burn!
If that's true, there's no justice.
Solar explosion!
Gao Kung.
Your show is over now.
You demon!
You say believe in God
and peace will reign.
How many people have you killed?
Let's see you survive this!
Nobody can stop me!
I can.
Claw Knife!
A metal plate!
His magical powers amount to this.
Now they've no god
they must look after themselves.
Mystical powers protect me!
Master!
How can this happen?
Let's go.
What kind of number?
I can't even read it,
this is no use to me.
Master!
Good, we meet again.
It's six o'clock, there's still time.
Hey, where is the name-book?
Name-book? Oh, no!
I was distracted by the soldiers
and forgot it!
Why are you so careless?!
I'll go back and get it.
Do we have enough time?
I must get it,
it's a matter of life and death.
Let's go.
Mr. Luke, it's well-guarded,
do we have to go in?
I must get the name-book.
The boat leaves in 30 minutes.
We can't be late meeting Sun at the pier.
Wait there.
Foon, see If Mr. Luke is ready yet.
I'll keep watch.
Mr. Luke, can I help?
I've got it, let's go.
Soldiers, let's hide.
Master Wong, this way.
Master
Come on, hurry up!
I'm going to die this time.
Help him up.
Where are you hurt?
Let me have a look!
It hurts, it really hurts.
Luckily they shot your watch...
Mr. Luke!
Get down!
Foon, you go first.
Mr. Luke, I'll carry you.
This way, Master.
Don't move!
Master, there's a way out.
There's a way out.
Are you all right?
I can't go on.
Leave me here.
Let me help you.
The name-book is vitally important.
Don't let the Government have it or
many Chinese people will be killed.
Take me over there.
You can't burn this cloth.
Master Wong, I beg you,
deliver this to Sun personally.
Tell him I died for the revolution.
He must live for the revolution.
There's blood here.
They're over there!
Foon, look after Mr. Luke.
General Lan?
We meet again.
Arrest the rebels!
Yes, sir!
Hold it.
What are you burning?
Wong Fei-hung, this will be
our last chance to spar.
I wonder how many of my moves
you can withstand.
Give me that now!
Here you are!
How dare you!
The name-book? Hand it over.
Foon, stay where you are.
Carry on with what you're doing.
Don't come over.
Master, take care.
Mr. Luke.
Lan, didn't you want to test me?
Wong Fei-hung?
Come on, then!
Come down!
You come up!
You wanted to fight?
Son-of-a-bitch! This is too much!
Why aren't you down yet?
Mr. Luke.
Time... is vital.
Be on time... at the pier.
Meet Sun Yat-sen.
Mr. Luke.
Wong Fei-hung, there's no way out!
Come back.
You killed the British consul
everyone will know sooner or later.
There's no way out for you either.
Well... we're both doomed, then.
Foon, you can't burn that cloth!
Master!
Foon, go quickly.
Time is vital.
It's a dead end
there's no way out.
Foon, what time is it now?
I can't tell the time
but it's getting light.
There's not much time left.
Mr. Sun must meet Mr. Luke
before he sails.
Wong Fei-hung?
Please give me the name-book
so I can go back to the Governor.
He won't let us go.
Try and find a way out.
Quick! Go!
Cloth Staff!
Foon, make the hole bigger.
Well done!
Thank you.
Foon, Get out of here.
I understand, Master.
Master, we can go now.
Yes, you can go to hell!
Foon!
No Shadow Kick!
Master.
Are you Dr. Sun?
All aboard! Hurry up, everyone!
All aboard! Hurry up.
We've found him.
Don't move! You're coming with me.
Stand back!
Grab the hand, crouch down and twist.
Master.
Fei-hung!
13th Aunt!
Where is Mr. Luke?
Dr. Sun!
May a new dawn break over our land.
May we never forget our martyr's blood.
Mr. Luke, your spirit will always be
remembered in our hearts.
Don't worry, I'll meet you at the pier!
Foon, are you missing 13th Aunt?
Are you, Master?
I asked you the question.
I think you're the one
who's missing her.
Really?