Those sons of bitches haven't come out yet
Yeah, they are still inside
Do you know how to rap?
Come on!
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry... Don't go... Don't go...
Stand up... Stand up!
Daijiro, by the time you read this letter,
I am already in HK, working as
a receptionist in Jackie Chan's office
Having a chance to meet Jackie Chan,
I am really happy
After seeing Jackie Chan's movies,
his face comes up in my mind all the time
We had a good time together,
- but life doesn't stop there
- What?
- It is time for me to see the world
- Ling has gone
Let us start another new life on our own
Let us treasure our good times
and let it be our memory
Who cooks for me then?
Who buys condoms for me?
Who sleeps with me?
Hey, Hitomi, this Daijiro
Have you seen Ling?
She left me because of Jackie Chan
What? You also want to see him!
Crazy!
Hey, Takako
It's me
Ling... She went to HK to be the receptionist
in Jackie Chan's office
What?
You want Leslie Cheung's poster?
What are you talking about? Idiot!
This is Daijiro! Did you see Ling?
In Shinjuku or Shibuya?
I don't think she is in Hong Kong yet!
Won't she call you then? Won't she?
Hey, don't hang up on me
Excuse me, do you have the poster of
Jackie Chan in "Rumble in the Bronx"?
We don't sell Jackie Chan posters
How about that one?
That one is not Jackie Chan...
That is Jackie Chun
That is not for sale
But we do have Jackie Chan dolls
Look, Jackie Chan doll
Jackie Chan...
Take it, this is for you
Wait, don't watch so many
Jackie Chan movies
What a nasty couple...
Hello?
Kenichi...
Ling...
Jackie Chan is here, wait
Really?
Hello
Hello, Jackie
I love you! Do you love me?
I know you got hurt
in "The Armour of God"
When you acted in "Rumble in the Bronx",
your leg got injured... But you insisted to continue
I have seen all you movies!
Idiot, it's me!
Stupid!
You are fired!
I wish your company to be successful
and our boss to be healthy
I wish all the best for you
Daijiro
I bought you your favorite snacks
It is so hard to find you in this mess
Cheer up!
Hey, I brought Sushi. It is good, try it!
Why don't you go back with me?
Stop dreaming of being a star
Get real, find a job
Is Ling too good for me?
Don't be like this, okay?
A lot of people suffer more than you do
Besides, you have
your own good qualities
Like what?
Like...
You can't even name one
You are smart
I didn't even pass
the entrance examinations
You can fight
I'm always the first to run away
You are caring!
I didn't even give you
a Mother's Day gift
Cut it out!
I'm trying to cheer you up
About Ling, you should stick to her
and go after her again
Stop talking nonsense, go! Get a grip!
Mom... What did you just say?
Nothing... Nothing!
Mom, you are right.
You are absolutely right
I will go to Hong Kong
Are you serious?
You don't even know any Cantonese
I have to bring Ling back
Ling, wait for me!
Hong Kong, wait for me!
You are very lucky
Why?
I've already started to live with my girlfriend
Yes! You can keep my room
It is very cheap, only $4000
$4000!
That only gives me
6 months to stay here
6 months will be enough time
to bring Ling back to Japan
I thought you were
looking for a job here?
What can I do?
Stuntman!
Can I? I'm afraid of pain
Is there any ghost?
Yes, that's why it's so cheap!
I can't live without Ling
That is why my mom let me
come to Hong Kong to look for her
It really hurts me
I understand
What do you understand?
Do you know how it is to be a short man?
Don't be like this
The jockeys are short too,
but girls love them
Jockeys are exceptions
I am talking about real Love
Real Love?
You have to help me find Ling
My life relies on you
Love? You can't push it
Maybe, next time when you meet Ling
you may see Jackie Chan
and Hung Kam Po
Really?
Yes!
Relax! If there is any news on her,
my friends will call me
Camera? Where is my camera?
Did I bring my camera?
Where is my camera?
It will be great when I really get to meet
Jackie Chan and Hung Kam Po and so on...
Will they come?
Really?
You don't have to be so excited!
I can bring you to the studio
Really?
But I don't know whether they will come
I can't believe
you have become a stuntman
Jackie Chan was a stuntman before too
Among all my friends, only you made it
So did Shimizu
What is he doing?
He robbed a bank with two jointed pike
What happened at the end?
He ended up in hospital
The police beat him down?
No, he injured himself
What a fool
What about you?
Are you still practicing?
Not really,
but I still have a couple of moves left
Show it to me, okay?
Okay!
I really miss the good old days
Right, everybody was working hard then
It's all over anyway
You really want to go back?
I really want to go back
You can't!
You can't go back
I really want to go back
I really want to go back!
Hello!
What's up?
Hello sir?
Hung Kam Po!
Wait, whatever he asks you,
just say "No Problem"
Yes!
He wants to become a stuntman,
he wants to learn from you
Do you have anything for him to do?
You want to become a stuntman?
No Problem!
Can you stand it?
Come over here!
Have you had breakfast yet?
No Problem!
Take this!
Are you okay?
Why did he kick me? No problem
Okay, wait for my notice!
Kenichi, am I in the group?
You took that kick, right?
Really?
Right, if you see Ling,
you have to be calm
don't make a fool out of yourself.
Keep in mind
I see!
My name is Kun...
Why did you hire a 6-feet-tall man?
You can do it!
Don't think I can't hurt you,
I can jump over your head
Did you wear any pads?
Yeah!
You wear them here!
You should wear them there!
Kenichi, he looks like me
That guy! He is hot here!
But he's a jerk!
Really? Our height is more or less the same,
so is our hairstyle
Protect with your hand!
Why you hit so hard, you want to kill me?
Boss, you are great!
You've got a pair of string legs, are you okay?
No problem?
Who is this guy?
Why you hit so hard?
Sir, he is my playmate in Japan,
the first day here
Rookie? Let me try! Come on
He wants you to fight with him
If you want to work here,
you have to let me beat you up first
Take it easy!
Take one punch and one kick
Yes!
You can't block, understand?
Yes...
Boss, are you okay?
What is the matter with you?
Why you dodge?
Boss are you okay?
Sorry...
You hurt him, you have to replace him
Straight to the gate!
Ready?
Camera roll... Action!
Cut! Everything okay?
No problem!
Bring him down slowly
Are you okay?
Check if I am bleeding or not
No problem!
The director said that you did well
Really?
He's asking whether you want to be
the main actor's stuntman
Of course
Calm down
Look over there!
Have some tart, Jackie's treat
Come and have one
Let's eat, come on
Can I have one?
Wait for a moment please...
I am here
Where is Jackie Chan?
Jackie Chan?
Jackie is busy.
He asked me to bring you guys the tart
Let me see him!
Jackie Chan?
Maybe, I will let you meet him later
You look slimmer
The pain of live cause me to get thinner
You are blaming me?
No, I am not, I come to talk to you
About us...
I made it very clear in the letter
I want to start a new life,
see some new things
We can do it together
If you want me to go bald, I will
Bald?
You always forced me to follow your way
in Japan, I want to be myself
Why did you treat me like that?
I won't say anything, you find your way
That's why
I decided to come to Hong Kong
I'd rather share you with someone
than lose you completely
I am not an object that
you can share around with other people
Ling, let's go!
Coming
I'll fix Maggie's schedule
Okay
Hello. Hold a moment please
Hello, Willie?
Okay... hold on
Ling!
You are going to dump me like this?
Do you think I am
some kind of cheap lighter?
No one is perfect
Even you can't remember you get fired
because you stole a vacuum once?
Haven't you returned Yamada's CD?
And you farted in the library!
Ling, Jackie is asking if the
person outside is your friend?
Yes! Sorry!
If he won't leave in 5 minutes,
he will ask someone to take him away
Sorry! I understand
You know how horrible Dioxine is?
Ling! Do you hear me? Hello!
Get lost!
Can you hear me?
What is it? It is so bitter!
Whatever you drink now is bitter!
This is Chinese medicine
which can cure your flu
It is too bitter
I have to be famous
then Ling will come back to me
I want her to worship me
like she worships Jackie Chan
Just make a lot of girlfriends
so that you don't need Ling anymore
Okay!
But I am not cold-hearted
if Ling understands she is wrong
and comes back to me...
Do you know what you are doing?
You want to learn how to fight
Stop
Come and fix Mr. Kwan's wire
Fight like a man? Stupid!
Kenichi, take him away
What are you doing?
Mr Kwan, sorry.
I will pay for everything tonight!
Take off your make-up
No need, I'll do it at home!
It's me, Daijiro...
Daijiro?! What are you doing here?
That actor is not here?
Of course no
Bye bye!
Stupid scary face in "Ring"
Calling Control, over
Still don't know where the gorilla went to
I haven't found it yet, over
You have to grow up, you know?
Cheers!
Good friends
You know that you are small & can't fight
but you still came to help me
Let me tell you,
if you need anything from now on
No matter what I will help you
He said that no matter what,
if you need help, he will help you
You help me, I help you
We will help each other!
Have you seen an illegal immigrant?
Seen Anybody? Anyone
you don't know come into your house?
Sorry,
I don't know what you are talking about
Thief!
I really don't know what you are talking about!
Sorry!
Sorry... Sorry...
Hello, Ling...
You can't sleep yet.
do you want to buy something to eat?
You will sleep better
with your stomach full
What? Do it in the bathroom?
No, really?
You've get a great body
and a pair of big breasts
It is so big and soft!
Do you really like it?
I am coming! Don't touch me there
I am coming
Hello
It's me
Kenichi?
Yes. What are you doing?
I am talking to Ling
Ling? I just met her at the studio.
She had time to talk to you?
I am talking to her answering machine
What?
I decided that
I will not sleep with any other woman
for the next 6 months
Suit yourself!
Can I hang up with you?
Okay!
I will call you later, bye!
Hello!
Hi, Ling
Stupid
Hey, who are you? Come out!
This knife is very sharp, look
Who are you?
Don't touch my things
I am Ching, I came from Szechuan
Police?
If anything happens, call us
Hello!
What?
No problem!
Can't understand you!
Come out!
Don't call the police. I am leaving
Police...
Police?
Hello
Stop it, okay?
You have filled my answering machine
Sorry!
But something big has happened
There is an illegal immigrant
who sneaked into my house
Should we call the police?
But she looks nice
Is she pretty?
Very pretty
Why don't you go after her?
What are you talking about?
All I want to say is she is nice
Can you talk to her?
Who are you? What is you name?
My name is Ching,
I come from Szechuan
You sneaked in illegally?
I met a man from Hong Kong a year ago
He treated me really nice
and I fell in love with him
He told me he was going to marry me
and he'd take me to Hong Kong
I didn't care about his money,
I only wanted to live with him
Of course living in Hong Kong is
better than living in Mainland China
Later he told me that
he was poor and couldn't marry me
I didn't mind and went to stay with him
in Shenzhen
One day he called me and
told me that he was really sick
And he had no money
and couldn't come back
After that, he disappeared
He only left me an address
I was worried about his health
So I sneaked into Hong Kong
trying to look for him
But who would know the boss wanted me
to work as a hooker to pay him back...
I refused and ran away
He then accused me of stealing his wallet
That is why I sneaked into
this Japanese man's house and hid myself here
That is why I sneaked into this Japanese man's house and hid myself here
Can I wait until morning?
It is another love story
To be dumped by your lover is
very painful
I have that feeling too
I come all the way to this strange place
I understand
I understand your feeling
I cried many nights too!
You are the translator and
you have to tell every single word!
He said that it's so poor to be dumped
He has the same feeling of it
Come to another country to seek his lover
He understands how you feel
You still love her?
Yes! Very much
Is she here?
Yes
Why don't you stay here for a while?
Thanks!
I don't expect you taking me in,
I don't want to drag you down
No problem! I am a Japanese
all I have to say is I don't know
Don't worry, I am a good person!
Ching, if you are not a bad person
he is a very nice person.
He loves to help people
His girlfriend won't...
His girlfriend won't fell lost
What are you talking to her about?
What I told, I don't have to tell you
Ling, we should help her
Your decision
Why don't I stay at your house
so she can rest here?
Don't talk nonsense
Miss, don't call the police
No! No!
I am not a nasty person.
I won't call the police
I will help you to find your boyfriend,
don't worry!
Are you serious?
Don't regret it after I translate that for you
Only helpless people
can understand each other
Ling, thank you very much
You are welcome
When you are talking sweet,
you are really are a nice person
If... I have any other questions
I will call you, okay?
Good night
Please
This...
Like this
If anything happens, take this
Don't worry, if anything happens, you...
use that. OK?
Good night
Go to sleep!
No one will bother you!
Ching, Good morning
Daijiro asked me to tell you that
he went to work
There is breakfast in the microwave.
The key is in the cup
There are a lot of police on the street,
be careful
Also, there is a fat white man
He is nasty, you have to be careful!
You want me to translate that!
Is there any problem?
You are crazy!
Who are you talking to?
You weren't this good before
I was!
I had enough!
Ready, action!
Hey, it is time for you
to pay me back my money
If you have no money,
you can be a hooker
Give me two more days, okay?
There are three customers waiting
Let's go!
Cut, cut
Okay. One more time.
Stuntman, get ready
Okay!
You have to squeeze harder
during the real shoot, understand?
Okay!
Ready! Action!
Harder...
I'm sorry
Sorry!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry
Director, are you okay?
I was looking for you the whole night
Why did you look for me?
A girl from Mainland China
sneaked into my house
Where is she now?
In my house
I promised her that
I would help her to find her boyfriend
Does Ling know about it?
She translated for me
Is that girl pretty?
Very pretty
No wonder
I only hope Ling will get jealous
Did she?
I don't think so
This means that she doesn't love you anymore.
You see?
Have you anything
about her boyfriend?
Just a little bit
Hey
Daijiro, how come you are here?
How come you are here?
He is nice to take me home,
it's none of you business anyway
Hey!
What?
No way?!
He can't stand it
Are you scared of blood?
What did you say?
Stop... Stop...
Are you okay?
Stop...
You too... Sop!
You crazy!
- Are you okay?
- I am fine
Bastard, I'm in pain
You lucky little fool
I am really sorry
Okay, no problem,
don't let me see you next time
We can talk by using this phone
I am going to make a call, wait
Hello?
I am Daijiro
I am very busy... Wait
I was born a loser
The sad part is that Ling was my first lover
She made me forget all my weaknesses,
like I have a monkey face, I'm too short
I was always the shortest in the class
My first love was pretty smooth
It made me feel that I was normal
But you are nice
It's only the words to soothe someone
who is ugly
Comparing to me,
you still know where your lover is
But I don't know mine
You take the risk to come all the way here
Just to find him
He must be very handsome
Not because he is handsome. But,
we spent a lot of special moments together
and he is my first lover
You mean sleeping with him?
Why do you ask her this kind of question?
Sorry! I am too straight-forward
I am very serious about this matter
You haven't answered me yet.
Is he handsome?
To me, he is the most handsome man
in the world
Is he tall and big?
To me, he is like a giant
Of course it's better to be
tall and handsome
He said that too
I also treated Ling well
That is her lost
I wasn't very short when I was little
But my dad said that
I would not be very tall when I grew up
How did he know?
My dad said
When I knew how to walk,
I always climbed on a chair
That is fate
Luckily I am 6 inches taller than you
What is wrong with you?! Even is you are
6 inches longer you are still he sex toy
What do you mean?
When I find my boyfriend then
I don't have to bother you anymore
I understand how you feel
You can rely on me
I wish that Ling will change he mind
and be with you
Thanks!
I have to sleep now
You should get some sleep too,
doesn't she have things to do tomorrow?
Yes
Hello
Mom!
How are you?
Are you feeling okay?
Okay
I am so busy recently
Don't worry
Where is Ling?
Mom.. Take care of yourself.
Stay away from too much diet
When my movie comes out,
I will send you a copy
Daijiro, remember this
In your mom's heart,
you are taller than Mt. Fuji
Mom, don't say it that way
Take good care of your health
Okay... Get some rest
Good night!
My mom
I know
I love my mom
But I left my mom for a person
who doesn't love me
I don't know what you are talking about.
But I understand
Maybe I don't need a translator.
I only need you to listen to me
I thought I would love Hong Kong
But if you don't have a person to rely on
It's very lonely here even though
this is the most beautiful city
This is the first time
to look at you so close
You are prettier than Ling
You take me in and help me
to find my boyfriend
I really want to thank you
I hope that Ling will come back to you
You feature is so nice
Your lips are thin and wet
My lips are always dry
You are not handsome, but you are nice
The beauty of your heart
It is an eternal beauty
How come you boyfriend left you behind?
You've got a great figure
and bigger breasts than Ling's
No, I can't think that way
It's too ugly
I was crying earlier, but now...
From your eye, I can tell
that you got hurt really deep
Get some sleep!
When you wake up
it will be like a new beginning
No, I can't do this
I can't
I will sleep here
Good night
Daijiro, Daijiro
time for breakfast
Thanks
let's eat
He is the person I am looking for
Right! We are going to look for
your boyfriend today
He is my boyfriend
So you like that type of man
I am better than him
Nothing
Let's eat breakfast
Kenichi, ask him if he knows
the man in the picture
Okay!
Everyone knows him around here
He doesn't always come here!
Really?
I think he went to Thailand
to have a good time
Yes! Go look for him at
the Golden Flower Night Club
Golden Flower Night Club,
where is it?
You don't know where it is?
It's two blocks down the street
Leave your telephone number here
when he comes back,
I will tell him to call you
Great, thank you
Can you two handle it?
Don't you need help?
We can handle it
Are you injured badly?
It is only a scratch
why don't you worry
about your boyfriend
Could you tell Ching that she is pretty today
I reject that
You have a low standard for the word, pretty
If my standard is low,
then you are ugly
Why do you use her to make me mad?
Take a deep breath and listen carefully
She is prettier than you
Miss, please,
show me your ID card please
What?
ID card
Japanese?
Passport please
(?????)
Hey, what are you two doing?
Flirting!
Come here!
Stop it!
Go! Go!
Where are you going? Hooker,
where are you going?
Hooker
Are you mad?
Does it hurt?
But I had to do that
If not you would have been taken
to the police station
I might have hurt you on your head
But I used my hands trying you protect you
I hurt badly too
I was forced to do that
This way please
Excuse me, do you speak Mandarin?
I am not mad at you for hitting me
I just don't want to sneak around
You will find your boyfriend in two days,
aren't you happy?
Okay, if he is not in Hong Kong
or is already married and has kids
You can still stay at my house
Tell her that...
I really like her
Where the hell did you go?
Leaving me like that?
Let's start
Japanese speaking class
Lesson one
Self introduction
I am a Japanese
No! You are a Chinese
No, I am a Japanese, Japanese,
I am a Japanese
Chinese!
Chinese
When you want to know
what time it is
What time is it?
Eight O'clock sharp
It is five minutes to eight
Five minutes
Minus five minutes
When you want to go to the bathroom...
Bathroom
Where is the bathroom?
Ba-th-roo-m
Not bad
Can you get me some toilet paper?
Can you get me a camera?
Toilet paper...
Hello
Why don't you call me?
I thought you might not like it
How do you know if you don't call me?
What are you doing?
I am teaching Ching Japanese
Isn't she looking for her boyfriend?
We've been there today
You said that she is very pretty, right?
Right! It is very subjective
others may not think that way
Daijiro, do you still like me?
You know why I came to Hong Kong
Could I get to see Ching?
Of course
Let me teach her Japanese then!
okay... I will call you again
Bye!
Is she prettier than me?
Yes!
Daijiro, no problem?
No problem
We ran out of tissue paper,
I will go buy some more tomorrow
Get some sleep! Everything is fine!
Hello... Ling
Where are you right now?
East Point Mall
I am free
You should get some rest then
Why don't you ask me to come out
and have a cup of coffee?
I am afraid that you would not like it
Sorry to keep you waiting
Please
Haven't seen you for a long time
Yes
That girl...
Ching
Right... How is Ching?
Let's talk about body first...
She is not really great
She dresses quite conservatively
but her skin is very smooth
She's got a pair of big eyes
that make you want to help her
Do I get to meet her?
Of course
This way
This is for you
What?
You have to go see your boyfriend
I don't want people to know that
you came here illegally
If you dress a little better,
the cops will not suspect you
Maybe your boyfriend will be
glad to see you dressed well
Try it!
Go change your clothes
You treat a girl
who has a boyfriend so good
So you have grown up
or it's that you didn't treat me
well enough before
Because I didn't treat you well,
I ended up here!
Ling, can you translate it for me?
Okay
Daijiro, I don't know how to thank you
for everything you have done for me
At the beginning, I knew you liked me
And didn't mind that I came illegally
Later, you knew I came for my boyfriend.
You still treated me so good
Can I ask you a question?
Do you love me?
Daijiro, do you know that,
I never loved you
I know what you mean...
I am not doing these things
to make you love me
I am just happy helping people
I don't mind whether you like me or not
Yes, I like you
But I can't love you.
Because I love Ling
Ling, you don't have to translate
what I am going to say
Daijiro is a good person
He is worth for a girl to admire
She told me that you are nice
Lots of girls will like you
Of course!
Let's go to eat something!
I can't stand it!
You want to seduce me?
If you don't want me to touch you,
you can push me away
Shit!
Excuse me
My girlfriend is sick!
She is coughing and very pale
Is she okay?
Don't worry. Just caught flu
Thank you!
Take the medicine
Wait
It's time for medicine
Excuse me
Take the medicine
I know it is bitter
I tasted it already
It is very bitter
We will wait until you get well
then we will go look for
you boyfriend, okay?
This place is quieter than
the cemetery
Go get some pretty girls
and do some interesting things
You can't afford it
Stop talking nonsense.
It is very dangerous to find girls from China
I found one recently.
She was very good
Her figure was just like Madonna
When I was trying to bring her here,
I discovered that her dad was a commander
If her dad had found out, I'd be dead
Excuse me
What is it?
I want to find Ming
Ming? Everybody knows him
Follow me
Wait
Where are you going to?
Ming, someone is looking for you
Who?
Don't take my wig?!
If the customer touches you,
what should you say?
Don't touch
Yuen
Yuen!
Ching... It's you
Finally get to see you
I am lucky
How come there was no news from you?
You didn't keep what you promised me
What have I promised you?
Take me to Hong Kong and marry me
After I left you, I came to Hong Kong
I was going to keep my promise
I made to you
I couldn't believe that when I woke up one day,
I discovered something on my tongue
I had headache and I puked
I went to see a doctor
He told me that I had cancer
I went to the hospital myself.
And received all the treatments
After 49 days, I got well
I didn't want you to worry about me,
so I didn't call you
I wanted to face this myself
So we could share the beautiful future
Who brought you here?
I sneaked into Hong Kong
What? It is very dangerous
After I came to Hong Kong,
the police were everywhere
Luckily I met a very nice Japanese man
He took me in and helped me to find you
He is outside
A Japanese man helped you?
That's great, let me see him
Where is he?
You have a nice view
Put the cushion here
My picture, is cute.
I am cuter than Jackie Chan
Cheer up
Yes
Do you want me to stay with you?
I don't want anything right now
Let's make love!
Do you really love me?
Ling!
She loves you more than I love you!
What?
My Chinese is not good
sometimes I make mistakes
Coming
Good Night
I am Ching's boyfriend
It's you, come in
You think you can just leave some money
and forget about everything?
What you did was like leaving a cat
in the wild mountain
Like abandoning a baby
on other people's footstep
You are not quite responsible
I have cancer
I teach the girls English
in the night club everyday
I just want to save some money for her
But you came to leave her to me
We can only live in the low class apartment
If you do this, it is like
pushing her down into an abyss
Besides, the amount you put down
is not enough
I know I will be dead soon
She likes Hong Kong so much.
She must want to stay here
So I want to buy her an ID card
I need some money
$20,000
$20,000?!
Yes!
Thanks!
No problem!
You are welcome
Thanks!
It hurts, $20,000
But for Ching, I have to do it
$20,000 is gone just like this.
It really hurts
Here is $2,000...
Coming
Are you Ching's boyfriend?
Boyfriend? You can say that!
This again
Has Ching stayed here before?
Yes
Has she slept on this bed before?
Has she used the bathroom before?
Yes
Let me tell you, I am her boyfriend.
You are with her now. I want to return her
No...
No... If you don't have sex so often,
you wouldn't be this tall?!
Let me tell you, I want break up fees
$100,000
Boyfriend back! Back!
Back?!
I'll be back!
Didn't I give you money already?
$20,000!
It's none of you business. I change
my outlook and I want $100,000 more
Let Ching talk to him
Daijiro
Ching are you okay?
I will handle this
No problem
This is my name card,
when you have the money then call me
Ouch!
Kenichi, where were you?
I was looking for you
I was looking for you, too
Why?
You say first
I need money
Do you want to make money?
What money?
The one you hurt before
The shorty?
He and the director will give $100,000
for anyone who can jump over a ten feet gap
I will do it
But it is 6 levels high
I think it's dangerous.
Even if you quit now
no one is going to laugh at you
I will think of another way
It is not all about money now..
If I jump over it
I will be very confident
Do you remember when Jackie Chan
jumped down from the bell tower?
It touched me so much
I went home and cried for a whole night
I thought that he was awesome!
Don't you agree?
You've got guts. But you don't have to
compete with Jackie Chan
No, I am challenging myself
I can make it. But... if I mess up
there is no take 2
Kenichi, leave me alone
We can start 15 minutes later
Director, he is ready
Ready
Cam 1 ready
Cam 2 ready
Cam 3 ready
Daijiro, remember, in your mother's heart,
you are taller than Mt. Fuji
Rolling
Speeding
Action!
Cut!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
I am fine!
You've got guts! From now on
you are the #1 stuntman
Thank you
You are great
I did it! I did it!
You did it
Bald head, release Ching
This is not enough! Where is the interest?
I will let her go if you pay up
What the hell did you say?
Just give me $100,000 more
then I will let her go
Do you know who I am?
I am a Japanese gangster
You too?! $8,000 will do then
Damn you!
You do act like it
I remember you.
You are the one who acts in TV series
Okay, okay
Little fool, it's quick, but you can't hurt me
So dirty
Police! Open the door
Police!
You are late
Is that so?
Are you taking drugs, or are you fighting?
No, just having a party
Shut up, I will hit you
Good friend, I am warning you
Don't let me catch you
doing something wrong
Sir, we have arrested
an illegal immigrant outside
Sir, she is my wife
Shut up, bring all to the police station
Ching...
Daijiro...
Ching, how come you are here?
Daijiro
Ching... Why don't you come over here?
Let her come over here
Daijiro. Listen,
thanks for everything
you have done for me
Understand?
I really...
like you
Understand
That day when you left me,
I understood
Ching, I... I don't like you
I love you!
I will see you again
What?
I will see you again...
You can go now
Miss, let me drive you home!