It rained for months on end.
The whole of Tokyo was flooded.
The damage
ran to billions of yen,
and the dead and missing
numbered in their millions.
The survivors
all mutated into
strange amphibian monsters,
adapting quickly to the
suddenly changing climate.
We're all going to die!
No, we'll mutate.
We mustn't breed!
Think what the children
would look like.
No, actually,
the horniness is
part of the mutation.
That's why the species
is so successful
from an evolutionary
point of view.
- Hello?
- Hiroko, where are you?
No, we're not lost,
just stuck in traffic.
- Where are you?
- Right now...
- We've just passed Shinsencho.
- You're almost here.
- OK, talk to you in a bit.
- OK.
Yeah, see you.
Are we going the right way?
Look at the map.
Sorry.
We're already... there,
I think.
Really?
Where? What color is your car?
It's silver.
A Honda.
Well,
more like gray, really.
I've got a red umbrella.
A red umbrella?
Spin it round.
I'll try.
I'm spinning it, I'm spinning it.
Can't you see me?
Now jump.
Jump? OK, here I go...
Now on one leg.
- Akemi!
- Hiroko!
- Here, towels.
- Thanks.
In Tokyo...
the bigger the
company you work for...
the smaller
the flat you get.
You should work
for a smaller company.
My company's
already pretty small.
- It's a nice place.
- You think so?
You still have Saburo, then?
Little Saburo!
It's raining tonight,
so your car should be OK.
But you can't leave it.
There's a hardware store
just over there. Park in front...
It's been closed for a while.
AKEMI SHIMIZU
Now for this week's episode
of 'Where Are They Now?'
Akira, what are you doing now?
Well... I'm a filmmaker.
He's just made a film
that he's showing around.
The film's about...
...is the main thing.
Please go and see it.
This is it.
But this is...
a porno theater.
It's a real theater, then!
It'll be dark and quiet.
You shouldn't have cut
my sex scene after all!
Are you making pornos?
No, that was a joke.
I had a part for Hiroko,
but she turned it down.
What a pity. No ambition!
Right!
That's her problem exactly.
Why did you pass up
the chance to be a star?
I don't like the sound
of my own voice.
It sounds like this.
I can't wait to see it.
- Really?
- Yes.
How about now?
- I've got the DVD here.
- She might be tired.
No, let's watch it now.
It's not too intellectual, is it?
There are so many lives
in the future.
Assuming we haven't
destroyed ourselves first
we could live on
after the end of the solar system.
In the infinity
of new souls created
there's no reason that one
shouldn't be me again.
Sorry.
I have to get up early
in the morning.
- Can you help me with this?
- This?
I liked the bit I saw, though.
You can change in
the bathroom.
Hiroko, can you pull that side?
I hope you'll be all right.
I'm sorry it's so cramped.
It's fine.
'A good soldier must suffer
with pride,' right?
'Enduring the unendurable.
Suffering the...'
Stop it, stupid!
Seriously, though. Thanks.
We'll start looking for
an apartment tomorrow.
My boyfriend's staying next
Sunday. He's driving from Nagoya.
His uncle works in advertising.
Shall I ask him
to come and see your film?
You think
he'd come from Nagoya?
Of course not!
That's my side.
His uncle lives in Tokyo.
I'm switching it off.
All that way, for your movie!
Three, two, one...
- Good night!
- Good night.
Don't forget
to move your car tomorrow.
The fines are huge.
I'm glad it's raining.
Don't forget to move your car
Look.
We'll be OK until Friday.
CLOSED UNTIL FRIDAY NOVEMBER 16TH
What are you doing?
It'll go up if we don't pay.
We're not kids anymore.
Cover me!
I'm going into the safe!
Copy that!
We can't make any more mistakes.
Our budget's tight as it is.
To rent an apartment...
Say the rent is 30,000...
We'd need a deposit
of two months' rent.
In all, we'd need...
We would need
400,000 yen in advance.
It's a good place
for young couples.
Who are you? Let me out!
It's popular with young couples.
Do you like the view?
Nice dead cat.
Something smells like shit!
I can't live in a dump like that.
There wasn't any soap left
in Akemi's place.
Do you think it's a hotel?
I didn't mean that.
My bad.
Let's go and buy some soap now.
What's wrong? Are you mad?
It's nothing.
Come on, what is it?
You said I have no ambition.
What?
Yesterday. You said
I have no ambition at all.
I said that?
It's not true.
I like photography and art.
I've got a boating license,
and I read a lot too.
But they're hobbies.
They're not the same as ambitions.
What's the difference?
You have to be able to define...
who you are in the world
by what you do.
What I like to do
defines who I am.
Doesn't that make me
a richer person?
You still have to be better at it
than others.
Something's wrong.
Something's wrong
with these buildings.
They refuse all physical contact
with each other.
You're always
say something clever
to avoid really talking.
Every night, flat ghosts
slide in and out of these gaps.
And wander about the city...
They wander about the city,
scaring the people shitless.
The authorities
fill in the gaps with concrete,
but the buildings
keep moving apart,
letting the flat creatures
take over.
I could make them
out of paper.
All right, what's the matter?
I'm listening.
I'm ready
for a dramatic conversation.
with flashbacks
and a big climax...
You've stopped
listening already.
You're the one who's 'dramatic'!
I'm listening.
But we're talking a lot.
That's not true!
Maybe you're right.
I don't think I know
what I'm doing.
What, here?
No, in general.
You take things too seriously.
Where's your sense of humor?
There are
these two poisonous snakes.
One says to the other.
'We're poisonous, aren't we?'
So the other one says
'Of course we are.
Why do you ask?'
And the first snake says
'I've just bitten my tongue!'
PART-TIME JOB AVAILABLE
WRAPPING PURCHASES
A part-time job.
We could work here.
No, they'll pay peanuts!
It'd take two weeks
to pay off the parking fine!
Wait till you find a real job.
I want to keep busy.
Anyway, I have no ambition.
so it's a perfect job for me.
Come on!
I did it without thinking
and got the job.
Only you, Akira?
But Hiroko's dog was great.
They are stupid.
It wasn't great.
And it was a cat.
You're better off
doing something else.
I won't work there long.
How long do you
plan to stay here?
- We haven't really...
- We saw a nice place today.
We have a good chance
of getting it.
Yes, a really good chance!
Where?
Tokyo...
No boyfriends, no pets.
Is there anyone
who actually checks?
Don't wrap two together.
Hello.
There seem to be some residents
already living here!
FRIDAY NOVEMBER 16TH
CLOSED UNTIL FRIDAY NOVEMBER 16TH
CAR No 55M46-51 TOWED AWAY
TO MUNICIPAL POUND
So I wrap nine boxes
with just one roll of paper.
But she says I should do eleven.
How am I supposed to do that?
Even ten is impossible.
What's the matter?
The car was stolen today.
What?
All our equipment was in it.
What about the screening?
I'm screwed!
No, you're not.
Yesterday, I moved everything
into the apartment.
I didn't like leaving it out there.
Akemi was upset
so I forgot to tell you.
Great thinking!
The smoke machine too?
I just told you.
There's the 15,000-yen fine
plus a 14,000-yen towing fee.
I don't have 29,000 yen. But
I need my things from the car.
Can you take me to it
so I can get my stuff?
Not until you pay the money.
We're open until six.
It's still my car!
Not until you pay the money,
it's not.
Let's just say
there's 29,000 yen in the car.
If you just show me where it is
I can get the money and pay you.
What do you say?
What'll happen to it
if I don't pay?
Make? Color?
Year?
Thank you.
I hate him. He's a cavity!
He's got bad teeth?
No, I mean he's a cavity himself.
Last year
he caught pneumonia.
Too bad,
he has a good doctor!
All that stuff?
Here you go!
Put it in here, please.
Where shall I put this?
Look!
There are so many lives
in the future.
Assuming we haven't
destroyed ourselves first.
we could live on.
If we moved our vessel or planet
close to the black hole
at the edge of the event horizon.
then tossed in
all our nuclear waste...
Great! I've never seen smoke
used like that in a film before.
No, Lucy.
It's the first time smoke's been
used that way 'outside' a film.
Using smoke 'inside' films
is so common.
I want to force
the audience's involvement
by breaking through
the surface of the screen.
The audience shouldn't feel safe.
Pleased to meet you.
It got to me, eh?
You should come
to my office sometime.
We usually do advertising
for medical products.
But we get more
creative sometimes.
Thanks.
I'll think about it. I'm
considering a few options right now.
Nice work! Pretty funny.
Really?
Being funny is the hardest.
I'm going for a beer.
Excuse me.
- I'll pass this on.
- Thank you.
You should be in films.
Come off it! Not me.
- Were you in the film?
- That's not me.
I'm more in transportation.
I helped with the editing too.
- Are you a filmmaker too?
- No, I'm just the girlfriend.
You must be a good one.
Relationships with artists
are tough.
They can be demanding.
I once went out with a painter.
He was always working
or talking about his work.
I felt invisible.
But when he had an opening,
with all those people.
I realized his art was more
important than my problems.
You said
they'd be out tonight.
Not so loud.
I told them you were coming.
I thought they'd understand.
Apparently not! One extra
person is bad enough, but two...
Don't say that.
They're my friends.
I have to help them.
They're just
taking advantage of you.
You're not helping them.
All you're doing is indulging them.
Your 'friend' doesn't think he has
to work because he's an 'artist'.
My uncle won't hire him.
He thinks he's an idiot.
Akira's not an idiot.
He's even got a job.
Hiroko is the problem.
She just hangs around all day
cutting pictures
out of my magazines.
Cold.
What the...
Did you see that?
Dear Akira
I hope that
this letter finds you well,
and that your screenings
are going well.
What about the wrapping?
Are you still doing that job?
Or maybe by now
you're a big-shot director.
Or perhaps
you're in advertising.
I wonder what
happened to the car.
I hope that someone
is having a good time with it.
I wonder how Akemi's doing.
And guys show up,
so scary...
I tried to fold this letter
into an elegant yacht,
but I got it totally wrong.
You know
how useless I am at origami.
As for me.
living between the buildings
with the ghosts.
Just kidding!
My life isn't that extraordinary.
I'm fine.
That's all
I wanted to tell you, really.
And I'm doing
all the things
I ever wanted to do.
In fact
I've never in all my life
felt so useful.
That guy!
- Who is that guy?
- He's 'The Creature from the Sewer.'
Hey!
Somebody help!
He's the Creature from the Sewer.
He's coming.
Run!
Please call the cop!
Call the police!
Get him, get him!
Tokyo is afraid.
Who is this creature who for
the past 2 weeks has been
terrifying citizens all over
Tokyo and then vanishing?
The media are calling him
'The Creature from the Sewers.'
A few shocked eyewitnesses
have managed to film him
on their cell phones.
Just watch, Mr. Nomoto...
His gait
his insane beard
his milky eye...
I wanted to run away too
but I was so scared,
I couldn't move.
He came towards me...
and then he... he licked me.
He was disgusting...
Sorry.
His eye was like this
his beard went like this
and he walked like this...
I was so afraid...
He was walking like this...
And smoking like that...
The police are still searching
the sewers and underground.
There.
There he is.
Don't move!
- Freeze!
And I plan to prove to the court,
without trying its patience,
in less than...
ninety minutes, that is,
before the clock strikes six
in this courthouse of
the Republic,
that it is quite unthinkable,
for my client,
whose whole life
has been dedicated
to the good and the beautiful...
That it is unthinkable as
I was saying for Mrs. Defrasnoux
to have murdered
by decapitation Leopoldine.
the cat belonging to the plaintiff,
Mr. Troucat.
K.U. TVNews
Where does the Creature
of the Sewers come from?
Under interrogation
he hasn't said a word.
All he eats is flowers,
and only
'ichimonji' chrysanthemum,
symbol of the imperial family.
The American government claims
to have spotted him
in footage
of an Al-Qaeda camp.
In Siberia, a woman claims
he is her son Igor,
an amnesiac genius pianist
who disappeared 17 years ago.
In Japan, a young woman
says she saw him
inside the Aum sect
10 years ago.
In Finland, a surgeon claims
he spotted him
in a Hungarian pedophile film.
What a story, Mr. Nomoto...
A French lawyer
Maitre Voland, has contacted
the Japanese government.
He claims that, although
he doesn't know the creature
he can communicate with him.
- There!
- Here! Here!
- Mr. Voland!
- Please say something!
Mr. Voland!
The Creature from the Sewer!
The Creature from the Sewer?
Sir.
Mr. Hirokishi would like to know
what you said that
finally made him react.
I asked him if he realized
that it's likely he'll be hanged.
And what did he reply?
He said, 'No, I don't want to.'
Did you ask him his name?
He said, 'Call me Merde.' Which sounds
very like the French word 'merde'.
Merde?
Shit
Following the Merde case,
the Japanese government
to toughen
immigration regulations.
Inside Japan,
there have been attacks
on white foreigners
with red beards.
Mr. Merde,
whose trial will start tomorrow,
will be defended
by the French lawyer Mr. Voland.
one of the only
three people in the world.
who can speak
the same language as Mr. Merde.
Mr. Voland has already declared
that he will plead insanity
and irresponsibility
at the time of the offense.
Let us move on to the motive
for this heinous act
if such a motive can exist.
Could you tell us
why you took the lives
of so many innocent people?
'I don't like innocent people.'
'I don't like people.'
So what...
you're going to kill us all?
Wouldn't it have been simpler
since you like no one,
for you to kill yourself?
'But I love life, imbecile!'
What?
Silence!
Maitre, instruct your client
the court will not be insulted!
At least modern terrorists
have the decency
to blow themselves up
with their victims.
'And among all people,
the Japanese are really
the most disgusting.'
Disgusting?
I understand now.
You should know that in Japan,
we don't really like
racist foreigners.
Besides,
nobody forced you to come
and live in our country!
'Yes. My god did.'
'My god always places me
among the people
I hate the most.'
'It's the cross I have to bear.'
So I ask you, Mr. Merde.
what do you have
against the Japanese?
'They live way too long.'
'And their eyes are shaped
like a woman's sex.'
'It's totally disgusting.'
Silence!
And Mr. Merde thinks
that 'he' is quite appealing?
'I don't know.
But if I knew, I'd answer yes.'
I've never looked at myself.
My god forbids mirrors.'
'But my mother,
who was gorgeous
used to say
I was a pretty little boy.'
Well...
then your mother...
sorely deceived you, Mr. Merde!
He won't talk to you anymore.
He says, 'It's not interesting.'
'My mother was a saint!'
'You all...
You all raped her!'
'And I am your son!'
Warders!
Make the defendant sit!
Silence!
Defendant, do you understand
that you risk the death penalty?
'No.'I don't want that.
'I'm against it.'
Hang Merde! Hang Merde!
Free Merde! Free Merde!
Today, the Pope condemned
Mr. Merde's appalling crimes.
In Japan, ultra-nationalists
are violently demonstrating
to demand the death penalty.
But in the eyes of many
Mr. Merde has become a star.
The trial's outcome
will be announced tomorrow.
CONDEMNED TO DEATH!
THREE YEARS LATER
He wants you to warn your client
he'll be hanged in an hour.
He said, 'No.'
Ask him what he wants
for his last meal.
'Flowers... and cash.'
He's asking for a last cigarette.
Non smoking
What's he doing?
He's praying.
Execute.
Dead.
- It's over.
- Yes.
It's over.
The sky has grown old.
He's gone!
Coming soon:
the adventures of Mr. Merde in NY
MERDE IN USA
Directed by Leos Carax
How long will it take
before this circle disappears?
10 seconds, 10 minutes,
10 hours, 10 days,
10 months, 10 years...
I've been living in this house
for 10 years.
I am a hikikomori.
Usually, hikikomoris live
at the expense of their parents.
but I live alone.
Defecating with the door open,
I don't care.
Falling asleep while defecating,
Strangely,
I don't watch television.
When was the last time
I watched it?
However,
I feed myself every day.
I don't need a table.
Those who are sensitive
would have noticed,
but my own way of tidying up,
practiced for 10 years
has now reached
the level of art.
It's hard to believe,
but I have read all these books.
Lately, reading magazines about
climbing, fishing and travelling
suddenly makes me miss home.
I never get into the room
that my father used.
The envelope of money
my father sends.
I open it every month.
The first year
money came with a letter.
For the next 9 years
only money.
Brand new crisp banknotes.
How exciting.
With money and a telephone,
everything is OK
as everything
can be delivered.
The bell is ringing. I open the door.
I take. I give.
I close the door.
With the delivery men.
I never make eye contact.
On Saturdays, I always order a pizza.
So you never look at
people's faces?
Right.
I hated having contact
with people.
with the sunlight too.
I like watching the sunlight.
I can see it...
The movement of the sunlight.
Others may not
but I can even see
the hour hand moving.
Everything is moving.
It has been 10 years
since I last moved.
It has been 11 years
living in the house.
Strictly speaking.
I am a hikikomori.
I digest better.
When I fall asleep
on the toilet
I have sweet dreams.
The reading continues.
The smell of my father...
Saturday is pizza day.
With the delivery men,
I don't make any...
The first eye contact in 11 years.
Excuse me...
Buttons?
C, o, m...
Coma.
Did you push it?
- Yes.
- You did?
There's a mistake.
The eighth one from the floor.
On the right.
This place is really perfect.
This smell is really awful.
Because of the shock,
for 2 days,
I couldn't do anything.
Even if I don't do anything
to start with.
What's wrong with me?
It's shaking.
Pizza's End?
How dare you answer me?
I'm not joking, cut the crap.
A guy like you, I'll cut off
both his hands and feet
to make sashimi.
Bring me some water.
It's me.
Don't hang up.
The weather is dull
and I wasn't in a good mood.
Sorry.
I said I'm sorry, punk!
You're really getting
on my nerves.
You're not even good
at delivering
and who do you think
you're talking to!
I paid your two-weeks salary
you should be grateful.
Are you trying to say
you are hurt?
Well, I am hurt as much as you.
Cut the crap, punk!
I am much more introvert than
you are! Moron!
Excuse me...
The girl who is working at
your place...
Is it her day off today?
Who?
Pale complexion...
Garter belt...
Buttons...
She's my wife.
Just kidding.
She also quit yesterday.
She stopped delivering?
This is really perfect...
The little one said...
she'd never come out again.
You must be all crazy.
She had been working for
some time.
Where does she live?
3 Daizawa, I think.
Don't bother about the pizza.
When a hikikomori
wants to meet a hikikomori
there is only one way.
What a blinding light.
It's so hot.
I hate sweating.
Why did I come out?
Right.
I'm going... Where?
To the left.
The subway station...
No, the bus is better.
3 Daizawa...
Right, I don't have any money.
Nobody must see me.
Where do I have to go?
Yes, of course.
Great.
This...
Passing by Sangenjaya...
Come on...
I can ride this...
I can be there in 30 minutes.
Whatever, Let's go.
Let's walk.
Off we go.
Good. Full steam ahead.
Excuse me. I would...
They all went back in.
All of them.
This man...
I was like him 5 years ago.
For her, it must
have been 10 years...
15 years?
This guy is a rookie.
As for her...
Come out, please.
Quick, come out.
If you don't come out now
you never will.
Listen to me.
Open the door!
At least, tell me your name.
It's collapsing!
Come out!
Everybody, come out!
What is she waiting for?
Don't go back.
Don't touch me!
Don't go back in.
I pushed it.
It's shaking.