Would you sacrifice your youth...
...for your love?
Do you?
It all began on ICQ
LEMON COFFEE, where are you?
We miss you!
LEMON COFFEE, go for it!
Cyber sex with me? Ooh...
Yes, come on baby, I'm a Thai girl
Why is a hot babe at home eating pizza alone?
Very sunny out...
Do you like the sun?
No, I hate it!
Only the sick will spread their germs
My garden
My big house
Hi, LEMON COFFEE
guess which one is me?
The cutest one of course
The sunshine here will kill all the germs
I'll tell you something personal!
I've neglected a lot in my life...
...like the people around me
Since I've been in a wheelchair...
...I see life from a different angle
It's actually a clearer angle
Have you noticed that...
...every flower and every leaf is different?
Have you noticed that
...everyone has a good side?
Now I cherish
everything around me
You are always online
Don't you have anything else to do?
Come to Koh Samui if you have time
I have a resort called "Coconut Villa"
I guarantee you...
You'll have a great time here
Stop! Stop...
Stop!
Miss, are you okay?
That was the first time I saw
Mr. And Mrs. Bond
Not until later...
...do I understand why Mr. Bond is
so strange
That's more handsome!
Go...
Thank you
A bet
whether the first customer is
LEMON COFFEE?
So what if it is?
If it is, you give me massage
If not, I'll give you a massage
Deal!
Let's make it official, lest you forget
Sawadeekup! Welcome to Coconut Villa!
Thank you
- What's up?
- I don't know
It must be her
Sawadeekup! Welcome!
You're our first customer today
You'll receive a complimentary drink
but please check in first
The girl doesn't smile
Like the way you were
This is your bungalow, very nice room
We have Full moon party
Half moon party and Black moon party
That means we'll have party every night
I'm sure you'll enjoy your stay here
Thank you
You know lots of girls on ICQ
...are actually boys!
Really?
You think this LEMON COFFEE is
a girl or boy?
LEMON COFFEE?
I heard a cool and pretty girl arrived
today and...
...she takes coffee with lemon
Coincidence?
Where is Lek?
What is it?
So? Are you buying tonight?
Don't worry
I'll buy!
Hey girl, for you!
Thank you!
And this, for you!
No... No... No
Don't ever stand under a coconut tree
at dusk
Be careful
Do you think that's LEMON COFFEE?
I'll tell you later
Don't look. She's looking over
Not bad looking!
She's cool, man
Don't scare her. Go back to work...
Lek
You said you were good with women?
Of course
Let's have a bet
What on?
If the girl doesn't smile within 24 hours
You'll give me 50% off
What if she smiles?
If she does...
You'll give me 60% off
You serious?
Sure, why not?!
Let's make it clear...
She has to laugh, not smile
A sad smile...
...won't count
- Laugh?
- Yes
- Start the clock.
- OK
Are you LEMON COFFEE?
Lek?
Fragile
This is LEMON COFFEE?
I can't believe you came
I'm Ching Wai. Call me Ching
I'm Lek. That means little
I thought you were lying. I didn't know...
...that I was really handicapped
Don't be sorry. I'm fine with it
I didn't lie. I am really happy
Probably more content than you are!
How long have you not smiled?
Two years, almost
No wonder you look uncomfortable
Really?
Did my video clip work?
The file was infected with a virus
No way! What virus?
I Love You
Chan Rak Tur
What does it mean?
It means "I love you"
If you are infected, you're ruined
Stay longer, you'll get better
Sounds awful!
Pretty good
No way!
You should sing and laugh from the heart
He didn't!
You can?
Of course
If you laugh loudly three times...
I'll sing for you
That was the first time I saw him
Who knew he was telling the truth on ICQ
It surprised me that...
...even tough he was wheelchair-bound
he could still laugh so hard
I talked to him for a long time
He loosened up
I haven't felt that way in a long time
I had the best post-computer sleep...
...that night in two years
The other people here are also cool
Everyone is laid back
Nothing seems to get to them
Actually
I would love to be like them
I think I came to the right place
Hello!
Mr. And Mrs. Bond bought you this drink
Please thank your boss for me
You mean Mr. And Mrs. Bond?
- They are regulars here
- Really?
They've been coming here every year
for the past 20 years
Mr. And Mrs. Bond
please dance for us!
Sure!
So early?
It's already lunch time
When will someone dance with me?
May I dance with you?
Sure!
Honey, the girl is sitting alone
Why isn't Lek here?
He needs some time
Especially the young
You think they behave like us?
It'd be great if we were 30 years younger
You're so greedy!
You're much younger than I am
If I'm gone...
Stop! Let's dance!
You never know!
If I go first...
Stop! Let's dance!
OK
Didn't pay the bill?
Of course I did!
Business is slow...
...this time of year
Too noisy if it was crowded
Right, B289 the fewer customers the better
Otherwise, you'll have to close down
Why?
You always buy them drinks!
Please...
We're in business, man!
It's alright. I don't mind!
- Hi!
- Hello
Have a seat!
No, please continue!
It's alright, have a seat!
Allow me...
This is Brother Wing, the manager here
Hi
This is Ching from Hong Kong
You're a smooth operator!
Why didn't you introduce me earlier?
She is a guest here. Arrived yesterday
Excuse me...
I have an appointment. I'll let you talk
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be
What's up?
Too much internet?
Want to get some sun?
Your computer in the lobby is infected
It's just a blackout
Small island problems!
How can I help?
You're here on vacation
You can work for me
You're hiring?
Just kidding
Small business... we can't afford it!
Everyone here has multiple
responsibilities
Let me take you out
Remember, don't walk under
the Coconut trees at dusk
Very risky
See!
Told you so!
God is so nice to us!
We don't have to climb up for it!
You're lucky to live in a paradise!
Trouble-free!
Really?
You don't have beaches in Hong Kong?
No sunsets?
Or you just don't look for them!
The wind blows the bottles here
this time of year
Northerners write their miseries down and
put them in bottles...
...thinking the water will wash
the problems away
It doesn't matter where you are only
what you believe in
You can't run away from problems
They follow you everywhere
Does it really work?
I think so. Try it
Together!
- Be careful.
- Yes, sir
Dr. Lai
Get me a bigger boat
I want to sail further
Sure
Alone again?
How come no one from your hospital
comes with you?
They don't see the fun in work!
How are you?
Have you been doing physical therapy?
Of course!
Let me rephrase...
Have you overdone the therapy?
I'll be careful
That... LEMON COFFEE...
Is she pretty?
Please, she's only next door now!
Why talk on ICQ?
Invite her to your room
Silly!
We're all nosy people
Dr. Lai, why work so hard?
You dive everyday!
I want to gather some microorganism...
...that's flowing in from the Indian ocean
These microorganisms stimulate our
nervous systems
If we inject them into you
you may recover!
There is a Chinese saying...
Heal a heart problem with a heart
medicine. What does it mean?
Psychological counseling?
That girl is depressed
I'm talking about serious things...
...that concern your legs!
You are talking about a girl?
I really want to help her
Do you have the "I love you" virus?
Let me give you a check up!
Brat!
Hurry...
Higher... come on...
That is guaranteed to wipe out depression!
I want to play!
You are not a kid anymore!
I want to try
Really?
Chang, not too high!
Got it!
Higher!
Coming...
Be careful!
Chang! Stop! Stop...
You...
Drink it!
It was an accident... you didn't intend it
I killed my two best friends
I can't!
I can't forget about them
I see them when I close my eyes
Everyone here knows my story
A couple of years ago, at the intersection...
...a truck knocked me down and broke
my spine
The driver called in the middle of the night
He wanted me to sue him
He said he'd feel better if he went to jail
I asked him why he hit me
He said the brakes failed
I said then it wasn't his fault
Later...
I told him I got to know myself better
I didn't realize I was spoilt and
bad-tempered
Because I lost some things
I learnt to value life
One always grows when faced...
...with adversities
The best thing was...
I learnt to forgive
Try it. Forgive yourself!
The doctor said I will never...
...stand again
I say...
1...
2...
Even if it's for 2 seconds...
I have to prove that nothing is impossible
You have legs
If you want to stand
you have to do it yourself
I made it
Try it
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
We've been waiting for ages for our food
We're really hungry
Seriously? I'm sorry. Be my guest, okay?
That's really nice of you.
Thank you very much!
What about us?
No problem, on the house
Brother Wing, my treat tonight!
Let's eat!
What's wrong?
Not enough here
What the hell?
I'm the boss! They won't let me eat
I'll join you!
Please excuse us
We have to discuss some private matters
- Really?
- Yes!
Troublemakers!
Let's eat!
Please!
This one too. Thai pineapple
The snacks here are famous
Very popular
Look!
And this one
Smells great!
The grill is great!
- What is it?
- It hurts!
Are you alright?
- It got in my eye.
- Let me see...
It's alright
Wash it with water
- It'll be fine.
- Let me see
Thanks...
I'm alright
This is for you
Where did you get it? Did you buy it?
No, I made it
I'll play it for you!
Look, hold it here and blow!
Try it
Blow into this hole
No, the mouth goes...
Give me some time! I can do it!
Some time?
10 years or 20?
I can do it!
If you try
Lek is a very charming guy
Like you used to be!
I'll cook you Chinese food
Are you bored? Go and chat with Lek!
There isn't that much to say...
How can that be?
Mr. Bond and I chat about everything!
How did you meet him?
We met right here
There weren't so many tourists then
No one knew about this place
- Really?
- Yes!
I had a boyfriend then
We had a fight.
I thought he would come for me
But he didn't
He didn't care anymore
So I picked up Mr. Bond here
I didn't know we were so compatible
He is 20 years older than me
My mother was furious
You hit on him?
Yes, he talked to all the girls...
...but me!
I was quite attractive
So I confronted him with it
And he said...
The first thing one says to one's future
wife is very important
...and I haven't thought of
what to say yet
Now I know
It was just a line
Luckily, I was good judge of character
He is a very nice man
You're amazing!
Who knows what the future holds!
Do what makes you happy
Don't think that I am old-fashioned
I'm very open-minded!
Lek is a good man
But...
...sympathy is not enough
If you like him, you must take the good
with the bad
Simple philosophy
Mr. Bond, be careful!
If Mrs. Bond knew you were drinking
she'd kick your ass
Silly, she can't sleep without me!
Good for you!
Are you two holding hands yet?
You're so aggressive!
Let's have a bet
Again?
If you can't hold her hand in 24 hours
The rent goes back up to 70% off
Mr. Bond
I think you are fooling the world
You claim to have Parkinson's but
your math is so good
I don't know why
Money turns my mind on
Honestly, do you like her?
Honestly...
I really want to help her
You can't fool me
You like her
Listen...
...you can't help someone half-heartedly
You must go all the way
Up ahead
This is it!
I've been keeping something from you
What is it?
I have a wife
Let me introduce you
Isn't it pretty?
I haven't taken it out for a long time!
Do you want to drive it?
You can do it!
If I can do it, so can you!
Relax, you'll break the steering wheel!
I haven't driven in a while!
It's alright. I'm here
Step on it!
Look at that!
What are you doing?
I only said to look
Don't take it...
Jackfruits are really sweet!
Come on... we'll get caught!
Hurry up!
You...
Hold on! It's like a safari!
Go!
What is it?
Stop!
Are you alright? What is it?
Lek, what is it?
My hand...
I can't move my hand
Go to the hospital!
How is he?
His spine is fragile
Some vertebras are dislocated
It may affect his upper body too
Why did you take him on a safari ride?
You knew his spine was fragile
Calm down
I gave him anesthetics. He's still out
You can go and see him
What are we going to do?
Miss Wai
I didn't know
I warned him to be careful
I'm worried he moves too much
He made me smile again
Please save him!
Don't worry, he's very tough
I was here when he had the accident
It was 6 or 7 years ago
I'll try my best. He has a chance
Nerves can now be connected
I've been searching for a specific
microorganism...
...to regenerate nerves
I've found it
I first need a body to cultivate these cells
When it's ready
remove it and inject it into the patient
I'll be the body!
There are a lot of legal procedures for
this kind of experiment
Who will know?
I'll sign whatever is necessary
I swear I won't say a word
as long as you save him
It isn't that simple
Calm down
Lek...
It's me!
They gave me a lot of anesthetics
I'm very dizzy!
Rest, you'll be fine
I'm fine
Go out and enjoy yourself!
Without you?
I didn't mean to spoil your holiday
Don't say that
I didn't see you just now...
I thought you didn't want to see me
Silly
Rest up
No!
I'm afraid I won't see you again
Where's Dr. Lai?
He just gone!
Stop!
Dr. Lai...
I don't care how dangerous it is.
I have to try
Calm down
the experiment hasn't been proven
If things go wrong, you may die
I don't care. I've lost two good friends
I don't want to lose Lek
Please, I beg you!
Isn't Lek your good friend too?
Don't you want to help him?
Don't give up!
Dr. Lai, please
If anything happens to him
I'll feel responsible forever
Please...
Welcome home!
Thank you...
Let me help you!
- Chang, hammer.
- What?
Help! It hurts...
Be careful!
Your toes moved!
There is sensation!
Really?
Can you feel it?
His foot has sensation!
That's great, man!
Look
Really!
1 ` 2 ` 3 ` 4 ` 5
6 ~ 7 ~ 8...
I want to dance!
Me too!
Ching
Where's Ching?
I haven't seen her
I've looked at the reports.
Something went wrong
How do you feel?
Older
Not only in appearance
my reflex is slower
Will I die soon?
I'm not sure
I'm sorry
Don't worry. I don't regret it
I don't blame you
- What about Lek?
- Don't tell him
I don't want him to know
I don't want him to be upset
Ching!
Ching...
Ching, where are you?
- Where are you?
- Ching...
Have you seen her?
No
Thanks
I swim here every morning!
No one came out
Ching's clothes!
Lek! Lek... Ching...
Lek! Come back... Ching...
Lek! Come back! Let me go!
Ching... Lek! No...
Ching! Ching...
Hey, Ching?
Dr. Lai, how does it look?
Please be calm, it doesn't look good
You should prepare yourself
Ching... Ching?
I'm here
How is Lek?
He's very depressed
Why don't you just tell him!
I'd rather he forget me...
He's given up and just stays in
his wheelchair
Why?
You know why
I don't want to force you. You decide!
I'm Ching's older sister
I'm coming to Koh Samui...
Honey, what are you writing?
Let me see, come on!
Ching...
Long time no see. You've grown older!
She is not Ching!
She looks... She is not?
I'm sorry
You are...
I'm Ching's sister, Sim Wai
Did you get my e-mail?
How are you? I'm Lek
I'm sorry, we tried our best
We couldn't find her
Don't worry, she's okay
She asked me to pick up her stuff
Really? That's good!
Come and sit down
- Have a seat.
- Thanks
It's typical of my sister
Disappearing suddenly
It's not the first time
Really? She didn't look the type!
What did I do wrong?
I don't know
Maybe she met another guy...
Or went somewhere else!
Typical
My husband recognizes you
I came back...
...to prepare for death
Don't say that!
Actually, we're in the same boat
The doctor said I only have a few months left
But it doesn't matter
I've had a rewarding life
Seize the day and enjoy the rest of
your life!
Follow your desires!
Will you keep my secret?
On one condition
If I go first, you take care of Mr. Bond
Vice versa
If I go first, you take care of Lek
Deal!
These two men...
...are so lucky to have us
Give me some more time!
No way!
We have some more customers coming!
A little more time!
No customers, no money!
Bullshit!
Take all the liquor!
Where is Lek?
He said to let them take whatever
they want
What's the problem?
Nothing... minor problem
It won't affect you!
They took everything and
it won't affect us?
Tell him I've bought the resort
I'll pay the debts
Say it or else they won't leave
You want to make a bigger scene?
He doesn't care
When will he get the money?
I'll get the cash next week
Cash!
Thinking about my sister?
You two look alike
She's prettier
Ching said you could stand...
Why stay in the wheelchair?
She mentioned me?
She's grateful you made her smile
I know you miss her
But you can't give up
Do you want the place close down?
I feel responsible
Nothing... I mean...
I didn't teach her well
Our parents died early and left us
big money...
I didn't teach her right
I want to help you because you were
good to my sister
If you have financial problems...
I can handle it
Do you know where she is?
Forget her!
Even if she was here...
...she wouldn't want to see
a miserable man
They all care about you
You have to cheer up and smile again
How could you be like this?
Lifeless, humorless
From now on, everything goes back to
the way it was
Come on, let's start
What?
She is right. We can't act like this!
Come on, let's get moving!
She is Ching
No, she is not
No? Yes!
Whatever you say...
Be careful!
There are lots of hawkers
The food here is great
Have you been here?
Yes, ages ago
No way! It just opened!
- Really?
- Really!
I love grilled chicken!
How much?
40 Baht
Don't go too close. It'll pop
Hello
- How much?
- 10 Baht... 10 Baht...
So expensive!
Have you ever seen such a bouncy
old woman?
Yes, you!
She's young at heart
She's an old temptress!
We can print the "Coconut Villa" logo
on the souvenirs...
...like T-Shirts, caps
We can sell some arts and crafts here too
We need to renovate here
Can we take out the windows?
Why?
The place will be bigger and cooler!
Cooler? I like it!
The words have to be painted again
You're responsible for the local tour
and water sports
You should think of some new attractions
Sim, this is a place to rest
The customers like the peace here
That's why they return every year
How long are you staying anyway?
You want to retire here?
It is a great place for retirement
But a better place for dying
Excuse her, she doesn't mean it
Isn't it better with the lights on?
Come on, let's clean up
Watch out!
Are you alright?
I'm fine...
Are you okay, Lek?
Are you alright?
I'm fine...
Are you hurt?
You can walk. You just don't want to
I can't
Try it, you can
Come on
Hold me
Nice and easy...
Keep going
I can't...
It's alright
Hold onto me
You can do it
Come on
Again
Thanks
What are you doing?
Slut!
I think that old woman likes Lek
No way!
What do you know? I'm a woman
I can tell right away
She melts when she sees Lek
Lek was with her sister
How can she do that?
Mr. And Mrs. Bond
you guys are elders...
What do you think?
Yes!
It's their business, not yours!
Nosy people!
He's getting old
But he is right
What does it have to do with you?
Talking to the sea again?
No, it doesn't talk back
Why not talk to me?
I talk back
They are too harsh on Sim
Because they care about you
What do you think of her then?
A nice person
Do you like her?
I don't...
That's fine
Don't fall in love with her...
...just because she looks like Ching
They aren't the same person
Don't worry. I understand
Good for you
Whatever you do, just be clear what it is
Mr. Bond, are you reading someone
else's letter?
Ching, Come on. Let's read it
I'm not Ching!
You can't fool me!
You think I'm that silly?
Don't! Drink from mine!
What's written in there?
Secrets of the human heart
I have a secret
What is it?
I can't just tell anyone
Don't tell me
I'm bad at keeping secrets
I know
I hope I'll be happy like you
when I get old
To begin happiness when you're old
may be too late, girl!
Do I look like a girl?
How old do I look?
Not old!
I would pursue you if I was 20 years
younger
Really?
Mr. Bond
I really envy you and Mrs. Bond
You remain so good to each other
You can do that too
You see me always making bets?
Don't think I'm swindling people
I just enjoy the experience
Even if I lose, I am still very happy
You think too much, Ching
Relax
If you really like Lek...
...ignore what others think
Do you know who am I?
You think I forgot?
You're Ching's sister, Sim!
Mr. Bond, if I have a secret to confess...
...should I tell my boyfriend?
Sometimes, you have to be honest
Some things you must keep to yourself
Bangkok Bank
Thanks, Sim!
When everything is done.
I'll pay you back
Don't mention it!
Let me give you some shares...
Friends should help each other, right?
Walk with an old woman
Sure
- Not bad.
- Too passe
It looks good!
Try this
Really?
Pretty nice, try it
It looks good
Let's go up and see
Wow, let's go up!
Slowly
Alright
My legs are getting stronger
Good. Soon, you won't need crutches!
Let's go up!
Are you tired?
Enough
Not good
How old do you think she is?
This one for you
Thanks
- 60
- No way?
Yes!
I don't think so. She must be rich
Rich?
Yes, like a widow
Her boyfriend is cute though.
What a shame!
Do you think he is a gigolo?
That would be cool!
You stupid!
He is on crutches. How can he perform?
A handicapped gigolo is a novelty
What?
You are just jealous of the rich folks
Not even
I would hire a normal one!
Let's go!
She's awake
Are you alright?
Lek, get the nurse for me
I'll take a look at your friend
Alright
Take it easy
You're sure you don't want to tell?
I'm sure
I want to leave him a good memory
of me
Why did you come back then?
I couldn't let him go
Another day with him is one more day
with him
Do you think he will reject you?
I don't want anyone to laugh at him
I look like his mother
He can find a new girl
There was a girl who got 70% of
her skin burnt off
Her boyfriend stayed with her
for an entire month
When she woke up...
...she found her face disfigured
But still
I got a wedding invitation from her
If the bride believed in what you
believe in...
...there would be no wedding at all
I know this is hard for you
But why not give it a try?
Because...
...the bride was not dying
Some women are not meant to have
weddings
What are you going to do?
Lek is the one who needs help
Don't worry, he'll be fine
Thanks
I promise you I'll take care of him
Promise me
do whatever he asks you to do
I'll see you off
No need
Are you going back to Hong Kong?
I don't know
I'll decide when I get to the airport
Lek...
...she won't come back
Don't wait for her. Find another girl!
Take care of the resort
Goodbye
What's wrong?
Something...
Every problem has a solution!
You won't understand
What?
Maybe I can help!
No
You're up to something?
Hi, how's business?
- Can I play?
- Okay
Dr. Lai, are you with Lek?
Yes, haven't you left?
Do you want to speak with him?
No
Please don't hang up
I want to hear his voice
Alright
Everything is over
Nothing matters anymore
The only question is...
...how much time I have left
Thank you all for coming today
We'll have a moment's silence
Mrs. Bond, don't worry
We'll take care of Mr. Bond
My wife?
Yes!
She's asleep
Really? This early?
We haven't had lunch yet!
Some things I don't remember
Yes...
I made a bet with her...
...to see who would die first
She's dead?
I lost
Just as well. If I went first...
...she'd be lonely
It's useless now. Chuck it
It's alright
Now, there's a handsome guy!
Alright, I'm leaving! Bye!
May 25th, 11 o'clock
Lemon Coffee arrives
she does not smile
I knew Sim was Ching right
from the beginning
no one believed me!
Ching saved Lek by doing an experiment
He recovered but she aged rapidly
He changed me
He brought me to the light
from the dark
I never thought I would trade my youth
to save a man
Never thought of the consequences
They say Scorpio women are very selfish
I don't want him to see my face so I left
I missed him, so I came back
I have something to tell Lek
But you have to keep the secret
Sure
You know how forgetful I am
Promise!
Yes!
Lek, I'm Ching
I've been back for a long time
Mr. Bond!
Was Ching really back?
I said it a million times.
No one believed me
Don't bother me!
I believe! I believe!
Are Sim and Ching the same person?
I don't know!
Hey, I'm fishing here!
Tell me where she is now
Where?
If I tell you, will you forget my rent?
I've never asked you for rent!
Why don't I give you my resort?
I don't want it. I have a house
What? Sim takes care of my house
She gave me money too!
Sim is very nice
Your house... Where is it?
On that island
It's very cheap. I've had it for a long time
Ching!
Wait for me!
Ching! Don't go!
Ching... open up! Ching!
You've got the wrong person!
I know everything
Would you open up?
Go! I don't want to see you!
I don't care how others see us
I don't care how much time is left...
...as long as we're together
My recovery is meaningless without you!
You did it for me, I know!
Please let me be with you!
I don't want your sympathy!
I only want to be with you
I don't want you to see me die!
I don't want to!
I'm staying whether you like it or not
What's the point?
You know we have no future!
I don't want you to get hurt!
Don't do this! Please, go!
You already know that?
Whatever you did to Ching
I want you to do it one more time
No! Never!
I wanted to help you
I never thought Ching would...
How can I do it again?
You wanted to save me...
...and make me happy
I can walk now but I am not happy!
The experiment was a failure
It won't succeed in the near future
You can't risk it
My life was almost taken away anyway
But you're okay now
Are you sure I am fully recovered?
And there'll be no side effects?
Dr. Lai, you don't want...
...me to live with regrets, do you?
You have to help me
I want to catch up to her
Ching!
Don't go...
Why did you...