How beautiful
(Yoko and I are alone on this island)
(Does that make us Adam and Eve...)
I knew he'd get there
We're like Adam and Eve, aren't we?
Didn't think he'd actually say it
Actually I've never traveled
I traveled with my parents when small
but I don't remember
When I was 3, I was in a plane crash
That was the last time
Oh, I see
My parents died in that crash
I was the only survivor
(I wonder why I was the only one)
When I learned I was the only survivor
I began to wonder why...
Why it was me... and only me...
I don't believe in God especially
but there's a reason why I'm alive here
And I still think so
What?
(Please... be quiet)
A Transparent
I'm sorry I had to be rough
Come in, Please
But I had no choice
(He won't overhear my thoughts I'm safe)
Excuse me. You are...
Shigefumi Japan's 1st Transparent
30 years ago,
when I was in fear of my abnormality
the government asked me to help create
the Committee and the Protection Act
I thought the 1st Transparent suicide
When I found that I was a Transparent
And I did consider suicide
(How to live with every thought exposed)
But the Committee knew those thoughts
Ironically, because I was a Transparent,
I couldn't even kill myself
And by the time they let me out,
I'd lost the will to do it
So you've been all alone on this island
Life's gotten awfully convenient
I can do things without personal contact
and get most things I need
(I've never given one to someone)
I never intended to meet anyone
Do you know Medusa from Greek?
Everyone sees her turns to stone
Transparents are a kind of Medusa
Whatever they think about another,
good or bad, it's all exposed
Their thoughts freeze everyone near them
No one wants to turn into stone
So someone like me,
has no choice but to live this way
(Thank God I was right)
(Talk to someone... who's with me)
I'm so glad I met you
and talked to you like this
(lt's so lonely being all alone)
I'd better be getting back
Wait, a little...
Yoko san
Go, now!
Shiraki san!
Forget it, just get out of here!
Don't come any closer
What's wrong!
I just touched your skin
The touch and warmth of human skin
It's been so many years since I felt it
I've tried not to think about it
Now that I have, I can't stop myself
(Your... your body...)
(I want your naked...)
Shiraki San
You can hear me,
how I imagine taking you inside my head,
(Breasts... lips... naked)
Even darker emotions...
I can't bear for you to know
Don't listen to my thoughts, get out
Please calm down, I'm a psychiatrist
I understand how you suffer
Just get out! Go!
Stop! Enough!
Yoko san!
You need help
Stay away!
You know nothing!
Your words won't help me
You can't imagine how terrible it is
Nobody can help me
Now you know The Transparent...
is the Medusa
I'm sorry. Please get out of here
Not for your sake, but for mine
...but I'm sure there's a reason
why I'm alive now, I still believe that
Yoko san
Where were you? I was so worried
(I'm so happy she's here)
(Oh, thank God she's back)
What were you doing?
(I woke up and she was gone)
(I was so worried and lonely)
(So all alone)
(So lonely, lonely...)
(Don't go anywhere again)
Yoko san?
(Why's she crying?)
(What happened?)
(Don't cry, please)
(Don't cry...)
Let's leave
What?
On that island, I learned
that I know absolutely nothing
of the overwhelming loneliness
Nor did I understand
why I had held Satomi Kenichi
in my arms or how I should behave
Excuse me...
(Did I do something wrong?)
(I don't get it)
(What happened?)
(Why did she cry?)
(What happened? I don't get it)
Kenichi
(I don't get it)
Kenichi!
What?
What are you dreaming about? Not in love
Give me a break and leave me alone!
Eat it while it's hot
What is this!
I'm sorry
Are you all right? What are you doing?
Dammit, it's hot!
Whatever am I doing?
Messing up my room
I'll do it
No, I'll do it
I will!
Let me do it You'll ruin the tatami mat
Oh, dear me, I made quite a mess
(Was grandma always this tiny?)
Let me do it, grandma
You're getting old, grandma
Just a little tired, that's all
You should have an exam at our hospital
I'll arrange it at the Health Center
There's nothing wrong with me
Just in case
Pancreatic cancer
The permeation is apparent
There's no doubt
Given its size, it's quite advanced
Any family?
Case #7 is her only family
Dr. Satomi...
We can't tell him He's a Transparent
We've told that she got hyperlipidemia
and we're admitting her for tests
I understand
We've to get Dr. Satomi out of hospital,
His grandma may find out what's wrong
The Committee has to make a move
that Transparent into research
What a blessing for us
That's right, yes
Thank you for being good to my grandson
Why, of course
Please continue your kindness
Grandma, what are you doing!
Thanking your colleagues
You don't need to
But I thought I would
OKay, that's enough Go to your room
(She's so embarrassing)
About the island...
I'm sorry
You don't have to apologize
(What happened...)
It's so inconvenient with grandma gone
Yes
can't hospitalize her for cholesterol
(I'm so relieved it's nothing serious)
You've always lived with her
That's why you're so close I'm jealous
Remember you asked me why to be surgeon?
It's before I went to elementary school
One night I got a terrible fever
It hurts, grandma, it hurts
You'll be OK, Kenichi
Kenichi, you'll be OK
Grandma'll take care of you
When grandma saved me that night,
I was just so happy what She did but...
I was so deeply grateful to her
But I didn't know how to tell her
That's why
That's why I decided to be a doctor
to help other people as well
That's the reason why I'm alive here
The Drug Research Lab has requested
you to join their staff the earliest
They want you to leave here
for new Lab job by the end of the month
But I've got to consider grandma
Then let me be frank
Our hospital has financial problems
The Board has ordered us to cut doctors
Surgery has to comply as well
You're eliminating me?
I would definitely cut you from surgery
(That's what you think of me)
Developing new drugs is important,
you'll help many more people
Can I think it over?
I'll report to the Committee
Recently,
I wonder what if I were a Transparent
That way, I'd never have to lie,
never have to hurt anyone
It's not just others who you hurt
Lying to others is not most difficult
They're the ones we tell ourselves
Grandma, the thing is,
I've been invited to the Research Lab
Really?
Researching new drugs is important work
If I succeed, I can help lots of people
I'm more suited to that work
Why that's wonderful
You should work hard
If you want to go,
you should do what you want
Oh, dear, I'm quite tired today
I'll lie down
Have a good rest
(Grandma, I'm sorry)
(I couldn't become a doctor)
Thank God, he will go to research lab
We'll be free of all his thoughts
Finally, it's back to business as usual
Don't tell about his grandma's cancer?
This shouldn't be told to a Transparent
He's leaving for the Research Lab today
Soon, they'll operate on Satomi Kiyo
This is the Committee's best plan
You've completed your mission as well
It's over, over
Finally, it's all settled
We should've sent him to the Lab earlier
Exactly
Please wait!
Given Case #7's psychological state,
you should postpone his transfer to Lab
What are you saying?
The transfer's cleared the Ministry
It's too late to change now
Taking him away from Kiyo
isn't necessarily the best idea
Let him stay until the operation finish
Don't consider the Transparent's wishes?
If he insists on staying as a doctor
We shouldn't ruin his dream of surgeon
A Transparent's still a Transparent
Transparents are humans, too
Even when they make the wrong choices,
they have the right to explore
Let him stay longer
Please
Unfortunately, that's impossible
Why is that?
As long as Case #7 is a Transparent,
we need to protect him
It's our duty
and it's the interests of his happiness
Trapping him in a cage is happiness?
OK, thank you
Dr. Azuma
Yes?
I'm very sick, aren't I?
We'll heal you over time
Can't you let my boy operate on me?
That's...
Maybe it's just family prejudice,
but he's worked so hard all these years
night after night,
chained to his desk...
All he wants is to become a doctor
who can help people
But...
I can't bear the thought of his
Hard work and devotion going to waste
But it's impossible
I'm sorry
I guess I shouldn't have brought it up
Thanks for everything
Work hard over there
Where's Dr. Satomi?
He just left for the Lab
Wait!
Kenichi
Stop, you have to follow our orders!
Don't worry, grandma'll look after you
You'll be fine
What happened?
Are you sure this is what you want?
I want? What?
Are you happy leaving this for the Lab?
Yeah, I'll be better at research anyway
(I can't be a surgeon)
Your grandma inspired you by saving you
Isn't it your turn to save her?
That's impossible I will join the Lab
(Why are you saying this?)
You're lying, Satomi
It's not like you to lie
I'm not lying
(Don't confuse me anymore Stop it)
Your grandmother has pancreatic cancer
What?
(Impossible... The test results...)
People at the hospital hide it from you
But why...
(Because I'm a failure as a doctor)
No, that's not...
This is not your fault
You should know what you have to do
Why are you alive here and now?
(The reason I'm alive here
Case #7 is heading back surveillance
Dr. Azuma
What, leave something behind?
Please let me treat my grandmother
What's this? You're no longer part...
So you know about her illness
Yes
(Pancreatic cancer... And terminal)
And you still want to treat her?
Yes
(I'll save her life... i will)
(Grandma... I swear I will)
(I swear)
(I become a doctor because of you)
Please let me operate
Do you know why I never let you operate
No
Because you're far better than I am
I was jealous
I didn't want to admit it,
so I lied to myself
You'll still have to leave the hospital
It'll be your first and last operation
I'll make up your lack of experience
It'll be tough, but go ahead
Yes, thank you
Dr. Mita
We've assigned a new surgeon
Yes Hurry, Dr. Mita
I understand
Wrong chart, Dr.
Is this Anesthesiology?
The surgery's assigned to other doctor
That's right, it's Dr. Satomi
It's just a little lump in your stomach
It's a simple procedure to remove it
(It's cancer...)
When it's gone, you'll live many years
I guarantee that
(Pancreatic cancer)
What's wrong, grandma?
You're so grown up
You were just a little boy
Thank you, doctor
(Sure)
(I swear I'll save your life)
Hurry
Back-up Team's here
We're scheduled for 13:00
No idea how forceful is his thoughts
We'll make security around 100m radius
Got that?
Yes!
(Once I open, I check primary lesion,)
(check hepatic metastasis)
(Mobilize the duodenum)
(Separate pancreas from peritoneum)
(After cutting away the stomach,)
(Separate the pancreas at the SMV
(Tape the hepatic artery, portal vein)
(and excise the stomach)
Sir
Why is Case #7 in the operating room!
Please, just be quiet and observe
I'm ready to begin Anesthesiology
Please
Scalpel
(You can make it, grandma)
Here we go, everyone
No obvious hepatic eventration
Right
The primary carcinoma's severe
Yes
(Grandma, I'll get it all out of you)
(Steady now)
(I shouldn't damage the portal vein)
(I've removed the pancreas)
(but the connective tissue inflamed,)
(and it's hemorrhaging Stay calm, now)
(Carefully suture one area at a time)
(Damn, there's permeation of nerves)
(I have to cut the advential tissue)
(Hang in, grandma It won't be long)
Stable now
(I just have to remove the jejunum)
Specimen
Specimen, please confirm
(Hang in there, grandma)
The carcinoma's out Now,
Amazing
What's going on?
His first surgery is so precise
Dr. Azuma
Can you take a look?
What?
Here Metastasization to the peritoneum
What happened?
What's wrong?
(It's too late...)
(we cut now, it'll recur)
It's really too bad
Yes
I'll repair and suture
30 Proline
(Grandma, I'm sewing you up)
(I'm sorry, grandma)
(I was so near you, but I never...)
(I never noticed you were sick)
(Grandma)
(I'm so sorry I cut you open)
(Cut you so badly)
(I'm so sorry, grandma)
(Grandma)
(I never even noticed)
Operation complete
Resume routine protective surveillance
(We lived together all that time)
(Why didn't I notice before it's late)
(I'm so sorry, grandma)
(It's too late. Too late)
(Forgive me, grandma Forgive me)
There are alternative treatments
It's your duty as physician to see her
What should I do?
Tell her what you have to
Yes
It's done, grandma
We got that lump out of you,
so you'll be fine
I see
I'm glad
You were great
Thank you, Kenichi
I have to go now
You're all grown up
(I couldn't save you... Grandma)
(Don't thank me...)
(Grandma...)
(Don't thank me)
(I was right there)
(But I couldn't help you)
(Forgive me, grandma)
(I couldn't do...)
(A thing for you)
(Forgive me, grandma)
(Why didn't I notice before it's late)
(I'm so sorry, grandma)
(Forgive me)
(Grandma...)
Dr. Azuma
How did my grandson do?
I've never met a more skillful surgeon
Oh, good
Now I have no regrets...
Don't say that, Satomi san
There are many other treatments
I'm in your hands
We'll lick this thing together
Thank you for everything
For the next 6 months,
Kenichi acts as his grandma's physician
He oversaw many treatments
He was always by her side
You could say that Kenichi failed
to save his grandmother's life
But his surgery had consequences
none of us could have dreamed of
Unfortunately, you have a tumor
It's malignant, but at an early stage
We consider it operable
Excuse me... Um...
Yes, what is it?
Can I request Dr. Satomi to operate?
He's a Transparent. Do you get it?
Yes... But,
I want Kenichi to operate on me
Well, he's... certainly a fine surgeon
You have to fill out consent forms
That's the 26th request this month
I won't send him to the Lab for awhile
And the Ministry of Health?
I'll explain and offer an apology
The Cabinet Secretary's furious with me
That man keeps increasing my workload
What?
The 1st time you refer Case #7 as a man
Did I... say that?
There's more to the myth about Medusa
When the hero Perseus slays Medusa,
Pegasus is born of her blood
Good morning
Thank you
How wonderful
Your patient, Dr. Mita
Right
In the modern age, as words proliferate
it is difficult to know people's hearts
And many people suffer because of this
Maybe the modern age needs Transparents
Is Dr. Satomi in?
May I help you?
Not you, again!
I just want him to examine me
If we all accept Transparents as normal
perhaps we'll have ushered in a new age
As Pegasus born from Medusa's blood,
spread his wings across endless skies
So I have come to believe
We're almost there, grandma
Don't worry
Everybody knows you're a wonderful boy
What are you talking about?
(What are you talking about?)
Look, grandma It's so beautiful
Grandma Grandma