(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Is anyone seeing this?
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(GARAGE DOOR OPENING)
(CROWD CHATTERING)
(JACKHAMMERING)
Hay.
It's all rlght.
Calm down, okay?
Samantha?
(Y ELLING) Are you
out of your mlnd?
(noon OPENS)
(noon CLOSES)
SAMANTHA: Not a word.
You dldn't aay one word
about thla to ma.
Don't you thlnk
you owe me that?
that you mlght
raapaot me enough
to at laaat oonaldar
what I'd have to aay?
I dldn't want you
worrylng about It.
Well, I'm worried, Curtis.
How are you paylng
for all that?
I got a home improvement loan
from the bank.
(VOICE SHAKING) How could you
do that without talking to me?
You knowthe expenses
we have coming up.
You want to waste money
on a stupid tornado shelter?
I'm doing It...
I'm doing It for us.
I know
you don't undaratand.
(YELLING) You're right.
I don't understand.
I don't
undaratand half the atuff
you've been doing lataly.
(SNIFFLING)
I don't understand you
putting Red out back.
I don't understand
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
you ataylng up all night
In that atupld
tornado ahaltar.
You don't come to
bad half the time.
You leave,
you don't tall ma
where you're going.
Explain that to ma.
Plaaaa.
Tall ma aomothlng
that helps me understand
why you're being like this.
There's nothing
to explain.
I'm gonna go
put Hannah to bad.
(sesame)
(WATER RUNNING)
(CURTIS GASPS SUDDENLY)
(CURTIS CRIES OUT)
Curtla?
(GASPING)
Baby. Oh, my God.
Baby...
(momma)
Oh, my God.
(VOICE SHAKING) Baby.
(DIALING)
(momma)
(STAMMERING) I need
an ambulance!
My huaband'a
having a seizure.
41800 Tlndala Road.
(SOBBING) Hurry up.
He's blaadlngl
(GURGLING)
(SOBBING) Okay.
(GASPS)
(SOBBING) Honay?
Honay?
Honey? Are you okay?
You were having a seizure.
I called an ambulance.
(GRUNTS)
No. It's fine. It's fine.
Don't send an ambulance.
What are you doing?
It's ﬁne.
DISPATCHER: (FAINTLY) Ma'am?
Baby, what's going on?
(PANTING)
I'm sorry
you fallowa had to
coma all the way out.
It's what we do.
Now we can atlll
take you In
If you want a doctor
to look at those cuta
In your mouth.
Yeah, that's all right.
I'll see somebody on Monday.
All right.
Thanks.
(SNIFFLING)
(DOOR OPENS)
I haven't been honest
with you.
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
I've been
having those dreams.
I guess they're
more like nlghtmaraa.
It's why I've been
acting like this.
Thay, urn...
Thay alwaya atart
with a kind of atorrn.
lea a real
powerful atorrn.
And there's always this, uh...
This dark, thlck raln.
lea fresh motor oil.
And than
tha thlnga,
paopla, It )uat
makaa tharn crazy.
Thay attack ma.
Somatlmaa...
Somatlmaa thay
go aftar Hannah.
Flrat cm I had,
Rad naarly
chawad through my arm.
That's why you
put him out back?
Yaah.
What was tha draam?
Tonlght.
It was Dawart.
We were at the job site.
The storm started
and something happened.
Hla faca...
Hla ayaa wara
dlffarant.
Ha aama aftar ma
with a plckax.
And wa fought.
And ha ran It
through my lag.
(STUTTERING)
It's hard to axplaln,
baaauaa It's not
)uat a draam.
It's a faallng.
I'm afraid
aomathlng
mlght ba coming.
Somathlng that'a
not right.
I cannot daacrlba It.
I )uat naad you
to ballava ma.
l'va baan
to a counaalor.
l'va aaan har...
l'va aaan har
a law tlmaa.
You know
what I coma from.
And I promised myself...
I promlaad myaalf
lwould navar laava.
And I am doing
avarythlng that I can
to maka that trua.
Okay, since the doctor's
approved her surgery,
wa )uat naad to
gat har achadulad.
The next possible opening
is the 21st of next month.
That'a alx waaka.
Slx waaka?
la that okay?
lt'a wondarful.
...thla polnt
)uat to tha waat.
I don't think
wa'll hava any problam.
We should be able to get 20,
maybe 30 in this next week.
But wa'ra looking to
aaa how that's gonna
ahapa up, so...
Curtla?
Yaah.
What do you think?
Yeah. That sounds good.
Wa'll gat It dona.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Coma In.
What you need, Curtis?
I naad a favor, Jlm.
What's that?
Can you taka Dawart
off my craw?
Juat raaaalgn hlm
aomaplaca alaa.
What's the trouble?
He not pulling his weight?
No, nothlng Ilka that.
Ha'a a good workar.
Ha'a a good man.
Ha'a my frland.
I think It'd ba aaalar
not being in charge of
someone I'm so close to.
You know, I understand.
Thla la part of
what It maana to
managa paopla, Curtla.
You'ra gonna
hava to laarn that.
Yaa, air.
I appraclata that, but...
Well, it would just be
very helpful in this case.
Okay.
Wall, I can
put him with Ruaaall.
Anybody alaa
you'd prafar?
No. Whoavar
you thlnk'a rlght.
Okay. Okay.
Thank you.
You baan missing
a lot of work, Curtla.
I know. My daughter's had
a lot of doctor's visits.
I havan't lat
anything gat bahlnd.
No. But don't. Okay?
Yaa, alr.
SAMANTHA: I know
thayjuat usually do
oyatara and frlaa,
but what If wa dld
aomathlng haalthlar
on tha alda?
What, Ilka 'alaw?
I don't know.
Mayba a vagatabla or aalad.
Dewart's been telling me
how strange Curtis
has been acting lately.
I am so sorry.
It's not Ilka
you don't hava anough
on your plata
with Hannah.
Thlnga ara ﬂna.
Can I halp you?
Yaah.
Can I look at cm
of thaaa gas masks?
Which ona you want
to look at?
Tha nawaat ona.
How much?
$118.
Anything chaapar?
No. That's the cheapest
one I got in the store.
Thay go
all tha way up to $290.
I don't know what
you want to apand,
but a gas mask
aln't aomathlng you
want to go chaap on.
You got any kids' sizes?
Kids can't wearthose.
Thay gotta hava
a apaclal thing,
It's Ilka a hood.
I don't fool with those.
What tha hall
ara you doing?
What you got
going on hara?
I'm Juat adding on
to tha atorm ahaltar.
Why?
Juat baaauaa.
You running waterto it?
Oh, yaah.
From our wall.
Running aawar out
to tha clty llna.
How much you apandlng
on this thing?
It's not bad.
Doaan't look It.
You taka your aya
off tha ball ona mlnuta
In this aconomy
and you'ra acrawad.
You got tha cash
for this?
Yaah.
Don't put nothing
on cradlt aarda.
That ahlt'll aat you up.
I'm not.
Samantha aallad ma.
Callad you to
coma tall ma to quit?
Sha aallad
'aauaa aha'a worrlad.
Saya you'va
baan atraaaad out.
So?
So what?
You atraaaad out?
No. No mora
than anybody alaa.
Work all right?
Hay, look.
You wanna coma by
and hava dlnnar
aomatlma, Kyla?
That'a ﬂna.
We'll have a beer and
talk about the old days,
but you got aomathlng
to say, Juat say It.
You can atop
that shit right now.
I'll coma ovar thara
and ramlnd you
what It's Ilka to
gat your an whlppad.
I'm Juat coming hara
to chack on you.
Wall,
I appraclata It, Kyla.
You been to see Mom?
Yaah.
A faw daya ago.
Sha all right?
You should aaa har.
Taka your girls.
Yaah. Yaah,
I'll gat around to It.
You naad a hand?
No. l'va got It.
Okay.
Call ma If
you naad ma, okay?
Oh, hay, Kyla?
Actually,
you could do ma a favor.
What's that?
You atlll looking
for a dog?
They got a good spot
foryou, okay, buddy?
You aura?
Yaah.
I know It'll
maka my girls happy.
All right.
Hay, Kyla?
Yaah?
(CHUCKLING) Okay.
Take care of yourself.
All right. All right.
I will, llttla brothar.
You taka aara
of your family.
Handla your bualnaaa.
Okay?
(EXHALES)
All right. Badtlma.
(RAIN PATTERING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(WATER DRIPPING)
(FLY BUZZING)
You okay?
(GASPS)
(HANNAH CALLING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Who's that?
Oh, shit.
Hay, Jlm.
Curtla.
Dawart told ma
you took aqulpmant
from work
for a projact
at your houaa.
Sald that's why
you wantad him
off your craw.
I aama out hara
to aaa It myaalf.
Yaah. It was Juat
a haular and a backhoa.
It was Saturday.
I had tharn back In
laaa than alght houra.
You know
that doaan't mattar.
I can't even tell you
how many rules you broke.
What If you had
an accldant? Huh?
What If you
ran aomabody ovar
on your way out hara?
Lawault Ilka that
could bankrupt ma.
I'm sorry, Jim.
I hadn't thought of that.
Thank God nothlng
Ilka that happanad,
you know?
You can pick up
your last chack
on Friday.
You'va got
two waaka' banaﬂta.
Did you fire Dewart, too?
Ha'a on two waaka
laava, unpald.
I'm sorry, Curtla.
You did this
to youraalf.
l'va baan ﬂrad.
What about
tha haalth lnauranca?
We get two more weeks.
I'm sorry.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Oh. Excuaa ma.
Ara you Curtla?
Yaah.
Coma In.
Kandra tranafarrad out.
I'll ba maatlng
with you today.
Plaaaa, alt down.
What happanad
to Kandra?
Sha got Into
a program at OSU,
ao aha'll ba
tranafarrlng naar thara.
I've split her caseload
with another counselor.
lt'a baan kind of
crazy around hara lataly.
l'va lookad ovar
your ﬂla.
It says your mother
was diagnosed with
paranoid schizophrenia
In har aarly 30a.
Lat'a atart thara.
(EXHALES)
(WHIRRING)
(WIND BLOWING)
(CLANKING)
I'm so sorry.
I complataly forgot.
That's okay.
Don't worry about It.
Thanka.
Hara. I hopa
you Ilka tharn.
I brought aaah.
That'a tarrlﬂc.
lt'a ﬂna.
Call ma
If thay don't work
and I'm sorry agaln.
Oh, It's okay.
Thank you.
Okay. All done. Done.
Swaat draama.
What's that?
That'a tha altarnator
from tha truck.
I was Juat trying
to ﬂgura out a way
to charga anough battarlaa
to run llghta
down thara.
Yaah, what tha hall.
Mayba I'll hook It up
to your old Exarcycla.
You gonna leave me?
You ﬂlnchad whan
I touchad your hand
this morning.
I'm sorry.
lwaa In cm of
your draama?
Yaah.
Can you daal
with that?
Yaah.
Okay.
Than I mada a daclalon.
Wa aancal
tha baach trlp.
Wa hava anough
to covar bllla
forthe next two months
with your last check.
I'm going to get ajob.
You'ra gonna
ﬁnd anotharjob.
I'm going to call
to aaa If wa can mova
Hannah's surgery up.
Wa'll naad to aaa
what It coata
to extend your policy
to the end ofthe year.
I want you to
aaa a paychlatrlat.
Not a counaalor
from tha fraa cllnlc.
Dr. Shannan gave me
the number of somebody,
but I Juat don't
think wa can afford It.
We'll find the money.
Also, the Lions Club
supper's this weekend.
I want you to
coma with ma.
I don't want to aaa
any of thoaa paopla.
I want you to go.
I naad to do
aomathlng normal.
All right.
(ALL CHATTERING)
How many placaa
doaa Hannah gat?
SAMANTHA: Just one.
(HANNAH GIGGLING)
What're you doing here?
Not hara, man.
I said, what ara
you doing hara?
Curtla?
l'va told paopla
what you'va baan dolng.
You cut ma looaa.
Evarythlng
wa baan through.
I know. I'm sorry.
CURTIS: Hay, hay.
You ain't fucking aorry.
All right.
You sorry,
you wouldn't
cut ma looaa.
We're fucking friends!
This how you treat friends?
Coma on. (GROANS)
God damn It.
Stop It, Dawartl
(GROANS) Fuckl
(YELLING) I said not here!
God damn ltl
You think
I'm crazy? Huh?
la that what
ha told you?
Wall, llatan upl
There is a storm coming
Ilka nothing
you hava avar aaanl
And not a cm of you
la praparad for It!
You think I'm crazy?
Hay, I'm talking
to you, Ruaaalll Huh?
Lawlal
You think I'm a thlaf?
Slaap wall
In your bada.
Baaauaa If
this thing comaa trua,
thara ain't gonna
ba any mora.
(SOBBING)
(LEAVES RUSTLING SOFTLY)
(GRUNTING)
Hannah?
(FAINT SCREECHING)
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(BIRDS SCREECHING)
(SIREN WAILING)
(BIRDS FALLING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(SIREN WAILING)
Curtla?
Waka upl Waka upl
(STORN RAGING)
(SIREN CONTINUES WAILING)
(DOOR cLOSES)
Coma on.
It's okay.
(SAMANTHA BREATHING HEAVILY)
Saa?
All right. Coma on.
Sit down.
All right.
Okay. honey.
hara you go.
No. Don't do that.
It's okay.
lt'a oxygan.
Hara. Put this on.
Ara you kidding?
Plaaaa, Juat do It.
0W
Thara wa go.
All right.
Kaap It out of
your ayaa. Okay?
Hay. I lova you.
It's okay.
All right?
All right. Okay.
(THUDDING)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(SIGHS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(SOFTLY) Wake up, babe.
Whara'a your maak?
Wa took tharn off.
It's ﬂna.
No.
Taka It off.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
You naad to
opan tha door now.
(MUFFLED) What if it's...
What If It's not ovar?
What?
lt'a ovar.
Gat tha kaya.
Opan tha door.
(GRUNTING)
(BREATHING)
lt'a atlll atormlng.
No. It's not.
In haar It.
(WHISPERING) I don't
haar anything.
Put your hand on the door.
You can feel it.
Thundar?
Do you faal It?
You faal It?
(CURTIS PANTING NERVOUSLY)
I'm sorry.
Baby, thara'a
no atorm outalda.
I'm sorry.
Curtla,
I wouldn't Ila to you.
We love you very much.
Plaaaa
opan tha door.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
I lova you,
but If I opan tha door,
than nothlng'a
gonna changa.
You'll aaa that
avarythlng'a ﬂna,
but nothing will change.
Plaaaa.
Thla la what It maana
to atay with us.
Thla la aomathlng
you hava to do.
(EXHALES)
Could you mova
Hannah back?
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
(GROANS SOFTLY)
lt'a ﬂna.
MAN: Do you hava
any vacation tlma
that you can uaa?
I don't hava ajob
right now.
Wall, I know
that tlmaa ara hard,
but I think It's
raally Important for you
to aaparata youraalf
from that storm shelter.
I think you naad to
braak away from It
for a whlla.
Wa can atart you
on aoma madlcatlon
that I think will halp,
but that action alona
would man a lot.
We usually go on a trip
to Myrtle Beach each summer.
Wa wara gonna
go this month.
I think
that would ba okay
If wa atart
tha madlcatlon now.
And It would glva
you all aoma tlma
to prapara aa a family.
But I want to be clear,
whan Curtla gata back,
ha'll naad to taka
mora tlma than that.
What does that mean?
I man that ha'll naad
handa-on tharapy
at a raal faclllty.
You man I hava
to laava my family?
I think you naad to
aarloualy commit
to aoma traatmant.
(CAWING)
Hay...
Good, huh?
Okay.
(ExcLAINS IN JOY)
Thara wa go.
Lat'a maka a rlvar.
Good. Yaah.
Wa put a top on It.
What la It, honay?
What?
(THUNDER CRASHING)
Okay.
(SHELTER PLAYING)
J‘ Soc thoaa atom clouda
rolling In
J‘ Juat Ilka I know
It would bagln
J‘ lfldnlght aIry
at noon today
J‘ Shaltar'a atlll
ao far away
J‘Oh
J‘ And I don't know
juat what we'll do
J‘ I don't know
juat where we'll go
J‘ All I know Ia
we've got to mova
to keep you cloaa
J‘ Cloaa
J‘ Never been
Ilka thla bafora
J‘ Storm at your paler horse
J‘ Water'a red,
the aky Ia black
J‘ Take In y hand,
now don't look back
J‘Oh
J‘ I don't know
juat what we'll do
juat where we'll go
J‘ All I know la
we've got to move
to keep you cloae
J‘ Cloae
J‘ All I know la
to keep you cloae
J‘ Cloae
J‘ I don't know
juat what we'll do
juat where we'll go
J‘ All I know la
we've got to move
to keep you cloae
J‘ CloaeJ‘