Shizuoka, 1977
What's the situation?
The plane's damaged, no idea of survivor
3 hours after the crash, hard to survive
That's the worst scenario if all dead
(Help)
You hear that?
Yes, I heard it too. A child's voice
(Mommy, Daddy)
(Help me...)
(lt's so heavy, please move it away)
Here he is!
He's alive!
Headquarters, we've located one survivor
Send a rescue helicopter immediately!
You heard him screaming?
(Where's Mommy? Where's Daddy?)
(It's time to go home now)
That's not his voice
What...
That's his thoughts reaching our brains
Impossible
We have an emergency
Report to the General immediately
Discovered one Transparent at crash site
Found a Transparent, request protection
A stretcher! Now!
National Defense Agency, Tokyo, 2000
Eastern Regional Battalion, #1 Division
Captain First Class, Komatsu Yoko
You report to the Protection Committee
Prime Minister's Office, Tokyo, 2000
I'm Komatsu Yoko of #1 Support Regiment
#1 Division, Eastern Battalion
Welcome
I'm Kunimitsu, Chief of Escort Division
What about this female soldier
Awfully dainty
Has she got what it takes?
After Military Medical Institute,
She's been a staff psychiatrist
Yes, I'm making a clinical study of PTSD
for disorder, and counseling soldiers
Excellent
You should be familiar with Transparent?
Bulesis Transmission Disorder
Inner thoughts expose to nearby peopl
Unfortunately, I've never met one
It is the mission of this Committee...
to protect and supervise Transparents
For years, being supported by government
We have promotion for Transparent
To enhance the public acceptance
Transparent's thoughts can reach 10m far
If you suddenly get another's thoughts
Don't panic, but react normally instead
Transparents are invaluable resources
don't reveal this knowledge to them
From the Specially Gifted Committee
Transparents never know their condition
Yes. When a Transparent discovers it
The psychological stress has sometimes...
...led to suicide. I know a case
Our first Transparent
A most unfortunate incident
Now, there are 7 Transparents in Japan
And their I.Q. are above 180
Look at this
#5, a genius on environment engineering
analyzed carbon dioxide with silicon
Reducing 5% in CO2 emissions mandated by
International Global Warming Guidelines
This increased our domestic GNP by 23%
Case #1, a genius on Quantum Physics
Case #4 proved the Hertz Moeler Theorem
Case #3 designed our 1st space station
All Transparents have great contribution
Some of them may seem of dubious value,
But Transparents are valuable resources
This is why our mission to protect...
and supervise Transparents
Transparents have been assigned to towns
Transparents live like average citizens
That's your new posting Where Case #7,
The 7th Transparent resides
We'll look forward to your reports
Yes
Case #7. His name is Satomi Kenichi
Born in 1973, he lost both his parents
In an airplane crash when he was 3
His grandma Satomi Kiyo lived in Okumino
A town for Transparent Protection,
Kiyo was allowed to adopt him
Case #7, his first day of primary school
Kenichi, your lunch
Graduating with top grades in school
Want to be a doctor and took the exam
You may begin
Passing the test with top scores
He passed the Medical Boards 6 yrs later
Now, Kenichi sit here. Got to tell them
After his residency, Case #7 worked
as a young doctor at the Mino hospital
Make him give up medical practice?
Yes
But why?
This drug is for Athlete's foot
What does that...
I've used it personally
It was Case #7, who discovered...
this hit product during medical school
Given more time in a real research,
He might find cures for cancer or AIDS
Actually, he has to
So, Transparents are national resources
Why he quit research and be a doctor?
Under the Transparent Protection Act,
Transparent's wishes shall be respected
Therefore, we let him to become a doctor
We have to make him change his mind
So he can carry on researching new drugs
That's where you come into the picture
In other words, I get close to #7,
In order to discover exactly why
He wants to be a practicing doctor
Precisely
You are psychiatrist. We have confidence
Sir, I'm glad to study a Transparent
We land in Okumino in 5 minutes
What's it like?
No local specialties nor any hot springs
Otherwise, they'd never have volunteered
Volunteer for having a Transparent?
They take in one Transparent to cut tax
Suddenly, their public works are funded
So, this town lives off that Transparent
TRANSPARENT
Thank you for coming. Oh, allow me
Thanks
I'm Homma. Nice to meet you
The Committee told us to help you,
You have new identity as an observer
Amazing hospital
The Committee built it
I see
This is built for Satomi Kenichi
It's a Transparent Public Works project
The medical unit
Good morning
This is Dr. Azuma, our Chief of Surgery
He supervises Satomi Kenichi
Nice to meet you
Dr. Satomi around?
This is Komatsu Yoko
She's here as an observer
Nice to meet you
Observer?
Actually the Committee's new spy
(Damn! I'm late again)
He just passed me. He'll arrive in 10sec
(Oh, shit! I'll never make it!)
At the door
Lobby area ready, Ready to escort
(Why do I turn off my alarm! Stupid)
(Jerk!)
(Jerk, you better watch those corners)
Don't bother!
He'll be here any minute now, sorry
(Shit, it's hopeless I'm totally late)
That was...
Seems he's arrived
What?
(Move! Move! Move, dammit!)
Unbelievable
(I'll get yelled at again)
I'm sorry, I'm late
(Here we go. What a drag...)
Satomi, this is the doctor I told you
Komatsu Yoko, here as an observer
Nice to meet you. I'm Satomi Kenichi
Nice to meet you, too
(Shoot)
(I thought she'd be younger. No chicken)
No chicken...
Oh, sorry, I just...
(What a mess)
(This morning, I have to order CAT scan)
(After that, it's rounds and conference)
(Make an intern do that crap)
His thoughts are crystal clear
I could never have imagined this
It's OK to broadcast that?
Apparently...
Case #7 has knowledge of Transparents
It would be natural to let him know
Because he doesn't know he's Transparent
And you are?
We're Special Police assigned to him
We always disguise as staff and patients
For the Unexpected
The Unexpected?
(Ouch!)
Are you OK?
(How dare you, you idiot!)
(God, how embarrassing...)
(How tacky. That hurts...)
Case #7 is a valuable national resource
Violating the Act is a criminal offense,
Someone might point out he's Transparent
So we have him under 24hour surveillance
So I see
He may be a genius,
But he causes trouble in this hospital
Trouble?
We shall begin Dr. Takemura's rounds
Rounds
How are you?
Fine, thank you
Oh, good. His chart...
(Chart, chart... here)
This patient has swelling in the neck,
Protruding eyeball and weight loss
What is the correct diagnosis? You
Yes... Aggravation of Thyroid function
(But first, you should do a scintigram)
(and check hormone levels in his blood)
But... first I'd do a scintigram,
and check hormone levels in his blood
Good. And an effective treatment?
Isotopic Therapy. Radioiodine
Collects in the thyroid
(lsotopic Therapy can reap benefits)
(with no radiation side-effects)
(Any idiot knows that)
Although it offers short-term benefits
You risk thyroid deterioration
You're Mita, right...
I see you study hard
Who's next?
Hirayama san's waiting for you
Yasuba san, with your good test results,
Doesn't mean you should smoke
(Lung cancer'll kill you)
It's hard to give up...
Listen, this hospital serves good food
Nice nurses. Maybe I'll move in for good
Well, don't overdo it
(Try to trick him with dirty old move)
(Damn I'm hungry What to eat...)
(Today's special is...)
Here he is
I'd like the special
One special coming up
here you are
Thanks for the food
(Lousy...)
Thank you, teacher
Kiyo san, you're so generous
You do not charge for lessons
But my Kenichi is a nuisance for others,
Giving lessons is the least I can do
No, We have life easy because of Kenichi
We can get gas lines and a sewage system
And big tax breaks to boot
No harm in hearing a few pesky voices
Compared to him, my son is a real leech
Might as well have been born Transparent
I mean, Transparents...
Excuse me, sorry to butt in
Why, Town Councilman
I'm sorry I have to be the one, Kiyo san
But your Kenichi's, what d'you call 'em?
Thought Waves!
That's right!
Your neighbors hear them all night long,
I'm so sorry for all the trouble...
The Case #7's thoughts are special
Everyone around him at the hospital
suffers extreme stress by his thoughts
It's obvious that Transparents can only
co-exist with citizens if they cooperate
Case #7's qualifications on surgical...
(Not again...)
(Still no surgery for me What is this?)
Good morning
You've got a gall bladder next week
It's your fifth case since coming here
You're the star of Surgery
(Why don't I get a bladder)
Sorry
(I can handle a gall bladder)
No way, because you're Transparent
Excuse me
Dr. Azuma
I saw the surgery schedule
(I'm better)
And?
You scheduled Dr. Mita for operations
Why can't I operate?
(Of course I'm better than he is)
Doctor
There's reason why you're not fit for it
(What's that?) What's that?
You lack the experience to be a surgeon
Excuse me
Because his thoughts are so transparent?
Not fit to handle really sick patients?
Although there is Informed Consent,
Patient should not hear every detail
Say the patient is a politician
His medical condition might affect a lot
If Transparent doctor leaks it to others
doctor-patient confidentiality is ajoke
I understand
Kenichi isn't suitable for clinical work
(Extraction of a gall bladder is speed)
(The approach I'd...)
(Why won't they let me...)
Good morning
(What does she want?)
How come you want to be a surgeon?
Why...
(Wow, that's Megumi)
(In a mini-skirt She looks so cute...)
Your reaction's abnormal
Sorry
(Girls like presents)
(A present... a pendant... Or a ring?)
(That's it!)
(Act naturally)
Hey, there
Yes
Do you prefer pendants or rings?
What?
I wonder which you'd like for present
No!
(Why not?)
you know... as an aspiring physician,
Wear things might pose risk to patients
So I never, ever, wear rings
Of course
(Of course)
Oops, I have to run to an examination
Excuse me
(She realized the dangers of a ring)
(I never even thought about it)
Who's she?
Kawakami Megumi, an intern here
She's 3 years younger than him
Definitely he's a Transparent
Well, everybody knows that
That's just it Everybody'll know
What if I date him. Not just our talk,
but if we had sex and how many times,
and whether it felt good or...
Just, just calm down now
The next day, all will know my business
I can't stand that even if I love him
Well then, why not just turn him down?
If he says he loves me, I can refuse him
How can I ask Do you love me?
You've got a point...
Please, give me a chance to reject him
Me?
Please
Right now, the biggest concern
Is that Case #7 seems to love Megumi
No Transparent has ever loved a human
Clearly, we must solve it quickly,
Consideration to Megumi's feelings
Under the Transparent Protection Act,
Transparent's thoughts subject others to
stress violates another's privacy,
the situation must quickly be defused
So, we need an immediate solution
I say let the hospital fire him,
and send him to the research facility
The Ministry controls teaching hospitals
The Ministry should cancel his license
There you go passing the buck as usual
You're out of your mind!
I understand
Given our Committee's record,
It's no trouble to break Case #7's heart
Thank you so much
But we'll need... your cooperation
Cooperation?
A date?
Will you mind if we had a date tomorrow?
What a surprise
(Does she have the hots for me?)
No, I will be with Megumi tomorrow
and I thought, the more the merrier!
(Megumi!)
I'm available, definitely!
(Go for it! Excellent!)
(Where? A date, let's see Where to go...)
I, um, hadn't decided...
(Where)
Oh, I see
You have a date? Where?
A festival in the next town?
There's fireworks, and it's tomorrow!
Get me the Cabinet Secretary for meeting
Interrupt him! This is a real emergency!
On the double! Clock's ticking!
The load-in is complete Next, the Team!
Why do we have to dress up this way...
Well, it is a festival
Not exactly my style...
(Damn! I'm late! I'm totally late!)
(Why'd I turn off my alarm!)
Sorry, I'm late Oh, no...
You look great in that
Oh, not at all
(She looks so cute in that)
What about me?
I'm sorry, there's no time
You are bribing us with cheap sake!
I'm sorry, it won't be long
You jerk! Everyone we need your...
(She can't drop a pendant even at work)
(She won't be scolded, it's perfect)
(I hope Megumi'll wear it...)
But, is this OK?
What's OK?
It's so sudden and so far
It is a date. It's just one town away
I heard once,
that Satomi's never go out of Okumino
What?
A Transparent will join you today,
be sure not to speak anything to him
And even if you do overhear his thoughts
If you break rules, you'll be arrested
so you must obey
Roger, report to me
We're doing our best, but something else
What?
Director Kunimitsu hasn't arrived
Why not?
How'd they end up at a festival!
Hey, hurry!
They've made me assistant Scout master...
Hey! That's it! Hurry! Hurry!
Chase it! Get ahead of it!
Get there faster! Hurry! Faster!
(When shall I give her the pendant)
(That's when I just tell her how I feel)
(God, it makes me nervous)
Just passed Point F
Go faster! We're out of time!
We need your cooperation
Faster!
(I've got a good feeling...
(I think today's the right day...)
Just in time
Protection Manual #17. Stage 1 begin
There we are
Hello
(Who's this guy?)
Let me introduce This is Takahashi san,
and we've been...
I'm Takahashi, Megumi's boyfriend
(... for real?)
OK
Stage 2
(What does he means, boyfriend...)
What kind of work do you do?
A friend and I started an IT firm
and it's finally up and running
He's the President
Wow, a real entrepreneur
(Entrepreneur! He's just nouveau riche!)
I heard your father's a lawyer?
Yes, I come from a family of lawyers
They still want him to become one, too
From a good family I'm envious
(Good family. Kind of spoiled rich kid)
(selfish, bratty and full of himself)
OK, now call Children 1 through 3
Children 1 through 3 standing by
5 seconds, 4, 3, 2, 1
Off you go!
No, I hate this color!
What? I said, just go!
Oh, it's Takahashi and his girlfriend
Hey, guys, Way cool
You're popular with kids
I volunteer as an assistant Scout master
So I take them camping and hiking
(So he's popular with kids...)
Assistant Scout master!
Yes, shall we go?
(So kids like him, big deal)
Not just kids Seniors A and B
Seniors A and B, standing by
5 seconds, 4, 3, 2, 1
Oh, Takahashi san
Hello
Thank you for the other day
The pleasure was all mine
I'll give you croquet tips. Come again
Right, stop teasing me...
(Maybe he's a decent guy, after all)
Site 5 passed. We follow the Manual
This is Site 4
Is the drunk on the main path?
Drunk?
Well, damn this Transparent
He ruined all the fun at the festival
Where's this Transparent of yours?
Emergency! Captain Komatsu, you're on!
Check the area! On the double!
I'm on...
Stumble!
Just stumble!
Yes
Dr. Komatsu!
Hey, Transpa...
Are you OK?
Just in time
(ls she nuts?)
Let's go on up
(What's with her?)
That was a close call
Moving onto Site 7. Pick it up at shrine
You gave him the ring?
I checked
Oh, sorry
(I wish I hadn't... come today)
(Me and my lousy luck)
(What am I doing here?)
There you are
Oh, good, I thought we lost you
Is everything OK? You seem a little down
Oh, no...
We're at a festival, let's have fun
(Right, if I'm down...)
(lt's no fun for them either)
The drums and fireworks will start soon
Followed by the dancing You must stay
(I've got to say something...)
Everybody will dance I've never seen it
What fun
(I've got to say something...)
We don't have a good view, let's move up
Sure
#7's watching you, get closer
Nice and romantic, let's go
5 seconds to fireworks,4, 3, 2, 1
(Oh... a ring...)
As a doctor, I never wear anything...
So I never, ever, wear rings
I'm going home
But the dancing...
I've just remembered something, goodbye
Great job
Thank you
Keep communication. Call off the alert
I just came to drop something off
Please
You're with the Committee?
You can tell?
None of his friends or colleagues
have ever come to visit him before, so...
I see
He's a grown man with a child's heart
He's never really dated a woman.
Actually, today he...
Sounds like he was jilted by Kawakami
I heard him
I realized you suffer more than anyone
You're with him 24 hours a day
ut pretend you don't hear a thing
We can't imagine how difficult it is
I'm not pretending
He's just an honest boy
Excuse me
Dr. Komatsu
Give me just a second?
I'm sorry to barge in
No, sorry for the mess
Oh, no
Please
Say...
What is it?
You left this behind
Oh... I'm sorry
For what?
For dragging you along
Were you bored?
Bored? Why no...
Actually
Actually I was in love with Megumi
Oh, I see... I had no idea
So I was thrilled when you invited me
My first real date I was all excited
I wanted to show her my feelings with it
But...
(I'm glad he seems like such a nice guy)
I mean, no use dwelling on it, right?
Besides, I think you're looking good
They just don't know it yet
Someday, you will find someone perfect
No, I... It's OK...
(Nobody ever said that)
(Dr. Komatsu's kind of...)
(Hey, I'm...)
(all nervous)
(I think she's kinda cute)
(Maybe... Maybe I...)
(In love...)
Not again?
Give me a present which is for other?
(Why isn't she wearing it?)
(She accepted. It means she likes me)
(Hey, is she being shy?)
(She's so cute)
Hear those thought waves?
Say, did you hear the latest?
Transparent's got a girlfriend?
Can you believe it?
I've heard, Yoko san You're so brave
Are you crazy! Why should Satomi Kenichi
and I go on vacation together!
Not so loud
What is the Committee thinking?
We must consider our employees' welfare
The Special Police who are covering #7
are exhausted from years of duty
What does that have to do with me?
It's even worse wherever Kenichi is
And so we've devised
solution to kill two-birds-with-a-stone
Here... But why me?
Your profession is...
Psychiatry...
Your specialty?
Research on Transmission Disorder
As a Transparent, Case #7 is also...
...categorized as Transmission Disorder
It's extremely rare
Only 7 cases in the country
What researcher would throw away this
first hand, round-the-clock observation
No one
In that case, here
But that's not the...
I want you to know, this is an order
A deserted island I hadn't thought of it
Bringing him when he's wiped out from
an extended shift is a nice touch
Thank you
The island is 8kms around
There's an old ruin on the north side
No one will overhear his thoughts there
You can relax
If anything should happen...
Anything should happen...
I'm done! I'm going in!
Wait!
(lt's so salty. So this is the ocean)
(Wow! I'm glad to be alive!)
C'mon, let's swim together
Exposing myself at this age takes...
Satomi!
Gotcha!
No fair!
Thanks for the meal
(Lousy)
It's good and spicy
Too spicy?