Sister, what's that sound?
It's coming form up there.
Windy!
Windy, give me your hand
Elder, shouldn't you be
calling me Hsiao-tsing?
Whether I call you Hsiao-tsing or Windy
there's no need to be bashful
I'll never reveal
what happened just now
I was really anxious on your behalf
Actually, I kissed you because
I couldn't control myself
Fortunately you made a quick get-away
Otherwise, if Moon had seen
you undressed and with me...
it would be hard to explain
even if I were Elder Chu Kot
Give me your hand
Moon?!
Moon, what are you doing here?
I was looking for you
Don't bother explaining
Moon!
No! Windy! Give me your hand
We're not fated for each other
I'm betrothed to Lord Ma's son
You're betrothed?
We weren't meant for each other
You should be looking
for Moon, not me
Windy, one at a time
I'm after both of you
Miss Moon, it's getting dark
Give me your hand
Go to my sister instead
I'll go to her next
Quick, give me your hand
Elder, aren't you the playboy!
You can only choose one of us
I'm not going to
compete with my sister
No need to compete
When I finish with you I'll go to her
Elder, there is something
I must tell you
Actually, love is a strange thing
My heart beats wildly
when I look at you
I don't even have the
courage to glance at you
I'm afraid that my heart
would jump right out
I'd be willing to die
if that's what you wanted
As long as I can be with you
forever and ever part
Help!
What's that?
Hurry up! That monster is back
Elder, what happened?
Go inside and search
Yes!
Inside there's a huge creature
I don't know what it is
Be calm! Use the "freeze" incantation
Together: Freeze!
Freeze!
It really works!
It sure does!
We froze it in its tracks
Everybody, jump up there!
The archery machine!
Be careful, Elder!
Moon, go and rescue Elder
I'll lure away that monster
OK
Put out the net
Yes!
Your hand...
Let's retreat from here
See what's going on up ahead
Yes!
Soldiers!
Hu, they're set up an ambush
Windy, Moon?!
It's father!
Lure the soldiers into villa
Use the archery machine
to mow them down!
Yes!
Trying to get away?
The monster destroyed
the archery machine!
We're surrounded by our foes!
Let me out!
Right!... Let Elder go!
Elder, what should we do now?
We'll stay on the sidelines
When the enemy comes in, the monster
will deal with them
Obviously a fake ghost
Unmask it
Let's rescue father!
Yes!
You're hopelessly outnumbered
I'll save you!
Swords are too dangerous!
Let's use our fists
I told you that swords
are too dangerous!
Father
Get out of here
Don't worry about me!
That giant corpse ran over here
Rescue father!
The monster is here!
Abracadabra! Hocus pocus!
Windy! Windy!
Possessed by evil spirits?!
Sister!
What happened to Windy?
She's been possessed
by evil spirits
What should we do?
Still a lot of soldiers around
Better get inside
Don't move!
Press down on her!
Sister!
Think of a way to save my sister
She's possessed by the den
She could turn into a
giant monster at any moment
It's your fault, you traitor!
I'll kill you!
Wait! His troops are still out there
We must keep him as a hostage
She's turning into a corpse monster!
Sister!
We must kill her immediately
Otherwise she'll turn into a monster
You can't kill her!
Are you a good person or evil?
You won't kill Hu, but
you'll kill my sister
Kill Hu!
No matter how many you kill here
you still won't save the kingdom
The emperor is surrounded
by sycophants
and has no idea of the
suffering of his people
Take my head to the emperor
Maybe it will move him
He'll be convinced of
our sincerity and loyalty
Father, if you die we'll
have no one to lead us
Take my head instead
No! Take our heads
Bastards! What good is it
to cut off your heads?
Who are you, ordering people about?!
lam the learned
and brilliant Elder Chu Kot
The learned and
brilliant Elder Chu Kot!
Please guide us
None of you are permitted to die
Please explain!
Explain?!
Your severed heads will
mean nothing to the emperor
You'll have died in vain
Need I explain more?
Stupid pigs!
What about her?
Windy!
To exorcise her, she needs
a dose of "yang" energy
lam not powerful enough
We better do something soon
or it will be too late
What can we do?
Try this magic charm
It may or may not work
Try it
Hurry up and pull Miss Windy down
OK.
I order the evil spirits
to be exorcised
How did this happen?
Really ugly!
I've forced the evil spirit from her
If she gets a quick dose of "yang" energy,
there will be a gleam of hope
Hurry up
Hurry!
I'm a monk. I must not
get too close to women
Don't be afraid of her ugliness
How do we give her "yang" energy?
With your mouth, of course
Mouth?
What then. Your ears?
Send me to her
Abracadabra! Hocus pocus!
Sister!
A real man is afraid of nothing
It's you!
Lord, a golden-robed priest
A golden-robed priest?
Lord!
Put your swords down!
Not enough! More!
Lower your swords!
Put all your swords down!
There are evildoers behind
every country's downfall
Take my head and collect your reward
The way that you look death
calmly in the face
proves that you are loyal
to our country
Even though our political
views are different
I'm still willing to help you
The golden-robed Taoist outside
is the High Priest
The High Priest?
All the rites and
rituals in the palace...
the emperor consults
him for guidance
If he speaks on your behalf
justice will triumph
Father!
Lord Fu, if you trust me
let me go to him
I'll explain the true situation
Father, he might betray you!
He could have killed me
had he wanted to
Still not awake?!
Enough! I'm going to puke
Elder!
Ning!
lam here to pay my
respects to the high priest
Lord Fu is not a traitor
He is a loyal subject, a patriot
I hope that you will uphold justice
There are many who cannot
tell between good and evil
They do not know the hardships
of the imperial court
The purpose of myjourney
is to pacify the people
I'll intercede at court
on behalf of these loyal subjects
Amen! Amen!
Thank you, High Priest!
How are you, Autumn?
Women are very tempting
If I didn't exercise self-control...
my energy would have been dissipated
Hu is treacherous and disrupts
the High Priest's harmony
Please stay here
The convict Lord Fu is here
to see the High Priest
I pay my respect to the High Priest
Amen! Amen!
You have a murderous air about you
Put down your weapons
I've been framed, but I am
concerned about our nation
You are so merciful
Guide the emperor to save the nation
Life is chaotic
Mistakes can always be corrected
In my former life I was evil
sol must do good in this life
Release my soul from purgatory
Evil chanting?!
Don't be tricked!
Sit down!
His mercy is false! Don't be tricked
by his devilish voice!
Abracadabra! Freeze!
I order the evil spirits
to be exorcised!
lam the absolute Buddha
What kind of evil spirit are you!
Even before Buddha you refuse
to reveal your true appearance!
The spirit of evil?!
lam whatl look like!
I don't believe you are Buddha!
Let's go over and see
if you're real or false
Don't
Abracadabra!
Hocus pocus!
Elder!
The bastard Hu betrayed us
I'll take care of things here
Leave quickly!
Abracadabra! Hocus pocus!
The universe revolves
May Buddha be in your heart
I knew he was false, but
couldn't conquer him
I failed!
I can't perform my magic
with you here
I'll open a tunnel in the earth for you
Hurry!
Autumn!
Hurry up!
I can't hold out
Hurry!
Abracadabra! Hurry!
Autumn!
Father!
They've escaped for now but I'll
get them in the end
Guard the three we've captured!
Yes!
What about Lord Fu?
They have admitted their errors
They have departed
People should acknowledge
the immensity of the universe
I just heard a fight going on
Your ears aren't clean!
Vacate your mind to attain
perfect peace of mind
I'm very cold
Hsiao-tsing!
Don't leave me!
Don't be reincarnated so soon
It's too hard to be mortal now
You're so good to Hsiao-tsing
I never realized how
much you missed her!
I never realized
how much you missed her!
Frost fills the sky
over Ten Mile Lake
Silken threads anxious of youth
Looking at the moon and feeling lonely
Envious of lovers, not of immortality
Hsiao-tsing!
Hsiao-tsing, what are you doing here?
Hide! You can't let
the sun shine on you!
If the sun shines on you
your soul will be scattered
You would never be reincarnated!
Why don't you listen to me?
Hsiao-tsing!
Oh, it's you! I'm sorry
Once again I've made a mistake
I mistook you for she
So there really
is someone named Hsiao-tsing!
Is she the one in the painting?
Do you miss her very much?
She's already dead and buried
We'll never meat again
If you want, you can
call me Hsiao-tsing for now
For now?
I understand
You're betrothed to another
When I knew Hsiao-tsing
she was also betrothed to somebody else
It's beyond my control
Hsiao-tsing said exactly the thing
You are mortal; she's a ghost
But you're both exactly the same
Are we very much alike?
Too much so
You gave me false hope
Anyway, false hope is
better than none
Excuse me!
Here's your tea
Your meal will be served presently
Please make yourselves at home
I've seen that man before
He's...
The tea is poisoned!
This inn is run by thieves!
Really!
Is the water boiling?
Yes
The blade sharpened?
Nice and sharp
Everything's ready
Put the man in the
cauldron immediately
Save the woman for tonight
to warm our could beds
Kill!
Slice them up good!
Right on!
Stop!
Watch where
you're stabbing!
They escaped through the window
It's dangerous here
This is no way to escape!
Betterjump into the tree and hide
I still haven't recovered
No energy to jump
Don't worry about me. Run!
No. I won't leave you
This time there's no escape!
I never thought we'd die here
Elder, it's our fault
for getting you involved
I'm not Elder Chu Kot
I'm just a poor scholar
No matter who you are...
I feel fortunate to die
with the one I love
We'll never be parted again
Hold me!
Let me be on the outside so that
the wolf eats me first
You're wonderful
So are you
If we could be like this forever
it would be great
Orchid Temple!
What's the Orchid Temple?
How could I have forgotten about Yin?
Who is he?
The bearded man in the Orchid Temple
A wizard in the occult
If we find him, we can deal
with the High Priest
Isn't the High Priest returning
to the capital city?
Why go to his palace?
He needs a tranquil place
to meditate
Only holy people may enter this
sacred place. Stay where you are
This is the hour of the eclipse
My body is changing against my wish
Why are all the officials
of the imperial court here?
Lord Chiang! Lord Yang! Lord Lee!
I was escorting Lord Fu
back to the capital...
But couldn't complete my mission
Allow me to explain
Lord Chiang!
A hollow shell?
Lord Yang is a hollow shell, too?
What kind of a place is this?
Are you demons?
What did you do with the flesh
and blood of these officials?
You demons, come out and face me!
Why did you do this to
the imperial officials?
What evil intentions do you harbor?
Are they all hollow shells?!
I'm going to destroy
all of you evil monks
Strange, where have they hidden?
Autumn? Moon? Lord Fu?
Lord Fu!
What happened?
Where are the others?
I was wrong to believe you!
You've caused so much harm!
What other plots do you
have up your sleeve?
We were tricked
The High Priest is a demon!
He turned many officials
into walking corpses
We must report this to the emperor
Otherwise, the kingdom will
be beyond redemption
Oh, he's the one who
instigated this calamity!
No wonder the court is in upheaval
We must hurry to rescue the others
We can talk later
Moon!
Dad!
Autumn!
There are demons in the court
so I must get involved in affairs of state
Everyone must do his bit
Hurry! There's danger everywhere
Let's get past this hurdle first
These demonic monks have
great magical powers
Once he's awake we won't
be able to escape, so hurry!
Autumn, get out of here!
Don't fight anymore!
This is a scene of desolation
Lord, ride my horse
More chanting!
Father!
I'll use my powers to
help you concentrate
Come back, Hu. You'll never beat him
Put down your butchers' knives
Bow before Buddha!
Hu, don't sacrifice
yourself in vain!
I mistakenly trusted these demons
and slaughtered righteous officials
To atone for my sins
I'll fight him to the death
Don't!
I'm headed for hell anyway
Hu!
Yin, why does the wind suddenly
blow so violently?
It's hard to tell which
direction is which
Yin, what should we do?
Evil spirits pervade this road
Our lives hang by a slender thread
We mustn't stop. Follow me!
Oh, boundless heaven and earth
Help me!
Recite the scriptures with me!
Prajna paramita...
The Diamond Sutra incantation?
Ignoramus, behaving so
boorishly in front of me!
Prajna paramite...
Ning, Windy. Get out of the way!
Oh, boundless heaven and earth
Help me!
Buddha is present!
If you dare to impersonate Buddha
What would you not dare to do?
You think you can hoodwink
the people forever?
I'm going to let everyone know
what you really are!
The masses love to
worship their idols
Why set yourself
against the people?
It's their ignorance
that has allowed you to succeed
I'll never let them
worship demons like you
You'll never deceive
the people again!
If you refuse to follow
my shining beacon...
you will be destroyed!
What crap! Look out!
Justice for all!
Swords are part of the infinite!
We've only destroyed
the false outer body
He can come back and
attack us at any time
We must use our swords to fight back!
Let me introduce myself
I'm from the Kunlun sect...
At a time like this, let's
not separate into sects
We're all fighting the same enemy
Destroy this demon!
Chant with me!
Prajna paramita...
The old demon has stolen into the earth
and broken through our ring of swords
What should we do?
Watch!
What kind of demon?
Come with me!
Hold on to me as I fly
Ning!
You pulled my sleeve off
What are you coming back for?
What happened?
Gone?
Keep quiet!
Be careful
The demon has changed its appearance
It's huge!
Be careful!
Moon, look after your father
I'll help Yin
Autumn, be careful!
The demon's actually
a giant centipede!
That worm can never be a dragon
Elder!
I've never had to deal with
such a giant creature
What should we do now?
Pierce the crown of its head
Ning!
Windy!
The flying sword!
Prajna paramite!
Exorcise the demons!
Oh, boundless heaven and earth
Help me!
Elder!
Autumn!
Two heads are better than one
Abracadabra. Hocus pocus
Hocus pocus
I've been in the Orchid Temple
for so long...
I didn't know the world
was so full of devils and demons
It's hard to separate
the living from the deed
The world is in chaos
It's a good thing you hid
in the Orchid Temple
Otherwise I might never
have found you
We share the same ideals...
We should roam this world together
and fight forjustice
We should work together
What are you saying?
I've always led a
solitary existence
Last time, I almost died
trying to help you save Hsiao-tsing
This time, I've helped you
battle the demons...
and almost lost my life
It's better if we go our own ways
When you need my help
I'll return and save you
Be careful, Autumn!
The demon still isn't dead
Autumn!
I really need your help this time
or I'm finished
We must bejinxed!
I'll take care of things!
Quickly, craw!
No good
Autumn!
That centipede flew over!
What about Autumn and Yin?
We're locked in. We must think
of a way to escape
You're right!
I've really caused you here
Our bodies are restrained. We can be
saved only if our souls can escape
Souls?
Will we have enough energy
to later let the sols back in?
This is the only way!
Chant along with me
The spirit of Buddha conquers all!
Goodness is indestructible
Prajna paramite. Abracadabra!
Abracadatra! Hocus pocus!
Oh, boundless heaven and earth
Help me!
Autumn!
Yin!
Soul, return!
My soul can't return to my body!
Autumn, catch the soul!
Autumn!
His power isn't strong enough
I'll help him
Prajna paramite...
I can't catch it
Moon!
Autumn!
Too late!
What's all the hubbub outside?
What hubbub?
I don't hear anything!
Who's getting married?
Such a large golden pig!
It's a gift to Lord Fu
from the emperor
Since he exposed the traitors
in the imperial court
he performed a great
service for the emperor
It's a wedding gift
for Lord Fu's daughter
Moon!
Ning!
Is Windy getting...
Sister is already married
Don't cause her any trouble
I'm about to start on a journey
Give her my best wishes
for a happy marriage
I will. Take care of yourself
Adieu!
It's hard to differentiate
between true and false hopes
Now I understand why you stay
away from our mortal world
Mortals are forgetful
Good deeds fade like the wind
No matter what you've done
it's soon forgotten
Is forgetting good or bad?
Should we have hopes?
Windy?!
You said you'd cherish no hope!
Sister, don't hesitate!
Go to him!
Windy?!
Ning!
Let's go, hurry!
You go back
Farewell!
Take care!
Let's go!