Rule number one, know your products.
Okay, whether it's a PC or a piece of paper;
know how it works.
Number two, know your customers.
Learn everything you can about them.
Listen to what they want
and what they don't want.
Rule number three, go the extra yard, okay?
If you don't have the answer; find it.
it's that simple.
Okay, let's go get those numbers up.
- Hi, Nick.
- Hey, Gary.
- Solid presentation there.
- Thank you.
Same one you gave last month, right?
How'd it go in Houston?
Great. It went great.
- How's the wife?
- She's fine, thank you.
- Kids?
I don't have kids.
Oh, right. Yeah. You don't have kids.
So listen, Nick.
The company has decided to make a change.
My numbers are as solid
as they've ever been.
- it's not about numbers anymore.
- I've done everything the company
has asked me to do.
I promised that my drinking would be
under control, and it is.
Not in Denver, apparently.
I made this office into a major player
My record reflects that.
You want to talk about your record, Nick?
1998, one month paid leave
for alcohol counseling.
2000, another 30 days.
2001, accused of assault.
It was a softball game.
The guy was blocking the plate.
2003, DUI.
2005, destruction of corporate can
I've given 16 years of my life
to this company.
And the company has rewarded you
very well for your loyalty.
Mr. Goodson and the rest of the higher-ups
wanted you to have this
as a token of their appreciation.
You can keep the corporate car
until the end of the month.
You can keep your health benefits, too,
which is good.
Your files are all corporate property,
of course,
but you can take three file boxes with you
containing your personal items.
That should just about cover it.
And one of those cherry Slurpees, too.
- This guy. I don't know.
- I got it. I got it.
Hey, bro, I'll give you 10 bucks
for that twack right there.
Aren't you a little young
to be drinking beers?
Aren't you a little old to be drinking
that Slurpee there, gray balls?
Is that what they teach you in school,
little shit?
What?
Hi. Are you in there?
If you are, can this happen another day?
Hi, it's Nick. I’m back.
I got your letter
I really want to talk to you, okay?
I 'll just be getting some
of the stuff off the lawn
and getting it out of here
if that's all right with you.
When you're ready, we can talk.
And you probably already heard,
I lost my job today. So...
Okay, bye.
Oh, great.
Hey, Elliot. You're home early.
Well, benefit of being the boss, I guess.
You know, having all that stuff on your lawn
is gonna destroy your root system.
Yeah, I'm sorry about the mess.
- I'll have it cleaned up by tomorrow.
- Great.
Listen, Nick. You know me,
I try to keep out of people's way.
But if I'm honest,
I saw this coming a mile away.
Thanks for warning me.
No problem.
Come on.
I like your bumper stickers.
Right, I probably should have taken them off
before I hit Texas, right?
- Here, let me help you.
- Thank you.
I'm Nick. My wife Catherine
and I live across the street.
Samantha.
You can just put that in there
with the others.
Okay.
So are you getting rid of your old stuff?
Yeah. Just a little spring cleaning.
- You a photographer?
- Yeah. Photography teacher.
- Really? Where do you teach?
- New York.
My husband...
Well, we are relocating for work.
I lived in Newark for two years.
Westchester County.
Well, welcome to Arizona.
Thank you.
Hey, could I ask you a favor?
Would you mind watching my stuff?
- I just need to run to the store real quick.
- Sure, yeah.
You know, no, I can't.
I have to go meet my new doctor.
Sure. Sure, I understand.
I'm sorry. It was nice to meet you.
Yeah, likewise. I'll see you around.
Yeah.
Can I help you?
Do you live around here?
My mom takes care of the lady
down the street.
Why aren't you at work?
I got the day off.
Why'd you get the day off?
Personal stuff.
With your wife?
Why do you say that?
I saw her yesterday.
Some dudes came over, too.
What dudes?
Like a locksmith guy, an alarm guy,
and, like, some movers.
She say anything?
She was screaming a lot.
And crying.
What's your name?
Kenny Loftus.
Listen, Kenny, are you hungry?
If you stay here and watch my stuff,
I'll go buy us some food, huh?
How's that sound?
Here's 5 bucks. Okay?
You just can't leave.
And don't touch anything.
- Where are you going?
- I don't know, the liquor store.
- What about the mini-mart?
- Yeah, I can go to the mini-mart.
If I go to the mini-mart,
will you stay here and watch my stuff?
I'd like some beef jerky and a Diet Coke.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
- What are you looking for?
- My car keys.
- You want to borrow my bike?
- No, I'll find them.
Sorry, dude, it didn't go through.
Can you just swipe it again, please?
It didn't go through, Mr. Halsey.
- Really?
- Nope.
Something's probably wrong
with the machine.
- Can you just call it in?
- I can't call it in, man.
- How much is it?
- $37.50.
Hey, honey, it's Nick.
I just tried to buy some things
with the credit cards and they didn't work.
Look, I'm gonna need them
to pay someone to move stuff off the lawn.
So if you can just call me back
and we can possibly work this out,
I'd really appreciate it. Okay?
Thank you. Bye.
Mr. Halsey, I checked the ATM
it's working fine.
Okay. Well, that doesn't make any sense.
There's $45,000 in that account.
The money's still there.
But apparently someone
put a stop on that account.
But that's my account.
Technically, it's a joint account
and either you or your wife
can put a stop on it.
Who authorized that?
You did. Your signature is right here, sir.
Next to your wife's.
Your service
has been temporarily suspended.
For an emergency, dial 9-1-1.
Can I help you?
Yeah, this is my car.
This car belongs to Office Expo Inc.
Really?
Well, that's my stuff right back there.
If it's inside the car,
it belongs to the company now.
So you're gonna have to
take it up with them.
Hey. Hey, look.
I don't want any problems, okay?
I just want my stuff.
Excuse me. Hey. Hey, hey!
This is my car.
Those are my golf clubs.
Why didn't you try to stop him?
He said it was his car.
Did you get my jerky?
Yeah.
Where'd you get that?
- That?
- Yeah.
- In the pile.
- I told you not to touch anything.
Why?
'Cause some of it, like this,
is worth a lot of money.
You know what this is?
A baseball?
A baseball signed by the entire
'78 world champion Yankees.
Reggie Jackson?
Thurman Munson?
Ron Guidry?
Never mind.
We have a good team at my school.
Yeah? Do you play?
I tried out last year, but I didn't make it.
Well, there's always next year.
Look, I've got work I've got to do here. So...
Isn't your mom worried about you?
She'll be gone till Miss Cooper dies.
She just leaves you alone?
My sister comes around at night.
Kenny, I'm gonna try the direct approach
with you, okay?
I need you to leave. Now.
I found your keys.
571 Xray. Yeah, we're out here.
Code 4 for now.
- Afternoon.
- Hi.
Can I see some identification, please?
I left it in my car.
And where's your car?
It's gone.
Even though, technically, it wasn't mine.
You want to tell me
what you're doing out here?
Yeah, I would.
I'm just organizing some of my things.
Why? Is there a problem?
Yeah, we've gotten some complaints
about someone living on their lawn.
Really? Who complained?
I can't tell you that, sir.
Well, this is my lawn. And this is my house.
And I'm pretty sure
I can do whatever I want on my property.
How much have you had to drink?
In my opinion, not enough.
You know there's a law against having
open containers in public, right?
There's a law that says I can't drink
a fucking beer on my front lawn?
Sir, you're gonna have to come with me.
I can't leave my stuff.
Your things will be fine. Let's go.
Turn around.
571 Xray. Yeah, why don't you...
Hey, stop talking into that thing.
- Stand by.
- Just listen to me.
Call Detective Frank Garcia, okay?
You want me to call Detective Garcia?
Yeah, call him. Call him. He'll fix all of this.
He wasn't violent, right?
No, man, he's just been drinking.
He asked me to call you.
Thanks, man. I got it from here.
I came as soon as I could.
I had a double homicide.
Thanks, Frank.
Did you talk to her?
No, I think it's worth
giving her a little time on this one.
She changed all the locks, you know?
Garage code.
How do you change the garage code?
You haven't tried to break in yet.
I'm impressed.
Last time I broke in, you arrested me.
That's right.
You know that the moment
that you even thought
about having a drink
you should have just called me.
Well, let's see.
Yesterday, what happened?
I got fired from my job and my wife left me.
So somehow calling you slipped my mind.
I got it. I got it.
You know, they say that the dining room
is the least utilized room in the house.
I think it's the front lawn.
It's starting to look good, don't you think?
I don't care how it looks.
You can't stay here. it's illegal.
I paid for this house, for her fish,
for this lawn.
This is my house.
- What's your point?
- My point?
This is my corner. Okay?
I'm not leaving my stuff.
All right. I'll call dispatch
and make sure nobody comes by tonight.
But slow down on the beer, yeah?
Get some rest.
We'll figure this out tomorrow.
She's coming up on a year.
I know, Nick. We still go to meetings.
- Hey, Frank.
- Yeah?
You're a good sponsor, you know?
Actually, Nick, I'm not.
I'll see you tomorrow morning.
It's a great rug.
Yeah, it was my mom's.
I got you some coffee and cigarettes.
I quit smoking.
Thanks.
You need any help moving today?
No, I'm good.
Really? Not planning to leave
anytime soon?
Well, since I don't have any money
or car or phone,
I was just thinking about just staying here.
Do you honestly think
that this is how you're gonna get her back?
I'm just living day to day.
Right. Right.
How many days you think
it's gonna take to get your shit together?
You're gonna make me leave?
I'm not gonna tell you what to do
because we both know that doesn't work.
But if it takes you sitting here
and making an idiot out of yourself
to get cleaned up, then so be it.
The city of Arcadia
allows a property owner to hold a yard sale
for no more than five consecutive days.
This buys you three days.
I don't want to sell my stuff.
Sell your crap, don't sell your crap.
I don't care.
But after this, you move on.
I got you some pens
and some paper to make signs.
I got to make signs?
- That was a joke.
- Don't make an ass out of me, Nick.
No, it was a funny joke.
You have three days
to get your shit together.
If not, I'm gonna have to
haul your ass off to jail.
Right. Mount Rushmore.
Grand Canyon.
That's nice.
- Hey, Kenny.
- Hey.
- I'm sorry about yesterday.
- It's cool, man.
How's your penmanship?
Pretty good.
I was thinking,
seeing as you're not doing anything
but riding your bike all day,
you might want to come work for me.
What Kind of work?
Make some signs.
Maybe sell a couple of things.
What are you offering?
Discussing salary and responsibility
upfront, smart, very smart.
I'm thinking 4 bucks an hour, okay?
If I have to leave, you stay here,
watch my stuff, act tough.
I'll feed you, give you bathroom and
cigarette breaks as required by state law.
I don't smoke.
Good. Great. So do we got a deal?
Arizona minimum wage is $7.25.
Okay, $7.25 it is.
What? It's a good deal.
I want to learn to play baseball.
You want me to teach you
how to play baseball?
Yeah, I don't know.
I see all your trophies and stuff on the lawn.
Yeah, I know. That's from high school.
Why do you want to learn to play baseball?
My mom says I need the exercise.
Okay, I could see that.
And my dad played.
Okay.
Now we got a deal?
- Deal.
- Okay.
Start making some signs.
This is the sign area right here.
No, I haven't met the neighbors yet.
Yes, there's grass.
What about these clothes?
Keep.
Put them in that top, left-hand drawer.
What about these?
Yeah, those.
Think I want to hold onto those.
They're actually pretty valuable.
You'd be surprised.
You can put 'em in that same drawer.
I'll know that they're there in case I want to
look at 'em.
So when are you coming?
Well...
Okay. Okay, Well, when will you know?
- Can I help you?
- How much?
I'm sorry, the shoes are not for sale.
They shouldn't be over there, actually.
How much for the chair?
You know, it's not for sale, either.
How much for this?
- You want to buy that?
- How much is it?
50 CENTS.
I'll give you 25 cents.
Yeah, I just can't do that.
Hold on, hold on.
Let's keep it at 50 and let's see.
I'll throw in some floss.
Great. Have a good one.
Rule number eight,
always give 'em a little something extra.
There's your take.
- Can we work on baseball now?
- I'm beat.
Why don't you go hang some more signs
or something and we'll call it a day?
I don't know why I'm hanging signs
if you're not gonna sell anything.
I sold some mouthwash.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- Where do you want this?
- I guess, just...
You can just leave it over there somewhere.
So is this your first time for a yard sale?
Yeah. Yeah, it is, actually.
Watch out for the pros on Saturday.
They’ll try to beat you up on price.
Do you go to a lot of them?
Yeah, they're good for finding old cameras.
Once you get rid of all that stuff,
you're gonna feel great.
- Yeah, I think so.
- Yeah.
Hey. I was gonna order Chinese food.
It's not New York, but...
You know, I have a lot of stuff to do
before my husband gets here.
Right. No, I understand.
- But thank you for the offer.
- Sure.
Could I use your phone?
To order?
Hey.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I saw you got your food
and I thought you could use
something to eat with.
- Here.
- Well, thank you.
You're welcome.
Can I... Do you want...
Can I make you a plate?
- Yeah, sure.
- Why not?
- Right. Thank you.
- Great.
No.
- Do you mind if I look through?
- Go ahead.
God, these are incredible.
Yeah.
Wish I still had mine.
Can't believe you still listen to vinyl.
I don't. They were my father's.
- He was a DJ.
- Yeah?
The Late Night Mix with Glen Halsey
on KZOV.
- Wow.
- Please, sit here if you want.
No, no, I'll use this. This is fine, don't worry.
There you go.
Yeah, he played
jazz, country, rock, Tejano,
all kinds of crazy stuff.
He sounds like an interesting guy.
Yeah, no. He was more of a drunk
who occasionally did interesting things.
So you're a teacher, huh?
I guess I should say I'm a photographer,
but teaching takes up most of my time.
Have you ever had any shows of your work?
Yeah, I've sold some pieces.
Not enough to get rich, but...
Actually, I sold one to my husband.
That's how we met.
Okay.
- So what do you do for work?
- Well,
as of yesterday, I was
regional vice president
at a very large corporation.
- Sorry.
- Don't be.
Look, I made good money.
I bought this house.
We've been to Europe,
the Caribbean, Japan twice.
- Wow.
- Yeah. So...
Does he have a name yet?
Yeah.
Yeah, my husband wants to call him Jack.
That's his name, my husband.
I think it's a little ridiculous
naming a child after yourself.
- Do you have kids?
- No.
No, we don't.
We have fish.
The gold one here...
- Asagi.
Yeah.
She had the breeders shipped over
in those special containers from Japan.
A grand each.
This used to be our swimming pool.
But it's not anymore. You know?
So what's the music for?
She'd read that it improves breeding.
You know, it's okay. You can...
You can ask me.
Ask you what?
About all that out front.
I mean, you just moved here
and you have to look at it.
Look, I'm sure whatever it is,
you can work it out.
I was sober for six months.
I had a couple of slipups,
you know, here and there.
Nothing major. But I was trying, you know?
And, well, I was on a business trip
and we completed this very big deal.
So I took everyone out to celebrate.
There was this new girl, Sharon,
from the Denver office.
So she got champagne for everyone.
I figured,
"I'll have a glass, right?" You know?
Just to toast.
We must have gone through
six or seven bottles.
And then it was just us,
in her room, you know,
keeping the party going.
So what happened?
In the morning, she was gone.
And then there were lawyers,
and investigations and interviews.
And, you know...
Did you do it?
Whatever they said you did?
I don't know. I don't know.
I should go.
Here, let me take your plate.
Let me walk you home.
It's fine. I can walk across the street.
Wait. Wait. Hold on.
Don't forget this. Fortune cookie.
Thanks.
Good night.
Hey.
I like it. I like it.
Are you listening to me? Pour some wine.
- Come on, pour it.
- Come on, bring it.
- That's it.
- Put it in! Put it in!
- Put it in!
- Bark for me.
Come on, bark.
Yeah. Yeah, bark. Bark for me.
Oh, I like that. You're a dog, aren't you?
You're a great big dog. Nice puppy.
Take it out! Take it out! Take it out!
I want some more wine.
Keep barking, baby. Keep barking.
You're a nice puppy.
Yes, Nick?
I'm interested in that rotisserie over here.
- The rotisserie?
- Yeah, the rotisserie.
One second.
Nick.
Hey, that guy wants to buy the rotisserie
5 bucks.
What am I gonna cook with?
You got the Foreman.
Okay, tell him I'll sell it,
but that I'll only take $10, all right?
He's not gonna do it.
Well, tell him why he should buy it, right?
Focus on the benefits.
Go ahead.
If you have to take $7, that's okay.
He won't accept the $5.
But I'll let you know
the rotisserie is brand new.
He's only used it twice.
You can cook anything with it.
He wants $10, but I'll take $7.
- $7 is good.
- Thank you.
Good sale.
You got the gift.
Kenny, take a seat.
Look, you've been busting ass.
I just want you to know I appreciate it.
All right? You know what?
This company needs a shake-up.
We need a little less "me"
and a little more "we."
Like this, not like this.
Don't do that. Do that.
Are you sure you're left-handed?
Yeah, I'm sure.
- Why don't you want to play football?
- My mom won't let me.
That's a shame, Kenny,
'cause you're a born left tackle.
Big, fast, smart.
How about soccer?
Black people don't play soccer.
Whole continents of black people
play soccer.
Pelé. You heard of him?
Yeah, try not to be afraid of the ball.
You know what? Why don't you practice
a little bit on your own?
- How do I do that?
- Just throw it up in the air and catch it.
- Hey.
I found this. Used to be my mom's.
- Wow.
- I don't Know if it still works.
Let me see.
Oh, God, it's beautiful.
- Is there film in it?
- I don't know.
Smile.
- Yup.
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- Keep it.
- No, I couldn't take it. That's sweet, but...
- No, please.
- Really?
- Yeah. Yeah, I want you to have it.
- Can I pay you for it?
- No. No. No. No, my gift to you.
Unless you want to play first base.
But I figured probably not.
Thank you.
Okay, that's good.
- See? Wasn't that helpful?
- I guess.
Let's do some grounders.
- What's a grounder?
- I'll show you. Throw it to me.
Ready? Hands on your knees.
When the ball comes, glove on the ground,
watch it into your glove. All right?
There you go.
How's Miss Cooper doing?
My mom says she's gonna die soon.
But I guess she's not suffering.
I'm glad she's not suffering.
She's definitely got a nice pool.
Hey, what does it mean when it says,
"Make it easy to buy"?
Well, it can mean a number of things,
getting rid of extra paperwork,
displaying things in a way
that are appealing to people,
explaining how products work.
- You actually interested in that stuff?
- Yeah.
If you read all that,
you'll know more than me.
- What?
- Nothing.
No, go ahead.
Are we friends?
Yeah. Yeah, I guess so.
Remember when I told you
I tried out for the baseball team?
Yeah.
I lied. I don't play sports.
Why not?
- They make you change in the locker room.
- So?
The other kids make jokes.
What kind of jokes?
They say,
"You're so fat
you got shocks on your toilet seat."
"You're so fat if your arm broke,
gravy would be coming out."
That's mean.
You heard this one?
Your mama's so fat
she heard it was chilly out,
she ran inside and got a bowl.
Your mama's so fat
she has to shower at a car wash.
Your mama's so fat she has 101% body fat.
You mama's so fat
you have to roll her in flour
then dive for the wet spot.
Do you know what that means?
No.
Yeah, maybe don't tell that one.
Kenny, look, you can't worry
about what other people think about you.
You just got to fight back.
Is that what you're doing?
- What?
- Are you fighting back?
Yeah, I'm fighting.
Who are you fighting?
Hi, Lynette. It's Nick.
Yeah, sure, I'll hold.
Hey, Gary.
I know. I know it was stupid. Yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
You're right, I am an asshole.
Yeah, Gary, I know. I know
it was fucking stupid to leave the knife.
Yeah. Hey, Gary. Gary.
Listen, why don't I come in?
Why don't I come in
and we'll sit down and we'll talk about this?
What? Gary?
Gary!
Hey, Kenny.
Let's put this in the for sale pile.
What about these books?
Is that you?
Yeah.
You look happy.
I was, I guess.
What happened?
What do you mean, what happened?
Life happened.
Work happened. Marriage happened.
Hi, this is Nicholas Halsey.
I went to high school
with your daughter Delilah.
Thank you, ma'am. Yes. You, too.
Listen, I'm on the high school
reunion committee.
We're trying to get in touch with Delilah.
Just wondering if you'd have an address
or a phone number where I could
send her some information.
Just a minute. Can I help you?
- Delilah?
- Yeah.
It's Nick.
Nick Halsey.
Nicholas. Wow.
- God, hey.
- Hi.
What are you doing here?
I was just in the neighborhood
and I thought I'd stop by.
How'd you find me?
I called your old number
and your mom gave me your address.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- What a nice surprise.
I'm just getting some dinner
ready for my kids.
Of course. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I just wanted to stop by and say hello.
You know what?
I'm gonna give the kids dinner outside.
And if you just wait,
I'm gonna bring the food out
and you and I are gonna catch up, okay?
- Great.
- Sound good?
- Yeah.
- Okay. it's gonna be great.
All right. Hey, you guys. Dinner outside.
No, I actually went out to LA
to study acting.
Yeah, I got a couple of decent jobs.
I got to do a IV commercial with Brad Pitt.
- Really?
- It was fun.
- Yeah.
- It was for Japan,
so nobody here got to see it of course.
It was cool.
We were in the desert at an old gas station.
And there were tumbleweeds going by
and we're drinking beers,
which, of course,
is why you could never see it in the US.
- Sure.
- And these Japanese tourists pull up
and they have one of those star maps
and they're asking directions.
I mean, this sounds dumb
but I got to say, "Y'all look lost."
And then Brad kind of smiles at them,
you know.
And he takes the star map
and he points to his own house.
I see.
So, it was cool.
He was a real sweetheart.
What an experience.
Then I had Lizzy and my husband left.
So we came back here.
And it's a good place for kids to grow up.
You know, it's safe.
So what about you?
- Are you married, or...
- Yes. Yes, I am.
- And you have kids?
- No. We're...
We're waiting for the right time, you know.
There isn't one, trust me.
Yeah, how do you handle all this?
All What?
The responsibility.
You know, raising them by yourself,
supporting them.
I don't really have a choice, right?
My dad always said to me,
"Good without the bad ain't no good at all."
So we just make it work, right, missy?
You're a natural.
Hi.
- Wow, it was great to see you.
- Yeah. You, too.
Is there something else
you wanted to say to me?
I'm sorry.
But when we were in high school,
you wrote this.
Oh, my gosh. Look at us.
"You're a diamond in the rough."
That was 20 years ago.
I know.
I know, I know. I'm sorry.
It's stupid.
Hey. No, I mean, we weren't really friends.
Exactly. It's stupid. I'm so sorry.
It was really great to see you.
Hey, you remember those crazy parties
at Brian Sever's house?
Yeah. Well, I showed up
with bright pink hair once
'cause I was going through a phase.
And the guys were super drunk,
especially Brian.
And he decided he was gonna try to
dunk my hair in the pool to get the pink out.
And everybody just thought
that was super funny.
I was really embarrassed and scared.
And you came over and tried to stop him.
And he wouldn't, so you punched him
and knocked him into the pool.
Then you gave me a ride home
while your girlfriend hung out at the party.
Don't you remember that?
No.
Well, I do.
You have a good heart, Nicholas.
That doesn't change.
So when you get yourself together,
you should call me
and we'll go have some coffee.
Sure.
Nicholas, are you gonna be all right?
Yeah. Yeah.
- What's up, man?
- Hey.
- How you doing?
- Good.
- That's all?
- That's it.
- $6.50, man.
- Yeah, I don't have $6.50.
Can I just get this?
I can't do credit on this, man.
You know that.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- On a six-pack?
- You're here all the time.
I know, I've been coming here all the time.
So can you just spot me?
Not at all, man.
I'll lose my job. I can't do that.
- Can you just give me one beer?
- No, not even one
- 'cause it's a whole case right here.
- You being serious right now?
- I'm being serious right now.
- Really? For real?
Can't you just tell?
I should fucking call the cops
on your ass for that.
You better leave. Yeah, run.
Hey, I don't mean to bother you,
but can I get a beer from you?
Can I get one of your beers?
I just need a drink.
These are Valium.
They'll help.
You feeling any better?
Thanks.
You know, you need some help.
I've tried help.
Yeah, well, maybe it wasn't the right kind.
You know, there's new medications,
new therapies.
I don't need medication.
Well, you can't live like this.
Why not?
'Cause it's not normal.
Normal?
What's normal?
That guy Stanley what's-his-name,
down in the blue house,
his wife blew her brains out last month
'cause her daughter
didn't make cheerleading.
Kenny practically lives by himself,
you know?
Elliot and Kitty,
I can't even tell you what they do.
I'm no different than any of you.
I just don't hide in my house, okay?
- What does that mean?
- What?
"Any of you."
Nothing. Nothing. I'm just saying...
No, you said "any of you."
Never mind.
No, go on. I'm a big girl. Say it.
I don't want to do this right now.
Say it.
What's his name?
- Who?
- Your husband. John? Jeff?
- Jack.
He started out in a regional office, right?
Yeah.
He impressed some people
who moved him up to the big leagues.
- How many years?
- Two.
Two years? Yeah.
Now he's back at the regionals.
You're sacrificing your promising career
as a photographer for him.
So?
I figured you out in five minutes.
He drinks.
They transferred him out here
'cause he fucked something up.
You probably thought
it was a good idea to come out here.
Might even save your marriage.
For better or for worse, right?
Right.
I just want to know one thing.
What kind of man lets his wife,
his pregnant wife,
move alone across the country?
And what kind of woman
stays with a man like that?
What kind of woman?
What, so it's my fault?
You must be really good at your job,
you know, just reading people so easily,
figuring out what bullshit to sell 'em.
- Hey.
- God, what?
You need to put up some curtains.
Why? So I don't have some drunk
staring at me all day?
No, so you don't have to look at your future.
Jeez.
Fuck you! Fuck you!
"Light up your life. Stop living in the dark."
- Hey.
- How long have you been here?
- A couple of hours.
Where did the tables come from?
- The tables?
- Yeah.
Your neighbor Elliot.
You got price tags on everything.
How'd you do that?
Market research.
I'm making it easy for the customer.
- Nice work, Kenny.
- Thanks.
Really nice work.
- Hey, how's it going?
- Hey. Good. Good.
Just thought I'd stop by a little,
check up on you.
Thanks.
So you're letting some of this stuff go, huh?
Yeah. I'm gonna sell it,
you know, everything I can.
- I'm proud of you, bud.
- Thanks.
Yeah, Catherine, we can...
I can work this out.
This is a good first step. It is.
Why don't you stop by the station
when you're done?
Okay. Yeah, I'll be there.
- Thanks for stopping by.
- No problem.
Excuse me. How much for the chair?
- The chair?
- Yeah.
- $2 and I'll throw in the macramé.
- All right.
Thank you.
That actually works.
Same taste in tapes, man.
That's right, throw it on the grill there.
You ever fish the lower Salt?
No.
At sunset with the water like glass,
it's religious.
Sounds nice.
I'm sorry, I've never fished the lower Salt.
I've never even gone fishing before.
I've never been fishing in all my life.
- That looks really good on him.
- Yeah, isn't it cute?
Really cute. Old school.
- I'm not sure.
- Your girlfriend is.
All I know is I bought this for $125.
I'm not gonna do $125.
- I'm not asking you to.
- Okay.
- I'm asking $25.
- I'll do $15.
- What about $22?
- $20.
- $217
- Okay.
- How much is this?
- $10.
Hey, that should be $15.
I got engaged in that suit.
I saw you checking out the blender.
I could do both for $25.
All right, deal.
Rule number one, always have power
so people can test appliances.
That's a good rule.
Hey, just wanted you to know
everything's going pretty good.
And I'm selling it, all my stuff.
All my crap. And it feels pretty good.
I'm getting rid of everything, Catherine.
Anyway, call me when you're ready.
On Kitty's phone, I guess.
I miss you. Bye.
Made in China, even though
it's supposed to be Japanese, so...
You know What? I'll give it to you for $25.
And I'll throw in this wolf and polar bear.
Okay, let's show 'em, ladies.
Hustlers. You're all hustlers.
You hustled me.
All right, another hand like that
and I'll be buying the table from you.
Who's deal? Sherry, your deal?
- All right.
- Right here. Here we go.
Yeah, you don't have to shuffle.
So, yeah, you can cook anything on it.
You can cook hot dogs.
You can cook bacon.
You can cook burritos.
- Who's in first?
- I'm in for $10.
- $10'?
- I'm in for $15.
- $15'?
- I'm in for $15 as well.
Okay, that's already too rich for my blood.
- I don't have that kind of money.
- You want to borrow a chip?
You know what?
I'm all in, plus the cat ashtray.
Okay?
- Yours sticks.
- Yeah.
- That's good luck.
- The high-level players can do this.
- How we looking?
- Take a look.
Okay, good.
I can't hardly even find this stuff anymore.
- How much for these?
- I'm sorry. They're not for sale.
Come on, man. What do you want for 'em?
- No, no, I really can't.
- Seriously?
I think you'll be happy with either.
- What do you think, green or blue?
- Go with blue.
All right, thank you very much.
How's that mouthwash treating you?
How much for the chair?
Can I ask why you want it?
I need a new chair.
What happened to the old one?
I got a new color IV over at a sale in Gilbert.
I need a new chair.
You know what? Why don't you take it?
I want you to have it.
Yeah.
Samantha?
Please, I know you're in there.
Nice house.
I just wanted to apologize for last night.
No, look, really, it's fine.
I shouldn't have pushed.
I don't know you.
I don't know your husband.
Yeah, well, I called him last night.
I told him I was going to leave him.
He said he was coming tomorrow.
So you're right.
Maybe you don't know people
so well after all.
Are you gonna go back to New York?
I don't know.
Well,
I don't think it's right
to make a decision like that
without having authentic Mexican food.
Have you had an authentic Mexican meal
in Arizona?
No.
Well, Kenny and I, we're gonna go celebrate.
He's buying.
So...
Sounds nice.
Great. Good.
'Cause we need a ride anyway.
Of course.
- Lively.
- He likes it.
Maybe. Or really doesn't like it.
- Are you ready for him?
- Yes.
No.
I can't figure out what color to paint
the baby's room.
I don't know why,
but somehow it seems really important.
It is important.
Every color has a specific effect on people.
What are you thinking?
Come on, it's what I do for a living.
You pick colors for a living?
No, I pick colors to make people buy things.
- I like yellow.
- That makes people anxious.
- Yeah.
- That's not good.
How about blue?
- Blue is soothing. Color of communication.
- That's good.
Yeah. Green is good, also.
Well, then I guess it's blue.
Or green.
Here's to blue or green.
To blue or green.
Nick.
Wow.
What brings you downtown?
Dinner with friends. You?
Drinks with the boys from the office.
How's everything at work?
Things are good. They're good.
Nothing new, really.
We filled your position.
Yeah, some kid
straight out of business school.
He's good. He's not as good as you,
but he's young and he's cheap.
Right.
Pretty good ballplayer, too,
from what I understand.
Think he even played in the Minors.
They got rid of that Sharon girl.
Really?
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, it turns out she threatened to sue
two other guys at her last job at Kittredge.
Total bullshit.
Wow, kind of makes you think, doesn't it?
If you hadn't stabbed my Mustang,
probably could've gotten your job back.
Sued for wrongful termination, even.
Yeah. Well, I'll see you around, man.
It's the kind of thing you kind of feel like
you want to touch,
but you're not really sure.
Think you forgot that.
Hey, can you drop me off somewhere?
- Yeah, sure.
- Okay, thanks.
Where are you going?
That's none of your business
where I'm going.
I'm a grown man.
I'll buzz you in.
- Glad you had the time.
- Yeah, I know.
- Just ate at that place over on 60th.
- Yeah?
And the sale?
- Great.
- Good. So listen,
- I've got to check up on a statement.
- Okay.
- You good? Want anything to drink?
- No, I'm good. Yeah.
- I'm glad you're here.
- Good to be here. Thanks.
Frank? Frank, it's Catherine.
I’m back at your place.
Call me back if you can hear me.
Frank? Frank, are you...
Can I stay at your house tonight?
Why don't I just get you a hotel room?
No, I think it would be better
if I stayed with you.
Well, you know you can't do that.
She didn't have anywhere to go.
She could have stayed with her sister.
She wanted a drink, so she came to me, bud.
She came to me. I'm sorry.
We always joked about this, you know?
- Yeah? What?
- Yeah, the 13th step.
- Come on, man.
- First you teach them the 12 steps.
Then you get them into bed for the 13th.
It wasn't like that, bud.
She came to me for help.
- Look, I'm sorry. I...
- Shut up, Frank!
Look, let's go get some coffee and talk.
She deserves better, you piece of shit.
She deserves better.
Okay. Okay. No. No. No.
- I got it.
- You all right? Stay there.
Do you know the success rate for a marriage
when one person gets sober
and the other one doesn't'?
Is it higher than the suicide rate for cops?
It's almost zero.
I know this because I go to the meetings.
I do the work.
You know, she came to me
about six months ago.
I told her to leave you.
But she wanted to give you another chance,
said she still loved you.
But then you go out and you get drunk
and you have sex with another woman.
I mean, it would be perfect
if it wasn't so damn sad.
Can I ask you a question?
How long since you guys slept together?
How long since you asked
her if she was happy?
You know what? Stop the car.
- Let me just take you home.
- No, just pull over.
Catherine wants a divorce.
And she wants the house, too.
I was gonna tell you tonight.
Here are the papers.
The keys to the house are inside.
There's some spending money in there.
She wants to keep it amicable.
So just sign the papers
and you'll get your share.
I want you to know that Cate and I,
we haven't given up on you.
If you want a new sponsor,
I could recommend somebody.
Frank...
Tell my wife I'm sorry.
- Hey.
So how are you doing?
Fine.
Here.
- What's this?
- The money we made.
I plugged the record player in
in case you wanted to listen to music.
Nice job, Kenny.
There's your take.
- This is too much.
- Take it.
I was skimming your profits for beer money.
Rule number 17,
never go into business with a friend.
Thanks.
So I guess I'll see you around.
Yeah.
Maybe we can catch a game sometime.
Been a pleasure working with you.
You, too.