Link's running.
What's the plan here, Jake?
There's no plan.
Tsu'tey is Olo'eyktan now.
He's not gonna let you near that place.
I gotta try.
Launching.
(EXHALES)
(COUGHING)
JAKE:
Outcast.
Betrayer.
Alien.
I was in the place
the eye does not see.
I needed their help,
and they needed mine.
But to ever
face them again,
I was gonna have to take it
to a whole new level.
(SCREECHING)
Sometimes your whole life
boils down to one insane move.
There's something we gotta do.
You're not gonna like it.
Yah!
(SQUAWKING)
The way I had it figured,
Toruk is the baddest cat in the sky.
Nothing attacks him.
Easy, boy.
So why would
he ever look up?
But that was
just a theory.
(GRUNTING)
(ROARING)
(ALL SINGING IN NA'VI)
(ALL MURMURING
IN GROWING ALARM)
(SCREAMING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(ROARING)
Toruk Macto?
(GROWLING SOFTLY)
(VILLAGERS MURMURING)
(PANTING SOFTLY)
I See you.
I was afraid, Jake.
For my people.
I'm not anymore.
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
You are Olo'eyktan,
and you are a great warrior.
I can't do this
without you.
(ROARING)
Toruk Macto,
I will fly with you.
My friend is dying.
Grace is dying.
I beg the help of Eywa.
(ALL CHANTING)
Look where
we are, Grace.
I need to take
some samples.
(JAKE CHUCKLING SOFTLY)
The Great Mother may choose
to save all that she is
in this body.
Is that possible?
She must pass through
the eye of Eywa and return.
But, Jakesully,
she is very weak.
Hang on, Grace.
They're gonna fix you up.
(MO'AT SPEAKING NA'VI)
(ALL REPLYING IN NA'VI)
(ALL CHANTING)
(SPEAKS NA'VI)
(CHANTING STOPS)
(WEAKLY)
Jake.
Grace.
I'm with her, Jake.
She's real!
(DISTANTLY)
Grace? Grace, please. Grace!
What's happening?
Grace!
JAKE:
What's happening?
Did it work?
Her wounds were too great.
It was not enough time.
She is with Eywa now.
With your permission,
I will speak now.
You would honor me
by translating.
The Sky People
have sent us a message
(TSU'TEY TRANSLATING)
that they can take
whatever they want
and no one can stop them.
Well, we will send them
a message.
You ride out as fast as
the wind can carry you.
You tell the other clans
to come.
(EXCLAIMING IN AGREEMENT)
You tell them Toruk Macto
calls to them.
And you fly now
with me!
My brothers!
Sisters!
(ALL HOOTING)
And we will show
the Sky People
that they cannot take
whatever they want,
and that this,
this is our land!
(REPEATING IN NA'VI)
(ALL CHEERING)
(ROARS)
Yah!
(EXCLAIMING IN NA'VI)
(SCREECHING)
(ALL CHATTERING EXCITEDLY)
(HOOTING)
Yah!
JAKE:
We rode out to the 4 winds.
(SHOUTS IN NA'VI)
To the horse clans
of the plain.
JAKE:
Back to the stars!
To the ikran people
of the Eastern Sea.
For our children's children!
When Toruk Macto
called them, they came.
(SHOUTING IN NA'VI)
(ALL CHEERING)
Yah!
(ULULATING)
(NEYTIRI HOOTING)
Everyone on this base,
every one of you,
is fighting
for survival.
That's a fact!
There's an aboriginal horde out
there massing for an attack.
Now, these orbital
images tell me
that the hostiles' numbers
have gone from a few hundred
to well over 2,000 in one day.
And more are pouring in.
In a week's time,
there could be 20,000 of them.
At that point, they will overrun
our perimeter.
Well, that's not
gonna happen!
Our only security lies
in pre-emptive attack.
We will fight
terror with terror.
Now, the hostiles believe that
this mountain stronghold of theirs
is protected by their...
(SCORNFULLY)
Their deity.
(SOLDIERS SNICKERING)
And when we destroy it,
we will blast a crater
in their racial memory so deep
that they won't come within 1,000 klicks
of this place ever again.
And that, too, is a fact.
(SOLDIERS CHEERING)
Yeah! Yeah.
(SOLDIERS CHATTERING)
Jake, it's crazy here.
It's full mobilization.
They're rigging the shuttle
as a bomber.
They've got these huge pallets
of mine explosives.
It's for some kind
of shock-and-awe campaign.
Fricking daisy cutters!
Quaritch has taken over.
He's rolling, and there's no stopping him.
When?
0600 tomorrow.
WOMAN:
Max! Max! I gotta go.
We're screwed!
(TRUDY LAUGHING)
And I was hoping for
some sort of tactical plan
that didn't involve martyrdom.
TRUDY: We're going up against
gunships with bows and arrows.
I have 15 clans out there.
That's over 2,000 warriors.
Now, we know these mountains.
We fly them. You fly them.
They don't.
Their instruments
won't work up here.
Missile tracking
won't work.
They'll have to fire
a line of sight.
If they bring
the fight to us,
then we have the home-field
advantage.
You know he's gonna
commit that bomber
straight to
the Tree of Souls.
Yeah, I know.
If they get to the Tree of Souls,
it's over.
That's their direct line to Eywa,
their ancestors.
It'll destroy them.
Then I guess
we'd better stop him.
(EXHALES SOFTLY)
I'm probably just talking
to a tree right now.
(SIGHS)
But if you're there,
I need to give you a heads-up.
If Grace is with you,
look into her memories.
See the world
we come from.
There's no green there.
They killed their Mother.
And they're gonna do
the same here.
More Sky People
are gonna come.
They're gonna come
like a rain that never ends.
Unless we stop them.
Look, you chose me
for something.
I will stand and fight.
You know I will.
But I need a little help here.
Our Great Mother
does not take sides, Jake.
(SIGHS)
She protects only
the balance of life.
It was worth a try.
(BOTH SIGHING)
MAN: Yeah! Yeah!
That's what I'm talking about!
Yeah! Yeah! That's what
I'm talking about, man!
This is Group Leader.
We are entering the Flux Vortex.
Switch to manual flight mode.
PILOT:
Copy. Manual flight mode.
This is Papa Dragon.
I want this mission
high and tight.
I want to be home for dinner.
Suit Team, go.
All right, ladies,
let's bring the pain!
STAFF SERGEANT:
Move, move, move!
AMPSUIT COMMANDER 1:
Bravo 1-1, move left.
AMPSUIT COMMANDER 2:
Bravo 1-1 moving left. Watch flank.
Watch formation.
Keep moving.
AMPSUIT COMMANDER 1:
Roger that.
Charlie 2-1,
watch your spacing.
AMPSUIT COMMANDER 1:
Copy that. Over.
Eyes up. Check that overhead.
And watch those thermal scans.
All call signs, Papa has lead,
pushing to target.
Escorts, stay close
on my shuttle.
We are gonna lose
some paint in here.
QUARITCH: Gun crews,
keep your head on a swivel.
Make no mistake, people,
they're out there.
All right, people, target in sight.
Range, 4 klicks.
Valkyrie 1-6,
get your payload ready.
Copy.
Prepare to offload.
Staff Sergeant,
stage the weapon.
Roll it to the ramp!
Let's go!
Hold!
AMPSUIT COMMANDER 2:
Charlie 2-1, got big movement.
Hold position.
Hold up, hold up.
We got movement
out there, 500 meters.
Charlie 2-1, hold position.
Sir, ground has movement!
Fast approaching.
PILOT:
Charlie Oscar, Rider section.
Firing line!
Targets closing.
Range, 400 meters.
Can't you clean it up?
No, sir.
It's the Flux.
(SHOUTING)
(WHOOPING)
(WARRIORS HOOTING)
(SCREAMING)
(SCREECHING)
(HOOTING)
(SHOUTING IN NA'VI)
(ULULATING)
(WHOOPING)
Brother, I'm gonna
punch a hole.
You follow me through.
(RESPONDS IN NA'VI)
(ALL ULULATING)
(APPROACHING WAR CRIES)
(SCREECHING)
(SCREAMING)
(EXCLAIMING)
(EXCLAIMS)
All aircraft, weapons free!
Weapons free!
Break right.
Come around.
Light them up!
Break formation,
engage all hostiles.
Yeah! Get some!
(SCREAMING)
Scorpions,
pursue and destroy.
Jake! Jake!
You copy?
We're falling back!
We're getting hammered!
Copy.
Get out of there.
(SCREECHING)
That's him.
Get after him!
Take him out!
Oops.
Light her up!
Right there!
You're not the only one
with a gun, bitch.
Keep her in your sights.
Purging. Feeding the leak.
Arming all pods.
That's it!
(GASPS)
(SHRIEKS)
(GRUNTING)
Seze!
(GASPING IN CONCERN)
(SHRIEKS)
(SCREAMS)
(SHOUTING)
TRUDY: Rogue 1 is hit.
I'm going in.
Sorry, Jake.
(GRUNTS)
Fire.
(PANTING)
Tsu'tey! Brother,
do you read?
Rogue 1, you copy?
Trudy!
(GASPING)
Time to target, 2 minutes.
Valkyrie 1-6,
you are cleared and hot.
Copy, Dragon.
We are starting our bomb run.
Arm number 1!
Number 1 armed!
Ma Jake!
I read you.
JAKE:
Neytiri!
Seze's dead.
They are very close.
They are many.
Do not attack.
Do you read me,
Neytiri?
Do not attack!
Fall back now. Get out of there!
That's an order!
Neytiri!
AMPSUIT COMMANDER 2:
I got movement.
Hold position.
Something's coming.
AMPSUIT COMMANDER 1: Bravo 1-1,
I got a big seating. Turn screens over.
We got movement 200 meters.
Hold your formation.
Be ready.
Watch your flanks.
Hundred meters and closing fast.
(TRUMPETING)
(EXCLAIMING)
We gotta get out of here!
Fall back! Fall back!
AMPSUIT COMMANDER 1: Move!
Fall back!
On the run! On the run!
(SCREAMING)
Jake, Eywa has heard you.
(SCREECHING)
Eywa has heard you!
(ALL SCREECHING)
Come on!
(SNARLING)
Fall back!
Move! Move!
(SCREAMING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(ROARING)
(ROARS)
(EXHALES SLOWLY)
PILOT: Sir! All escorts
are down or falling back.
Let's get this done.
Valkyrie 1-6, this is Dragon.
Press to target.
Copy.
Pressing to target.
Stand by to drop,
30 seconds.
(SHOUTING)
On my mark.
2, 1, mark.
Drop! Drop! Drop!
Go, go, go, go!
(SCREAMING)
QUARITCH:
Brace!
It's Sully.
(ALARM BLARING)
Mask on!
Breach alarm!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(ROARING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
Come on.
Come to papa.
(NEYTIRI SCREAMING)
(HOWLING IN PAIN)
(SHRIEKS)
(GRUNTING)
(NEYTIRI GROANING)
(HISSING)
JAKE:
Give it up, Quaritch!
It's all over.
Nothing's over
while I'm breathing.
I kind of hoped
you'd say that.
(GRUNTING)
(ROARING)
(GASPING)
(GRUNTING)
(ALARM BEEPING)
Come on!
(GASPS)
Hey, Sully, how's it feel
to betray your own race?
(HISSING)
You think you're one of them?
Time to wake up.
(ALARM BLARING)
(JAKE GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(ALARM BLARING)
(COUGHING)
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(GROANS)
(GASPING)
(EXCLAIMS)
(GRUNTS)
(HISSING)
Jake?
(GASPING)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
Jake.
(PANTING SHALLOWLY)
(GASPS)
(EXHALES)
(MOANING)
Jake! Ma Jake!
(AIR HISSING FAINTLY)
(COUGHING)
(PRESSURIZING)
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
I See you.
Subtitles: Arigon
JAKE: The aliens went back
to their dying world.
Only a few were chosen to stay.
The time of great sorrow
was ending.
Toruk Macto was
no longer needed.
(SCREECHING)
Well, I guess this is
my last video log.
'Cause whatever happens tonight,
either way, I'm...
I'm not gonna be coming back
to this place.
Well, I guess I'd better go.
Yeah, I don't want to be late
for my own party.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah, it's my birthday,
after all.
This is Jake Sully
signing off.
(ALL CHANTING)
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(I SEE YOU PLAYING)
Walking through a dream
I see you
My light in darkness
breathing hope of new life
Now I live through you
and you through me
Enchanting
I pray in my heart
That this dream never ends
I see me through your eyes
Breathing new life,
flying high
Your love shines the way
into paradise
So I offer my life
I offer my love for you
And my heart was never open
And my spirit never free
To the world
that you have shown me
But my eyes
could not envision
All the colors of love
and of life evermore
Evermore
I see me through your eyes
Flying high
Your love shines the way
into paradise
So I offer my life
as a sacrifice
I live through your love
I live
Through your life
I see you