Can you return him alive to me?
Can you...?
You can't do a thing
Nothing!
Accidents some time affect
a patient's mind so much...
that they either lose their memory
or remember things very faintly
Medically, this state is
called retrograde amnesia
Patients like them
lead a normal life...
but they can't remember their past
That's just what has
happened to your daughter
Simply put,
she has lost her memory
With great difficulty we have
convinced her that you are her mother
Doctor, when will she
regain her memory?
It might take days,
months or even years
Or maybe she will never
regain her memory at all
She might have to spend
a lifetime in this state
Nothing can be said for sure.
We do try to make patients...
regain their memory by reminding
them of past incidents...
but that's not how
Tia's condition is
The slightest bit of pressure on
her mind can drive her insane
She could suffer a brain hemorrhage.
She could even die
This is why you must
hide from her...
the truth of her husband's death
and her son's identity
That's not all. You must destroy
all things that remind Tia of her past
If possible, take her to a place
where no one recognises her...
but do not try to remind her
of any old incident
Destroy all old memories
On this auspicious occasion
of her birthday...
I think I'd rather marry Tia
and take her away...
instead of giving her a present
But are you going to bother Tia
even after the wedding?
Absolutely. This fun and laughter
is what life is all about
It's great fun to be in a hospital.
Keep lying down like a Queen...
everyone runs around to serve you,
but I've never been ill!
Mother... please listen to me
That which is destined,
is what always happens
Good things and bad things
But I was terribly upset
to hear of your loss
Loss...?
This is the first time I've seen
death at such close quarters
This accident is going to
drive me mad, mother
Give me one chance, please!
Madam, the doctor has forbidden you
from disturbing the patient
You're the one who's
disturbing us
She's like my own daughter.
We're very close to each other
Aren't we, Tia?
But... who are you?
What? Haven't you recognised me?
- Mrs. Bharucha...
Tia, this is Mrs. Bharucha
But you...
- Mrs. Bharucha...
Doctor Modi wants to meet you.
- What for?
He wants to ask you something.
- Ask me...? Let's go
He's in his office. Let's go
Don't ever crack such
jokes again, Tia
Please have your medicine
What was she talking about?
- I don't know what she was saying
Please take your medicine
What if I had said more...?
Someone or the other is surely
going to remind her of the past
What are you thinking about?
Mrs. Bharucha speaks of one problem
There are going to be many more.
I know, mother...
you hate the sight of me. I'm
responsible for whatever has happened
But I want to stand by you
in this hour of crisis
I want to devote my entire life
in the service of your family
Sister... wounds heal with treatment
And grief is alleviated
when you share it
What do you want me to do?
To forget everything and forgive him?
Him?
Only till Tia regains her memory.
After that...
I'll accept any decision
the two of you take
Please give me one opportunity
to make up for my blunder
All right. So you don't want
to give my son this opportunity
Don't forgive him.
Do as you wish...
tell your daughter the truth
and kill her!
I'm trying to reason with her,
but she...
Madam, in a car accident,
people pay money to hush up matters
No one comes forward to take
responsibility for the dead or ailing
But my son has taken this step.
On his own responsibility...
he wants to take you folks
far away from this place...
so that no acquaintance
will rake up the past...
and become the reason
for her death
But you aren't letting that happen.
Because you own their lives, you see!
Because of my son's mistake,
Raj lost his life. But you...
you will lose your daughter because
of your arrogance and stubbornness
Whether you forgive my son or not,
you must at least think...
of your daughter and
your grandson's future
We were going to South Africa,
to your best friend Anita's house
When the car met with an accident...
Anita and Jai were also there
with you in the car
You lost your memory in the accident
and Anita lost her life
Anshu is Anita and Jai's son...
he loves you very much
You're his aunt, after all
If you stay with him, he won't
feel the absence of a mother
As the doctors have said...
there will be an improvement in your
health, if you go to a new place
That is why Jai is
taking us with him
Don't cry, Anshu...
enough, my child...
Give him to me
Come to me, my son...
come to your aunt
You're doing so much for us...
mother has told me
Don't say thanks, please
I'm the one responsible for
whatever has happened to you
The truth is that
when I think of your loss...
I find my own grief
to be so very little
My P.A., Swami
- How's the little boss..? Anuj!
You haven't recognised Uncle Swami?
- His name is Anshu, not Anuj
Sorry. Faux pas.
- You must think before you speak
She's stern.
- Bring the luggage in your car, Swami
They'll come in my car.
- Take the baby, Tia
Give him to me
Greetings, sir.
- Greetings
Get their luggage from the car
and show them to their room
If there is anything you need,
please let me know
Anshu's crying
Swami, why's he crying?
Looks like he needs servicing
We'll have to change his nappies
You mean me? I'm his dad, after all
When you grow up...
join the fire brigade!
Sir, here I go for a dry-cleaning
You don't know how to take care
of a child
I'll learn.
- Why haven't you yet?
I didn't have a child...
I mean, he always clung to his mother
Henceforth, he'll cling
to his aunt. Right, Anshu?
By the way, who has
he taken after?
He's exactly like his mother.
The same lovely eyes, the smile...
the beautiful moon-like face
Come, steal my heart...
my sweet little angel
Give me a smile...
I have always been
in love with you...
but how do I tell you?
You do not understand
how I pine
Come, steal my heart...
my sweet little angel
Give me a smile...
My life now revolves
around you
My hopes are all pinned on you
The sight of you
makes me realise...
you are the one
my breath is tied to
Make me forget my woes...
my sweet little child
Do smile, my sweet little angel
Come, steal my heart
I live in a world
of your memories
Never can my heart
ever forget you
You mean the life to me.
Come, let me show you...
every time my heart beats,
it craves for you
Put me to a test,
O sweet little angel...
Do smile...
O sweet little child
I have always been
in love with you...
but how do I tell you?
You do not understand
how I pine
Come, steal my heart...
my sweet little angel
Give me a smile...
my sweet little child
I've brought tea for you
Tea.
- No, I've already drunk some
Have it. I don't make a bad cuppa
It's so hot...
and you drank it all in one gulp?
Yes, actually I'm getting late
for my office
Sit down... while I finish my tea
So how did you find Cape Town?
- I have a long list...
how many things will I tell you about?
There are trees that remain standing
Mountains that don't
budge an inch
And the Sun... it rises and
sets at its own time
The atmosphere is pretty healthy
and cooperative out here
I've seen the morning,
evening and night...
I can see it all from your terrace.
Come over, if you have the time
I'll show you Cape Town too.
- In that case, get ready...
to take you around Cape Town
is my responsibility
This is Cape Town's most
interesting place
This is where the Atlantic Ocean
and the Indian Ocean...
after miles of journey,
leaving everything else...
merge together. From here begins
a new identity for them...
a new journey.
- And a new story
Like mine.
After losing my memory...
I am also moving in a new direction
I some times wonder
what my past was like
Was it better than what I have now?
Or did I lose something precious?
And then, I laugh it off
What is lost, is not coming back
And what I have,
I don't want to lose
You have come to terms with yourself
in this situation, Tia
But there are people in the world who
would want to live their lives again...
if they are given the opportunity
Jai, do you also look forward
to starting a new journey...
giving up the past like these oceans?
- Yes. I'm one of them too
But life doesn't give everyone
the opportunity
The past never returns...
memories are all we have
Shall we go?
Know what, Jai? I wondered how
I'd adjust life in this alien city
But you've made everything
so easy for me
In you, I've found a friend I
can be angry with, fight with...
and also love
How about an ice-cream?
Let's have our palms read
Sit down. I've shown many
people the right path
What are you getting into, Tia?
Come on
One moment... let's see
what he's going to say
Suspicions are but natural.
You can't control your mind
Extend your palm
without any hesitation, lady
Your nice times are about
to begin
A very bright future!
- Forget about the future
Can you tell me something
about my past?
About the days gone by?
- The days gone by...?
So you want to test
my prowess, I see!
Ask what you want to!
Without any hesitation
Who am I...?
- A girl, a female
Let's go, Tia.
- One second
Your past is all too clear
in your palm
Your past speaks of
a husband and a son
Let's go, Tia. Please.
- However...
your past is eclipsed
What does that laughter mean?
- You're getting it all wrong!
That isn't my past,
but it can very well be my future
I told you, they will say
anything for the money
Here you are. Let's go.
- It's God who gives
I'm only a medium! One day,
you will get to know the truth!
My predicition is never wrong.
- Don't take him seriously, Tia
They'll speak any lies for money
His lies could well prove
to be the truth
The truth is that you were
far away from me...
and I wanted to get close to you.
And now that you are close...
I must keep away from you
You have lost your memory.
And I've lost sight of my goal
I walk, but there is no path.
I live...
but I'm not among the living
Give me that photo.
- Can't I see Anita's picture?
Oh my heart...
this heart of mine...
oh this heart of mine...
when shall it be
worthy of you?
My heart...
I hear the bridal shehnai
being played at a distance...
and I dream
of a bridal palanquin
That I will be your bride...
says the chiming
of my anklets
Every step you take is towards me...
for I am your goal
Oh my heart...
this heart of mine...
when shall it be worthy of you?
I shall love you forever...
you're the one
I'm crazy about, my love
In what words will I tell you...?
this heart of mine
beats only for you
Do please solve this
predicament for me, my love
Oh my heart...
my heart...
when shall it be worthy of you?
My heart... oh my heart
How did you find Cape Town?
- It's nice
I slipped on the beach, Ma...
Tia, go to your room and change
All right
Tia's speaking the truth...
- I want no clarification!
If I have agreed
to stay with you...
it's only to keep
Anshu and Tia together
Do not try to take advantage
of my daughter's plight...
and drive her wayward.
- But mother...
I gave only Raj the right
to call me mother
You mustn't even dream
of taking his place
Not in my life,
not in Tia's
The father won't telephone
and the son shows airs!
Come, mother
Anshu's so cute, isn't he?
Do you like him?
Very much.
- Me too
How about everything else?
- Everything else?
Swami
And Jai?
What is the matter, mother?
You don't ever talk about Jai
Don't you approve of me
talking and joking with him?
Every relationship has
its limits, Tia
But a relationship of the heart
knows no limits, mother
Which is why, despite losing
everything, I have a mother like you...
a son like Anshu
and a friend like Jai
Jai has defined his
own limits, mother
It would be good for every one,
if he keeps to his limits
The girl I wanted to
make your daughter-in-law...
is in your house today, Ma
But I still can't make her
your daughter-in-law
All I'm destined to have is
Tia's company, Ma. Only her company
Not her love
You thought you'd
give me a surprise
But I found the opportunity first.
Right?
I have another surprise. Come on
Your jacket, sir
You may keep your bag at your side.
As for the food...
Chef Tia has personally
cooked your favourite dishes
How do you know these
are my favourite dishes?
When hearts meet, one gets to know
of the other's likes and dislikes
Like you found out that
blue is my favourite colour
Let's make a wish today
Maybe this is the moment that
will bring light into our lives
And what will I have to do?
Close your eyes
and make a wish
What happened, Jai?
- I'm very tired
At least have your food.
- I'm not hungry
Listen, Jai...
How helpless am I?
I'm a shattered man
My heart is sinking...
and the shores are close by
What do You want...?
What do You want after all?
You took away my memories.
But I didn't complain
I thought whatever You did,
was for the better
But why are You distancing
Jai from me?
Why don't You awaken love for me
in his heart?
Complaint aren't the solution
to your problems
Every setback ought to be
your ladder to move forth
Your determination will get stronger
and you'll get what you wouldn't have
That's easier said than done.
Mere words of courage that don't help
They do help, my child.
- Child...?
Who are you and how did you
get into the house?
I walked in through the door.
- The door...?
All right, but what are you
doing in this house?
I'm here to meet Jai.
- Do you know him?
I've heard of him, but we've
never done business together
You mustn't. He can't respect a girl.
What business will he do?
He can't concentrate on his work.
He'll ruin the whole business...
and bring the old man on the streets!
- Old man?
His dad
His dad, the old man! Thanks for
giving me the inside stuff
Can I solve any problem for you?
Weren't you talking about
a problem just now...?
Well, to my misfortune,
I've fallen in love with him
With Jai
But he won't even look at me.
The sonofagun!
Useless chap! He's earning
curses for his father!
There isn't another girl, is there?
I've been told that
Jai Mehta is a playboy
What...?
Get up! Up!
- What happened?
You don't even know Jai and
you're already bad-mouthing him?
Get out!
- Strange!
If I say something about him,
it's a bad thing
You weren't singing praises
for him just now, were you?
I'll go and tell Jai Mehta what
sort of people live in his house!
Who are you to interfere
in our family affairs?
Who...?
I'm the gun, and he's my son
You're his...?
- Father
Swami told me that you've arrived
You weren't even attending the
hotel's anniversary. I was...
The anniversary was just an excuse
Tell me something, my child
Are you convinced that Jai
is not in love with you?
Absolutely. There are only two
people who matter in his life
Anshu. And Anshu's mother
You're so right, my dear
But that which has gone away,
never comes back. Does it?
No
So Jai must also try to start
life afresh, mustn't he?
Yes, he must
After all, one accident isn't
bigger than life itself
It is. Some times,
an accident is so big...
life itself is dwarfed in front of it.
- May I say something?
Despite a journey of mishaps,
life still goes on
Absolutely right.
Yesterday is past-tense
It can't be changed.
- You're right
Nobody can change yesterday. It's
better to forget what has happened
It's time for Anshu's meal.
I'll attend to it
Whatever anyone says, my child,
I accept you as my daughter-in-law
You will have my support in anything
you do to win over Jai's heart
There's a party to celebrate the
anniversary of our hotel tomorrow
So...
I admit, there is a limit
to which love can go...
I do agree, there is
a limit to one's patience
I agree, my heart beats
only for my beloved
I agree, there is a limit
to which I can yield
My love, O my love...
O my love...
In love, when fear
gripped my heart...
this distance between us,
my heart could not take
I went so crazy,
I could understand nothing...
in love, when fear
gripped my heart...
this distance between us,
my heart could not take
Oh my love...
my love...
O my love, my love...
In love, I must live and die
Without love,
I have nothing else to do
I'm not going to fear
the world anymore
Love possesses
every heartbeat of mine
In love, when fear
gripped my heart...
this distance between us,
my heart could not take
O my love, my love...
To fall in love, isn't easy.
It's very difficult
Those that tread the path of love,
never find their goals
In love, you gain nothing
What is love...?
Nobody could ever understand
In love, when fear
gripped my heart...
this distance between us,
my heart could not take
I went so crazy,
I could figure out nothing
O my love, my love...
my love, my darling
I know how it feels when your love
is reciprocated with indifference
But I also know that you are
the only one Jai loves
I mean, you are the only one
Jai will love
We must find a way
to make Jai promise...
to make you my daughter-in-law
in the next 24 hours
Promise, my foot
He loves you very much, doesn't he?
- Oh yes, so...?
So...?
- So...!
Tia, why are you crying?
Jai, your dad has had
a heart attack!
Come home immediately!
Are these clothes okay
for the death scene?
She's talking to him! Any clothes
are okay for a death scene
Jai has left the office.
Get on with the preparations
I'm so nervous, I hope I don't
really have a heart attack
We'll handle it, if you do
The whole game depends on you!
- You remember the lines...?
My son...
- Wrong!
Your heart is on the left.
- All right
Jai, after you are dead...
- Speak the lines properly!
It's your death scene. Not Jai's!
Jai, my son... after I'm dead...
- Exactly! Get that!
My son, after I'm dead,
buy a new house for yourself
Make a new house, I say!
- Settle down! Not make a house
I see, so it's settle down!
- May I play the role?
I remember all the lines.
- Here comes another actor!
But this is an original play.
We can't change fathers!
May I say something,
if you don't mind?
You're a very bad actor.
You can't remember your lines!
Bring out the pain...?
- I'm trying...
I'm squeezing my sides,
but I feel no pain
Bring it out from the insides.
- I see, all right
Where are you going?
- You said inside, didn't you?
I mean, feelings from
inside your heart
Master Jai is here!
- Is he...?
Look, son. I've had a heart-attack...
- Go on inside!
What happened to dad?
- In your room upstairs
Have some holy water
Swami, what happened to him?
- He's going away
Tia, did you telephone a doctor?
- The doctor was here
He said it's too late.
There are no chances of survival
Hasn't Jai come as yet...?
- I'm right here, dad
What happened to you?
- Heart attack
You used to take such good
care of yourself. How did...
Quickly say what you've got to.
You don't have much time, uncle
That's right.
We can't see you suffering
My son, you'll have to do
what I ask of you today
Of course, I will.
- Promise me, Jai...
after I die...
- Keep talking. Don't stop
It'll relieve you of the burden.
- Say it
After I'm dead, make a house...
settle down
But dad...
- Don't refuse, Jai
You've given me your word.
You'll do as I say
Anshu needs a mother
for his upbringing
I want you to settle down
with Tia
With me...?
- Anshu won't call you aunt
He'll call you mother.
Mother!
If you wish, for Anshu's sake,
I will...
Tia has agreed to the wedding
And Anshu's so happy
with the development
Promise me... that you
will marry Tia alone
But you know...
He's gasping for breath!
Say yes!
I promise...
- Will you marry me?
What are you staring at?
Nothing's wrong with me!
I'm fit as a fiddle!
The heart-attack...?
- There was nothing! Nothing!
I wanted you to promise that you
love Tia and that you'll marry her
And you said it!
Does anyone joke around
with death?
Perhaps you forget.
Tia's is the mother of Raj's child
Perhaps you even forget
that it is your son...
who has brought Tia
to this state
You also forget that Tia is leading
a life of illusions
The day she gets
to know the truth...
she will start hating you
and your son
You seem to have
forgotten everything
All right
But you must not forget,
Tia's mother is still alive
It would be better if you kept
only your duties in mind...
and left my daughter's and
my grandson's future to me
I seek your forgiveness
for whatever happened today
But if you could forgive Jai...
I understand your feelings.
But before you make any decision...
about your daughter's
and grandson's future...
please open this boxes
and take a look
After that, I will respect
whatever you decision you take
Good bye
Red: Bridal Wear
White: For widows
Come to your aunt
Tia, Jai's father came to me to
ask for your hand in marriage
I have agreed
You were against it till last night.
So what happened?
All of last night, your words
echoed in my mind...
that relationships of the heart
know no limits
I can't live with Anshu
And Anshu cannot live
without you
And you... without Jai
This is why I have
accepted the proposal
But Jai always keeps
a distance from me...
I know. He stays aloof,
only because of me
When you tell him that
I have consented...
he'll surely agree
Do you want me to
have a word with him?
No, mother.
The past is sure behind me
But I want to see my future
bright and clear
I want to know what's
in Jai's mind
I'll break the news to him
Anshu, you will call me mother,
won't you?
Once he starts, you're the
only one he'll call mother
You have found your mother
You have found your mother, Anshu
Tia's life isn't like a piece
of blank paper, Ma
It's stained with blood.
Because of me
She's in love with me today. But
what if she gets to know the truth?
For my happiness,
I can't forget the past
I can't forget it. I can't
You had once forgotten everything
and prayed for a new life, Jai
Tia...?
God has today heard your
prayers and mine, Jai
You don't understand
My mother has consented
to our wedding
My palms will now be adorned
with bridal henna for you
I shall apply the
bridal vermillion for you
That's not possible.
- Not possible?
Man doesn't stop living when he
loses his dear ones, does he?
Both of us have had to
go through the accident, Jai
It's just that I didn't express
the anguish I felt
I'm fumbling in darkness, Jai.
With just a lamp of hope
You are my lamp of hope, Jai
You... you won't understand
my compulsions
Nobody understands it.
- What compulsion is that?
My conscience is stopping me, Tia.
- Conscience...?
So why did you buy that gift for me?
Why did you write my name on it?
Why can't you tell me how you feel?
Why don't you admit that you love me?
Because I can't forget my past.
- You will have to forget it!
Tia... what happened?
Why are you crying?
We are not staying here anymore.
- What's wrong?
Where is the need to tell Tia?
What has happened is in the past!
You forgot the doctor's words?
She could have a brain hemorrhage!
She could go mad!
Yes, I've gone mad!
I don't want to live with Jai!
And what happens of Anshu...?
- It's Jai's duty to think of him
When he won't take me as his wife,
how can I be his child's mother?
Anshu is Tia and Raj's son
When she gets to know that,
what will she think of me?
Are you then waiting for her
to regain her memory?
So that she becomes a widow
and starts hating you?
No! But I know what I'm doing!
You're giving her more trouble
by spurning her
You're snatching away from her
the joys of her future
Calm down, my child.
I'll make Jai see reason
No, you are not doing that.
I don't want any pity!
But my child...
- You called me your child, right?
So come with me. Right now!
- We can't go away, Tia
You can't be my mother!
Tia! Listen to me!
Where are you going?
Jai! Tia has sped away in the car!
Stop her!
In love, I must live and die
Without love,
I have nothing else to do
Love is the intoxication
clouds my eyes
in love, when fear
gripped my heart...
this distance between us,
my heart could not take
Oh my love...
my love...
Tia! Stop there!
What's gotten into you?
Have you gone mad?
I'll do what I want to.
Who are you to stop me?
Let me die!
- Will death set everything right?
Yes, it will. Leave me alone!
- You're thinking only about yourself
You don't care for others.
- There is no one!
That's not true, Tia.
- That is the truth too!
Every relationship is fake...
- Nothing is fake
It's just that you don't understand.
- I don't want to understand!
Whatever we are doing
is only for your welfare
I don't want anyone's sympathies!
I don't need anyone!
I don't want to live anymore!
- You will have to live!
For your mother.
For your son Anshu...
What did you say...?
Anshu... my son?
Is Anshu my son?
Wasn't he born to you and Anita...?
Tell me the truth, Jai
Or else...
- Anita was only my friend
I was never married
The accident in which
you lost your memory...
killed not just Anita...
it killed Raj too.
- Raj...? Who's Raj?
Your husband
My husband...?
Yes, Tia.
You were married to Raj
You and Raj were in your car
when it collided with mine
I'm your culprit
I'm the one because of whom
this accident took place
Anshu lost his papa
Anshu is your son and Raj's...
not mine
Anshu... my son!
Because of what the doctor said...
- No, mother...
I had to lie to you
To keep you alive, Tia
I did whatever I had to, for the
sake of my daughter and my grandson
But it's Jai who has made
the biggest sacrifice
He has done more than his bit
And still, he mustn't
have spoken his heart
No, let me talk today
Know what, Tia? You are the only
girl he has ever loved in his life
Only you. Not just now...
from even before you got married
But he lives with a guilt complex.
He hopes for your memory to return...
so you will pronounce a punishment
for what he did
That accident was part
of my destiny, Jai
If not you, someone else
would have collided into us
If my words will help taking
the burden off your chest...
I do forgive you
Where are you going?
Uncle, despite being told everything
and getting to know the truth...
why don't I recall my past?
But I know today that
I'm a mother, I'm a widow
But Tia...
- No, Jai
You've tolerated me enough.
Not anymore
Wait, Tia. For my sake
You're only thinking about
yourself and your child, Tia
For you, I was a married man
and a father till yesterday
So why didn't all this
occur to you then?
You know why, Tia?
Because you're in love with me
What if I tell you today that I
love you more than I ever did...
and that I won't be able
to live without you?
If I tell you today that I want to
give Anshu the love of a father...
and my name... what will you do?
Will you marry me?
My Ma has today found
her daughter-in-law
And Anshu has found his father