Sorry
- I said, I'm sorry.
- Being sorry won't change facts
- Then you tell me what I should do.
- Can anything be done anymore?
- That's my point, what can I do?
- Shame on you, Sanjay
- You'll never know a girl's mind.
- But I can try. One more chance...?
Don't even talk to me
- Will you say something?
- You just said don't talk to me.
- What's my problem?
- You're no good at relationships.
- I'm sorry, Ria.
- What use being sorry now?
I'm really very sad.
I loved her so much.
And she dumped me, just like that?
It didn't take her even 20 minutes...
to get over a 20 day affair.
Broke my heart.
Sonia, you've hurt me.
My heart's broken.
For the 8th time, Mr Sanjay Malhotra
in the last 11 months
Now get up and get it over with
Ria... listen to me
But one point. Over the last 11 months
8 girls broke my heart...
but only after I won their hearts, no?
Follow your heart, you can change the
world. 8 girls, 9th can't be too far
That's Sanjay and Ria.
But this isn't their story
This is Sanjay's and Anjali's story.
Sanju and Anju, who became friends...
long before they knew what friendship
meant. All they knew was...
they couldn't live
without each other
One minute, what's wrong?
Was touching her a crime?
You want what I want
- Tell me, it's thrilling, isn't it?
- Not another word
At my touch she becomes unworthy
of you? You care so much? What's she?
- Your fief, private property, what?
- Friend
Friends! Hear that? Can a boy and
a girl ever be friends?
See for yourself, that's an example
of friendship
What a pretense
Prem...
A boy and a girl can never be friends.
Actually it's a...
You forgot the lines! I win the bet.
So you get to do the cooking
- I didn't lose.
- No...?
- I was thinking...
- Thinking? What?
This is a film, right?
With films, it's different
But in real life, can a boy and
a girl be friends?
When a boy and a girl are friends
they either fall in love...
or else, they part ways
In any eventuality,
the friendship is terminated
Of course there can be a friendship
between boy and girl.
Look at us
You are a girl, I'm a boy. Between us
there's none of your so-called "love"
Our story is different.
We did go around for a week
But I knew on day three that
nothing could be more foolish...
than falling for you.
You get that?
Don't you forget, Ria Chowdhury was
the first girl who ditched you
Thank you for saving me!
As if she's some beauty queen
If you may spare some time off your
busy schedule, then it's for you
Anju's...?
How was your trip? Was America fun?
How are your parents?
America was fun!
Mummy-Daddy enjoyed themselves
- I returned 3 weeks ago.
- And you're calling me now?
- I hope you didn't forget my list?
- Yes, I picked up everything
But hear me out first.
This is very important
- Sanju...
- Yes tell me
I'm getting married, Sanju
The wedding is next month.
Everyone is coming
You got to be there too.
Come over, quick
- You're... getting married?
- You never get anything fast, do you?
Now don't waste time, just pack and
take the first flight to Delhi
If you aren't here by tomorrow evening
...Sanju, are you listening?
Not just you. Everyone's surprised.
Everything happened so soon...
Just come over, I'll tell
you everything
I'm a bit busy for a few days.
Say hi, to Anu and your parents
I can't believe this...
she's getting married?
Who's upto what?
Anju... Anjali is getting married
- Wonderful news, no?
- Yes, I'm glad, very happy, I'm thrilled
- You don't seem so.
- What rubbish
I'm glad, very happy, thrilled!
It's only a bit sudden
Anjali, your childhood friend?
Childhood? Ever since...
she was four and I was five.
And we were always together
School, college...
we were like buddies
- How silly of Anjali...
- Anjali... has a lovely smile?
- Thinking her smiling makes me smile.
- And your cheese omelettes?
It's Anjali who makes the real
cheese omelettes.
In comparison, I'm sordid
But how come you...? How come you
know all this about Anjali?
I know only bits and pieces.
But I'd like to know more.
Want to tell me?
- What do you want to know?
- About your friendship
About your Anju.
About Anju!
How do I tell you...?
How do I introduce her?
"Here's a girl"
"What can I tell you about her?"
"She's crazy"
"She's different"
"Every moment..."
"there's something new about her"
"They shower flowers upon her path
and heads turn, wherever she goes"
"Oh what can I tell you about her?"
Tell me more about her
"She'll throw a tantrum"
"But then she comes around..."
"with a smile"
"She'll be quiet, without a word"
"And then she'll start humming..."
"a sweet song"
"How do I describe her?"
"She's only like herself"
"They shower flowers upon her path and
heads turn, wherever she goes"
"What can I tell you about her?"
You miss her?
"Every moment..."
"I spent with her"
"I dream of, I don't know why..."
"Memories..."
"of that parting"
"hurt me,
I don't know why..."
"Now we have parted"
"But I pray for you,
my friend"
"May you find flowers upon your path
and make heads turn, wherever you go"
"Oh what can I tell you about her?"
Stop pacing and say something.
I'm wondering...
whether I ought to tell you.
Why not?
You can't take the truth.
Come on, out with it...
whatever this truth is.
And you will hear me out?
I will, most patiently. I won't scream,
I won't say "what rubbish"
The truth is, you are in love
with Anjali
I know you think, I'm talking rubbish.
Because you don't realise...
you're in love with Anjali.
From Dehradun to Bombay...
you didn't take this trip alone.
Anjali came too, hidden in your heart
And in every girl you met afterwards,
you tried to find Anjali
Sonia. Her tresses reminded
you of Anjali
Megha. Her cheese omelettes
were passable
One Ria too. Her smile was
somewhat like Anjali's
But not Anjali. And how could
you find another? Anjali is unique
Every girl who looked into your eyes
found, not to herself, but someone else.
That was Anjali.
Do you read, Mr Sanjay Stupid Malhotra?
The absolute truth about your life
Absurd
See...? I didn't crack up, never said,
"what rubbish", never even got angry
In spite of the fact that I never
heard such a stupid theory
I said it in the beginning,
you can't take the truth
You are getting irritated.
Anjali and I...
how did you imagine?
Given brains, you'd imagine too.
What rubbish, what rubbish, what rubbish
- Anjali and I are friends, period.
- No point talking to you
Listen to me
- Not a word.
- I don't want to talk to you, either
No one cares to listen
You were right
- We men are very selfish.
- If you insist, I'll accept
No, it's true.
Men are dogs
And our convictions are so convenient
I too concluded so conveniently
that Anjali is mine
I mean, she'll always be
where she is...
waiting for me to marry her
when it's convenient for me
I never considered she's human.
That she has her desires, her dreams
But what if I'm not part
of her dreams?
Never imagined, someone else
could come into her life
And how would Anjali possibly know
something I never told myself?
But then, how could I have
told her?
Only today I have come to know
how dearly I love her
Today...
when she is about to marry
someone else
I can understand, Sanjay. Some things
can be comprehended only out of loss
So what will you do now?
The 8:40 flight
You're... going... to Dehradun?
I know you're going to be hurt
to see this wedding happen
Anjali is about to marry someone else
and yet, you're...?
Ria, you don't understand.
Yes, I'm going
But not to attend the wedding,
I'm going to break it up
Anjali is only about to marry someone
else, she hasn't done it yet
She'll marry only me
Because, if you follow your heart...
You can change the world?
"May joys abound"
"May health abound"
"May goodwill abound"
"May sorrow be dispelled"
"May peace abound"
Peace? How am I to keep my peace?
Please, don't be cross.
Anjali is like a daughter to you
That's exactly why, Vishnu!
This I shall grudge you forever
I am her uncle. And you finalised
her wedding without consulting me?
- Goodness!
- You're creating a problem for nothing
Now I am "for nothing"!
You be my judge, who's the elder?
- You are my elder.
- And I'm older than you are
- I have finalised this match.
- Look, mother...
- Now what's your problem?
- You're always butting-in
Shut up and touch the sacred fires.
Then embrace your brother
Come on brother, -You'll take
a thrashing someday
My husband is a little scared of you.
But my brother-in-law too?
No, his wife scares him worse
I'm not afraid of anyone.
Pull down the wall, I say
Ma, if the door isn't facing east...
Mother-in-law, you'll pull down walls?
Just for the wedding?
My dear anglicised son-in-law...
I'd rather tear down walls than
defy the scriptures
Bridegrooms never enter from the west!
Good God! This is sacrilege
So what Kappo? Lord Rama entered
from the west when he went to wed
- How come?
- Ayodhya is west of Mithila
- How could you forget that?
- How could you forget dear brother?
Lord Rama was exiled for 14 years.
Had he observed the scriptures...
Lord Rama would've been happy, no?
Can you match that?
Our sister-in-law is matchless!
Convinced him, at long last
I wonder if I could've convinced him
to get married
Anju's wedding is going to be fun!
This sister-in-law of mine...
happens to be everyone's favourite!
And our wedding was no less grand
Yes, but there's no sign of the one
who regaled everyone at your wedding
- Who...?
- Sanju
- Bahadur Singh, are the gates washed?
- Yes
Plant the new saplings
You said the prayers without
waiting for me?
- Sorry "girlfriend", I'm late.
- Not too late
- There's much you can do.
- That's why, I've come
- Hello Uncle!
- There you are
- All set?
- All upset
The engagement is next Sunday.
And everyone is in an uproar
I'm going to the office.
You've got to take care of everything.
- Has everyone arrived?
- Everyone.
- Uncle, aunt...?
- Both
- I better time my entry.
- Rascal! Go in, I'll join you
Take in Sanjay's luggage
- I'll be back in two hours.
- No, please...
Hey girl...
I'll pull your hair
Stay back
First, have you found someone who can
straighten you out? A nice girl, like me?
Now... what can I say.
You married him and broke my heart
Somehow, I found someone.
Now I hear she's getting married too
- Nice girl?
- Nice? Mind-blowing
- More mind-blowing than me?
- You're unsurpassable
She's somewhat like you.
Could be a little sister to you?
Oh, but what good is all that now?
That boy is incorrigible
- My obeisances to the Aunt. Bless you...
- Enough, enough, enough...
Aren't you a bit too early for a
post-wedding appearance?
I would have come earlier were it not
for a black cat that crossed my path
- Goodness! And then?
- I took a round trip to get here
- That's the right thing to do.
- Forget all that
- Have you met Anju?
- I'll be seeing her
Look her up, before I leave...
I mean, I got to be going out
How's the business?
How is Wall Street treating you?
- Anjali is upstairs.
- Upstairs... Anjali
Yes, go on
Sanju Uncle!
Hi! Kutkut, You recognised me?
- Yes and Grandpa wants to see you.
- Good Lord!
- Obeisances, Uncle.
- Keep the obeisances for later
First, out there in Bombay
have you married secretly?
- Good Lord!
- Good Lord! Without your approval...
- Can I ever marry?
- Look at him, how understanding
What a good boy! And take our Anjali
...have you met her?
- Sanju! You haven't met Anjali yet?
- No Nilu-didi
But why is everyone all
agog about Anjali?
- Sanju, what's this I hear?
- Hello Grannie
Bless you. Haven't you seen Anju yet?
I will, I will, please sit down
- What's the hurry?
- But of course...
Sanju! Here you are...
Anjali is waiting for you
- Where...?
- Upstairs. Now come on
- Let me say hi to the others.
- Later. Now come along
Oh come on, we've been expecting you
for ages. I mean, Anjali is waiting
- Waiting for me... why?
- Would I know?
It's between you and your Anjali.
Go, she's waiting. Excuse me
Now he's floored
Today, little Anju, you've had it
Getting smart with Sanju?
- You aren't giving me the slip.
- Come on
Let me see how can you
escape from me
- Nice couple, no?
- Yes.
Could've been better
Could've been you
That's what I always thought.
Whatever we think... marriages
are made in Heaven
Could've been different.
Nilu could've been my Aunt Nilu
"If you're in love,
why is the heart afraid of love?"
- Hello, how are you?
- Hello Mr Khanna
- Weren't you supposed to come yesterday?
- If you wish, I'll leave
You see, I just couldn't stay away.
Went to Delhi for few days
But couldn't stay there.
Where's our girl? Where's Anjali?
- I'm here.
- There she is
- Samosas. For you.
- Bless you
No. First, what did you
get from Delhi?
Blackmailing me? Wait...
till you're married. Then I'll make you
cook hot samosas for me every day
I could cook for you. But your son, the
doctor, will he let you eat fries?
Between you and I and samosas
how did that fool crop up?
When is Rohit coming?
Sanjay, come over here
- Sanjay. He's Mr. Malhotra's son.
- The late Mr. Malhotra...?
- The one whose house I bought?
- Yes
So you are Sanjay!
Though we've never met,
I know your entire history
Anju speaks so much about you.
Whenever she's at our place...
she starts reeling off, here's Sanju's
room, this is where we played carrom...
so on and so forth.
Do come over some day
- It's your house.
- Was. Now it's yours
Anjali still calls it
Sanju's house
Silly, doesn't even realise
where she's going
After Mr. Malhotra died in the accident,
he moved to Bombay. Settled down well
Destiny is strange. Motherless boy,
at 20, he lost his father too
But he didn't break down
I like that boy
This is still here?
Last year...
there was talk of cutting down this
branch. For 3 days, I cried
I went on hunger strike for 2 days
and at last, Papa relented
Why not let him cut it if he wants?
How could I...? You made this swing
For hours we sat on this swing
as we plotted our mischief
- Come, sit.
- I hope it doesn't break
If it hasn't broken in all these years
how can it break now? Come
You see? An old relationship
never lets you down
- Go on, shoot.
- What...?
I know what's your tricky head
is full of
- Full of what?
- Questions, countless questions
- About him.
- About whom?
About Rohit, stupid. Who else?
Everyone is asking about him
But I haven't told anyone anything
Because I wanted you
to be the first to know
Rohit... where do I begin?
Last year... Rohit's father came
to live in your house.
Papa told you, no?
Rohit has never come here.
Lives in America. He's a doctor
His father is a very nice person.
He started socialising with us
His house was always like a second home
to me, ever since your times
Everyone was worried about my trip
to America.
Rohit was out there. Uncle Khanna
assured us, there's no reason for worry.
That assured Papa
But I was so apprehensive.
Remember, I called you from the airport?
The prospect of travelling to America
all alone was so daunting
You were the one who gave me courage.
Were it not for your encouragement...
I might never have met Rohit
Takes a fool to shoot himself
in the leg
and I stepped right into the gun?
That a few days with Rohit would lead
us into this, I never expected
We hadn't quite met each other,
hardly had we got to know each other...
when his father made the proposal.
Papa asked me and I said yes
And look, we're getting ready
for the wedding
Sanju I need you to encourage me
once again.
I'm so nervous
Getting married for the
first time, you see
But now you're here and I know.
Everything is going to be fine
Mine is going to be
one memorable wedding
Anjali, over here...
Coming, Didi (Didi: Sister)
One memorable wedding, for sure.
You won't forget it. Nor your Rohit
- Your paan.
- Paan? Thanks
I've had a word with the priest.
The kulfi supplier is confirmed. 5,500
Bagged the queen already?
He still needs a cover for score
Here you go
Uncle, bad luck! Lost your queen
- For him, nothing new.
- What do you mean?
Means nothing.
Just put your heart into the game.
Winning, losing... makes no difference.
Right?
Now what's on your mind?
- Rohit.
- What about Rohit?
Unlike you, I know nothing about him.
Know what? He's a doctor
- Where?
- In America
Where in America?
You got an address?
A telephone number? Something?
Anjali would know.
Is that all you care for her?
About the two of you, he wanted
to satisfy himself fully
While you were waiting for approvals.
He was investigating you thoroughly
Before the wedding was finalised,
he had every detail about you
Your photo was vetted even by the
farthest-flung relative
Naturally, it's a brother's duty to vet
his sister's prospective suitors
And how have you investigated Rohit?
You don't even have his numbers
Sanju, think before you speak.
Sorry, I said what I felt right
Strange, no?
Here's a wedding in the offing and
no one has even seen the boy's photo?
Well, modern times
Look, nothing's wrong
He belongs to a nice family.
And we were from bad ones?
- No, I mean, his parents are nice.
- And our parents were bad?
- Photo! Must-see!
- You must show us a photo
Quiet, I'm telling you.
Why are the kids after you, Anjali?
- She won't show us his photo.
- Whose photo?
- Her fiance's.
- I don't have any photos
Yes, she has his photo.
Uncle, will you scold them?
Kids, stop harassing her
and get lost
Come on, sit beside me
- Come on, show it to me.
- What?
Your fiance's photo
Go on, let him see the photo.
In my time, I went to town...
with your grandfather's photo.
I showed him off to everyone...
the barber, the tailor, the confectioner
You can see Rohit when he comes.
Day after tomorrow
Upto you if you want to wait
till day after
But the eager will come to
Sanju, the magic man
The bridegroom's photo.
How did he get his hands on it?
Rohit's photo?
Where did you find it?
I know every inch of your room
Sanju... don't you dare...
"I just heard..."
"you've chosen a mate for life"
"Now that you've made your choice..."
"tell us what is he like?"
"He's incomparable"
"He's smart and he's straight"
"And everyone thinks he's nice"
"He never lies"
"He never poisons minds"
"At heart, he's clean and honest"
"Understand, kid?"
"Tell me, or can't you?"
"What's his species?"
"Unlike you, he isn't trash"
"He belongs to the new age"
"Did you take pity on him?"
"Did he come crying to you?"
"Tell me, trust me"
- "I know what you're getting at"
- "I warned her"
"Got to investigate boys, you know"
"Be quiet"
"We just heard..."
"you've chosen a mate for life"
"But why did you have to make
such a choice?"
"What a choice"
"Does he keep mum? Is he a chatterbox?
How boring is he?"
"Wherever he is, he makes
such sparkling conversation"
"Is he Indian? Is he British?
"Is he an oaf? Is he witty?"
"Is he brave, like me?"
- "Is he useless?"
- "How good will he be as a husband?"
"Just make sure he isn't like him"
"Surely not that type"
"We just heard..."
"you've chosen a mate for life"
"Well, now that you've made
your choice..."
"will you tell us what he's like?"
"Whatever you heard,
is absolutely correct"
"I have chosen my mate, but why should
I tell you about him?"
Can I take a walk?
Whose wedding is it?
Who's arriving? Rohit!
Then Rohit get's red carpet
Move it... not on that.
Get lost
One minute
- Strange! No obeisances?
- Good Lord!
Bless you.
Before anyone else...
I wanted to pay my respects to you.
Bless me...
that I may imbibe at least in part...
the ethics and the morality that
you have taught everyone
May such come to be
- Obeisances, Uncle.
- May you live long
On my way, I carried oblations from
the temple of the Mother Goddess
Aunt, this book is for you.
Feng shui
What's that?
Ancient scriptures from China
- Scriptures!
- Your favourite, no?
Wonderful! May you live long
Were I a son in this house
instead of a son-in-law...
you'd surely expect that before
I pay my respects to you...
I must obeisances to grandmother
and then to uncle and aunt
That's why...
- I hope I wasn't wrong.
- Oh no
Bless you
Bless you, son
Welcome Mr. Khanna
Will you never enter the sea?
Will you only watch from ashore?
Why drown yourself to learn what
someone else's mistakes can teach you?
You... must be Sanjay?
Guy Number Two who's close to Anjali.
Number One
Number Two, is you
Just like Anjali described you.
Where's my Anjali?
Lord...
now I'm here
Let not this silly girl
pester You any longer
She can ask me for anything
she wants
- Rohit, what are you doing here?
- Like you, praying
This is unbecoming of you
I asked your grandmother's permission.
What have you done?
I've fallen in love with you
- Now what do you want?
- I've travelled far
I ought to be rewarded
As of now, you're in a temple.
Oblations, is all you'll get here
Period
I'm making do, Lord.
But You must intercede
How can he better you?
Sanjay is the best
No Ria. I was over-confident.
But I don't compare with him
I think I should cook up an excuse
and leave tomorrow itself
Is Anjali there?
Where can she go?
I mean, is she there with you?
Can you see her?
Yes, I can see her.
Only Anjali?
You see what you're leaving behind?
You did it once
A second time...?
Will you be able to forgive yourself?
Do you still want to come back?
No, not without Anjali
And... that Rohit?
Rohit? Forget it, Sanjay is the best
There you are Sanju. Anu and Rajesh
are expecting you for breakfast
- It's stuffed fried pancakes.
- I prefer this sweet you make
Put that back.
It's for offering to the Gods
Okay
Call Anjali. She hasn't had breakfast,
isn't out of bed. What's she upto?
- Say that again.
- Anjali
My name sounds so different
when I hear you speak it
Say my full name
The name that's going to be mine
Anju, your mother wants you downstairs
Put the phone down.
If you want to go, you disconnect
You know it, I can't disconnect
until you disconnect
Disconnect
No, you do it
Let's do it
at the count of three
One
Two
Three
You haven't disconnected yet
No, how many times?
Disconnect... Please
Done. Now come on
Disconnected?
Rohit, your chocolate and ma'am,
your boring strawberry
- What's so boring?
- You'll only find out...
Once you try another flavour.
Have you ever tried anything else?
None of your fault, though.
It's your life that's so boring
Look at me, some black currant,
some mango, dash of mint
Lollipop, also. Variety my dear,
is the spice of life.
Say what?
But when I look at you,
I think your life's boring too
In your life, I'm sure,
Anjali is the first and last girl
You mean, you had girlfriends?
Before Anjali?
Girls, who make friends.
But more girl than friend, yes?
Rohit, how come I know nothing
about your girlfriends?
Maybe because... you don't know?
You never told her?
I always wanted to tell you.
But you always said...
you aren't interested in my past.
I wasn't. Now I am
Me too. Go on tell us.
Fine. Our relationship...
will be grounded in truth.
Ask whatever you wish.
You got the right to know
What we want to know is,
how many girlfriends?
Count
- I think four, no actually, five.
- Five? How long ago was this fifth?
Say, three months.
When you were seeing me...
you had a girl friend?
Yes, but...
when I saw you for the first time
I realised that you are the girl...
I want to spend a lifetime with.
I told her, she understood
Really? That's so amazing!
Why get worked up over that?
Everyone has a past. It's natural.
If you had a past, I won't get upset
Anjali's past! I'm Anjali's past!
Boring as her life is...
there was no friend, except me.
No chance of your getting upset
Sanjay, don't but in.
Rohit, I'm really hurt
You shouldn't have hidden it from me.
What's there to be hidden?
Why didn't you tell me?
What's there to be told?
Not to be told and nothing to hide?
What's this all about?
- Nothing. For nothing, Anjali...
- For nothing...?
My fiance has had five affairs
and till this day, I don't know?
- Three happened when I was in school.
- I don't want to hear anything
People are staring.
Not for another minute... do I wish to
embarrass you, Mr. Rohit Khanna
- Sanju, will you drop me home?
- May I have my ice cream? No...? Okay
Got to go
You're so nice, but that's
also why you must die
You got to go, Rohit. Go away
from Anjali. Far away. Forever
Poor guy
Was nice
I ought to be thanking you.
Even unwittingly...
You've played a major role in
cementing my relationship with Anjali.
How so...?
Back in America... Anjali told me about
the swing you rigged up for her.
For her... it's a cherished childhood
memory.
- And guess what I did?
- What?
I rigged a swing too.
Then I did it up with flowers,
and I held her eyes shut...
as I took her to sit on the swing
and that was when I asked her...
Anjali, will you marry me?
She opened her eyes, saw the swing
And she gave me a quiet smile
Till this day I don't know what
she smiled at. Me? Or the swing?
The swing, of course
Yesterday, Anjali misbehaved with you.
In your place, I'd stop talking to her
- What? I was about to call her.
- How silly
You see Rajesh?
You'll end up like him. Henpecked
- Take my advice, you needn't call her.
- Why?
She fought with you.
Let her apologise
- But Sanjay...
- Trust me, I know her
You needn't say a word. Tonight, at the
engagement, she will apologise
How about a light massage for me?
- What did he say on the phone?
- Nothing?
- But he surely said something?
- He never even called
- Doesn't he call every morning?
- All except this morning
- Maybe he's jogging.
- That was hours ago
- Was he all right?
- He was enjoying himself
Said he had a good night's sleep
and he was looking so fresh
- I think he's still annoyed.
- Annoyed he is
- So that's why he never called.
- That's like a man
Not crazy, like me. In his place,
I would've called ten times by now
And I would've realised my mistake
and I would've apologised
But not Rohit. He'll never do that.
Because he knows...
If he takes the first step,
you will forever have the upper hand
And Rohit is unputdownable.
He's so smart
I could never be as clever.
I'll slave for my wife
You wanted to say sorry, no?
Go ahead. He isn't stone-hearted
He will forgive you.
Why should Anjali apologise?
Rohit is to blame for making
a mountain for a molehill
Anu, he is Anjali's fiance.
She can misbehave with her friends
- She can do it to me. But Rohit...
- I can do it to Rohit too
And you needn't take sides with Rohit.
Whose friend are you? Mine or his?
And I won't to talk to him unless he
calls me. Tell your clever friend that
But Anjali...
Anu...
Sanjay, you're a genius
Nice pair
Could be nicer
Could be... someone else?
Could be... you...?
Didn't I tell you?
Marriages are made in Heaven
And I say, follow your heart
and you can change the world
- Meaning...?
- It's no more than an engagement
Whether it will culminate
in a wedding...?
- I do not understand...
- Keep watching. You'll get to know
"The braves will carry
their brides home"
- Why aren't you talking to me?
- I don't want to talk to you
Are you annoyed?
- Why didn't you call me?
- You didn't call me either
Bachelor party?
- Will be great fun man!
- What gives you those grins?
Tomorrow, we're having
a bachelor's party
- I said, I don't want to discuss it.
- What would you rather discuss?
- When are we coming back from America?
- What...?
I asked, after the wedding, when do we
come on vacations from America?
Whenever you wish.
Let's get married first
- Are you trying to be evasive?
- Evasive? What are you saying?
We got to decide these things
before we get married
- Really?
- Yes
But make sure no one
gets an inkling
- No one gets an inkling.
- Not a soul
No one gets to know
- No one gets to know, what?
- Nothing
I Rohit Khanna...
swear by God...
that after I'm married...
My wife Anjali...
once every year...
sometimes twice a year...
- We never discussed twice a year.
- You said, whenever I wish
Yes, whenever. But twice a year?
Are you trying to tell me... that I
can't come visiting twice a year?
The home where I spent my entire
childhood... where my parents live...
Yes Anjali, but in some years...
we might not be able to make it twice
I'm a doctor, I got to work,
build a career
Your career means everything?
My parents mean nothing?
You won't even give me
such a small request?
How about celebrating this half
of a wedding over dinner?
Already at it?
Wonderful
But why go partying so far away?
- These bachelor parties... are best
done on the sly. - But why?
Because if we women get to know of
their antics, these men have had it
- Will there be song and dance?
- And women
My sister-in-law says, you got to
see one of these parties...
- ...to see what scoundrels men can be.
- Then I'm going, for sure
For all his naive looks, who knows
your brother might be a scoundrel
I'm going too.
Must see what Naren is upto
I got to keep an eye on Raju.
And there's Rohit. It's said...
the bachelor who's being given the
party might do just about anything
Let's see what Rohit demands
Wonderful party
He has organised this party
Cigarettes?
- Ajit too? What a revelation!
- Now I know!
- Sanju said it'd be a lively party...
- I know, where are the babes?
I can't wait!
Be patient and you will
be rewarded, sweetly
I don't mind the sours,
but I can't wait
At this grievous juncture...
before another bachelor falls
to the blade of matrimony...
here's from me and from the
brotherhood of bachelors...
a requiem, in the words
of Mr Sanjay Malhotra
Today, weds my friend.
But I am not happy
Love, culminates into marriage.
But I'm far from happy
I stopped him, I even tried
to reason with him
For friendship's sake,
I told him
I posed obstacles for him,
I lay a thorn in his path
Like a blossom,
I even tried wilting
He's walking away with the most
beautiful flower of Spring...
it's like a wedding in Eden.
But I'm far from happy
At my friend's wedding,
I'm unhappy
Love, culminating into marriage
but I'm far from happy
"Swaying, gyrating..."
"lighting fires in hearts..."
"with my eyes"
"Spark"
"I'm a spark"
"My body is like flame"
"Don't you get too near"
"In the fires of the lamp..."
"die those who hover too close"
"You loonies..."
"try to understand"
"Keep distance..."
"while you watch me"
"Spark..."
"I'm spark"
"Like lightning I strike"
"Like snake I sting"
"I'm the ecstasy
"that makes you swoon"
"I can bring out
your true colours"
"I can be the fragrance
on your breath"
"In a moment..."
"I can sway your heart"
"Spark"
"I'm spark"
"Swaying and gyrating..."
"lighting fires in hearts..."
"with your eyes"
"Spark... sparkle"
"You're a spark"
Spark - Spark...
I'm a spark