Good morning.
It was just the two of
us after my father left.
He said I should count
the new baby he had
with his new wife, Marjorie,
as part of my family, too.
Plus Richard, Marjorie's son.
For the most part, my mother
never mentioned my father,
or the woman he was married to now.
You could always come live
with Marjorie and me.
I mean, if that was something you
wanted, we can have her evaluated.
No. Mom is great.
She's learning to play the cello.
I just asked because
I get the feeling her...
That she's getting worse.
I don't think losing my father
broke my mother's heart
but rather, losing love itself.
Even at that age, I understood this
and wanted to make up for
some of the neglect.
Oh, what did you do?
- You made all this for me?
- Mmm-hmm.
"Husband for a Day."
I made her a coupon book.
- I cleaned.
- "One week of clean dishes."
Did little chores around the house.
"Handyman."
There was a coupon
for a shoulder rub.
A bubble bath.
I even took her on a date.
A man should know how to dance.
When a man can dance,
the world is his oyster.
Some men just set their hand on
your shoulder or against your back
but there has to be
strong pressure there.
At the time, I was too
young to understand
the part of being husband for a day,
I was not equipped to carry out.
But I sensed my own
terrible inadequacy.
I could feel her loneliness and
longing before I had a name for it.
Hey, Henry. How's your mother?
Fine.
I hope to see her in
here one of these days.
I understood who my
real family was.
Her.
Even if that meant
only leaving the house once a month
to pick up supplies at Pricemart.
I think it's this way.
Is it all right if I go
check out the comics?
Um...
Okay. Just don't wander.
I'll be right over there.
I wonder if you could
give me a hand here.
You're bleeding.
Yeah, well, I fell out a window.
We should get help.
No, I wouldn't want
to upset anyone.
Did you come here with
that woman over there?
My mom.
She looks like the kind of
person that could help me.
I... I don't know.
What I want to ask is,
you think she'd give me a ride?
Hmm?
This is my mother, Adele.
Mom, this is Frank.
He needs our help.
You got a good boy here, Adele.
He was kind enough
to offer me a ride.
Oh.
Um...
Well, he may have, but...
We have a big afternoon.
I don't think we can help you.
Well, that's a shame.
I thought we could have a catch.
- I suck at baseball.
- Hey.
Maybe you used to.
Don't you throw around
a ball with your dad?
I only see him on Sundays.
- Oh.
- No. I'm sorry.
I won't be any trouble.
We really can't help you.
Frankly,
this needs to happen.
Oh, here. Why don't
you get in back?
Where do you want to go?
Your house.
Just for a few moments,
to rest my legs.
You'll have to excuse the mess.
We've been busy.
Nice place.
How do you, uh, take your coffee?
As is.
How did you hurt your leg?
I'm going to be straight
with you, here, Henry.
I'm not going to lie.
I hurt my leg jumping out of a
second floor window at a hospital
they'd taken me to to
get my appendix out.
At the prison.
That's how I got out.
When?
This morning.
You escaped?
So, now, the police
are looking for you.
I would have gotten further
except for the damn leg.
I'd be grateful if you let
me stay till nightfall.
I'd try and help out.
I wouldn't ask anything of you.
You just did.
Nothing more than a place to lay low
and rest my leg for a few hours.
How do I...
How do I know you won't hurt us?
I've never intentionally
hurt anyone in my life.
You understand how that
could be hard to believe.
Yeah, I do.
How far are the train
tracks from your backyard?
Running?
Limping.
Twenty minutes, maybe.
People come over. Often. Randomly.
Friends, salesmen,
religious people.
I'll make a run for it tonight and I
can stay out of your way until then.
I mean, they'd notice
if I went quiet.
Even for a little bit.
I just escaped from prison.
The last place
I want to go is back.
I'm stronger than you think.
I don't doubt that.
And I won't let anything
happen to my son.
He's in good hands.
Welcome back to Action News.
Commuters may have
experienced delays
on their drive home this afternoon.
Roadblocks on Route 73.
Who are police looking for?
Frank Chambers, an inmate
at Stinchfield Prison,
who escaped earlier this morning.
Captain! Where is Frank Chambers?
Considering his injuries,
we believe he hasn't gotten far.
Now keep in mind that he is
dangerous and quite possibly armed.
Chambers was recovering
from appendicitis
on the second floor
of this hospital
when police say, he just
made a jump for it.
Um, I went to check on him and the next
thing I knew, he was out the window.
Authorities would like
to remind our viewers
that this kind of leap
can spell desperation.
Especially in an inmate
serving 18 years for murder.
Coming up next on
the Channel 7 News,
the hottest day in 11
years in New Hampshire.
Didn't happen that way.
Isn't it against the law
to hide a fugitive?
You got a wise son here, Adele.
It's good to know he's
looking out for you.
It's all going to be fine.
It would only be a problem
if someone found Frank here.
And that doesn't need to happen.
He can just lay low for a few
hours, and then keep moving.
That's true enough.
It's still not acceptable to place you
and your family here in jeopardy.
If someone were to come by, it would
need to look like I kidnapped you.
That's why I'm going
to have to tie you up.
It's about keeping up appearances.
I think you understand what I mean.
- Who are you going to...
- Only you.
Henry here knows he doesn't want
anything to happen to his mother.
Right, Henry?
Hmm?
Open these.
Grab a bowl.
I don't suppose your father has
told you anything about sex.
Most people put all this focus
on the physical changes
you'll be going through soon.
It's okay.
They explained everything
in a health assembly.
Well, there's another aspect that your
health teacher is unlikely to explore.
People act as if making love is all
about secretions and body functions.
Mom. It's okay.
For all the discussions of
body parts and hormones,
they forget to mention
how it feels.
There's another kind of hunger.
The hunger for human touch.
Desire.
People never tell you
about how it feels.
The longing.
What time do the trains
start in the morning?
I don't know.
I'll just have to keep an
ear out for them, I guess.
I don't blame you for wondering.
Just know that there's more to this story
than you'll see in that paper there.
How did you escape?
I told the guard at the hospital if he
left, I was going to jump out the window.
He heard that and
went to have a smoke.
Nothing misleads
people like the truth.
You have any brothers or sisters?
No. My mom tried, but...
I've got a stepbrother
and a half-sister.
My dad takes me out to
dinner with them on Sundays.
How does a fellow let a woman
like your mother get away?
He got together with his secretary.
Good riddance.
Good morning.
We won't be needing
that any longer.
But if the day comes and you have to
say I tied you up, you won't be lying.
Haven't heard any trains go by.
Holiday weekend.
Breakfast?
You have to try one.
Okay.
Hey, give me a three-quarter-inch
ratchet wrench.
Ratchet wrench.
That day, Frank changed
the oil in the car
and replaced the fuse
for the blinkers.
Then he replaced the
filter on the furnace.
He checked out the cord of
firewood that just got delivered
and informed my mom that
the guy was shorting her.
Then he washed the
floor and waxed it.
Then you rotate the ball.
Grip it loose.
Two fingers up top,
thumb on the bottom.
Just let it rest there.
Barely tight enough to hold.
And when you release,
snap your wrist down, like a whip.
Just crack.
And then you grab those seams
when the ball leaves your fingers.
You bite your lip when you sew.
I'm trying not to stick you.
How'd you get that scar?
Stars and Stripes Forever
routine for my dance recital.
Halfway through rehearsal,
they got rid of the ramp.
I tapped myself right
off the stage.
Come here! Come here!
Answer the door, Hank.
Let them know your mother's out.
And I trust you're not gonna
get nervous and say something.
Now go.
Oh.
Hi, Henry. I was looking
for your mother.
I'm sorry, Mr. Jervis,
she's not home.
Oh. Well, that's...
That's not like her.
Has she been following
the news, do you know?
Did she leave you here by yourself?
No, I just mean she
can't come to the door.
- She's taking a bath.
- Oh.
Are those for her?
Yeah. I had so many, I didn't
know what to do with them.
I thought your mother
might like them.
Thank you.
I'm sure she'll appreciate them.
Let her know there's something
I'd like to discuss with her.
Is everything okay?
Well, uh...
Look, Henry, I don't know if you've
heard, but there's a guy loose.
Broke out of Stinchfield.
He's probably long gone
by now, but till they find him,
I wouldn't be opening the
door without an adult.
Thank you for telling me.
Look, I doubt he's
anywhere near here by now.
Just remember, I'm right
across the street.
You have any problems,
just give me a jingle.
He had more than he needed.
You did good, Hank.
Um...
Henry, why don't you
go check on Joe?
I'm sure he's fine.
It's a hot day.
Make sure his water
hasn't dried up.
Yeah.
You can't do that again.
What? What did I do?
My son is not your lookout.
He's not your accomplice.
And I don't...
- it was just a neighbor.
- It doesn't matter!
Don't forget what's going on here.
Not for a second.
Now, I see the way he looks at you.
What he wants.
That encouragement,
pat on his shoulder.
And I want it for him.
But not for that.
I can't promise what's going
to show up at the door.
I know.
Okay, then.
It's a good peach.
It's too bad they're all so ripe,
you'll never get through them all.
We should throw most of
them away before they rot.
No, I have another idea.
Take a peach.
Thank you.
Now, the filling is easy. What
I want to talk about is crust.
You've got to keep
your ingredients cool.
Hot day like this is
challenge enough.
The phone rings while you're making
a crust, just let them call you back.
Mix it up.
Pie crust is a very
forgiving thing. Forks.
You can make all kinds of mistakes,
but don't forget the salt.
- All of it?
- Yeah, before it gets too warm.
Keep everything cool.
Then mix it up.
Take that knife.
It's all about instinct.
Pay too much attention to
recipes, you forget how to feel.
It's like reading a
book on gardening
when all you've got to do is get
dirt underneath your fingernails.
All right. Put it in there.
That's it.
Now, don't over-handle.
You want it right on the verge
of crumbling at any moment.
There you go.
Now grab the outside.
Heel of the hand.
People buy all these fancy gadgets,
but sometimes the best tool is
attached right there to your own body.
Okay.
Scatter a little tapioca,
like salt over an icy road.
Cure for a soggy crust.
The whole thing.
Make a little mountain out of it.
Perfect.
Okay, moment of truth.
Can't go too fast.
You can't hesitate.
I don't know when my mom's hands
started shaking exactly.
But eventually, it was
beyond her control.
Help me put a roof on this house.
Perfect.
I should go.
They won't come back
for a few hours.
This is as good a window
as I'm gonna get.
Maybe tomorrow,
once your stitches have
had a little more time.
They're not going to
stop looking, Adele.
They have dogs that
can smell your blood.
You should probably let
your stitches heal.
You should stay.
Thank you. I'm really nervous.
You have to...
I understand.
We'll just lay here a while.
We haven't had anybody in this
house for such a long time.
Let me get my...
Rhythm.
This was the word that
burrowed into my brain
as I listened to their late night
conversation quietly dissipate.
I thought about
that word, "rhythm,"
and whether my mom
thought Frank had it.
These were the images
I returned to at night.
Particularly now that the
evening was no longer silent.
The next day, Frank fixed the
loose floorboard on the stairs.
He got the squeak out
of the kitchen door,
then cleared the debris
out of the gutters.
Thank you.
I'll tell you this.
You don't want to wait
to learn to fix it.
Especially if you got a lady in the
seat beside you when it happens.
They did laundry. He ironed.
And in return, my mom
taught him to rumba.
Two... three... four.
Shift your weight this way.
For lunch, Frank thought
it only right that we
fire up the barbecue.
So, he sent me to
pick up groceries.
You know, drinking from
aluminum gives you Alzheimer's.
Is that true?
Uh-huh.
It's the perfect crime
'cause you can't
remember how you got it.
Is there anything
to do in this town?
There's bowling?
Bowling.
If you ask me, I think he's
holing up in someone's house
waiting for things to cool down.
I just can't get his
face out of my head.
The worst part is knowing that a
man like that has nothing to lose.
Life to a person like that
is worth about 10 cents.
They'll get him eventually.
They always do.
- Henry. How's your mother?
- She's doing great.
Where's all the canned goods?
You usually buy like you're
planning for a tornado.
Yeah. Special recipe.
Henry. This is a man's razor.
Your mom wants one of the
pink ones on aisle 7.
It's not for my mom.
It's for me.
You practicing?
All right. Just do me a favor
and keep the cap on, okay?
Keep an eye out, all right?
Mom?
You were just a boy.
I was 21.
You didn't know what
you were doing.
Doesn't make it right.
Why didn't you say something?
Adele?
Hey, Henry, where's your mom?
I don't know!
Um, let me go... Let me
go get her. Stay here!
I need you to watch Barry!
Ev, hi!
She asked me to watch Barry.
Listen. I'm at my wits' end.
I really need some help from you.
I have to go.
My dad's in the hospital.
Oh, my God. I'm sorry.
So I need somebody to watch Barry.
- Like, right now?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'll be back tonight.
You know, I can't. Um...
- Hey, Barry. How's it going?
- Good.
They don't expect my dad
to hold on for long.
Yeah, normally...
I really don't have any
other options, Adele.
I know. I really want to help you.
I promise he'll be good.
You're gonna be good, right, Barry?
You remember Henry? And his mom?
And all the good times
you've had here?
Evelyn.
Please. One mother to another.
I would not ask you if
I wasn't desperate.
It's just that...
I don't have any
other options. Please.
You're not going anywhere.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Thank you, thank you. I owe you.
I will be back by the end of the night.
It's about two hours' drive.
Ah, okay.
Just put his chair
in front of the TV.
He loves cartoons.
Okay. Um...
Come on. I'll get you inside.
Here we go.
The door.
Hey, Barry, you look mighty
toasty in all those clothes.
I swear, she dresses him
for winter in August.
Well, you got here just in time.
We needed a third baseman.
Now, Barry, my name's Frank.
That's right. Frank.
There you go.
All right. Let's see that swing.
Don't get your hopes up.
Want to run that by me again?
Bat up. Shoulders forward.
Choke up on the bat,
hands together.
Knees bent.
There we go. Good.
When I throw it
to you, see the ball.
- See the ball.
Keep it fluid.
- There we go.
- Whoa!
See the ball.
The thing was, when Frank
threw the ball, I hit it.
If I had more time to work with
you, we could really get somewhere.
You ready? Your turn?
- No, no.
- Come on.
Take a deep breath.
Relax.
There you go. Bend your knees.
Hands together.
There you go.
- I can't do this.
- Yeah, you can.
You are doing it. Bend your knees.
Ready?
Bring on the heat, Hank.
- There you go.
- Whoa!
The count is 2 and 2.
The Red Sox are leading, 4 to 0.
Cleveland batting
in the 5th inning.
All four Red Sox runs in the 2nd.
You fool.
Tonight at 11:00, more on
escaped convict Frank Chambers.
Our psychologist weighs
in on what to expect
from a murderer on the run and
where he might be hiding.
That and more at 11:00.
Okay, Barry.
Looks like your mother is here.
- Hi.
How's your dad?
Oh. It's complicated and not all
good, but he's under supervision.
Did you have a good time today?
Yee-yeah!
This is Lynn Jolicoeur
for News Four New Hampshire.
Tonight's top story is
our continuing coverage
of the escape of Stinchfield
Prison inmate Frank Chambers,
a convicted murderer.
Well, we've had a busy day, so...
Uh, listen, I've been on
the road for two hours.
Could I trouble you
for a glass of water?
Uh, sure.
Henry, would you grab
Evelyn some water?
leaving police with very few clues.
So, was he difficult?
No. No, not at all. No. We had
the best time with Barry.
We went outside and
threw a ball around.
Oh, God. Did you put on sunscreen?
Yeah. Of course.
A lot of people don't do that.
Fwah. Fwah. Fwah!
Yes, I know. We're going.
Fwah, Fwah, Fwah!
Oh, God.
Okay, okay. We're going home.
I just need a sip of water.
Fwah!
Leaving Labor Day motorists with
more than the usual delays.
Fwrank!
We're gonna watch television
when we get home.
Fwranh! Fwrank!
Stop it!
He needs some rest.
You were so young.
Why didn't you appeal?
I don't know. I thought
I got what I deserved.
But you don't feel that now.
No, now it doesn't matter.
You couldn't take a lot.
Might seem suspicious.
We just start driving?
Just like that?
You couldn't tell any
of your friends.
No one to tell, really.
I can't imagine you not being free.
I can't call myself free until I can
walk down the street, arm around you.
I'd like that.
Take you on road trips to
places we don't know a soul.
Like on the run?
Mmm-hmm.
That's right. On the run.
My ex-husband would never
let me take Henry away.
You know what that would mean.
I know.
All right, then.
I noticed a spot under the shower
where the water is finding
its way under the linoleum.
You don't want dry rot.
I'll tackle that tomorrow, okay?
Maybe it doesn't matter.
What do you want to do?
I don't know.
I think you know.
Come on.
Just say it.
What's the matter?
Is it cold?
You're a tough guy.
I think you could take it.
Is it too cold to grow things?
It's mostly farms.
It sounds nice.
Morning, sport.
Hey.
How'd you sleep?
Fine.
Um, I was wondering if you
could do me a little favor.
Top secret research.
Research?
Just a trip to the library to pick
up a book on Prince Edward Island.
Your mom says it's beautiful.
Can you pick up the book, Hank?
So, do you go to
school around here?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to...
I just moved here from Chicago.
I'm supposed to try out
living with my dad this year.
Oh.
What happened?
The official reason is
I have an eating disorder
and they think a new school
environment will help.
But really, I think my mom
just wanted to get rid of me
so she can fool around
with her boyfriend.
I understand.
This guy, he just moved
in with my mom and me.
And now he wants you out.
- I don't think so.
- He will.
So they can have sex.
So, what are you reading?
I'm investigating my legal rights.
You see, I got into this
really great private school
where they only focus on drama.
No one cares about sports or
what kind of clothes you wear.
The teachers stay off your case.
It's really elevated.
But at the last minute, my parents
decided they didn't have the money.
Could they get a loan?
Oh, they have the money.
They're just using me as a
pawn in their sick little game.
What's that?
It's for my mother.
She wants to know if Canada
might be a good place to move.
And how do you feel about that?
Moving. Leaving your friends.
I'm asking because
that's what I had to do.
And frankly,
I consider it child abuse.
I don't know. Canada seems nice.
Do you even know if
they're taking you?
My mom wouldn't leave me behind.
When people have sex,
it affects their brains.
They can't see things normally.
It's like a drug.
I'm not sure if that's true.
Well, you're probably gonna
need an intervention.
Maybe even need to deprogram her.
- Deprogram her?
- Yeah.
This guy...
Does he have charisma?
Maybe.
Too bad your mom and my
dad couldn't get together
before this whole boyfriend
person showed up.
But then if you and I got married,
it'd be kind of like incest.
My mother doesn't
normally date anyway.
I see only one hope for you.
You need to find a way to
get him out of your life.
I don't know if that's possible.
Either you get rid of him, or he's
probably going to get rid of you.
All these people
here love you a lot.
A lot of them don't even
know you and they love you,
because you represent so very much.
But I'm very, very proud that
I could put this show on for you.
And I hope next year
we can do better
so that you can sit in
a different position.
We love you, Mikey
Neufeldt. God bless you.
What time is Women's League?
Women's League is Tuesday.
Mandy?
Hey, pal.
So that's the fool that
walked out on you.
You full? Yeah, Chloe?
He's good. You're a
good eater tonight.
Uh-Oh. Fribbles.
So...
Seventh grade. How about that?
Richard's thinking of
going out for lacrosse.
Aren't you, Rich?
Yeah. Maybe.
How about you, pal?
Lacrosse? Soccer, maybe?
Probably not football till you get a
little more meat on those bones, huh?
Actually, I was thinking of signing
up for modern dance group.
Well, I'm not sure that
would be such a good move.
I know how your mother
feels about dancing,
but people might get
the wrong idea.
They might think...
- They might think you're gay.
- Richie.
Or they might think
I like girls in tights.
You boys are reaching
that stage of life.
Probably time for us to have a
little man-to-man conversation.
I already had that
with my real dad.
I guess that just
leaves you and me.
It's okay. I'm up to speed.
Well, I'm sure your mother
gave you the basics,
but there are some things a
guy needs to hear from a man.
It can be difficult not having
a man around the house.
Who says I don't?
Before you know it, you two boys
will be going out on dates.
A couple of lady-killers!
If I was still in seventh grade,
I'd think you two were the cutest.
Gross. If you were still in seventh
grade, I wouldn't even be born.
Not to mention it'd be incest.
Were you serious?
About a guy hanging
around the house?
- What do you care?
- Hey.
You're my kid. I'd like
to know who's around.
Thanks.
- See you later.
- Bye, pal.
Henry, your mom is
some kind of dancer.
Most people wouldn't tackle the
cha-cha in this kind of weather.
Yeah. it was a little loud.
It's just music.
I just figured we were
trying to avoid attention.
Oh, come on, Hank.
You can have the next dance.
I'm going to go to bed.
Henry, wait!
Um...
There's something we wanted
to talk to you about.
After your father left, I thought
I would be alone forever.
I didn't think I would care
about anyone else besides you.
I'm really happy for you.
We're thinking Canada might be
a good place to start over.
Canada?
They speak English.
And you don't need passports
to get across the border.
Thanks for the research, bud.
We've decided to go together.
Will I ever see you again?
What are you talking about?
Do you even care about
what happens to me?
What?
You didn't think...
We're all going.
Really?
I would never leave you.
You would have to leave school.
And you couldn't tell anyone, okay?
We would just pack the car and go.
What about the roadblocks?
They're looking for a
man traveling alone.
They won't be expecting a family.
A family.
- Half.
- But, I just...
Half.
I'll be back in a little bit.
Hank, we still have work to do!
I know. I'm almost done.
Any luck getting that sex
fiend out of your house?
I don't think he's a fiend.
But, no. He's still there.
It's easy, you know.
Just tell your mom he touched you.
It's not like that anymore.
We're actually getting along.
They're going to take me
with them. To Canada.
When?
Tomorrow.
On the first day of school?
It's him, isn't it?
You're on the run.
This one, right?
Are you okay?
Probably just need some aspirin
before we hit the road.
- Let me take a look.
- No, I'm fine. It's fine.
If this is going to work, sometimes
you need to let me take care of you.
Oh.
Jesus.
- You need medicine.
- No, it can wait.
No, it's infected.
I'll send Henry to the
pharmacy. Let me do it.
It's okay. You go.
No, there's still too
much packing to do.
I don't think you're going
to make a run for it.
Okay.
How'd you escape?
It's not like that.
He trusts me.
Or maybe he was just waiting
for you to leave the house
so they could run off together.
It's just like Bonnie and Clyde.
Who?
They made a movie about them.
Bonnie was this woman who was bored
because she hadn't had
sex in a long time.
This guy, Clyde just showed
up one day and took her away.
They drove all around, holding up
banks and living out of their car.
What happened to them?
In the end, they got killed.
Federal agents tracked them and
gunned them down in an ambush.
The part where Bonnie gets killed
there's so much blood, my
mother couldn't even watch.
Could you imagine if your
mom got killed in an ambush
and you were right
there watching it?
They probably wouldn't shoot
at you since you're a kid,
but you'd see the whole thing.
It'd be pretty traumatic.
I bet you never did that before.
Now you'll always remember I was
the first girl you ever kissed.
It's a shame you're leaving
just as we started dating.
I'll have to find another
boy to make out with.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
If you're not up for this,
you need to let me know.
No, it's not that.
Because tomorrow you're
gonna say good-bye
to everyone you've ever known.
I've already said
good-bye. It's just...
We're gonna hit the road
and never look back.
There's gonna be roadblocks
and border-crosses.
I know, I know.
So, if you don't want this,
you need to tell me.
No, I do want this.
More than almost anything
I've ever wanted in my life.
Then what is it?
After Henry was born,
my body just
forgot how.
The first time it happened, I woke
up with these horrible cramps.
I felt something slip
from me. It was tiny.
If I could have just held tighter.
I know this is a very difficult
and painful time for both of you.
My doctor said that this was
more common than we thought.
I was young. We could try again.
But two more times...
I'd start feeling the
nausea and the swelling.
We'd celebrate.
Began setting up the nursery.
Only to wake up feeling
betrayed by my own body.
No...
No. No. No. No.
By my fourth time,
we knew better than to celebrate.
We knew better than
to tell our friends.
Or think of baby names.
We hadn't even packed a
suitcase for the hospital
when the contractions started.
All right. Two pushes. Two pushes.
Stop. Take a breath.
One more. One more. This is it.
- Last big one.
- This is it. Come on, come on.
- Push, push, push.
- There you go.
We'd made it.
What?
What is it?
Maybe they just took pity on me.
They'd wrapped her in a pink
blanket and put on a diaper.
The only one she'd ever wear.
As I stared at this
beautiful little girl,
her long eyelashes,
her daddy's nose, my chin,
the little mouth that would
never take a breath,
I knew there would be no
further conversations.
No more attempts.
We were done.
The world had become a cruel place.
I stopped going for walks.
I couldn't leave the house.
I couldn't even open
a window at night.
Eventually, when Gerald left,
I understood.
I'd become a prisoner.
I came to save you, Adele.
Tomorrow that's exactly
what I'm going to do.
I can't...
I can't give you a family.
You already have.
By the end of the afternoon,
everything in the house
had been neatly separated
into essentials and
things we'd leave behind.
For no practical reason more than
it seemed like the right thing to do,
we cleaned each room.
Is he even mine?
Huh?
Is he even my son?
You fool.
Mandy?
Mandy, honey?
No!
No, no!
Morning, son.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
You want to tell me
where you're going?
I'm just walking. Heading home.
Well, hop in.
Your parents are probably
worried about you.
It's just my mom. She's fine.
Well, just to be safe,
I'm gonna give you a ride.
I'm... I'm really fine.
You not going to make
me arrest you now?
School starts today, doesn't it?
What grade are you in?
I'm going to guess, uh, sixth.
- Seventh.
I've got a son about
to start fifth,
although I guess you wouldn't
associate with a grade schooler.
So, what are you doing out here?
I left something at my dad's house.
But he'd already left for work.
Thank you for the ride.
No.
- What does he want?
- I don't know.
Found him by the side of the road.
Did you know he was out?
He said he'd be right back.
He's got to be in school in
a few minutes, doesn't he?
Sure does.
Thank you for bringing him home.
You going on a trip?
Hmm?
You taking a road trip?
Um...
No.
Just taking some old things
to sell on consignment.
You need some help?
I'll be fine.
I don't want to take you
away from your duties.
No.
I think the streets are
safe for the moment.
That's the heavy one.
Nice place.
Clean.
This one?
Mmm-hmm.
You weren't kidding.
What've you got in here?
Some old kitchenware.
Hey.
Thank you for your help.
A pleasure.
Got a good handshake
there, partner.
Have a good day, ma'am.
He seem suspicious?
I don't know.
We have to get out of here now.
Take Henry to the bank.
I'll finish up here.
- Hey.
- What?
We're going to be fine.
Okay.
Hey, Henry. Nice to
see you in here.
You need to sign it.
Hmm? Oh.
Of course.
Adele?
Thought you'd be in school today.
He has a dentist appointment.
On the first day of school?
My teeth hurt.
Oh, sorry.
Is Adele here?
Uh, she'll be right back.
She's dropping her kid at school.
I just brought these to
thank her for something.
Well, I'll make sure she gets them.
And you would like
this all in cash?
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah.
With an amount this large, I just need
to get it approved by my supervisor.
I'll be right back.
Is that really...
Are... Are you a friend?
Just the handyman.
I shouldn't have tried
to get so much.
I should have just asked for half.
It's gonna be fine.
They're just being extra careful.
- Hi, Adele.
- Hi.
I just wanted to make sure you
weren't experiencing any problems.
No.
Everything's fine.
Are they going somewhere?
I don't know.
It sure looks like it.
Well, maybe I should get my pan back,
then, in case they're gone for a while.
It's just a somewhat
unusual situation for us
having a person withdraw
this much in cash.
Normally, when transferring
funds of this quantity,
our clients prefer
a cashier's check.
Yeah, I, uh...
Yeah. Mmm.
Yeah, it's...
I just don't really get
out much anymore, so...
Did they say where they were going?
I'm just here to fix a few things.
Some would even call a withdrawal
like this a little suspicious.
Actually, we've packed
up all our things.
We're emptying our bank account
and then gonna make a
run for the border.
You know, like Bonnie and Clyde.
Of course you are.
Well, come on, Muriel, let's not
keep our friends here waiting.
We should go.
Get in here. Get in.
Henry's father called
and left a message.
Did you leave him
some sort of note?
I wanted him to know
that I'd be all right.
- Why would you do that, Henry?
- We need to go, now.
I just need to say
good-bye to my room!
Oh, Henry, don't! We need to leave!
Listen to your mother!
Henry!
Don't be scared.
What do we do?
Where do we go?
We have to get you out of here.
No.
We have a perimeter.
Open the door slowly.
Step outwith your hands open and above
your head, palms facing forward.
You're a fine boy, Henry.
Anybody who says otherwise
is not worth your time.
I'd take 20 more years just to
have another three days with you.
Open the door slow.
Hands above your head!
Keep them up!
- Hands above your head!
- On your knees!
- Get down.
- On your knees, do it now!
Hands behind your head!
All right, all right,
we got him! Move in!
Move to the kitchen.
Okay, I need to run some tests.
Don't be scared, son.
Your mom will be fine.
We got the guy.
He won't be able to do anything
to you and your mom anymore.
Ma'am, over here. I need you
to look over here, please.
- I'm going to cut the tape.
- Can you hear me okay?
They charged him with kidnapping.
When my mother heard,
she drove to see the prosecutor
with me as a witness
to make him understand that no
unlawful detainment had taken place.
He didn't hurt us.
He is a good man.
He was kind to my son.
She omitted the fact
that they were in love.
Adele, these situations
are never simple.
Never clean.
It may take years for you to
fully weave it all together.
Now, perhaps, before putting this
kind of statement into record,
you might want to take some time to
think about what actually happened.
Harboring a fugitive is a major
crime we don't look lightly upon.
And, of course, there is
delinquency to a minor.
You could lose custody of your son.
They gave Frank 10 years
for the escape and 15
for the kidnapping.
My mother tried to visit him once,
but was told he was doing solitary.
She wrote to Frank, sometimes
daily, but received no response.
Eventually, a package arrived
containing all of her letters
stamped with a prison seal.
None of them had been opened.
She called to enquire and was
told Frank had been transferred.
Within a month, my mother voluntarily
relinquished custody of me to my father.
He rarely knew what to say.
More often than not,
he just kept quiet.
The newspapers had
said it all anyway.
When I visited my mother,
she would act busy and distracted.
Calls to make, chores to do.
I think my presence
made her uncomfortable.
A strange reminder
of what was missing.
All those two had was each other.
That was enough.
By my junior year,
people hardly brought up the events
leading up to seventh grade.
For the first time, I had
someone to call a girlfriend.
There's something I've been
meaning to talk to you about.
Oh, Dad, please. We're
having such a pleasant time.
Everybody talks about all
this crazy, wild passion.
That's how it goes in
the songs. You know.
Your mother was like that.
She was in love with love.
She couldn't do anything partway.
She was a terrific woman.
Funny.
So beautiful.
A better man might have stayed around
and helped her through all that sadness.
But I couldn't bear it.
I just wanted a regular life.
I don't know what these last
few years have done to repair,
but I'm sorry I cut out on you.
It's okay.
I'm going to get the check.
The next day, when I suggested
I move back in with my mother
for the rest of senior year,
he didn't argue.
And it was there in my mom's
kitchen, my final summer at home,
that I first tried
my hand at baking.
Dear Henry.
I hope you will remember me.
We once spent Labor
Day weekend together.
Five of the best days of my life.
I had always wondered who you would
become and what you would look like.
And then one day, I came
across a familiar-looking pie.
And there you were.
I'm proud of you.
I will understand if you choose
not to respond to this letter.
However, I am due to
be released shortly.
I am no longer young, but I have
plenty of good health remaining.
And I'd like to live much
the same way we discussed
that weekend back when we
thought we'd be a family.
Most likely, your mother
has remarried by now.
But on the off chance
that she might be alone,
I wanted to ask you whether
I might write her a letter.
I promise you,
I would sooner cut off my own hand
than bring any more grief to Adele.
I wrote him back that day
to say that it wouldn't be
difficult to locate my mother.
She lived at the same address.
I spent half of my life
worrying my mother
wouldn't be able to go out
into the world on her own.
But as it turned out,
she wouldn't have to.