Panasonic.
Ideas for your life.
These are awful.
They are really bad.
Hair-raising.
We need something edgy.
Something that is not totally out.
Our smartphone,
must be intelligent.
It is beautiful. It's perfect.
Thank you.
You have a great taste.
Do you know
what else I like about you?
You are conscientious.
You are incredibly intelligent.
And you are ambitious.
Well look at that!
It is organic.
- Traditional?
It's healthy.
Hello!
- Hello.
Two drunk
työmuurahaista at work.
I will probably bother you.
I think I'll leave.
Do not go. It remains of course.
I love surprises.
So you love.
Hey, Isabelle.
- Hey, Dirk.
I even this source.
Can just leave them.
- Ice, Isabelle.
Good night, Dirk. Good night.
- Isabelle, wait.
Outside it is freezing cold.
This is for you.
You can keep it.
- I can take against this.
I think we have a good team.
- Yeah, we are. I will continue to work at home.
You are crazy. Awesome.
Damn.
Stop it.
Stop it, damn it.
Faithful assistant.
- I'm sorry to wake you.
I got a great idea
campaign. Can you come?
You're the boss.
- Put on your tightest farkkusi.
Rolf? Hey.
I can not.
This weekend is busy.
I'm going to London for a minute.
Being sent from Reynold?
Okay. I invented something.
It would be in it.
Let's see what we have.
What do you think?
- My bottom is wonderful.
What do you think about the rest?
- It's brilliant.
I would like to list
all budgets tomorrow morning.
I do not have time to...
- Do I have to do it yourself?
No, because it's your job, Eric.
Thank you, this was all.
Good morning.
- Hello! Good morning.
What's wrong with your eyes?
Do you have a hangover?
I woke up in the middle of the night
and I would come up with a solution.
Biscuits solution?
- I think so.
I did one thing in the morning,
and I want you to look at it.
I think it's pretty good.
- Really?
Hello. How great are
my friend new jeans
truly spectacular.
I saved on a flash drive,
so you can watch it on the plane.
I do not think so.
Why do not you?
- You're going to London.
Really?
- Oh, yes.
You know, these campaigns would thoroughly.
You take care of your home to do the job.
You did not see it completely.
- I saw enough. I trust you.
Dirk will meet you at the airport.
Hello. How wonderful
girlfriend's new jeans are
How will clarify this matter?
Are you ready?
- Guaranteed!
Ass test.
- What
Are you ready to watch,
what the man in the street is .
Now the party.
I booked a table Margaux.
It has more stars
than the Milky Way.
I'm really tired.
See you tomorrow.
To think that you are here with me.
- You are amazing. You are beautiful.
We liked the idea very much.
We use it internationally.
That's great!
I was in the middle of the night
brainwave and...
Sometimes it just happens.
Great. Worried,  when you do
not come to the meeting itself.
I'm sorry. I stayed here because
of the financial statements.
Briiffasin Isabelle thoroughly.
I was ready to come
according to need.
Nice work, Christine.
- Thank you.
Would you be interested in returning to
home to New York?
And I would reject from there?
I'm fond of them.
They could indeed be ready to
to stand on their own feet.
Can I think about it?
- , Of course.
Shocked
I would expect you to do
I wanted New York,
This is not a back puukotusta.
We are a team. You have the ability,
Thank you.
Nice.
I heard about it.
Aggravated thing about me. - What?
Christine can be reached in New York City
thanks to you.
When the team works, everybody wins.
My success depends on him.
Check this out. Omniphone ad
public opinion poll.
Have you ever seen
such figures?
Here are the changes.
They do not make any sense.
Good, girls.
Set out shoes for a friend.
An overview of the shoes. Oh, great.
Excellent. Walk to the center.
Here, here, here.
The next girl.
Beautiful.
- It's high.
The next girl.
Show what you know, Waruschka.
Next, thank you.
- I like those details.
Oh, great.
Oh, my God! Who hired her?
Down from the stage.
Could you please leave?
Cocktail Invitations are really boring,
but they have to show up.
How do they feel?
- These look great.
That's the main thing.
- I do not seem to be able to walk in these.
Did not they know the weather too
you feel a bit tuhmaksi?
You are truly mysterious.
- Am I?
We have been colleagues for months,
Or what you want.
What do you want?
I do not know.
Before I wanted to be admired.
- I admire you.
Now, I want to be loved.
Are you ready?
- I think.
I do not know mahdanko to survive.
- I'll teach you to chat.
Hey, Mark!
Now it's your turn.
- Do what?
Do you see that bald man over there,
He was an important man in the company.
If you catch him,
nettoat lot.
I do not know.
You remind me more
than you think. - I'm drunk.
So much the better.
Put him to talk about themselves.
It is a man's favorite topic.
Are you ready? Go.
Wait a minute. Hold this.
Show a bit of bare ground.
Nice to meet you.
Hey. I'm Isabelle.
Whether it's a nice surprise.
What do you say next weekend?
- I'm busy. Some other time.
Stop, Rolf.
And not just my machine.
I saved you Lontoolta boring.
I'll call you next week.
Can not you leave?
You are drunk. Go to the home.
Isabelle.
- I'm going home. My head hurts.
That is not like you think.
I did not send you to London, therefore,
so that was a comfort to me.
I sent you to London,
because I trust you.
And what does it matter anyway?
Take another drink.
- I'm going home. I have a bad feeling.
I live here.
Do you like this place?
What with him?
He likes role play.
Does that sound like fun?
He thought it was a lot of fun.
Check that.
He gave me a beautiful scarf.
Oh, no!
Do you want it back?
- I do not.
It suits you better.
Thank you.
- Not at all.
That is, he did.
The day's program has been completed.
Are there issues?
Isabelle, New York sent
you report a new comment.
Did you get it?
Did I get it?
I have not read it yet.
- Do not dithered with it.
I want to change the data immediately.
Thank you. That's it.
It remains for a while, Isabelle.
Are you still angry.
It bothers me,
I like you very much.
I love you.
Why can not you just say it?
When I was six years old,
my parents bought -
me and my twin.
Do you have a twin sister?
Alternately cycled to school.
Clarissa was a better bike ride.
He knew how to ride a bicycle standing up.
One day, the
I wanted to show,
that cycled as well.
Pedal faster and faster.
Clarissa had to run hard.
I let go of the handlebars.
I felt like to fly to.
It felt wonderful.
I wanted to see myself, -
so I looked at the window,
and thus the shadows.
I do not know what happened.
Bike slid into the middle of the street.
Truck ran towards me.
All of a sudden I noticed that my sister.
Then I remember just...
Terrible... thump.
When I woke up in the hospital,
I saw Mama cry.
I asked him,
He did not even look at me.
No one said anything,
but I knew their thoughts.
That I killed him.
After that, they do not ever
said he loved me.
I love you.
- Do you love?
You are a wonderful person.
You called me.
Here I am.
Hey, Isabelle.
- Hey, Dirk. How are you?
Happy.
- You are so tricky.
If things are like this,
is the best continue to work hard.
Good. - Would you leave.
He is adorable.
- Yes, it is.
What we do for scams?
- Fraud?
I need a couple of months time.
Then all is well again.
For a week.
- You are crazy. It is impossible.
New York makes its annual accounts.
I do not want scandal.
My company has been working for you
I wrote the budget in Annex.
I'll put it in the folder.
Read it.
Do you know what myyräni
New York says?
Now the spotlight has them.
They're going to make a new version
choosing the right actors.
Okay.
- No!
Upload to YouTube and show your spot,
it is that you're a genius.
If anyone sees this,
I'm a goner.
Pay the money back,
I'll rip it.
Listen to me, Christine.
This is about me.
- What the hell are you doing?
Did you get my text?
What's going on?
- I have problems with this.
Christine does not help me.
Please let me know. I can help.
- You can not.
A terrible famine. Where do we go?
- Around the corner is a nice restaurant.
You can not help me.
Tell me what happened.
What? - This is
thing between us out now.
Why? What did he say?
What Christine said?
What happened in the meeting room?
You do not get it. Christine does not care
we give a shit.
Do not do this.
- Do not call me.
Do not send out text messages.
Go on about your work.
What?
Who is sick?
Your daughter?
I did not know you had a daughter.
Tomorrow?
How about?
How about,
you do not ever call me?
OMNIPHOHE CAMPAIGN
PROPOSED CHANGES
Would you visit us, Dani?
Mark?
Hey. Christine here.
So, it is a long time.
For far too long.
What are you doing?
You are right. This is bullshit.
Fuck them.
Let's see what you think.
Lovely.
You know my taste.
After all, there's not too noisy?
I'll take it. Manhattan Apartment
are wildly expensive.
All right.
We'll talk in a few days.
Goodbye.
Wow, Mark!
So?
- Isabelle? J. J. Koch here.
Did I wake you?
- No, not at all.
Incredible trick.
Not reach Christine.
Sorry. Christine
did not know about it.
New ideas were just so...
Do you know how many times
ad has been viewed?
10 million, although it has been
visible only five hours.
My phone was ringing non-stop.
Great.
We'll be there tomorrow.
We're going to London
and pop into while there.
Isabelle Omniphone ad
has spread like a virus.
Advertisements should be put
in magazines and television.
The preliminary estimation is that the.
Every single denim brand implores.
This is a huge success.
Thank you.
Isabelle and Christine,
I would like to talk to you.
Great job, Isabelle.
Congratulations concept
and its implementation.
Christine, do you know how to smell
abilities and train them.
What comes to New York City,
Now is not the best moment.
Is expected yet.
Let's talk about that later.
No errand is no rush.
I have a lot to keep you busy here, too.
Oh, great. Isabelle, the way we
New York months.
Right.
- Thank you to both of you.
Goodbye.
- Thank you.
Why?
I think
their amendment were false.
I had to act
very quickly.
I missed you last night.
Just answer the question.
Why?
I watched you.
I listened to.
I picked up a few things.
This is not a back puukotusta.
This is just business.
So be it.
So?
- Thank God.
Thank you for responding.
I here.  - What do you want?
You were right. Christine forced
me to put an end to our relationship.
Forced?
- He's fucking dangerous.
You do not understand. He is a bit
strange because of her sister at work.
Her sister? What are you talking about?
- Twin Sister Clarissa.
He does not have the double sisters.
It is exactly those of his thing.
He told you the sad
story to compassion.
Does not he have sisters?
- .
How do you know?
- I know Christine.
I know what he's like.
Is exactly what he is.
He says any
kusettaakseen you.
Do not let her do
this to us.
Can meet tonight
I do not know, Dirk.
- I need you, Isabelle.
I need to see you.
I want you, Isabelle.
I'm sorry.
Realize
This is his fault.
I'm sorry.
All right.
- Nice.
Nice, nice, nice.
I'll pick you up.
Hey. You are late,
I do not see you.
Is the camera on? Dirk?
Guess again. This is me.
Dirkiäkö miss you
He is here.
Do not point it at the camera
me. Turn it on.
He is a bit Areana.
While we spend so nice
evening watching a movie.
In fact, you movie.
London.
Would you like to see?
Hell!
Shit!
Isabelle!
Isabelle! Is everything all right?
What happened? I need to talk.
I noticed one strange thing.
I am looking for one contract,
which was carried out earlier this year.
I noticed a huge difference
Dirk Harriman on the figures provided -
and the Middle East markets
the actual budget range.
Christine added a folder in the Annex,
which is like a criminal prosecution.
I knew that the man?
There was something strange. - What?
Dirk betrayed the money, and Christine
stopped protecting him.
Can I help you with something?
- Bring me some coffee.
Did you hear already?
Our managers to keep cocktail party
all department managers.
Tomorrow night here.
If not turn up,
get a toaster for Christmas.
We have a little surprise for you.
I hope it amuses you.
What are these walls
is actually happening?
I've put together for us
a small document.
"Very stressed-out leader
not very secret life. ."
Also included is the ecstasy and suffering
and little instruction.
One manager will be pissed.
Familiar to us all.
Should not be given the frustration
to domination.
Take a deep breath,
relax and keep going.
Is not that right?
This will be the next piece.
Caught red-handed.
We all have a need for
extract a bit of pressure at work.
You know the ones, who you are.
Go still next time the hotel.
Outside working hours, thank you.
What about then?
The impact directly on the concrete column.
Someone is not happy
parking place.
Come on, Isabelle.
It was just a joke.
Where's your sense of humor is?
I think you really get hurt.
I'm really sorry.
I thought that we could
laugh at this one.
It was funny.
Hey. I would like to talk about
Katzman with your doctor.
Stefan? Isabelle James here.
I need to see you.
Come on in..
Close the door.
Isabelle, I said I was sorry.
And yet, I got this.
- What is it?
"I'll never forget that humiliated
to me. You'll pay for it. ."
"Revenge is sweet."
I have not written that.
- It was sent to you from your computer.
Not very clever.
- I did not write it.
Hard to believe after the behavior.
Alright.
Deposit of this
a safe place. Approx.
It's taken a bit of a runaway
out of control in recent times.
I like the small dinner party
Saturday.
There will be a few friends.
It is the folder in which you told...
Dirk folder.
That's it for me.
- Okay.
In this folder you requested.
- Thank you.
I want to go to the ballet.
"Afternoon of a Faun" presentation.
At ten o'clock on a Saturday night.
- Okay.
Are you okay?
- I am.
I beg your pardon.
After all, he already eats pills.
- That bitch claimed him.
It is an embarrassing story garage claimed him.
He should resign.
I'm coming.
Good. A bit more of a smile.
Very good.
Thank you.
I'll walk you out.
Isabelle, nice to see you,
that you use a scarf.
How about a little kiss
and reconciliation?
What are you doing?
- How so?
Why kissed the bitch?
After all he is doing.
Do not talk to me like that tone.
Keep your mouth shut and go back to work.
Do you think nobody would notice?
- What?
What do you want.
- What do you mean?
Her pussy.
Isabelle and I laugh at it.
- I do not believe you.
Do you think I did not notice,
lesboaivoissasi what happens?
Jealousy ruin
työtoveruutemme.
I'm not going to put up with it.
I want you out of here.
You can not fire me.
I do not separate you.
You resign yourself.
I want your resignation is
on my desk Monday morning.
I'm not going to resign.
While this was the
sexual harassment. - What?
The word against the word.
Which mahdetaan believe?
You are so charming all.
And all so wonderfully boring.
All and sundry.
Especially you.
It's true.
Good night.
Christine.
Hello, Christine.
- Thank you for your help.
I need to talk.
- Thank you. Good night.
Hello to you.
- You are quite drunk.
Yes, I am. Let's go inside.
How did you get here?
- I drove the car really hard here.
For God's sake. What's wrong with you?
What's going on?
We need to talk.
You made me...
- There is talk now.
You forced me to do
a very bad thing.
You owe me.
Do not leave me in the lurch.
DO NOT LOCK THE DOOR
RIISUUDU, go take a shower,
SIDO your eyes and come to bed.
Let me in, Christine.
Open the door, Christine.
I'm coming.
Are you there?
Days. I am a detective sergeant Bach.
He is my colleague.
Are you Isabelle James?
- I am.
Can we come in?
- Why?
Are you all right?
- I do not. I have not.
I took sleeping pills.
I can not sleep.
Do you know that Christine Stanford
throat was slit on Saturday?
Do you recognize this?
It has been sent from your computer.
Is not the victim of some
humility now on you at work?
Miss James?
We found... Miss James!
I am here.
We found the victim's hand, fibers,
derived from scarf.
Such,
that you have in this picture.
Can you explain it? Where were you
Saturday night at 23.30 - 01.00?
I was at the ballet.
- Where?
Ballet.
Were you alone?
- I was.
To identify any of you?
- Why would it have been?
Sometimes you can meet people,
who may remember.
Remember what?
- You to attend.
You would have an alibi, and you should
could not kill Christine Stanford.
I could not...
I will never...
If you have a lawyer,
you should call him.
Open your mouth.
Laboratory confirmed,
the fibers are scarf.
You will be charged with murder.
Isabelle, are you okay?
Can we get him in the water?
- Miss James.
Is a break?
Do you need a doctor?
I do not.
- Let's get this soon.
Lavastitte burglary,
aggravating the offense.
It is, therefore, of a deliberate murder.
Why do not you just recognize?
It would save everyone time and money.
You have a few fiber, which is suitable for
my client scarf image.
How many other scarf they fit? Did you
find the sacrifice of my client's DNA?
Surmasitteko Christine Stanford?
- Do not answer.
Yes, yes, I suppose so.
- Think about what you say, Isabelle.
What do you mean "probably"?
Surmasitteko?
Did you kill her?
- Do not answer.
Acknowledge that the murder?
- He did not do it.
I confess.
Hell!
- Forward.
Login now!
Away from the door!
Are you all right, Isabelle
Surmasitteko Christine Stanford?
- Do not respond to.
Surmasitteko
- He did not do it.
Did you kill her?
- My client's mental state...
Heads of confessed to the murder.
- I confess.
What?
- I want to see my lawyer.
I did not kill Christine.
- You want a confession back?
I'm innocent.
- Then why are you confessed?
I do not know. I was so tired.
I was a pill drunk.
I would have recognized anything.
I need to talk
with the prosecutor immediately.
This looks the same material,
but my scarf is not broken.
Where is it?
- Somewhere in my apartment.
We studied the apartment thoroughly
and did not find anything.
Seek out yet. The scarf is there.
- He has no reason to lie.
You've wasted enough of my time.
- Why would I be murdered Christine?
You had a strong motive. Revenge.
- I have not written that.
And if I were, then it would have been
foolish to kill him.
Christine probably sent it to the
my computer.
Creator. Look at the date.
This is referred to
days before the lumps.
Do you see? The day before
he humbled me.
This does not make sense.
I did not write this.
I was about to get a promotion,
Christine and bear it.
He tried to suppress Isabelle.
Many department confirms -
that my client became depressed
Christine's bullying of.
Are you crazy?
That's defenses?
Spare
mitigating circumstances for the judge!
I'm only interested in evidence.
- It is what we are trying to give.
I was not Christine's house.
I was at the ballet.
You claim it.
I talked to
Ballet with an usher.
He had a gray, curly hair,
and he spoke bad English.
He remembers me.
Have you seen this woman?
- I do not.
Do not you surely?
Days. Katsoisitteko this?
Have you seen this woman?
I am.
- Do you?
He sat there. He wanted to
may sit in the middle of the line.
I had to guide him in there.
Whether or not this will certainly
this woman? - There was.
I booked a ticket
Saturday night's myöhäisnäytökseen.
He could not be
Christine's home.
Maybe he left the States. Christine
the house was ten minutes away.
Why do not you ask Dirk harrimanella?
He was reportedly there.
He was furious,
Christine rejected because of him.
And he was drunk.
He knew everything from ballet.
- It is a well-known classic.
Usher guarantee him an alibi.
What else do we have?
His DNA was not
the murder weapon and the crime scene.
No DNA but e-mail,
which is the only who could not write.
As if we were forced
labile to recognize the woman.
Just check
Christine male friend.
Witnesses saw them
fighting over the crime scene outside.
Or even miesystäväkin.
Either the house is checking out?
Together, this evidence
nolaan myself in court.
My client was accused of
wrong reasons. He has an alibi.
Against him is not
no evidence. No DNA.
What about the scarf fibers?
- They are not my huivistani.
You say, then, that you have for one.
- It must be found. It is not broken.
May I make a suggestion?
- Of course.
Do you offer to help my client
scarf for search?
What's this?
Christine found out that Dirk
tried to cheat a large sum of money.
How much?
- I do not know the exact figure.
More than five million.
The sum of one million of Class,
and Christine was going to expose him?
Why piilottelitte proof?
We are friends. Dirk needed
just the time to restore the money.
So hid the information. Do not you
understand that it is a motive for murder?
No! Dirk could never do that.
We have to leave.
- Wait a minute. Can I look for?
My scarf is in that box. Sometimes
they slip out of the back of the box.
Alright. Let her look.
- Thank you.
It's got to be here.
- That's enough, Isabelle.
It's got to be here! No!
Even a minute!
Just one minute! Do not be!
I did not do it.
Of course not.
I know that.
Headscarf is
in one of the apartment.
You have to look for it.
What a mess.
Should I clean up?
Where did you get this?
- It was dirty, the back of the box.
I took it to the cleaners.
Ms. Wirth, this is outrageous.
You will get another cleaner.
Detective Chief Inspector Bach.
Mr. Harriman.
- What do you want?
I am a detective sergeant Bach.
You are accused of embezzlement.
We studied the place.
First the car, then your apartment.
You have to get the wire.
- The prosecutor will explain to you everything.
Christine broke into Stanford
apartment night of the murder?
I will not.
- Do you deny olleenne there?
I do not.
Were you his guest?
- I was. I arrived late.
When?
- I do not remember.
You do not remember?
Is this you?
It was scarf.
Was that?
- Yes.
If that's Christine Stanford
blood... Put the recovery.
This is ridiculous.
- Kavalsitte company money.
Christine was going to report you.
You're a villain but also a murderer.
I do not speak any
without a lawyer present.
Is not it incredible?
He bought me a bouquet of roses.
Then he showed up at my door
apologize.
He was quite red
naamaltaan and bathed in sweat.
He was so sorry,
I was arrested a while.
The time sweet.
Did you invite him in?
No, you crazy?
I smiled sweetly, -
I took the cheap roses fool with explanatory
notes and threw them in the garbage.
Bach poor. What a cliché.
The hard-boiled cop
fall in love with the beautiful killer.
I'm not a murderer.
Oh, yeah.
Dani...
I know what you did for me.
You would have done the same for me.
- Of course.
Shall again
number 26? - Okay.
They are okay, but do not
good enough. What do you think?
Dani!
That kiss did not happen.
I love you.
I want you, Isabelle.
That's the problem.
Why?
- Jesus Christ! Are you kidding me?
After all, you love me.
- I do not. What's wrong with you?
I do not love you.
- You love.
You may not want to admit it,
but you love me.
We have drunk too much.
I make espressos, and I'll call a taxi.
Go home and sleep.
Talk to you tomorrow.
No, not tomorrow.
It's not true, Isabelle?
You love me.
- Stop it. You are pathetic.
Am I pathetic?
All my support after that?
I am grateful. Thank you.
- That you gave already.
This is the espresso. Sit down
and then find out. I'll call you a cab.
Hello. The most space taxi.
Ytyjä pills.
You know, I'm not at risk.
I was wondering pills popsimistasi.
Until a couple of them fell to
teeheni and I tasted them.
They were
Sweetening harmless.
I followed you to see
what are you gonna.
First stop
was a scarf store.
You bought the same scarf as
got Christine and hide it.
interesting.
What about then?
Oh, and ballet.
Followed you and saw how
cause a conflict and you got an alibi.
last stop
was Christine's house.
All the pieces fell into place
place.
The perfect moment.
Let me in, Christine.
Confession was the bait.
- I confess.
It's a fool lieutenant swallowed up the
false hook, line and sinker clues.
The perfect murder.
- Except for...
Videos.
I gathered them aggravating
folder Lieutenant Bach.
And I downloaded this folder.
And can not be traced?
- I bought this for that purpose.
Is not it cute?
You just have to press the send button.
What do you want?
- Do not talk like that tone.
Come here.
Sit down.
Come closer.
Kiss me.
Do not like it?
You love me.
Turn around.
I love you.
I thought,
the twin sister of a fairy tale.
I did not get the opportunity to
ask for forgiveness.
So?
SEND?