At the end of the Qing dynasty, the lands of China
were dominated by foreign powers.
Unable to fight back,
the Chinese were branded as "Sick Men of Asia"
It seemed that no one could stand against it.
To further trample the pride of the Chinese...
The Shanghai Foreign Business Association
organized a fight,
pitting four experts from different countries
to challenge the Chinese people.
This time, one man
stood up against the challenge...
and he was Huo Yuan Jia.
"1910, Shanghai"
"Theatre Biarya, French Constitution"
"Match Venue"
Ladies and gentlemen...
Our four challengers are from
the Shanghai Business Association
They will challenge Huo Yuan Jia
from the Jing Wu school.
The outcome of the fight...
will be determined by knockout or surrender.
"Boxing Champion, Peter Smith England"
Begin!!
"Royal Knight Instructor, Hans"
"European Fencing Champion, Anthony"
And for our final round,
the brilliant Japanese fighter...
Tanaka Yasuno will take on...
Huo Yuan Jia of the Jing Wu School.
"30 years ago, Tian Jin, Huo household"
Young Master!
Come on now, let's go!
Stop!
How dare you!? Who let you in here?
I came to bring you some tea, Dad.
I've told you many times not to come in here!
Go back to your room and study.
Continue.
You always get me to do your work!
Someday, your Dad will find out
and you'll be in trouble!
If we don't tell, who's gonna know?
Hey, I want to show you something.
Hurry up, Nong Jing Sun!
I'm coming...
Today, Huo En Di from the Huo family...
and Zhao Zhong Qiang from the Zhao family...
will fight on this stage
to determine who's the best!
What are you two doing? You want to die?
Your dad will lose today.
Your dad will taste the Huo Fist.
Just wait and see.
The life and death agreement has been signed!
Victory or defeat is decided by men.
Life or death is up to Heaven.
Masters! Begin the competition!
Zhao Jian, now your Dad will understand
the power of the Huo Fist!
And the winner is...
Zhao Zhong Qiang!
Thank you! Thanks so much!
Yuan Jia!
Let's go, Yuan Jia. Yuan Jia!
You were so arrogant before.
Look at you now. Got any guts?
Don't just cower like a rat...
Get up!
Zhao Jian, you better not go too far!
Shut up!
You're just stupid. You and your Huo fist!
Spar with me if you dare.
I'll show you the power of our Zhao fist!
On stage, now!
Yuan Jia! Stop fighting!
Now that you've had a taste of the Zhao fist...
I don't want to hear about the Huo Fist again!
I won! I won!
Yuan Jia!
Let's go.
I swear...
I will not be beaten here again!
Young Master...
let me apply some medicine...
Lai Fu... You can go now.
Yes.
What happened? Why are you angry?
Mum, why won't Dad let me learn martial arts?
Because your dad loves you.
You were born with asthma,
and you have a weak constitution.
You can't stand the strain.
Doesn't martial arts make your body stronger?
Are you so keen to learn martial arts...
simply to strengthen your body?
No, I want revenge.
I want Zhao Jian to acknowledge
the power of the Huo Fist.
My son, the most powerful aspect of martial arts...
is not to defeat others.
It is to curb your thirst for victory.
No matter what,
virtue and morality must not be lost.
Martial arts is to strengthen one's body
and to help others.
It's not for you to cause trouble
and it's certainly not for revenge.
To get along well with others...
you must respect and treat them nicely.
Then others will respect you in return.
If you are good in martial arts,
who dares not to respect you!?
Fear and respect are two different things.
Come on, finish it all right?
Otherwise, your Father will punish you again.
"Death Fist"
I'm the winner!
We're flying! We're flying!
We're falling! We're falling!
I won't fall down, I won't fall down
Then I'll knock you down...
I won't fall down!
Come on, again come on!
Move faster!
Be careful!
Good morning, Mum.
Yuen Jia, you forgot
to take your medicine again this morning
Ever since I trained at West Lake...
my asthma hasn't relapsed.
Just look at your child...
without a mother since an early age,
you have doted on her too much!
You should marry again,
so that someone can help you take good care of her
I have been busy building up our family name.
I want everyone here in Tian Jin
to know and respect us!
How will I find the time to remarry?
You can't get me, I want to go out with you, Dad!
Even though you have remained undefeated
all these years...
your biggest obstacle is yourself.
And what you really must conquer...
Is also yourself.
I understand.
"Issue of Challenge"
Master...
All right.
You have a good rest first, Mum.
Dad...
Your fist wasn't fast nor ruthless enough.
But don't you worry with me around.
The Huo's family name won't be defeated again!
"Live and death agreement"
I'll definitely become number one in Tian Jin!
Dad!
My little Chui!
For me?
- No, I won't!
- Give it to me, come on.
No, I won't!
Then, what can I do for you
so you'll give it to me?
I will give it to you after you win.
Really?
Promise?
"1900, Tian Jin"
Master Huo...
When will you become No. 1 in Tian Jin?
I don't know... What do you think?
Just today! Today!
Hey, Zhao Jian!
Where have you been hiding all these years?
I've travelled Jiang Nan's 17 provinces
and 38 prefectures.
I've mastered a great deal of Kung Fu.
I'm invincible in Jiang Nan now!
Bullshit!
You're the bullshitter!
The life and death agreement has been signed!
Let the competition begin!
Come on! Come up!
What? Afraid?
Come up. Come up and fall to your death!
Just you wait!
Well done, Master!
My horse-stance is as stable as a mountain
and rooted to the ground!
Today, I will defeat your Huo Fist!
Okay, I'll give you a chance...
...to lose!
Well done, Master!
- Pussy claw?
- Tiger Claw!!
Down you go!
Well done, Master!
I won't go down just because you say so!
- Pussy claw.
- It's Tiger Claw!!!!
You've lost!
Master!
- You all right?
- I'm fine
What a tough guy!
Don't touch me!
And our winner is...
Huo Yuan Jia!
Well done! You're great, Master!
Thank you! Thank you!
Congratulations, this way.
- Good Job, Master Huo!
- Thank you!
We reserved a table for you upstairs Master Huo.
Yuan Jia!
Hey, Jing Sun!
Why so late?
Same old place, come on.
Congratulations, Master Huo!
Hello, everybody!
Come on, now.
Jing Sun...
Your business is booming!
This is all because of everyone's support!
Still remember when we were kids?
You were just a bookworm.
I never expected you to do so well in business!
The economy is bad!
A bookworm like me can only run a business.
I don't have a choice!
Eat up, Yuan Jia!
It took me some effort
to get famous chefs from all over.
Try and see if the local cuisine suits your taste
All right!
You first, Master Huo!
Who the heck are they?
- My name is Xia Xiang!
- My name is Xu Da Shan!
We sincerely hope
Master Huo will take us on as disciples!
We are willing to do anything for Master!
All right... you look upright enough!
Serve the wine!
After drinking this cup of wine,
we will be brothers!
Drink it!
Congratulations, Master Huo!
Thank you, Master!
Since today is a joyous occasion,
everything is on me!
All right!
Come on, let's eat up!
Little Chui, don't wait any longer.
It's time to sleep.
Take her to her room.
Qing Qing, go back to your room and sleep.
My good child, listen to me.
It's time to sleep now!
Come on...
What is this!?
This is called coffee. It's from the west.
Not used to this?
For commoners to improve themselves...
they will have to learn modern things from others
Just like me, even though I am a scholar
I can't just think about earning money.
And those that study martial arts...
shouldn't just keep to the fighting arena.
National affairs are important too.
I'm just a fighter.
I just want to be No. 1 in Tian Jin.
Is it really that important to be number 1?
Hey, come with me...
Jing Sun, you were always
a spectator below the stage.
Now that you're up on the stage...
do you feel any different?
What's the difference?
Below the stage...
the life and death struggle on stage
has nothing to do with you.
You're just watching for fun.
But once you stand here...
you must win at all costs and never lose.
Well then, you can choose not to go on the stage.
Jing Sun, listen...
Listen to what?
I can't hear anything.
I can hear it...
You're a hero, Master Huo!
Good job! Well done!
Master Huo, greatest in the world!
Iron head technique!
Thank you!
You're great, Master!
Let's save all the trouble...
whoever signed the agreement can come all at once!
All of the challengers, up on stage! Now!
Huo Yuan Jia...
When will you become No. 1 in Tian Jin?
And what do you think?
Well, today! It's gonna be today!
What the heck are you all doing?
We want to be Master Huo's disciples,
and will do anything for Master Huo!
All right, all right! You are all good men!
Serve the wine!
After this cup of wine, we will all be brothers!
Come on, drink it!
Come on now!
Congratulations, Master Huo!
Thank you, welcome!
Boss, all of these bills are for Master Huo.
All right...
Come on, drink up!
Come on! Drink!
Get a bigger jar! Why didn't you drink it?
You have yet to defeat my step-father,
Master Qin!
Come on, drink it!
Yuen Jia,
you have already won 38 rounds consecutively...
You have no more opponents in Tian Jin!
That's not right. There's still one left.
Do you still have to fight?
In order to be
the undisputed champion in Tian Jin...
I have to keep fighting.
What about areas beyond Tian Jin?
The capital, Liang Guang, Shan Xi and Hunan.
How long will you keep fighting?
Do you think I don't understand
what you've just said?
But I can't stop! I have to keep on fighting!
Through fighting I can prove
that I'm stronger than them!
So what?
Yuan Jia...
You should stop for a moment,
and think things through carefully.
What is this?
These are the bills your disciples and friends
have spent this month!
I'll cover that.
They are just a bunch of useless thugs!
How many of them
really treat you as their brother?
This is the way things are in this circle.
It is what we call righteousness.
And this righteousness...
Fine.
I'll get someone to send you the money tomorrow.
Yuan Jia...
I didn't come here for money.
While accepting disciples and friends...
You should look at their moral qualities.
Not just how well they can drink!
Watch your step, Master Huo.
Good morning, Master Huo!
Good morning, Master Qin!
Aren't you Master Huo,
the self-proclaimed No. 1 in Tian Jin?
What a coincidence...
Master Qin. Long time, no see!
I thought you had aged and gone back to
your hometown to spend your last years.
The fact that so many people
are coming to me to be my disciple...
is something I can't help.
Oh, really?
And you prepared such a large gift for yourself!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
This large present was actually bought for you.
Go help your Master!
Welcome, Master Qin!
Master!
Never mind that your income is not enough
even for the family...
the bills from your disciples have been mounting.
What about our family assets?
They were used up three months ago.
Nothing left?
Master!
Fine, Fine. I told everyone to train properly...
but no one listens to me.
Who's responsible?
Master Qin!
Master!
Today is Master Qin's birthday!
We wish Master Qin a long life!
Well done!
Father!
I sincerely wish you a long life!
Good!
Master Huo, today is my step-father's birthday.
He has booked the whole restaurant.
If you came for a drink
could you kindly go somewhere else?
Please, Master Huo.
You aren't qualified to speak here!
Hey!
Today is my birthday.
I don't want to fight, if there's a problem,
let's discuss it another day.
As an elder...
You have no shame hurting my disciple!
I'm coming for justice today!
And what do you want?
I've already signed, if you have any guts,
put your name down!
Otherwise, bow down and apologize to me!
Excuse me! Yuan Jia!
You're too much!
Master Qin's guests are present.
Can't you discuss this some other day?
I can't stand by, while my disciple is insulted!
No matter what...
I won't allow you to cause trouble,
when people are celebrating a birthday here!
- I'm causing trouble?
- Yuan Jia!
You're just afraid
that I might destroy your restaurant!
I, Huo Yuan Jia will pay for all the damage!
I can't believe what you just said!
Leave now!
Consider our friendship for all these years over!
We've been friends for years,
and you're throwing it away?
The blade is blind...
All of you, get out!
To avoid hurting the innocent!
Come on, let's get out!
Master!
Master won again!
Let's go and have a drink!
Drink till we drop!
Careful!
Let me toast to you!
Come on, another one!
Master is invincible!
He's invincible! Just look at him!
Master Huo!
Congratulations!
You've achieved your dream
of becoming the number one in Tian Jin!
But let me tell you...
Four hours ago...
Master Qin died.
Huo Yuan Jia!
When will you become number one in Tian Jin?
Well, it's today!
It's today!
Huo Yuan Jia!
Well, it's today!
Number one in Tian Jin!
It's today!
I'm the one that killed your family!
I'll take full responsibility for my actions!
Take care of yourself, Mother.
Tell the master what you've done!
- Tell him!
- Master!
I'm so sorry... It's all my fault!
I had an affair with Master Qin's daughter.
That's why Master Qin punished me.
Master!
All the others knew about it...
I thought they would have told you about it!
Master!
He's got a fever!
I'll go and make some medicine.
After he takes it and sweats it out,
he will be fine.
He will be fine. He will be fine.
- Go, go, go!
- Go, go!
He needs to rest, go, go!
When I was 13 years old...
my vision started to deteriorate.
In my eyes,
there seemed to be a fog that could not be lifted
I cried every day.
Grandma told me...
when you're feeling unhappy you should cry.
After that, you need to move on.
But in my heart, I can see things clearly.
Do you believe that?
I'll help you wash your hair.
After some time, your hair gets tangled easily.
Wash it often and it will stay smooth and clean.
Grandma always says,
people should always keep clean
only then can you walk with ease in this world.
There aren't many knots that can't be undone.
Ah Niu!
Ah Niu, you can sleep a lot!
You sleep as much as our cow!
So I called you Ah Niu. (Niu=Cow)
Come, come, come, follow me!
Ah Niu, are you awake?