(gentle classical music)
I remember those cheers
They still ring in my ears
And for years
They'll remain in my thoughts
'Cause one night I took off my robe
And what did I do? I forgot to wear shorts
I recall every fall, every hook, every jab
The worse way a guy can get rid of his flab
As you know, my life wasn 't drab
Though I'd much... Though I'd rather
hear you cheer when you tell... No.
I'd rather hear you cheer
When I delve into Shakespeare
A horse, a horse, my kingdom for a horse
I haven 't had a winner in six months
And though I'm no Olivier
I would much rather...
If he fought Sugar Ray, he would say
That the thing ain 't the ring, it's the play
So give me a stage
Where this bull here can rage
And though I can fight
I'd much rather recite
That's entertainment.
(Jake) That's entertainment.
(commentator) Jake La Motta
and Jimmy Reeves in Cleveland.
La Motta is undefeated
but well behind on points.
The Bronx Bull has taken
a lot of punishment.
Jake is cut around the left eye...
Jack, why do we have to come to Cleveland
for you to get beat?
- Do the fucking right thing.
- He's got you by the balls, Jake.
You have to knock him out.
- Bite him, kick him, do anything you gotta do.
- (Jake's trainer) Listen to Joey.
Just like home. Knock the motherfucker out.
You understand? Knock him out.
You wanna go in there?
(woman screams)
(woman) Help!
We need a knockout. That's where it's at.
- Tenth and final round.
- Good luck.
(commentator) La Motta fighting
out of a half crouch.
A tough fighter.
He doesn 't know how to back up.
La Motta continues to bore in.
A bob and weave.
And Reeves is down!
The crowd is urging Jake on.
The referee is tolling over Reeves.
He's got to get up.
La Motta comes at him again.
Reeves misses a right, takes a left.
A hard left
and Reeves is down for the second time.
A determined Jake La Motta is making
a great comeback in the tenth round.
Reeves is up again. La Motta coming at him.
A left hook to the jaw. Another left and a right.
A hook on the jaw. Two more lefts to the head.
Reeves goes down for the third time.
The referee pulls La Motta away.
Two, three, four, five...
The referee is counting over Reeves,
but time is running out.
And there is the bell.
And Reeves has been saved by the bell,
but did La Motta do it soon enough?
It's no good. This is Ohio, not New York!
You waited too long.
Joey, put my robe on right, huh?
Put my robe on right.
- Ladies and gentlemen!
- (bell rings)
Under the rules of the Ohio Boxing Commission,
after ten rounds,
the winner by unanimous decision...
...Jimmy Reeves Junior!
Jake La Motta, the Bronx Bull,
has lost his first fight.
That's Jake's fight! Come on!
Jake won that goddamn fight!
Don 't leave. Don 't get out of the fucking ring.
You won. Let him go first. Stay here.
(commentator) La Motta floored Reeves
seven times, but La Motta still lost.
(cheering)
(crowd chanting) Jake! Jake! Jake!
(whistle blows)
(bell rings)
(screaming)
No!
("The Star-Spangled Banner")
He's dead, and they tell him he won the fight.
People went crazy.
That shit woulda never happened
if Tommy was there.
He's gotta be with Tommy to get a title shot.
He'll wind up punch drunk, your brother.
- I know.
- Make him understand it's the best thing.
- I said I know.
- But you gotta make him know.
- Make him understand it.
- Jesus Christ, when the fuck you gonna stop?
I told you, I understand.
He just wants to do things for himself.
You got a head like concrete.
You think it's easy? Why don 't you talk to him?
- I can 't talk to him.
- Why?
- He don 't like me.
- Nobody likes you.
They knew. They knew who's the boss.
The judges didn 't know.
What happened with them? The people knew.
You don 't believe me.
You thought I was fooling around.
You thought I was fooling around, didn 't you?
- I ain 't fooling around. That's in your mind.
- Yeah, so what?
When I get that championship belt on me,
that's when I fool around.
- Is it done?
- No, it's not done.
Don 't overcook it.
If you overcook it, it's no good.
It defeats its own purpose.
What are you doin '?
I just said don 't overcook it. Bring it over.
- You want your steak?
- Bring it over. Bring it over!
It's like charcoal. Bring it over here!
- You want your steak?
- Yeah, right now!
Good. There's your stupid steak.
Can 't wait for it to be done.
- No, I can 't wait.
- Good. OK? Happy? Happy?
- That's all I want.
- There. No, more.
- You're bothering me about steak, huh?
- That's great! Yeah!
We should be with Tommy.
If he's in a good mood, I'll talk to him.
Tommy tells me every day to talk to you.
I'm gonna wind up in the middle.
- I'm his brother. He's got me fuckin ' nuts.
- If you can 't talk to him, who can?
- I'll talk to him.
- Do what you can.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Where are you gonna be?
- At the gym or the other joint.
- I'll catch you by the gym.
(under breath) Go fuck yourself.
- Complain some more. I wanna hear.
- (Jake) Complain?
- I wanna hear.
- Call those carrots?
- You ate them. Did you eat them?
- I got no choice!
- I can 't believe you!
You got no choice?
Get in there. Get in there!
- I can 't get nothing right from you.
- (banging)
- What's the matter with you, you animals?
- What?
- You animal!
- Son of a bitch is calling me an animal.
- Hey, you!
- Come on, Jack.
I'm gonna get that dog and eat it for lunch.
- You hear me, Larry? Larry?
- (dog barks)
- Crazy animal!
- Who's an animal?
Your mother's an animal, you son of a bitch!
You're gonna find your dog
dead in the hallway tomorrow.
- (wife) I can 't take it!
- People can hear you. Relax.
- I can 't take this any more!
- You break anything, I'm gonna kill you.
- I'm gonna come in there and kill you.
- Yeah, sure.
- You wanna calm down?
- (wife shrieks) Oh, fuck!
- What'd I do?
- I'm fed up with this!
Come on, let's be friends.
- Truce, all right?
- It's not all right!
I'm tellin ' you, you can 't
fuckin ' eat and drink like an animal,
put up with this, you can 't do this.
Forget about the Reeves thing.
You got a million other fights coming up.
You just can 't keep doing this.
What's wrong?
Something's the matter. What's up?
You know what's bothering me?
- My hands.
- Your hands? What about 'em?
I got these small hands,
like a little girl's hands.
I got 'em too. What's the difference?
Know what that means?
No matter how big I get, no matter who I fight,
I ain 't never gonna fight Joe Louis.
He's a heavyweight,
you're a middleweight. We know that.
I ain 't never gonna fight the best there is,
and I'm better than him.
I ain 't never gonna get a chance.
You asked me what was wrong.
You're crazy to even think about that.
He's a heavyweight, you're a middleweight.
It'll never happen,
so why go crazy thinkin ' about it?
It's not normal.
- Do me a favour.
- What?
- I want you to hit me in the face.
- Forget about it.
- Joey, hit me in the face. Go ahead.
- Forget about it. I ain 't doin ' it.
- We have fights all the time. Hit me.
- No.
- Are you afraid?
- Of what?
- Don 't be a little faggot. Hit me.
- I ain 't a faggot.
- Take your best shot.
- Come on, you gotta be a real jerk.
Hey, Joey, did I not tell you just to do it?
- I ain 't hittin ' you.
- I'm your older brother.
- I'm tellin ' you somethin '.
- I know what you said. I ain 't doin ' it.
I don 't care if you get mad.
I ain 't doin ' it. Fuckin ' nut.
I'm not doin ' it.
I don 't have any gloves, anyway.
- Use that over there.
- What?
Use that. Wrap it around your hand.
How many times I gotta tell you?
Not many more. Want me to hit you?
Hit me with everything you got.
Lay me out.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
Harder.
You throw a punch
like you take it up the ass. Harder.
- Harder.
- That's hard, you fuck. What do you want?
- Take it off.
- You wanna stop now? That's enough.
- Come on!
- Don 't fuck around.
- I'm gonna smack you again. Throw it again.
- That's enough.
- Harder, harder.
- No, your fucking cuts are opening.
What are you tryin ' to prove?
What does it prove?
Hey, Vito.
Joey, what's what?
Hey, Jake, you're looking good.
How you doin '?
Don 't stay here.
Joey.
Come here. What's going on?
He looks mad, huh? Looks mad.
I spoke to him yesterday.
You tell them to come up here?
- Answer me.
- Yeah. Why? Can 't I have my friends here?
- I'll break his head.
- Take it easy.
- Don 't ever bring them up here.
- (bell rings)
They look like two fags up there.
(punches continue thudding)
(bell rings)
Joey, we're gonna go. I'll call you tomorrow.
Hey, Jake, watch you don 't hurt yourself.
How's your wife? Everything OK?
Anybody bothers you, let me know.
- Go ahead. Wave. They're your friends.
- What is wrong with you?
They only came
'cause Tommy told 'em to try to help us.
What's the matter with you? Help who?
How are they gonna help me? By taking
my money? Is that what you're talking about?
I'm here breaking my ass, not them.
Don 't ever bring them here again.
You a jerk?
I'm a jerk? You're a fucking asshole.
Why the fuck are you hittin ' me?
Yeah, you fuckin ' hard-on!
You fuck!
(children calling)
(man singing on radio)
Marty, give me a Coke.
Hey. You gonna go to the dance?
- (Jake) Who's that girl over there?
- (Joey) The blonde? Vickie.
- Where's she from?
- The neighbourhood.
She's a neighbourhood girl.
- What's her last name?
- Vickie, that's all I know.
Vickie.
- She knows them?
- She knows them, they know her.
She comes to the pool every day.
You know how that shit works.
- Does she go with them?
- She's 15 years old.
Where the fuck's she gonna go?
The Copacabana?
(Jake) I heard there was a girl he went with,
very beautiful. A young girl, blonde.
It's not her?
I doubt it very much.
What are you thinking about, anyway?
- She ain 't a girl you fuck and forget about.
- Why are you always cursing?
Don 't do it around me.
Do it around your friends. That's all.
She's not the kind of girl
you bang and forget about.
You gotta spend time with her,
get involved, you know.
- Did you bang her?
- No.
- Tell me the truth.
- I just told you the truth. Don 't ask me again.
I always tell you the truth.
If I didn 't, you would know.
- I took her out a couple of times.
- You didn 't try and fuck her?
- I try to fuck anything.
- She didn 't go with you?
- She didn 't go for it.
- Naturally. She knew better.
- What do you mean, she knew better?
- She knew you were an animal.
(Jake) Her whole reputation would be ruined.
- I thought he was talking to you, Vickie.
- The same guy? I gotta break his legs.
He was over here yesterday.
You missed him.
- I was up the house yesterday.
- You stay in the neighbourhood.
- I'll catch him.
- (Jake) They're in a huddle. Business meeting.
They come by the pool and they sit around
and talk, and make sure she can hear.
Hey, like the big man.
Get the fuck outta here.
Where you goin '? Don 't get your hair wet.
(Jake) Big shot.
Get 'em all in a back room, smack 'em around,
no more big shot without his gun.
They're all tough guys.
- They're all tough guys.
- (Joey) Why do you keep looking?
You're dead. You're married.
You're a married man. It's all over.
Leave the young girls for me.
(Jake) Big shot.
Let's get outta here.
We'll never get going.
- Where the hell are you going at this hour?
- Business.
- You go out, I'm going out.
- What do I care?
I'm not gonna be here
when you get back, fucking guineas!
- Why don 't you stop?
- You fucking stop!
- Business! You're gonna suck each other off!
- Have some respect.
- Suck him! Suck him, baby!
- (Jake) Larry! Hey, Larry!
Now you got something to talk about
with your fucking dog!
- Fuckin ' Jew. Why don 't you hit her with a bat?
- She's still my wife.
- How much abuse you wanna take?
- What can I do?
Leave me here like a dog!
You and your fucking ass! You too!
- What's the matter with you?
- You gonna leave me here?
I couldn 't give a shit, you fuckin ' queer! Faggot!
I called you a faggot!
(jazz music)
Oh! Beans!
Jack.
Beansie said we could sit with them.
- Which Beansie?
- Huh?
- Beansie who?
- Beans. One of the guys.
- You'll know him.
- She'll be over there?
I don 't know, but you can see from there
at least. Come on, let's go.
- Hello, Joey.
- Thanks for the seats. Hey, what's up?
I got trouble with
these fucking greaseballs downstairs.
- Jake.
- Father, how you doing?
- Father.
- Father, you wanna get laid? You're sure?
(Joey) Father, bless the table. Give us a shot.
- Did you put money in the basket?
- You'll drive the guy crazy.
- See her right there?
- I saw her, I saw her. I saw her.
- Don 't wait.
- Go ahead. Go ahead.
(impatient yelling)
Get the fuck out! Get out! Get out!
- You too! Get outta there, you fuckin ' bum!
- (Jake) Go back where you came from.
Hey, Vickie! Vickie! Vickie!
- Hi, Joey. What are you doin '?
- Not too much. What are you doin '?
- That your car?
- No, it's my brother's.
- Did you ever meet my brother?
- No. Is that him?
- Wanna meet him?
- All right.
Hey, Jack.
Come here.
This is my brother Jake.
He's gonna be the next champ.
- (Vickie) Oh.
- How you doin '?
Nice to meet you.
- Nice car.
- You like that car?
It's nice.
Where you from?
Round here.
You wanna go for a ride?
All right. Give me a few minutes.
I have to change, OK?
- All right, I'll be back in a while.
- I'll be over there.
(The Ink Spots singing "Do I Worry")
Move over.
- I never played this game before.
- It's the only way to learn. I'll show you.
- That's right.
- Like this? Hit it?
Hit the little one.
You see it?
No.
What does that mean?
It means the game is over. Come on, let's go.
(knocking)
Daddy!
Dad!
Come on in.
Probably went shopping or somethin '.
Let me see.
Daddy?
Yeah, he must have gone shopping. Sit down.
- You want something to eat?
- No.
- Sure?
- Mm-hm.
Salute
Why don 't you sit over here?
Sit a little closer.
You're so far away,
like on the other side of the room.
(she laughs)
Come here. Come here.
Come here. Sit over here.
Come over here a minute. Come here.
That's better.
No. Thank you, anyway.
Some water?
Wanna see the rest of the place?
- All right.
- I bought it for my father. I bought the building.
Oh, yeah?
- From fighting?
- Yeah.
What else?
This is the dining room.
That's a bird. It was a bird.
He's dead now, I think.
(mutters)
Sit down.
That's me and my brother,
fooling around.
I know.
You look good, though.
- What are you smiling about?
- I don 't know.
Do you know how beautiful you are?
Anybody ever tell you you're beautiful?
Yeah, they tell you all the time.
(commentator) Sugar Ray Robinson and
Jake La Motta in Detroit for their second fight.
The undefeated Sugar Ray
defeated Jake at Madison Square Garden.
You can see the contrast in their styles.
The speedy Ray Robinson up on his toes.
La Motta moves in flat-footed most of the time.
Now he's hurt Robinson.
La Motta coming at Robinson again.
A left and a right.
- A left hand to the body thrown by La Motta.
- (bell rings)
Round eight,
and it's anybody's fight at this point.
La Motta drives both hands to the head.
Left hand to the jaw, right to the body.
Robinson with a right on the nose.
La Motta drives him across the ring.
A hard left and Robinson is driven out of
the ring, for the first knockdown of his career.
This is the nearest Robinson has been to a loss.
The fight nears its end.
La Motta has taken charge.
The undefeated Sugar Ray,
his winning ways are in jeopardy.
La Motta coming at him again,
feigning a left hand.
(bell rings)
After ten rounds, Judge Rossi,
eight to two, La Motta.
(cheering)
Judge Murphy, seven to three, La Motta.
- (cheering)
- (commentator) La Motta has won the fight.
A unanimous decision for the Bronx Bull,
handing Sugar Ray Robinson
his first loss as a professional,
and Robinson doesn 't like it.
With this victory, La Motta broke
what was considered the impossible,
the invincible Sugar Ray's record.
La Motta has proved he shouldn 't be denied
a shot at the middleweight crown.
- Are you sure we should be doing this?
- (Jake) Come here.
You said never to touch you before a fight.
- Come here, before I give you a beating.
- You've been good for two weeks.
Come here.
Touch my boo-boos.
Ah!
The boo-baas. That's it.
- Boo-baas?
- Boo-boo. Give the boo-boo a kiss.
Make it better.
Mm.
- Take off my pants.
- Jake.
Go ahead. Take off my pants.
(unfastens belt)
(unzips flies)
Now take off the rest.
- You made me promise not to get you excited.
- Go ahead. Do it.
Take off your panties.
I like the gym smell.
Huh?
I like the smell of the gym.
All right, enough.
I can 't do any more. I can 't do any more.
I gotta fight Robinson. I can 't fool around.
Ah-ah-ah-ah!
What are you doin '? What are you doin '?
What are you doin ' to me?
(commentator) La Motta and Robinson
meet for the third time.
These men are unique, becoming classic rivals.
These two men, fierce, powerful fighters,
so dangerous that no other fighter
will go near them.
So they fight each other, three weeks apart.
They've each won one, and they'll probably
fight again, the way it looks now.
- (bell rings)
- They go to close quarters at the bell.
Round seven, with Sugar Ray ahead on points.
La Motta may need a knockout.
And Robinson is down
for the second time in his career.
He was down in the last fight too.
La Motta watches Sugar Ray
take the count from the referee.
- Robinson trying to get up.
- (referee)... six, seven, eight...
He's up on his feet and the referee
is wiping off his gloves. He is stunned.
La Motta comes at him. Despite being knocked
down, Robinson is well ahead on points.
- He hooks a left to the jaw.
- (bell rings)
(bell rings)
(announcer) Your attention, fans!
Judge Joe Lanahan scores at eight, one,
one even in favour of Sugar Ray Robinson.
(booing)
(commentator) A big vote
for Sugar Ray Robinson.
(announcer) Six, two and two even
for the winner by unanimous decision,
Sugar Ray Robinson!
(Joey) Cocksuckers! Fucking...
For Christ's sake!
(mutters)
They only gave that fucking decision
'cause he's going in the army.
I knocked him down.
I don 't know what else I gotta do.
You won! They robbed you. They're miserable
because their mothers take it up the ass.
I've done bad things. It's coming back to me.
(knocking)
I'm a jinx maybe. Who the hell knows?
Forget about all that shit.
This was your shot. They robbed us!
- Jake, it's Vickie. You wanna talk to her?
- No, I don 't wanna talk to nobody.
- Joey, take her home.
- All right.
- Jack, you gonna be all right?
- Yeah.
- You sure?
- Make sure she's all right.
All right.
(door closes)
(gentle classical music)
(voice on radio)
Ho, don 't ever do that Janiro bullshit again.
No more deals like that.
- What are you talking about?
- Look at that. 168Ibs.
- Stop eating.
- I told you I didn 't wanna do it, didn 't I?
No, you didn 't. You told me
you could get down to 155Ibs.
- Did I pull it out of the fuckin ' air?
- I'm lucky I make it to 160.
On top of that, you sign me for a fight at 155.
If I don 't make it, I lose 15,000 dollars.
- You're supposed to be a manager!
- I did what I wanted.
- That's what I'm worried about.
- You want a title shot?
What am I, in a circus over here?
- I ask him, he's got more sense.
- You've been killing yourself for three years.
There's nobody left for you to fight.
Everybody's afraid to fight you.
Along comes this kid Janiro.
He's young, up-and-coming, he'll fight anybody.
Good. You fight him.
Bust his hole. Tear him apart. Right?
- What are you worried about?
- The weight.
- The weight?
- I just said the weight!
Let's say you lose because of your weight.
Will they think you're not as tough as you were?
Good. They'll match you with guys
they were afraid to before.
- You'll kill 'em. They'll give you a title shot.
- Coffee, please.
Why? There's nobody else.
Who they gonna give it to?
- Coffee.
- In a minute.
- You listenin ' to me?
- Please, bring me a coffee.
- How long I gotta wait?
- (Joey) Are you listenin '?
Let's say you win, you beat Janiro.
You definitely should beat him.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- They still gotta give you a shot at the title.
- Why?
There's nobody left.
They gotta give you the shot. You understand?
If you win, you win. If you lose, you still win.
There's no way you can lose.
And you'll do it on your own,
without any help from anybody.
Just get down to 155Ibs, you fat bastard.
Stop eating. What's the problem?
- You can do it. You understand that?
- Joey's right.
Janiro's up-and-coming, good-Iooking, popular.
- You beat him now...
- What do you mean, good-Iooking?
- I'm saying popular. If you win...
- Who are you to say good-Iooking?
- I'm just telling you Joey's right.
- Are you an authority or what?
Get outta here.
Take the baby and get outta here.
Everybody all of a sudden 's an authority.
Where did she find out he's good-Iooking?
(Joey's wife) She didn 't mean nothin '.
- Who asked you?
- You gonna start with me now?
When people are talking, you don 't interrupt.
It's none of your business.
Especially if it's my brother and his wife.
Get outta here. Take the baby inside.
Come on. Let's leave the grouches here, OK?
- Come on.
- Change her diaper.
- She's gonna cry. She stinks.
- You make her cry.
- I'm gonna make you cry.
- Yeah. Mm-hm.
- They're a couple of babies.
- (Joey) 155Ibs. Let's go to the training camp.
No distractions. No wives, no phone calls.
Nobody around to bother you.
- Your usual schedule, usual diet...
- Joey, I wanna ask you somethin '.
When I'm away,
you notice anything funny with her?
- Vickie?
- Yeah.
- Like what?
- What do you think I mean?
- I don 't notice anything.
- I want you to keep an eye on her.
- For what? She don 't do anything wrong.
- Keep an eye on her when I'm away.
- You start trouble for nothing.
- I got a reason.
You and I both know any woman,
given the right time, place, circumstance,
they'll do anything. Anything's possible, right?
You're right, you're not wrong,
but you're picking on this girl.
You're worried about your weight
and you tell her, "Go inside. Who asked you?"
You're gonna give her an excuse to go out.
- She was talking about a guy.
- So what? She was talking on your behalf.
She was talking about a pretty kid,
saying he's good-Iooking.
- So you make him ugly.
- Never mind. Just do it.
You know what you should do?
Go inside and make up with her.
And we'll go out before you go away.
You'll go away with a clear head. You took
her out and had a good time. All right?
All right. Where do you wanna go?
- Out out, you know.
- All right.
Listen, though, if you tell her now, don 't say
nothin ' in front of Lenore. I'm not taking her.
What do you think, I'm gonna tell her?
- Do what you're gonna do.
- I am.
Hey, hey, hey.
Come here.
Good evening.
It's great to be back in the Copa Lounge.
What a great audience! Lady, lap it up.
I laugh when you come in.
But, seriously speaking,
we have a special guest tonight.
I'd like to introduce the world's
leading middleweight contender,
the Bronx Bull, the Raging Bull,
let's hear it for the great Jake La Motta,
ladies and gentlemen!
- What's your name again?
- Janet.
Janet, sorry. Just couldn 't...
It's toast time.
He hits me with a left hook.
No hand, just a hook he had.
- Where are you goin '?
- I'm going to the bathroom.
- Hey, Vickie.
- Hi.
- You're looking great. Joey here?
- Over there. Jake's here too.
I'm over here with Tommy
and some of the old gang.
If you get a chance,
come over and have a drink.
- Hello, Jake. How are you?
- How you doin '?
You're not drinking, are you?
Joey, how are you?
- How you doin ', Salvy?
- Look like you're having a ball.
- I'm with Tommy Como. Come over.
- Tommy's here? I didn 't see him come in.
I'll see you later, Joey.
That's some suit. He looks good, huh, Jack?
(laughter)
I thought that was my best joke.
- Look who's here.
- (man) Hi, Vickie.
- (women) Hi, Vickie.
- Hey, Vickie.
How are you, honey? Good to see you.
Say hello to Charlie. Sit down, have a drink.
- I can 't. I have to get back to Jake.
- Thanks for coming by.
- Not a bad kid, Vickie.
- She's with that fuckin ' gorilla.
She must have caught
a hundred beatings off that guy.
- What took you so long?
- I went by Tommy's table.
I saw you say hello to them.
What took you so long?
- Nothing. I said hello and then I came back.
- What else did you say?
He asked if I wanted a drink,
I said no and left.
- What were you talking to Salvy for?
- He asked me if Joey was here.
Then he said Tommy's over there,
say hello, and I did.
- Are you interested in him?
- No. Why would I be?
- You sure you're not interested in him?
- Yeah.
You're not interested,
but you could be interested in somebody?
Jake, don 't start, huh?
(Jake) Shut up or I'm gonna
smack you in the face.
These are... These are from... Mr Como.
- Shall I take the...
- What?
- Shall I take this?
- I'm not through with it.
These are the jokes, folks.
I'll tell you the truth...
- Hi, how are you? Bald-headed fag.
- (laughter)
- Hey, Joey.
- Tommy. Thanks for the drinks.
- How are you?
- How's everything?
- (Tommy) Where's Jake?
- (Joey) He's over there. He don 't wanna come.
(Joey) If you call him, he'll come.
I'll be right back.
You don 't call anybody any more.
We never see you any more.
You can 't even make a call? What is it?
- I'm busy. I'm out of town a lot.
- Busy.
Look at him taking me seriously.
I'm only kidding you.
What a fuckin ' kid!
That's the best fuckin ' fighter around.
Them mulenyams. Forget about it.
They're all afraid to fight you. How you feelin '?
- I'm all right.
- Strong?
- Strong, yeah.
- Janiro's gotta watch his ass, right?
- I think he should.
- I won nothing but money with the guy.
- He's no piece of cake.
- Attractive. All the girls like him.
No marks. Clean.
Jake, did you gain a few pounds?
- Yeah, I'll knock it off right away.
- Right off.
Right off.
Let me ask you something.
I'm just talking.
I'm telling you that I'm gonna bet
a lot of money on you, this fight with Janiro.
Yeah.
What would you tell me?
What could you say to me?
- I would say bet everything you got.
- Everything?
Everything. 'Cause I'm gonna open his hole
like this. Excuse my French, girls.
- I'll make him suffer.
- What's the matter with him?
I'm gonna make his mother
wish she never had him.
Didn 't he say something in the papers?
No, he's a nice kid, a pretty kid, too.
I got a problem,
whether I should fuck him or fight him.
- Fuck him or fight him!
- You're liable to get fucked. Watch out.
- By who?
- Janiro.
- You want me to get him to fuck you?
- Me? No.
I could do that easily. I'll give you both
a beating and you both can fuck each other.
- I'll get all full of blood.
- You're used to that.
(Tommy) Come on. Drink up.
That's ginger ale, Jake.
Salute
- Jake, good luck.
- Good luck, Jake.
Hey, Vickie.
- Vickie.
- What?
You awake?
No.
- Can you hear me?
- What?
You ever think of anybody else...
when we're in bed?
- What do you mean?
- You know, like when we make love.
No, nobody, I love you.
How come you said that thing about Janiro?
- What did I say?
- You said he had a pretty face.
I never noticed his face.
Well, how come you said that, then?
I don 't know what I said. I don 't even know
what he looks like. Go to sleep.
(cheering)
(bell rings cheering)
(crowd chanting) Jake! Jake! Jake!
- He ain 't pretty no more.
- He really messed him up.
(announcer) And the winner,
by unanimous decision,
in ten rounds, Jake La Motta!
Give me a little piece of ice,
just for my tongue.
- No water!
- Come on, I'm dying.
Fuckin ' hard-on.
Four pounds. Keep workin '. Come on, move.
I saw the fight with Janiro.
Destroyed this guy. Incredible.
He knocked his nose from one side of his face
to the other. It was hanging off.
- Who are you fighting next?
- I don 't know. He's away in training camp.
- They gotta give him that title shot.
- Jackie Curtie, Joey.
- I heard a lot of nice things about you.
- We're gonna get the title shot.
- I like your brother. Made money on him.
- Probably more than he did.
- (Curtie) On the Oscar Jackson fight.
- Whatever happened to Oscar?
- You see him any more?
- He's punchy. Probably died. Who cares?
- It's a beautiful table.
- It's the worst table in the house.
(Curtie) He's working downtown. Big building.
Working an elevator. Happened to be there.
I'm not Italian. I don 't care.
- Took me right up.
- Oscar did you a lot of good.
- He was tough.
- (Curtie) Gave a hell of a fight.
- Cutty Sark and water.
- Excuse me one minute, fellas.
Come back, Joey. Come on back. OK.
(Salvy) Hey, Joe. Hey, Joey.
Look how he's looking. Something's up.
- They're having a problem.
- You're worried about it?
- (Vickie) I was just having a drink.
- Shut up!
I feel like a prisoner. I look at somebody
the wrong way, I get smacked.
- You think you're right?
- I am right.
- No, you're wrong.
- I'm tired of having both of you up my ass.
- Shut up.
- I'm tired of listening to you.
Don 't make me get nuts in this place.
- I gotta sleep by myself every night?
- What did you marry him for?
- I love him.
- You do?
- This guy don 't even wanna fuck me.
- He's just been a contender too long.
It'll be all right as soon as he gets his shot,
and then everything'll be OK.
Too many people hate him.
- You're drinking with them.
- I'm gonna have a good time.
Get your stuff.
You ain 't stayin ' here.
You're makin ' an asshole out of my brother.
- Joey, relax.
- Shut up! Mind your fuckin ' business!
- You're takin ' this all wrong.
- I said shut up, didn 't I?
There's nothing goin ' on here.
We're only havin ' a few drinks.
- Relax, no problem.
- You know better than that.
- Let's all calm down.
- We've been friends a long time.
- It's my brother's wife.
- There's nothing goin ' on.
I'm sorry. We can straighten this out, right?
Nothing goin ' on? Nothing goin ' on?
You dirty cocksucker!
(women screaming)
(Joey) Fuckin ' hard-on!
I'll bite your fuckin ' head off!
Joey! What the fuck are you doin '?
Come on. Come on.
Fucking cunt.
- Stop him!
- I'm gonna suck your fuckin ' eyes out!
- (shouting)
- Who are these fucking Indians here?
Don 't mention Tommy.
You do what you do, we do what we do.
- You're wrong, Joe.
- He's wrong!
- (woman) Stop him!
- (shouting)
Get him away!
Take it easy.
(gentle classical music)
(Tommy) You got a lot of years between you,
done a lot of things together.
Joey, it was your brother's wife,
but you don 't create a scene like that
in a place like that.
We've heard everybody's point of view here,
and we're gonna forget about it.
I shouldn 't forget about it,
but we're gonna forget about it, huh?
I want you two guys to shake hands,
forget this whole thing, and no grudges.
That's the most important thing. No grudges.
Now come on. S hake hands
It's all right with me if it's all right with you, huh?
- I only wish this thing never happened.
- We all wish it never happened.
- We'll get over it.
- Salvy, let me talk with him alone a minute.
- All right? I'll see you Monday, Tuesday.
- Ooh!
I'm sorry. I forgot all about it.
Are you fuckin ' nuts? You're killin ' me.
Aside from everything else, the family all right?
Yeah, they're fine. Everybody's fine.
- What, you can 't talk?
- What do you mean?
Why have you got this funny attitude?
I can 't figure you out.
What is it with all the quick answers?
"Yeah, they're all right."
- You wanna get outta here?
- It's not like that.
Just, you know, all the aggravation
and everything, and all the fights.
Listen to me. Now, Jake,
the guy's become an embarrassment.
He's embarrassing me with certain people
and I'm looking very bad.
I can 't deliver a kid
from my own goddamn neighbourhood.
Why does he have to make it
so hard on himself?
He comes to me, I make it easier for him.
The man 's got a head of rock.
It's hard to explain, Tommy.
Jack respects you.
He don 't even say hello to anybody.
You, he talks to, he likes you.
But when he gets something on his mind,
he likes to do things his own way.
Jesus Christ could come off the cross,
he don 't give a fuck,
he wants to make it on his own.
Make it on his own. He thinks he's gonna walk
in there and become champion on his own.
- Yeah, he's crazy. He's nuts.
- Yeah, he's crazy.
He's got no respect.
He doesn 't listen to nobody.
- That's not crazy.
- He respects you.
He doesn 't respect anybody.
Now, you do this for me.
You tell him I don 't care how colourful he is,
how great he is.
He could beat
all the Sugar Ray Robinsons in the world,
but he ain 't gonna get a shot
at that title without us.
You're a smart kid.
You go to him and you tell him.
(thunder)
Son of a bitch. 20-dollar shoes.
Aren 't you gonna ask me what happened?
Huh?
What's the matter?
- Ho! What's wrong?
- I remember when I met her here.
- Who?
- Vickie.
Why? What's the matter? What did she do now?
Huh?
I know she's doin ' somethin '.
I just wanna catch her once. Just once.
Jack, wanna do yourself a favour?
Bust her fuckin ' hole, throw her out.
Either that or live with her and let her
ruin your life, 'cause that's what's happening.
How much could you take?
How much shit could you take?
So what did that guy say?
He gave me the "good news, bad news" routine.
The good news is
you're gonna get the shot at the title.
The bad news is
they want you to do the old flip-flop for them.
- What else is new?
- You didn 't see that coming?
Ah, you win some, you lose some.
This one we'll lose.
Billy Fox. 173 and three quarter pounds.
Jake La Motta. 167...
I guess you've heard a lot of the stuff
going around, rumours.
A short time ago you were a big favourite.
Now you're a 12 to 5 underdog.
- People are talking.
- I never heard anything.
It's out there, and it's not good.
The bets are off on this one. Nothing going.
Smart money is saying
you're getting ready to hit the tank.
- That's bullshit.
- Yeah, it's bullshit.
You got any money you wanna bet?
You bet it on Fox.
'Cause I'm gonna win.
I don 't go down for nobody.
- That's all I wanna hear.
- I want you to know that.
- You came down here just for that?
- That was it.
(bell rings)
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to
the Madison Square Garden feature attraction.
In this corner, with...
- Commissioner, how about a picture?
- Can we get a picture over here?
Billy Fox!
(cheering and applause)
Hey, Steve, your brother
got out of the hospital? Did he get out?
- Charlie, let me sit over there, will you?
- Sure.
- Tommy, what's the matter? You all right?
- All right, yeah.
Touch gloves now. Come out boxing.
vo soco nds
(bell rings)
Come on, stand up. Stand up!
What the fuck you doin '?
Hit me, you fuckin ' bum. Come on. Come on!
- What are you doin ', Jake? Box him!
- (booing)
(bell rings)
What the fuck's the matter with you?
- What do you think you're doin '?
- A little slow.
- What are you doin '?
- Take it easy. He'll be all right.
- He'll make it up.
- Come on, pick it up a little, Jake. I'm sorry.
(spectator) Come on, Jake.
I got some money on you!
- Hit him back, you bum! Hit him back!
- You can 't take a dive in the fourth!
Keep your dirty money!
You phoney bastard! The fight's a fix!
They stopped the fight, you jerk,
and you standing there. Go down.
(announcer) We stop this bout
at 2 minutes 26 seconds of the fourth round.
The winner, by technical knockout,
and still undefeated, Billy Fox!
(sobs)
Don 't fight any more.
It's a free country. Don 't fight any more.
(Jake) Aw, what did I do? What did I do?
- What did I do?
- (Joey sniffs)
What did I do?
(shouting)
It's all right, Jake. It's all right.
Why did I fuckin ' fight him?
They got some balls. Some balls.
I take the dive.
They want me to go down, too?
- I ain 't goin ' down for nobody.
- Do me a favour. Put your hands up.
Put your hands up.
- What the fuck is so hard about that?
- Joey, you don 't understand!
I had to fight a bum. He's a bum.
I tapped him, he's all over the place.
You don 't have to fuckin ' pick him up.
If I don 't pick him up,
I'm gonna be in worse trouble.
- I don 't know.
- Look at this.
"Purse was withheld pending DA's probe."
Look at that.
Look how they make me look.
- Like a bum, like a Mameluke.
- A what?
Like the Mameluke of the year.
Tommy ain 't gonna forget us. He's gonna
get you a shot as long as he don 't die.
- As long as who don 't die?
- Tommy.
- What are you talking about?
- Tommy's gonna get you a shot.
- If he don 't die.
- He got a disease?
- No, I'm just saying.
- What's wrong with him?
I mean, that's the only way
you wouldn 't get it is if he dies.
(Joey) It's an outdoor arena.
You wanna fight in the rain?
- You waited this long, you can wait longer.
- I don 't wanna wait 24 hours.
I don 't either, but we gotta, so we'll wait. Hello?
- You guys wanna stop now?
- Get off the phone.
- Fuckin ' reporters.
He don 't wanna talk to nobody.
Hear him yellin '?
There's enough confusion up here.
Please, don 't call.
No comment. Right, thank you. Bye.
- Pains in the asses. I don 't believe them.
- Why don 't you just hang up on 'em?
- What do you want to eat?
- I don 't want nothin '.
Eat somethin '. You gotta eat somethin '.
You can 't go without eating.
Eat a steak.
Chew it, spit it out, you'll still make the weight
tomorrow. You worried about that, huh?
All right, I'll order a steak.
If you want it, it's here.
- OK.
- Vickie, what do you want?
- Order me a piece of cake.
- All you want is a piece of cake?
Why don 't you get a cheeseburger,
French fries? It's better for you.
- That's good. Order me one of those.
- (Jake) What do you want to eat?
Since when did you order one of those?
- That's what I want.
- Order what you want.
- Don 't let nobody influence you.
- (Joey) I was just suggesting.
- Why are you telling her what to ask for?
- I don 't give a fuck what she eats.
- What are you telling her for?
- Order me a cheeseburger.
Just order her a cheeseburger, that's all.
What the f?
- How long does this thing take to do?
- 40 seconds.
You gotta do it in 30 seconds.
If we gotta stitch him up, that's how much time.
- (knocking)
- Jack? You up? Ho!
- What?
- Somebody's here to see you.
- Tommy, how you doin '?
- How are you?
- Say hello to Charlie.
- Nice to see you.
- Lots of luck.
- How are you feelin '?
- I'm feelin ' all right.
- Are you feelin ' good?
- As good as I'm gonna feel.
- I gotta get in there and fight.
- All right.
- We came by to wish you luck. Need anything?
- No.
- Sure?
- No. Thank you, though.
Take care. Good luck. God bless you.
- You'll be all right.
- Yeah, I'll be all right.
- Say hello to everybody. Vickie, goodbye.
- (Vickie) Tommy, wait.
- (Joey) It's really nice of you. I appreciate it.
- (Tommy) Any time.
- A time like this is important to him.
- I just wanna say goodbye.
- Take care of him.
- I'll take care of him.
Joey, any little thing, call me.
He's very nervous.
Goodbye, honey.
Look at that face.
Can you believe that girl?
Just as beautiful as ever.
- Bye-bye, Tommy.
- (Tommy) So long, everybody.
So long, Tommy.
Vickie.
Vickie. Hey! Come here.
Come here a minute.
- What was all that about?
- All what?
You know what I'm talking about.
What was that all about... with him?
- I just said goodbye.
- All of a sudden you're so friendly?
You say hello, you say goodbye. You hear?
- I hear.
- Hey! You hear what I said?
You don 't ever have any disrespect for me.
You hear what I said?
- Yeah, I hear.
- All right. Go in there. Come here.
- Why don 't you stop that?
- Shut up! Shut up!
I'll fuckin ' take care of you later! Shut up!
I'm disgusted with the two of you.
I'll get to you later.
I'm the boss. I'm the boss. I'm the boss.
I'm the boss. I'm the boss.
Hit the fuckin ' thing! Hit it!
(faint cheering)
(loud cheering)
(majestic classical music)
(bell rings)
Welcome to the middleweight championship
of the world. 15 rounds.
In this corner...
(music drowns out announcer)
...quarter pounds, the Bronx Bull, Jake La Motta.
(cheering)
(referee) Shake hands now
and come out fighting at the bell.
(bell rings)
(Joey) Finish him off. He's all stupidata.
(spectator) Come on, Jake!
(Joey) Blow on him. He'll fuckin ' fall right over.
Look at him. You all right?
- He's had enough.
- Can he continue?
Commissioner, come on in.
I'm gonna stop the fight.
(bell rings)
(announcer)... Cerdan unable to continue,
the referee stops the fight, and the winner
by a technical knockout in the tenth round,
and the new middleweight
champion of the world,
the Bronx Bull, Jake La Motta!
(cheering)
(crowd chanting) Jake! Jake! Jake! Jake!
(rattling)
Don 't shake that.
Jack, don 't shake it like that.
- It's the worst thing you could do.
- (soft music on TV)
- (door closes)
- You're home.
- Hi, Vick.
- Hi, Joey.
- Hi.
- Where were you?
- Went out. What's the matter?
- Television won 't work.
Where did you go?
I went out, went shopping,
went to my sister's, you know.
(man talking on TV)
What's with this kissing on the mouth?
- Can 't I kiss my sister-in -law?
- Ain 't a cheek good enough for you?
- I don 't even kiss Mom on the mouth.
- You're not supposed to.
That's what I'm talking about.
- How's that?
- That looks like something.
Get back. I can 't see nothin '
with your stomach in the way now.
What are you giving me dirty looks for?
You're supposed to be a champion.
You eat like there's no tomorrow.
Forget how long it took you to get to the title.
You're gonna defend it next month.
Keep eating.
Giving me dirty looks
like I don 't know what I'm talkin ' about.
What happened with you and Salvy
at the Copa that time,
when you gave him a beating?
You mean when I caught his head
in the taxi-cab door?
- Yeah.
- I told you about that. Didn 't I?
- No.
- I never told you?
- You never told me.
- It was no big thing.
I smacked him in the mouth.
Had to go downtown and straighten it out
with Tommy. It's all forgotten about.
- How come you never told me about it?
- It didn 't have anything to do with you.
Had nothin ' to do with me?
Who did it have somethin ' to do with? Vickie?
I just explained the whole thing.
It was between me and Salvy.
If it had anything to do with you and Vickie,
I would have told you.
- That's not what I heard, Joe.
- What do you mean?
That's not what I heard. I heard some things.
- You heard about me and Salvy.
- I heard things, Joey.
- You heard that I cracked Salvy all around.
- I heard some things.
You heard things! Don 't start that worrying shit.
Worry about this title fight next month.
That's what you should worry about.
Do that.
Christ.
- Did Salvy fuck Vickie?
- What?
Did Salvy fuck Vickie?
Jack, don 't start your shit. No, really, don 't start.
- I asked you to keep an eye on her.
- I did.
- So how come you gave him a beating?
- That didn 't have nothin ' to do with you.
- He thinks he's a wise guy.
- Don 't lie.
- I'm not lying.
- What do I look like?
I'm your brother. Don 't you trust me?
No, I don 't trust you when it comes to her.
I don 't trust nobody.
- Now, tell me, what happened?
- I told you exactly what happened.
He got out of line, I slapped him around,
Tommy straightened it out and it's all over.
You're giving me that look, Joey.
I gotta accept your answer, you know,
but if I hear anything, I swear on our mother,
I'm gonna kill somebody.
- I'm gonna kill somebody, Joey.
- You're the tough guy. Go kill people!
Kill Vickie, Salvy, Tommy Como.
Kill me while you're at it.
You're killin ' yourself the way you eat,
you fat fuck.
What do you mean, kill you?
Me, kill me. Start here. Do me a fuckin ' favour,
'cause you're drivin ' me crazy.
- You're a big shot. Just kill. You're a killer.
- What do you mean by you?
- So? What does that mean?
- Even you don 't know what you meant.
- Don 't mean nothin '.
- Joey, that meant somethin '.
You mentioned Tommy, Salvy, you.
You included you with them.
You could have said anybody,
but you said you and them.
You let this girl ruin your life. Know how
fuckin ' nuts you are? Look what she did to you.
- You fuck my wife?
- What?
You fuck my wife?
How could you ask me a question like that?
I'm your brother. You ask me that?
Where do you get your balls
big enough to ask me that?
Just tell me.
I'm not answerin ' you.
I'm not gonna answer that. It's stupid.
You're very smart, Joey.
You've given me all these answers,
but you ain 't given me the right answer.
I'm gonna ask you again.
- Did you or did you not?
- I'm not gonna answer.
It's a sick question,
and I'm not that sick that I'm gonna answer it.
I'm gonna leave. I'm not stayin '
in this nuthouse with you. I feel sorry for you.
Try a little more fuckin ' and a little less eatin '.
You won 't have troubles upstairs
and you won 't pick it out on me.
You understand, you fuckin ' wacko?
You're crackin ' up.
Fuckin ' screwball, you.
- Where were you?
- I was at my sister's.
- Where did you go after that?
- To the movies.
What did you see?
Father of the Bride
How come you didn 't tell me
about the Copa? Huh?
- Tell you what about it?
- You know.
How come you didn 't tell me about it?
Why didn 't you tell me about it, huh?
- I don 't know what you're talking about.
- Why didn 't you tell me?
- Did you fuck my brother? Did you?
- Get off me, you fat pig! No!
(locks door)
- Open the door.
- Get away!
- I wanna talk to you.
- You're sick!
- Why did you fuck Joey?
- Get away!
- Open the door.
- No.
(screams)
- Why'd you do it?
- I didn 't do anything!
Why'd you do it? Why did you fuck them?
I didn 't do anything! I fucked all of them!
- Who'd you fuck?
- All of them. Tommy, Salvy, your brother.
I sucked your brother's cock.
What do you want me to say?
- You sucked his cock?
- Yeah, and everybody else on the street.
You're nothin ' but a fat, pig, selfish fool!
- Get...
- I'm gonna fuckin ' hit you.
His fuckin ' cock's bigger than yours too!
Where are you goin '?
Where are you goin ', you bastard?
You sick animal! Where are you goin '?
Get off of me, you piece of shit!
If you put your hands in that plate one more
time, I'm gonna stab you with this knife.
- Christ.
- Can 't eat in peace here. Relax.
I don 't have to eat like you...
Jack! Jack! What's the matter with you?
You fucked my wife, huh?
- You fucked my wife!
- (screaming)
Jake, get off of him!
- I'll kill you!
- Stop it! He didn 't do it!
(Lenore screams) I'll call the police!
I'm gonna fuckin ' kill you!
Get out!
(silence)
Vickie, don 't leave, honey. Please.
Honey, look, I'm a bum
without you and the kids. Don 't go.
(murmurs)
Mm?
Less than a minute to go and La Motta
is losing the title he won from Cerdan.
After the plane crash that took Cerdan 's life,
Dauthuille vowed
to bring the title back to France.
Tonight he only has to last this 15th round
to be crowned the new middleweight champion.
La Motta is taking terrible punishment,
as Dauthuille bangs him
with lefts and rights to the head.
And La Motta's been playing possum.
He's got Dauthuille hurt.
A right hand to the body,
two left hooks to the jaw.
Dauthuille is reeling around the ring.
The tide has turned, no question about it.
And he wobbles into the ropes
and goes down.
Dauthuille is down, and the referee
comes over and starts the count.
He's trying to get up. Six, seven.
He'll never make it. Nine, ten.
- You're out!
- It is all over. He is knocked out.
Jake La Motta,
with 13 seconds left in the final round,
has made one of the most remarkable
comebacks in boxing history.
Come on.
Just tell him you're sorry, you miss him.
He's your brother.
You have to talk to him sooner or later.
I'll dial him for you. Then you talk to him.
Tell him you're sorry, then say what you want.
Hm?
- OK.
- Champ, I'd like to ask you a few questions.
- Not now.
- Excuse me.
- A great angle here...
- Don 't bother me, please. Get outta here.
- Come on.
Get outta here. Get outta here.
I asked you nice...
(ringing tone)
(Joey) Hello?
Hello?
Salvy, this ain 't funny any more.
Is that you?
I know somebody's there.
I can hear you breathing. You listenin '?
Your mother sucks
fuckin ' big fuckin ' elephant dicks.
You got that?
(mouths)
(distorted echoing sounds)
(groans)
The fight of the year. The next time
that bartender says, "What'll you have?",
give that answer the world gives:
Pabst Blue Ribbon.
Those punches by La Motta
explain themselves.
They fought five times
between 1942 and 1945.
It has so far been a blazing bout
for the middleweight championship.
La Motta couldn 't score the big one.
That's it. That was the last shot.
- Round number 13, the hard-luck number.
- (buzzer)
There's the buzzer,
and you know both the boys.
Robinson hurting La Motta.
He's hurting him now.
He has La Motta on Queer Street, holding on.
That was one of the most damaging evidences
of punching you have seen in recent years.
Come on! Come on, come on!
Come on! Come on!
Come on! What are you standing there for?
Robinson, apparently tired,
punched with a fare-thee-well
and rocked La Motta to his heels.
Come on, Ray.
These are clean, whistling shots.
How he can survive them, nobody knows.
No man can endure this punishment.
The fight is stopped
on a signal from Frankie Sikora.
Row after row after row from the ring,
the crowd is standing and cheering,
as he just cannonaded Jake La Motta
into a certain defeat.
When I say that, I mean
Jake wouldn 't wanna quit. He wanted to go.
Hey, Ray. I never went down, Ray.
You never got me down, Ray.
You hear me? You never got me down.
You hear? See? Look.
(commentator) In the 13th round,
the hard-luck round,
the championship of the world
has changed hands.
And there you see it,
a champion gone down to defeat.
And so now we wait for the announcement
from Eddie Flint, the ring announcer,
and then we'll join with the radio audience
throughout the world,
and have a brief interview with Ray Robinson.
- We're waiting for the time to be announced.
- (bell rings)
It is being handed to Eddie Flint.
The fight was stopped on a signal...
Attention, ladies and gentlemen.
The winner by a technical knockout in
two minutes and four seconds of the 13th round,
and the new world middleweight
boxing champion, Sugar Ray Robinson!
(cheering)
- Why are you pulling out of Wednesday's fight?
- Boxing's over for me.
I'm through. I'm tired of worrying
about weight all the time.
All I used to think about was weight.
You realise there are other things in life.
I'm grateful. Boxing's been good to me.
I've got a nice house,
three great kids, a beautiful wife.
What more could I ask for? Huh?
- Hey, what's your name?
- Bob.
Take a picture, Bob.
Let him take a picture, honey, for us. Smile.
Thank you, Bob. Take a picture of all of us.
Jackie, come here. Sit over here.
All right, everybody smile. Smile.
Vickie, Mrs La Motta,
how do you feel about Jake's retirement?
I think it's great. He picked the right time.
- He's home with us all the time now.
- You through?
- Yeah.
I just bought a club on Collins Avenue,
bar, package store, everything.
Guess what I'm gonna call it. Take a guess.
(lively march)
- All right, shut up. Enough, enough.
- (applause)
Thank you.
(microphone whistles)
Just trying to see what a microphone
on a sexy girl sounds like.
(kissing)
Good evening. I haven 't seen so many losers
since my last fight in Madison Square Garden.
OK, honey.
- Thank you. Ain 't that somethin '?
- (man) Bring us another drink.
Salute
Terrific girl, the kind you wanna bring home
to your father, especially if he's a degenerate.
- Did I say that?
- (laughter)
Seriously, folks, it's a thrill to be standing
here before you wonderful people tonight.
- Well, in fact, it's a thrill to be standing.
- (laughter)
If you believe it's a thrill to be standing before
you wonderful people, then you're all full of shit.
Me and my wife Vickie's getting married.
What am I talking about? I'm out of it.
Is she here? She's not here.
Vickie? No, she's not here.
By the way, me and my wife Vickie's
gonna celebrate our 11 th wedding anniversary.
- (applause)
- Thank you, thank you.
That reminds me about two friends.
One was married, one was single.
The married guy tells the single guy,
"What's the matter with you?"
"Look at me, look at you
and look at me and look at you."
(laughter)
Let me get out of it.
"When I come home,
my wife's at the door with a drink,
then she gives me a nice hot bath,
a nice rub down,
she makes passionate love to me,
makes me a nice dinner."
"You ought to try that."
The other friend says, "That sounds great.
What time's your wife get home?"
(laughter)
Though I'm no Olivier
If he fought Sugar Ray, he would say
That the thing ain 't the ring, it's the play
So give me a stage
Where this bull here can rage
And though I can fight
I'd much rather hear myself recite
- # That's entertainment! #
- (drum roll)
Jake, hey. Over here.
Hey, hey. You were just great.
Good thing Sugar Ray wasn 't here tonight.
- He told that joke last week.
- (laughing) Come on.
He repeats himself. Gettin ' a little senile.
I'd like you to meet State's Attorney Bronson...
and his wife.
You shouldn 't be here this week. It's next week
we've got the shakedown payments, right?
- You got a sense of humour.
- That is a joke, right?
- Only you know if it's a joke.
- Just kidding, right?
- We'll talk about it later. This is your wife?
- Yes, Mrs Bronson.
Very pretty lady. Charmed to meet you.
He's really a nice guy.
You can take a joke, can 't you?
- Oh! Sorry.
- That's all right.
Hey, Carlo. Carlo.
Carlo, give them another drink.
Something happened over here.
- Linda, come here.
- Where's your wife?
My wife? What's it to you?
You think I'm gonna let you bums
get involved with her?
Especially the State's Attorney over here.
He comes here a lot, darling. Watch him.
He knows I'm only kidding.
Keep an eye on him.
- What's the problem?
- She doesn 't look 21, so I had to ask for ID.
- How old are you?
- 21.
21? Can you prove that you're 21?
- Mm-hm.
- Prove it to me.
Any girl that can kiss like that
can drink in my joint. How old are you?
- 21.
- Can you prove that you're 21?
- Yeah.
- Prove it to me.
Come here.
She's 21 too?
She has convinced me that she's 21 too.
OK.
(The Hearts singing "Lonely Nights")
# Please come home
# I miss you so
# Miss you so
# Miss you so #
- Jake.
- Watch while I pour.
- Your wife's outside.
- Why don 't you tell me a little louder?
# I would die
# I would die darling days and nights #
There.
# Hope you 're all right hope you 're all right #
Come on, Jake.
(pretends to sneeze)
# Lonely nights
# I'm so lonely
# Please come home
# You great big lump of sugar
# I miss you so much
# Please come home
# Lonely nights #
It was a busy night last night.
Everything all right?
- I'm leaving you, Jake.
- What else is new?
No, I mean it this time. I didn 't wanna tell you
till I had everything worked out.
- Move over.
- So you can put your hands on me? No.
- Open the door.
- We're getting a divorce.
- I'm getting custody of the kids.
- Let me in.
No, I already made up my mind.
I'm leaving. That's it.
If you show your face around,
I'm gonna call the cops.
- That's it.
- Don 't act that way, honey.
Hey, Jake. Jake.
Hey, Jake. Come on, champ. Wake up.
Wake up, champ.
What's up?
- We're from the DA.
- I know where you're from.
- They wanna talk with you.
- You all look the same.
- They wanna talk.
- About what?
- I don 't know. They just told me to bring you in.
- What do you want? For what?
Do you recognise this girl?
Has she been in the club?
- This is the same girl?
- Yeah.
- No.
- She says you introduced her to some men.
I introduce a lot of people to a lot of people.
I introduce him to... to men.
But I don 't say nothin '.
She's 14. Put on your shoes, Jake.
- She's how old?
- 14.
She's 14? Let me see that.
Let me ask you something.
- You gonna tell me that that girl looks 14?
- She's 14.
- I'm gonna ask you man to man.
- Come on. We gotta go.
- We gotta go downtown?
- That's right.
Because of this girl?
- Vick?
- You drunk?
I'm out on bail.
I've gotta pick up one thing and I'll leave.
- The kids are sleeping.
- Let me just get something.
- (quietly) All right.
- What?
- Don 't make no noise.
- I won 't.
- What are you doing?
- I need 10,000 dollars to get the case dropped.
- They don 't have a case against you.
- No? Ever see a 14-year-old testify in court?
- The papers said, "La Motta on a vice rap."
- What are you doing?
- What difference does it make?
- Can 't you get the money from friends?
- What friends?
- You're gonna wake my kids up, Jake!
You're gonna wake the kids! Stop it!
(smashing)
- Don 't you put them so they don 't fall?
- Get out!
What about the belt?
Isn 't that what you wanted to sell me?
- These are the jewels from the belt.
- Where's the belt? It's a very rare item.
I wish you'd come to me in the first place.
- Give me 2,000. Give me 2,000.
- 1,500 top, that's all...
- Give me 2,000.
- 1,500 top, Mr La Motta. I'm sorry.
- I'd lose out.
- Give me them.
You're not gonna make a profit? You're lying.
I'll bet you I'll get twice what you're offering.
I can 't raise the 10,000.
I tried, I tried. I tried a lot of places.
What am I gonna do?
If that's what they're gonna do, what can I do?
Fuck 'em. Let 'em do what they're gonna do.
(yelling)
Right, this is where it's at, right here.
(all yell at once)
Trying to shirk, huh?
You pulls your load here, boy.
You ain 't the goddamn boxing champion now.
- Fuck you!
- Breaking my arm, son of a bitch.
- You hear me? Hold onto him.
- I got him.
See it? See it?
Look at it, son. Live in it!
Live in it!
- You understand that? Live in it!
- Your mother's cunt, then!
Cocksucker!
Let that son of a bitch sit. Fuck!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Fuck your mother!
Dummy, dummy, dummy, dummy,
dummy, dummy.
Dummy, dummy, dummy.
Why? Why? Why? Why?
(sobbing) Why? Why? Why? Why?
Why? Why? Why? Why? Why? Why?
Why? Aagh! Aagh!
(continues screaming)
You motherfucker!
(sobbing) My hand! Aagh!
(sobbing) Why'd you do it? You're so stupid.
You're so stupid, so fuckin ' stupid. Stupid.
They call me an animal.
I'm not an animal.
Why do they treat me like this?
I'm not that bad. I'm not that bad.
I'm not that guy.
Guy finds his wife in bed with another guy.
Wife says, "Look who's here, big mouth.
Now the whole neighbourhood'll know."
(some laughter)
Thanks for laughing.
Spread it around a little bit.
The first night I was here,
I said to the owner, "Where's the toilet?"
He said, "You're in it."
- (man) Let's go.
- Leave me alone. I'm trying to do my routine.
- Up yours.
- You're gonna force me to make a comeback.
- Funny.
- Fuck you.
- And the horse you rode in on.
- (woman laughs)
- And the whole cavalry behind you.
- (some laughter)
- (man) Funny man.
- That's why I'm here.
(some laughter)
Give him another drink. Piss in it for me.
I'm gonna introduce
a woman who's made a world tour,
with top billing and all that bullshit
when they all hated her.
Give a warm welcome...
I know you're capable of it.
You look like a bunch of junkies.
Her name is Emma 48's.
(some applause whooping whistling)
Taxi!
Honey... I'm gonna take a little walk.
I got a couple of things to take care of.
- Will I see you later?
- Yeah.
- I'll be home later. All right.
- Thank you.
Be careful.
Ho.
Hey, what are you doin '? Joey.
Come on, Joey. Why don 't you turn around?
Huh?
Come on, Joey. Turn around.
Hey, Joey. Come on.
Joey.
Joe.
- Come on, Joey, wait.
- Huh?
Come on. What are you gettin ' so angry about?
Come on. Be friends.
- You're my brother. Be friends.
- I'm your brother?
Yeah, you fuckin ' bum.
Give me a break. Kiss me. Give me a kiss.
Let me call my wife and kids, let them see.
Are you gonna forgive and forget?
It was a long time ago. Just give me a kiss.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, give me a kiss.
Huh?
Come on.
- How's everything? All right?
- Good.
Everything all right? Huh?
Family? Come here.
- Come on.
- You don 't wanna do this here. Come on.
- Let me call you. We'll get together.
- You'll call me?
- I will.
- You won 't forget? Huh?
- I'll call you.
- All right.
(Jake)... legitimately, and nobody can
take that away from me, nobody.
Some people aren 't that lucky,
like the one that Marlon Brando played
in On The Waterfront
an up-and-comer
who's now a down -and-outer.
You remember that scene with his brother,
a small-time racket guy? It went like this.
"It wasn 't him, Charlie, it was you."
"You remember that night you said,
'Kid, this ain 't your night."'
"We're goin ' for the price on Wilson?"'
"Remember that? This ain 't your night?"
"My night. I could have
taken Wilson apart that night."
"What happens? He gets a title shot
in the ballpark. What do I get?"
"A one-way ticket to Palookaville.
I was never no good after that night, Charlie."
"It was like a peak you reach
and then it's downhill."
"It was you, Charlie. You was my brother."
"You shoulda looked out for me a little bit,
just a little bit."
"You shoulda taken care of me,
instead of making me take them dives
for the short-end money."
"You don 't understand."
"I could have had class,
I could have been a contender,
I could have been somebody,
instead of a bum, which is what I am."
- "Let's face it. It was you, Charlie."
- (door opens)
- "It was you, Charlie."
- How you doin ', Jake?
- Everything all right?
- Yeah.
- Ready?
- You got about five minutes. Need anything?
- No.
- You sure?
I'm sure.
- A lot of people out there?
- Yeah, it's crowded.
(door closes)
Go get 'em, champ.
I'm the boss. I'm the boss. I'm the boss.
I'm the boss. I'm the boss.
(gentle classical music)
Subtitles: Sally Lewis
www.broadcasttext.com