WORLD ON A WIRE
Einstein! Don't be a fool,
you've no chance.
I won't go back,
I want to live!
Get help! Call Edelkern!
Call someone for help.
You have to speak up,
I can't hear you.
I'm hard of hearing.
Telephone! Help!
Edelkern, I'm in the cafeteria.
I need help, quick!
What's wrong, Fred?
What happened?
Take him to a hook-up station, fast.
And load the program for 0001.
He looks like Fritz Walfang, right?
In reality, he's identity unit 0001.
Vollmer named him Einstein.
Yes, but, I mean...
I just saw him.
Come with me.
Ready?
Nearly.
Let me do that.
I had no idea...
About what, Holm?
What could happen.
What in God's name happened?
Careful.
Quiet now.
Anything?
- No, but...
- That's OK.
I wanted to see
if I could hook myself up, too.
But...
He switched their minds.
He should be here.
Hi, Fred.
Don't bother, she's not in.
Why not?
She's been gone for six weeks.
Sick.
Yes, but...
On sick leave. For six weeks.
Do you have a key?
Me?
Oh, it's you.
We haven't seen you for a while.
No.
Where were you? Were you sick?
We wondered where you were.
We were talking about you.
The key's under the mat,
where it belongs.
I always see it when I'm cleaning.
The upper lock.
Please, after you,
you know the way.
A real ambulance
came and took her.
I wasn't there,
but I sure heard about it.
Six weeks...
A long time.
I could do with a leave,
but our sort...
Where are you going? The key!
Strange...
She was always
compulsively tidy.
Lovely little bar, huh?
If you say so.
No, it's lovely.
Especially in the afternoon,
when everyone's working.
It gives you a feeling of...
Is that your line?
- Line?
- For meeting women.
No, I don't have a set routine.
On the contrary,
I'm a bit of a chameleon, you know?
I adapt.
Hahn? Hello.
Whiskey?
Whiskey... Hi...
milk, anything at all.
Angry?
- Pardon?
- You angry?
Two whiskeys.
I'm not angry, I'm...
- Heard you hit a glitch.
- I did.
Strange, I always thought
switching minds was a utopian joke.
- A joke?
- A very sophisticated one, but...
It's not a joke.
You seem pretty upset about it.
Not about that.
Come on, out with it.
What's eating you?
I know why Vollmer died.
High voltage.
Right, high voltage.
Tell me.
He couldn't take it.
800 volts, you mean?
Sorry, bad joke.
- Why didn't I think of it?
- What?
The people in our simulation model
think their world
is the only real one.
So?
Who says this isn't
also a computer?
You, me, all of us...
Just electronic circuits.
Identity unit 3, 124,000,
named Hahn.
How does that sound?
Drunk.
The whiskey, peanuts...
all artificial.
Why are you gobbling them down?
Nervous?
No, I was thinking they taste good,
for artificial peanuts.
Don't joke about it.
You must have a screw loose.
Yeah, an artificial screw.
I bet Vollmer panicked.
- Vollmer, why?
- Because he knew.
Knew what?
That this isn't
the real world.
I mean, he was convinced of it.
And, if he was right,
then they'd...
Yes, they.
They'd have simply deleted him.
Exit Vollmer.
How did we deprogram Nobody?
Who?
Christopher Nobody.
His name was a joke. Well, how?
By pressing a button.
Yes, but discretely.
Do you understand?
It has to look like an accident
so the other units don't suspect.
Like Vollmer.
The system remains stable.
Do you see the parallel?
I see you're drunk.
And Lause?
Who? Oh, yeah.
Lause was removed
from the system too quickly
for them to have time
to think up a plausible excuse.
So they deleted him
from people's minds.
No one remembers Günther Lause.
- Who?
- You see?
How it works.
God!
I was taken in.
Want me to drive you home?
You need to rest.
The contact unit! That's it!
The contact unit.
We needed a contact unit
for our simulation model to work.
Einstein.
If we're the simulation model
of a real world
there must be
an Einstein here who knows...
who's in contact with above.
Help me find him, Hahn!
You can always count on me.
It could be anyone,
Siskins, Gloria Fromm
Eva Vollmer, Walfang,
even you, Hahn.
Me?
Even you. Why not you?
Why not me? Well...
It's true,
I wouldn't just admit it.
You'd have to corner me,
trip me up.
OK, fine.
Besides, there's proof.
- People keep disappearing.
- Who else?
First, Lause.
- Now Maja Schmidt-Gentner.
- Who?
- My secretary.
- Gloria?
No, before her.
Oh, her.
On leave, supposedly.
But no one would go away
leaving their flat like that.
Yes, but...
Come, I'll show you!
If you insist.
The tab!
I don't know,
everything looks normal to me.
But two hours ago, it was completely
different. Everything was...
The bed...
the bathroom.
You?
I think he's gone crazy.
When did you get back?
An hour ago. The janitor...
Oh, forget it.
Come here...
When do you say the story appeared?
May 31.
On May 30 the world ends.
Uschi! Bring me May.
Right away.
How's the computer?
OK.
And Siskins?
Fine, thanks.
Still pals with Hartmann?
Maybe.
Why not? There are stranger reasons
to be friends.
Yeah, I guess.
Look, I'm doing you a favour.
You could give me
some information.
I'm lousy at making deals.
Does United Steel
have a deal with IKZ?
Thank you.
I think so.
But I can't provide photocopies,
if that's what you mean.
The official simulation program
must contain projections
that would be very useful
to United Steel.
I guess so.
May 31.
It's a new article.
Let me see.
"CS"... Christoph Simon,
our correspondent in Rome.
Could it have been another day?
No.
Here, ladies and gentlemen,
you see our reporters.
It's they who write
the stories.
They start with news leads
the yeast for any article -
then add background information
to write their stories.
The copy, once it's finished
is sent for typesetting,
as you'll now see.
Thank you, and good-bye.
Tell me...
Was there another edition
on May 31?
They're both there.
If the existing forecasts
don't meet Hartmann's needs,
could they program others in?
Yes, if they wanted to.
It was on this page.
But here's CS's article again.
Do they want to?
They, perhaps. Me, no.
"Vanished into Thin Air",
I remember it perfectly.
"Vanished"... No idea.
"Drug Ring Broken up in Rimini".
Not as punchy, but there it is,
black on white.
I don't get it.
- This guy...
- Christoph Simon?
Yeah. Couldn't you
check with him to see
if he actually wrote this article?
Come on, I'll look like a fool.
Alright, if it helps clear this up.
Please!
Cable Christoph Simon in Rome
about his May 31 article.
Ask if there are any developments.
I'll see you out.
So this steel analysis?
- I forget.
- Forget?
Alright. Simulacron forecasts
transportation needs
through the year 2000.
That could be quite important
for a steel conglomerate.
Well, that's something.
Not Chinese.
- Why not?
- I dunno, it's too sweet.
No, it's not. It can be spicy, too.
That Stiller is definitely screwy.
I sent off your cable.
What? I just said that
to humour him.
It doesn't matter.
Uschi, get me a book on forecasting
transportation needs.
You've been looking at me
so strangely. Is something wrong?
I don't know.
A headache.
Then go lie down.
I don't feel bad,
I just have a headache.
Maybe I'm just going crazy.
Employees are continuing
to work to rule
to back up demands
for a wage increase
The Daily News
quotes a reliable source
that the CEO of the prominent
Cybernetics /nstitute
Herbert Siskins
maintains close ties
to a certain steel conglomerate
The paper has expressed suspicions
that Simulacron 1
the simulation computer
developed by /KZ
is being used for
not only scientific
but also commercial purposes
The News writes "The computer's
revolutionary findings
must remain in the hands
of responsible individuals
to ensure they are applied
for the good of society "
End of quote
The Science Ministry has named
a commission to investigate
And Siskins?
Herbert Siskins has vigorously
denied the allegations
and initiated legal action
against the paper
And now in brief
Helsinki The Finnish poetess
Araba Suukoonen
distinguished for her translation
of the Nibelungenlied
died yesterday at the age of 86
when her small private plane
collided with a glider
at an airport near Helsinki
The glider pilot
suffered minor injuries
This brings an end
to our broadcast schedule
We wish you good night
Good night.
Siskins...
or not Siskins.
Holm or...
Pardon?
I only said good night
to the announcer.
It's Stiller, give me Siskins.
Hello, this is Stiller.
Feel like visiting
the computer room?
I have a surprise for you.
Come in.
What's up?
What's this?
It's you.
I programmed it myself.
Interesting, isn't it?
Yes, indeed. Very interesting.
It's funny.
You find it funny?
How many Siskins are there?
I have no idea.
Have you programmed others?
It's the only one in that world.
You're the only one here.
And above?
Where, above?
Don't you know "up"?
You're talking nonsense.
This is above, and that's below.
Or, how much deeper does it go?
Infinitely, maybe.
Yes, quite true.
And infinitely higher.
That's very funny.
What's he doing now?
Very impressive, Mr. Siskins.
Isn't it?
I began to carry out my scheme
Jessie's eyes gleamed of love
And she whispered Maybe
Hey maybe the sofa's
wide enough for
three!
Nice setup, Mark.
Really nice.
What do you mean, nice?
Like the entire world.
It's nice, isn't it?
Quit playing around.
What do you want?
I know, Mark.
You can stop pretending.
What do you know?
That you're the contact.
You found out?
So what?
I just wanted to tell you,
Stiller knows.
- Put him on
- Sure.
It's him.
But Stiller it was clear
from the start
What was clear?
That Holm was to be Hartmann's
contact The decision was mine
Mine alone
Hartmann's contact?
Oh, God!
What was that?
He seems pretty screwy, our Fred.
He just walked out.
I think we can proceed.
Yes I agree
Hey, you? Are you OK?
Is he dead?
No, not exactly.
Hey, wake up!
Right, he's not dead.
Thanks, I'm OK.
Mr. Siskins ordered me
to take you home
and look after you.
Come along.
Go back to work, it's over.
Wake up. Breakfast's ready.
That's right, you're still here.
They're Mr. Siskins' orders.
They are.
Well, then...
Got a cigarette?
Thanks.
I think...
therefore I am. Right?
Yes, I exist.
I can't be alone in thinking
that nothing really exists.
Right. For Plato, reality exists
in the realm of ideas.
And Aristotle!
He conceived of matter
as passive non-substance
that only becomes reality
by thought.
Got a friend?
What? Of course.
Good. Let's suppose
he disappears without a trace.
He's standing next to you,
and suddenly he's gone.
But that's...
We're just supposing.
So, you inform the police.
Next day, the papers
run a story on it.
Suddenly everyone maintains
this friend never existed.
So they maintain.
What would you tell them?
Me? I'd tell them they're crazy.
After all, even the police...
The police also say
they never heard of him.
But it was in the papers.
According to you.
It's not there anymore.
There's something different.
I see.
You realize that
I've given you a hot tip
how to get yourself
declared crazy. In case
you ever need it.
More coffee?
No, thanks.
I'll take a shower.
I'm sure you all know
the reason we're here.
Of course, we...
The story in the News took us all
by surprise, aroused our concern.
Mr. Siskins, I'd like to hear you
answer the charges.
Certainly, Mr. Secretary of State.
To my regret, I must acknowledge
that Simulacron 1 has been
the object of misuse.
Mr. Holm will report
on the situation.
Excuse me...
but who is Mr. Holm?
Mr. Holm is assistant
to Mr. Stiller, our director.
I see.
So, well...
during an inspection we discovered
that a program completely
unrelated to our research
had been loaded into Simulacron.
And for what purpose?
That's hard to say.
The answers obtained
by this new program
are meaningful only
if one knows the questions.
I see, and...
And the questions are known
only to the programmer.
Who is?
We're not absolutely sure yet.
But we have suspects in mind.
And they are?
Mr. Holm, please.
Naturally, I can only
report on things
that I've seen for myself.
Draw your own conclusions.
Lately I've been doing
a lot of testing at night
and Dr. Stiller has always been
at the computer.
Dr. Stiller?
Several times he's thrown me out
saying he wanted to be alone.
I asked what he was doing.
He said, "None of your business. "
I'm sure he'll deny it all.
Dr. Stiller?
What do you have to say
to these accusations?
Which ones?
That you were alone at the computer,
and threw Holm out.
If he says so, it must be true.
I can't stand him.
Yes or no...
Did you use the computer
for unauthorized purposes?
What if I did?
What would it matter?
Unheard of!
Yes, unheard of!
I hear...
you.
I hear.
He's...
Crazy.
Yes, he is.
Is he?
Stop! Your cigarette...
Are you sure that's a cigarette?
It's...
The idea of a cigarette.
You see?
The real cigarettes
are somewhere else.
Where real people sit
on real chairs. Is that a chair?
Say, "It's a chair. "
- It's a chair.
- It's not a chair.
It's...
the idea of an idea of an idea...
- The man is...
- Crazy.
We agreed on the term long ago.
What colour's your coffee?
It's brown.
Why is it brown?
Because coffee's brown. Isn't it?
Of course.
Your coffee's not brown
because coffee is brown.
But rather
because somewhere outside this box
there's real coffee
that may be brown.
But it may be purple, too
and some idiot
made this stuff brown
to laugh at us
drinking brown coffee.
You're not a human, sir...
Stop it.
You're nothing.
There's the rub.
Because nothing doesn't think
it's secretary of state.
That's it.
Do you remember... who was it?
Professor Vollmer, right.
A similar situation.
Still...
Excuse me, but...
I'm the psychologist
at the Institute.
I've been observing Stiller
for some time
very closely.
He's suffering from a case
of acute paranoia.
He's an extreme example
of psychological degeneration.
He is, in so many words,
not responsible for his actions.
I recommend he be put
on leave immediately.
For treatment...
I mean
I'm certain he'll return to normal
one day, perhaps.
Thank you, Hahn.
Thanks so much.
I think that would eliminate
the problem, gentlemen.
Yes, indeed. If Stiller...
So he's not responsible, Hirse?
No, definitely not.
For now
I recommend Mr. Holm assume
Stiller's responsibilities.
As you like. You're still free
to make personnel decisions.
Thank you, gentlemen.
I'd be grateful if you'd prepare
a clarification for the press.
Of course.
Still, the parallel to...
Professor Vollmer
is quite baffling.
And now?
Nothing, I'm on leave.
That's terrific.
There's no one in Holm's way.
So what?
"So what"?
You used to care about
what happened to the computer.
That was then, this is now.
I can't figure you out.
Tell me...
What are the limits
to the perceptive faculties
of our identity units?
Listen, suppose
we were beings who had been
programmed in a computer.
We'd sit here, drinking whiskey.
We'd perceive what is in fact
our imaginary world
as if it were the real one.
Of course. An electronically
simulated environment
would appear real
to an electronic being.
Good.
And can glitches occur?
It's possible, but not very.
And what would a glitch be like?
A glitch?
Here's a simple example:
You're driving down a street
that suddenly ends because
it hasn't been fully programmed.
But after a few seconds
the artificial being
would see a completed street
because the correcting software
had kicked in.
It's obvious:
What can't exist, doesn't.
Did you read my headline?
"Director Suffers Nervous Breakdown"
- I don't like it.
- Why not?
It's too simple.
Stories written by life
are never simple.
No? But truth
is stranger than fiction.
Either way. Two sides
of the same coin.
You read it?
What?
The cable from Simon in Rome.
No, what's he say?
"Never wrote about
drugs in Rimini.
Besides, was sick at the time. "
That's impossible.
That's not all.
Naturally I asked
what's in his edition of May 31.
- Want to see?
- Give it to me.
"Mine reads
'Vanished into Thin Air'.
Hope that helps.
Christoph Simon. "
I must be going crazy.
I can't help think that
Stiller's caught up
in a massive intrigue.
Siskins must be a bigger gangster
than I thought.
I brought your things.
That's very kind.
Fred, I'm so sorry.
About what?
Your sick leave.
Especially since
I'm partly to blame.
What do you mean?
I've been spying for Siskins.
I was obliged to tell him
all you said that night
and everything else.
Of course.
I've known that for a long time.
But?
But I still like you.
Me, too.
Whiskey?
Yes, please.
Does he pay you, or?
Or what?
Do you love him?
Both.
At least you're honest.
You're my type of man,
well almost.
You're exactly my type of woman.
Siskins is exactly my type of man.
I can't bring myself to leave him.
Do you want to?
I don't know.
Probably not.
I don't know if I could.
You can if you want.
That's a fairy tale.
Right.
I'm one of his puppets.
But what's even worse is...
I love it.
At least at night.
Want to sleep with me?
How's it going?
We're running the analysis.
I hope you can interpret the data.
No need to insult me.
I don't want our friend Hartmann
to make a bad investment.
I told you, you're not wanted here.
Beat it!
This department is still
my responsibility, Mr. Holm.
Don't be impertinent.
I'm not being impertinent.
Not at all.
I'm merely doing my job.
We'll decide what your job is,
my good man.
You're mistaken there, my good man.
My contract contains
a precise job description.
Contracts can be terminated.
Or broken, like Dr. Stiller's.
What's he got to do with it?
Quite a bit, doesn't it?
- Does who?
- What?
What, what?
Besides, Stiller's on leave.
I see.
That's something else entirely.
What you did to him's scandalous...
Watch it!
Both of you.
But personally I'm curious
why you're so intent
on keeping me out of here.
Because you're incompetent,
that's why.
That's the only reason.
And now, please, we're busy.
OK, my good man.
But you'll hear from me.
Good-bye, Mr. Siskins.
He's next.
You should watch what you say.
Why?
There are employee committees,
unions.
Don't forget that.
Alright, I'll do my best.
I hope so.
Finally! Make sure
he doesn't stir up trouble.
- Yes, sir.
- Of course, Mr. Holm.
Tell me, Holm.
What about Stiller?
If everything went
according to plan,
he's in a straightjacket right now.
My head!
Yes, it's me.
What time is it?
330.
Morning or afternoon?
Afternoon.
Then we slept for 18 hours.
You slept for 18 hours.
I'll see who the idiot is.
Great. Siskins' latest trick.
- What?
- Have a look.
Hurry, you must get away.
I don't care.
They'll put you
in a straightjacket!
Maybe I belong in one.
Stop joking.
Hurry up!
Take the fire escape.
What can I do for you?
The madman.
Which madman?
What do you mean?
Stiller. He lives here.
You mean Freddy?
Yes, he is crazy...
in bed, if you get my drift.
In bed?
Crazy. Definitely.
Let us by.
Or else...
Alright, if you insist.
Eva!
Open up police!
We know you're inside
Stiller don't make it any harder
We'll break down the door
Get in, you can't escape.
I'll take you to a room here.
No one will find you.
Thank you.
My God! You?
Yes, me.
What's wrong?
Don't you get it? It's him!
The contact unit.
Of course, him!
What an idiot I am!
I fell for it!
But Stiller...
Hahn's been providing us
information on IKZ for months.
What's the problem?
Information?
Yes. On Siskins and the computer.
Then...
Still suffering
from your delusions?
Delusions?
Listen, Hahn.
I like Vollmer's delusions
more and more.
Yeah, I know what you'll say...
A madman finds proof everywhere.
Maybe I am crazy after all.
But...
Vollmer died for a reason.
If he was right,
God, or someone, help us!
By the way,
I got an answer from Italy.
You got... What did it say?
You were right.
I was right.
Simon never wrote the article
on the Rimini bust.
In his edition, the headline is
"Vanished into Thin Air".
What?
It's troubling
but we'll figure it out,
don't worry.
When is the strike?
What strike?
The strike at IKZ. You said...
Oh, that. I don't know.
Tomorrow or...
What's wrong? Don't you feel well?
Sure, I'm fine.
For now.
What strike?
A certain Fritz Walfang
has been organizing the workers.
To have you reinstated.
Reinstated?
It's great: Worker initiative,
solidarity. You should be proud.
None of it matters anymore.
You're right, Hahn.
His nerves are completely shot.
Günther Lause?
Chief of security at IKZ?
Siskins' party.
Say something!
Like what?
- We can't both be...
- Crazy?
Why not?
You're the expert.
Where are you going?
- I'm just going.
- You can't go.
Why not?
Every cop is carrying your picture.
Tell me...
the story about
your so-called contact unit...
I just meant...
I want to find out who's crazy...
us, or everyone else.
Well now, that's what I call
a noble motive.
Come with me,
I'll smuggle you out.
Your only chance.
It's not Siskins, Holms,
Gloria Fromm or Walfang...
It can't be Rupp
or you or me or Eva...
That's ridiculous. Eva Vollmer...
Stop at that pay phone.
My God, where were you?
I slept at your place,
I climbed in through a window.
No, but I was worried.
OK, fine.
Could I see you, right now?
Anywhere.
No, nothing urgent.
My God, I just want to see you.
I need you.
I'm not tense, I'm...
Can you hear me?
That's Stiller, the murderer.
The murderer's getting away!
Murderer!
Are you sick?
No, it's nothing. I'm fine.
Today we're going marching
to the sound of a new beat.
/n the lovely Westerwald forest
the wind blows so cold
/n the lovely Westerwald
Oh you lovely Westerwald!
Eucalyptus cough drops
The wind blows so cold
over the hill
Yes, sir?
Roast filet of wild boar
and some Gewürztraminer.
Very good. Excellent.
Halt!
Left face!
Right face!
Fire!
Oh you lovely Westerwald
Eucalyptus cough drops
The wind blows so cold
over the hill
but the weakest ray of sunshine
penetrates deep into our hearts
I'm a public safety inspector.
I'm here to check the exits.
Sent it back!
Barbarians!
Where does this door lead?
- The garbage cans.
- I'll have a look.
Were killed
The highway between Essen
and Bochum was closed
The police have launched
a manhunt for
36-year-old Fred Stiller
a former employee
of the Cybernetics /nstitute
Stiller is a suspect
in the murder of Henri Vollmer
the former technical director
at /KZ
and that of Franz Hahn
a colleague of Stiller's at /KZ
who died today
in mysterious circumstances
Stiller is described
as unstable and dangerous
People are warned to avoid contact
with the fugitive
and to inform the police
of any information
regarding his whereabouts
Franz Hahn.
A man who knew too much.
My God, are you hurt?
Say something, please.
What's going on?
Someone fired a shot.
I fired, because...
I was afraid.
Why are you here?
I heard you're wanted
for my father's death.
I just don't believe it.
I thought you needed me,
I wanted to be with you.
- You can't stay here.
- But...
No buts!
I didn't murder anyone.
It's all a plot
by Siskins and the police.
All I can do now is defend myself...
by any means.
No one believes me.
I believe you.
And I love you.
Go now.
When I know more,
I'll come into town or I'll call.
I'm scared for you.
Go now, Eva. You must go.
Believe me.
How did she know I was here?
I never told her about my cabin
Then it's her
And I'm nothing
Why are you here?
Aren't you afraid?
I'm a murderer. Do you hear?
A murderer!
Tell me...
- What was your name?
- Echo.
An unusual name.
Not in my family.
Perhaps I should take you
to a hospital.
No, I'm fine.
It was just the car.
Please don't smoke
monsieur?
Echo.
Mr. Echo.
I'm extremely allergic to nicotine.
The other day
I saw a fantastic accident.
Simply awful.
A lamppost went right through a car
and the driver...
Stop! I feel sick. I'll throw up.
Mon dieu,  please, not on the seats.
The leather...
Stop, the man wants to get out.
I wouldn't try to run away.
Sorry, darling, but I don't
want you to escape from me.
Naturally.
But you must have
more subtle methods...
you people up there.
Up there, yes,
but not down here.
You understand a lot,
Fred Stiller.
You've become a bit too
intelligent for us.
Are you the contact unit...
as we call it?
I'm the projection of a real Eva
from the real world.
We don't have
contact units anymore.
They were a mistake,
we got rid of them.
And now you'll get rid of me.
Like a caged rat
after your experiment.
I want to help you, believe me.
Please come with me.
Don't cause trouble. Please.
I don't give a damn.
Do what you want with me.
I give up.
Deprogram me, kill me, anything.
I just want it to end...
this horrible nightmare.
You can trust me, Fred.
Here.
There's a lot I have to explain.
You can do anything
you want with me.
Even so, listen...
There never was an Eva Vollmer
in your world.
When I appeared, you quickly
threw together a memory.
That's how simulation units react.
I know how simulation units react.
We shouldn't have let you develop
your own simulation model.
It's easy to learn too much.
But we needed the closest
possible resemblance
to our own technological standard.
Got any cigarettes?
And Vollmer?
At first we found it interesting
and wanted to observe
what happened.
Of course he became a threat
to the entire system
so he had to have
an accident. Right?
There was a decision to send
an observer down here.
That's me.
I was periodically
called back to report.
That's why you were gone
that night.
I understand.
And Lause?
He knew all about Vollmer.
We programmed him away
because he was going to tell you.
I love you, Fred.
I want to stay with you.
We have to find a solution.
We?
What's it got to do with you?
I love you.
OK, fine.
They have to delete you.
You could cause
your world to be deleted.
They'll pull the plug
and it'll be over.
The man in my world
who's sitting at the computer
is a total megalomaniac.
His power over this artificial world
drove him crazy.
He thinks he's God,
he's playing his games with you.
You, for example... He didn't want
to kill you right away.
On the contrary.
He got enormous pleasure
from your fear
and your despair.
What will he do to me?
You'll be shot.
When?
Tomorrow morning.
- So we still have some time.
- Yes.
At night, there's only technical
supervision of the computer.
Like a drink?
Yes, a whiskey.
Tell me...
Why should I trust you?
I want to help you.
Well, we'll see.
Cheers.
What happened to Hahn?
You saw.
We had to, after that screw-up
at the paper.
- Imagine what would've...
- Bravo.
Good work.
My attacks, all my dizzy spells?
You get them when he tries
to hook-up with your mind.
And the street that vanished
and reappeared?
A faulty circuit, nothing more.
Something doesn't add up.
Why?
How can a real person
love someone who's not?
Very simple.
Because you remind me
of someone I loved, up there.
Who was he?
He's...
You'd call him technical director,
responsible
for our simulation model.
Tell me, what's his name?
Fred Stiller.
That's me.
No.
But you just said...
Like Vollmer did with Lause,
and you with Siskins.
He programmed a copy of himself
for the fun of it.
Do I resemble him?
In appearance, yes.
But not in character.
Fred is a megalomaniac
and you are you.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Come here, please.
Why are you getting dressed?
I have another headache.
But this time it's worse.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
The Institute, probably.
No, Fred. Please stay!
Let me help you.
Since Holm's been here
everything's upside down
We can't go near the computer
For that reason alone
I urge you to join in the strike
so Stiller will be reinstated
But he's a murderer! A madman!
He lined his own pockets!
Murderer! Murderer!
Quiet down please
Just for one second
Stiller was set up
Set up by Siskins and Holm
Friends, listen to me!
I am Fred Stiller.
What Fritz Walfang just told you
is true.
Friends, listen to me, please!
It's true, what he just said.
It's true!
I switched your mind
as you lay dying down there.
Like that time Einstein came,
instead of Walfang.
Hair, eyes...
mouth
neck
shoulders.
I am.