Get down on your knees!
Listen carefully.
Jackie and Alan were close friends,
but later clashed because of Laura.
Jackie left the band to start his
career as a high society Robin Hood,
calling himself Asian Hawk.
What has this to do with the
last 3 pieces of The Armour of God?
A holy sword recently
put up for auction
was stolen by him
from an African tribe.
If he can get the sword
he can get the remaining 2 pieces.
Let's hire him
to get the other pieces then.
Idiot, let him continue.
We can hire him to do that,
but we don't have to pay him.
What do you mean?
Laura is now a famous fashion designer.
She's going to a fashion show in Paris.
She's Alan's girlfriend
but Jackie still cares for her.
Get Laura for me.
Now the "star"
of today's auction appears.
This is the famous holy sword.
The starting bid is $30,000
increasing in units of $5,000.
I now declare the auction open.
- $35,000.
- $40,000 - $45,000.
- Any bid higher than $45,000?
- $50,000.
- $55,000.
- $60,000.
$65,000.
Any bid higher than $65,000?
It seems we're still warming up.
$70,000.
Any bid higher than $70,000?
$75,000, $75,000.
$100,000.
The lady offers $100,000.
Any bid higher than $100,000?
Anyone offering higher than $100,000?
The bid has now reached $100,000.
$105,000.
I bid $150,000.
The lady bids as much as $150,000.
Any bid higher than $150,000?
$150,000 is close to the true value
of this holy sword.
Any bid higher than $150,000?
Any bid?
I offer $300,000.
What an exciting bid!
The gentleman seems determined to win it.
$300,000 is undeniably
a very attractive bid.
Let's see if anyone
wants to raise the bid.
Any bid higher than $300,000?
$300,000, going once.
$300,000, going twice.
I offer $400,000.
$400,000!
I proudly announce the conclusion
of the bid at $400,000.
You did well to have won.
You did better
to have got such a good price.
Yes.
What a beautiful car.
- Let me give you a lift.
- OK.
Stop.
What is it?
The car's great,
but the wind's too strong.
I'd rather take my own car.
I can drive more slowly.
Go!
Thank you.
Room 206, please.
Mr. Chen, some messages for you.
Thank you.
So many.
Please, call back. It's urgent.
Help! Please, call my cellular phone.
I'm booking a flight.
I'm trying to get a seat.
Wait for me.
I'm flying to your side to seek help.
I'm waiting at the airport.
Don't go away.
Where on earth have you been?
I'm waiting in the lobby. It's urgent.
Come at once. Only you can help me.
Jackie.
Laura's been kidnapped?
How much do they want?
If money could fix it,
I wouldn't need you.
If money can't fix it,
I'm not needed either.
I'm not a volunteer.
They want the Armour of God
as ransom.
The Armour of God?
You said it's worth a lot of money.
I've just sold the holy sword.
Buy it back for me at once.
The Armour of God consists
of five pieces
but I only know
the whereabouts of three.
Where?
Two were sold to a Count.
The last was sold to a lady.
You can get it back then.
Why should I help you?
What a silly question.
Don't you care for Laura?
Don't take advantage of my feelings.
What about the feelings between us?
What feelings between us?
What? We grew up together.
We formed a band together
and chased the same girl.
We were like brothers.
Don't you remember?
You always bullied me.
You said my voice was bad.
When I dated Laura,
you stole my pants.
Have you no shame?
So you still hate me
because you lost Laura.
I didn't lose her, but I don't want
this to affect our friendship.
So, you do think
there's friendship between us.
There was, but not now.
So you suffered greatly because of her.
I shouldn't have come to you.
I'll try some other way to rescue her.
I just hope she's still alive.
Have you finished the American
ginseng I gave you?
- Yes, two years ago.
- I like the stamps you sent me.
I came in such a rush,
I didn't bring anything much.
Just some preserved
bean curd that you like.
It's hot.
Just forget that I came.
- I know I'm stubborn.
- You're not.
I am stubborn.
OK, you are stubborn.
Let's not argue any more.
- How do you plan to rescue Laura?
- I'm not sure I want to.
Why?
You may not know it, but what I value
most is our friendship.
I don't want to lose you
because of Laura.
Goodbye.
Hold it!
How can we contact
Laura's kidnappers?
They've given me a map.
They want me to bring the three
pieces of the Armour of God
to a small town
where we exchange for Laura.
Let's try to borrow the two
from the Count
then get in touch
with the lady buyer of the sword.
Do you know what it says?
I think...
You don't know then.
Is there a bell?
The house is over there.
Stop.
Calm down.
What now?
What? I'm scared.
Excuse me. Please, follow me.
Now I know what that sign says.
Even a moron knows now.
The owner of this house
must hate deer.
Deer hunting is a European pastime.
Don't be afraid. He's leashed.
Please come with me.
So you need these pieces
to avert a world disaster?
It's not that serious.
The fact is we need them
as ransom for my girlfriend
or they'll kill her.
Isn't that serious enough?
To me, every life
is equally as important...
or unimportant.
If I lend you these to save her life,
I'd have to donate all my property
to save the countless
starving in Africa.
I'll return them to you
once we've saved her.
Can you guarantee that?
Yes, I will.
But I have no reason to trust you.
I'll pay you for them.
Why would I be interested
in your money?
Let's not get discouraged.
Would you care to see my antiques?
I'm not interested in antiques.
I do have an interest in them.
So we're two of a kind.
Please follow me.
This is amazing!
This looks more like a small museum.
In fact, museums all over the world
borrow my collections for exhibition.
Security must be tight here.
I keep fifty dogs and three leopards.
They keep away intruders.
Why should I need guards?
Show me your two pieces
of the Armour of God.
They're over there.
You can't leave valuables
lying around like that!
To me, they are a memento
from history.
But not everyone shares my opinion.
What's the origin of these?
Are they linked
to my girlfriend's abduction?
Sit down...
They say that before Christ...
evil was rampant.
The true God that stands for justice
waged a holy war
against these forces.
Finally the true God won of course.
The weaponry they used is called
the Armour of God.
Recently evil cults
have staged a comeback.
They believe that by destroying
the Armour of God
the religion of the true God
will perish
and they'll prosper
and rule the world.
That really defies logic.
Religion exists only
when there is faith.
When it brings peace,
happiness and well-being
it's the force of righteousness.
Who kidnapped my girlfriend?
Sorry, I can't answer that.
It's getting late.
Hawk, I didn't expect your visit.
I have a party to attend.
Stay for a few days
and let me entertain you.
No need...
It's the most beautiful place
I've ever seen. We'd love to stay.
Splendid, it's settled then.
Tell my butler if you need anything.
Take good care
of my two guests tonight.
Just make yourselves at home.
Please, follow me.
- Thank you.
We've only just finished supper.
Why have you ordered so much steak?
It's for the dogs and leopards.
What do you mean?
Hawks always take,
without asking the owner's consent.
What? You expect me to steal?
As he said, it's not guarded.
We're his guests.
He told us to make ourselves at home.
So you steal from your own home?
- Do you want to see Laura killed?
- Of course not.
You want her to be killed by others
because you can't win her love.
You really are crafty.
What? I'm saying don't steal.
Not that I won't help you.
When are you going to do something?
We're living like kings.
Have you spared a thought for Laura?
Don't think I feel any better.
But stealing won't work.
Isn't it worth trying?
You're more stupid than you look.
You think you can just take it?
I'm ready to borrow the Armour of God
from the Count whatever he demands.
Why don't we steal it and return it later?
Isn't that more clean-cut?
I already said no, I won't help,
and I won't let you steal it either!
OK, I give up.
I never really knew you until now!
Good night!
The Count wants to see you, sir.
Please.
Quiet.
- Are you all right?
- I was nearly the dog's dinner.
Don't worry.
They won't attack without orders
from me or my daughter.
Do something.
Hurry up. Out!
So it's you.
This is my daughter, May.
We met at the auction.
So you know each other.
That's better.
I found this.
- Is this the one you talked about?
- It is.
This is the man who got someone
to compete to buy back his own sword?
I didn't know she was your daughter
or I wouldn't have done it.
So you were up to no good.
And Daddy treated you as guests.
He did that
only to save his girlfriend.
I swear I will return them to you
intact after rescuing my girlfriend.
- What's that?
- It's not an ice-cream van.
- Show the police in.
- Yes, sir.
I'd like to let it go, but the police...
You've captured me.
Do anything you like!
Have you got the right to speak?
No, but you have.
In what way can you help me?
Go on, be nice to him.
Do you want the Armour of God?
- Go and take care of the police.
- Yes, sir.
The Armour of God has five pieces.
The kidnappers only asked for three.
- So they've got the other two.
- You're smart.
That coincides with my information.
If you lend me your pieces,
I'll guarantee their return
and I'll get the other pieces
to make one complete set of Armour.
It's a deal.
But I have one condition.
I go with you.
No problem.
Can't two men take care of a woman?
OK. You must guarantee
she returns safe and sound.
I'll only guarantee her safe return
not her sound return.
We'll see about the rest.
Splendid.
What is that?
You wouldn't like it.
Let my try.
Help yourself.
There's no point in worrying.
You won't see the kidnappers
until tomorrow.
I'll go with you.
Why are you staring at me like that?
You think women are good for nothing.
I was runner-up in last year's
European Women's shooting.
You'll be safe with me.
Only two women
took part in that contest.
What is this?
Chinese butter.
It tastes funny.
It turns into cheese
when you keep it.
- Jackie, this stuff is rotten.
- I know.
- Why are you eating it then?
- I'm eating butter.
Did they give you any special sign?
No, they only told me to come to the
town with the armour in a black bag.
They told me to come alone.
I can't accompany you then.
I'll keep an eye out for any suspects.
Let me jockey for a position.
You look OK.
She is very attractive.
You'd risk Laura's death with a fake.
We risk getting robbed
with the real one.
Don't hand it over until we know Laura's safe.
Let's go.
Go alone. I'll keep watch.
- No looking at the ladies, now.
- I won't.
Miss, our religion
has many advantages.
I'll consider it.
- Do you believe in a Creator?
- What? I have no religious faith.
Believe and this person
shall be saved.
Laura.
Next time remember
to pay the balance.
OK.
The Armour of God?
Right here.
But I want to know she's safe.
It's a fake.
My friend's got it, but only if...
Don't try anything!
Come over here.
Jackie, stop fighting.
Come here. Safety zone.
Keep away, it's dangerous.
Dangerous? Come here.
Get him, get him.
She's a nuisance.
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- No, we must interrogate them.
Go ahead...
Here are those two Chinese.
Let's go.
- You haven't interrogated them.
- Go ahead.
I said bring the genuine one.
Now what will happen to Laura?
Stop talking. It won't help her.
I can't even talk, now!
How are we going to find Laura?
Someone's coming to tell us.
Look out!
Move it!
Look up there.
Sit still.
They're getting close. Do something.
- What's that?
- Hold on.
Bump him...
They're coming.
Great, we got away from them.
- What are they doing?
- Trying to hit us.
What now?
Hold tight.
Tight?
What are you doing?
This car's crowded.
It was designed for me alone.
Goodbye!
Please, sit down.
Three beers.
OK, right away.
What? You asked us here for beers?
Next time ask what we want first.
Not everyone likes beer.
I ordered all three for myself only.
900 dinars for three beers.
- Keep the change.
- Thank you.
Keep the change.
I'd like to ask some questions.
My answers are very expensive.
How much?
US$100 for each question.
Normally I ask questions
everywhere I go.
I ask this and that.
I answer all questions.
I saw some robed people
in the square.
Who are they?
The disciples of a nearby missionary.
- Where can I find them?
- On the hill.
That's no way to spend money.
What are their other activities?
They come down on the first
of every month for supplies
and take girls with them.
What sort of girls?
Don't answer that. Let's go.
- Do you know what they are?
- Prostitutes, of course.
We must spend $100 more.
Tell us the route to go up.
Sorry, I don't know.
Thank you.
- We'll come again next month.
- Thank you. Bye-bye.
Hurry up.
Drop it.
- Why are you here?
- I'm a prostitute.
This is dangerous.
What will you do after getting there?
Don't worry. At worst I'll die.
No need to die.
I'll show you how to be a whore.
It's nice to see you. Come down.
Come down... Come down...
- Be careful.
- Thank you.
Be careful.
This way, please.
Go up.
May God bless you.
According to our latest report over
3000 new disciples joined last month.
Come in...
Tell them come in.
This time we're getting more.
Yes.
It means more
believe in our religion.
Well done...
What about the harvest?
The poppies produced
3,600kg of opium.
It can be delivered soon.
I'm tired.
This long flight of stairs
is killing me.
Get going. No more nonsense.