These ties of the heart...
are oh so lovable
And yet, I have such a crazy heart
No, not a word!
I've won the round today
I've got to Bombay before Jai!
Sushma...
You're late again, dad.
- Who's that...?
My flight got delayed
in London by 2 hours
Or I would surely have
beaten you at it this time
That's all right.
Try next time
So... where is she?
In the room?
Who?
- The girl
Where is my daughter-in-law to be?
You've returned empty-handed again?
You're the one the girls
are crazy about, dad
We can always talk about the girl.
How about wishing Mom first?
Have you met her?
I'm the first to arrive, but it's
your right to greet her first
I'm late. It's my mistake
And your son wouldn't meet you
because he wanted me...
to wish you a happy birthday first
You've given me a great son.
But there's one hitch
He hasn't brought me
a daughter-in-law yet
A daughter-in-law isn't everything...
all right, she is
I promise, I'll bring one
by the next year
But you're with me, aren't you?
He's still not willing to believe
that the plane-crash...
he still thinks that you will
return some day
I mean, I'll get a wrong shot
One moment
Give me the camera and stand
with Jai. I'll take the pictures
Say paneer (cottage cheese)
- It's cheese, dad
Cheese is too English, son. Paneer
brings out the Indianness in you
Say paneer
Wow! God has given you
your soulmate...
What's happening, dad?
- I sometimes think...
you do make a great couple.
- Couple...?
I'm Jai's best friend.
Not girlfriend
No marriage for Anita.
Only social-service, right?
Social-service...? You mean you do
social service in those clothes?
It isn't necessary to wear hand-spun
clothes for social service
What is necessary is to make people
like you dole out the money
I get it! I was only taking
a picture of yours...
and you're getting me on film!
Sit down and chat
You may leave, uncle. But you're
coming with me tomorrow, Jai
Apart from earning money, you must
also do some charity in life
It's good for the soul.
- But dad's waiting for me
It's only for ten minutes, Jai!
- Now look, Anita
You spoke about charity, I agreed.
You wanted a lift, and I gave it
And now...
- Give me ten minutes
I want you to the meet the principal
You haven't taken an appointment?
- No. She's here at 10 every day
I'm not meeting her
without an appointment
You still have 9 minutes.
Go and take the appointment
You're giving half a million
in charity, Jai
8 minutes...
7 minutes
6...
5,4,3,2,1 ... time out!
What do I see...?
You're studying?
You passed out of school
because I bribed them...
and bought the college you studied in.
And you're now studying?
You've fractured your finger?
No?
Know what? I bribed my way
through education too
I don't have the brains to understand
that. What are you saying?
Not you, dad.
- So?
So there's a girl...
My son's in love!
Fantastic!
And you've been scanning
the books for romantic lines?
I'll give you the best possible
line they've used in love. Say...
I know
That's exactly what
I'm trying to memorise
I love you isn't something
you got to memorise
But if you still must,
repeat it after me
I'd tell her, if she could listen.
- What does that mean?
She can neither hear nor speak
Now please don't play the
villain between us, okay?
In your happiness lies mine, my son.
And it's good too
She can't hear, nor speak.
She won't know when we fight!
Let's go...
- Where to?
You're the groom, I'm the guest.
Let's go and bring her
No, dad. I don't know
anything about her yet
You drive your car at
the speed of a jet...
but you move at snail's pace in love?
Find out about her folks
I'll prepare for the wedding
Would you know of the
beautiful teacher...?
Where's the Principal's office?
- Over there
I'm going to have word with her...
You went away yesterday!
Mr. Jai... who wanted
to see you yesterday
Have you brought your cheque today?
- Oh yes
Your cheque.
- You can speak!
You can even hear!
- You can hear and speak too!
What did you think? That everyone
here can neither hear nor speak?
Happens, you know. People often
mistake me for a deaf and dumb
I don't want to
give you this money
Not just this money.
I want to sponsor the whole show
I have a condition.
- What?
I want to help in organising the show.
- You won't be able to do it
I mean... what will you do?
- I can do just about anything
Dusting the chairs, perhaps.
Or hammering in a nail...
or just gaping at you.
- What?
I mean, you can hear and speak.
So can I...
it's these kids who
need to be looked after
Who's there...?
Who is it?
Me. Only me
- What are you doing up there?
Following you...
I mean, with lights
That isn't your job.
Please come down
I told you I could do
just about anything, I...
Are you all right?
The sand saved me
You asked me to come down...
I took the shortcut
Ever since I fell
in love with you...
I can't go to sleep,
nor do I have any peace
Your choice.
- How did you know?
When one gets close to someone...
go on
one gets to know about
her likes and dislikes
I always thought I'd have to
be very formal with the sponsor
But you...
- No formalities
No formalities.
So...?
You've become a part
of our lives so soon...
you don't seem to be
an outsider at all
Like it?
- Oh yes
And Mr. Sponsor wants me to
wear it during the show?
Oh no. Actually...
I'm lucky to have the opportunity
to wear such a beautiful necklace
Watch it
What are you doing?
- For memory
One day to go for the show.
After that...
After that it'll all be over.
This tension and stuff
And our relationship, too.
- Jai...
relationships are made.
They never end
What are you doing here?
- Won't you say something to her?
Are you crazy? I was just...
- Tell her how you feel
Put some sincerity into it. It must
look as if you can't live without her
No, it's not happening
Oh go away...
you're ruining all my confidence
Dad, please play Tia for a while
Come along, dad
Shut that mouth... please
Tia, there's something
I want to tell you
Ever since I have seen you...
why're you glaring
at me like that, dad?
Forget it, Jai.
It's not your cup of tea
Looks like I'll have to do something.
I'll tell her
Don't you dare say a word to her.
- I will too!
Goodness...
Goodness me...
my love, you are the one
I have fallen in love with
Goodness!
With my eyes, I have
secretly told you that I yield
How will I meet your gaze?
I feel so very shy
How will I live
without seeing you?
It almost kills me
It goes berserk in love with you...
my anklets won't listen to me
Pining torments me.
Love has been my undoing
Goodness!
With your name on my lips,
I spend my days...
I spend my nights pining
I remember every moment
the naughty things you did
My lips thirst for love.
The fire rages on
How will I reason with my heart?
It's so crazy
Goodness!
You are the one I have loved
You are my beloved.
You are the one I love
Thanks for saying yes
This humble gift... for you
To the beginning
of our new relationship
I'll first have to say I love you
I've had it!
Whom are you talking to?
I'm glad I met you.
I personally wanted to thank you
It's because of you that this
charity show is a success
Oh no, I only put in some money.
- Not just the money
You have put your heart in it too
- Actually, you're right
And I'm also glad I've met you.
Because I too...
Yes? Go on.
What is it?
May I say it?
- Of course, go ahead
That's all I've learnt...
for you
The first time I saw you,
I thought you were...
I've been all over the world
But no girl has ever made
a place in my heart
And I think you too...
Here's your beloved, Tia!
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
But my plane let me down again
What are you doing out here?
There's no one around...
has the show-time changed?
- The show is over, Raj
Shall we go?
- Looks like I'm in for trouble
Sure, let's go
Tia, when is this programme of
yours going to be telecast again?
After all, I'll have to
watch your programme too
Please tighten your seat-belt.
We're ready for take-off
Say something, Tia... please
Tell me something. If you were
angry with me, why did you hug me?
And since you have hugged me,
why are you angry with me?
Say something, please
If not anything something good,
you may even scold me
You're not going to find
a lover like me, Tia...
I'm begging to be scolded!
I can make you open your mouth.
Which ice-cream will you have?
Give me an ice-cream that
will change the lady's mood
Be ready. The moment they
walk in, switch that on
And you... shower rose-petals
the moment he arrives
Astride the mare
goes the bridegroom...
with the sword tied to his waist
He looks so proud to have
found a beautiful bride...
they do make a great couple
Raj...
- At last, she speaks!
Looks like the ice-cream
has worked its magic
Yes?
- Do you love me?
Love...?
That's a very crooked question.
- Tell me
Tia, we've known each other
for four years
The first time I met you,
I felt a sense of belonging
Yours is the face that lingers
before my eyes all day and night
Whether I'm busy or far away...
you're always close to my heart
You're the one I will
live and die for
What I actually mean
to say is that...
I want to grow old with you
And some day, on this very bench,
I want to lie in your lap...
and have an ice-cream
Is this what they call love?
Why don't we get married then?
- Married...?
There's a problem.
- What?
Tell me, Raj
It's like this, Tia.
The two of us do want to get married
But who will marry us?
I had decided to bring your
daughter-in-law home today
I even proposed to her.
But at the last moment...
I'll do my best, Ma.
I'll do what I can
God... why does this happen
only to my son?
He couldn't forget his mother...
how will he ever forget his love?
Who's calling?
- I'm her friend
Tia, call for you
Who is it?
- Your friend
I have a request, Tia.
I want to meet you
Jai, if there's something you
want to say, tell me now...
No, Tia. I've got to
talk to you in person
I'm sorry, Jai.
I won't be able to come
Once... only once.
Remember what you said?
Relationships are born.
They never end
Do come for whatever relationship
you think we share
Cafe Bistro, at 5 this evening.
I'll wait for you
You will come, won't you?
Come
What is the matter, Jai? There are
no people in your restaurant...?
There will be no one.
It's booked only for you
Your choice
Tia, after the show got over,
when you were no longer with me...
I felt as if there was
a huge void in my life
Jai, you know I...
- I know everything, Tia
What you perhaps don't know is that
I run a huge business empire
M.D.'s and CEO's the world over
long to spend time with me and I...
I long for you, Tia
You have the whole world to
get on with your business, Jai
So why must you want to make my
little world your business?
Because I'm in love with you, Tia
I want to marry you
You can't turn an acquaintance of
a few days into such a relationship
Why not?
- Ties of the heart...
that you want to forge with me,
I already share with Raj
So why are you...
- Now look, Tia...
if you wish, we could right now...
- Excuse me
If you've called me here to seek
an answer to your proposal...
my answer is No, Mr. Jai Mehta
Thank you very much.
I'm getting late
I was so sure that Tia loves you.
She looked so happy with you
How could she refuse you and go away
with that guy on the mobike?
Cheer up, my son
Now listen to this!
There was this boy like you...
who went crazy looking for his girl
And someone gave him the idea
of advertising in the newspapers
Wanted wife
The boy agreed
He issued an ad...
Wanted Wife
He got thousands of letters in a week.
One thing was common in all of them
Guess what...? Take my wife away
any time you want to they said!
I'm only trying to change your mood
She came there, didn't she?
That's it, she's interested then
Her parents could have
made a commitment elsewhere
But she need not necessarily
agree with it
She isn't married yet, my son.
You still have a chance
Don't lose hope
Keep trying, your appeal
for love will be upheld some day
Welcome, Mr. Late Latif.
- Me...?
Who are you?
The master has sent these flowers
and a letter for you
He has also asked for a reply
- Royal style, all right!
These flowers are testimony
of my love for you
And I wait for the day
when you will love me too
The dust and pollution of this city
could make your beauty wither away
This is the key to the car at
your door-step. Your birthday gift
From me.
Yours, Jai
Give this back to him
Tia, tell Raj I'll be there
in a moment
Raj hasn't arrived yet, Mother.
Someone rang the bell by mistake...
You're back again?
I love you so much, I keep
coming back to get a scolding
This bouquet?
Where did you find it?
A gift of nature.
- Nature?
Yes. We were brought up
on wind, dust and water...
so nature obviously gave it...
- Where did you find it?
I found it lying outside and liked it.
I thought I'd pick it up for you
Isn't it nice?
- Can't you even buy a bouquet?
So you're late again?
How are you?
- Not nice at all
Nice flowers.
- He's brought someone else's bouquet
He can't even remember to buy flowers!
- Your love makes me forget everything
Why don't you forget coming here?
Or where I live? Or me instead?
I forgot that too,
but I had left my licence here
I saw a cop and remembered.
So where's my licence?
Which means... he doesn't even
remember my birthday!
My God! Is it your birthday?
No wonder you're looking so good today.
For the first time ever
Look at him, Mother!
You know how Raj loves
to tease you
He can't digest his food
till he pulls your leg
Why did you do that...? You
could've spared her at least today
It's her birthday.
Now go and placate her
You look very beautiful
today... really
On this auspicious occasion
of her birthday...
I think I'd rather marry Tia
and take her away...
instead of giving her something
What say?
You're right. I think it's time
the two of you got married
But are you going to bother Tia
even after the wedding?
Absolutely. This fun and laughter
is what life is all about
So let's decide the rest
of the things too
The rest of the things...?
- I have no one of my own
So I'll myself have to
talk about the dowry, right?
Dowry...?
As you know, Raj... everything
I possess, belongs to Tia
What else do you want?
Tell me
Think it over, mother.
- Raj, what are you...?
I've thought it over.
What do you want, tell me
You, mother
I want a mother in dowry
I don't want to be orphaned
all over again
But a mother does not live
in her daughter's house
She lives in her son's house,
doesn't she?
Even if you don't call me your son,
treat me like one, mother
Say yes mother
I have everything today, Mother.
Everything
Take your girlfriend to a seven-star
and she says she loves you
Here's the seven-star
Wait... where are we going?
Get down
Here?
- Where else?
But you said...
- Seven-star. This is the one
Even if it's a small place,
one must have a large-heart
You got to be hungry to eat.
Are you hungry?
Come on
Do something special today...
it's Tia's birthday
Will be done, sir
Please sit down
I'll be back in a moment, sir
What do you think of the place?
Why've you kept the plant here?
- It's the lady's birthday, sir
Oh yes, it is
You've changed the whole scene.
Why did you have to spend so much?
I have... so it's all right
Such a huge cake... for me?
- No. It's not our cake
Mister... please take the cake away.
It's not ours
Stop kidding, Raj. It even has
my name written on it
One moment... let me confirm
Any girl by the name Tia in here?
You, perhaps...?
I think you're the only one
who's Tia
May I cut the cake then?
- No
Aren't you supposed to close
your eyes and make a wish first?
I've done it.
Raj, what are you...?
Nothing. Just cut the cake
Where are you taking it?
- Let me serve dinner, sir
What for? We're going
to be happy with the cake
I'll have the upper-deck,
Tia'll have the lower one
Nice joke...
- I'm not joking!
Raj, I'll never forget
this lovely evening!
Neither will I.
After all those dishes...
I mean, we have yet to eat
Please get me the bill.
- Your bill has been paid, sir
Paid?
But please give me the bill.
- As I said, sir...
Maybe I look like a tramp,
but I'm a decent guy
You can adjust with me, if I'm short
of dough. You can keep my watch
Sir, you do crack nice jokes.
- I don't crack jokes at all
I'm a serious man.
- So am I...
and I tell you seriously
that your bill has been paid
This is strange!
Who could have paid the bill?
I know who paid it.
- Who?
Was it fun?
Jai, I've told you in plain terms that
there is no place for you in my life
So why did you...?
- So you're the one who sent...
those flowers and the cake...?
I'm very happy to meet you
What makes me more happy is that you
have changed the colour of our evening
Not at all. Such a big day in
Tia's Iife and this dingy place...?
I thought I'd make it
worthy of Tia
Mr. Jai Mehta, maybe you're
a big man...
but you have no right
to call someone small
And who gave you the right
to do that? Who...?
And you call Raj...
- Not me, Tia...
he called the eatery small.
- You don't understand, Raj
He sponsored the show
at our school
He even proposed to me...
but I turned him down
Ever since, he has been trying
to impress me. He's trying to...
create misunderstandings between us.
- Tia, is there room...
for misunderstanding between us?
Jai-saheb, we aren't married yet
But we've divorced each other
several times
Just think what a deep relationship
we must share
It's not your mistake, I must say.
Tia is indeed very beautiful
I call it my good-fortune
that Tia's in love with me
Actually, intimacy between hearts
can never be forced
It happens on its own
Now for the bill you paid...
Please keep it.
For Tia's sake
Your arrangements were excellent.
The food and especially the music
See? This is how my Raj is
If you're so fond of
making arrangements...
my wedding is coming up next week.
With Raj
This relationship of hearts
is so loveable
And yet, we are
so crazed at heart
We are madly in love
with each other...
the whole world knows that
This relationship of hearts
is so loveable
Your kiss on my eyes, my love...
your kiss on my eyes, my love...
has made me blossom
You have made me blossom
And yet, we are
so crazy at heart
This relationship of hearts
is so loveable
In loneliness, my love...
in loneliness, my love...
I have called out
to you very often
We sure are crazy at heart
This relationship of hearts
is so loveable
Jai...?
- Raj?
What a co-incidence!
My motorbike has stalled
Come, I'll give you a ride
So where will you go?
- The hospital
Bikes are repaired in a garage,
not hospitals
Tia's in hospital
Which hospital?
- Avon
What happened to Tia?
- That which happens after marriage
Tia's becoming a mother
I don't drink
Jai, my family will
be complete today
Tia will be a mother
and I - a father
This is the biggest joy in the
lives of those in love, isn't it?
Oh yes, I guess so
I forgot to ask about you
You've grown a stubble...
no problems, I hope?
Forget about me.
You're becoming a father and...
starting a family. How does it feel?
- Fantastic
Should I sing, dance, go berserk...?
I don't know what to do
Because I'm an orphan, I know
how precious the love of parents is
But my child isn't destined to
lead the life of an orphan
He'll get love from his
mother, his grandmother...
and what is most important...
the name of his father. My name
When someone asks him what
his Papa's name is...
he'll say in his
babyish way, Laj
My papa's name is Laj
The happiness shows in your eyes.
- Yes, I've found all relationships
Relationships of the heart
Aren't you coming in?
You ought to spend this time
with Tia alone
And Raj...
should you ever need something...
Tia, here comes your beloved
The nurse told me it's a baby-boy!
Here he comes. Late, as usual
- I'm not late...
Careful!
- So sweet! My little boy!
He's taken after me, hasn't he?
- Yes
But his eyes are like Tia's
His eyes, nose, cheeks,
ears, mouth...
are all like Tia's.
The rest is all like you
See? Your mother and my mother
have ganged up together
But that's all right.
You're going to be my darling boy
I'll give you all the love...
I never had in my childhood
You have given me the relationship
I probably wasn't destined to have
You have given me
the cheerfulness of the Sun
the calmness of the Moon
You have given me
every happiness
You are very kind, my dear lady
We are so crazy at heart
We are madly in love
with each other...
that we are madly in love
the whole world knows
This relationship of hearts
is so loveable
This intimacy between our hearts
Don't cry, Anshu...
look, Papa's here
What happened, Raj?
- I'm tired, mother
I'm tired of life, Tia. I have
the same rickety motorbike...
the same irritating life...
shut up!
I thought my life would change after
you came... but nothing happened
The same old mobike!
- Am I...?
And I thought Anshu would be
bring me a stroke of good luck
But it's the same old motorbike!
When you can't get your motorbike...
serviced properly,
how is my son to blame?
Who's blaming him? I ask,
when Anshu grows up...
how will the three of us
go on the motorcycle?
On the rickety motorcycle!
- Yes! How will we move on it?
Like everyone else does!
Raj, we are happy. Even if
we're making less money...
we are at least happy, aren't we?
- But I'm not happy!
I think I'll give up...
I can't take the nagging!
What?
- Why think? I give up!
Right now, I give up!
- What's gotten into him?
Go and find out. Go
What's gotten into you, Raj?
- I said, I give up!
I told you, I give up!
I give up this rickety motorbike!
For you, a new car!
A new car and an old driver
You don't want a new driver,
do you?
What happened?
- Raj has got a new car. Look
The office gave it to me.
And a promotion too
The post of branch manager.
- Why did you tease Tia?
For fun, mother
As compensation, let's all
dine at a 5-star this evening
5-star or 7-star?
- I told you
The two of you may go.
- No, Mother. You must join us
There are times the husband and
wife must go out on their own
We'll can always do that, mother.
- I told you!
Hear that...?
That's what Anshu wants too
Tia, here comes your beloved
Where are you going?
I'm your husband
I've got mother's permission
Park it carefully, please
I could only dream of
such 5-star hotels
Give up these dreams. They're
part of someone's life now
You're right, Anita. But how
will I reason with my heart?
It still dreams of Tia
What else do you dream of?
Another promotion, another car
and another visit to this 5-star
That's not what we are here for.
- What else?
We are here only for your smile
Your smile, the dot on your forehead,
and those eyes...
what happened?
She's my first and last love
How will I forget her?
- Who's asking you to forget her Jai?
I'm only asking you to take courage
from her memories
That's easier said, Anita.
It's easier said
This much would've paid the
grocer's bill for a month!
Do you now understand
what a 5-star is?
It's all right.
For the sake or our happiness
We don't come here every day
Shall we leave?
- The change...?
It's a tip.
- So much...?
20 rupees should be enough
May I say something, sir?
- Go ahead
If your love is true, God will
always brings hearts together
See?
- He's right
If love is true.
- I understand
So you mean I'm not really
in love with Tia?
You are. But have you thought
of how much Raj loves her?
Have you thought that Tia's
happiness lies in Raj?
Have you ever considered that
if your love for Tia is true...
in her happiness must lie
your own joy
But why would you think like that?
Henceforth...
No more booze for me!
Here's my car
You won't forget your promise
after you sober down, will you?
So you don't trust me?
- I do
So your trust is perfectly in place.
Give me the keys
I'll drive the car tonight.
Please! Only tonight
Here you are
Jai Mehta's starting a new life.
- Papa will be very happy
All thanks to you
Watch out!
What are you doing...?
You're in the wrong lane, Jai!
You've saved a jilted lover
from dying
Nothing will happen to you
Nothing's happening to you
Go to sleep...
go back to sleep
Raj and Anita...
- I know, my son
And Tia?
- The doctors are trying to revive her
Hasn't she regained consciousness?
Please take me to her
Tia, my child...
Tia, look at me...
Doctor...
what's happened to Tia?
- Everything will be all right
Why doesn't she speak?
- Please don't worry...
we are doing our best
Doctor, what's happened to her?
Nothing can be said
about a case like this
Please arrange for the money.
We might need an operation...
You needn't worry about the money.
I'll meet all the expenses, doctor
But you must save this girl's life
Who's he...?
- Mr. Mehta
It's his son's car your
daughter had an accident with
Please come with me, Mr. Mehta.
We have many formalities to complete
We'll keep the patient under
observation all 24 hours
Mother...
I'm your culprit, mother
I've made this mistake, mother
I wasn't in my senses
I was drunk. So when Raj's car...
You can hit me as much as you want to.
Give me any punishment you wish to
Because of my negligence,
my friend Anita...
she had told me that
she wanted to drive the car
Had I listened to her,
Raj wouldn't have died...
Not Raj alone
Under the wheels of your car,
it isn't just Raj...
you have crushed my entire family
My daughter...
she had just begun a new life
And you've turned her into
a widow, in just a moment
You have!
Her son is longing for his mother
He hadn't even held his father's hand
and learnt to walk yet. And you...
you have orphaned him!
You have!
And you come seeking pardon
after committing a crime?
What can you do...? What?
Can you bring Raj back to life?