Watch out for the devil!
Yin!
Prajna paramita!
She is here!
I'll take care of her, come on
Watch out!
I saw it
This Tree Devil is very powerful
Now its energy is gone!
Let me freeze it with
the power from my palm
But it will resurrect
in a hundred year's time
Hocus pocus!
Prajna paramita!
Master, we've finally
found Kwan Bo County...
It's just over...
There? Over there?
Look at your map
Hey... it's flown away
Where's it gone?
We'll get to Kwan Bo County
if we head west
Master, there's rain clouds coming
Let's find shelter
Alright
Let's go...
There's a place to hide
Buddha, please make the rain go
so we can get on our way
Master, I'm not thirsty
you drink it
It's bad luck!
Go!
Gentlemen!
I didn't even recognize the skull
Give me my money back!
He's a master swordsman!
The man with the money
should go on ahead!
Run, run!
It's a tragedy, tragedy!
Master, there's a
killer outside, he's...
Here?
Thank god I got my money back!
I've been saving
if those thieves took it...
It's a bit cold, isn't it?
Money is illusion
why kill for it?
Be merciful, or you will
pay for your deeds
Merciful?
You don't have to make a living
I worked hard for this money!
You want to fight?
Master!
It's only a hoe
Fong, dust to dust
ashes to ashes...
Go and bury the bodies
This guy's really shifty, the gold...
Stop talking and start working
I'm soaked!
Don't mind if I light a fire?
Master, the bodies are in pieces
Do I bury hands with hands
and legs with legs?
No, be sure to bury whole corpses
I'm not sure that's possible
Alcohol keeps out the cold
Want some?
Let's all get warmer
You stupid fool!
Fire! Fire
Master, is this how you punish him?
Rubbish, I'm not an arsonist!
I'm sorry, we all make mistakes
I've made you lose your shelter
The market is just ahead!
We're all wanderers
We don't bear grudges
See you later
I've put the bodies back
together again
But there's one finger left
With my expertise
I don't bother with fingers
Maybe someone else did it
Are there other chopped up bodies?
This is common fighting ground
may die...
Enjoy putting them back together
Oh! It's getting dark
Ghost Festival sword
and weapons for sale
Help! Murder!
You hit me! Stay there!
This sword is the latest style!
Do you think I'm buying jewelry?
Who hit me? Show yourself and fight!
Who hit someone?
What's happening?
Make way!
Police passing through, make way!
Police passing, make way!
What's going on here?
I don't know
Forget it then
Hey, stop staring at me!
It's nothing, nothing's wrong!
Come look at our swords, sir
It's Ghost Festival!
The human race has stooped
to new lows
How can we Buddhists
redeem their souls?
I really don't know
With my wisdom, I can save them
But my body's feeling very weak
Let's find an inn
get some food and sleep
Buddha meditated facing
a wall for 3 years
and you complain after
no food for one day
For penance, chant 5,000 times
to purity the mind
Right!
Look, food, let's eat
then purity my mind
His brain's in his stomach!
That cretin
I'll kill him for 15 dollars
It was only 10 dollars
last time, why more?
Because I'm a better
swordsman now
So you say, but how good?
Beef brisket and noodles!
Hey, I never ordered that
Are you saying I made a mistake?
Orders returned are charged double!
What do you want?
I told you I didn't order it!
It's just a misunderstanding
As I improve
my price will rise again
If you don't like it
find someone else
For that price
I need some sort of sample
You want me to show off? No problem!
You want to see sample?
Sir, spare us some food?
I bet you my head
No, get lost!
Fong
My sword's a bit long, I'm sorry!
We shouldn't stay here, let's go!
Every time I see you there's trouble
Brother
and more trouble now
with that lump of gold!
Master, there's shelter ahead
It's a Temple
Orchid Temple
The entrance is over there
They've gone inside
But Orchid Temple's haunted
wait till dawn
Yes, let's wait!
Dawn? What if someone else gets it?
Hey, you lead! Me?
A ghost got my fool, run!
Run!
It's a bit draughty in here, Master
Don't be afraid, let me tell you
Orchid Temple is haunted
What? Haunted...
Master, Master!
Fong, stop stepping on my heels
I just want you to
know I'm behind you
If you're so scared
sleep outside the door
It's pouring outside
Master, if it's really haunted...
I don't mind if we carry on walking
Fong, we have Gold Buddha
to protect us
No one will dare come in
So we won't have to worry
about it being stolen
We'll just stay overnight
Shall we satisfy the God of Hunger?
You beg the ghosts
to spare you some food
Funny, I've forgotten
what I've just said!
Who said a ghost got his foot?
Was it you?
No
He did!
If it got you, how come you
could run so fast?
There's a woman singing, up there
Sister, it's raining
so hard outside
I wonder how long
before they come inside
We're here!
So many men!
Women! They're beautiful!
Smells so good
Don't go, so beautiful!
Come on
There are more!
They're so ugly!
The one in the middle's
the prettiest
She's so old!
The one next to her's beautiful
Priestress, there are so many
I'll help Lotus
Alright, that way I won't
have to wait so long
These men're already trapped
who needs your help?
I thought you'd be quicker
it took you ages
They're already ours
so what's the rush?
Take your clothes off
she's coming
I'm taking the prettiest one
Hands off!
Your skin's so soft
Give me a kiss!
Go to hell
There're all kinds of games
want to try?
Something in the water
bit me. What is it?
What is it? Let's go!
What's happening?
Let's go, they're demons
What's that sound, Master?
The ghosts are out
What shall I do? Master
Watch the Gold Buddha
and stay
I'm going to catch the demons!
Don't come near me
I have a Gold Buddha
You're powerful
you hide even from me!
Show your true selves!
Stars scatter!
Still able to hide
it's powerful!
Priestess, what about that monk?
Don't worry!
He maybe powerful
but he's no match for me
We'll play with them awhile
You seduce the little monk
Priestess, let me go
I can handle him
You're not experienced enough
when it comes to men
Priestess, I know exactly
what you mean
You don't want her
wasting your time
Let me bring him back to you quickly
Sorry
I forgot your cover was damaged
You got all wet
I'll say some prayers
as penance later
I know you have great powers
If we really meet a... ghost
Please help me destroy
whatever it is
Buddha!
Oh no!
Help, there's a ghost!
A ghost chasing her?
That means she's not a ghost
Help!
Ghost!
Lady!
There's a ghost! Ghosts!
I'm so afraid!
I'm so scared, please help me!
I can see flesh!
Where is the ghost?
Let me hide behind you!
Look there's something
moving over there
Hold me tight!
Your leg
Feel my heart
it's beating so rapidly!
Come on!
I break my vows if
I'm near a woman!
Let's pray together
it'll keep the ghosts away
Don't pray now
let's do something else!
Let me go, or I'll break my vows!
Did you know, you're my first man?
Let me help you undress
What? Undress?
Hey wait, my shoe!
If Master sees me like this
He'll never believe I was
saving your life!
No! I must pray
Where're my prayer books?
Fire! Come and save me!
How did it catch fire?
My clothes are on fire!
Take your clothes off!
Fire, help!
Stop undressing
They're not burning now!
I must, I'm afraid of fire!
But I'll see everything
Lady
Hey, monk... has the fire gone out?
It was so dangerous!
My clothes are all burnt, what to do?
Cover yourself with my robe
You're so kind!
Put it on quickly, I won't watch
I tripped on your clothes
Stop or I won't be able
to control myself!
I'm a bad girl
Are you as bad as me?
I thought you were being
chased by a ghost?
Ghost? Here's your ghost!
Come and get me
This is fun!
But it didn't last long!
Lucky I prayed in time
Or I would've done that
"stuff" with you
Hey, monk...
What would you have done?
Tell me
I said means I want...
I want means I desire...
I desire means I'll do...
If I do, I'll never stay a monk!
No, I must pray
Stop praying, help me up
Quick!
I'll help you up
But you promise not to
come too close
Damn I saw it!
Aren't you interested in me at all?
Interested? In what way?
All men are interested in this!
Don't take off my pants
It's strange!
Your head aches when I pray
You weren't being
chased by a ghost!
You are a ghost!
I'm going to get you!
It's really haunted
I'm scared!
I better run!
Come over here!
Reveal your true form!
You're mine
Reveal yourself!
Stupid monk, why've you
stopped praying?
Go, if Master returns
you'll never escape!
Why are you letting me go?
I'm giving you a
chance to reform
So you can reincarnate
as a good person
I'm evil! I'll never change
Hey, my robe!
If you want it, get it yourself!
It serves you right!
Help me, quick help me!
Go on, scram!
Waiting for me to hit you?
Hey, my robe!
Still playing games with me!
Master!
You appeared so suddenly!
Fong, what're you doing
here half naked?
It's too hot
I came outside to cool down
Hot? Where's the Gold Buddha?
It's inside, it'sjust fine!
Well, did you see anything untoward?
No way, not with the
Gold Buddha here
No ghost would dare come near
Even if it did
it wouldn't get away!
And did you find anything?
That demon is quite something
Anyway
we're staying
only one night
and leaving tomorrow
with the Gold Buddha
So we'd better get some rest
Or we'll be tired tomorrow
Okay...
I'll capture them sooner or later
Your senses are impure
that's why you're hot
Take the Gold Buddha out and pray
Take the Gold Buddha out?
Pray all night
in front of it
On my own?
Why, you want me to keep you company?
No, no!
Okay, let's go inside!
Will you stop that
If Master sees it, I've had it!
Fong
Good morning Master
Bring the Buddha, we're leaving
O kay
Darn, he'll find out
sooner or later
Please help me find
the Gold Buddha!
What did you say?
Nothing, just saying my prayers
Fong
I'm glad the Buddha's safe
Or there's no point in
going to Imperial Temple
That's right!
Master, if we leave like
this now
It's not quite right
Since you know Orchid Temple
is haunted
Shouldn't we stay
and get rid of the demons?
Sort of say in some manuscript
"If no one goes to hell
and we don't go to hell
Who will go to hell?"
You're a monk
and you don't know which manuscript!
I've always had a bad memory
But leaving like this
is irresponsible
You're right! I'll stay
and catch the demons
You take the Buddha
to Imperial Temple
Right, I'll go
Fong, are you alright?
Yes
after praying all night
my mind is pure
But my stomach is even purer
and now in the sun, I feel faint
Are you saying that...
You're sick?
I'll be fine Master
I'll overcome it
I'll make it
I'm getting there
it's getting better...
No it's not working...
I'm going to faint
I think you're hungry
I'll beg for food
My student does not
behave like a monk
Buddha be merciful!
Gold Buddha
I'd better find you today!
Haven't slept all night
I feel faint
I'll find the Buddha
and get Master to leave
Or when he's out
she'll come for me again
and it'll be another sleepless night!
Snake!
What now? Oh no!
I only have a day left
Buddha, have mercy, help Fong
Buddha!
Look this blade cuts heads
off like slicing melons
Really?
Let's try it on your head
Please be merciful
put down your knives
Get lost
Give me something
Shove off!
You monks
always lecturing people
You're ruining our business
Get lost!
Give me the money you owe me
I don't have any money
Give my money back!
No money?
What's all that on the ground?
That's my money!
It's mine now
Since when did I owe you money?
When you asked me to do the job
Whatjob?
I don't know you
Exactly, he doesn't know you!
The money's mine
I don't know him
Go to hell
Sir, how do you know
the money's yours?
He's right, prove it's yours
and you can have it!
Right, you said it
you better mean it
Abracadabra...
Rise...
Money, money, are you mine?
Ah! It's black magic!
Let's go!
You also follow Buddha
you should do good
Not concern yourself with money
How else would you get any alms?
I wouldn't accept that sort of money
No? Then leave
At least I earn my money
You wander around
begging for food
You're just a beggar in disguise!
Money is only illusion
You can't get what's not yours
Monk, is this your doing?
Mercy, Buddha is merciful
You're a fake, monk!
Admit your pranks!
There must be a way
to break his spell!
Hey, don't go! Don't go!
My money!
Another fruitless job
Damn monk!
It's getting dark!
What shall I tell Master?
I'll say the
snakes took it
How could the snakes take it?
Right, I'll say the
ghosts took it
The Gold Buddha repels ghosts
impossible!
I'll tell him the truth
That'll be Master
I didn't mean it Master
I just dropped it!
Master, actually...
It's you?
It's you again?
What are you doing here?
Darn!
Let me rest for one night okay?
The way you live
don't you feel like a whore?
Perhaps if you were human
making a living
But you're a ghost
why a slut too?
Am I a slut?
Anyone who strips a guy's
pants off is a slut!
What are you looking for?
The Gold Buddha...
I don't know where it...
The Gold Buddha?
Why're you getting so close?
I had enough fun last night!
It's only down there
Don't come so close to me!
You think I don't want to?
I can't leave till the
Gold Buddha's found
I'll help you
The Gold Buddha's
very powerful
Aren't you afraid?
There's no other way
If you don't leave
I'll have to move!
That's a point!
Let's go together!
Last night you surprised
me and I fell
I dropped the Gold Buddha
somewhere here
Don't step on my clothes
If they fall off
you'll say I was stripping
Where is it?
Snakes! I forgot to say
there're snakes here
Where?
Over there!
Stop it, my head aches!
I'm only praying very softly
Go upstairs
you're getting in the way
With you here
I'll never find it!
Go on!
You're right
Mind the snakes
Snakes! Lots of snakes!
The Gold Buddha! I found it!
Where is it?
Over there, help me
There're many snakes
I didn't tell you to kill them
How did this happen?
What will I say?
How can I put it back together?
I've been bitten by a snake
It hurts!
Help!
I don't want to kill you, go!
Are you alright?
I've been poisoned
What shall we do?
Suck the venom out
with your mouth
Please, quick
I can feel the venom...
I feel faint
Is that alright?
That's fine, thank you
It's okay, anyway your
wound isn't real
Then why did you swallow the blood?
To keep you happy
The wound isn't real
but the venom is!
You're right, that means...
I'll help you suck it out
No, that means mouth to mouth
You'll die once
the venom takes effect
Pretend I'm not a woman
Then who are you?
Pretend I'm your Master
He would never do this
Pretend I'm your mother
I've never met my mother
Try someone I've seen
How about him?
Him?
O kay
Whatever
What are you doing?
Sucking the venom
What did you stick in my stomach?
My tongue
Why stick your tongue
in my stomach?
To suck out the venom!
There's still some left in you
Really?
Is your heart beating rapidly?
Yes!
Does your whole body feel hot?
Yes
Do you feel sweaty
your head ache?
Yes
That's the effect
of the venom
We have to carry on
I'd rather die
Don't die here
Or you'll become
one of us
Okay, come on
Hang on
Are you ready?
Yes,... why didn't you stick
your tongue inside?
No! there's no venom
I was lying
How dare you deceive
an honest man
It's because of you
I dropped the Buddha
Look how I treat you
Is this my thanks?
I'm a monk!
I have rules to follow
You keep seducing me
You're trouble!
Really?
From what you say
isn't it a bore being a monk?
You can't do what every
man wants to do
Don't you feel deprived
being a monk?
Deprived?
I never had anything to lose
The priority is to
fix the Buddha...
So when Master comes
back we can leave
Don't set your clothes
on fire again!
Why're you a monk
if it's such hard work?
The first person I set
eyes on was Master
My first clothes
were monk's robes...
What else can I be
except a monk...
Do I have a choice?
You're grown up now
you can choose
I've been with Master for years
He's family...
Why'd my parents
leave me in a monastery
I'd like to know what
my parents look like...
So that if I ever met them...
I could avoid them
Don't fall off!
Your life is better
than mine was...
At least you have a Master!
No...
I was sold as soon
as I was born
Whoever bought me
became my parents
Finally a rich man
took me as his 2nd wife
I was murdered by his mistress
and buried here
That's the first time
I've told this story
I way lying
I'm glad it's a lie
If it were true it
would be tragic
So in comparison
you're free now
Not being sold again and again...
Pity you're a ghost
we could've been friends
Aren't we friends now?
Little monk
could you get close to anyone else?
I don't know
Do you think I'm beautiful?
Oh no, Master's returned, run away!
Fong, what are you doing?
Master, I'm just repairing
the stairs...
Wait outside, it's almost done
The feeling of evil
is stronger today
Master, you can't go inside
There are snakes inside
Snakes?
My powers protect and make me
immune to venom...
Snakes don't come near me
She must be gone by now!
The demons are close by
Fong
Why're you holding a comb?
I bought it to...
comb my eyebrows
It looks great...
You want to try it?
Shave your eyebrows
and you won't need a comb
Where's the Gold Buddha?
It's over there Master, see it?
Fong, close all the windows
To stop the demons entering
Very clever, Master!
Thank God, Master didn't
run into her!
Fong, bring me the gold paint
O kay
Oh, it was on the table
Your gold paint
Oh no, it's finished, Master
I haven't written on
all the windows yet...
Bring out all our holy objects
Seal all the entrances
Oh no!
Fong, what is it?
Did you see something?
It's just that I haven't
eaten all day...
I'm feeling a big faint...
Master, let me help you
I found you some food
get it from my bag
The ghosts will come
from this direction...
But we've run out
of holy objects
There's a gap over there...
Why don't you hang it up there?
This is where the evil's
the strongest
I'll repel it
Master, some ghost
took your beads!
Strange, how could a ghost
take my beads?
I'll get rid of all of them!
Help!
Fong is in trouble!
Little monk!
You shameless demon!
Help! Help
Help me! Master! Help! Master!
Mercy shrouds the world!
Help me!
The stars will scatter!
Fong, listen to me...
Go back and bring me
my holy objects
Right!
Mercy is boundless!
Help! I'm up here!
I warned you not to play
with that staff
Help!
Are you alright?
Get it away from me!
How come you are... so cold?
Leave me alone, I have to rest...
Otherwise I won't survive
as a ghost
Right, I'll go and save Master then
It doesn't look like you can move
Have you recovered?
I must go and save Master
Hush!
It feels cold!
What's happening?
One of my sisters is here
Good. I'll ask her to help you!
No, we hate each other
If you bring her here
we'll both be in trouble
So what can we do?
I can smell a human
Let's have a look
Don't worry, I have the staff
There's no time
Oh, it's you!
Are you surprised?
Fooling around behind
the Priestess's back?
How dare you disobey her orders?
Why do you look so ill?
Maybe you're the one
fooling around!
Are you bitching because
you feel guilty?
I helped the Priestess
fight the two monks...
and I got wounded...
Come over and help me...
Why should I help you?...
You put on these airs...
I'm sorry, I have no time
What was that?
Someone's hiding behind me
Who?
The little monk
Really?
Trying to trick me
into helping you?
No chance!
I'd never help you!
Why don't you stay
and wait for the Priestess
You're so cunning...
Trying to delay me
from helping the Priestess...
I won't tall for your tricks...
Let's go
That was a bit bluff...
If she'd believed you
I'd be dead
But if we didn't hate each other...
You wouldn't have had to hide
So you change your story
as it pleases you?
Fong!
I can't take you further
I must save Master...
You be on your way
Fong
What?
I was called Lotus
when I was alive
Why're you telling me?
I won't be visiting you...
and you won't be visiting me...
Man and ghost can't be together...
and even if you were human
it'd be hopeless
Because monks and women
can't be together
Remember, be more
careful in future
If you meet any
other monks
they won't give you a chance
Take care of yourself!
Damn monk, think you're
the most powerful?!
Tree Devil, you kill innocents
and insult God...
I'm going to capture you
That will be your punishment
Punishment?
You mean I will reap what I sow?
Exactly!
Those are the karmic rules
Don't you know wicked people
are buried with honour
Their deeds enshrined
in books and songs!
But when dead
they suffer in hell
Hell is only as dark as
the human world
Only the powerful
and ruthless thrive
There's still time to change
your ways, bald monk!
I've been to hell
so I know
Master! Your staff!
But I used it to pin down
the other ghost!
The dark deep underworld arise!
There is no justice!
Master!
Evil will win, and never fatter!