II anyone :00an thls?
Hay.
It's all rlght. Calm down, okay?
Samantha?
- Ara you out of your mlnd?
Not aword.
You dldn't say one word about thla to ma.
Don't you thlnk you owe me that?
Don't you thlnk that you mlght
respect me enough
to at laaat oonaldar what I had to say?
I dldn't want you worrylng about It.
Well, I'm worrlad, Curtla.
How are you paylng for all that?
I got a home Improvement loan
from the bank.
You know the expenses we have oomlng up.
You want to waate money
on a atupld tornado ahelter?
I'm dolng It... I'm dolng It for us.
I know you don't underatand.
You're rlght. I don't underatand.
I don't underatand half the atuff
you've been dolng lately.
I don't underatand you puttlng Red out back.
you ataylng up all nlght
In that atupld tornado ahelter.
You don't come to bed half the tlme.
You leave, you don't tell me
where you're golng. Explaln that to me.
Pleaae.
Tell me aomethlng
that helps me underatand
why you're belng llke thla.
There'a nothlng to explaln.
I'm gonna go put Hannah to bed.
Curtla?
Baby. Oh, my God. Baby...
Oh, my God. Baby.
My huaband'a havlng a aelzure.
41800 Tlndale Road. Hurry up. He's bleedlngl
Honey?
Honey? Are you okay?
You were havlng a aelzure.
I ealled an ambulance.
No. It's ﬁne. It's ﬁne.
Don't send an ambulance.
Ma'am?
Baby, what'a golng on?
I'm sorry you fellowa had to come
all the way out.
It's what we do.
Now we ean atlll take you In
If you want a doctor
to look at those cute In your mouth.
Yeah, that's all rlght.
I'll see somebody on Monday.
All rlght.
Thanks.
I haven't been honeat wlth you.
I'm sorry.
What'a golng on?
I've been havlng theae dreama.
I guess they're more llke nlghtmarea.
It's why I've been aotlng llke thla.
They...
They always atart wlth a klnd of atorm.
lee a real powerful atorm.
And there's always
thla dark, thlck raln.
lee freah motor oll.
And then the thlnga,
people, It Juat makes them crazy.
They attack me. Sometlmea...
Sometlmea they go after Hannah.
Flrat one I had,
Red nearly chewed through my arm.
That's why you put hlm out back?
Yeah.
What was the dream? Tonlght.
It was Dewart.
We were at the Job alte.
The atorm atarted and aomethlng happened.
Hla face...
Hla eyes were
dlfferent.
He came after me wlth a plck ax.
And we fought.
And he ran It through my leg.
It's hard to explaln,
beeauae It's not Juat a dream.
It's a feellng.
I'm afrald aomethlng mlght be comlng.
Somethlng that'a
not rlght.
I eannot deacrlbe It.
ljuat need you to belleve me.
I've been to a counselor.
I've seen her...
I've seen her a few tlmea.
You know what I come from.
And I promlaed myaelf...
I promlaed myself I would never leave.
And I am dolng everythlng that lean
to make that true.
Okay, alnce the doctor's approved
her aurgery,
we Juat need to get her acheduled.
The next poaalble openlng
lathe 21at of next month.
That'a alx weeke.
- Slx weeka?
- la that okay?
It's wonderful.
...thla polnt Juat to the weat.
I don't thlnk we'll have any problem.
We should be able to get 20,
maybe 30 In thla next week.
But we're looklng to see
how that's gonna shape up, so...
- Curtla?
- Yeah.
- What do you thlnk?
- Yeah. That sounds good.
We'll get It done.
Come In.
What you need, Curtla?
- I need a favor, Jlm.
- What'a that?
Can you take Dewart off my crew?
Juat reaaalgn hlm someplace else.
What's the trouble?
He not pulllng hla welght?
No, nothlng llke that. He's a good worker.
He's a good man. He's my frlend.
I thlnk It'd be eaaler not belng In
charge of someone I'm so close to.
You know, I underatand.
Thla la part of what It means
to manage people, Curtla.
You're gonna have to learn that.
Yea, alr. I appreclate that, but...
Well, It would Juat be
very helpful In thla eeae.
Okay.
Well, lean put hlm wlth Ruaaell.
- Anybody else you'd prefer?
- No. Whoever you thlnk'a rlght.
Okay. Okay.
Thank you.
You been mlaalng a lot of work, Curtla.
I know.
My daughter's had a lot of doctor'a vlalta.
I haven't let anythlng get behlnd.
No. But don't. Okay?
Yea, alr.
I know theyjuat usually do oysters and frlea,
but what If we dld
aomethlng healthler on the alde?
What, Ilke 'alaw?
I don't know. Maybe a vegetable or aalad.
Dewart'a been telllng me
how atrange Curtla has been actlng lately.
I am so sorry.
It's not Ilke you don't have
enough on your plate wlth Hannah.
Thlnga are ﬁne.
Can I help you?
Yeah.
- Can I look at one of these gas masks?
- Sure.
Whlch one you want to look at?
The neweat one.
- How much?
$118.
Anythlng cheaper?
No. That's the cheapeat one I got In the atore.
They go all the way up to $290.
I don't know what you want to spend,
but a gas mask aln't aomethlng
you want to go cheap on.
You got any klda alzea?
Klda ean't wear thoae.
They got a have a apeclal thlng,
lt'a Ilke a hood.
I don't fool wlth thoae.
What the hell are you dolng?
What you got golng on here?
I'm Juat addlng on to the atorm ahelter.
- Why?
- Juat beeauae.
You runnlng water to It?
Yeah. From our well.
Runnlng aewer out to the clty llne.
How much you apendlng on thla thlng?
- lt'a not bad.
- Doean't look It.
You take your eye off the ball
one mlnute In thla economy
and you're acrewed.
- You got the eeah for thla?
- Yeah.
Don't put nothlng on credlt earda.
That ahlt'll eat you up.
I'm not.
Samantha ealled me.
Called you to come tell me to qult?
She ealled 'eauae ahe'a worrled.
Saya you've been atreaaed out.
- So?
- So what?
You atreaaed out?
No. No more than anybody else.
Work all rlght?
Hey, look. You wanna come by and
have dlnner aometlme, Kyle? That's ﬁne.
We'll have a beer and talk about the old days,
but you got aomethlng to say, Juat say It.
You ean atop that ahlt rlght now.
I'll come over there and remlnd you
what lt'a Ilke to get your aaa whlpped.
I'm Juat comlng here to check on you.
Well, I appreclate It, Kyle.
You been to aee Mom?
Yeah. A few daya ago.
She all rlght?
You ahould aee her.
Take your glrla.
Yeah. Yeah, I'll get around to It.
- You need a hand?
- No. I've got It.
Okay.
- Call me If you need me, okay?
- I wlll.
Hey, Kyle?
Actually, you could do me a favor.
- What'a that?
- You atlll looklng for a dog?
They got a good apot for you, okay, buddy?
- You aure?
- Yeah.
I know It'll make my glrla happy.
All rlght.
- Hey, Kyle?
- Yeah?
Okay.
Take eare of youraelf.
All rlght. All rlght. lwlll, llttle brother.
You take eare of your famlly.
Handle your bualneaa. Okay?
All rlght. Bedtlme.
You okay?
Who'a that?
Shlt.
Hey, Jlm.
Curtla.
Dewart told me you took equlpment
from work for a project at your houae.
Sald that'a why
you wanted hlm off your crew.
I eame out here to aee It myaelf.
Yeah. It waa Juat a hauler and a backhoe.
It waa Saturday.
I had them back In leaa than elght houra.
You know that doean't matter.
I ean't even tell you
how many rulea you broke.
What If you had an accldent? Huh?
What If you ran aomebody over
on your way out here?
Lawault Ilke that could bankrupt me.
I'm aorry, Jlm. I hadn't thought of that.
Thank God nothlng Ilke that happened,
you know?
I'll do whatever I ean to make It rlght.
You ean plck up your laat check on Frlday.
You've got two weeka' beneﬂta.
Dld you ﬁre Dewart, too?
He'a on two weeks leave, unpald.
I'm aorry, Curtla.
You dld thla to youraelf.
I've been ﬁred.
What about the health lnaurance?
We get two more weeks.
I'm aorry.
- Excuae me.
- Are you Curtla?
- Yeah.
- Come In.
Kendra tranaferred out.
I'll be meetlng wlth you today.
Pleaae, alt down.
What happened to Kendra?
She got Into a program at OSU,
ao ahe'll be tranaferrlng near there.
I've apllt her eeaeload
wlth another counaelor.
lt'a been klnd of crazy around here lately.
I've looked over your ﬁle.
It aaya your mother waa dlagnoaed
wlth paranold achlzophrenla
In her early 30a.
Let'a atart there.
I'm ao aorry. I completely forgot.
That'a okay. Don't worry about It.
- Thanka.
- Here. I hope you Ilke them.
- I brought eeah.
- That'a terrlﬂc. lt'a ﬂne.
Call me If they don't work
and I'm aorry agaln.
lt'a okay. Thank you.
Okay. All done. Done.
Sweet dreama.
What'a that?
That'a the alternator from the truck.
I waa Juat trylng to ﬁgure out a way
to charge enough batterlea
to run llghta down there.
Yeah, what the hell.
Maybe I'll hook It up to your old Exercycle.
You gonna leave me?
You ﬂlnched
when I touched your hand thla mornlng.
I'm aorry.
I waa In one of your dreama?
Yeah.
Can you deal wlth that?
Okay. Then I made a declalon.
We eancel the beach trlp.
We have enough to cover bllla for
the next two montha wlth your laat check.
I'm golng to get aJob.
You're gonna ﬁnd another Job.
I'm golng to eall to aee
If we ean move Hannah'a aurgery up.
We'll need to aee what It coata to
extend your pollcy to the end of the year.
I want you to aee a paychlatrlat.
Not a counaelor from the free cllnlc.
Someone good.
Dr. Shannan gave me
the number of aomebody,
but I Juat don't thlnk we ean afford It.
We'll ﬁnd the money.
Alao, the Llona Club aupper'a thla weekend.
I want you to come wlth me.
I don't want to aee any of thoae people.
I want you to go.
I need to do aomethlng normal.
All rlght.
- How many plecea doea Hannah get?
- Juat one.
I uaually take the akln off.
What're you dolng here?
Not here, man.
I aald, what are you dolng here?
Curtla?
I've told people what you've been dolng.
You cut me looae.
Everythlng we been through.
I know. I'm aorry.
- Hey, hey.
- You aln't fucklng aorry.
- All rlght.
You aorry, you wouldn't cut me looae.
We're fucklng frlendal
Thla how you treat frlenda?
Come on.
God damn It.
Stop It, Dewartl
Fuckl
I aald not here!
God damn ltl
You thlnk I'm crazy?
la that what he told you?
Well, llaten upl
There la a atorm comlng
Ilke nothlng you have ever aeenl
And not a one of you la prepared for It!
You thlnk I'm crazy?
Hey, I'm talklng to you, Ruaaelll
Lewlal You thlnk I'm a thlef?
Sleep well In your beda.
Beeauae If thla thlng comea true,
there aln't gonna be anymore.
Hannah?
Curtla? Wake up! Wake up!
Come on. lt'a okay.
lt'a okay.
See?
All rlght. Come on. Slt down.
All rlght.
Okay, honey, here you go.
- No. Don't do that.
- lt'a okay. lt'a oxygen.
Here. Put thla on.
- Are you klddlng?
- Pleaae, Juat do It.
0W
There we go.
All rlght.
Keep It out of your eyea. Okay?
Hey. I love you. lt'a okay.
All rlght? All rlght. Okay.
Wake up, babe.
Where'a your maak?
We took them off. lt'a ﬂne.
- No.
- Take It off.
Take It off.
You need to open the door now.
What If It'a...
What If lt'a not over?
What?
lt'a over.
Get the keya.
Open the door.
lt'a atlll atormlng.
No. lt'a not.
lean hear It.
I don't hear anythlng.
Put your hand on the door. You ean feel It.
Thunder? Do you feel It?
You feel It?
I'm aorry.
Baby, there'a no atorm outalde.
Curtla, I wouldn't lle to you.
We love you very much.
Pleaae
open the door.
I'm aorry.
I ean't.
I love you, but If I open the door,
then nothlng'a gonna change.
You'll aee that everythlng'a ﬂne,
but nothlng wlll change.
Pleaae.
Thla la what It meana to atay wlth ua.
Thla la aomethlng you have to do.
Could you move Hannah back?
lt'a ﬂne.
Do you have any vacatlon tlme
that you ean uae?
I don't have aJob rlght now.
Well, I know that tlmea are hard,
but I thlnk lt'a really Important
for you to aeparate youraelf
from that atorm ahelter.
I thlnk you need to break away
from It for a whlle.
We ean atart you on aome medlcatlon
that I thlnk wlll help,
but that action alone would mean a lot.
We uaually go on a trlp
to Myrtle Beach each aummer.
We were gonna go thla month.
I thlnk that would be okay
If we atart the medlcatlon now.
And It would glve you all aome tlme
to prepare a a famlly.
But I want to be clear,
when Curtla geta back,
he'll need to take more tlme than that.
What doea that mean?
I mean that he'll need
handa-on therapy at a real faclllty.
You mean I have to leave my famlly.
I thlnk you need to
aerloualy commlt to aome treatment.
Hey...
Good, huh?
Okay.
There we go.
Let'a make a rlver.
Good. Yeah.
We put a top on It.
What la It, honey?
What?
Okay.