When you go to the ball ...
you have to learn how to dance
like a princess, right?
1, 2, 3 ...
- 1, 2, 3 ...
- Yeah!
What are you gonna wear today?
- I'm gonna wear ...
- You're gonna wear ...
- A bucket on your head.
- No!
- 1, 2, 3 ... No?
- And a barrel round your bottom.
- No!
- And cloth bags for shoes?
- Nooo!
1, 2, 3 ...
Good morning.
Hey buddy!
Want something to eat?
No. I'm not hungry.
Yeah, that's fine.
Yeah.
Franklin?
Hey. It's me. I just
wanted to leave a message.
Do you think we could make
some time to talk later
just the two of us without kids?
I really wanna work this thing out.
Okay?
I miss you.
Eva Khatchadourian!
It's a lot.
Look, Eva.
I don't really care who you are
or what you've done as long as
you can type and you can file.
You can have this job.
Oh, that's wonderful.
Thank you.
I wont let you down.
I promise you. Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Sure.
See you Monday.
Great. Thank you.
Looks like someone is having
a nice day?
Enjoying yourself?
I'm sorry?
I hope you rot in hell, you
fucking bitch!
Jesus. What the hell was that?
Are you ok?
No, no, no, it's nothing.
Its really... its nothing.
- Let me call an ambulance.
- No, no, it was my fault.
- But she just ...
- No, no, I'm fine.
Eva, when are you coming home?
I missed you.
I love you.
Promise me you'll never
go away again.
I will never, never,
never go away again.
Promise me. Promise me
you'll never go away again.
Is it safe?
No, it's not safe.
Sure?
Are you sure about this?
This really happened?
I can see, I can feel it ...
We did it.
I'm gonna need these processed
today, Eva.
Uh, but today my afternoon off.
You remember? I told you.
Ah shit, that's right.
- Look, give these to Massughi.
- Sure.
- Hi Eva.
- Hey, Al.
No, let go of me!
Let go of me, man!
- Get off me!
- Keep walking.
Hey lady. Lady. Lady. Please help me!
I didn't do nothing, man!
Get off of me!
Eva, you can stop holding back.
Stop holding back, Eva.
Eva!
Rise and shine.
It's late, Eva.
The day is almost over.
- Hiii! - Don't pick him up.
Please don't pick him up.
I just put him down, Franklin.
Hi.
There he is. You wanna play?
You wanna play?
It's alright.
Just rock him a little bit.
He's alright.
Do you think I'm exaggerating?
You just have to rock him a
little bit.
There's my little dude!
Jesus! All 12?
- I'll take them as they are.
- But they are totally broken ...
I will take them as they are!
You're gonna be a good looking boy.
All the girls are gonna love you.
I know it. Don't wake up.
Don't wake up.
Can you say "mommy"?
"mom-my", "mommy", Kevin?
Can you say "ball"? "ball"?
"ba-", "ba-", "ba-".
"Ball"?
No?
Okay.
I'm gonna throw it to you, and you're
gonna roll it back to me, okay?
Okay.
Roll it back to mommy.
Roll it back. Roll.
Roll it back.
Okay, okay.
Roll it back, okay?
Roll it back.
When he was a baby,
he never stopped screaming.
I thought maybe it had damaged
his hearing.
No, his hearing is fine.
But shouldn't he be talking by now?
I read somewhere that non-verbalizing
was the...
an early sign of autism.
He has none of the tell-tale rocking signs.
I wouldn't worry about it too much.
He's a fluffy little boy, isn't he?
But there is nothing wrong with him.
Thank you.
Okay.
Roll it back to mom.
Okay. Gonna roll it back again.
That was really good, Kevin.
Okay. Here we go.
Okay?
"E" is for elephant,
large as a house,
he's big as can be,
not small as a mouse.
Can you say "Elephant, Kevin?
"Elephant"?
"Elephant".
Kevin!
Kevin?
Can you say "mommy" for me?
No!
- "mommy"?
- No!
- Just say "mommy".
- No.
Trick or treat?
Hey lady. We know you're in there.
I don't like that!
Mommy was happy before little Kevin
came along. Do you know that?
And now mommy wakes up every morning...
and wishes she was in France!
That elevator is a death trap.
He needs a yard,
somewhere he can toss a ball,
fill a pool.
But I love New York.
Come on!
You sound like a bumper sticker.
It's a matter of priorities, Eva.
He's only gonna be a kid once.
You can house hunt all you want.
I'm telling you, I'm not leaving the city.
Kevin, stop that. That's enough.
Let mommy and daddy talk.
Kevin, quit that!
You have your family room here.
Master bedroom is back there
and two huge walking closets.
The bathroom is amazing.
Here we are guys.
Our very own castle.
I'm gonna go and grab some lunch.
Does anybody want anything?
Hey! Hey!
Wait up! Ms. K!
Hey. It's me.
Soweto.
Hi there.
I just wanted to see how you were.
I'm fine. Thanks.
You look well.
Yeah. The doctors are saying there's
a chance I might walk again.
That's great.
You take care, ms. K.
You too.
Come on, come on!
Die! Die!
No! No! No!
- Die!
- How do you jump?
Die!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Hey Kev? Are you out there?
Kevin?
Kevin, you hear that?
Dad goes pee pee.
You can do that too.
So you want a connector right there.
You see? And click on that link
and it should open right up.
And If it doesn't ...
we'll try it again.
- So you left click. Wanna give it a try?
- Yes.
- No, no.
- I'm sorry.
- Right click, right there.
- Yeah.
See that? It comes up.
Right. Yeah, thanks.
I think I got it.
Thank you for your help.
I pooped.
Hey buddy. What?
You pooped?
Oh okay. Here let me help you.
Okay.
Go to your room. I'll be right there.
Let's not wake up mommy.
Go on! Go on, buddy.
These scribled squares of paper. They are dumb.
Everybody needs a room of their own.
You have your room.
This is the mother's room.
I can help you make your room special,
if you'd like.
What do you mean, "Special"?
Well, so it looks like your personality.
What personality?
I think you know what I mean.
They're dumb.
No, no, no. I mean it's good.
You don't need me to do that?
And... and the guy...
Okay.
Well, I mean if you handle the lot ...
I could.
Really?
Well. That all sounds great.
Okay, John.
Okay. I'll talk to you later.
Goodbye.
Kevin?
What else do you have to say?
Go wash your face!
He said, he's really sorry.
And that he was only trying to help
make it special.
Do you remember how you got that?
It's the most honest thing
you ever did.
Do you know how they potty train cats?
They stick their noses in their own shit.
They don't like it.
So they use the box.
Okay. Let's work on our counting.
- What comes after 3?
- 9.
- What comes after 7?
- 71.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5,
6, 7, 8, 9, 10,
11, 12, 13, 14, 15,
16, 17, 18, 19, 20,
21, 22, 23, 24, 25,
26, 27, 28, 29, 30,
31, 32, 33, 34, 35,
36, 37, 38, 39, 40,
41, 42, 43, 44, 45,
46, 47, 48, 49, 50.
Now, can we quit?
There.
You can add that together
if you think you're so smart.
You did not ...
Are you enjoying yourself?
I can see the doctor by myself.
I have to tell you something, Eva.
It's a brave boy you've got there.
- Thank you.
- That's fine.
What mamma did
was very, very wrong.
And she's so, so sorry.
Kev? Kev, hold on a sec!
Kev?
Kevin?
Hey Kev.
What happened?
I broke my arm.
How did you brake your arm?
I had poopy pants.
Mommy went to get wipes.
I fell off the changing table
onto my dump trucks.
Mom took me to doctor Goldbutt.
It's all my fault.
No, don't be silly.
You can't watch him
every second of the day.
Franklin ...
Unbelievable.
How did you get him
to do that?
Well, whatever it was it worked.
Not yet.
Okay.
I love you, kiddo.
I don't like that.
Turn it off.
Honey. Do you mind if we stop
over at the store?
I wanna go home.
It's just that I need to pick up...
Home it is.
Hi guys!
Hi Dad. How was work?
Did you take any cool pictures?
Eva, he is just a boy.
He's a sweet little boy.
That's what boys do.
Mom is fat!