Is today the day?
I don't know.
Maybe.
What's your gut tell you?
That I'm nauseous.
How about less literally?
I'm afraid of deciding.
I'm not afraid
of either scenario,
but I just want this
to be something we're doing,
not something we're not doing.
What does "this" mean?
"This" meaning
whatever we decide.
Well, "this" sounded like
some kind of decision.
No.
It wasn't.
What are we gonna do today?
Brooklyn or Manhattan?
That's not
what we were talking about.
I know what we're
talking about.
What do you want to do?
Hey.
What?
Why not?
We can't do that.
Hey.
Hi.
Hello.
So I thought it would be a
good idea to get my mom flowers,
so we'll stop at a florist
on the way.
She'll like that.
Yes, she will.
Can I take credit?
It was my plan.
Dim sum.
Is it cool we're not seeing
your family for the barbecue?
Yeah. It's great.
I needed the excuse.
I can't be around them today.
And I'm the perfect excuse.
No, I wasn't trying
to make you--
No, it's all right,
'cause your mom adores me
so much anyway.
Hold on, there's a seat belt
in my ass.
What is this?
Did you get a new phone?
No.
My God, this is, like,
the 2010 version.
Someone is hating life
right now.
Let's just give it
to the cabbie.
No, no, wait,
don't give it to him.
Don't give it to him.
Come on, let it.
No, no, no.
Why?
He won't give it back;
he'll just sell it.
Don't you remember
I lost my phone just, like,
a month ago in a cab,
and I never got it back.
If you give it to
the cab company then they'll--
they'll call the people that--
No, they won't.
They won't.
So what are you, like,
a Canadian Mountie?
Gonna save the phone?
Why you got to make it
about Canada?
I'm gonna get it back
to whosever this is.
Hi, my name
is Bobby Thompson.
I just found this phone
in the back of a cab,
and I'm trying to get it back
to its rightful owner.
My number is 917-817--
Why are you giving them
your number?
What?
Sorry. My number
is 917-817-65--
And, we'll try to figure this out.
Okay, thanks.
What?
Why would you be calling,
leaving your name and number
when the person
who lost this phone
is just gonna call
their phone number
and expect somebody
to answer it?
You don't have to go through
their roster
of friends and family.
Just don't--
Hi, my name
is Bobby Thompson.
Don't leave your name.
Why not?
Excuse me, I'm sorry.
It's yours.
It's not in my purse.
Probably your mom.
Don't answer it.
Yeah, it's your mom.
Hi, Sylvia.
Keep the change.
Hey, thank you.
Thanks for not taking
The Bowery.
Hey, I got a call
on this thing.
Bobby, careful.
Hello?
It's Perez, you assfuck.
We had a deal for that phone,
didn't we, Dmitri?
I think you got the wrong guy.
I've had it with this bullshit.
I just picked up this phone.
Who was it?
Was it the guy?
I don't know.
I'm going inside.
Go ahead, go.
Hello?
I'm so glad
that you picked up.
I think you found my phone.
My name is Dmitri.
Yeah, I found your phone
in the back of a cab.
Hi.
2 please.
Be about 10 minutes.
Man, I'm glad you called.
I've been calling around.
I left a few messages.
What are you talking about?
Who did you call?
I don't know,
but some guy just called back.
He said his name was Perez.
Perez?
Okay, look, I need to come
get phone right now.
Don't call anyone else.
Where you are?
What is address?
The address?
Address!
It's...
it's 40 East Broadway.
Okay, I'm getting in the taxi
right now.
I'm wearing a red jacket,
okay?
Red jacket.
Red jacket, okay?
How will I know who you are?
I... I'm wearing
a yellow T-shirt.
Hey... how come your mom
thought we might not be coming?
When did you talk to my mom?
The phone just now.
I told you not to answer
that call.
You didn't know
it was your mother.
If I ask you
not to answer my phone,
you shouldn't answer it.
You can't just not answer
the phone.
That is not my rule.
Wasn't that the turn?
Shit.
You got me flustered!
Sorry.
My God.
Is that a stray?
She's gonna get hit like that.
Do you see anyone
she belongs to?
She came from over there.
Come here.
Careful.
Come here, girl.
She's nice.
She's gentle.
Where's she coming from?
I don't know.
Where are you going?
She just licked my hand.
Where are you going, doggie?
Here, she's got a tag.
"Tiger."
Maybe we shouldn't go
to Fitz's party.
No?
I'm gonna want a margarita.
I thought you could have one
now and then.
Yeah, maybe.
Maybe not.
You're kidding.
I'll be right back.
And I'll wait in line.
Hello?
Hello, my name is Dmitri.
I think you found my phone.
I must have left it
in the taxi this morning.
Okay.
Where are you?
I'd like to come get it.
You know, someone else
named Dmitri just called
and said it was his phone.
I don't know
who you talked to,
but that's my phone,
and I need to get it back.
Can you bring it to me?
No.
What do you want?
I'll pay you.
You hear me?
Where are you?
No, man, I'm here
at a restaurant in Chinatown
with my girlfriend.
Where are you exactly?
The address here
is 40 East Broadway.
You can come down here
and work it out with
the other guy if you want to.
What? Don't give that phone
to anyone else.
What's going on?
It belongs to me;
it's my phone.
I don't know who you talked to,
but it's mine.
Look, I don't know
what the deal is.
You can work it out with him.
Actually, he's already here.
What?
That's my phone,
do you hear me?
Was that gunfire?
What just happened?
Can you hear me?
Just get out of there.
You're in danger,
do you hear me?
Take the phone
and get out of there.
You're in danger.
Come on!
Do you think he followed us?
No.
It's okay.
He didn't follow us.
You okay?
Bobby, is that man gonna die?
Yeah, he's dead.
It's okay.
It's okay, all right?
Listen.
Listen, look at me.
Look at me, okay?
We're safe here, okay?
We're safe here.
We're safe, okay?
Just breathe.
Now, we should go and ask
where there's a police station.
There's one in Union Square.
The nearest is in Union Square.
There's one--
okay, we'll go there.
Okay.
Don't worry about anything,
okay?
There is a downtown
local train now at Union Square.
Come on, pooch.
Look at this.
You okay? Okay?
We'll go to the police;
we'll tell them what happened.
All right?
I love you.
If this gets weird,
you just tell me.
It's fine.
Trust you and let's see,
we could do this.
Hello.
What took you so long?
Where have you been?
Look what we found.
Hey, Bobby.
Hi, Felix, how are you?
How are you doing?
Good to see you.
Happy July 4th, I guess?
Yeah, happy July 4th.
Hi, papa.
You look relaxed.
Hey, why shouldn't I be?
Why shouldn't you be?
I know.
He's sleeping.
Tip-toe.
Hi, mami.
I miss you.
Look at how thin you are.
I know, you always say that.
Hi, Sylvia.
Hi.
Hi, Bobby.
Those are for me?
For you.
Thank you.
My pleasure.
They're beautiful.
That was your idea?
Yeah.
I knew it.
Very nice, thank you.
I'll put them in a vase.
Who is she?
This is--
We just... just picked her up.
She was trying to cross
Jamaica Boulevard.
We were afraid
she might get hit,
so we picked her up.
But, you know,
is she vaccinated or something?
I mean, it can be a danger, no,
for the children?
Mom, I wouldn't have brought
her here
if I thought she was a danger.
I don't know.
If you want, you know--
Look at all your meat.
Look at all of it.
Well, I-I have your salmon
and your salmon.
Thank you.
Hello, hello!
Emily!
I thought I heard
a Broadway star in the house.
Hi, Emily.
How are you?
Good. How are you?
Good to see you.
You look great.
Thank you, so do you.
Hello, Mr. Bobby.
How are you?
I'm good. How are you?
Good to see you.
Who do we have here?
This is our new friend.
Yeah?
Yeah.
You got a dog.
Yeah, they found it
in the street.
You know, actually,
maybe it would be a good idea
if you run upstairs and use
the computer in Hector's room
and make some "dog found" signs.
Yeah, good idea.
"Dog found" signs.
The computer is broken,
but perhaps you might fix it?
Yeah, I'll take a look at it.
Thank you.
Okay, sure, of course.
By the way,
how is your father?
My father?
He's well.
Yeah?
Thank you.
Yeah, he's living
with his brother in Calgary.
Calgary.
I'd like to see a picture.
Perhaps,
next time you're coming,
you can bring one?
Okay, I'll try to--
I'll--I'll find a picture.
Thank you.
Okay.
How nice, Calgary.
Mami, why would you ask him
for a picture of his father?
Well, I'd like to see
a picture of his father.
Do you--do you know him?
Why is Uncle Diego
all alone out there?
Sorry?
I'm going outside, Mom.
Hey, Katalina.
Tio.
Hey.
Katalina.
Como estas?
So how are you?
I'm okay.
Yeah?
Yeah.
How are you?
I'm doing okay.
Yeah?
I'm fine.
You're not so bad?
How's your dancing?
It's so good.
Yeah?
Yeah, I'm in a show.
In a show?
Yeah, on Broadway.
On Broadway?
Yeah.
Can I come and see it?
You already came to see me.
You've seen it.
I'm going crazy.
Yeah, I came to see you.
Get her! Get her!
Come back, Tiger! Come on!
It's a dog.
What is that dog doing?
Bobby and I found her
crossing the street.
It's him.
Hello?
Tell me what just happened.
Talk to me.
I just watched a guy get shot
is what happened.
I need to get that phone.
It belongs to me,
and I need to get it back.
I'm taking the phone
to the police.
Don't do that;
listen to me.
Tell me where you are.
I can be there quickly,
but don't...
I said we're taking it
to the police,
and if you want it,
you can get it from them.
I'm done with this.
What is with this phone?
We should have just given it
to the cab driver.
So this is my fault?
We're gonna do that right now?
No, that's not
what I'm saying.
Don't answer it.
I didn't.
That's your phone.
Fuck.
He has my number?
Bobby, please don't answer it.
Don't answer it.
I'm not asking you
for the phone, Bobby.
I'm telling you.
How'd you get this number?
You're not listening to me,
Bobby.
That phone belongs to me,
and I'm getting sick
and fucking tired
of asking you for it.
Get off.
We're gonna run, okay?
Go! Come on!
Come on!
Shit.
Come on, you okay?
Wait.
Damn it!
Slide it again.
Come on!
It's him.
Watch out.
Excuse me!
Come on!
Fuck!
Okay, there.
Train on the other side.
Come on! Come on!
What the fuck just happened?
You okay?
How did he find us
in Union Square?
We were only there
for 2 minutes.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
How did that happen?
I don't know.
He has my cell phone number.
That means he could
have my address.
He has your cell phone
because you left your name
and number on those phones
or the 2 answering machines
or whatever.
You're right.
And we should have just
given it to the cabbie.
Okay, yeah, we should have.
That could have happened,
but it didn't happen.
This happened, okay?
Let's deal in reality.
What's on this fuckin' thing?
What is all that?
Cyrillic.
What's that?
It's the Russian alphabet.
Man, look at all this.
This series of numbers,
this is how computers
talk to each other.
This is--this might be
why they want this.
Bobby, that's you.
My God.
$500,000?
What's on this phone, Bobby?
We need to go to the police.
City Hall?
There's a police station there?
Yeah.
Okay, we're gonna turn
all our phones off, okay?
They must be tracking the thing.
Listen to me, okay?
All right?
That's more like it.
Hi.
Hi, baby girl.
So what are you gonna
tell the police?
I'm just gonna tell them
what happened.
We'll give them the phone.
Hopefully that'll be that.
How can a phone
be worth $500,000?
That's a good question.
I don't know.
Hey.
Here you go.
Let's just put this
through first.
Hi.
We just found this in the back
of a cab a couple hours ago.
Since then, 3 different
people have called us.
What do you need?
We've been followed,
we've been chased.
We think that
there's something--
We witnessed a murder.
You witnessed a murder?
Yes.
All right, listen, you're
gonna need to speak to--
Hey, you're gonna need to speak
to Sergeant Hill.
Now, he's not here right now,
so what you need to do is sit
down on these benches back here.
When he gets back in,
I'll send him down,
and he'll talk to you, okay?
We just saw someone
get killed.
And we think it has something
to do with this phone.
Yeah, yeah...
lady, I get it.
We saw it.
I get it.
You need to speak
to Sergeant Hill.
Now, when he comes back in,
I'm gonna have him come down
and talk to you.
Go sit down on the benches back
there, okay?
Okay, can we leave this
with you?
No.
But it's not ours.
Well, it's not mine either,
honey.
Take your phone
and sit down on the bench.
Don't call her honey, please.
Easy--
Take your phone, sit down,
relax.
Yeah, how long you think
it'll be?
When the sergeant comes in,
he'll be back and talk to you.
How long do you think
it'll be, please?
I don't know.
Thank you.
Very helpful.
Thanks.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Okay, now we put this here.
Ta-da!
Okay.
Hey, it's going.
I'm gonna do this side here.
Daddy woke up.
How you like that?
What are you doing,
little raccoon?
So, how is Bobby doing?
Bobby's doing good.
How's his job?
His job is fine.
How are you?
How are the both of you?
We're doing good, Mom.
Good.
Kate, how's the show going?
You said it might close?
Yeah, it's gonna close
in 3 months.
No, you're so good
in the show.
Thank you.
Are you bummed
that it's closing?
Are you okay?
What are you gonna do?
You know what you should do
is to call Peter.
Yeah?
Would you like me to call Peter?
I mean, he could help you.
Who's Peter?
Peter is this producer
that she's been trying
to set me up with.
She keeps saying that he's tall,
dark, and handsome, and he's...
Really?
Well, yes, he's handsome,
but I'm not trying
to set you up with.
I mean, I like Bobby.
Really, I do.
Sylvia, you're almost
out of olive oil.
Yeah, well,
I'll get some later.
Let's chop that...
Okay.
Quickly.
Yup.
I need it.
Yup, yup, yup.
Do you think we can use
these computers?
I don't know.
I'm gonna go ask.
Excuse me.
Hi.
Are these computers
for public use?
Yeah, go ahead.
Knock yourself out.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
Looking up this guy Perez.
The baseball player?
"Lottery deputy director George
Perez was charged with 3--"
Lottery deputy director?
"The indictment is certain
to be merely the first move
by a grand jury."
I mean, there could be a lot
of different George Perezes.
Do you think this is him?
I don't know.
It could be him.
It sounds like him.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
"Whether Perez is under
investigation for arson
in the fire that destroyed
a lottery building."
Right? Doesn't that sound
like the guy?
A guy who'd pay half a million
dollars for a phone,
works for the lottery
commission, stealing money.
So, wait, you think
that's what's on the phone?
Whatever information
is on the phone
that's in my pocket right now
is probably being used to--
And you think it's this?
We have to get rid
of this fuckin' thing.
Bobby?
I mean, I don't know
if this is him.
Bobby?
There could be a lot
of different George Perezes.
What?
Come on.
What if--
What?
What if we sell the Treo?
$500,000 is a lot of money.
You're not kidding?
No.
What the fuck's Dmitri
gonna do to us
if we give it to Perez?
Dmitri is the guy
who has my number,
that probably has my address
and knows where I live,
that found us in Union Square,
sent somebody after us.
You--
No.
You could only sell it
to Dmitri.
But he hasn't asked to buy it.
He would.
He definitely would.
But how would we contact him?
You'd have to turn on the phone,
and then they could track us.
Yeah, so you'd have to
talk to him.
You could talk to him
through e-mail.
You set up an e-mail account.
You get him the new address.
But then you'd have to call
him to give him the e-mail,
and he could still
track us.
That's true, we would have to
turn on the phone
for, like, a second.
Turn it on,
get him the address,
and turn it right back off.
So how would they
not track us?
Well, you could do it
while we were moving.
You know, we get on a bus,
send him a text,
turn it on, turn it off.
We take it one step at a time.
We can come back here
whenever we want to.
Okay.
$500,000...
Is a lot of money.
Yeah.
Over here.
One more.
How's it going?
That's so cute.
This one...
or this one?
That one.
That one?
Okay, that's it.
Sweet dog.
Yes, you are.
Who do you belong to?
Do I remind you of my mother?
Is that a trick question?
What, you think I-I--
you--I do?
I don't know,
I don't know how to answer that.
I was raised by a single dad.
'Cause, you know, she just...
grilled me down there.
It was so intrusive,
and it made me not want
to be here, so, that's--
What did she ask?
She's asking a lot
about your job, and--
and then she was asking me,
am I happy?
I think she asked me, like,
if I was happy,
if you and I were happy,
and it made me so uncomfortable,
considering what's going on.
Well, she's your mother.
She should want to know
if you're happy, right?
I mean, I don't know.
Look at her.
This goes here.
She's so cute.
It's a good flyer, right?
Hi, I'd like to use
the internet, please.
I need your credit card
for a deposit.
Here you go.
And can I have
some of those crackers?
This'll just take a minute.
Then we'll find a bus.
Don't use your real name.
Yeah.
What's your password?
You gonna tell me what it is?
It's "I love Treos."
Now...
we have an e-mail address.
Get it, come on!
Tiger! Tiger!
You ready?
All right.
"We have an offer
for the phone.
$500,000."
Wait, 5.
Yeah.
$500,000.
"Will you match? "
Yeah.
"Contact us via e-mail
at anonymous123@gmail.com."
Okay, is that it?
Yes.
Okay, send.
Okay, turning it off.
Put it away.
It's off.
Bobby, what are we gonna do
if he actually says yes?
Well, I mean, I guess we'll
meet him somewhere, and he'll--
What do you mean you guess
we'll meet him somewhere?
I don't know, I mean,
we didn't talk about it.
Fuck, Bobby.
This isn't all me.
This isn't--
Okay, so, please,
a small bottle, nothing fancy.
Okay.
Just Bertolli
or something like that.
May I buy the olive oil,
please?
No, thanks.
It's--it's on me.
It would really be
my pleasure.
No, no, I insist.
I can't. I can't. I can't.
Mom, let him buy
the olive oil.
No, it's my bottle
of olive oil, okay?
That's okay, thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
I tried.
Buenos dias.
Hey, Diego.
How are you?
Hi.
Good to see you.
It's Bobby.
Hi, Bobby.
Hi.
Sylvia, can you make me
some breakfast?
That okay?
It's lunchtime.
It's okay,
he doesn't remember you.
he barely remembers me.
Okay.
Katie!
In here.
Where's that mutt you found?
Here she is.
Let's see if this works.
There we go.
Bobby can keep his belt.
Nicely done.
Thank you.
Yeah.
All right, take her outside
before she goes all over
the kitchen floor, all right?
Mom, I'm gonna check on
the kids, okay?
Wash your hands.
We're leaving too.
Don't take too long.
We're just gonna put up
the signs.
See you.
Don't be too late.
See you later.
Have fun.
Hey, tio Dio, you want to play?
No, no, I'm waiting
for something to eat.
Which way should we go?
Let's go this way.
Sit.
Good dog.
My God!
Did you see that?
Bye, papi.
We'll be back soon.
All right, see you later.
I can't believe
what idiots we are.
How could we not
think it through?
Okay, let's just say
that he agrees.
He says, "Okay, I'll pay."
He's gonna want to meet us
face-to-face.
He's not just gonna give us
any money
without getting the phone
right away.
But you can't trust a guy
like that.
If we meet him face-to-face,
you don't know
what he's gonna do.
He could kill us.
It's kind of ironic,
plotting criminal activity
with all these guards
and cameras and security around.
That would do it,
though, right?
Guards and cameras would do it.
If we were somewhere
with a bunch of security,
what could he do?
If we were standing right there,
he couldn't do anything.
What, at the UN?
We can't do it there.
Okay, well, we find somewhere.
Like an airport.
Or even a bank.
Right?
We say, "Meet us at this bank
at this time.
We bring the phone;
you bring us money."
Yeah, we're safe
when we're inside the bank,
but what happens when we leave?
We have the money;
he has the phone.
He could just--
You're right,
he could just follow us.
He could have a gun.
He will definitely have a gun.
It's hot.
She must be hotter
than we are.
Hey, not as hot as you.
I don't feel very hot.
Why not?
That's my ringer.
Yeah, sorry,
I still have it in my pocket.
It's your mom.
Thank you, Bobby.
Hi, mami.
Okay, we'll be back soon.
Bye, mama.
Bye. Bye.
What if the money stays?
We leave it there.
It's a bank.
We can't open a checking
account with $500,000.
But we could open
a safety deposit box.
Leave it
in the safety deposit box?
Yeah, we could leave it there,
and then when we leave the bank,
we don't have anything.
There's nothing
he can take from us.
Makes sense, right?
Yeah, makes sense.
I think I know a good bank
to do it in.
You okay?
You didn't say anything
to anybody, did you?
I thought we're not
saying anything.
'Cause Emily, she kept staring
at my boobs and my stomach.
That's 'cause you got
nice boobs and a nice stomach.
That's not what I mean.
You're not showing.
Nobody can tell.
I can't tell.
I-I just feel like I'm lying
to everybody who loves me,
and it feels wrong.
I can see that.
I mean, it is kind of sneaky,
I guess, the way we're--
Are you calling me sneaky?
No, us.
We're--we're--
Even if we knew
what we were doing,
we might not, you know,
talk about it to other people.
I just think we should have come
to some sort of decision by now,
because the longer we wait,
it's just gonna get harder
and harder.
Yeah, I think we should
just talk some more,
and keep talking about it
forever,
and talk and talk,
and then we will have talked,
and that'll be really good.
Is that what's known
as a pregnant pause?
You're so funny.
Well, I write music,
not lyrics.
Katie?
How you doing?
Hi, Danny.
I'll get the oil.
How you doing?
Good, where you been?
I moved to Fort Greene.
Fort Greene, very nice.
Excuse me, can I have
an instant lotto millionaire?
I should ask you
about this dog.
We found her
at this intersection today.
She was crossing it by herself.
I mean, she seems to be
pretty well trained,
so she must belong to somebody.
Have you seen her around here?
No.
No, sorry.
Is this okay?
Yeah.
Hey, I'm Bobby.
Hey, Bobby, how you doing?
I'm Danny.
Nice to meet you.
This is it.
This is the one
I was telling you about.
Look, it says "safe deposit box"
right there.
It's good, 'cause it's glass
on all sides.
These doors are glass.
We can see anyone coming
from any direction.
There's a camera right there.
God, there's 3 back there.
There's another one.
I think this is gonna work.
Let's go check e-mail.
Where is everybody?
Well, he's out there.
Meet me all by break of day.
If we shadows have offended,
think but this
and all is mended,
that you have but slumbered here
while these visions did appear,
and this weak and idle theme,
no more yielding but a dream.
Gentles, do not reprehend.
If you pardon, we will mend.
And, as I am an honest Puck,
if we have unearned luck,
now to 'scape
the serpent's tongue,
we will make amends ere long.
Else the Puck a liar call...
And so good night unto you all.
Give me your hands,
if we be friends,
and Robin shall restore amends.
My God, hi!
My God!
How long have you been
standing in the corner?
See you downstairs, guys.
So guess what?
My drama teacher knows this
agent who was in the audience,
and he was there watching,
and he's, like, referring me
to his associate in L.A.,
so, like, so I'm gonna have
an agent when I go to L.A.
Anyway, this is my friend Beth.
Beth! Hi.
It's great to finally
meet you.
I've heard so much about you.
This is Bobby.
Bobby, Beth.
Great to meet you.
Are you excited for fireworks?
Yeah.
Very.
How was your trip out?
Hi.
Number 13.
Thanks.
Let's do this quickly, Bobby.
Do you remember the password?
Yeah.
Fuck.
Hey, we got an e-mail.
My God, Bobby.
What?
We have to get out of here.
The men in the SUV
are downstairs.
Is there another way
out of here?
Washroom, something?
Come on.
Can you break it?
We shouldn't.
They'll know where we are.
Okay, come on.
Hold this.
All right?
Okay, let's go.
How the fuck did they find us?
I don't know.
You can't trace
an e-mail account that fast.
It was probably the credit card.
Paid for the internet
with my credit card.
So, Bobby, you like it here
in New York?
Yeah.
Yeah, I like New York.
It's a nice town.
You think you'll stay here?
That's a good question.
What, do you have to get,
like, papers and things?
You do.
They call it a green card.
Hey, viejo,
here's some more.
Bozo, that's great.
All right, is this ready?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was just gonna start that.
Bobby, how do you like
your salmon?
On the rare side, I guess.
You got it.
Thank you.
I'm gonna cut this up,
all right?
That's good.
You don't eat meat?
Nah, I've been...
cutting out the meat of late.
You're a fish guy.
A fish guy?
Yeah, one of those fishitarian
alien men.
Vegaquarian?
Did you have
a bad meat experience or...
It's funny you should
ask in this house.
It kind of started here.
Kate's got a-a thing with food
and--and her mom.
Which makes Bobby
give up the gift of meat.
Yeah.
Pretty much.
Just checking.
I mean, whatever makes it work.
Hey.
How you doing?
I'm nauseous.
Can you go get the ginger pills
out of the car?
I thought so.
How'd I know?
Will you go first?
I'm scared.
I knew that you were gonna
disagree with me,
so I made the decision
on my own.
Really?
Yeah.
Come on, you are so smart,
and, you know, sometimes
you're so confused, you know?
So if you don't get
the scholarship next year--
I'll get
the scholarship again.
That's not gonna be a problem.
And if you don't,
then what?
I think...
I'm gonna get it again.
It almost went over me.
It flew past, a bee.
Well, we don't want to kill
the bee, do we?
Let's try it again.
You're gonna go back
to your studies?
Yes.
I don't think so.
Well, why don't you
just let me
make that decision for myself,
okay?
I'm 18.
I've done really well in school.
I think I've earned the right--
What do you want?
You want to struggle
like your sister?
What struggle
are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
No, what?
No, nothing.
You all have jobs.
You have--
they're all happy.
Here's the ginger.
I'll be outside.
I'll get that.
The Shermans?
Yeah, yeah.
Is this enough filling
for one?
Yes, that's perfect.
Can you tell your father,
please,
that the Shermans are here?
Papi?
Papi.
How you doing?
Look at you.
Darling.
She looks great.
Hello!
Hey!
How you doing?
Hey, Sylvia!
So nice to see you.
You too.
This is my casserole for you.
Okay, thank you very much.
That's for Felix.
What's that?
Go get your son, please.
That's a very nice one.
Jack!
We got 3 now.
We pissed him off.
God.
Okay, so it's his guys
at the internet place.
He's scared.
Doesn't seem scared to me.
He's making threats.
Fuck.
Okay, well,
that's what we wanted.
That's what we talked about.
We're gonna do it?
Okay?
You sure?
Okay, I'm gonna send it.
No, I want to send it.
Okay.
Maybe we should
turn the Treo on.
What, just to fuck with him?
Yeah.
That's a good idea.
I got another message
from Perez.
What does it say?
Nothing.
He just wants to know
why we didn't get back to him.
He doesn't know anything
about us, though, does he?
No, I don't think so.
Okay, I'm turning off the phone.
So now what?
What do we do?
We wait until the morning.
You hungry?
I'm always hungry.
You did good.
Look how much you ate.
I appreciate you
taking care of these.
All right, make a little
space here, please.
Good.
Really good, yeah.
All right, round 2.
Nice.
Mami, there's more down here
if you want any--
you just let me know, okay?
Hey, guys?
This is the time for a toast.
Para arriba.
Para abajo...
Al centro.
Pa 'dentro.
Salud.
I want everyone
to taste my empanadas.
That's what you want.
I'll go for you.
Earl, we will get you
some gardening going here.
I actually own, finally.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Little piece of New York.
That's right.
It's like me in a cubicle
with a phone and a computer,
and that's really it.
Yeah.
You know?
All day long, right?
All day long.
I don't have anybody bringing me
fresh tomatoes like you did,
or my--or my coffee
or something like that.
There was interference there.
Their player
went out of the line,
and he hit the guy in the--
They lost.
Here--here they come!
Can I have one?
Yeah, pass the plate.
These are just vegetarian,
right?
They're beef.
No?
I can't have?
What do you think, everybody?
They're great.
You're my little girl.
I'd love to go to Harvard.
She should.
She just--she just deferred
her scholarship.
They are driving me
absolutely insane, tio.
Do you know what happened?
So it's yours.
It's gonna be ours.
This isn't renting.
There's no more renting.
It's gonna be so much larger.
We've had, like, no time.
I'm working extra shifts,
and we got 2 kids,
she's taking off.
She gives me shit
for not cleaning up the home,
because she wants everything
to be perfect.
My father was there when--
he was stationed in--in New York
when the Giants were here,
and that--that's part of why
I wanted to come here, actually.
Don't you worry about it.
They give me all the credit
for getting the grades.
Relax.
But they don't let me
make my own decisions.
The same happened to Katalina.
Don't worry about it.
Your father used to give
a hard time to Katalina,
and look at her.
She's doing good now.
You should do the same thing.
The same happened with
the music, okay, for Hector.
Hector had the pa--
the passion.
Tio?
Where is he?
Why isn't he here?
Tio, don't you remember?
Hey, Felix.
Felix.
Tio.
Why isn't he here?
Why isn't Hector here?
Where is he?
Diego. Diego.
Hector is not coming.
Remember, I told you that?
He's not coming.
Right?
Yeah, right.
Relax.
Excuse--excuse me.
You don't have to leave
the table, tio.
Do you want me to come inside
with you?
No, sweetheart, that's okay.
Just stay.
Stay.
I had no idea it was this bad.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, he's--
Mami.
I don't know what to say,
but I guess he's also drinking
a little bit.
He'd always sit up here,
right?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
It's a shame, you know,
so young and--
Hey.
You want to come outside
and smoke a cigarette with me?
Mami, you okay?
Okay.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Okay.
You want more sausage, mom?
You want more sausage?
No.
What, did you quit again?
No, I'm just not smoking
right now.
Why?
Because I don't think
I should.
Oh, my God.
Katie.
I know.
My God.
Katie.
I know.
I'm sorry I didn't
tell you sooner.
No, that's okay.
That's okay.
Does Bobby know yet?
Yeah, it's been 11 weeks.
I know.
But it's just that every time
I try to make a decision...
I don't...
make a decision.
I don't know why.
You're really mad about this,
aren't you?
Can't believe
you're eating roast beef.
One sandwich.
It--it will lead to others.
One sandwich does not mean
that I've failed
in my commitment
to fishitarianism.
You know,
I'm not gonna kiss you
till that shit's
out of your system.
How do I know
when it's out of my system?
Hey.
Salud, Bobby.
Salud.
For many more.
Maria, I love you.
My son.
Mami.
Cheers, Bobby.
I love you.
Don't shoot it;
just sip it.
That's good.
We'll take some of this with us.
This Earl knows what he's doing,
let me tell you.
Look who we found eating
ice cream in the kitchen.
Aparecido, muchacho.
Me estaba comiendo
un helado deliciosa.
Mira, mira.
Numero cinco.
The fireworks.
My God.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
we should go to the--hey.
I liked it.
I did.
That's good.
You okay?
Yeah.
Where are we gonna go?
I don't know.
My back hurts.
Those seats were tiny.
Your back hurts?
Yeah.
That's so funny.
Hector would always talk about
seats being too small for him,
so he'd have to sit
in the aisle.
Hector did?
Yeah.
You don't talk about your
brother as much as you used to.
I know.
Bobby, where are we gonna go?
I don't know.
We can't go home, though.
I don't like being
on the streets.
Well, we could go
to Fitz's party.
I told him we were gonna come.
All right, let's go.
Why not?
Come on.
Go like this.
Hey, Bobby, can you do this?
You want a beat?
Do something.
* Te deja un paseo
* Como es estudiante
ya se va Escalona
* Pero de recuerdo
te deja un paseo
* Que te habla
* de aquel inmenso amor
que llevo
* dentro del corazn
* que dice
Sorry, excuse us.
Sorry.
It's so fucking hot.
We got to say hi to Fitz.
Bobby!
Hey.
What's up, man?
How are you?
Thanks for having us.
Absolutely.
I brought Kate.
Kate!
Hi.
I think there's a roof.
Okay.
Yeah.
My God.
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Come on, girls.
Don't get hit by a car!
Tiger on there.
Did you hear that?
Yeah.
Hey, will you slowpokes
hurry up, please?
You know,
I don't talk about my brother
as much as I used to because...
I just don't think about him
as much.
You know, he's been dead
a long time.
It's been 5 years.
My mom thinks about him
every day...
Every minute.
Makes me think like
something's wrong with me.
There's not.
Promise.
Would we be people
with a kid...
or parents?
What's the difference?
Jack?
Come on, girl.
Ay, come on, girl.
Bye, Bobby.
Nice meeting you.
Nice to meet you.
It was really nice
to see you guys.
I'm gonna go say good-bye
to mami.
Felix, thanks again.
Hey, my pleasure.
Hey, had a good time?
Si.
Tranquilo?
Yeah.
I'll--I'll pick you up next week?
Thank you.
And we watch some football.
I asked Bobby if he could
drop off Uncle Diego.
Yeah, he said it's fine.
So here is the pasta,
las empanadas.
Mama.
I want to ask you something.
Could you talk to your sister?
Please, talk to her.
You know, I...
I want to talk to her,
but it's impossible.
I mean, she's not listening.
I mean, I do everything wrong.
She's gonna trust you, you know?
You're assuming
that I agree with you.
You do agree, don't you?
Please, I can't sleep, you know?
It's a big mistake.
I mean, I cannot rely
on your father.
I'll talk to her.
Want to put this in a bag?
Yeah?
We're leaving.
Hey, what?
I thought--I thought that you
were staying over tonight.
No chance in hell.
Okay, well, listen, you have to
call me this week, okay?
I will.
You have to keep me posted.
Call me tomorrow?
Sophie, I think--
What?
You were so wonderful
this afternoon.
Thank you.
I'm so glad you got to see some.
Me too.
Okay, bye.
Bye.
Love you.
Call me tomorrow.
I will.
Okay?
Okay, love you, bye.
I love you, papi.
I love you.
Bye, mama.
Bye.
Happy Independence Day.
I'm not feeling
very independent.
So how long has he been living
in this place?
Couple years.
How long did he box for?
God, since way before
I was born.
Did you ever see him?
I did.
Hey, tio Dio?
Yes?
I'm pregnant.
That's beautiful.
You're gonna have a baby,
Katalina?
Do you hear that, Tiger?
Katalina's gonna have a baby.
That is nice.
Who is the father?
Tio, Bobby.
That's nice.
Can you kick it up a notch?
Like, kick it up?
O Canada
Yeah, that's it.
Our home and na--
You know, we haven't
known each other for that long.
10 months?
10 months.
It's not that long.
No, it's not a long time.
It's not.
Doesn't it feel like
a long time, though?
Okay, good point.
What if you couldn't
write music anymore?
What if--what if you couldn't
play music anymore?
I'd kill myself.
Very funny.
I'm gonna play music.
Look, I know what you're saying,
all right?
Because based on our decision,
there's consequences for that,
for me.
I know, things change.
Things change
based on our decision,
but I'm gonna play music,
and you're gonna dance.
Dancing in a kitchen?
It wouldn't happen like that.
Do you see what's behind you?
It's beautiful.
Why don't we
stay up here tonight?
Okay.
We're here, tio.
Welcome back, Diego.
Hi.
Did you have a good day?
Yes.
I love you.
I love you too, Katalina.
Wanna say bye to Bobby?
Okay.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
You want to come over?
Okay.
Okay, girl.
Come on.
Come into the kitchen.
Do you have a bowl or something
so we can give her some water?
Yeah.
A bowl that doesn't have,
like, light soy sauce.
Yeah.
Mint Moroccan tea?
That's new.
I'm so hungry.
Yeah, we haven't eaten today.
Almost.
What?
What are you thinking?
How many months
have you been here?
Not that many.
I can't tell if you're
still unpacking or packing.
Unpacking.
What are you really
thinking about?
I think my mother
is all right.
What do you mean?
I just saw
so clearly today how...
she thinks life has...
disappointed her.
Really?
You know what I saw today
in your mom
that I never saw before?
Just how strong she is.
She reminded me of you today.
What?
You scared?
I know.
I don't want to
disappoint you.
Will you kiss me now?
Let's get down to the bank.
Dog in the house.
Tiger.
Come here, come here.
We're out of coffee.
I'm supposed to be
at work later today.
What was that?
It's a text from Fitz.
Asked why we didn't come
last night.
I thought it'd be
something about Tiger.
No, it's not.
What are we gonna do
with the dog?
Hi, we'd like to open
a safety deposit box, please.
Yeah, upstairs.
Upstairs?
Yeah.
I just need some signatures
on the back where the Xs are.
There.
Now, the both of you
are gonna be on there?
Yes.
Okey-doke.
We need to decide
what size box you want.
We have the 2-inch
and the 5-inch.
They're both 18 inches long.
5x18.
5x18?
All right.
Do you ever feel like
you're pretending?
I hope you're not talking
about last night.
And I think we're all set.
If you'll just follow me,
I'll show you
where they're kept.
Is that gonna be big enough?
How big is $500,000?
That's what I'm saying.
So, just have to show you
how it all works.
So I had this cup
of espresso.
I'm talking just a tiny shot,
you know?
The tiniest shot.
Not even, like--
it's a single,
not a double.
And I felt it instantly
in my body.
Like, I was jittery.
I had a hard time concentrating,
and I felt it in my stomach.
Like, I felt it here.
Of course, I had to go
to the bathroom immediately.
Then I was thinking,
"Oh, it's not gonna be that way
with tea,
or diet sodas probably
don't have the same effect."
But I think tea is different,
right?
You think?
Are you sure that's decaf?
Yes.
All right.
I'm turning it on.
Look, are you sure
you want to do this?
We can't stop after this.
Call him.
Okay.
Hello.
Is this Dmitri?
Yes.
Yeah, this is Bobby.
I know.
We're at a Chase bank
at the corner of Canal and Mott.
You meet us here, right now,
you bring the money,
and you put it in
as small a case as possible.
We put the money
in a safety deposit box,
then you get the phone.
I'm on my way.
He said he's on his way.
Let's get back inside.
You know, when I was little,
my dad told me
that babies grew on trees.
My dad told me
I came from his balls.
Well, that was the truth.
Yeah.
How old were you?
Should have been here by now.
What did he say?
I told you what he said.
I mean, did he give you
a time when he'd be here?
He said, "I'm on my way."
That's all he said.
What if it's a boy?
I don't know anything
about boys.
I'm a boy.
Where the fuck is he?
Shit.
The guy's here.
The guy's here from yesterday.
Come on. Come on.
What guy?
The guy with the gun.
Dmitri?
No, not Dmitri,
the Chinese guy.
My God.
Shit.
Do you see anything?
He's down there.
I can see him in the mirror.
How did he find us?
I don't know.
But the Treo's on.
What is he doing?
He's got his phone open.
We're safe here.
Doesn't feel safe.
This was our plan.
I know,
but it's a stupid plan.
Fuck, he's coming up
the stairs.
Get in the elevator.
Go, go.
Fuck.
Bobby, turn it off!
I am, I am, I am.
Turn it off!
I am.
Shit.
Give me your purse.
Take it!
Just go!
Sorry!
Sorry.
Excuse us!
In here!
In here, in here.
Go, go!
Get back there!
Okay.
Bobby, is he there?
Bobby.
Look at me.
I don't think
I can run anymore.
Yes, you can.
No, I don't think I can.
The door's locked.
The door's locked, okay?
Come on.
Come on!
Okay.
You're okay.
Bobby, I can't.
Come on, okay?
We have to find a way down.
Okay, okay.
Fuck!
Come on.
Okay.
I got you.
Come on.
Shit! Go!
Go, go, go!
Crap!
Come on!
Bobby, I can't.
Got you.
In there! In there!
Bobby, the lock!
Is it locked?
Let's go.
Okay.
God.
Which way, Bobby?
The... south.
Do you see him?
No.
The bridge.
Fuck!
Wait.
This is fucking crazy.
I know.
I almost told my mother
last night.
And then you came
to your senses, right?
Well, I mean,
I told my sister.
Yeah, I know you did.
But I-I know that my mother
wouldn't understand
that it's a decision, you know?
I mean...
The fact that
not wanting to have a baby
was my first instinct,
one I thought that I'd--
we'd absolutely act upon,
and I thought that's
definitely what we'd do.
That's what we both thought.
Okay.
I think we're all right.
That didn't go so well.
What happened?
What do you think we did wrong?
Ethically or logistically?
Yeah, you choose that one.
It's time we decide.
I know.
You don't know.
I do know.
We'll decide.
And it'll be a good decision.
Will it be the right decision?
Yeah.
Are we through?
God, yes.
Here, hold this.
What are you doing?
Bobby?
Hello?
It's Bobby.
Things didn't work out.
We're taking ourselves
out of the equation.
Just give me the Treo, Bobby.
All I want is the phone.
The Treo's on.
Nice shot.
What time do you have to
go to work today?
No particular time.
Guess I'll probably go
after you go to the theater.
So what do we do now?
I don't know.
Guess we just keep going.
What do you want to do now?
I don't know.
I guess we just keep going.
I know.
Subtitles by Arigon