You...
Where the hell
did you come from?
I work for Scorpio.
Scorpio?
I thought he was out.
Stay still...
or else I'll slash you.
- Then, you're dead, too.
- I'm serious. Motherfucker.
Give me the knife.
Get him.
Whan.
Hey.
Hey!
Hey, aren't you
going to the market?
God,
I miss Sunny.
Let's go see her.
She's so sexy.
God, wake up.
- Hey...
- Hey, what the hell is this?
You there. Staying here
isn't going to solve anything.
Get out.
When did you start operating?
A month ago.
We didn't know the building
was condemned.
We signed a lease.
What do we do?
Look, fellas, you should
have checked before signing.
Who are you?
I told you to get the hell out!
I'm sorry about your
situation but...
Whan!
Any fucker can come
and try to mess with me.
Lay your hands on me,
I'll cut you up!
What are you doing?
You insane?
Yeah,
I'm crazy.
You'd be crazy too
if you were in my shoes.
Just because your share in this is
small you may not be so desperate.
If I lose this place,
my life is over.
Where do you think you're going?
- Throw the knife away.
- Get out.
Don't do this.
Throw it away.
I'll kill you, too.
Son of a bitch.
This is not going to be
an easy case.
Don't come near me.
Don't come near me!
Hurry, just bring the money,
fuckers.
Your friend is
in for a serious crime.
However, the prosecutors and
the investigators are friends of mine.
If we reach an agreement first,
we can pull some strings.
It's going to cost him.
You little rat.
I don't need this.
Crazy son of a bitch
who can't see anything.
Go ahead, stab me!
Stab me, you lousy son of a bitch.
Please,
don't do this.
How are we gonna make a living?
Cocksuckers. You're not
the only ones who are mad.
Did you bring it?
I'm sorry.
What? You think this
is enough for a settlement?
Please, we have to reach an
agreement before prosecution...
I promise to bring the rest.
- $3,000 more and I'll settle.
- Listen...
He's giving you a good deal 'cause you
kids seem to be in a difficult situation.
Ask around.
No one takes $6,000
for a case like this.
Damn,
there's nothing left to sell.
We hit Woojin first so we got
no reason for turning down duel.
He can't get involved directly.
'Cause he's got his arm injured.
Lots of first-class knuckleheads
working under Woojin.
So even though they're
outnumbered, they can survive.
- What?
- I'm looking for Taesoo. I'm Min.
My friend.
Tell him to wait.
Who's he?
I think I told you about him.
He's my best friend, Min.
Why haven't you been talking?
- What's up?
- Thought you were busy.
Busy? Make time for you.
Let's roll.
Whan!
Why did they release me?
I've been here since 9 o'clock.
Eat this.
You can't afford a lawyer.
Forget about it.
Let's get something to eat.
What do you want?
Does Sunny know about this?
How can she?
Tell Sunny that...
I had a little trouble with the mob
so I had to lay low for a while.
You crazy fuck!
- You fool...
- Hey...
Hey,
I've been to the slammer.
Oh, yeah?
Come on.
Mom!
Hold it!
Keep your word.
It's difficult to find men
who keep their word.
You win this one,
but...
- if you invade our territory again...
- it's war! Let's go.
They may attack anytime.
Get ready in 24 hours.
Come here.
Yo, Won... Check the club first,
and then get your boys together.
Have them stationed in each
district within 24 hours. - Yes, sir.
This mob thing is
a real shitty business.
You can't trust anyone.
Boss likes you.
So,
your name is Min.
Let's get a drink?
Later.
You're such a dumb ass.
Take it.
It's a bonus.
This is it.
No more fighting.
You know I lied to you?
Romy was never in New York.
She told me that she had spent
over a year in a sanitarium.
She also told me about
Kyung's suicide,
But I was too tired to listen.
Everyone looks happy.
Except me...
How many do you think
are really happy?
Ever since I was little,
I thought I could do anything.
Then I screwed up.
You know what my dad said?
He said I fell in the early
part of the race in my life.
So,
if I stand up and run again,
I can be faster
than anyone else.
Do you feel the same way?
You still don't know me.
I'm trying to stand up.
It's pathetic.
Do you want to know
how I really feel?
In the end,
you'll go to college.
And when you graduate,
you'll meet a man from
a good family and get married.
You're just out for a walk now.
You know?
Let go.
Romy was living in her own hell.
My past two years...
weren't exactly spent
in heaven either.
Everything was trembling.
Everything before my eyes...
We need to have a serious talk,
Romy.
Do you remember what
Richard Bach said?
About the bird that flies
higher seeing further?
You can broaden your
view overseas.
I don't want to fly high.
Or see far.
If you fly low,
you can see things up close.
Romy!
- I don't want to talk to you.
- Sit down.
I told you I'm not
going to college!
Then you can study overseas.
I thought I was abroad studying.
That's what you told everyone.
Fine,
you don't have to go.
But being who you are, do you really
think you can stand your friends...
looking down on you?
Romy! You're just temporarily
out of the race...
- If you just pick yourself up...
- Not that story again, Dad.
I'm going to stay down,
for the rest of my life!
Whan,
you have to...
open a big restaurant someday.
Thanks.
Min!
Do you know how hard it was
to find this place?
These are so heavy.
My arms are killing me.
How are you?
Hey, come in a little later.
The room is a fucking pigsty.
I...
ran away from home.
Let's go in.
Romy had things
her way all the time.
There she was right in front of me,
confusing me all over again.
Still...
I was glad to see her.
Eat dinner?
Can you tell him
to go somewhere?
I want to be alone with you.
Romy,
this is Whan's place.
He's letting me crash here.
I asked Taesoo for help.
Come in.
Taesoo found a place
for us to stay.
He even lent me some money.
It didn't feel good but...
I was glad
I could do something
for Romy.
Wait a second.
Like it?
No?
It's not that.
Are you close to Taesoo?
Yeah,
like brothers. Why?
I don't like him.
He scares me.
Puts me in a funk.
God,
having a pad is a pain.
Why?
Don't you think it's weird?
There's not a single piece
of furniture in this place.
Wake up!
Is breakfast ready?
- Hey... Get up.
- Okay, I will! I'm up.
Fuck,
I'm a first time offender.
But that's not a big deal.
What matters is how you live.
That's not a big deal.
...fuck.
I'm really going to pay back Min.
Everything.
Hey, hey.
Have you done it?
What?
You know. Men.
Women. Sex!
Did you?
C'mon, tell me.
Don't you want do it with me?
Can't you see I'm reading?
I told you.
We're not right for each other.
You don't want me
when you look at me?
How does it feel like?
- Say something. - Hey, give it back.
- Say something.
It happens naturally
if you both want each other.
You don't want me?
- Don't answer it. - I have to.
- C'mon, leave it.
Tell me about it...
Where you going?
- Come here, come here.
- Hello.
- Don't answer it. Just hang up.
- Yeah, it's me.
Tell me about it...
Sure. Later.
Where you going?
Taesoo wants to see me.
Back soon.
For some reason,
I felt uneasy.
Think I loved her too much.
Hurry up, guys.
Listen up while you put them on.
We're from Dong-A Wrecking Co. no
matter what, understand? - Yes, sir!
She could walk out on me
anytime.
I felt pathetic.
Insecure...
Let's go.
We can't control the situation.
They won't evacuate
from the condemned buildings.
I got it.
Listen up!
No smashing heads.
- Go for the shoulders and thighs, Ok?
- Yeah!
Now, go on.
Take this.
- I'm going home.
- Asshole...
we need you for a head count.
This is what you meant by "gifts"
and "success"?
Been worse shit than this.
You know we can't choose things.
- You've let me down, Taesoo.
- Min.
Hey, Min.
I'm out of here.
Taesoo, we're in.
What should we do?
- Shut the fuck up!
- Sir...
You're in this together.
Aren't you, dickhead?
Hey, he's a gang member,
too.
You can't force us out of here.
Don't you have your parent?
Son of a bitch!
Min!
You're awake. Sorry,
I wanted to come sooner but...
You do what you want,
and I'll do what I want.
Romy,
what's wrong?
Can't you see?
I want someone
who can be with me.
Do you know how I feel
when you do this?
Did you ever care about me?
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I saw Kyung tonight.
She was staring at me.
I was scared.
I couldn't even breathe.
I waited for you...
'cause you're the only one
who can protect me. - Sorry
Where were you?
I'm sorry. I didn't realize
you still had those nightmares.
It wasn't a nightmare.
She was here.
Hey, it's just an illusion.
Your own guilt.
Get it together.
Don't treat me
like a sick person.
- Romy.
- Let go. No more arguing with you.
- Let go! Let go!
You don't know
anything about me!
What-don't you think
about anyone else?
Look at me. Shit goes down.
I'm fucking wrecked.
Why does it have to be
your feelings first, huh?
Hey, did you ever
stop to think about me?
I don't pretend to be
a good person like you.
Everyone thinks about
their own selves first.
Let go.
I wanted to make her stay.
But,
Romy was too much.
When she was with me,
I felt nervous...
and when she left,
I felt deserted.
Thank you for coming.
You dance so hot.
Keep going...
Sunny.
- Wait!
- Why? - Just wait!
I got you something.
Put it on.
Hey,
now that you have my back,
it'll be cool.
They say I made it too fast.
But that's bullshit.
You know what my dream is?
I'm going to be a boss.
Someone everyone knows
and respects.
Min.
I'm going to do it.
When you've got it,
no one fucks around with you.
You'll see.
Taesoo is going to be somebody.
Good for you.
I'm a fuck up.
Hey,
you're the only one I respect.
Today, we're gonna drink 'til
we pass out, all right?
I'm already gone.
Just one more bottle.
I don't want it.
- I don't like gifts for no reason.
- Hey, but it's for you.
- Min.
- Hey, man. Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Let me go.
Hey... c'mon...
Taesoo controlled
his life like a man.
As for me,
I had none.
Min! Hey,
get up.
How long did I sleep?
Don't get up. It's still dark.
Want some water?
You know what my dream is?
I want to be a singer.
What's yours?
Nothing.
I wish you could be my man.
You like me?
Yeah.
I can't make you happy...
- and I don't have nothing.
- Still I like you.
Min.
Hey-wake up.
Don't you think
you're way over your head?
Get out.
Fuck this.
Leave me alone.
Something I said?
You look like shit,
you know.
Asshole!
Hey!
Get it together.
- Stay out of it.
- No, you get out and don't bother him.
Min doesn't take orders
from nobody.
Did you fuck her?
Hey, Whan.
What did you say?
Just say yes or no.
Shut the fuck up.
So gang members can
screw everyone, is that it?
What? You son of a bitch!
Who the fuck do you think you are?
Fuck you.
You fucked her. And you call
yourself a friend? Asshole.
Taesoo.
Do something.
Hey, back off. He's your friend.
Don't make a fool of yourself.
Let go.
I know you can fight.
So, go ahead, hit me.
Whan,
you fuck ass...
Hey,
you're asking for it.
Oh yeah, take your best shot,
come on.
I know it's Romy.
But she's not the only pussy
in the world.
Shit...
Fuck,
you cocksucker.
Get the fuck out.
Somebody help.
Stop them.
Stop it, man.
Please. Stop!
Hey, I'm leaving
this fucking dump...
Sunny.
Whan,
you listen good.
I'm not a whore.
I slept with Min
'cause I like him.
So what?
Boss. Let me take
over Sang's night clubs.
Don't rush it.
I can handle it.
I'd give my life to
make the business.
Boss.
Don't you trust me?
If you make it too fast,
you'll be a target.
That doesn't scare me.
I am.
Take it slow.
Work it easy.
Those are my rules.
It's me,
Taesoo.
Hope you're feelin' better.
Call me up,
okay?
This is Whan.
Pick up the phone if you're there.
- Whan.
- Look out the window.
- Whan, the other day, I was...
- Come to the window.
Now I don't owe you anything.
Strange...
I can't picture Romy's face.
But I can still smell her.
Feel her.
Miss her crazy bad.
It's better than pork ribs.
Help yourself.
Welcome!
- Some more soup, please.
- Sure.
Careful,
it's hot.
Whan,
get me a bottle of Soju.
How's business?
Do I still owe you something?
Whan.
I'm sorry.
About Sunny,
I made a mistake.
I'm really sorry.
How would you feel
if I slept with Romy?
Let's not see
each other anymore.
I don't want to make trouble.
I'm going to change.
I can make it by myself.
Forget about me.
Do your own thing.
Let me tell you something.
You're not a bum.
Don't fuck your life
'cause of Taesoo.
You're smart,
you'll be okay.
Got to go.
The boss here?
There you are.
Congratulations.
It's a great place.
You'll soon be a conglomerate.
Sit down.
You kids wait outside.
This wasn't a clean job.
If the press gets on our back,
we're in deep.
If we get a good deal with
the prosecutor,
it'll be less than two years.
During your absence, Woojin
here will look after your business.
You've met before,
right?
I need time.
Are you there?
Min. It's Taesoo.
Scorpio betrayed me.
It's a war.
Get down here fast,
I got no time.
Boss,
there's no answer from Kee.
Think word is out?
Think Scorpio is stupid?
Asshole.
He starts by cutting our hands
and legs.
We strike first.
- If not tonight, we're dead.
- Okay.
Promise you'll only love me.
What are you going to do now?
I don't know.
Maybe go to the army.
Go to college. If you start now,
you'll get in next year.
Don't count on it.
I can't.
You haven't tried.
You can do it.
I'll study,
too.
As soon as we go to college,
let's get married.
A year after,
we can go abroad
to France or the US.
I'll help you until
you take the exam.
I can't be at home anyway.
You motherfuckers,
where the fuck are you?
Come out like a man!
Boss,
over there!
Shit...
- Hello?
- Min!
Taesoo's in deep.
We're at the night club...
Hello? Hello?
Where to?
To the store for
some cigarettes.
What about me?
Stay.
I'll be back soon.
Get some sleep.
Just returning your knife.
I'll kill you motherfucker.
I'll cut you up good...
so you stay there.
You dug your own grave with
your greed.
You little prick.
You come for the corpse?
Stop.
He's gone.
Why not let him go?
Hand him over.
Get the hell out.
If I see either one of you...
you're dead!
Heavy to carry home,
ain't it?
Taesoo.
I always thought I had nothing
to lose in this world.
I never had anything.
But I had you.
I'm so fucking angry.
It's all nothing.
It's too late.
You're killing me.
Taesoo,
wake up.
Taesoo...
Taesoo, please.
Damn it.
Taesoo...
Kill the bastard!
Where are you?
Hurry back.
I don't want to be here alone.
Get some ice cream and bread
on your way back. Bye!
I had no dreams.
Romy...
But now I have so many dreams.
Whan and Taesoo,
and all those times together
with you...
Everything feels like
a beautiful dream.
Romy,
I miss you.
But I can't come to you.