- Give me a hand here.
- I'm coming.
How is he?
- Get him out of the water first.
- Gator! Gator!
- Gator's dead.
- We're in Hong Kong.
When we were at sea with San-po,
we wanted for nothing.
We had everything. Now look at us.
We're washed up here like driftwood.
Who did all this to us?
Dragon Ma, I'll rip you into pieces.
Right, let's all make a solemn oath.
We're all agreed -
Dragon Ma must die.
Good morning, Mr Chun.
- This way.
- Morning.
Please sit inside.
- The usual?
- Yes, thank you.
- The bill.
- Bill, please.
They're prepared to go to jail.
Their families will be compensated.
- And the reporters?
- They're upstairs.
- We're ready when you are.
- Let's order some food.
The stuffs upstairs.
- I'll get it for you.
- Thanks.
- Please wait here.
- Help yourself.
- Don't move! This is a stick-up!
- Don't move!
- No!
- My money!
My money...
- Don't move!
- It's time to leave.
Stop them!
- Robbery!
- Check it out.
Police, hold it!
Sir!
- Take them away.
- Go check out the shop.
Mr Chun.
Chan-jim.
- We're reporters.
- You're everywhere.
- We'll take a photo.
- Come on.
- Not for me.
- You caught the men so easily.
- Were you acting on a tip-off?
- No, I was just on my beat as usual.
Mr Chun, do you mind being called
Lightening Chun?
To tell the truth I'm very flattered.
- What are you charging them with?
- Robbery and assaulting an officer.
Let's take a photo.
Stand closer. Grab his neck.
Sir! The shop owner is dead.
- They should be charged with murder.
- I agree with you.
What?
We just did what you told us!
- We didn't murder him!
- Lock them up!
Stop there.
I only got $300! You promised...
They were escaping.
Take away the bodies!
Mr Chun, over here.
May I have an explanation?
We all knew that
Chun has been staging his arrests.
Now the public's aware of it, too.
If you hadn't pushed him so much,
he wouldn't have had to
falsify his arrests.
You gave him three districts!
Chun is the only Chinese policeman
who can carry a gun.
I knew this would happen.
- I'm against them carrying weapons.
- Are you against paying them, too?
The situation should dictate
which officer carries a weapon,
not the officer's nationality.
And they should be
paid the same, too.
We'll address that another time.
Let's concentrate on Chun here.
He's responsible for three districts.
It's not easy to sack him.
We'll ease him out slowly,
starting with Sai Wan district.
But who'll replace him?
I have a man in mind.
The man who carried out
Project A so successfully.
Take them back!
Sir, but I'm not qualified.
No one knows that
and it's worth a try.
It'll be a change of scenery for you.
This is for your outstanding service.
Congratulations!
Thank you, sir. Thank you, sir.
We'd also like to relieve you
of some pressure.
That's not necessary.
We don't want our top officer
overburdened.
So we're handing over one of
your districts to a new man.
We've received some new guns.
Your gun's been in service a long time.
I want to have it checked.
See if you need a new one.
Reporting for duty, sir.
Dragon, now you're Chun's assistant
in Sai Wan district.
These are your official orders.
From now on,
you and Chun will work together.
If you've got any questions, ask him.
It's an honour to work with you.
Welcome, I'm quite sure you'll be
a valuable addition to the district.
Let me know if you need anything.
Chun, you may have lost
one district,
but the Commissioner
will see you gain another.
Really?
You never know.
I see. I see.
The corrupt Manchurian Government
has made our country poor.
- We have become an inferior race.
- Would you like to buy a flower?
If we want to save China,
we have to have the right attitude.
To enjoy a decent standard of living,
we have to overthrow the Government.
Dr Sun set up the "Revive China Society"
to support the revolution.
China cannot be saved
by speeches alone, we need action.
We need weapons
and the money to buy them.
Police.
Thank you for listening.
Would you like to buy a flower?
Maggie!
- Regina!
- Stop here.
- Where have you been?
- Were you looking for me?
- Not really. Where are you going?
- Sai Wan.
Hop in.
My cousin, Carina -
my classmate, Regina.
- Haven't seen you before.
- She's just arrived.
I'm having a party next week.
You're invited.
- Is it your birthday party?
- They're always such fun.
Bring Carina.
- Will you come?
- What will I wear?
- She'll lend you something.
- Sure.
Support the revolution
and buy a flower.
- No, thank you.
- Can I have one?
If he wants to save China,
give me one, too.
- Good idea, I'll have one, too.
- Thank you, sirs.
- You're right. I'll have one, too.
- How much?
Sir, the revolution will succeed
if everyone was like you.
I hope so.
- Thank you.
- Where do you usually sell these?
Wherever there are people
to buy them.
Come on, eat.
- What is it?
- The police, hide the boxes.
You're spreading rumours,
disturbing the peace and racketeering, right?
- You have no proof.
- The flowers you have are the proof.
And look at the flowers you sold.
You men are my witnesses.
Did this woman sell you the flowers?
No.
What's that?!
What the hell are you doing
with flowers in your jackets?
We're pen pals meeting for the first time,
and as we don't know each other
the girls said they'd hold baskets
and we said we'd wear a rose.
We didn't see you there!
You should hold them higher.
Come on, sit down.
You look much prettier
than your handwriting.
Let me introduce everyone -
Mr A, I'm Mr B, Mr C, Mr D. Sit down.
Is it an offence to meet pen pals?
I must admit you won this time.
Watch out. Don't let me
catch you selling flowers.
And we're not used
to making idle threats either.
Some tea, miss?
I hate those who oppress us
on behalf of their foreign masters.
Right. They think they're wonderful
under that uniform.
- They're morons. Don't you agree?
- Not really.
There are cops who are honest
and hardworking.
- I've never met any.
- Yes, you have!
We're all policemen.
We've never oppressed anyone.
- So all of you are policemen.
- Excuse us.
Miss,
China depends on patriots like you.
Don't forget your money boxes.
Dragon, if they weren't so beautiful,
do you think you'd have helped them?
- Cheque, waiter.
- Yes, sir.
Those policemen were really kind.
If it wasn't for them,
we'd have been in trouble.
There aren't any good policemen.
- How many did you sell?
- Quite a few.
It's your lucky day.
- And you?
- Not much.
- Help!
Come back!
No, you don't.
So it's you again.
What's going on?
- They tried to rob those ladies.
- Come on, make way.
- Really? What ladies?
- Make way. Come on.
Don't block our way. Move along.
Strange, where did they go?
- Officer, what's up?
- Nothing. Take them to the station.
You can tell me
what this is all about.
- I'd like to see the man in charge.
- He's talking.
- Sir?
- What?
- We work for Tiger.
- That's right.
- Still, that's no excuse.
- But we didn't rob those ladies.
- Really?
- How did you know they were ladies?
- Be quiet! Who asked you?
- Look, is Sergeant Chi here?
- Sergeant Chi?
You lost.
Do I place the same bet again?
- Make it a dollar.
- Really?
Yeah.
Wait, they want to see Sergeant Chi.
This way.
Right, you lot, sign here.
You shouldn't be messing
things up like that!
- We didn't, sir.
- Bullshit.
- 201, show these two out.
- Get out of here.
- Can I speak now?
- What do you want to say? Go ahead.
- I want to see your superior.
- Why?
I want to report
some police irregularities.
All right.
Shang, take them to the back room.
Wait! One at a time.
You come with me.
- Sung!
- Coming.
This way.
- So where is he?
- Our superior is right here.
Now what's this about police irregularities?
You can tell him.
You didn't expect your little show
earlier today would go unpunished?
I'm going to teach you a lesson.
No, help me. Can somebody help?!
Don't. Don't do that.
Stay right there. I'm the new
superintendent for Sai Wan.
Here's my appointment.
Superintendent, a terrible mistake.
If police officers believe
they can use their power
for personal attacks
and use their position
to protect criminals...
- that's also a mistake.
- Sir, you mustn't believe that.
I just saw it with my own eyes.
Who do you think you are?
If this is the way it's going to be,
then I'm quitting.
Right, you can do all our jobs.
So you've never made a mistake?
You really want
everyone here to quit?
All right, I quit!
What has got into you boys?
He's saying it's for your own good.
Please, don't take
any notice of them.
If every officer does his duty,
then I'll ignore what happened.
Hear that?
Welcome, Superintendent Ma!
A little welcome present for you, sir.
- From all the boys?
- Yes, sir.
So Sai Wan is a good place
to make money.
Just to show our appreciation.
But there's one constable who
refused to show his appreciation.
Who's that?
Constable Ho,
he's still out on the beat.
Send him in when he returns.
Yes, sir. Let me know
if you need anything.
All right.
Sir, that's a lovely flower you have.
Thank you.
Look. He's been
on the wanted list for three years!
He's the suspect for many recent cases.
He still lives in Sai Wan.
He's down as a suspect here.
So why haven't they arrested him?
Maybe they didn't want to.
- Superintendent. Constable Ho, sir.
- You didn't contribute. Why?
As I don't take bribes,
I couldn't afford to.
- So the others take bribes, then?
- I didn't say that.
If you don't wise up,
you won't stay in your job long.
My job is to serve the people
and uphold the law.
- I'd rather quit than accept bribes.
- You sound like an honest man.
Tell me about all these unsolved
cases where no one's been arrested.
Tiger Au's the kingpin around here.
I'd love to arrest him.
But I don't have the power.
He's got lots of guards.
- These criminals are his men.
- So where does he hang around?
He runs most of the illegal
businesses in Sai Wan.
He's usually at Po Luk Hotel.
Tell the other officers
to come in early tomorrow.
All right, as long as each of you
does your duty, I'll be happy.
I don't need envelopes.
Would you like to
live near a brothel?
Or see your own children
gamble or smoke opium
knowing the damage they do
to the family?
You wouldn't like it and neither
would Sai Wan residents.
But brothels, gambling
and opium dens exist everywhere
and you all know who owns them.
It is our duty to protect
this community and I intend to do it.
Therefore starting today,
we're going to clean it up.
Let's go.
Superintendent, if you've enough men,
I'll stay here.
- Can I have a day off?
- Why?
- Can I have a day off, too?
- Tell me why. One by one.
- My wife's pregnant.
- My sister's pregnant.
- What a coincidence!
- My sister is his wife.
- My wife is his sister.
- Yeah.
- Sir, can I resign now?
- For what reason?
I'm the only child in my family.
So I'd rather not go.
Me, too. For what I'm paid,
it isn't worth the risk, so I quit.
- I quit, too.
- Me, as well.
All right, operation cancelled.
Dismissed.
But Dragon...
Come on.
Now you see why I'm so fed up.
They never want to do any real work.
They made Dragon cancel his plan.
What do you mean?
There are good reasons for that.
Maybe he wants someone
to check Tiger out first.
No. He's testing the men to see
who's brave and who's a coward.
Now he knows he can't trust anyone.
Am I right?
He's right. We've been with Dragon so
long now, we know how his mind works.
Oh, really?
- Right now it's not working.
- Are you kidding?!
If this operation fails,
we'll have to leave this place.
He's right.
We can't fail or we're finished.
Mars, I want you to take a note
to the marines.
- You're asking for a transfer back?!
- We'll go and arrest Tiger tonight.
Well, it's been ages
since we were all together.
To your health.
Tiger, I hear you have
a small job for us.
That's right.
I just met Chun.
His Sai Wan district
has been given to some new upstart.
We'll wait for Mars here.
You go check the place out.
Thank you.
We've changed clothes,
why are they staring?
Your hat's on backwards.
- How about now?
- That will do.
- What's this for?
- Here.
Forget that.
Let's get something to eat first.
Tiger, if we've lost
Chun's protection,
who'll look after our interests?
Since he's asking for a favour,
we have to help him no matter what.
As soon as this new guy shows
his face around these parts
we'll fix him permanently.
Why wait for him to come out?
Go fix him at the station.
Who is he anyway?
Is he some kind of monster or what?
Mars, over here.
I spoke to Ying.
She said the marines were
off training somewhere.
Is the operation still on?
- We'll do it on our own.
- We can't back down now.
Not much happening.
- What did you say his name was?
- Dragon Ma.
Dragon Ma?
Remember the one
that killed the pirates?
- Which one of you is Tiger?
- I am.
In that case, you're coming
down to the station.
- To the station? Who are you?
- Superintendent Dragon Ma.
You're wanted in connection
with 3 murders, 4 robberies,
one case of arson and 3 of assault.
This is the warrant.
I did all those things?
Let me see that.
Sorry, I missed.
Dragon, are we leaving?
Stop the music.
Stop it.
All right, we're police officers.
If you've no business here, out!
Time to go.
Come on, everybody. Come on.
Dragon Ma.
Nice of you to drop by.
I wanted to meet you.
Right, I've always wanted to meet
the famous Dragon Ma.
You must be after me.
Those two Causeway Bay murders,
I did both of them.
You'd better arrest me, too, because
I'm going to kill a policeman soon.
Dragon Ma, didn't anyone tell you?
You're dead.
One day I'll die for sure
like everybody else.
In the meantime, you're under arrest.
Dragon!
Dragon, the third unit are outside,
awaiting orders.
Dragon!
The other two units
are all in position.
No one told me about this.
Don't just stand there.
Get them in here.
- Get them in here.
- Right.
I'll tell them to charge.
They're all ready.
Forget it. No more bluffing,
we're all alone.
You've got courage.
You shouldn't be worried about
arresting anyone,
You should be more worried about
getting out of here alive.
- The doors.
- Right.
Steady.
- Steady.
Get out of here!
Steady!
What do we do now?
Now...
don't think
you're getting out of here.
Get them!
Look out!
Bastard! Let me teach you
a good lesson.
Bastard!
Arrest me?!
You'd need more lives
than a cat to arrest me.
- You four kneel down. Go get him!
- Right!
Had enough yet?
Don't forget my name is Wong.
Forward!
Upstairs. Spread out!
Dragon, are you all right?
Dragon, what a surprise!
I see you're hard at work.
How's it going?
They were resisting arrest.
Really? I see, take them away.
Hold it. What?
Are we pirates? Are we smugglers?
This is dry land,
you can't arrest us here!
I realise that, sir. But I suspect
there are pirates in this hotel.
Superintendent, please carry on,
I wouldn't want to interrupt you.
Lock them up.
Round them up,
take them back to the base
and question them
to see if they are pirates.
You. You. Round them up.
Take them back to the base!
Fall in.
Take them away.
- Are you all right?
- You could have come quicker.
- Move it.
- Come on.
- Thank you. I owe you one.
- They were out at sea.
They came as soon as
they got the message.
Dragon Ma!
- If it wasn't...
- Shut up!
Hold it!
Release these two.
If you two manage to walk
out of this place, you can go free.
Right, leave us.
You, too.
Lock them up!
You're still the same.
If police work was that easy,
I'd have taken your job long ago.
I know, sir.
Just remember,
you're still one of us.
We must go fishing again.
Dragon, Father says things are very
different on land, especially here.
You have to be careful.
Take them back to the station.
Move it! Go on!
- How was it?
- It's Dragon Ma for sure.
- Let's kill him!
- Let's do it.
How?
They've got an entire army out there.
The police were looking for pirates.
See? They've already
got wind of our plan.
- What do we do now?
- We can go to bed early.
- Where do we sleep?
We can't kill him now,
so we'll find a hotel.
We have to wait.
- You're here.
- Yeah.
- Cigarette?
- No, thanks.
- Chun, are you taking those files?
- I was going to.
- But I'll need them when I'm back.
- Really? When will you be back?
I believe it will be soon.
Not everyone can sit in this chair.
You're right, sir.
Find a place to store them.
He'll be back soon.
Sergeant, could you...?
Dragon Ma!
I've always wanted to arrest these
gangsters, and now you've done it.
- This is terrific.
- Thanks.
- Chun.
- Shut up!
- What do you mean?
- Lock them up.
- You've changed your tune.
- Take them away.
- Chun!
- Shut up!
Do you hear me?! Take them away!
Do you hear me? Take them away!
201.
Put Tiger in the security block.
267, 357.
Put Wong here in cell two.
282, take some men
and seal off the hotel.
Sergeant Ching.
Lock up the rest of this rabble
and take their statements.
The rest start working on
the wanted criminals.
- Understood?
- Yes, sir.
Get to work.
Get going!
You've been working very hard.
Take a break.
See you later.
That's right, sir.
You put your feet up.
I'll make you a nice cup of coffee.
- These files, where do I put them?
- Idiot! Put them away.
Dragon, the Commissioner is extremely
pleased with the way the raid went.
Don't thank me.
And we can't give you any medals yet.
Remember, don't get carried away.
- No, I won't, sir.
- I'm here to make sure you don't.
Keep your eyes peeled at
the Commissioner's daughter's party.
I'll be on the alert.
That's not good enough.
You must anticipate
Chun's every move to cause trouble.
If anything goes wrong,
you'll be blamed.
Thanks for the advice, sir.
You'd better get
something smart to wear.
You and your men need new clothes.
This ought to cover things.
This rat won't even feed one of us.
Where are you going?
To rob a shop.
I want to eat proper food, not rats.
- We've got nothing to lose.
- That's true.
But we've come to kill Ma.
If we go out,
we'll be arrested in a matter of minutes,
then we'll never avenge
the death of our captain.
Shall I make rat soup?
I haven't eaten meat soup for ages.
Guys, I've talked to Chun.
I've agreed to steal a necklace
at the birthday party.
I don't get it.
We're not doing this for Chun.
We are doing this for the revolution.
He'll pay good money
and we can use it for weapons.
- Does Chun know your background?
- He knows I smuggle weapons.
- But he thinks I'm a thief.
- That's great.
I think we should give it a try.
By the way, before I left Canton,
Dr Sun gave me a warning.
After the murder
of the governor of Canton,
the dowager empress sent
secret agents to arrest us.
Tell Maggie and Carina
to be careful selling flowers.
Dismissed. Come with me.
- I found it.
- What did you find?
- Lobster.
- Really?!
- It's a lobster's shell.
- Only the shell.
- Here's some fish.
- That's nice.
- What did you find out?
- Normally...
they're spread out all over the city.
It's hard to know where they are.
But Carina's often seen around here
when she sells flowers.
We could start with her.
This time we must liquidate
all of them.
Yes, of course.
It's beautiful!
I feel stupid dressed like this.
- Don't be silly.
- But I do.
We'll change inside.
It's Mr B.
The invitation's for one person only.
It says here one person.
But can't she come with me, please?
Sure, I don't think
that will be a problem.
- Maggie. You finally turned up.
- You're late.
Come on!
Why are you late?
- You go first.
- Make it quick.
Come on, let's find you some dresses.
That gentleman wouldn't let my cousin
in without an invitation.
- And who are you?
- We're policemen.
We're here for security.
And what's your name?
This is Dragon Ma.
I forgot to give her the invitation,
may she come in?
Of course.
- Thank you. Come on!
- Thank you, Mr Ma.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't worry.
Tell Mars to keep an eye on them.
- Who are they?
- The man's called Man.
- I don't know the woman's name.
- Beware of strangers.
Thank you.
She's very pretty.
- Do you know who she is?
- I've no idea, sir.
So no one can introduce me then?
I'll introduce her to you, sir.
She's not a friend of yours?
- Are you ready?
- Go ahead.
This way. The necklace is
in the office behind the painting.
- Breathe in.
- Nearly.
That should do it.
This dress is very tight.
They're all like that.
- Get the back.
- Don't move.
- That's enough. What do you think?
- Lovely!
So you were brought up in Shanghai,
but you don't have an accent.
Maybe I don't, but you don't have to
have athlete's foot to be an athlete.
Sorry.
Miss, you're really witty.
I like meeting people like you.
He says that to all the ladies.
Don't listen to him.
Your Excellency has found
a rare pearl indeed.
You look wonderful in this dress.
- Better stay alert.
- Right.
Daddy, do I look pretty?
Absolutely lovely, my dear.
And what about the dress?
But I was talking about the dress.
Let me have the first dance. Come on.
Miss, may I have the pleasure
of this dance?
- Go on. It'll be fun.
- May I have this dance?
I've never danced
with so many people before.
- Daddy, are you happy?
- Of course.
- You're very beautiful tonight.
- Why aren't you looking at me?
- Where do you live?
- James' Street.
It's a dangerous town,
you must be careful.
With policemen like you to catch
all the criminals, I feel quite safe.
Do you think Hong Kong
is a dangerous place to live?
Dangerous? Not really.
- What do you do all day long?
- Sit in my office and drink coffee.
When I leave the dance floor,
go upstairs with Carina
to distract the security guards.
Don't worry. We know what to do.
How can you say it's not dangerous
with all the crime?
If there wasn't any crime,
there wouldn't be any police.
Perhaps we could take tea together.
Excuse me,
did you have garlic for lunch?
The Commissioner's office
is opposite Maggie's bedroom.
I'll climb up outside.
Wait for me in her room.
Right.
In my spare time, I go shopping,
I go to theatre or I paint pictures.
You paint? I love painting.
- What is it?
- I've torn the dress.
What's up?
- Let's go and fix it.
- Excuse me.
Nobody has changed partners with us.
- Don't you like my company?
- Of course.
- But I have to use the ladies.
- All right, I see.
- Let me show you where it is.
- Thank you.
Right, let me fix it for you.
I can't see. Stop that.
- It's really hot.
- It's not.
- You're right, open the window.
- I'll do it.
The invitations are real,
but where did they get them from?
He's not dancing, do you think...
Tell me which one you like.
- It's lovely.
- Which one?
Be quiet.
What is it?
- Nothing. You have a lovely figure.
- Really? Thanks a lot.
- What's going on, Carina?
- Nothing.
Which one shall I wear?
Go!
I am sorry, I am so sorry. Please.
Daddy, I was thinking
about this one for the cake.
Why don't you ask my friend Miss Pak?
- You look pretty in anything.
- Thank you.
I liked the one you wore earlier.
Then maybe I'll put it back on.
These girls...
- Have you seen...
- I've seen nothing,
but you've seen my daughter undressed.
Being in charge of security doesn't
mean you can charge in anywhere.
He's out of his mind!
All right now, ladies.
Don't take too long.
My bedroom's here.
What does your bedroom look like?
Quick. They're waiting
for me for the cake.
Your room is huge!
I find it much too big
since my wife's death.
Please.
This is beautiful!
It's just a normal office
for a colonial service man.
I only own the paintings,
all the rest belong to the Government.
So you can't give me a souvenir?
I just bought them.
So they're not framed.
- May I see them?
- If you'd like to, sure.
Of course. I bought this in London.
I liked it very much when I saw it.
- I like it very much, too!
- I'm sure you'll like the other one.
Let me get it for you.
Besides being a collector,
do you paint?
Yes, I do. I paint sometimes.
But I'll be embarrassed
to show them to people.
And you? What do you like
to paint most?
- Chinese landscapes mostly.
- Really? I love Chinese landscapes.
But I don't know much about them.
I have two more somewhere,
but I can't remember where I put them.
They're not here.
They might still be in the box.
Don't worry if you can't find them.
We've got time,
the cake's not ready yet.
They're not here. Strange.
Maybe they haven't arrived yet.
Don't move!
- Hold it!
- What's going on?
- Thief, sir.
What's happening?
- What are you doing?
- There's been a theft!
Damn!
What a lovely cake!
It's so big.
Yeah.
It's beautiful.
I'm sorry.
Stay where you are.
I'm sorry, everyone.
You're under arrest.
- Me?
- What's going on?
He can't deny it. I saw him
stealing something in the study.
Somebody's stolen the necklace
I bought for Regina's birthday.
He's the one.
You're accusing me of stealing?
And the evidence?
You better search him.
He has a number of accomplices,
I doubt he still has it on him.
Dragon, if you make accusations,
you'd better be able to back them up.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we don't like this any more than you.
But to prove your innocence,
I'm sure you won't mind
a search by one of my officers.
- You want to search me?
- If you're innocent, you won't mind.
Needless to say,
you'll start with me.
However, to be fair
I think we should start with Mr Ma.
All right.
Chun, can you search him?
Chief, it's better if you do it.
Right, if you wish.
It's part of the diamond necklace.
Where did you get this?
Someone must have set him up.
Mr Ma really is a wonderful actor.
Ladies and gentlemen, this was all
part of the evening's entertainment.
However Mr Ma is such a good actor,
he fooled everyone present.
I just hope everyone enjoyed it.
- Daddy!
- A surprise.
- You almost scared me to death.
- Let's have the cake.
You really arranged everything, sir?
Of course not. Where's the necklace?
I've no idea, sir.
Then what is this doing
in your pocket?
I demand an explanation!
So it wasn't a game?
- Did it look like a game to you?
- No, I suppose it didn't.
- What now?
- I should be asking that.
- You're the policeman.
- Arrest him.
- But, sir...
- Shut up! It's an order.
I expect you to get to the bottom
of this and quickly.
Take him away.
- You have to make a wish.
- All right.
Did you set Dragon up with
the necklace that night?
I don't know much about that,
but he's innocent.
He's a nice person.
We had to do it for the good
of the country, don't forget.
Hot dumplings!
- Do you want some dumplings?
- All right.
What do you want in them?
Carina.
Where are you?
Maggie, what's the matter?
- My cousin has disappeared.
- What?!
- She just disappeared into thin air.
- Really?!
She won't talk, but I found this.
Go to this address,
see if you find the others.
Yes, sir!
- You must avoid the police.
- Yes, sir.
You're in big trouble
if the Chief finds out.
Not if we find the necklace.
Why do you think Carina's involved?
She and Man were dancing all evening.
Sir! I have a release order here.
I'm allowed to take him out.
Is this your first day?
You've forgotten the handcuffs.
Sorry.
I'll keep this with me for safety.
- What's up?
- We don't have to show everybody.
Let's go and see the warden.
All I want is for the prisoner to be
taken down the road towards the sea.
After that,
you'll never need to work again.
- It's really that simple?
- It's that simple.
It's a deal.
Anyone here?
With any luck, she'll be back by now.
Be quiet!
Carina. Carina!
Oh, no. I can't find her anywhere.
- I wonder who kidnapped her.
- Sometimes it's better not to know.
It's her!
You two again.
- Right. Any news of Carina?
- She's not back yet. And you?
We're still working on it.
Hold on, I'll finish changing.
- Who is it?
- Dragon and his man.
It's about the necklace.
I'd better hide.
- Any ideas?
- It's linked to the necklace case.
- That's right.
- Are you involved?
That's what the Commissioner
told us to say.
- Does your cousin know a Mr Man?
- No, she doesn't.
Sit down, please.
- We're like brothers.
- Yeah.
- Do you need to go the bathroom?
- No.
- But you said you needed to.
- When?
Yeah, I did say that.
- Where's the bathroom?
- The bathroom?! Over there.
- Thanks.
- I only have one bathroom.
- We always go together.
- Yeah, since we were kids.
- All clear?
- They're in the bathroom.
All right. I'm leaving now.