Alright it's the final match of the
season ladies and gentlemen...
And as we approach the finish, it's still not clear
which team is going to lift the champions cup...
Two minutes to go... and the
score stands at 1 all...
The Rangers have the ball and are dribbling
through... Is this going to be a goal?
But just as I say that, Dev Saran
has intercepted them...
...and has possession.
My God! Look at him go...
He's moving closer and closerto the goal...
Just look at him go.
Dev Saran looks determined...
Is this going to be the decider?
Oh my God! He's underthe D...
he's through... he's through them all...
Is that going to be a penalty?
That definitely should be a penalty...
If that's a penalty... the Rangers probably just
threw the game away...
Good morning Sir. The limousine is
ready forthe wedding.
What wedding?
Your wedding, Sir...
Shit! Maya's going to kill me...
Maya... Maya... come on hurry up...
The groom will be here at one...
Yes... I'm married... and I have a son...
And just to make it clear...
I keep my personal life...
...and professional life separate...
That's all very well Mrs. Saran...
But ourfashion magazine needs a lot of time...
Your magazine does not need time... It needs me!
Yes? - Who are you?
Whoeveryou want me to be, honey...
Dad! Dad!
Hey... - Dude... What are you doing?
Sorry son... Just a little... tied up...
Oh God... da... And how did this break?
I'll teach you how... I will... hello darling...
I'm leaving Sam... and forthe record
that was the best ever...
Oh thanks...
I'll call you... - Yeah... call me... call me...
Bye sweetheart...
Amazing isn't it, when a call girl calls you...
call girl... calls you...
Dad! I'm getting married today and you...
What do I do, my son?
Before dying your Mom made me
promise that after she goes...
...I should do all that I never did
while she was alive...
I'm just fulfilling my promise...
And what about the promise I made to Maya?
Can I fulfill that?
Of course... Why not? - Can we go?
Just a minute... just a minute...
This is from me...
And this from your Mom... God bless you...
Hello... - Dev... I got the job...
What? - I got the job!!
Wow... That's amazing... You got the job...
Guys... Rhea got the job...
What is this noise? I can't hear a thing...
Nothing... Nothing at all...
Just a small match that we won...
Oh yeah! The match... of course...
I'm so sorry... I forgot completely...
Rhea, I'm your husband...
just don't forget that...
Shut up, Dev... And congratulations baby...
Tell me how was it?
Fantastic... My last goal...
All that tension... excitement...
God... Rhea... Rhea, you should have been here...
Yeah... I know...
But I had an interview...
I know sweetheart...
I know... You know what...
We'll fix up the next match after
checking with your busy schedule...
Dev...
And if you have the time just have a look...
...at my five million dollar contract...
Five million dollars?
Why? Jealous?
That now I earn more than you?
Not jealous baby... Happy...
Happy that your dream has come true...
Our dream, Rhea...
Yeah I know... By the way I'm going to fetch
Arjun from school...
Will you please fetch Mom
from the wedding?
God... I completely forgot that...
What's the matter, Rhea?
You seem to be forgetting a lot these days...
Yeah! That's true...
And by the way, Happy Anniversary!
Shit... Happy Anniversary!
Hey guys... My son's getting married...
My son's getting married...
Today I'm going to part with my daughter
and get a daughter-in-law home...
Hey Maya... We are coming...
I'm the happiest guy in the wor...
Hey, what's with you?
Dude... I'm nervous... - Why?
It's taken herthree years to say 'yes'...
She won't run away at the last minute,
will she?
No... No...
She can't run away anywhere...
Yeah... After all where will she
find a husband like me, right?
No... Our security is very tight...
Move it... Move it...
We are already running late...
Oh my God! Chris...
Why are you serving this now?
This is not a dip... It's dessert...
It's called suji ka halwa...
Who Suzie? - Not Suzie...
Give it to me... come on... Go...
Go into the kitchen...
They'll drive me mad...
All the idiots from New York...
God... That scared me...
- Didn't mean to...
Hello... - Hello...
I'm Sam... And this is my house...
I'm Kamal, and this is my food...
Really... may I?
Wow... Definitely a sardarni...
How did you know that?
Because I have been fed
and slapped by them...
I know...
I have heard a lot about you...
Don't go by what others say...
But all that's said is always
by others, Mr. Talwar...
Whose word does one go by then?
Mine... My word...
You are from chandigarh...
And how did you figure that out?
Definitely chandigarh...
Mom... What are you doing?
Just... Nothing...
Ready to go?
No... I don't know what's
taking the bride so long...
You carry on... I'll come on my own...
Are you sure?
- Yeah... You go...
Excuse me... excuse me...
Please don't mess the garden...
I have just cleaned it up...
Are you the gardener?
- What do you think?
I think you have stolen the bride's clothes...
Should I inform inside?
Could you please leave me alone?
- Of course... not...
It's your wedding and you are
sitting outside here... Why?
Do you have a problem?
Not directly... But indirectly I do...
My mother has a problem...
The fasteryou go inside,
the faster my mother can leave from here...
You are a strange man...
You sat down?
Should I lie down and chat?
One to one discussions always
happen sitting down... - Discussion?
Yes... I know you have a problem...
come on... Talk to me...
Tell me your problem...
Why should I discuss
my problem with you?
So you admit you have a problem...
By the way, I don't take advice from anyone...
...but I'm always ready
to give advice to others...
You should always listen to strangers...
Sometimes they know betterthan our own...
Are you married?
Einstein... It's five years today...
What did you think before marrying?
Who thinks before marrying?
Just kidding...
Rhea and me, are friends from college...
So we thought we'd give our
friendship a new meaning...
...besides what can be betterthan spending...
...your entire life with yourfriend?
At times friendship replaces love and
then there's no space left for love...
Yeah... yeah...
By the way, the guy waiting foryou inside...
...is he yourfriend oryour love?
You can't take that long...
I have known Rishi since childhood...
After my parents died, Rishi
and his father have been my family...
Oh... What a sweet family...
But that's not the answerto my question...
Do you love him?
I do...
But not the way I thought I would...
Like how? Like in good books and bad films?
That kind of love?
No... The way love ought to be...
That kind of love...
But where does it exist anymore?
Listen to this...
'The sagas of everlasting romances
have gone past long ago...
Just learn to make do
with tiny love stories...'
Does that mean you don't love your wife?
You can't take that long...
We are happy...
We have made our little world together...
That's not the answerto my question...
The question here is more
about your life than my answer...
You are at a crossroad in life
where there are two roads...
One that leads to happiness,
which I think you deserve...
...and the otherthat leads
to an endless wait...
Wait for love...
Which you may neverfind...
What if I find that love after marriage?
If you don't look for it...
you won't find it...
And you are definitely not finding
it sitting on this bench...
Go inside and get married...
The wedding is waiting foryou...
...and here you are sitting
with a stranger making small talk...
You should be ashamed...
What will people say?
Shame on you... Go on... go...
go and get married... Go...
It was nice talking to you...
Well... I'd rather be playing football...
But it was a pleasure to meet you, Ma'am...
Maya...
Dev... Dev Anand... bad one...
Now go fast, get married and be happy...
Good bye... Sayonara... Goodbye...
Not good bye...
Goodbye kills the hope of meeting again...
And who knows?
We may meet again...
[Skipped item nr. 178]
Just like fragrance merges into breeze...
And fades away...
Intense moments, with time...
Have a way of seeming like dreams...
Who knows? We may meet again yet...
You should never say goodbye...
Never say goodbye...
They say time heals all wounds...
But in some relationships,
some wounds only get deeper with time...
Do you guys have a permit forthis? Damn...
Ready? Black Beast...
That's the new fearthat stalks New York...
Known as the Black Beast,
this dangerous criminal has kidnapped...
...yet another child from central Park...
No one knows if it is a man or a woman...
He's nicknamed Black Beast...
...because the criminal wears
a trademark long, black coat...
Shit...
Don't cry my son...
don't cry... I'm right here...
What the... What are you doing?
Sitting on my leg...
Sorry sir... Please don't mind...
My Tinu here is just a little nervous...
...he thinks the Black Beast
is going to kidnap him...
Please don't mind sir... please...
Why should I mind?
My leg's already broken...
Oh Tinu... my small, fat little angel...
...the Black Beast will not kidnap you...
To kidnap you he has to lift you first...
And have you looked at your weight?
My little fatso... Your son's not a child...
he is a pig... pig!
What?
...and with God's blessing
even if he manages to lift him...
...he will die of a heart attack...
Mummy! - Mummy!
You mean she's still alive?
How did she survive
the weight of yourfather?
How rude! - Rude?
You football field!
Just pick this football of yours
and leave right now...
come on... let's go...
we don't want to sit here...
come on go...
You should have asked before sitting...
And by the way, does your entire family
everfit in a single photograph?
Should we go?
You know I'll leave when you want to...
What's the need to ask?
God... Dev...
Ijust asked a simple question...
God... Rhea...
Even I didn't answer in French...
I'm going home...
Good... very good...
Do you know the way home?
Yes Dev... I know the way...
Ijust don't know you anymore...
It's strange... No one seems to have a
sense of humourthis morning...
come on... let's go... together...
Maya... Maya... Maya... MAYA!
What is it?
- The house will collapse if you clean
Rishi...
What? - Take off your pants...
Take off what? - Your pants...
Here? - Where then?
But why? - Why?
I know why... Oh my God...
come on, Rishi... Quickly...
I don't have time...
I know...
I've always wanted to do this in the kitchen...
It's been a dream...
- Yeah... Mine too...
Wow! - Fast...
Hello...
Now it's yourturn... - Why?
Why? Then how are we...?
Lt'll be kind of tough...
Rishi...
I don't have to remove anything...
...because my clothes have no stain...
Stain?
Yes... Stain... A big one...
And you were all set to go out with it...
Maya...
When will you stop being my
mother and be my wife?
When you stop being my child and
become my husband...
If I stop being your child
who will you motherthen?
What happened?
Nothing...
Since I can't have children of my own...
...I should think of you as my child, right?
Oh come on, Maya...
You know that's not what I meant...
I really don't care about that...
- Here... Take this... It's gone...
Thank you...
Listen...
Tonight's the Sanderson Hotel opening...
What time do you want to go?
- I'm not coming...
Maya... If I go alone everywhere people
will think there's a problem...
I don't care about people...
- And me?
Look, Rishi...
This night life, events, parties...
I don't belong to that part of your life...
Then which part of my life
do you belong to, Maya?
Which part of my life
do you belong to, Rishi?
When was the last time we did
something that I wanted?
You want to clean the house...
And that really isn't my idea of an
ideal weekend babe...
Then babe... What's your idea?
Actually my ideal weekend
would involve a lot of...
Ok... come... let's discuss it...
Whoa... Discussion... No... No... bye!
- Why? - No...
This is great! You start something
and then don't want to pursue it...
Rishi, I want to discuss...
Rishi... Rishi!
You are such a child!
Maya!
Congratulations, Rhea...
- For what?
The figures just came in...
Diva is America's No.2 fashion magazine...
Thanks to you...
come on, Rhea... let's celebrate...
Hold on guys... One minute... One minute...
there will be no celebrations...
We will celebrate when DIVA
becomes the No.1 fashion magazine...
So pull up your stockings ladies...
'cos you have more late nights...
more hard work...
And if your husbands leave you...
Trust me, you are better off...
...back to work!
Hey, Rhea... Wait up...
Ijust spoke to the London head office and
we think you should move there... - Really?
Yeah... So that you can control all the fashion
magazines in the group...
But isn't this all a bit too...
Rhea... Rhea... Rhea... Do you even
understand the meaning of all this?
This will be the biggest move
of your career...
No, Jai... This will be a big move
foryour company...
You know what?
You are something else...
You are intelligent, confident, beautiful...
Just one problem... You are married...
But anyway married or unmarried...
How does it matterthese days... Right?
It matters to me, Jai...
What is he doing here?
When I have said that we are not
organizing the party, why is he here?
But Rishi, what can I do?
He refuses to leave...
He says he won't go till we agree...
What do you mean he won't leave?
- He's even threatening to sue us...
Sue... Who is he to...?
Excuse me... Excuse me...
Yes...
Dude... I have already told you, I'm not
organizing this party...
But why?
You organize parties forthe whole world...
Why can't you do it foryourfather?
The whole world hasn't had two heart attacks...
Give some thought to your age...
What's age?
Just look at my heart...
Ask the beauties around...
they think I'm a rockstar!
Dad! Before you embarrass
me any further, please go...
Hey... Listen...
Why are you being so difficult?
It's just a simple party to be organized...
Just give me a sixties setting, the best wine
and a hundred beautiful girls... That's all...
And what do you plan to do
with hundred girls?
What? - Right... - Yeah!
I want to know...
Why do you throw this party every year?
Now look... That is not your problem...
Just organize this party and
my red Ferrari is yours...
Dude... If you think you can
buy me out by bribing me...
You are absolutely right...
I love that car... - Yeah!
What do you want the girls to wear?
- Nothing! - Done...
Good morning... soccer moms
and soccer dads... get ready...
Ourfirst team today are the seven time
winners from Westside High...
The Tigers...
coached by George Push...
with a lovely tusch...
Playing against the Tigers are the...
...tiny little
coochie-coo, oh-they're-so-cute, Dolphins...
coached by Dev Saran...
What's wrong?
Your wife's still paying the bills?
No... Now yours is...
The match is about to begin...
Where are you going, idiot?
Go... - No... - Yes...
Hit... Arjun... Hit...
Yes...
Your ball...
Happy?
I'm sorry... I'm sorry... Papa... I'm sorry...
I don't want to play football...
I want to play the violin...
What? You want to play the violin?
Wear a dress from tomorrow...
You will look perfect... Don't do that...
Just shut up...
Hi... Hi, Your Highness...
Your son has lost the match again...
Looks like he's taken after his father...
Let's celebrate...
Dev... Please...
Stop taking your anger out on him...
He'd probably have won
if you coached him well...
We'd probably have won if you
were here to boost our morale...
can I speak to him please?
Yeah of course... It's the Queen Motherforyou...
come on... come on...
Mama... You have to be there forthe
next match... You never come...
Yes sweetheart...
Next time I'll be there for sure...
Guess what?
Mama's got you a new playstation...
Play station? Wow... I love you Mom...
Wow, Mom... I love you... Playstation?
If they are selling some time
at the toy shop please buy that...
Arjun needs that a little more...
Dev... You... What's your problem?
Tansen... I'm going to buy the tickets...
If you move from here, I will slap you...
Let's go home and I'll make you wear a dress...
Ok, Tanya... Now listen to me...
Stay close to me all the time...
I read about the Black Beast this morning...
We never know where he might
be lurking in his black coat...
Now hold my hand... is it clean?
Good girl... Should we go here?
Orthere? Who should I ask?
I saw you my beloved...
And it dawned on me how crazy love can be...
Me?
I saw you my beloved...
Here I come Simran... Here I come...
Thank you, Maya... I really owe you one...
Not at all... She's a real sweetheart...
Black Beast... When will they nab him?
Got you... I told you not to move from there...
Then why did you move?
You kids have really troubled me today...
Specially you...
You know what I am going to do to you?
I'm going to cut you into tiny pieces...
...and put them in a mixerto make Jamba juice...
I like children's Jamba juice...
Shut up... idiot...
Black Beast!
- Are we going to stand here all day?
Come with me now... and don't you
dare get lost again... come...
I don't know why children are born at all...
Why can't humans be born full grown?
I'm taking you to your Papa...
I won't let anything happen to you...
The next time you lose, I'm going to...
Arjun...
Arjun
Black Beast!
Give me a minute here... come now... Run!
Maya!
She's become the Black Beast?
But why are you crying?
I thought I was being kidnapped...
I don't have such good fortune that
someone will kidnap you...
Should I kill you?
- No... - Quiet then...
Sir... You will have to come with us...
- I will officer...
I hate you, Black Beast!
E.R.! Patient with a leg injury...
Patient in trauma... be prepared...
Be prepared... patient with leg injury...
On the way...
Make way... make way...
Patient with leg injury here...
...make way...
Excuse me... I have a leg injury...
Oh my God... get him...
Take the child...
- Take him and keep him...
Sir, do you have a leg injury?
- Yes... No... I used to have a leg injury...
You're in trauma... lay down... lie down...
calm down... calm down
we're here to help you...
Arjun... tell the fatso...
calm down!
Don't touch my ass!
I am going to kill you...
I am going to save you...
God bless you...
Don't touch my... Mummy!
Arjun... Papa loves you...
can I help you?
I'm here to see the Black Beast...
My wife...
Hi... Excuse me... I'm so sorry...
All this is my husband's fault...
Your husband is the Black Beast?
No... he's just a beast...
But all's well now... Your wife is
fine now... Just a minor sprain...
Thank God... Rishi Talwar...
Rhea Saran...
Rhea Saran? The Diva from DIVA...
Guilty as charged...
Wow... Small world... I run a small
PR firm - Kamakaze...
I've been trying to meet you for a while...
It's not easy meeting me...
Trust me, it's even more difficult to avoid me...
So sorry to disrupt your
wonderful conversation...
But if you'd like to see your husband and
your wife... they're in room 502...
We tranquilized you by mistake...
We're so sorry forthe confusion...
Are you ok?
Does your mother love you? - Yes...
'cause she's really gonna miss you...
I'm going to kill you...
My lawyer will call you...
My lawyer will speak with you...
And my lawyer will speak to you...
You... I know you...
Even I remember... We've met before...
Now I can't walk for a week because of you...
I can't walk for life because of you...
What?
If I hadn't met you, my life
would have been different...
My pain would have been different...
And if I hadn't met you
I wouldn't have married...
Wouldn't have married?
Is that a good thing or a bad thing?
Good... - Good? - Bad... - Bad?
I mean... I don't know...
I don't know?
Are you happy?
You can't take that long...
- Who are you to ask me all this?
You can't answer a question with a question...
Why should I bother about your questions?
Why should I answeryou? Who are you?
Who am I?
I'm the father of the child you were
running away with...
Don't you have your own children?
Oh...
...you don't...
Yes... I don't have any...
I can't have them...
I teach children...
I'm a motherto all of them...
Mother India...
Teaching children... Running away with them...
...are you able to fill your emptiness with all this?
Because your life is empty... incomplete...
It shows in your eyes... Just like in mine...
Dev...
Mama... - Oh, Rhea...
Why did you take the trouble?
You are so considerate...
I'm beginning to feel pressurized
by your niceness...
Dev, please... it's been a really long day...
I apologise on his behalf...
I'm so so sorry... Once again...
Rhea, look... It's cool... It's cool...
It's cool...
We haven't met... Rishi...
Rishi Kapoor?
No... Husband...
Nobody's perfect...
My head is spinning... Bye bye...
Sayonara... Goodbye...
No good bye...
Goodbye kills all hope of meeting again...
And who knows? We might meet again...
Dev... No one ever wants to meet you again...
Ok... Bye...
Ok... Nice meeting you... Bye...
Is he on drugs?
There you go... Not to worry, Maya...
...the doctor has said you'll
be fine in two to three days...
Afterthat it's back to your normal exercise...
Dusting, cleaning, vacuuming,
brushing... - Shut up!
Sorry...
God... Not you... It's that...
What was his name?
Dev... he was talking nonsense...
...and did you see how he was talking to his wife?
He's so rude...
Maya... Not all husbands can be
as good as me...
To keep my heart at yourfeet...
Love you all day long...
God, Maya...
You are so sexy...
Tonight I'm going to...
Maya...
Maya!
Hi...
You?
Of course not... It's someone else...
What a strange question!
You? Who else will I be?
Whatever... I'm glad you are here...
- Were you thinking of me?
Yes... I've been thinking of you for a week...
Listen all that I said that day
was because of the injection...
I'm married... And to think of a married
man in that way is a sin...
You talk rubbish... - Yeah!
I wanted to meet you to say that the
things you said to me that day...
...are true... And the truth is always bitter...
You are bitter!
Not the truth... And who are you?
The Supreme court?
To pass judgements on others' lives?
I'm not listening to this...
- Just listen to me...
I'm not... - Just listen...
OK...
Listen... I'm very happy... Thank you...
You should think about your own life...
I'm sure your life is empty...
and your dreams, unfulfilled...
That's why you keep searching
forthe same in others' lives...
You are an unhappy man
and will always be...
You are a beautiful woman
Maya... Maya... Just listen...
We are both alike... very alike...
I'm sorry...
We travel from the same station...
Both teach children...
Both of us are wounded...
It's just that my wounds show... yours don't...
And we can discuss our sad lives over coffee...
No Thank you...
My husband's waiting for me at home...
Well... Even Rhea must be home by now...
Hey!
Hey! Dude! What's going on here?
What went on is over now...
come on, Dad... This is my house...
Just chill... chill... chill son...
We were just passing by and
so we thought we'd just...
...you know... rock n roll...
If Maya arrives now she will kill me...
Papa is going to kill me...
Today was the music class
so I bunked football...
No, my child... Nothing will happen...
I'll take care of it...
No, grandma... he's going to kill me...
Why will he kill you?
You are learning the guitar
and that's a good thing...
Not guitar, Mom... violin...
Oh... violin... I don't understand
why he is so scared of Dev...
But Mom, you don't understand...
- No darling you relax...
But Mom...
Shut up! Nothing's going to happen...
I'll tell Dev that you are not well... Ok?
Ok...
Why should we lie?
We'll just get back to you darling...
Now come on go upstairs and grandma...
...will give you a nice hot water bath later...
Good boy...
Shit... Maya has come...
Please hide this one somewhere?
In my arms?
Dad... Just put some clothes on...
Ok... ok...
Mom... he's come...
Hi!
How was your day? Do you know...
I know... I know everything...
Everything? No... I think you...
Please... watch it... Don't try to hide
from me I know everything...
Yes... I know... I saw it with my eyes...
Did you hearthat? She knows everything...
Look at this...
And we were trying to hide from her...
Dad! Even you know?
What do you mean when did I know?
It was my idea to make an excuse...
Now the poorfellow is hiding
in the bathroom...
What? He's in my bathroom?
She is in my bedroom?
Don't go in... Poorthing...
She's not wearing any...
What is she doing without clothes?
What do you do without clothes?
I will not let him live...
I'm going to... What are you doing?
Dev... listen... please... Stop it, Dev!
I pray to you... he's already too scared
I'm going to him now...
Why? - To give him a bath...
So now you will bathe him?
That too in my bathroom...
The bathroom doesn't belong to just you...
It's mine too... he will use it...
Both of us will bathe him...
Oh yeah... Sure! - Shut up!
How could you do this?
Aren't you ashamed?
But what have I done?
Please... Please... You two stop fighting...
I'm taking herto my house...
Why would you take herto your house?
Because I paid her...
- She takes money?
Yeah... Nothing comes forfree these days...
By the way what's the rate these days?
Per day or weekends? - Weekends...
Let's see now... the last time... - Stop!
Both of you have gone crazy!
No, Dev... You are crazy...
Look at what you are doing...
I can't take this anymore...
I'm sleeping with him tonight...
Me too... - You too?
Have some shame...
Look at his age and yours...
You look at your age...
Don't cross your limits...
Mommy! What about your limits?
The two of you... both...
Yes? - Disgusting...
And she... I will not spare her... Rhea...!
Rhea?
Rishi...
Rishi?
I'm so hot, I am so hot, hot, hot, hot...
Rhea... Rhea...
Oh God! Rishi?
He was just inviting me for his Dad's party...
...so that I can see his work...
It's just a PR exercise, Dev...
What about the flowers?
Rhea sent them foryou...
Oh God... This confusion...
Where are you going, baby?
And who is this?
This? This is your motherto be...
I don't believe this...
You thought I was having
an affair with Rishi?
What's with you, Dev? You are crazy...
I'm crazy? I thought you were crazy...
I mean, what's happened to yourtaste?
The next time you want to
have an affair let me know...
I will look forthe right guy...
After all, you have to maintain a standard,
the great Rhea Saran...
Dev... Don't try to hide yourfeelings with...
...your stupid sense of humour...
You were jealous and I love it...
Yeah right!
This just means that somewhere
there is a little love left... Right?
Yes... very deep inside...
come on get ready... I'm ready to go...
You are coming wearing this?
No... I'm taking this off and coming nude...
No, Dev... Why don't you wearthe
suit that I bought last week...
Why sweetheart? Embarrassed?
Embarrassed, that I'm wearing this?
Embarrassed, that in these clothes...
...I won't look like the rich and famous
Rhea Saran's husband?
I'm sorry to disappoint you, Rhea...
...but even new clothes are not
going to make me new...
Even I love the old Dev...
but he is lost somewhere...
You are the one who lost him...
Maya!
What are you doing, Rishi?
I'm celebrating!
Celebrating what?
My wife's jealous...
I got some reaction at last...
God, Rishi... Stop behaving like a child...
...We are getting late... come on...
Maya...
Rishi... We are getting late...
Please go and change your clothes...
Tell me something... What if I was
really having an affair?
What would you do? - Rishi...
come on... Humour me... - Rishi...
Please...
Ok... If you were truly having an
affair I would think... analyse...
...try to find out why it happened...
And then I would discuss it with you...
Discuss with me?
Come on woman, show some passion...
Say that you would scream... shout...
...weep hysterically... Some drama...
Drama? If you wanted drama you
should have married an actress...
But you settled for a boring teacher...
So sorry...
Oh God, Maya... you are so touchy...
Then why do you say such things?
- I was just kidding...
What if I was having an affair?
What would you do?
Your affair? Fantastic... very good!
What was so funny?
What do you mean what's funny?
You can't handle one relationship...
How will you manage two?
But anyway I like the attitude... keep at it...
I'm going to get ready... See ya...
What's the matter, Rishi?
I can't handle a relationship...
No passion... No drama...
I'm not a good wife... can't be a mother...
Since I have so many flaws
why don't you leave me?
Both of us have flaws, Maya...
But the difference is that you always talk...
...about breaking the relationship...
...and I talk about making it work...
Please make sure there's
service everywhere... ok?
And why is nobody serving in that corner?
Come on, come on, please move it... Oh, hello...
Hello there... Long time no see...
Just as well...
Incidentally hasn't the size
of chandigarh increased...
...since the last time we met...
It's the number in your eye
that has increased, Mr. Talwar...
Hello... Aren't you going to introduce
me to your daughter?
Daughter? Maybe yours... Meet Saturday...
Saturday?
Yeah... I can't remember all their names...
...so I call them by the day I meet them...
yeah baby?
Yeah!
Yeah right... See you later gorgeous...
Who's that? - My mother...
Ah! Rhea... thanks for coming...
Of course we had to come...
By the way the sixties theme is a great idea...
It's all so beautiful...
No... No... You are beautiful darling... hello...
I'm Rishi's father... in every way...
And I'm Rhea's husband...
in almost every way...
Oh...
Do you like my suit? Do you like it?
Rhea... You look gorgeous...
Thank you...
I really think we should have that affair...
Sure... I know for a fact that my
husband will not object...
Neither will my wife...
as long as we sit and discuss it later...
Right, darling?
Oh, wow...
You guys have discussions at home?
In our case we have to meet by appointment...
I think I need a drink...
Ah super... Let's all get drunk...
Rhea?
Super...
Do you know a good divorce lawyer?
I hate these parties...
I think these parties are organized
to touch other people's wives...
Don't even think about that...
Don't worry...
I haven't reached such desperate days...
Look at them... Just look at them...
Oh my darling...
Mwaah... Mwaah... Mwaah...
You know... I have just realized that
not only do I hate parties...
I hate people...
As far as I know, even people
aren't crazy about you...
Not that they are crowding
around you either...
It doesn't make a difference to me...
They are all strangers...
Even your husband?
Rishi...
Fair skinned faces...
Moon lit faces...
Dark long tresses...
Sky blue eyes...
Fair skinned faces...
Moon lit faces...
Dark long tresses...
Sky blue eyes...
They weave dreams...
They lead you astray...
Take away your sanity...
They drive you crazy...
They ignite a fire...
Intoxicate your being...
Rock and roll, my love
My heart sings foryou...
Rock and roll, my love...
come sway with me...
Rock and roll, my love
My heart sings foryou...
come sway with me...
These lithe bodies...
These swaying hips...
First they attack the heart...
Then go foryour life...
These flashes of lightning...
These sorceresses of love...
I have seen many and yet fall prey...
They come... and they go...
At their whim and fancy...
These angels... these fairies...
At a mere glance from them...
The world can go crazy...
And be at theirfeet...
And yet these beauties...
Don't know what love is...
Rock and roll, my love
My heart sings foryou...
Rock and roll...
come sway with me...
Rock and roll, my love
My heart sings foryou...
come sway with me...
Head in a cap and a red scarf waving...
Oh... What do I say?
Fair skinned maiden
with a black strand on the face...
Oh... What do I say?
These pretty faces...
These beautiful women...
They don't know what love is...
Or what it is to be loyal...
These stonehearted lovers...
What do they care?
What we go through, coping with them?
They are ignorant... like strangers...
What do they know about feelings?
They don't know...
they don't care...
That hearts can break with words they say...
Like asking for comfort from fire...
Orfire from ice...
We have spent out entire lives...
Now we know what we lost...
Wasting ourtime that was precious...
Rock and roll...
My heart sings foryou...
Rock and roll, my love
come sway with me...
My heart sings foryou...
Rock and roll, my love
come sway with me...
Rock and roll
Fair skinned faces...
Moon lit faces...
Dark long tresses...
Sky blue eyes...
They weave dreams...
They lead you astray...
Take away your sanity...
They drive you crazy...
They ignite a fire...
Intoxicate your being...
Rock and roll, my love
My heart sings foryou...
Rock and roll, my love...
come sway with me...
Rock and roll, my love
My heart sings foryou...
Rock and roll, my love...
come sway with me...
Rock and roll, my love
My heart sings foryou...
Rock and roll, my love...
come sway with me...
Rock and roll, my love
My heart sings foryou...
Rock and roll, my love...
come sway with me...
Maya... Rishi...
And all you wonderful people...
Thank you for being here with me tonight...
And I hope that all of you are
having a great time... yeah!
Yeah!
You know, people always ask me
why I throw this party every year...
What's so special about this day?
The day is special...
It's on this day that I met my
wife forthe first time...
That's why, every year, I celebrate...
...this day and also seek herforgiveness...
Forgiveness for each day...
...when I chose my dreams
over my relationships...
Forgiveness for each minute when...
...I hurt her and didn't even
botherto make up...
But, most of all, forgiveness for
all those innumerable moments...
...when I forgot to tell her
how much I loved her...
...assuming that I will have a
lot of time to say so...
But I was wrong...
With her death I lost that time...
That's why I always say
that time means 'now'...
If you have to love, love 'now'...
If you have to ask forforgiveness, ask 'now'...
If you want to hold hands, hold it 'now'...
Or else years lateryou will find
yourself at a party like me...
...asking forforgiveness from your beloved...
So...
All you wonderful married couples out there...
Look to your partner and tell them 'I love you'...
And all of you that are single...
Turn this way... Girls only...
And tell me that... Alright... Ok...
This speech is getting really boring...
Let's party... come on guys...
Hit it... Eh chandigarh...
Last night I encountered
the real Samarjit hidden...
...behind 'Sexy Sam'...
I liked him...
Really? And what was the difference
between Sam and Samarjit?
Sam runs after girls and Samarjit,
after memories...
You really miss your wife very much...
Don't you? I can understand...
Tell me...
How do you cope with your loneliness?
I spend time with friends...
I have very few friends...
Not from today...
Oh... so you will be my friend?
Absolutely...
So... friendship means no touching?
All you are going to get is this...
Thank you... It's good for a start...
Mummy!
What... What are your intentions?
The intentions are very noble my son...
Just that I won't take dowry...
I'm anti dowry...
Mom... What is he saying?
Sam... What are you saying?
- Kamal... What is he saying?
What are all of you saying?
I'm scared to come out of the station...
You never know what you'll get to see...
Not only the station...
you should not get out of the house at all...
The world is evil...
Sam... Just a minute... Both of us...
Wow! So now it's 'us', huh?
Samarjit and I, are both alone...
We lost our love years ago...
And when two people are going
through the same phase...
...they understand each other better...
They become close...
What they can't say to others...
they can say to each other...
Precisely...
Two strangers... Same situation...
Then friendship...
and the problem is solved...
That's it... Simple... right, Maya? Cheers!
My marriage is failing, Dev...
And from what I can see, so is yours...
I can't save my marriage on my own...
I need a friend...
Afriend who will understand me...
who will make me understand...
Who is familiar with my circumstance...
And who can do this betterthan you?
That's why I'm here to extend
a hand in friendship...
Will you accept it?
I'm hurting, Maya...
I want to sit down...
And that's how two strangers came together...
...to save their relationships, and
gave birth to a new one...
On that rainy day, neither of us
saw the storm that awaited us...
Afterthat we met everyday...
I don't know why, but when I was
with Maya, I was different...
I had found my lost smile...
We had considerably increased the business...
...of the New York cafes quite a lot...
We spoke a lot about Rhea and Rishi...
How wrong they were...
How right we were... then how right
they were and how wrong we were...
But in relationships, no matter
who's right and who's wrong...
...someone has to make the first move...
And we decided it should be ours...
This is a very interesting book...
It says don't look foryour spouse's
faults in your marriage...
Improve your own flaws...
And what if someone's perfect?
Ya... Right... Anyway let's start with me...
...tell me all the things that are wrong with me...
And listen tell me the truth... be frank...
be honest... orthere's no point...
Alright... here goes... You are that teachertype...
Boring... with no personality...
You are a compulsive cleaner
to the point of illness...
...basically, you are a loyal maidservant...
What?
You don't have anything womanly in you...
You are not sexy...
Not from any angle...
Maybe from behind...
But no man will get excited looking at you...
I know your husband gets excited...
...but that's probably because
he is visually impaired...
because you don't have...
Dev... You are so rude... So mean...
What mean? Rude?
Didn't you just ask me to speak the truth?
But you could have said something nice...
But did you ask me to say something nice?
And what would you say if I had?
That your eyes are the most
beautiful eyes in the world...
But you didn't ask, so I didn't say...
You know what your problem is?
You don't know how to speak to a lady...
And you know how?
Yes... I know what to say to a woman and how...
Oh... So you are a lesbian?
Shut up...
I know because my husband says...
...the most romantic things to me everyday...
Any woman would go crazy listening to them...
Right... Except you of course...
- Listen... Do you want to learn or no?
Wow... This place has so many beds...
Maya, if you were so desperate, we
could have booked a hotel room...
Why have we come here?
Listen, Dev...
I have no time foryour sense of humour...
You have to learn a lot on this bed...
On this bed? What are the new things
you are going to teach me here?
Just so you know only my leg is broken...
All the other parts are absolutely perfect...
OK... This is not going to work...
No... Dev, serious... Serious...
Serious? - Yeah... serious...
Ok... the situation is that Rhea
has come back tired from work...
Now I will tell you what you need to do...
I'm Dev and you are Rhea... understand?
No... I don't but whatever...
Let's start... - Let's start...
Ok... Bouncy bouncy bed...
Start... - What? - Rhea...
Oh yeah... I'm Rhea...
Rhea would say...
As soon as she came home...
It's been a long tiring day!
I think you need a massage... - I do?
Here?
It feels good, huh?
Actually, it does... really...
You can't do this...
Oh, Rhea... You are so beautiful!
Rhea... Your eyes... Your lips...
...Your everything...
Oh! Your arms... I want to die in them...
Don't stop! No... no... Go...
come here... come here...
I'm taking this bed...
Please do...
Maya... Rishi... says and
does all these things to you...
And yet you don't... you... don't...
Actually, you are quite sexy... really...
You just need to show it to Rishi...
That's all...
What's this?
- This is my sister... - What?
We were separated as children... Maya...
You need to wear clothes like
these foryour husband...
No... Dev... If I wear clothes like these...
...I will look like 'that' type of a woman...
Yeah... That's the type that men like...
Dev... But that looks cheap...
Yeah... cheap... cheap is nice...
I like cheap! Maya...
You taught me how to talk to women...
how to massage them...
how to romance them...
If you want to learn how to be sexy...
then ask me... I'm the man...
Dev...
Don't worry... This will protect you...
But this...
But not that... 'Butt' this! That's the whip...
Hit me baby... hit me...
So dude... tell me...
Did you tell Maya about this last
minute football party?
You think she'd allow if I told her?
You are so dead, man!
Hey, Rhea... The head office is still
waiting foryour answer...
What have you decided?
I know, Jai, but please understand...
I know it will be the biggest move
for my career...
But to shift to London is not easy for me...
I have to think of too many things...
Anyway, can we talk about this tomorrow?
Ok... I'll call you... Thanks...
Hi...
Hello!
How was your day?
Nice...
God... I had a long tiring day...
Good... I mean... I think you need a
massage... baby...
Massage?
I'm going to be your masseur, Baby...
You like that? You like that?
I want to die in your arms...
Your ears... Yourforehead...
Your nose... your cheeks...
Your lips... All of it is... blue...
Dev... If this was a joke then it
really wasn't funny!
Maya!
Maya! Here I come! Best of luck...
Where are you? Where are you?
Where are you?
You've been a bad, bad, bad boy...
I'm going to hit you on your...
You're gonna like that... Won't you?
Come to me you naughty...
naughty... naughty... boy!
Where are you? Where are you?
Where are you?
We are all here!
Hello!
So what if we failed the first time?
We'll try again...
Try what? Marriage?
Not marriage... We'll try again...
you know this book says...
What are these books
that you keep reading?
'Fighting foryour marriage' bestseller
by Anna Marie Lou...
She knows a lot about marriages...
Of course she would...
She's married fourtimes...
Anna Marie Lou is out to cheat you...
Watch it... hey... one second...
Do you wanna fight foryour marriage?
I'm not married... I'm gay!
Good foryou...
You know Dev,
I have one more superb plan...
It'll be farfrom superb... It'll be a bullshit plan...
Don't you get tired?
I'm tired... Saving my marriage...
salvaging relationships...
I want a holiday from all that today...
I want to do something that I want to do...
There's a big football match today...
Ohio Extremes v/s chicago Rangers...
I want to see that...
I don't have tickets forthe match and
probably won't get them...
...yet I want to see it...
Will you come?
It's only football...
[Skipped item nr. 1077]
O my heart, just whisper in my ear
Which way are you headed?
What is it that you yearn for?
What is it that you seek?
All desires unsaid... All dreams unfulfilled
Spell them all out now...
My beloved...
What does your heartbeat sing?
Don't hide from your own dreams...
O my heart, just whisper in my ear
Which way are you headed?
What is it that you yearn for?
What is it that you seek?
All desires unsaid... All dreams unfulfilled
Spell them all out now...
My beloved...
What does your heartbeat sing?
Don't hide from your own dreams...
My beloved...
On this path of life...
On this path of love...
On this path of life... On this path of love...
You have set eyes on someone special...
You keep questioning...
You keep thinking...
Whetherthis is the one you pined for...
Yes, this is the one...
She is the one foryou...
You are a thirsty traveler and she is the river...
Why don't you accept it and say it to her...
All desires unsaid...
All dreams unfulfilled
Spell them all out now...
My beloved
What does your heartbeat sing?
My beloved...
Don't hide from your own dreams...
Dev... Do you know day after is both
our wedding anniversaries...
So I think we should do something special
for Rishi and Rhea... What do you think?
Maybe we should leave them...
That will be pretty special...
come on, Dev...
Maya... Maya... we will do
whateveryou want to do...
Your eyes have found their destination...
But yourfeet hesitate to take the step...
When your heart does a merry dance...
Why do you shackle yourfeet?
Dance to the tune of love you fool...
Let caution fly to the winds...
Why would you want to deprive your soul...
All desires unsaid... All dreams unfulfilled
Spell them all out now...
My beloved...
What does your heartbeat sing?
Don't hide from your own dreams...
O my heart, just whisper in my ear
Which way are you headed?
What is it that you yearn for?
What is it that you seek?
My beloved...
I'll take it...
Thank you, Dev...
Thank you...
This was our best anniversary ever...
Fantastic...
By the way, I want to tell you something...
The head office has offered me a promotion...
...they want me to shift to London...
It means a better position,
higher salary, big house...
...basically the works...
And this morning I decided that...
...that you will shift... Wow!
And of course there was
no need to consult me...
After all who am I? I'm just your husband?
What status do I have?
I'm just here to applaud foryour success...
This one decision of yours can
change all our lives...
But why would you think of that?
Because, Rhea Saran only
thinks about herself...
...her rocking career, her success,
her happiness... dammit...
It's always about you, you and you...
No goddamn it... It's about you,
you and only you, Dev...
I was just going to tell you that
I have refused the promotion...
Afterthinking about you... this family...
But where do you listen?
If you refused the promotion what
was the need to tell me?
Trying to show off your magnanimity?
I wasn't showing off, Dev...
I was baring my heart...
Do you have a heart, Rhea? What heart?
Arjun! Arjun! Stop that noise...
This is no time to play the violin...
It's time foryou to sleep...
You've got school tomorrow... Go now...
Don't touch the violin... get out of here...
Arjun! Arjun!
Why are you venting your anger on him?
What has he done?
Don't you dare tell me how I should
behave with Arjun, Rhea...
I know how to handle him...
I have brought him up...
Only I...
You had no time from your work...
Did you ever have time for him? Did you?
Yes Dev... I didn't have time...
because I work very hard...
No one asks men when they are busy...
...when they have no time fortheir children...
Then why are you asking me?
Tell me Dev, how can you ask me?
Because the truth is, that
I'm the man in this house...
I couldn't be Arjun's mother because
I had to be his father...
So that he could have all the happiness...
...that a football coach cannot
afford to give him...
How did that sound, Dev?
It hurts, doesn't it?
Now you know how it feels?
You have only hurt me, Dev...
I always thought you hurt those
you love the most...
But that's not true...
You don't love me at all...
You don't love anyone...
You only hate...
You hate yourself... your life... yourfailure...
And I haven't been able to figure out
what angers you more...
...yourfailure or my success!
Yes, Rhea... I'm a failure... That's true...
But do you know, there's a greater
failure than me in this house?
And that's our relationship... Our marriage...
Thank you, Rhea... Thank you, for letting me
stay in your house, Rhea...
Why are you so angry, Rishi?
What's the big deal if I didn't feel
like it one night?
Come on... Don't behave like a child!
Shut up! Just shut up! I have heard enough!
What's the problem, Rishi?
Maya... Do you rememberthe last time
we were intimate with each other?
When, Maya? When did we touch each other?
Held hands or embraced? Anything?
Do you remember?
When did we not turn our backs to each
other in bed? Do you remember?
I don't remember...
You don't remember or don't want to remember?
I don't want to discuss this...
Why? I thought you like discussions...
come on... let's discuss...
let's discuss why... Why my wife doesn't
want to sleep with me? Come on...
Our relationship cannot grow just
by sleeping with each other, Rishi...
It can only grow when we embrace
each other's sorrow and happiness...
And when was the last time
we did that? When, Rishi?
A husband and wife don't just share a bed...
they share their lives...
What? How dare you?
Do you think I'm the kind of man...
...who only feels the need for his wife in bed?
How dare you, Maya?
To embrace each other's happiness and pain,
one has to embrace each other...
And you have neverfelt that way about me...
'You are a child, you are a child,
you are a child...'
I'm fed up of hearing that...
If I was truly a child, I'd have
broken down long ago...
I tolerate you because I'm a man!
I have heard enough...
Today you cannot leave like this...
You will have to tell me today...
The truth... tell me... Why did you marry me?
Why? I married you because I love you...
But why did you marry me, Maya?
Tell me... Why did you marry me?
Rishi, leave me please... Rishi, please...
You are hurting me...
Rishi... Rishi... Rishi...
The truth, Maya, is that you never married me...
You compromised... I'm your
life's biggest compromise...
A compromise that you regret
every day of your life, right?
Give me an answer...
What answer?
You have nothing to give... Not love...
Not happiness... Not affection...
You haven't even been able to give me a child!
And Maya, I have never made you feel
inadequate about that... never...
You just did... Just did... Rishi...
Fouryears ago, you said that everlasting
romances don't exist anymore...
Remember, Dev?
Will you say the same even now?
Fouryears ago, you said that...
...if I don't look for love after
marriage I won't find it...
What will you say now, Dev?
What will you say?
Answer me...
What are you and me doing at the
station in the middle of the night?
What are we doing, Dev?
Answer... I need answers to
all these questions...
I don't know... - Tell me...
Where are you going, Dev?
I want the answers... tell me, Dev... tell me...
Answer... I want to know... tell me...
18th March 2002... You met me
forthe first time, Maya...
I rememberthe exact time, Maya...
Since that day I have felt like
I have known you forever...
Is this the answerto your question?
Maybe not... Maybe this...
Everyday yourtrain leaves the station at 4.32...
...and mine at 4.21... and everyday
I miss my train so...
...that I can spend some
more moments with you...
Is this the answerto your question?
Dev...
Everyday I leave you at the station but
yourthoughts don't leave me...
Is this the answerto your question?
Then try this... I'm a married man
Maya, and I think you forget...
...that you are too...
Since both of us are married...
...what are we doing at the station
in the middle of the night?
Bingo... Bingo... I think I have the answer...
That's the answerto your question, right?
Listen to the answer...
I love you, Maya...
...and you love me too!
Mom, why are we discussing this?
You are Dev's mother... you will take up for him...
I'm a woman before I'm a mother, Rhea...
And I know you are right...
But what happens just because I think so...
...the situation is not going to change...
Things will only change when Dev changes...
And that's not going to happen...
Rhea... Rhea...
Mom... please... I'm tired...
I've tried enough to understand him...
to get closerto him...
One fine day, he just decided to
step back from the relationship...
He did not step back, Rhea... You raced ahead...
You have to wait for him...
Why? Why is a woman always expected to wait?
Because they are stronger...
And have you thought about Arjun?
I'm not the kind of woman...
...who will use her child
as an excuse to back down...
I'm not that weak...
You are not weak...
Your relationship is...
You have to give it strength...
You have to give it time...
I will give this relationship nothing
till Dev gives it love...
You are going somewhere?
Paris... Forten days...
To organize a few events...
Last night the things you said to her...
Last night I said a lot of things
I shouldn't have...
...and a few that were very important to say...
Try to understand her, Rishi...
How do I understand a heart that
has no place for me?
That's not true, Rishi...
She loves you a lot...
Look into her eyes...
Who else can all that love be for?
I wish the love in her eyes reached
her lips once in a while...
Dad, everyday I tell her how much
I love her... has she ever said it?
Sorry, dad... I can't take it... Not anymore...
Now?
Now what, Dev?
It was important to say that we love
each other... So we've said it...
And what did we gain by saying it?
I don't know but if we hadn't,
we would have lost something...
You know Dev, that this
relationship has no future...
Yes... I know...
That's why it needs to be abandoned
on this beautiful note...
One last cup of coffee?
No...
Yourtrain...