Your girl is beautiful
Not the girl. Kuljit is plain lucky
And my name is Rajeshwari.
Miss Rajeshwari Singh
If the little one is like this,
what will the older one be like?
I’ll tell you, after the wedding
Listen
The day after tomorrow is the engagement
The wedding is on the 25th
Sweets
I'm worried about something
I don't know why I see this
sadness in Simran's eyes.
Even her smile is hesitant.
Is everything all right?
It's nothing, Ma
It's a new place, it's a change.
In a few days, she'll adjust
Don't worry for nothing
Here you are, kheer
Simran hasn't forgotten him yet?
- She has agreed to get married
By and by she will forget everything.
- If she remembers, she'll regret it
"I saw you, I realized..."
"what madness love is"
"When I saw you, I realized..."
"From here, where to?"
"Just let me die in your arms"
"My eyes... dream of you"
"My heart holds memories of you"
"Nothing's mine. It's all yours"
"My life, my breath is yours"
"When I weep for you, your tears..."
"my sorrows begin to smile"
"I saw you, I realized..."
"what madness love is"
"From here, where to?"
"Just let me die in your arms"
"I don't feel like anything"
"What do I say, what do I do?"
"In front of me... just keep sitting"
"Just let me look at you"
"You called out to me, and look, here I am"
"What greater than the promise to love?"
"I saw you, I realized..."
"what madness love is"
"From here, where to?"
"Just let me die in your arms"
Take me away from here, Raj.
Take me away from here!
What...?
- You don't know...
what's going on in there!
Day after tomorrow is the engagement
The wedding is after a fortnight.
All arrangements are in place
Babuji gave his word to his friend.
And he lives by his word
He can do anything, but he
can't go back on his word
We have to run from here. We must!
- No Simran. I'm not eloping
I haven't come here to steal you. I
might have been born in England
But I am Hindustani. I've come
here to take you as my bride.
I’ll take you only when your
Babuji gives me your hand
You don't know my Babuji!
We have to get away from here, Raj.
Please Raj, take me away from here
Do you love me?
- More than anyone else
Do you trust me?
- More than I trust myself
Then listen carefully to what
I'm going to say. From now on...
we're strangers. I don't know you
and you don't know me. Go back
Let things happen as they're happening.
Leave the rest to me
What I'm up to is daunting. But I
have complete faith in our love.
But alone... I cannot tread upon this path.
You will have to be my strength
You must co-operate. Tell
me, will you stand by me?
Remember one more thing.
I'm here only for your sake.
Till I have you for lifetime's
sakes, I am not leaving
Listen, what's the name of
the one you're marrying?
Kuljit Singh
Help!
Anybody here?
Somebody, help me!
Where's everyone? Help!
Anybody around?
Had Raj not arrived in the nick
of time, I would've been the prey
Raj, I'm sold out!
- What are you saying?
- Where are you from?
I've never seen you before
- I'm from London
Our guest from London!
What have you come here for?
- To achieve something
To achieve what? Do tell us
Land... land.
- Land...?
Yes, if I could find a good stretch
of land, I want to set up a factory
Factory, making what?
- Beer
Tell me something, Kuljit.
Will8-10 million pounds...
be enough to set up a factory?
What happened?
- 8-10 million pounds?
Too less? I can get more.
- No! That's a lot. Enough
God is great! He makes us meet.
We'll get along fine together
You want to set up a factory?
As good as done
Done, my man
By the way Raj...
where are you staying?
- You see, I don't know anyone around
So I'm putting up at the Circuit House.
Strange! Now you know me
I have a palatial house! And you'll
stay at the circuit house? No way!
Binda, go and get his luggage from
the circuit house. Drop it home
What are you doing, Kuljit?
- Not a word
You've saved my life, saved Kuljit!
Can't I do as much for you?
I know, you're from London.
Here in Punjab, we're lions
You're going to enjoy yourselves.
- Well, if you're forcing me...
as you wish.
- That's like it!
What about babes?
We'll have a blast!
You haven't gone yet?
Go on Binda, hurry up.
Get a Black Label for Raj
I'm going to have a scotch with Raj
Show me a cigarette, man. Strange!
The lighter too
You have done us a great
favor in saving Kuljit's life
No, it was my duty.
- May you live long, son
Preeti, give Raj some sweets
Enough
10 million pounds! Why
didn't you tell me before?
I was about to...
- Raj! My son!
The sweets.
- I have some
Let me feed you. That's like it!
You want to set up a factory, no?
We'll set it up for you.
- What was I telling you?
Get dressed fast. We're
going to Baldev's for lunch
Who's Baldev?
- He's my friend, man!
His daughter is marrying my Kuljit
What am I going to do over there?
- That's true. What will he do there?
But if you insist, I'll come along.
- That's like it!
Baldev is a bit British.
He'll mind it if we're late
Let's make it on time.
- That's like it!
You get dressed fast. We're
always getting late because of you
Kuljit, I have something to tell you.
- Don't worry about the factory
I have...
I’ll take all of it
Compliments
My compliments
Listen...
- I...?
How did the shopkeeper get here?
I've seen you somewhere before.
- Not me. I never step out of the house
In London...?
- But I haven't been beyond Ludhiana
Have you met my friend Raj?
He has just arrived from London
What are you saying?
- Balli, the doctor...
Raj is the one who saved
Kuljit's life yesterday
You know who this is? The oldest
of my friends. My kinsmanto-be
What are you staring at?
Touch his feet
My respects
Hurry! The doctor has been
asking for you for ages
This doctor is a wonderful fellow.
Come on, man
Old foggy has quite a memory.
- What happened?
Nothing. This is great! Lovely house!
- I told you
This is Raj. My friend.
He has come from London
This is Simran
Namaste, Simran-ji
Were it not for him yesterday, you
and I wouldn't be here together
What a thing to say...
Very glad to meet you, Ms Rajeshwari
What is this?
- A little gift. For a little bride
Mr. Raj, folks I like can call me Chutki
And folks who like me, call me Raj. Only Raj
Namaste, Simran-ji.
- Namaste
Come on now
This is Raj, my British friend
The one I told you about.
- My respects
May you live long, son.
- Coming
Have some.
- Thanks Ma-ji (Mother)
Let me do the rest for you.
- No, you belong to the grooms people
You're our guest.
- How strange of you
A moment ago you called me your son.
The next moment, you disown me?
Allow me
Just try this lassi. I made it with
my own hands! Here you are, Aunt
Here you are Parjai-ji (Aunt).
This is for you, Aunt
That's a lovely dress
Excuse me...
After you
Why are you taking all this trouble?
We kids can manage. Allow me
That's what I've been saying all
along. But no one will listen to me
I've been given all the work.
- That's my point
Hey... who are you?
- I...? I'm Raj
Raj, who...?
- Your son-in-law to-be
Kuljit is your son-in-law to-be, no? I'm his friend
Darling boy! Put the glasses there.
- Sure
Such a darling!
Today I see the best sign!
For the first time...
I'm seeing Simran laughing with such mirth!
Give that to me.
- I won't
True, Ma-ji. Simran looks very cheerful
Son of an Englishman! Get up!
Hurry! We're going hunting
Look at him
Aren't you coming? Get up.
I'm sick. I have high fever
Caught such a chill last night,
I slept in my shoes, you know
You're wearing only one shoe.
- That's the leg that caught the chill
Sorry friend, I just can't go hunting with you
You British are so feeble.
I'll send medicines for you
Make sure you're fine by this evening.
We're having fowl for dinner.
Don't worry, you'll be fine.
Hey Kuljit...
Come on Raj, get started
What's this?
- Keep moving
What's all this Raj?
- Wonderful thing happened today
Met a minister on my way. Turns out
to be my Daddy's childhood friend
He gave me all this. Let me take
care of that. Don't tire yourself
I'm alone fellow you know. What use
this sugar, rice and wheat for me?
So I thought I'd bring it over.
There's a wedding in the offing here
Could be useful, no?
- Maybe so, son
But we're the brides people.
Can't take anything from you
Not again. Once and for all,
decide what you take me for
Either you don't call me a
son, or you treat me like a son
How do you treat sons?
- You don't argue with sons
All right. I won't argue.
- That's like it
Now listen to the real thing, Ma-ji.
My mother used to say...
one who helps out with a
wedding, gets a pretty bride
All this, for a pretty bride?
- What else? Only lucky ones...
find good brides nowadays.
- What kind of bride do you want?
Say, someone like you
Don't say that.
Give me your blessings.
Granted. You'll get a bride you want
All right, I'm off.
- Will you please open this?
It's going to open
Aunt, don't keep looking,
don't even think. Just take it
Stuff like this is hard to find
even in Delhi or Bombay
Just wear it and step out, and
you'll make the girls stare
Don't even ask me about the boys
- It's nice
Not special
You show me that one.
- Okay. Here you are
Superb stuff. Just take a look at
the borders. On you, resplendent
Such bad ones! If you have
something special, show me
I have to wear it for the wedding.
- Here you are
This is for weddings. If you aren't
pleased, I'm no connoisseur
Pure goldthread.
On you, looks exotic!
Don't talk rot! It's not that good
Not that bad either. I'll keep it
Pack it. And put a good price
You've worn me out
Raj, let's have a song from you.
- I can't sing
Coy like a girl? Sing.
- Oh no Grannie...
Sing... please
I'm in love, why am I afraid?
I've loved, I haven't stolen anything
Why should I weep secretly?
I'll live for love, I'll die for love
What else have I to do?
- I'm in love, why am I afraid?
You've got your aim all wrong
Forget it, you can't even sing
The lover will carry his bride away
The brides people will be left gaping
What are you doing?
Everyone's out there! Let go!
On one condition.
- What?
Give me a kiss Senorita.
- Are you crazy?
One kiss
- Mamight see!
Let her see
Chutki might see!
- Let her see
Aunt might come by.
- Let her come
This Babuji is going to get me killed!
What are you wondering Baldev?
There's no countermove
First time in20 years, I have you checkmated
Good move, indeed.
This once I'm checkmated
That's check. And mate.
- Wonderful!
Yes Babuji, I'm wonderful
How did he checkmate?
No, I'll put it back.
- No, let me take a look
What happened?
You know what's about to happen tomorrow?
What?
Tomorrow, I'm going to be engaged to Kuljit
Tomorrow, Kuljit will put a ring on this finger
You know why the engagement
ring is worn on this finger?
Because the artery from this
finger leads straight to the heart
I can't wear anyone else's ring but yours, Raj
If you want me to walk up in
front of everyone with a ring...
and put it on you, I'll do it.
No problem
All this is a great joke for you,
isn't it? What I'm going through...
you can never imagine
- Look at me
Look
I feel everything Simran, the way
you're pining, your pain, your tears
But why don't you understand?
This is just the beginning
These people haven't even
gotten to know me properly
I need more time, Simran.
And I need your support
I want you to smile. And listen,
no son of a gun can take you...
You're mine, only mine
Chutki might wake up. Go away
Listen
Didi...
Can I say something?
- Go on
I don't like this Kuljit one bit.
Don't marry him
It's very late. Go to sleep
Didi, I like the one who was on the roof
What did you say?
Didi, isn't Raj the one you met in Europe?
Yes
I like him a lot! You marry him.
- Don't you worry
He's the one I'm marrying
Yes Grannie?
- Pistachios for the sherbet
Done
Raj, where are the flowers?
- You put them beside the staircase
Oh I forgot! Were it not for you,
everything would be topsy-turvy
That's what I'm saying.
The lover will take his bride away
Raj, weren't you with the
grooms people? Have you switched...
over to the brides people?
- Someday I'll have a bride too, no?
Just putting in some practice. Get it?
- Never mind. Get lost
Son of a gun
Kuljit is so lucky!
- Really
Now give her yours
Simran, offer your hand
Simran, put your hand out
Come on
What's this?
Never mind. The other hand
"These girls are poison pills"
"These boys are rogues"
"Poison pills.
- Rogues"
"Make sure you're painted with henna"
"Make sure the bride's palanquin is ready"
"To take you away, o' beauty,
your lover is coming"
"Make sure you come with your face
hidden behind the bridegroom's sehra"
"It's a matter of hearts.
Keep it in your heart"
"For a signal from your flying tresses..."
"with bated breath, the
bachelors await your suit"
"The maidens will go into hiding out of shame..."
"for these are all madmen
from town come to our village"
"Keep your eyes downcast:
Keep yourself chaste"
"To take you away, o' beauty,
your lover is coming"
"I'm a young boy: You're a pretty girl"
"If our hearts are swayed, what's my crime?"
"You should've held your heart.
This beauty is magic"
"If the magic is working, what's my crime?"
"Keep up for me, leave the door ajar"
"To take you away, o' beauty,
your lover is coming"
"Say no more now, do no more now"
"It's a matter of hearts.
Keep it in your heart"
"Make sure you're painted with henna:
Make sure your palanquin is ready"
"Make sure you come with your face
hidden behind the bridegroom's sehra"
"O' my precious one..."
"O' my precious one... you know not..."
"you're still pretty, and I'm still young"
"I could still die for you, my love"
"Make sure you're painted with henna:
Make sure your palanquin is ready"
"Make sure you come with your face
hidden behind the bridegroom's sehra"
Babuji, yesterday you were wonderful!
What a dance! Bested all the others
No Babuji, just a speck of dirt.
Now it’s clean
Too few doves, don't you think?
The whites ones...
Look... one, two, three
No, maybe same like yesterday
I've decided. Today I’m talking it over with Raj
Is it something to be ashamed of?
- Raj is here
Back? So early?
Raj! My precious son! Come here.
We were just talking of you
I've something important to tell you.
- Sure, go on
This ought to be discussed by elders.
But since you're so close to us...
I thought, why not talk to you?
- Tell me
I wish this friendship to become a relationship
Why not, why not?
- For my daughter, Preeti...
I seek your hand
Raj! Better think up something fast!
Else, they have you trussed!
Raj, have you any objections?
- What...? Oh no. How could I?
My son!
- But I can't take...
such a big decision all by myself.
So you will have to talk to Pops
Pops...?
- Father
See? What a good boy!
- I never do anything...
against my father's wishes.
- No problem. Give me his number
I'll talk to him over telephone
Let ask him to come over.
- No problem
My country, my soil, my Raj!
Here I come, son
Step out of the country,
and you'll find everything...
but the matthri your wife serves up.
- Compliments, lady
Neither the language, nor the culture.
For one who loves the Ganga...
what's a Thames? So I told
Raj to return only with his bride
That's like it!
- Such conviction
What do you do in London?
- Back in London...
London...?
- Forget London. All I know is...
Go East, go West,
Punjab is the best!
Son!
Don't you worry. I've got it all tied up
You don't even introduce me to your Daddy
What a wonder! Just this morning,
we were talking about him...
and I find him in the marketplace,
armed with a photo, asking about you
Whatever anyone says, this marriage
was made in Heaven! Right, lady?
Right.
- Right...?
You're strange! You don't need
my permission for a good deed
What do you mean no? Have
I ever refused you anything
How about sweets?
Your son-in-law’s waiting
Right away!
- Go on!
The wedding must be done right away!
A good deed can't wait
I was thinking of Kuljit and Raj
getting married at the same time
What was that?
It's final!
- Raj, are you happy?
Give me a sweet! Quick!
My son is happy!
Now you're marrying Preeti.
Her brother is Kuljit...
the one who's about to marry Simran.
And you love Simran. Not Preeti
What was Preeti doing in London?
- Not Preeti. In London, it was Simran
Yes, Simran... who's this Simran?
- Pops! Just give up thinking! Please
Can anything be done
without giving it a thought?
I'm here. Everything will be alright.
- By now, it's done already!
Wedding must be done right away!
Good deed can't wait! Why did you come?
It was a mistake! Won't happen
again. I'll tell them that I forgot...
about your mother's death anniversary.
Matter laid to rest for a month
May I come in?
- Sure, come right in
You're going to live very long.
Raj and I were just talking of you
Sit
You sit too. Milk for me?
Thank you!
Tomorrow's Karwa Chauth.
- What's Karwa Chauth?
I'd like to keep fast for
Raj's well-being. May I...?
Sure, no problem!
- Karwa Chauth, Pops...?
Karwa Chauth...? No! Never!
Why...?
- We consider it a bad omen...
for a girl to observe the ritual for
her husband before her marriage
Besides my child, we can't
discuss the liaison for a month
It was during this month that
Raj's mother passed away
We have to fix another date for the
wedding. Let's talk to your father
Ajit...
Raj, you know what day it is tomorrow?
What's it now?
- My first Karwa Chauth
I want you to give me water
and food after my fast
Hands off.
- What?
I told you. Hands off
Simran, if you don't love me,
just tell me straight. I'll go away
Then you can marry Kuljit. It's going
to save me this everyday melodrama
Is it something I said?
- But you never say anything, no?
I want you to give me water
and feed me the first morsel...
of food after my fast
Are you out of your mind? You expect
me to make a grand entry saying...
"Hi Simran! I'm your husband-to-be!
Here, take a drink of water"
I don't care! I'll even die of hunger!
But the first drink of water,
and the first morsel of food...
you will feed me! Get it?
Just like her father
So why should I be the butt of the joke?
You're unique, Mr. Malhotra.
Your dress doesn't indicate...
your affinity to Hindustan.
- The dress has fooled even you?
I keep Hindustan in my heart.
- Wonderful!
Wonderful...?
Ajit was saying you're here to set up a factory?
The factory is just an excuse.
If you ask me the truth...
I'm here to choose a bride for Raj
Then men are all out in the outhouse
They say, they don't want
to disturb us on Ladies' Day
Are you keeping a fast too?
- Yes
May you live long, my child.
My Kuljit is lucky to get...
a bride like you. Come
Ma-ji, this is my Pops. Father
Your son has cast a spell over everyone here
That's my son
I’ll join you
Pops, this is...
- I know
She can only be Simran
No one even watches his step.
Hold this. The flowers...!
"Let it rain flowers!"
"My beloved is here"
Kammo, where are the flowers?
Hurry up
I'm Raj's father. From London.
- From London...?
Actually from Bhatinda. But I've been
in London for many years. You?
I'm Simran's Aunt.
- You can't be!
What...?
- You could be her sister
Listen... aren't you keeping fast?
- No. I'm still a maiden
Nothing could've been better.
- What...?
One of your flowers.
- Maybe it's for you. Keep it
When is the moon going to rise? I'm starving
I hope it kills you.
Did I ask you to fast?
Eat this on the sly.
No one's looking
Don't
The moon is up.
- Where?
There
"On this night of prayer for the wedded woman..."
"I look at the moon, I pray with folded hands"
"Then I break my fast"
"Give me the water, take
your slave for your queen"
"Tonight, give me what I desire"
"Come home o' wanderer,
your beloved beckons"
What happened?
- Water
Simi, my child
- Drink water
What happened? What happened to her?
- She swooned
Get up. Come, my child
What happened?
- It's all right. She just swooned
It's nothing. Come on, let's eat
She's so fragile, no?
Why are you anxious?
Are you fasting too?
No...
- Then come along
It isn't easy for him to get away.
Everyone's asking for Raj all the time
He won't be able to come, Didi.
Please, eat something
I won't! I'd rather die starving.
- Very well, kill yourself
I'm sorry, I'm late. But what to do?
They weren't about to leave me
It was tough getting away.
Here, eat
Eat it
I said I'm sorry. Now eat.
Else, you'll swoon for real
Chutki, tell him there’s no
need for him to worry for me
I was about to faint of hunger.
And there he was, filling his stomach
Anyway, it's my first Karwa Chauth.
Why should he get so worked up?
Whether I live or die, is he bothered?
You don't know this. But Raj hasn't
eaten anything all day either
He wanted to break fast with you.
And he told me not to tell you
Sorry Raj, but I couldn't keep shut any longer
Come here
Talking to me?
- Come here
I got carried away.
- No matter, Senorita
In big places, such small things happen
My turn Senorita. Feed me
I told you, not to betray my trust.
Simran hasn't forgotten him yet?
If she remembers, she'll regret it
What happened to me won't
happen to my daughter
No more sacrifices at every step
as daughter, as sister, as wife
She'll live life as she wishes.
She'll have her share of happiness
Come in
Keep this
Ma, this...?
- Not a word! I know everything
I've seen everything. Raj is the
one you met in Europe. I know
I also know, the two of
you love each other dearly
I was wrong Simran! My daughter
won't sacrifice her happiness
She isn't going to sacrifice her love
I know Raj, you'll make my daughter
very happy. You have my blessings
Take my daughter away.
Leave
No one here cares for your love.
Take her away from here
I’ll take care of everything.
- No Ma-ji
I don't want to hear anything! No!
Please go away from here!
I beg of you, son!
- I will Ma-ji. I’ll take her away
Come... sit here
Keep this
Ma-ji, I was a little boy when
my mother passed away
But whatever I am today, is because of her
To this day I haven't forgotten
something she said. She'd say...
"Son, at every turn in life, you'll
find two roads. One right, one wrong"
"The wrong route will be easy, it
will draw you. But the right path..."
"will be hard, with lots of
hazards, a lot many troubles"
"On the wrong road, initially, you
might find success, happiness"
"But in the end, you will lose.
Upon the right path, initially..."
"you may trip at every step, you
may face hazards, difficulties."
But... in the end, you will always win"
Now you tell me, Ma-ji. Am I
on the right, or in the wrong?
Your way is absolutely right, son.
But you don't know my husband
And Ma-ji, your husband doesn't know me
If I wanted to elope with Simran,
I could've done it already
But I want to be given Simran.
I don't want to steal her
I don't want to take her away
on the sly. I want to do it openly
If I have come, I'll surely carry my bride away
But only when Babuji gives me
her hand, of his own volition
Now Simran isn't your problem.
She's my headache
As for you, you have given your daughter away
Just a matter of time now
before the bride is carried away
Is this crying illness in the genes?
How strange Uncle-ji! Tell me.
- The girl... what's her name...?
Yes Simran. I don't approve of the match
Why Uncle-ji?
- Girl's fine. But no match for you
You're a strong young Jatt d'Punjab!
And this girl is frail, subdued
Is this any match? Match for
you is a girl like a sparkler!
Just come with me to London.
The girls I'll introduce you to...
will drive you crazy!
And we’re going to be in London,
meeting your sparklers!
Pull out all the stops!
- You son of a gun
As a little boy, I'd ride out to the
fields on my father's shoulders
Ever since, I struck up a friendship
with these doves. I find it...
so peaceful out here.
I love spending time with the doves
Tell me Babuji, are the doves here
different from the doves in London?
Difference there is. The doves
here know me, they recognize me
They belong to my land.
Even the doves out there are alien
Could it be that you perceive it
differently? Maybe a dove out there...
took to wings from here, from
your land... one who knows you...
one who recognizes you.
Maybe you don't recognize him?
What happened?
What are you doing?
- My Ma used to say...
the soil of our land is very
powerful. It's going to be fine
But this is outrageous!
Who might've done this?
Babuji, look
Let's go.
- Babuji...
Are you still angry about my beer act?
I was childish.
Won't you forgive me?
I forgot that long ago
I was wrong about you.
You're right
I didn't recognize.
Come, let's go
Ma-ji, what is the matter?
You asked for me?
Son, whatever the doctor might say,
I know my time's up
Speak of nice things, Ma-ji.
What a thing to say?
Not to be anxious. I'm of
the age when one leaves
I've had a wonderful life.
Son, I have nothing to complain about
But now that I see Simran...
after years a desire wells up in my heart.
I want to see Simran married
Before she marries, I wish I don't...
- How can you talk of such things?
Listen son
The bride's palanquin has just got to
cross over from one house to another
Now that everyone is here, what
difference would it make if...
the wedding is pre-punned to tomorrow?
- Absolutely correct!
The wedding happens tomorrow.
Yes Baldev? Right tomorrow
Yes Ma-ji. Tomorrow
We will have to take Simran away on the sly
Nothing else is going to work.
Don't worry. I have it all worked out
We're taking the morning train
out. I’ll wait for you at the station
Somehow or the other,
just get there with Simran
Whatever happens next, we'll see
Are you listening?
I know this isn't your way. You don't
want to take Simran away like this
But son, it's too late now. If you love her...
if you want to spend a lifetime with
her, you must elope. Understand?
Please Raj, take me away from here!
You don't know my Babuji!
We have to run from here. We must!
- I've come to take you as my bride.
I’ll take you only when your
Babuji gives me your hand
What is to happen tomorrow, I don't know
What I'm going to do tomorrow, I don't know
But you must trust me
Whatever I do tomorrow,
is going to be for both of us
Do you love me?
Do you trust me?
Then it's just a matter of time before
the bride is carried away, no?
"Oh heart's love"
"Oh my love"
"I give you..."
"to God to keep"
"So strange are the ways of the world"
"The heart is crazed, yet so helpless"
"What's left to be heard?
What's left to be said?"
"Just let it lie between us"
"The hide-n-seek is over. I'm getting married"
"Howl wish it doesn't kill you"
Simi, come down, quick! Time for
the ritual body-painting with henna
"Oh my love"
"Oh my Moon"
"You are my life..."
"my beloved"
I wanted to tell you
You were right. I failed to recognize
You enter my house, and before my family...
you play with my honor?
You have deceived me! You have
taken advantage of our trust!
You made a joke out of our cordiality?
How dare you have an affair with Simran?
Did you imagine you'd marry Simran?
You aren't even worthy of yourself
How can you be worthy of Simran?
I was right about you.
Liars, wastrels like you never improve
They only become worse
No Babuji! No!
Didn't I tell you to take me away?
No one cares for our love!
Didn't I say, let's elope?
- No Simran, don't
You can only run from strangers
From the ones we call our own
Our elders are our parents
All our lives, they've brought us up.
They gave us so much love
About our lives, they can
decide better than we can
We have no right to make them
sad for the sake of our happiness
Babuji is right. I am a liar, a cheat
Even if I lied for your sake, a lie is always a lie
Babuji is right. I'm not worthy of you
And so what if I can see nothing beyond you?
And so what if I can remember no one but you?
Babuji is right. I'm a wastrel.
How did I think of marrying you?
So what if this wastrel loves you like a madman?
Love isn't everything, is it?
Babuji is right, Simran
Babuji is right
Here you are Babuji.
Take your daughter
I didn't come here to break anyone's heart
I just wanted to win hearts
Maybe I fall short of expectations
Maybe that's why I couldn't win you over
If you think Kuljit will make
Simran happier...
then you're right.
What's best for Simran, you know best
Forgive me
Forgive me Preeti
I know I have hurt you
Where's Simran, Raj?
Raj, where is Simran?
She will come, Pops.
She'll come
Babuji will bring her. Personally
He will have to
I wish to hear no more.
Go away from here
Your son has deceived all of us.
He has shown us where he belongs
I won't let my daughter marry a liar!
- Enough!
I am proud of my son.
Don't incite me to passion
Kuljit and Raj are fighting at the station
We must go there!
One might kill the other!
Come on
Come with me Simran
Stop
Let me go, Babuji!
Please let me go
Raj means all my life!
Without him, I can't live
Let me go to my Raj
Please let me go to my Raj
Go Simran
No one can love you more than him
Go my child. Go to your Raj
Go on Simran.
Live your life
In big places, such small things happen
The lover will carry his bride away
made by chandler matthew
chandler_ping@hotmail.com