Where did you go?
Excuse me, nurse.
We're from Interpol.
Would you mind if we have
a few moments with the boy?
You know, the man outside
says you're not eating.
You should eat to gain strength.
How are you feeling?
Feeling. Feel.
Feeling.
Bit bumpy out there
on the ocean waves?
Bit rough?
Out there?
Out there on the high seas?
Bumpity-bumpity?
Excuse me. We have to take him
for a checkup now.
Yes, yes, yes.
Wait.
I think this belongs to you.
Half for me?
Nice lad.
You okay?
That nurse...
Yeah.
Her boots...
No.
Her boots.
Oh, boots.
Nurses don't wear boots.
Watch out!
- Get out of my way!
- Sorry.
- Get the boy.
- Stop him.
What the heck?
Give me that!
There he goes!
Come here.
- I got him. I got him.
- There he is.
He's mine. I've got him.
Let's go.
Jai!
- Clear all exits.
- Right, sir.
Watson, are you there?
I'm not here.
What happened?
Snakehead's men.
They were here for the boy.
- I'm gonna keep him with me.
- Good idea. Keep him safe. Yes. Yes.
Watson, you did all this alone?
No, Eddie is...
I mean, I think I mentioned that Eddie
wasn't the only one with a black belt.
So you're all right?
Perfect.
- Great.
- Okay. I'll see you back at the...
Yeah. I'm gonna do a couple of
press-ups and meet you back there.
Yes. Yes.
You just take care of the boy.
- Eddie, listen...
- Watson, something wrong.
Snakehead's men got away again,
but at least the boy is safe.
I mean, something wrong with me.
Hit me.
- What?
- Go on, hit me.
No, I can't do that.
It's okay, I don't mind.
Well, I mind. I mean...
A chap could break
a finger, you know.
Okay.
Use this.
- No, thanks. I went before I came out.
- No, hit me with this.
- For real?
- Yes.
God.
There you go. All right?
Harder.
I can't do this. This is ridiculous.
- The queen hits harder than that.
- How...
How dare you.
Oh, my God. Are you all right?
Oh, God. I'm so sorry, my friend.
Did it hurt?
Of course it hurt.
But nothing.
I was shot before...
...but I was okay.
Shoot me.
Go ahead.
No, I think the embalming fluid
has gone to your head.
- This is ridiculous.
- Give me the gun.
- Absolutely not.
- I'll show you.
You know how many forms I have to
fill out if I fire my gun? Absolutely not.
- This is how accidents happen.
- Look.
Amazing.
No blood.
Incredible.
- See?
- I mean, still...
That's incredible. I mean, just...
- Stop that.
- I'm sorry.
That was below the belt. I'm sorry.
That's what I mean.
Can one of you explain
this latest failure?
Why you couldn't
retrieve one small boy?
Sir...
...this might sound crazy...
...but I emptied a whole clip into that
Chinese cop and he still wouldn't die.
What Chinese cop?
That's Eddie Yang.
He's supposed to have died yesterday,
drowned in that container.
Then it's true.
Professor. Doctor. Doctor.
Thank you for being here.
We've come across something
very interesting.
Have you ever seen this before?
- Doesn't ring a bell. Doctor?
- I've seen that before.
- The fish is the sign of life.
- That's interesting.
- And the snake is the sign of...
- Whoa.
The medallion.
You're gonna love this.
Now, it should have a serpent
on one side.
And a fish on the other.
If what you have is real, that is
the Holy Grail of Eastern mythology.
And maybe the secret to eternal life.
Sweet!
- Where'd you get the medallion?
- I recognize the fish.
- You got it from a kid, didn't you?
- Yes.
The legend says
every thousand years...
...a child is chosen that can bind the
halves together...
...and restore life to the dead.
You get that kid and the medallion...
...you're a god.
- That's nonsense.
- So where's the other half?
- Wait!
The ancient texts say that if you want
superhuman strength...
...and immortality,
you need both halves.
The only documented case
of a genuine resurrection...
You can't weigh it,
measure it, smoke it.
Look, ancient texts aren't fairy tales.
Thank you, professor. Doctor. Doctor.
- Cheerio, for now.
- Good luck.
Why would a young boy
have something like this?
This Snakehead chap, is he
after the medallion or the boy?
By the way,
take good care of that kid.
The medallion can not only give life,
it can take it away.
Okay, I'll cover the front door,
call in for backup.
You go to the rear to Nicole's
apartment as fast as you can.
Got it.
Sorry.
You know, for a little person,
you sure do eat a lot.
Still going?
What did you have?
Okay.
Here we go.
Try that.
That good?
You don't like... You're not...
One of my culinary skills...
...other than peeling fruit, of course...
...just so happens to be a toasted...
...peanut butter and jelly sandwich...
...which, I might add, Eddie could eat
for breakfast, lunch and dinner.
Then again, he didn't really
have any choice.
- Why?
- Because I can't cook anything else.
I just can't believe
that he's really gone.
He's not gone.
Jai...
...do you not understand that Eddie's
not coming back?
I pulled him back.
Okay...
Jai, Eddie's...
He...
Just hold on.
See?
Oh, my God.
Eddie?
Eddie.
Jai!
No!
Eddie!
You see? I told you he wasn't dead.
The boy, sir.
Yes.
Welcome...
...my old friend.
So...
...a quick, painless death...
...followed by resurrection...
...immortality...
...and powers beyond your dreams.
Are you sure?
His order is ruled
by reverence for life.
My death before him
must be reversed.
And if it isn't...
...kill him.
And then who would bring you back,
Chosen One?
Pitiful mortal.
So...
...I have no further use
for you, Chosen One.
You're not immortal.
What?
To become immortal, you need
both halves of the medallion.
Where's the other half?
Tell me!
- Nicole.
- Eddie.
It's me. I'm fine, really.
I just...
I still don't understand, Eddie,
because I was there...
...and I saw you, and...
- Nicole, it's me.
You see, it's just that I was at the
container and you were dead.
I mean, you were dead.
Nicole, the boy uses the medallion
to give life.
That's why Snakehead took him.
With the boy and the medallion,
he could...
He could become like you?
Yes, but he needs
the whole medallion...
...and he only has half.
Look...
...this is a touching reunion.
We're all glad that Eddie's
amongst the living...
...but we still haven't found
Snakehead's helicopter.
Get online. Find anything
that was in the air in the last hour.
I don't care if it was a bird, a plane
or bloody Superman.
No offense, old chap.
Eddie.
If he needs the other half, he's
gonna come looking for you.
If he is looking for me...
...he'll be looking for my partner.
Me?
My family.
Cool.
See, that's not normal. I mean,
that's not natural. What...?
Eddie, take my bike!
Thank God.
They're all right.
Charlotte?
Charlotte? I have something
I have to tell you.
Yes, dear?
Eddie...
Watson! They're here!
Go!
Charlotte, where are you going?
This is no time for cleaning.
Take your shield!
Watson!
- Are you all right, love?
- Yes, I'm fine, dear.
Catch!
Here. I'll lead them away.
Your wife?
What the...?
There you are. Quick. Quick.
That's a good boy.
Now, listen. Guns are very dangerous
things, all right? Right.
How dare you shoot...
...at my...
...wife!
My Lord.
Where'd he go?
We meet again...
...Eddie Yang.
Where's the boy?
My guest is no concern of yours.
All that matters is that you have the
other half of the medallion.
Don't run, Eddie!
You can't hide from me!
The medallion is mine!
You think it's a game?
Well, let's play!
We're the same, you and I.
What a pity. What a waste.
You don't know
what powers you have.
Destiny calls.
He's sleeping. At least, I think that's
what he's doing.
He doesn't even look like he's
breathing.
The boy!
Oh, God, I wish
you wouldn't do that.
Eddie, you're all right.
The boy's in danger.
He's going to kill him. Right?!
Snakehead has taken the boy
to Raven's Keep.
I told you everything I know.
I did.
We need to move fast.
Of course I can fly this thing.
I built it myself.
You take the bike.
I'll guide you from the air.
I'm driving.
That's Raven's Keep.
It's five miles away.
You should wash your hands.
Come on.
Nicole.
Be careful.
You too.
- What the hell are you doing here?
- Where's the boy?
- Let's get out of here!
- Move!
You cowards!
Watson. Watson!
Are you crazy?
Be careful.
Interpol. Freeze.
Jai, are you all right?
There she is! Get her!
Excuse me.
You looking for something?
Interpol! Freeze!
Interpol! Free...
Jai, thank God.
You're in danger.
It's over.
You're safe now.
I don't think so.
No, it's all right.
Run!
For your lives.
It's not nice to take things
that don't belong to you.
Fetch.
My brother...
...don't be sentimental.
It's so unnecessary.
It's so human.
So normal.
You and I will live forever.
We are the lords of time.
We can take whatever we choose.
I mean, what difference can a single
human life like hers make to us?
We are immortal.
Let me show you.
Eddie, use the medallion
to end the life that it gave.
Can you?
It's your turn.
What's that for?
That, Eddie Yang,
is for not catching me.
And that, Eddie Yang, is for not
catching me.
Interpol! Freeze!
Isn't that lovely?
Of course...
...when he came back, he was naked.
I mean, completely starkers.
Not a stitch.
I'm not complaining, mind you.
Listen, I have this cough.
I think it's quite serious.
Honestly, I could snuff at any point.
I don't suppose you'd consider
a rub on your medallion?
I really am. Hello?
It's very bad...
Very bad. You...
Please, the med... One quick rub.
That's all. Oh, the medallion.
Quick. Give me the medallion.
Give it.
All right.
It was only a tickle anyway.
Come with me.
Wait!
Nicole! Eddie!
You can't leave me here.
Goodbye!
Okay, that wasn't scary at all.
He walked through a vortex
to the next universe.
I'm going this way.
- Quiet on the set. Are cameras ready?
- Cameras are ready.
Jackie, Claire. And action.
I'm sorry.
Can you overlap
that line for me?
Eddie Yang. I knew there
couldn't be two of you.
- Will you say action, or am I just...?
- I did. Okay, here we go.
And action.
Three months and not so much
as a phone call?
That made me so nervous.
I slapped you so hard.
- Come on! Oh, my God!
- In the middle...!
- I got slapped for nothing!
- I'm so sorry.
- I am so sorry. I'm so sorry.
- I can't believe it.
- Oh, no!
- Claire.
Jackie, I'm so sorry.
That rea... That hurt me.
- You should continue filming!
- Oh, I didn't know!
- Now I got another one!
- Oh, no!
- That was really bad.
- Try it again.
Let's go.
Let's move.
Take one.
Eddie.
All those things that I said...
I was right there.
- Seven, take three.
God bless, Eddie.
Action!
Cut!
Cut.
Take one.
You... Now, how...?
It's Giscard.
- Really? What about Snakehead?
- Snakehead is not here yet.
Is he not here?
What about Ken?
- Yeah. Ken is...
- Pete? Pete?
Pete is just right beside me.
That's it. We're fine.
- Now, that's...
- Somebody let Jackie in.
Here's the plan.
We have to...
Whoops.
I got it wrong.
It's this way.
Oh, sorry. It's the other way.
Oh, damn.
Oh, I missed.
Watson.
- Cut. Print.
- Phone.
- A-camera.
- Action.
Watson. So many things are going on.
- Marker.
- Come on.
- One more.
Watson.
Sorry. What? It's... No, you... No.
- Again.
- Sorry.
Marker!
- Cut.
- Cut!
I want ice cream.
Cut!
Slate X67, take one coming up.
- A-marker.
- Like a woman.
That's it. That's it. Okay.
It's just down there.
Down.
Then the bottom.
- Sorry, Jackie.
- What's this? "The bottom."
- Marker.
- Move!
Wait, wait!
Oh, shit.
Nicole, the boy used the meda...
Very good. Cut. Cut.
The dog barking.
Yeah, I heard it.
Go. Go away.
And action.
Interpol! Freeze!
Cut.
A-camera.
In case of emergency...
...the exits are here...
...here...
...and here.
- I slapped you.
- Again.
- Sorry. I'm sorry.
- Oh, my God!
- It was meant to be fake. Sorry.
- You do on purpose.
Are you doing on purpose?
Try it again, Claire.
A little harder.
It drives me crazy.