Hurry up!
Try this!
We're late.
You look stupid holding that bag!
These are mine.
Get rid of them fast! The car is coming.
Give me 2 packs of cigarettes.
What brand?
Miss.
What's this? Let me have a look.
Police! What is it?
Show me your ID card.
You throw this bag to Shanghai.
You be careful! Get on.
You don't trust me?
Don't trust me?
Tell him to come over.
Have I ever overcharged you guys?
Never! You get what you paid for.
Paul, those 2 girls will come to night.
Boss, here they are.
You'll be satisfied with these girls.
I won't hold you up. Do have fun!
Enjoy yourself!
Keung, come.
Yes, Boss?
What did you say to him just now?
Nothing.
What did you say?
Really, nothing.
You did say something to him!
Truly, I did not.
Damn!
You didn't?
No, Boss.
Paul, what are you hiding?
Show me.
Why do you keep our customers' numbers?
Just to help in calling them.
Just to help yourself, I suppose?
I heard that you've set up a new den.
You want to betray me?
So you don't trust me, Boss.
Relax, I'm just joking.
My congratulations
if the rumor were true!
Be smart!
Boss.
Ling and Susan, 13th floor.
Helen and Jane, 15th floor.
Pinkly, 16th floor.
Hey, they've got bigger.
Keep your hands off.
This one is just night.
She's our new girl.
Take her to my room.
Will he pay me?
Ah Chiu found your girl in Yaumatei.
Her boyfriend was killed.
So we seized her.
You heard that? So get lost!
Will he pay me?
God, he will pay after.
I go to the washroom.
I can stand it.
I'll soon see my Brother.
I can! Surely can.
I shouldn't cry!
I have no right to cry.
A month will pass soon.
I treated you well.
Why did you elope?
It's wrong!
You're my girl.
Don't make me lose face!
Just told me if you had an affair.
Things wouldn't have gone this bad!
Now he died on the streets.
Shame on you.
But don't worry. We can talk.
Drink this!
Drink!
Try to play dumb, you bastard?
Drink it up, or you die!
Come over here.
Strip off!
Undress me.
Pay me first.
One banknote each service.
The whole bundle will exhaust you!
That bitch, she...
Help me...
That girl has killed the Boss!
Go and kill her.
Yes.
Are you alright?
Please go.
Stay.
They're after me. Please help me.
- Stop!
- Get down! Stop her!
Thank you.
Why are you so late?
It's your turn next!
Have I ever let you down?
Beware of Fatso. He's sly...
Look where you're going!
She's over there!
Get off!
Who took the girl away just now?
Which girl?
The one in white.
No.
Stay when I'm talking to you?
Or I'll fix this place up.
Get our men here!
Who lit firecracker?
Which bastard did that?
You know who controls this place?
You know who is the boss?
Who cares!
Just don't fool around here.
Be careful, Baldhead!
If I know who's hiding the girl,
I'll kill him.
Let's go.
Give way...
Let's go!
Let's go in.
Where is my money?
5 laps only. We're sure to win.
Give me five.
"Man in black on motorbike..."
Stay away!
I'll collect the money.
Give me the money!
Come on, loser, pay me!
Don't you want to keep you promise?
Of course, it's only $15,000!
I'll beat him next time.
Let's wait and see.
Call me if you've enough savings.
Here's your money.
Plus $100 for you, Bootlicker!
James, when will we have a race?
Come on, say something!
You're scared me?
Come here tomorrow night!
Is this a challenge?
Come down! Yankee.
I'm not talking to you, Cripple.
You win if you follow close enough.
Stop all this shit!
- Race me now if you've the guts!
- OK!
- Let's go for a drink.
- Leave me alone.
- Accompany me to take some food.
Come on!
You may lead
by the length of Broadcast Drive!
Nathan Road? Castle Peak Road?
- Go to hell.
- Go!
Hell your mother.
Bill, is your head alright?
It's OK.
Bill's back. Let's tease him!
- Bill.
- Bill!
Yes... Billy.
Your head's OK, Billy?
We heard that you fought with a woman.
We thought you were great.
Later we knew,
she hurt your head.
Poor Billy!
Stop it or I'll kill you.
I'll beat you even you are that old.
Stop bluffing, or I'll kill you.
Damn you old bag.
What? You want a fight here?
I got hit!
Bill, come to my office.
Your record is bad enough.
Stay cool and take it easy!
There you are 2 months off.
Take a break, old folk.
I'm fine.
Officer Lau.
Yes?
We found photos of women from China.
They said she'd killed their Boss.
They're after her too.
A chic killed the pimp-good ending.
Inspector Chan asks you to see him.
How can she kill him?
Don't disclose the information.
Yes, sir.
Bill, take a break. Don't overwork!
She's really fierce!
You like her? That'll cost you $2,000!
I can afford that.
Wait! Don't touch them.
What do you want? Go away!
What are you doing here?
Police.
So what? Don't mess it up!
I lost something.
I've just tied it up!
You can't touch that either.
Or I'll throw them to police station.
I got it!
Crazy old man!
Bureaucrats shield one another.
I'm innocent.
Just let them lock me up.
They'd release you for $50,000.
I'll raise the money anyway.
Sister, be sensible! They don't even...
I won't sit and let you suffer.
Anyway, I'll get you out.
Whatever I can do at any cost.
Mother!
Mom...
Mom
Frank was here! He's good boy!
Take his flowers away.
He's your son after all.
Why you so hard on him?
Mistress loved you both.
If she knew all these things.
It'll break her heart.
Say no more.
We'll be leaving HK soon.
Then you can't see him.
It's a waste to throw them away.
- Give me an ice-cream.
- Alright.
Paul.
Shall we have a chat?
I told everything at the police station.
Don't be so arrogant!
Yes, your boss is dead.
Only you can replace him!
What you try to bull here?
The ice-cream.
Give me that too.
Have some, Paul.
You've argued with your boss
before he died.
What was it about?
What do you mean? Old man.
Who are you anyway?
A woman hurt you. You're on leave.
Everybody knows that.
Be smart and get lost,
or you won't even get your pension.
Have it first!
Don't play the fool!
All your boss's girls
go to your place now.
Go to hell, old fool!
Shit, bastard!
We must find that chap.
Keep an eye on that old fool.
OK.
Excuse me, did you see my money?
No.
Thank you.
Does it hurt?
You want your money back?
Damn! He's so fierce.
You lost it last night?
We know where it is.
Come over here.
Lucky that I bet on him,
but we won't gain much.
It's his show tonight.
He's great!
I'll get the money.
The amount's right.
"Riding in black leather jacket."
"My tears fall in the rain."
Happy? Pay me back now!
I'll pay you later.
Jack, be honest!
You placed a bet on Dino!
But you still owe we $50,000.
Leave me some please.
No, you must pay when you can!
Hurry up!
I've got your money.
You should've said earlier!
I'm all turned on now!
You won't get it back
even if they find it.
How can I recover the money?
I've been looking for it
since last night.
It's no use staying here. Let's go.
Ice-cream cones and lollies!
- A lolly please.
- Two ice-cream.
Thank you.
Have you ever seen this girl?
No.
You want girl, go to nightclub!
Two mungbean lollies.
Isn't she the girls who...
You've seen her?
Somebody took her away.
Stop.
Show me your ID and license.
I don't have ID card.
Get inside.
Put this on.
I'm very hungry.
Take a rest first.
Thanks.
"The chocolate flavor lost,"
"it suits you!"
Are you looking for somebody?
He is Frank's father. Is Frank there?
He's out.
Sir, go in and wait.
I'll pick you up later.
Come on in.
Please sit down.
Thanks.
Who are you?
I'm Celia.
This is plain congee. You like some?
Frank'll soon be back. Please have some.
No thanks.
Come on!
You go ahead.
There are gingkoes inside.
The congee is good. Please try.
Frank and his mom used to hate gingkoes.
Where's his mom?
Passed away.
Thanks for the congee.
I'll find it for you.
Is he still riding motorbikes?
Yes.
Tell me if you need money.
Don't touch my things.
I...
Cut it out.
I don't know how long you'll stay.
But don't touch my things again.
Your father's been here.
He's been waiting you long.
He's looking for a chain.
Sorry for all the troubles.
"Too much milk
will spoil chocolate flavor."
"But if chocolate flavor is too strong,
there'll be no taste of milk."
My dear brother, isn't that funny?
Hong Kong is a beautiful place.
People are so nice to me.
I work hard and hope to come home soon.
Give me a packet of cigarettes.
$20.
For that guy with a red motorbike,
do you know where he lives?
I don't know him!
Don't be so nasty!
You hurt me!
I'll catch you.
Police. Run!
How dare you are? You know who I am?
Stay!
Thank you.
Where are you going?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
You don't want it any more?
Where else can you go?
Go to my house.
Hang on!
I'm not afraid.
But I'll be a burden to you.
Don't push yourself.
Your brother needs you.
My brother is a man of calibre.
He's a writer of anti-corruption.
God will bless him.
Until I've money to save him from jail.
You think so?
Does it hurt?
My arm.
Aren't you afraid at all?
Stay here.
They won't find you.
Your mother looks very pretty.
She's fond of playing.
So do you.
Therefore, dad scolded us often.
She bought me the first motorbike.
For that, dad grumbled her for months.
Did she die of illness?
She died because of me.
So, you're on bad terms with your dad?
Yes. Dad loved her so much.
He drove me away.
So he won't forgive me.
No, it's you not to forgive yourself.
If your mother died because of you,
could you forgive yourself?
Let Dino talk to me if you can't decide!
Stop the crap.
Just ask him yes or no.
I'm using mobile phone.
It's costly.
I'll wait.
Am I afraid?
What?
$100,000 is good enough, alright?
You really think you were a Dino?
Why laid such a large bet?
This dummy always want to race with me.
I said no because he's not my type.
Anyhow, let's take the bet.
We'll win for sure.
I only need $50,000.
The other $50,000 goes to me then.
Lost again?
Damn it!
What's happened to your foot?
Don't touch me, I can stand.
Go change your jeans.
No.
I care about you.
The chains were stolen together.
You're still keeping yours well.
But mine is like a crap.
See you at car racing park.
I'm going out, I'll be back soon.
Frank.
Come back early. I'll prepare supper.
How can you win like this?
You've to concentrate.
I'm concentrating!
You've got to use your brain!
Are you ready?
Ready.
Give me five.
Wait.
Why are you so sad?
It's OK!
Bingo! Won!
Why a fall?
It crashed. Give me money!
Don't worry, I'll pay.
It's still a lot
after deducting what you owe me.
Make it quick.
Jack!
Jack...
It's a set up, I won't take it.
I don't care what you're up to.
No tricks with me!
One of you must answer for it.
Or else I won't let it go.
Fine, we'll make the show go on.
Good. Stick to the rules.
Stay clear!
Go home!
How is it up there?
Who knows, it's a mess!
Did you see this girl?
- She's about 20.
- No!
Take a good look.
- She is my informer.
- No!
Go to hell.
Don't come close, it's dangerous!
Hairy, we can't find her.
Spread up and try again!
Are you alright?
They fired to force me out.
I couldn't get anything out.
This is all I could salvage.
I'm sorry!
Sorry!
A condom?
Out.
We can't go home. They're still around.
Let me help you.
Let's stay here tonight.
I'll find you another hiding place.
Don't help me anymore.
I owe you too much.
If my destiny let me survive.
Let me look after you,
before I leave.
OK?
It's my free will.
I'll never regret.
Excuse me.
Don't play game. Tell me where they are!
Speak up!
I don't know.
Say something!
This is Celia.
Be quiet!
It's that China girl.
You finally call.
Stop looking for me.
Give me a day, I'll see you tomorrow.
But I'll call first.
There is no towel.
I'll get you one.
Thank you.
Sorry to have got you into this state!
Never mind.
If that girl had called sooner,
you wouldn't have suffered that much.
- Sure...
- Take it as your birthday present!
Be careful!
Don't come over!
I've to counter attack!
I want to kill you bastard!
Mr. Cheung!
Mr. Cheung...
Sir, look!
Stop.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
You came out suddenly. I couldn't stop.
- Sorry...
- You're really OK?
Yes.
Your hand...
I'm here to give you this chain.
Will you forgive him?
He asked you to come?
Please forgive Frank, your son!
He even doesn't tell Frank
he's leaving HK today!
How can you be so cold?
Don't let Frank become a nobody child.
I was angry with him.
But I've always waited for his return.
I wonder you've said so.
Take a look please.
This one.
- This one?
- Right.
I'm at your dad's place.
He's going back to the States
this afternoon.
He's forgiven you.
Come quickly.
Don't hurry. Handle with care.
Sir, master is back.
Master is back.
Dad.
I've lost my wife.
I don't want to lose my son.
Uncle Man, we'll miss the plane.
So what?
This is a reunion.
Don't disturb them!
Come to the States and we can talk.
Sure.
Come, so you two can have a long talk.
Uncle Man, take good care of dad.
And yourself too.
Yes.
I'll take the luggage.
Remember to bring Celia together.
Where is Celia?
She left already.
Tonight, at the garage.
Boss, should we seek help?
Nonsense.
Just a chap and a girl!
Eat!
Did you get Fei's money?
He said later.
Later? I'll go myself.
When will the girl show up?
I don't know...
Don't know?
Tell me!
Tonight at the garage!
Are you checking out tonight?
Frank.
Where's the girl?
You can't protect her the whole life.
I'll use you as a bait.
The girl must be with you.
You want to play games?
I'll go wherever you go.
Handcuff me!
Angry?
Here's the police station. Blast it!
Keep cool.
Use your brain!
The chick will ruin your life.
Why are you always after her?
A fight?
I haven't had good fight for a long time.
Stop or I'll hurt you!
Stop!
I don't know what's between Paul and her.
You'll save her if you bring her to me.
Where's she now?
I want to know too.
For her own good only.
Paul ordered to kill her.
Tell her.
5 o'clock tomorrow at the Pier,
a boat will leave for China.
I've paid already.
Fetch your girl from the garage now.
How do you know she's there?
I've betrayed you.
I can't guarantee that's the last.
Her life is in your hands.
Your face?
I hope you can save her, my brother.
I owe you nothing now.
Where are you going?
I've been sucking from you too long.
It's time for me to be a hero.
It's worthwhile even if I lose to Dino.
Jack!
Boss, the girl is coming.
Where's the chap?
No.
Go to get him.
Yes.
- Hairy.
- What?
- No matter how, kill him.
- Alright.
- Move!
- Ok.
Let's go.
Let my friend go, he's innocent.
Let him go.
Alright!
Come on, shoot.
I've been looking for you.
Go, none of your business!
- You promised to let him go.
- Shut up!
You think you can cover it up?
If she dies, all will know
you've murdered your boss.
Are you threatening me?
Aren't you scared?
Bill, is the news reliable?
Why should I fool you?
- Follow me.
- Yes, sir.
Drive the car.
Get inside.
Move on quick!
Tell everyone stays away from the office.
Sorry.
You've helped me a lot.
I can't leave you this way.
No matter what, I'll help if I can.
You should have started a new life.
It's not the time for romance.
Drive faster!
Don't beat him.
I told you to shut up!
Are you afraid?
No!
What trick is this?
Stop the car!
Stop or I'll shoot you!
Stop!
Will you regret?
I won't.
Are you mad?
Stop!
Let him go. He's innocent.
Arrest me.
Send her away if you love her.
What are you looking at?
I must save Jack from trouble.
Wait for me at the pier.
You must come.
What are you looking at?
She'll leave by speedboat tonight.
Please take her there.
Me?
You'd rather let her die?
I'll come.
I didn't promise!
I'm a cop!
Get help if you can't manage!
Dummy!
I'm fit enough for this!
Your feeder isn't coming.
Hold your tears!
Want me to crush your head?
Here's your feeder.
Go and open your mouth!
Don't go.
No!
Playing tricks again?
Just once.
Let me be the hero!
I was a hero too!
Not moron.
You can make it?
Leave me alone!
Beat him!
A plastic leg?
Alright, give me back!
I want my leg!
That's enough!
How can a peg fight!
Go away, busybody!
Let's race?
Good. Tonight's race will be fun.
Let me look.
What have you put on your face?
Hair lotion?
Watch out!
Ready.
I'm still a fast racer!
Get away!
Fuck you!
Bump me if you dare!
You want to lose the other leg?
I started it. Let me help.
- Go away now!
- I'll go all out tonight.
I'll make it a tie at least.
Look! I've done it!
Keep chasing after Baldhead!
This ass is pretty fast.
Frank. Don't give up.
Frank, get his bike.
I will beat you.
Go to hell.
Quick!
We win...
Coming again?
Stand up, quick!
This won't help!
Is that enough?
My legs...
Worse than mine.
Celia is waiting for you.
Get away.
Monkey, lend me your van.
I'm in a hurry for marriage registration!
No way.
I'll beat you if you don't!
Get out!
Be careful. It's still on mortgage.
You bastard!
Why?
Bastard, I'll kill you!
Why did you shoot him?
Frank, stand up.
Stand up!
The bad times were over.
We're buddies, aren't we?
Stand up.
Don't leave me alone.
Celia is waiting for you.
Bill, please have mercy.
Why shouted at me?
I'll be in trouble if I delay.
Ok, 15 minutes more.
Ok, 15 minutes.
You promised. No more bargain.
Roger, Bill, roger.
Roger, sir.
Where are you?
At gas station.
What bloody station!
Paul's man killed the chap you wanted.
You're looking for trouble.
Bill, did you get it?
I'm coming back.
Go now.
Let's wait for Frank.
We are going now.
Why don't we wait for him?
Go!
We're keeping others waiting.
I'll wait for him
and tell him you're safe.
Shut up,
it's the first time I've begged you.
But now you refuse to help me!
Don't yield to me,
remember you're smuggling!
Shit!
Set off!
Please ask him
to bring me that handkerchief.
He gave it to me to dress my wound.
I keep it.
He'll recognize.
Thank you.
Celia...
Nothing.
Bye...
Take care...
You too, bye.