JAKE: When I was lying there
in the VA hospital,
with a big hole blown through
the middle of my life,
I started having
these dreams of flying.
I was free.
Sooner or later, though,
you always have to wake up.
(SIGHS)
(MONITOR BEEPING)
In cryo, you don't
dream at all.
It doesn't feel like 6 years.
More like a 5th of tequila
and an ass-kicking.
Tommy was the scientist,
not me.
He was the one who wanted to
get shot light-years out in space
to find the answers.
Are we there yet?
Yeah, we're there, sunshine.
We're there.
AGENT 1:
It's about your brother.
JAKE: So, a week before
Tommy's gonna ship out,
a guy with a gun
ends his journey
for the paper in his wallet.
You've been in cryo for 5 years,
9 months and 22 days.
You will be hungry.
You will be weak.
If you feel nausea,
please use the sacks...
JAKE:
Yeah, Tommy was the scientist.
Me, I'm just another dumb grunt going
someplace he's gonna regret.
Up ahead was Pandora.
You grew up
hearing about it,
but I never figured
I'd be going there.
Your brother represented
a significant investment.
We'd like to talk to you
about taking over his contract.
And since your genome is
identical to his,
you could step into his shoes,
so to speak.
AGENT 1: It'd be a fresh start
on a new world.
AGENT 2:
And the pay is good.
Very good.
Exo-packs on! Let's go!
Exo-packs on!
ASSISTANT:
Exo-packs on! Let's go!
Remember, people,
you lose that mask,
you're unconscious
in 20 seconds,
you're dead in 4 minutes!
Let's nobody be dead today!
Looks very bad on my report.
Hell's Gate tower,
this is TAV 1-6 on approach.
Crossing outer marker.
Mine is in sight.
JAKE:
One life ends,
another begins.
Harnesses off!
Get your packs!
Put it together, let's go! Let's go!
ASSISTANT: Harnesses off. 1 minute!
When that ramp comes down,
go directly into the base. Do not stop!
Go straight inside.
Wait for my mark!
Go, go, go, go!
Get out of there!
Keep moving!
Let's go, let's go!
JAKE: There's no such thing
as an ex-Marine.
You may be out,
but you never lose the attitude.
I told myself I could pass
any test a man could pass.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
They can fix a spinal,
if you got the money,
but not on vet benefits,
not in this economy.
Let's go, special case!
Do not make me wait for you!
Well, well,
ladies.
Look at all this
fresh meat! Whoo!
JAKE: Back on Earth, these guys
were Army dogs, Marines,
fighting for freedom.
AMPSUIT OPERATOR:
Look out, hot rod!
JAKE: But out here
they're just hired guns,
taking the money,
working for the company.
Check this out, man.
Meals on wheels.
Oh, man,
that is just wrong.
MAN 1: I got 2 guys
free in about 20 minutes!
MAN 2:
Got it! Need them!
QUARITCH:
You're not in Kansas anymore.
You are on Pandora,
ladies and gentlemen.
Respect that fact
every second of every day.
If there is a hell,
you might want to go there
for some R&R
after a tour on Pandora.
Out there, beyond that fence,
every living thing that crawls,
flies or squats in the mud
wants to kill you and
eat your eyes for Jujubes.
We have an indigenous population
of humanoids called the Na'vi.
They're fond of arrows
dipped in a neurotoxin
that'll stop your heart
in one minute.
And they have bones reinforced with
naturally occurring carbon fiber.
They are very hard
to kill.
As head of security,
it is my job to keep you alive.
I will not succeed.
Not with all of you.
If you wish to survive,
you need to cultivate
a strong mental attitude.
You've got to obey the rules.
Pandora rules.
Rule number 1...
JAKE: There's nothing like
an old-school safety brief
to put your mind at ease.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Jake!
You're Jake, right?
Tom's brother.
Wow! You look just like him.
Sorry, I'm Norm.
Spellman.
I went through avatar training
with him.
(CHUCKLING)
...into the bio-lab.
We're gonna spend
a lot of time up here.
Hey! How you doing?
Norm, avatar driver.
FEMALE SCIENTIST: Hi.
MALE SCIENTIST: Hey.
Link... Here's the link room
right here.
This is where we're connecting
to the avatar.
JAKE: Me and Norm
are here to drive
these remotely controlled bodies
called avatars.
And they're grown from human DNA
mixed with the DNA of the natives.
Hey. Welcome.
Hey.
Welcome to Pandora.
Good to have you.
Thanks.
(LAUGHS)
Damn! They got big.
Yeah, they fully mature
on the flight out.
So the proprioceptive sims
seem to work really well.
Yeah, they've got
great muscle tone.
It'll take us a few hours
to get them decanted,
but you guys can take them
out tomorrow.
There's yours.
Hey. Dr. Norm Spellman.
Dr. Max Patel. Great to meet you.
NORM: Good to meet you, yeah.
(HEARTBEAT THUMPING)
Looks like him.
No, it looks like you.
NORM:
This is your avatar now, Jake.
JAKE: And the concept is that every
driver is matched to his own avatar,
so that their nervous systems
are in tune,
or something.
Which is why they
offered me the gig,
because I can link
with Tommy's avatar,
which is insanely expensive.
Is this right? I just say
whatever to the video log?
Yeah, we gotta get in the habit
of documenting everything.
You know, what we see,
what we feel.
It's all part
of the science.
And good science
is good observation.
Plus it'll help to keep you sane
for the next 6 years.
All right.
Whatever.
So, uh...
Well, here I am,
doing science.
MALE TECHNICIAN:
They're coming out!
WOMAN ON PA:
Attention. Drivers coming out of link.
(SIGHING)
Oh, God.
(GROANS)
FEMALE TECH:
Where's the lab coat?
Who's got my goddamn
cigarette?
Guys! What's wrong
with this picture?
Thank you!
NORM:
Grace Augustine is a legend.
She's the head of the Avatar Program.
She wrote the book,
I mean, literally wrote the book
on Pandoran botany.
Well, that's 'cause she likes
plants better than people.
Here she is,
Cinderella back from the ball.
Grace, I'd like you to meet
Norm Spellman and Jake Sully.
Norm. I hear good things about you.
How's your Na'vi?
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(CHUCKLES)
Grace?
This is Jake Sully.
Ma'am.
Yeah, yeah.
I know who you are,
and I don't need you.
I need your brother.
You know, the PhD who trained
for 3 years for this mission?
He's dead.
I know it's a big inconvenience
for everyone.
How much lab training
have you had?
I dissected a frog once.
You see? You see?
I mean, they're just pissing on us
without even the courtesy of
calling it rain.
I'm going to Selfridge.
No, Grace,
I don't think that's a good idea.
No, man, this is such bullshit!
I'm gonna kick
his corporate butt.
He has no business sticking
his nose in my department.
Here tomorrow, 0800.
Try and use big words.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING ON RADIO)
Scorpion 2-Hotel,
Hell's Gate tower.
You are cleared
for south departure.
Hover taxi, Delta runway.
Squawk ident.
Mmm! You see that?
Yes, sir.
No, you didn't.
You were looking at the monitor.
I love this putter, Ronnie!
I love this putter.
Parker, you know, I used to
think it was benign neglect,
but now I see that you're
intentionally screwing me.
Grace, you know,
I enjoy our little talks.
Oops.
I need a researcher.
Not some jarhead dropout.
Well, actually,
I thought we got lucky with him.
Lucky?
Yeah.
How is this
in any way lucky?
Lucky your guy
had a twin brother,
and lucky that brother wasn't
some oral hygienist or something.
A Marine we can use.
I'm assigning him to your team
as security escort.
The last thing I need is another
trigger-happy moron out there!
Look, look, you're supposed
to be winning the hearts
and the minds
of the natives.
Isn't that the whole point
of your little puppet show?
If you look like them
and you talk like them,
then they'll start trusting us.
We build them a school,
we teach them English,
but after, what,
how many years?
Relations with the indigenous
are only getting worse.
Yeah, that tends to happen
when you use
machine guns on them.
Right. Come here.
I can't...
This is why we're here.
Unobtanium.
Because this little gray rock
sells for 20 million a kilo.
That's the only reason.
It's what pays for the whole party.
It's what pays
for your science.
Comprendo?
Now, those savages are
threatening our whole operation,
we're on the brink of war,
and you're supposed to be finding
a diplomatic solution.
So use what you've got,
and get me some results.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
So, how much link time
have you logged?
About 520 hours.
That's good.
You're in there.
You're here.
How much have you logged?
Zip. But I read a manual.
Tell me you're joking.
This is cool.
Let's go.
Don't. I got this.
(SIGHING) So you just figured
you'd come out here,
to the most hostile environment
known to man,
with no training of any kind,
and see how it went?
What was going
through your head?
Maybe I was sick of doctors
telling me what I couldn't do.
Biometrics are good.
Link 3 is ready.
Keep your arms in, hands in,
head down.
Down. Just relax and let
your mind go blank.
That shouldn't be
hard for you.
(CHUCKLING) Kiss the darkest part
of my lily white...
Initiate link.
Run sequence unit 3. Go.
LINK TECH:
Launching.
I have the first congruency.
That's a gorgeous brain.
Nice activity.
Hmm. Go figure.
Phase-lock 40%.
All right.
Going in.
I'm going in in 4.
Phase-lock 99%.
Link is stable.
(RESPIRATOR HISSING)
(DISTANTLY) He's in.
Jake, can you hear me?
Can you hear me, Jake?
Pupillary reflex is good.
Pinna response normal.
How you feeling, Jake?
Hey, guys.
(CHUCKLES)
Welcome to your new body, Jake.
FEMALE TECH:
Good!
Yeah, we're gonna take this
nice and easy, Jake.
And touch your thumb
to your fingers. Yeah.
Thumb to your fingers.
No problem.
That's good. I can see
you can remember that one.
Got it.
Well, if you want
to sit up,
that's fine.
Okay, good. Just take it
nice and slow, Jake. Good.
Okay, well, no truncal ataxia,
that's good.
Are you feeling lightheaded
or dizzy at all?
You're wiggling
your toes!
MALE TECH:
Good. Good, Jake. That's great.
(JAKE GASPING IN AMAZEMENT)
Distal motor control is good.
Good, Jake.
Are you feeling
any numbness or pain?
That's great, Jake. Hold on, now.
FEMALE TECH: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Take it easy.
Don't get ahead of yourself, okay?
There's a few more sensory motor
reflex tests we need to run,
so take it easy.
Ooh! Wait.
Jake.
Sit down, Jake.
Jake! Listen to me. Jake!
Whoa.
I need you to sit down.
Jake! It's okay.
Buddy, listen to me.
It's all good. I got this.
Jake, you need
to sit down right now.
Guys, get him back
on the gurney now.
Listen to me. For your own safety,
you need to sit down.
You need time to adjust to the avatar...
Whoa! Jake!
God, Jake, watch your tail.
(LAUGHING)
Yeah!
Sedate! Sedate him!
1,000 milligrams of Supitocam! Stat!
MAX:
Guys! Guys! Whoa! Whoa!
NORM ON INTERCOM:
By the numbers.
Jake. Come on.
Jake! Listen to me.
You're not used
to your avatar body.
This is dangerous.
This is great.
MAX: Jake? Jake, listen to me.
Come on. They're gonna put you out.
(JAKE LAUGHING)
MALE TECH:
Norm, sit down.
No, no. I gotta get
out of these leads.
God damn it!
Bring them home!
Norm! Do not leave control!
FEMALE TECH:
You're not ready for it!
Oh, come on,
you ain't got no skills.
Ooh! Ooh! So close!
I don't even have
to play defense on it.
Hey, guys. Hey.
MALE AVATAR: Whoa.
NORM:
It's okay, I'll get him.
Jake, you have to come back!
Jake! Jake!
Excuse me.
Watch it!
Sorry!
Come on!
Jake! We're not supposed
to be running!
(LAUGHING)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
Jeez! Sorry.
Watch it!
GRACE:
Hey, Marine!
Damn.
Grace?
Well, who'd you
expect, numbnuts?
Think fast.
Motor control's
looking good.
(CHUCKLING APPRECIATIVELY)
(CHUCKLES)
GRACE: Come on, everybody,
quiet down!
All right, gang, lights out.
Come on, Louise,
chop-chop.
Hey, hey, hey!
GRACE: Don't play with that,
you'll go blind.
That's kind of freaky.
Come on. Scat.
Good night.
Lights out!
See you at dinner, kiddies.
(CREATURES SCREECHING)
(SIGHS)
(GASPS)
MAX:
Welcome back.
You okay? You all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I'm Trudy. I fly all the science sorties.
And this here is my baby.
Hold on a second.
Hey, Wainfleet!
Get it done!
We bounce at zero-nine.
Yeah, I'm on it, capitaine!
Vine strike's still loose.
You guys are packing
some heavy gear.
Watch it!
Yeah, that's 'cause we're not the
only thing flying around out there.
Or the biggest.
I'm gonna need you on a door gun.
I'm a man short.
I thought you'd never ask.
There's your man.
See you on the flight line.
You wanted to see me, Colonel?
This low gravity'll make you soft.
You get soft,
Pandora will shit you out dead
with zero warning.
I pulled your record, Corporal.
Venezuela, that was
some mean bush.
Nothing like this here, though.
You got some heart, kid,
showing up in this neighborhood.
I figured it's just another hellhole.
I was First Recon myself.
A few years ahead of you.
Well, maybe more than a few.
3 tours Nigeria, not a scratch.
I come out here?
Day 1. Think I felt like
a shavetail louie?
Yeah. Oh, they could fix me up,
if I rotated back.
Yeah, and make me
pretty again.
But you know what?
I kind of like it.
It reminds me every day
what's waiting out there.
Hup! The Avatar Program
is a bad joke.
Bunch of limp-dick
science majors.
However, it does present an opportunity
both timely and unique.
Clear!
MAN: Clear!
(POWERING UP)
A recon gyrene in an avatar body.
That's a potent mix.
Give me the goose bumps.
Such a Marine could provide
the intel I need,
right on the ground.
Right in
the hostiles' camp.
Look, Sully. I want you to learn
these savages from the inside.
I want you
to gain their trust.
I need to know how to force
their cooperation
or hammer them hard
if they won't.
Am I still
with Augustine?
On paper.
Yeah, you walk like one of her
science pukes, you quack like one,
but you report to me.
Can you do that
for me, son?
Hell, yeah, sir.
Well, all right, then.
Son, I take care of my own.
You get me what I need,
I'll see to it you get your legs back
when you rotate home.
Your real legs.
That sounds real good, sir.
Link's ready!
LINK TECH:
Phase-lock 40%.
Just keep your mouth shut
and let Norm do the talking.
LINK TECH: I have 5 congruencies.
Phase-lock 90%.
MAX:
Link 3 ready.
GRACE:
All right, I'm going in.
(SQUAWKING)
(WHOOPING)
(CHUCKLING)
Shut it down.
We're gonna stay a while.
Norm! Your pack.
Pack.
Stay with the ship.
One idiot with a gun is enough.
You the man, Doc.
(DISTANT YOWLING)
(CREATURE COOING)
(SQUEAKING)
Prolemuris.
They're not aggressive.
Relax, Marine.
You're making me nervous.
NORM: So, how will
they know we're here?
GRACE: I'm sure they're
watching us right now.
JAKE:
Keep moving, Norm.
GRACE:
Keep up, guys!
And here I go.
NORM:
Scanning.
Oh, wow!
It's that fast?
(LAUGHING)
Amazing, isn't it?
Yeah.
So, that is signal transduction
from this root
to the root of
the tree next to it.
So, we should
take a sample.
NORM:
Okay. Sample.
You know, it's probably electrical,
based on the speed
of the reaction.
GRACE: Norm, you've contaminated
the sample with your saliva.
NORM:
Right.
(GASPS)
GRACE:
So, here I go.
(GRACE CONTINUES CHATTERING)
(LAUGHING)
(TRUMPETING)
Don't shoot. Don't shoot,
you'll piss him off.
(TRUMPETING)
It's already pissed off.
Jake, that
armor's too thick.
Trust me.
It's a territorial threat display.
Do not run, or he'll charge.
So, what do I do,
dance with it?
Just hold your ground.
(GROWLING)
(TRUMPETING)
(SCREAMING)
(SCREECHING)
(LAUGHING NERVOUSLY)
Yeah? Come on!
What you got?
Oh, yeah. Who's bad?
That's right.
Yeah, that's what
I'm talking about, bitch.
That's right, get your punk ass
back to mommy.
Yeah? Yeah, you got nothing.
You keep running.
Yeah, and why don't you bring back
some of your friends, huh?
(SNARLING SOFTLY)
(ROARING)
Oh, shit.
(CREATURES ROARING)
So what about this one?
Run? Don't run? What?
Run! Definitely run!
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(ROARING)
(GRUNTS)
I'm gonna have
to call it, guys.
We're not allowed to run night ops.
Colonel's orders.
I'm sorry, Doc, he's just gonna
have to hang on till morning.
He won't make it
till morning.
(CREATURES CHITTERING)
(PANTING)
(GROWLING)
(CREATURES GROWLING)
(CREATURES HISSING)
(GROWLING)
(GRUNTING)
(CHITTERING)
(SNARLING)
(SNARLS)
(HISSING)
I don't have
all goddamn night.
Come on!
(YELPS)
(YELPING)
(GRUNTING)
(SNARLING)
(YELPS)
(YELLING)
(YELPING)
(GRUNTING)
(HISSING)
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
JAKE:
Hey, wait. Don't!
(SCOFFS)
Great.
(WHIMPERING)
(GRUNTS)
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(WHIMPERING STOPS)
Look, I know you probably
don't understand this,
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
but thank you.
Thank you.
That was
pretty impressive.
I would have been screwed
if you hadn't come along. It was...
Hey, wait a second.
Hey, where you going?
Wait up!
Just... Hey, slow down.
Look, wait up, I just wanted to
say thanks for killing those things.
(EXCLAIMS IN PAIN)
Damn!
Don't thank.
You don't thank
for this.
This is sad.
Very sad only.
Okay. Okay.
I'm sorry.
Whatever I did,
I am sorry.
All this is your fault.
They did not need to die.
My fault? They attacked me.
How am I the bad guy?
Your fault!
Whoa!
(GENTLY)
Shh. Easy. Easy.
You're like a baby.
Making noise, don't know what to do.
Easy. Shh.
Fine. Fine.
If you love your little
forest friends,
why not let them
just kill my ass?
What's the thinking?
Why save you?
Yeah. Yeah, why save me?
You have a strong heart.
No fear.
But stupid!
Ignorant like a child.
(SCOFFS)
Well, if I'm like
a child, then...
Look, maybe you should
teach me.
Sky People cannot learn.
You do not See.
Well, then teach me
how to See.
No one can teach you to See.
Whoa.
Look, come on, can't we talk?
Say, where'd you learn
to speak English?
Dr. Augustine's school?
(GRUNTING)
You're like a baby.
(SIGHS)
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
I need your help.
You should not be here.
Okay, take me with you.
No! Go back.
No.
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
Go back.
(EXCLAIMING IN NA'VI)
No!
(SPEAKING SHARPLY IN NA'VI)
(REPEATS SOFTLY)
What...
What are they?
Seeds of the Sacred Tree.
Very pure spirits.
Uh-huh.
(CHUCKLES)
What was that all about?
(WHISPERING IN NA'VI)
Come.
Come!
Where are we going?
Come.
What's your name?
Shit!
(GROANING)
(GASPS)
(ALL ULULATING)
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Okay.
(YELLS)
(SHOUTING IN NA'VI)
(SPEAKING IN NA'VI)
What's going on?
(GROANING)
Wait.
(ORDERING IN NA'VI)
What's happening?
Hey!
(VILLAGERS CHATTERING)
(HUNTERS WHOOPING)
(NEYTIRI SPEAKING NA'VI)
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
What's he saying?
Hey, what's he saying?
My father is deciding
whether to kill you.
Your father.
It's nice to meet you, sir.
(ALL EXCLAIMING IN NA'VI)
(MO'AT SHOUTING IN NA'VI)
That is Mother.
She is Tsahik. The one
who interprets the will of Eywa.
Who's Eywa?
(IN ENGLISH)
What are you called?
Jake Sully.
(GRUNTS)
Why did you
come to us?
I came to learn.
We have tried to teach other
Sky People.
It is hard to fill a cup
which is already full.
Well, my cup is empty,
trust me.
Just ask Dr. Augustine.
I'm no scientist.
What are you?
I was a Marine. A...
A warrior of
the Jarhead clan.
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
(EXCLAIMS IN ANNOYANCE)
It is decided. My daughter
will teach you our ways.
Learn well,
Jakesully.
Then we will see if your insanity
can be cured.
(VILLAGERS CHATTERING)
(DRUMS BEATING)
(SINGING IN NA'VI)
(CHATTERING AND SINGING STOP)
(STAMMERING)
Good evening.
Please don't get up.
Excuse me.
(EXCLAIMS)
Sorry.
(CHATTERING
AND SINGING RESUME)
Hey, how you doing?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTING)
GRACE: (ECHOING) Jake. Jake!
MAX: He's in alpha.
He's coming out
right now.
Jake. Jake!
GRACE: Come on back, kid.
Come on. That's it.
(GASPING IN CONFUSION)
There you go.
You're okay.
Damn! You were
dug in like a tick.
(GROANING)
(SIGHS)
Is the avatar safe?
Yeah, Doc.
And you are not
gonna believe where I am.
(LAUGHS)
The last thing we see
is this Marine's ass
disappearing into the brush with
this angry thanator coming after him.
Hey, it's not something
you can teach.
MAX:
That is awesome.
You know, for reasons
I cannot fathom,
the Omaticaya have chosen you.
God help us all.
(MEN LAUGHING)
"Jarhead clan"?
Mmm-hmm.
(LAUGHING)
And it worked?
Hey, I'm practically family.
They're gonna study me.
I have to learn to be one of them.
That's called
taking the initiative, son.
I wish I had 10 more like you.
Look, Sully. Sully.
Just find out what
the blue monkeys want.
You know, I mean, we try to give
them medicine, education, roads.
But no, no, no,
they like mud.
And that wouldn't bother me,
it's just that they're...
Hey, can you...
Can somebody just... Sector 12.
Okay, go, go, go,
stop. Stop...
Rich, stop!
That's... Jesus!
Their damn village happens to be resting
on the richest unobtanium deposit
within 200 klicks in any direction.
I mean, look at all that cheddar!
(LAUGHS)
Well, who gets them to move?
Guess.
(SCOFFS)
What if
they won't go?
Oh, I'm betting
that they will.
Okay, okay, hey.
Look. Look.
Killing the indigenous
looks bad,
but there's one thing that
shareholders hate more than bad press,
and that's a bad
quarterly statement.
I didn't make
up the rules.
So just find me a carrot
that'll get them to move,
otherwise it's gonna
have to be all stick. Okay?
You got 3 months.
That's when the 'dozers get there.
Well, we're wasting time.
I like this guy.
MAX:
Guys, right now...
GRACE:
Okay, let's run through them again.
Mo'at. Dragon lady.
Eytucan. Eytukan.
He's the clan leader.
But she's the spiritual leader.
Like a shaman.
Got it.
T'su'tey.
Tsu'tey.
He'll be the next clan leader.
Neytiri.
She'll be the next Tsahik.
They become a mated pair.
So who's this Eywa?
(SHOCKED)
Who's Eywa?
Only their deity. Their goddess,
made up of all living things.
Everything they know!
You'd know this if you had
any training whatsoever.
Who's got a date
with the chief's daughter?
Come on. That's...
GRACE: All right, knock it off, you two.
Let's go.
Village life starts early.
Don't do anything
unusually stupid.
JAKE:
Easy, boy.
Pale is female.
(NEYTIRI SPEAKING
SOOTHINGLY IN NA'VI)
JAKE:
Okay. Easy, girl.
(GRUNTING)
(SPEAKING SOOTHINGLY IN NA'VI)
(WHINNYING)
(EXHALING)
That is tsaheylu.
The bond.
Feel her.
Feel her heartbeat.
Her breath.
Feel her strong legs.
You may tell her what to do.
Inside.
For now, say where to go.
Forward!
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHING)
You should go away.
No, you'd miss me.
I knew you could speak English.
(SCOFFING)
(SPEAKS NA'VI)
Again.
JAKE:
If you want to hit this thing,
it's gonna be complicated.
Your scan doesn't show
the internal structure.
There's an outer row of columns.
QUARITCH: Uh-huh.
Real heavy duty.
There's a secondary ring here,
and an inner ring.
There's a core structure
like a spiral.
That's how they move
up and down.
We're gonna need accurate scans
on every column.
Roger that.
What else can you tell us about
the structure?
JAKE: I'm guessing this secondary ring,
that's also load-bearing.
So where are we going?
Getting out of Dodge.
I'm not about to let Selfridge and
Quaritch micro-manage this thing.
There's a mobile link up at Site 26
we can work out of,
way up in the mountains.
The Hallelujah Mountains?
That's right.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Yes!
(NORM LAUGHING)
The legendary floating mountains
of Pandora.
Heard of them?
We're getting close.
Yeah, look at my instruments.
Yep. We're in the Flux Vortex.
We're VFR from here on.
What's VFR?
Means you gotta see
where you're going.
You can't see anything.
(LAUGHING)
Exactly. Ain't that a bitch?
Oh, my God.
(LAUGHING)
You should see your faces.
Thank you for
flying Air Pandora.
(AIRLOCK HISSING)
Welcome to camp.
GRACE:
So, this is my bunk.
This stuff is nasty.
GRACE: Norm, go under.
NORM: All right.
JAKE:
Grace didn't miss a thing.
GRACE:
Trudy, you'll take the top one.
She knew I was talking
to the Colonel.
But I had what she needed,
a way back in with the clan,
so she's playing nice.
All right. Jake, hang a left.
You'll be in the link at the end.
Unit one. Beulah.
She's the least glitchy.
(IMITATING BIRD CALL)
(BIRDS CAWING)
(SQUAWKING)
(LAUGHING NERVOUSLY)
Holy shit!
Do not look in her eye.
(SPEAKING NA'VI)
Ikran is not horse.
Once tsaheylu is made,
ikran will fly with only one hunter
in the whole life.
To become taronyu,
hunter,
you must choose your own ikran
and he must choose you.
When?
When you are ready.
(EXCLAIMS)