'If anyone finds this,
it means my plan...
didn't work...
and I'm already dead.
- Evan?
- I think he's in here.
But if I can somehow
go back to the beginning
- all of this, I might be able
- Evan!
To save her.'
Evan!
We're gonna be
late again.
When did you ever care
about getting to school on time?
We're putting up pictures
for parents' night.
Don't worry,
you'll have plenty of time.
Is Dad gonna come?
You know the answer to that.
Can't he just
come out for one day?
We've been over this 100 times.
It's too dangerous for him.
But Lenny said
his dad's coming,
and Tommy
and Kayleigh's dad...
Okay, I get the point.
But I'm not so bad, am I?
No.
Okay, have a great day.
I love you.
I'll pick you up later. Gotta go.
Bye.
Bye!
Mrs Treborn, I need
to speak with you.
Can it wait till tonight?
I'm late for work and...
I think you really
need to see this.
Tommy, leave Lenny alone.
Don't make me send you
to Mr Voytek's office.
I was gonna show this
to the principal,
but I thought I should
talk to you first.
What is it?
Yesterday I had all the children
make drawings
of what they wanted to be
when they grew up.
Most of them made drawings
of what their parents did.
But this...
I don't understand.
Evan did this?
- Can I keep this drawing?
- Oh, of course.
Um, there is one more thing,
Mrs Treborn,
- I feel bad even mentioning.
- What?
When I asked Evan
about the drawing,
well, he couldn't
remember doing it.
I don't wanna go.
I don't like this place, Mum.
I think it's creepy.
I promise I won't
make any bad pictures.
You're gonna be fine, okay?
He just wants to do
a couple tests, that's all.
- Oh.
- You'll like him.
That's good.
You're doing great.
Just tell me he hasn't inherited
his father's illness.
I'm sure the test results
will come back negative.
But there's something else you can do
to monitor his memory.
- Anything.
- A journal.
Just have him write down
everything that he does.
- And what will that do?
- It could help jog his memory.
See if he remembers
anything new the next day.
These test results
will come back in a few days
- and we'll take it from there.
- Okay.
'Today Mummy is taking me
to play with Kayleigh and Tommy.
I will meet their father
and see what a real dad is like.'
Great, see you soon.
Evan...
Evan, what are you doing
with that knife?
What happened?
Honey...
what were you doing
with that knife?
I don't remember.
- Hey, Andrea.
- George.
Hello, little man.
Watch your step.
Thanks, George.
- Not a problem.
- Here's my number at the hospital
in case there are any problems.
And please keep
an eye on him 'cause...
What, are you kidding?
We're going to have
a great time today, right, sport?
Okay, be good, kiddo.
I love you.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye, George.
Go long. Go on.
Right in the backyard.
Here it comes.
Evan, Evan, guess what?
Dad got a new video camera
and we're all going
to be in a movie.
That's right, Evan.
And you get to be the star.
I thought I was the star.
Hey, what did I tell you?
Now, Evan...
You have to promise
your bestest,
super-duper promise
that this will be
our little secret.
- You think you can do that?
- Um-hmm.
I'm r...
Where am I?
Where did we all go?
Calm down, kid, stand still.
I was just somewhere else.
How did I get here?
Quit acting like some damn retard,
or I'll call your mother
and tell her what a naughty
little shit you've been.
Kayleigh...
what happened?
The good news is
the results are negative.
I found no evidence of lesions,
haemorrhaging, tumours.
But you must have
something you can go on.
If I was to guess, I'd say
the blackouts are stress related.
But he's seven years old.
What kind of stress
can a seven-year-old have?
Plenty. Maybe he has
severe coping problems
about not having a father.
You said the last time
the blackouts occurred
he was visiting
his friend's dad.
Well, he has been pushing me
to meet his father
- and I've been putting it off.
- It's worth a shot, Andrea.
We can arrange
a controlled meeting.
A careful dose of sedatives
for Jason, some security,
Evan comes in
for a quick visit,
and with a little luck,
no more
missing father complex.
'April 15th.
Today I get to meet my father.
His name is Jason
and he's crazy.
I hope he lets me
call him Dad.'
You mean Dad lives here?
Not in this wing, actually, no.
Now if your dad seems
a little sleepy,
it's because
of the medicine, okay?
Okay.
It'll just be a moment, okay?
It's okay. I won't bite.
You've seen pictures
of me, right?
Uh-huh. Mum says
I have your smile
and your hair.
Nooo!
He has to die!
It's the only way!
Jason, stop!
No!
It's gonna be okay.
It's gonna be alright.
He's hurt bad.
Get a stretcher.
- Come on, let's get him out of here.
- I'm so sorry.
In sure and certain hope
of the resurrection
to eternal life,
we commend to almighty God,
our brother Jason.
The Lord bless him
and keep him,
the Lord make his face
to shine upon him,
and be gracious unto him
and give him peace. Amen.
Come on, where is it?
Damn, I know it's down here somewhere.
Tommy, I'm bored shitless
over here. What's up already?
Yeah, what are you
looking for, anyway?
Shut up, lard arse. And you,
hold your fucking horses.
You know,
it's here somewhere.
We should go soon.
If dad catches us smoking
down here, we're dead.
So let's go.
I knew Dad had
a blockbuster down here!
Let's blow the shit
out of something.
Here you go, buddy.
What? No freaking way.
- I'm not touching this thing.
- The hell you aren't.
Any of us does it and you're gonna
puss out and nark for sure.
Ain't gonna work this time, buddy.
Look how small this fuse is.
- I'll get killed.
- Not necessarily.
There you go.
It should buy you
two minutes at least.
Gee thanks, friend.
Aw, for Christ's sake,
Lenny, you moron, just do it.
- Thanks.
- You got balls, man.
Shit took you long enough.
What the hell? Come on!
Evan, come on.
Help me get him up!
Evan, get your arse back here
and help me get him up.
What the hell happened?
Where are we?
Oh my God.
What did we do?
Evan, come on. Help me.
Oh my God, how could we?
- Come on, let's go!
- Shit, Lenny, what happened to you?
He's fine.
He's gonna be okay.
Everything's gonna be fine.
What's wrong with him?
Why isn't he speaking?
He's in shock, ma'am.
What is it?
What happened?
We were just in the woods
building a fort
when Lenny freaked out.
One minute he was okay,
and then he just froze up.
Right, guys?
What happened, Evan?
The truth.
I don't know.
I don't remember.
Something must have happened.
Something set him off.
I blacked it out.
Don't try to use your blackouts
to get out of this one.
You're not making it up?
Breathe in and breathe out.
And relax.
You are completely asleep.
Relaxed.
I want you to take me
to the time
you were in the woods
with Lenny.
Think of it like a movie.
You can pause, rewind,
or slow down
any details you wish.
Understand?
Yes.
Where are you now?
I'm standing next to Kayleigh.
My hands are over her ears.
Are you hurting her?
No, I'm protecting her.
Okay.
Now let's move forward in time.
What do you see?
I see a car.
Yes, Evan,
tell me about the car.
Go on.
Nothing can hurt you.
Remember, it's only a movie.
You are completely safe.
I can't...
The car vanishes
and all of a sudden
I'm on the ground
in the woods.
The car doesn't vanish, Evan.
The movie in your head
is broken, that's all.
Now tell me about the car.
I can't!
It's coming...
Fight it, Evan, hurry.
It's coming!
- Oh my God!
- On the count of 10,
- you'll wake up feeling refreshed...
- What are you doing?
...and remembering everything
that we talked about.
What is happening?
Make it stop!
One, you're feeling awake. Two,
your eyes are not feeling as heavy.
- Five, six.
- Wake up!
- Come on, Evan, wake up! Nine, 10.
Oh God.
What happened?
Did it work?
Alright, thanks, Mum.
See you later.
Wipe that sad-arse look
off your face
before you get us busted.
Did you see the way Evan's mum
was looking at you?
Sorry.
Alright, will someone
tell me already
what the hell happened
with the mailbox?
Don't you ever
bring that shit up again.
Not ever!
Let's go.
Are you okay?
Holy shit!
Look at that fat fuck!
He's got bigger titties
than Lenny's mum.
- Shhh!
- Shut up, faggot.
No one's talking to you.
I'm sorry, Kayleigh,
this was a bad idea.
You really don't remember
anything that happened?
You're so lucky.
Look, everything's
gonna be okay.
Lenny'll be fine. You'll see.
Sorry.
It's not your fault.
Mrs Kagan called Dad
and blamed us
for what happened to Lenny.
Your dad did that?
- I deserve a lot worse.
- What are you talking about?
What you deserve is
a better father and brother.
All they do is
make you feel like shit.
You really have no clue
how beautiful you are, do you?
What the fuck are you doing?!
Buying popcorn.
What the fuck are you doing?
- Whoops.
- I can't believe you freaking did that.
- He's a little punk.
- Why are you being such a dick?
I can't believe
what you just did.
Stop it!
Stop hitting him.
What's wrong with you?
Somebody, please help us.
Alright, that's it, kid.
You're out of here.
Get him away! Get him away!
Now in another story,
the peaceful town of Briarville
was rocked this afternoon
in the wake of a horrible
act of vandalism.
While police officials
in upstate New York believe
this was a simple act
of criminal mischief gone awry,
the tragedy has clearly
devastated the community.
Now this was the grisly aftermath
of a powerful explosion
believed to have been caused
by an unknown quantity of dynamite.
The police have no leads,
no suspects and no motive...
Good night.
We're moving.
I can't believe
Tommy's still pissed at me.
He knows
I'm moving away, right?
He's been acting
real strange lately.
He won't even look me
in the eyes anymore.
Duck, here they come!
Did your mum say
if Lenny was okay?
He must be. I mean,
they're letting him out, right?
Welcome home.
I thought you might like
some fresh air for a change.
- Is Tommy with you guys?
- No. It's cool.
So, what'd you do in there?
It was awful.
You can't sleep because
everybody's screaming
all night long.
I never want to go back.
Do you see that?
Yeah, what's up
with the smoke?
Crockett!
What are you doing
with my dog?!
- Look what you made me do!
- What the hell's wrong with you?!
Kayleigh. Oh, God, come on,
please wake up.
Wake up, please!
Wake up!
Why don't you fucking kiss her,
Prince Charming?
Ow.
How long was I out?
Kayleigh, what's wrong?
Oh shit.
I'm sorry.
Aced it.
And time.
Put your pencils down
and place your bluebooks
on my desk before you leave.
You too, Mr Nelson. We're all
in the same time-zone, here.
So how'd you do, Evan?
I don't know. I might have got
some of the stories mixed up.
Was it Pavlov that conditioned
his dog to lick his nuts?
Typical psych major,
a complete wise-arse.
And how's your project coming?
Are you still planning to change
the way we humble scientists
- view memory assimilation?
- Don't really have a choice.
Oh, jeez, it smells like
patchouli and arse in here.
Cricket, this is my well-mannered
roommate, Evan.
Yeah...
you're the one
that fucked up the bell curve
on my anthropology final.
- Later, Thumper.
- Bye.
Fucking dick.
- Wow, sweet girl, man.
- I found your shirt, bro'.
Oh, you sick fuck.
Alright, man, get dressed.
You're taking me out.
Why, what'd you do,
ace another midterm?
No.
Better than that,
seven years, no blackouts.
Fuck yeah, bro',
let's do this!
- Oh, yeah!
- Yeah! Come and get it.
Be gentle with me! Be gentle!
I'm postcoital. I'm tender.
Did she cradle the balls
and work the shaft?
Nice.
Look at this fucking guy.
Get the fuck out of my bar.
So, which one of you
has the pet worm?
Worms, plural!
Ah. That's so gross.
Talk to him about it.
He's got the fetish.
Watch it.
It's a psych project actually.
It's a study on memory loss.
Better explain before all this excitement
gives me a heart attack.
10 bucks says he
eats it off the floor.
Well, if I can figure out
how the memories
in a simple worm function,
it should help me to understand
the complexities...
of the human brain.
Let me get this shot.
- What the fuck, weirdo?!
- Fuck this...
Well, I guess
that's your game.
Go, you go.
It smells like sex in here.
Yeah, Thumper had
a busy afternoon.
You're kidding?
He's so big.
Yeah.
Well, I guess charisma
and eyeliner go a long way.
- You want a beer?
- Yeah.
You got any incense or scented candles
or something?
Okay.
Whoa, no.
Let me put this away.
Most guys usually tuck porn
under their bed.
All you've got
are comp books?
Yeah, they're my journals.
I've been keeping them
since I was seven.
Wow.
Read me something.
I ought to be getting
something out of this.
That's all I've got to say.
Here we go.
'It's like my mind refuses
to believe what I'm seeing.'
'... Hearing Crockett
make those awful screams.
Just writing about it
gives me the shivers.'
Come on. Go on.
'It was like Tommy
was possessed or something.
There was a hate
in his eyes that... '
Are you okay?
Where am I?
What the hell's going on?
I can't get it open!
Drop it or I'll slit
your mother's throat in her sleep.
Uhh! I got him, Lenny.
Save Crockett!
Listen to me, Evan,
and you listen to me good.
There's a million
other sisters in the world,
so why'd you have
to fuck with mine?
It's okay.
It was just a dream.
Uh-huh...
it didn't feel like a dream.
Maybe because
they never do.
So, Don Juan, you pass out
on all your dates?
Lenny...
hey, I've got a surprise for you.
You're never gonna
guess who's here.
Hey, it's me... Evan.
What are you working on there?
A model?
Look, uh...
I can see that you're busy,
so I'll try to make this quick.
Remember, uh...
that day at the junkyard
when we were kids?
I was just hoping that you
could help me remember.
Like, just any details about it or...
I couldn't cut the rope.
Yeah...
that's good. Um...
anything else?
'Drop it or I'll slit
your mother's throat in her sleep! '
Uh...
Jesus Christ.
It really happened.
Wow, uh...
Wow, Lenny, l...
'Make one peep
and I swear it'll be
your last, motherfucker.'
'The last thing I remember
before the blackout
was holding my hands
over Kayleigh's ears.
I think I was more
focused on her hands
on mine
than on the mailbox...
across the street.'
Maybe it went out,
should someone check it?
Yeah, you do that, Lenny.
You make one peep and I swear
it'll be your last, motherfucker.
Ugh!
Fuck!
What's this?
Huh? What's this?
Want to get the mail?
How's my sweet girl?
You need a change,
don't you, honey?
You wanna open it?
- Oh my God!
- Holy shit!
Run!
Fuck, Lenny, come on!
Lenny, come on!
Come on, Lenny, let's go!
No, baby. That's my finger
in your arse.
Christ, man.
Fuckin' brutal!
What the...?
- Hello.
- Hello. Who is this?
Mrs Kagan, um,
it's Evan... Treborn.
I hope you know
how much you upset Lenny.
Yeah, I'm... look,
I'm really sorry about that.
It took me over an hour
to clean up the mess you made.
Can I just talk to Lenny?
Don't call here.
Mum.
I can't help it.
I'm just so proud of you.
Hey, did... did Dad...
Did Jason get good grades?
Please, he got straight As
without ever touching a book.
It was the one area
his memory never failed him.
Did he ever say that he, like...
figured out a way to recall
his lost memories
like years after he blacked them out
in the first place?
- Why do you ask?
- No, I just figured with him being
you know, such a brain and all
it's like, you would think
that he would figure out
a way to remember
stuff that he forgot.
Well, when he was your age...
almost exactly your age
come to think of it,
he said he figured out
a way to remember his past.
I couldn't tell
if they were real memories
or just his imagination.
Then, just before
it got so bad, he...
had to be institutionalised,
he said he could...
What?
What... what did he do?
Forget it.
It's nothing.
He was far too sick by then.
'I never wanted to be
in the movie, anyway.
I was cold, so I wanted
to wear my clothes.
Mr Miller took my shirt off.'
What the fuck are you doing?
Shhh, I need quiet for this.
Are you stupid or what, man?
Maybe there's a reason
you repressed the day
some pervert had you
in your tighty whities.
I'd think twice
about what you're doing.
You could wake up a lot more
fucked up than you are now.
- More fucked up than I already am?
- No, l...
You think you know me?
I don't know me!
Whoa!
I'm sorry.
No, it's my fault.
Can we get through
one damn day
without you
breaking something?
Hey.
Evan.
Oh my God.
It's been a long time.
How you been?
Same old, same old,
you know?
No, I don't know.
Fill me in.
Uhh, well...
I'm going to State now.
It's going good.
My Mum's good.
- I don't know.
- You want a smoke?
- No, not since we were kids.
- No?
I've quit like 100 times.
- Are you walking home?
- Uh-huh.
- Can I walk you?
- Sure.
- Oh my God.
- So...
how's Tommy?
Well, they kept him
in juvie for a few years,
but now he's working
over at Dale's Auto Body.
That's good.
Still living with your dad?
No.
I emancipated myself at 15.
Must've taken a lot of courage.
Not if you remember my dad.
Well, couldn't you have just
moved in with your mum?
No, she had a new family.
Wasn't enough room.
Whatever.
Well look, the reason
I came back to town
was to talk to you.
To me? Why?
Well...
remember when we were kids
and I used to have
those blackouts?
Yeah, of course.
Well, some of those memories
have been coming back to me.
And I just...
I wanted to talk to you
about one of them in particular.
Well, I'll try to remember.
When we were kids, uh...
your dad was making a movie
about Robin Hood... something.
What do you want
to know, Evan?!
Is... did he...
What happened
in the basement?
Look, it was a long time ago.
I know.
Is that why you came
all the way back here?
To ask a lot of stupid questions
about Robin Hood?
No, l...
I just think that something really bad
might have happened.
Is there a point
to any of this?
Look, whatever happened
it wasn't our fault.
We were kids. I mean, there was nothing
that we could do to deserve...
Just shut up, Evan!
You're wasting your breath.
You can't hate yourself 'cause
your dad's a twisted freak.
Who are you trying
to convince, Evan?
You come all the way back here
to stir up my shit
just because you have
a bad memory?
What, do you want me to just cry
on your shoulder
and tell you everything's
all better now?
Well, fuck you, Evan!
Nothing's all better, okay?
Nothing ever gets better.
You know, if I was
so wonderful, Evan,
why didn't you call me?
Why did you just
leave me here to rot?
When he was your age... almost exactly
your age, come to think of it...
he said he figured out a way
to remember his past.
Some dude left
a message for you.
You can smell that all the way
to the bathroom.
Hi, Evan, this is Professor Carter.
I just wondered why you didn't
hand in your essay this afternoon.
I was a bit concerned.
Call me to schedule a make-up.
What'd you say
to my sister, motherfucker?
Last night she cried on the phone
for over an hour to me.
She said you came
and saw her last night.
She...
she fucking
killed herself tonight.
She's dead...
and so are you!
'If the scar on my stomach
didn't just come out of nowhere,
maybe my father wasn't
as crazy as everyone thought.
If I can make scars, do I have
the power to heal them?
What about Kayleigh's scars? '
'I never wanted
to be in the movie, anyway.
It was cold, so I wanted
to wear my clothes.
But Mr Miller took my shirt off.'
I've got an idea.
Let's go down to the basement.
It'll look more like
a dungeon down there.
A little light here.
Huh?
Hey, now what did I tell you
about keeping that door shut?
But I wanna see.
You're going to see the back of my fist
in about two seconds
if you don't do what I tell you.
Now, in this part of the story,
Robin Hood has just
married Maid Marian
and they have to kiss and stuff,
like the grown-ups do.
So, take off
your clothes, Kayleigh.
Come on, just like
when we take a bath.
Don't make a big deal out of it.
You too, Evan.
Come on, let's go. Let's go.
We're making a movie here.
Put your hands on your ears.
What time is it?
It's time for you to do
what I tell you to do.
Wrong answer, fuckbag!
This is the very moment
of your reckoning.
In the next 30 seconds, you're going
to open up one of two doors.
The first door will forever
traumatise your own flesh and blood.
What... what's happening?
How are you doing this?
It'll change your daughter
from a beautiful child
into an empty shell
whose only concept of trust
was betrayed by her own
sick paedophile father!
Ultimately...
it'll lead to her suicide.
- Nice work, Daddy.
- Who are you?
Let's just say you're being
closely watched, George!
Your other option is
to treat Kayleigh like...
say like a loving father
treats his daughter.
Sound okay to you, Papa?
Yes.
Listen close then, fuckbag.
You screw this up again,
I'll flat out castrate you.
What you need to do
is discipline your son Tommy,
because the kid
is one sadistic pup.
One last thing.
Don't ever touch me again!
I... I won't.
Ahhh!
Faster, faster!
Crockett!
Kayleigh, I can't believe
you came!
I think you got one.
Check out our new house.
- Forever.
- Hell or high water.
Honey, are you alright?
Oh my god, Evan,
you're bleeding.
Kayleigh, you're still... You...
Incredible.
Well, thanks. Go get cleaned up
and come back to bed.
Ohh. Where are my clothes?
Those are your clothes, silly.
The bathroom is...
Hurry up. I want a quickie
before school.
What?
Unfucking believable.
Alright.
I wish I could get as excited
over a nosebleed.
Sorry, uh, I didn't
see you there.
What?
You're the girl that
was with those arseholes
throwing popcorn at Thumper.
What?
And your name is Gwen.
I know you.
Seriously, Evan,
lay off the blow.
- Hi.
Hey, um...
don't freak out
when I ask you this, but...
do you remember when your dad
got that video camera?
What's up, man?
Yeah, um...
I think he had it like
the first day
and then he gave it away
or something.
Why would that freak me out?
I don't know.
Just being weird.
You are such a goofus.
So I'll see you tonight.
Okay.
- Andrea...
- Evan...
- and Chuck...
- aren't home right now.
You know what to do.
Uh, hey, Mum.
It's me. And hey, Chuck.
Ah, I'm just calling
to say hi, I guess.
Give me a call back.
Hey, Thumper, do you know
what time it is, man?
What's the matter,
you lost your Rolex?
Fuck you, frat boy!
Remember, everyone,
there's only two more weeks
until your psych projects
are due.
Uh, about that essay
I missed last week,
we're still okay
with the extension, right?
And you are?
Evan... Treborn.
Well, the answer's no, Mr Treborn.
Now please take your seat.
The exam is about to begin.
Alright, settle down, everyone.
The exam will begin
in one minute.
Get off me, arsehole.
You guys started that shit.
Evan, you're hysterical.
Did you study for this?
Oh, uh...
we'll find out.
Me neither.
Holy shit!
Are these the answers?
Damn, Evan,
keep it on the dl.
Hey, uh...
I want to do something special
for Kayleigh tomorrow night.
Uh, so if I said that I needed
some help from you
and the brothers...
I'd say, 'blow me.'
Get the pledges to do it.
- Right, the pledges.
- Yeah.
You may begin now.
Oh, that was so good.
Oh my God.
Where'd you learn
those new tricks?
Why?
It... it wasn't weird, was it?
Yeah, if you call
multiple orgasms weird.
Hello?
- Fuck 'em.
- Hello?
Oh.
What do you think
it is about us
that makes us so perfect?
I mean...
why did you sneak out
to visit me
after I moved away?
'Cause I missed you.
What, do you think my dad could have
stopped me from seeing you?
What's he gonna do?
Oh, my gosh.
My toes are numb.
Do you think that we'll
be together forever?
That is the plan, isn't it?
'Hell or high water'?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's...
I was just making sure.
Yeah, that's the plan!
Alright, uh...
all you rushes, you know
what you have to do for me.
Pledges, uh...
we're pledges, sir.
Uh, brother Evan, sir.
Are you kidding me?
What?
What did you say to me?
You know what, give me the Greek
alphabet. Give it to me!
- Uhh-uhh.
- Alpha, beta...
- Alpha, beta, gamma, delta...
epsilon, zeta, eta, theta,
iota, kappa, lambda, mu, nu, xi,
omicron, pi, rho, sigma, tau,
upsilon, phi, chi, psi, omega, Sir.
Maybe that's what it is.
Don't fucking look at me, look down.
Uh...
alright, um...
so, you... you pledges
you guys know what
you need to do for me.
And you guys take a shower
and if anyone
gives you any trouble,
you tell 'em I said it was okay.
What?
Shower that, bitch.
I don't understand.
Where are you taking me?
I'm not telling.
Oh my God!
Wow, it's beautiful.
Go on, sit down.
Thank you.
! You gave us
some place to go!
! I never said
thank you for that...!
Why are you doing this for me?
When I woke up this morning...
I saw your smile.
That smile.
And I knew
that I wanted to spend
the rest of my life
with you.
! Now I'll never
have a chance!
! May angels
lead you in...!
I've been looking
all over for you, man.
Someone trashed your car.
What the...
Who did this?!
Who did it?!
It was probably
those Beta fuckers.
No, no, no.
How did somebody
get away with this
right in front
of the frat house?
- Dude, what is that, a dog collar?
- Tommy.
Don't.
He might be watching.
It's my fault.
I should have told you
he was released a few weeks ago.
Yeah, it might have been nice.
God.
Like this is gonna
do any good.
Maybe one of the frat guys
has got a gun.
Evan, don't even joke!
He's not going
to hurt you, okay?
He's just trying to scare you
away from me.
He killed my dog.
- You don't remember that?
- Evan, it's not his fault.
You know how bad he had it
when we were kids.
Oh no, don't give me
this bad upbringing shit.
You turned out just fine.
My father never
laid a hand on me.
It's like that prick
saved it all up for Tommy.
Okay. Alright. Uh...
We'll let campus security
deal with it. Okay?
You know what?
I think I should sleep alone.
No, you're not staying alone.
I'm staying with you.
Evan, I just... I don't want Tommy
to see us together right now.
No, I lost you once
and I'm not losing you again.
What do you mean
you lost me once?
Evan, you've never lost me.
What are you talking about?
God, you've been
acting so weird lately.
Look, my car just got wrecked, okay?
I'm kind of freaking out.
I know that, but...
your accent's changed.
- You don't even walk the same.
- What, I walk differently?
I mean, that dinner tonight,
it was so beautiful.
It was gorgeous.
But it just wasn't you.
I can't do
something nice for you?
Wait...
isn't that your jacket?
Tommy!
You stay away from us,
you sick fuck.
Oh, get this 'us' shit.
Like I'd ever lay a hand
on my own sister.
You're doing real nice
for yourself, Evan.
You've got a nice life,
you got nice friends,
not to mention
you're fucking my sister.
Not a bad piece of arse
if I say so myself.
- Shut up, Tommy!
- Oh, come on. That's a compliment.
What are you doing, man?
What the fuck?
Oh, it's not good enough that
the whole fucking world loves you?
But you've got to take
the only thing on this Earth
that doesn't think
that I'm a piece of shit?
You know I love you.
No one thinks that
you're a piece of shit, Tom.
What was it you said?
I think I believe it was, 'sick fuck'!
Don't! Tommy!
Stop!
Stop! Oh my God!
Oh my God!
Oh!
No, Evan!
Stop!
Stop it!
- You're gonna kill him!
- He's a fuckin' maniac!
Don't do this,
I'm begging you!
You ruined Lenny's life!
You killed Crockett!
You killed
that woman and her baby!
Now you're trying to kill me.
Just tryin' to fucking kill me!
Oh my God!
Oh my God,
what did you do?
Oh my God!
You right there, faggot!
First time?
Yeah.
You'd better not
bitch up, man.
You'll wind up someone's
luggage that way.
Can you protect me?
Jesus himself
couldn't make me stand up
against the brotherhood.
Look, man...
when they come,
you go someplace else
in your head, man.
Be somewhere else.
Back your arse up.
Yo, gimme that.
I spoke to your lawyer.
And he says he's sure
he can get you off
on self-defence.
So if you're just patient...
Mum...
How long am I gonna
be in here?
I don't know.
These things take time.
What about the journals?
Did you bring the ones
I asked you to bring?
I found these two.
The others are still in storage.
Mum! I...
I need them all,
all of them.
And I'm going
to get them to you,
but right now, you need
to concentrate on the case.
Please.
Alright.
You're right.
What about Kayleigh?
Is she alright?
Try to tell her I'm sorry.
Time's up.
I'm not going
to lose you, kiddo.
Promise me you'll hang on.
Shit on my dick
or blood on my knife.
They're mine...
Come on!
Back the fuck off!
Show's over, ladies!
Put this maggot
back in his cell.
Move it!
Come on, let's go!
We'll be seeing you
later on tonight, little sister.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Come on, Reese.
You're religious, Carlos,
you believe in that whole bit,
the Lord works
in mysterious ways?
Straight up, man.
'Cause I think Jesus sent me
to your cell for a reason.
For you to help me.
Shit.
I knew you were crazy, man.
I ain't bullshitting you.
Jesus speaks to me
in my dreams.
Oh, yeah?
That's cool. Great.
A pack of smokes says
I can prove it to you.
When I'm out, I need you to watch
my hands and face closely.
You need to see
the prison shrink, man.
Just tell me if you see
anything just... weird.
Weirder than this?
It could be marks.
It could be scars.
It could be anything,
I don't know.
'On Wednesday, I got in trouble
for a drawing I didn't do.
Mummy won't let me see it.
Hey, no monkey business, Evan.
Sit down and finish your drawing.
That's great, everyone.
Just imagine
what you want to be.
There's no limits.
Oh, Mrs Boswell.
Sweet Jesus, it's a miracle!
Look, it's stigmata, man!
What'd you see?
What'd it look like?
The signs of the Lord, man.
They just come out of nowhere.
Man, I thought you were...
I though you were
fucking crazy, man.
So now you believe me.
Straight up, man.
Wanna make a deal?
Alright, look. I'm new here,
but I think I get
how things work.
You either join a gang
or you're dead.
Well, I sure as fuck ain't joining up with no
spics or niggers.
And I don't want to die.
So...
what do I gotta do?
I'm the new guy.
I've got to work my way up, so...
should I...
suck your dick now...
or...
Is your blood pure?
Well, I ain't no fucking kike,
if that's what you're asking me.
Well then, let's see
what you got, honey.
Watch the fucking teeth
or you'll be leaving without 'em.
Yes, Sir.
Come to daddy.
Carlos!
'We took the woods
behind the junkyard
just to make sure we wouldn't
bump into Tommy!
We hadn't seen
the smoke yet.'
Hold 'em. Hold 'em.
'We took the woods
behind the junkyard
just to make sure we wouldn't
bump into Tommy.
We hadn't seen
the smoke yet.'
Rot in hell,
you fucking animals!
Wait, before we...
we need something
that could open the sack.
I want you to take this, Lenny.
Today's your day of atonement.
I know how guilty you feel
about that woman and her baby.
Evan, stop it.
It's not the time.
Now's the only time! Today you get
a chance to redeem yourself,
to start all over with a clean slate.
- What are you talking about?
- Evan, you're acting crazy.
Please, if you've ever trusted me before,
trust me on this one.
Cut the rope.
Come on.
- Listen to me good, Evan.
- I'll do whatever you want.
You don't want me to see
Kayleigh ever again, fine.
Just let Crockett go.
Besides, if you kill him now,
they'll stick you
in juvie for sure.
And I know you'd never leave
your sister alone with your father.
Lenny, no!
Oh God.
Oh God, Lenny.
I said cut the rope.
It's all backwards.
Ah! Ah! Ah!
Evan...
What the fuck?
Lenny, no!
Want a ride?
Lenny!
Somebody call 911!
Evan! Evan!
Fuck! Evan!
Hey, doc.
What's the damage?
- How much time do I got?
- Cute, Evan.
It's a little complicated. I haven't seen
results like these before.
Not even with my father?
Well, actually, they didn't
have these tests 20 years ago.
So, what did you find?
We're finding most of
the haemorrhaging is coming from here,
the outer layer
of the cerebral cortex.
That's where
the memories are stored.
- Thank you, Evan.
- Uh-huh.
I've never seen
anything like it.
We compared these
to the ones taken last year.
We found severe haemorrhaging
and massive neural reconstruction.
What does that mean for Evan?
What he's saying, Mum,
is that I've jammed
40 years worth of memories
into my head in the last year.
It's overload city. I've completely
reprogrammed my brain.
- That about the gist of it, doc?
- Yeah.
Alright, I'm going
to go wait in the car.
The light in here is kind
of bugging my eyes, so...
It was good seeing you, doc.
It really was.
It was very... very informative.
But, you know,
I got people to see
and things to read.
Alright, see ya.
Hey.
It's me...
Evan.
Can I get you anything?
What about...
what about some of those
model airplanes you like, huh?
I bet I can get a shitload
of those model airplanes up in here.
Lenny.
You knew the whole time,
didn't you?
When you put that shard
in my hand...
you knew something big
was going to happen.
Didn't you?
Yeah...
- I knew.
- Then you should be where I am.
You should be
where I am.
'Today I get to meet my father.
His name is Jason...
and he's crazy.
I hope he let's me
call him "Dad."'
You okay?
'Cause you look like
you went somewhere else
there for a second.
Look, Jason, I need some
fast answers from you
if I'm ever gonna fix
what I've done.
I was praying this curse
would have ended with me.
Yeah, but it didn't.
So now I need information
to make things right again
and you're the only one
that can give it to me.
There is no right.
You can't change who people are
without destroying who they were.
Who says you can't
make things better?
You can't play God, son.
It must end with me.
Just by being here you may
be killing your mother.
That's bullshit, you know?
I'll send you a postcard when
I made everything perfect again.
Ahh! No, no!
Just get out, did ya?
Hmm?
Oh, nothing, just that my brother
did a stint in the pen
and he used to eat like that.
I come from a big family.
Well, I meant no offence.
None taken.
Hey, uh...
Does Kayleigh Miller
still work here?
I'm sorry.
I never heard of her.
God! Can't a man get a little
goddamned peace in his own house?!
I don't suppose
you're here to sell cookies?
Good guess, fuckbag.
Remember me, huh?
We had a nice chat once
when I was seven.
I got one question for you.
Where can I find
your daughter?
Oh, I thought
you were someone else.
Make it fast,
I'm expecting someone.
Hey. It's good to see you.
Can I come in?
If I knew you were coming,
I would have cleaned
the stains off the sheets.
What do you want?
I just needed to see
a friendly face.
Well, time is money, Evan.
Money.
I guess I can spare 10 minutes
for an old friend, right?
So, how's tricks?
Sorry, occupational humour.
I got it.
You can stop now.
Oh, sorry.
Does my line of work
make you uncomfortable, precious?
No, just that you felt like
you had to use it to hurt me.
I've been where you've been.
Ha!
Where is that?
You wouldn't believe me
if I told you.
I know people always say that,
that you wouldn't believe me,
but in this case
it's not even worth trying, so...
I knew I needed to find you,
so I went over to your dad's
and made him tell me
where you were.
Then I came here
and the rest you know.
You're right, Evan,
I don't believe you.
I never thought you would.
That's why I never bothered
to tell a soul until now
and I never will again.
I'm the only person you've told?
That's a great line.
Does that make other girls wet?
Do they actually
eat up that bullshit?
You know, I could give a shit
whether you believe me or not.
Frankly, I'm too tired
to prove it to you...
Oh, there's proof now, huh?
How else would I know you have
twin moles on your inner thigh?
Anyone with 50 bucks
could tell you that.
Okay.
Forget that.
How about the fact
that you prefer
the smell of skunk to flowers?
Or that you hate cilantro
because for some reason
unknown to you
it reminds you
of your stepsister?
Or that when you have an orgasm,
your toes go numb?
I'm sure all of your clientele
are privy to that.
You know? Look, I just
thought you should know.
Know what?
That you were happy once...
with me.
You know there's one
major hole in your story.
There's no fucking way
on this planet
or any other, I would ever be
in some fucking sorority!
You were happy there.
Oh, you're crying?
You sure you don't
want your wallet?
No, I don't need it
where I'm going.
What, are you off to change
everyone else's life again? Is that it?
Maybe next time you'll pop up
in some mansion
while I end up in Tijuana
doing some donkey act.
You know what? I'm over it.
Every time
I try to help someone
everything just goes to shit.
Well, don't give up now, slick.
Hell, you've already
done so much for me.
Why don't you go back in time
and save Mrs Halpern
and her baby?
And then maybe Lenny wouldn't
freak out and ruin my family.
No, go back
to when I was seven
and fuck me in front
of my daddy's video camera.
Straighten me out a bit.
You're on my bed.
Get out!
Buddy, I thought it would be okay
what with you being sick and all.
I'm not going to say it again.
'The last thing I remember
before the blackout
was holding my hands
over Kayleigh's ears.
I think I was more focused
on her hands on mine
than on the mailbox
across the street.'
Lady, stay back!
Don't go near the mailbox!
- Idiots!
- I mean it, woman! Get the hell back!
I'll save you, lady!
God damn it, I thought
I told you two to get out.
Oh, sorry, man.
Did we wake you?
No, it's cool.
Okay.
It's really cool.
What the fuck is this?
- Please save his arm!
- Can you open up my locker?
- Happy Birthday!
- Can I come too?
Do you want me
to hold your popcorn?
Evan? Get a towel!
Get a towel!
Evan! Oh my God!
Evan! Evan!
Evan!
Hey, where you going?
You ever notice Kayleigh's smile?
I love her smile.
Lenny's the best.
You guys make a great couple.
You ever think
that I'll find someone?
Evan!
Where are we going?
We're taking you
to the hospital, Evan.
- No, take me back.
- Sorry, your mum would kill me.
- Oh.
- You take me back, Lenny!
You owe me that much.
What are you geeks
looking at?
It must be nice to be
so goddamed perfect, huh?
Fucking losers!
Lenny, help me!
Here, get him over.
Get him over.
Hey, Brian, how's
your head feeling, buddy?
I saw that girl
you went home with.
Did she borrow
your razor this morning?
You're so bad.
Hey, there's Tommy.
Hey, Tommy! Tommy!
Hey, what's up, guys?
Hey, man,
I did what you said.
We're pooling our student funds
with the Hillel house
and we're having
an awareness dance.
Oh, awesome.
Maybe I can spin my chair around
to a techno remix
of 'Hava Nagila' till I puke.
Maybe we should be
getting to class now.
What's the point
of psych class now?
Tomorrow I could wake up
a dirt farmer in Bangladesh.
Let's go for a stroll.
Bye, babe.
- Yippee.
- Bye, sis.
What's up with him?
So Tommy's really
into this Jesus freak thing, huh?
You know how spiritual
he's gotten
ever since he saved
Mrs Halpern and Katie.
He saved Mrs Halpern?
Please. The twisted fuck.
Here, why don't we sit right here?
Want a granola bar?
Here, just...
Yeah, I gotta fix
these things or something.
Kayleigh...
do you ever think about us?
I mean, do you ever wonder
if things might have been
different between us?
Sure, Evan.
You were the first person
I really ever cared about.
- I was?
- Yeah.
That's why when I was little,
I never went to live with my mother.
I don't get it.
When... when my folks split up,
they gave me and Tommy a choice
of who we wanted to live with.
And I couldn't stand my dad.
But I knew that if I went
to move with my mum,
I'd never see you again.
I didn't know that.
So you still think about us...
together?
Well, it's crossed my mind
from time to time.
And?
Well, a lot of things
have crossed my mind, Ev.
I mean, I could play out the entire movie of
our lives in one second.
Boom, we fall in love.
We get married.
We have kids.
Our kids grow old, as do we.
Matching burial plots.
The whole thing.
Plah, it took a lot longer
to spit out than to imagine.
Things like that usually do.
So...
do you think that
it might have worked?
Yeah.
I mean, but that's
not how things wound up.
I'm with Lenny.
Lenny is your friend
and...
and that's where it ends.
Well...
would it make a difference
if I told you that
no one could possibly ever
love anyone as much as I love you?
I'm not saying that. I...
- Yeah.
- I'm not... I'm just saying it like
if you were a girl,
would that be something
that you would want to hear?
Hold on one second.
Lenny's calling.
I'll be right back, Ev, okay?
He's a little down...
I love you.
You forgot to put
the toaster on the ledge.
Lenny likes Pop Tarts.
You guys are all
that matter now.
Man, I know it's hard,
but you can't give up.
I can't even
fucking kill myself.
Don't talk like that.
Alright, I've got
to get you out of here.
Visiting hours
are almost over.
Did Mum
get transferred again?
What are you talking about?
She's been here the entire time.
Looking... good, kiddo.
Lung cancer?
You started chain smoking
when I blew myself up.
Sorry, Mrs T, he's been
acting out of sorts lately.
Mum...
you're going to be okay.
I can change it.
Um, maybe... I wanna go
down to the chapel.
You're... acting...
just like your father.
I'm going to get you
out of here. Okay?
No.
You're not going
to hurt anymore.
I'm going to fix it.
No.
No, no.
Are you sure
you even packed it?
My mum packed it.
I think she sent
everything I ever owned.
- Is this it?
- Yeah.
What do you want it for?
I don't get you lately.
Duly noted.
Okay, I have to ask you
one last favour.
- What?
- I need you to be quiet.
I have to concentrate
if I wanna destroy the blockbuster.
- What? What, the blockbuster?
- If I hadn't blown off my arms,
my mum would've never started
smoking in the first place.
Never mind. Just open it.
Turn it.
There.
'Today Mummy
is taking me to play
with Kayleigh and Tommy.
I will meet their father
and see what a real dad is like.'
Now, how do I destroy
the blockbuster?
Evan, what are you
doing with that knife?
Well, that didn't work.
Go on, turn it.
Turn it. There.
'I never wanted
to be in the movie anyway.
It was cold so I wanted
to wear my clothes.
But Mr Miller made me
take my shirt off.'
In this part of the story,
Robin Hood has just
married Maid Marian.
And they have
to kiss and stuff,
like grown-ups do.
Wait, I need my belt.
Hey, don't even
bother about a belt.
- Hey.
- Back off, fuckbag.
Amazing that word never fails
to make an impression with you.
Easy does it, Evan.
Don't be a bad boy
or I'll tell your mother
what a naughty
little shit you are.
And I'll tell
Child Protective Services
about your little
kiddie porn endeavours.
One step closer
and I'll shove this up your arse.
Hey, that's dangerous.
You could blow off your hand.
Been there, done that.
Hey!
- Sparkler.
- Kayleigh, no!
No! Kayleigh, no!
Hey, man.
...good, kiddo.
I've got no choice but to commit you
to Sunnyvale Institution...
You're gonna have to live
somewhere else for a while.
- A squashed butterfly.
- I want my mummy!
I'm so sick of this!
I think we should
up your medication.
Where are
my goddamn books?
Hey, Evan, we're not supposed
to meet for another hour.
Where are
my goddamn books?
Books?
My journals.
I... I need them.
So, if you'd give 'em to me,
it'd help a lot.
It really hurts me
to go through this again.
There are no journals.
There never were.
It's part of the fantasy world
that your mind created
to cope with the guilt
of killing Kayleigh Miller.
Think, Evan, think.
You've created a disease
that does not exist...
alternate universes with colleges
and prisons and paraplegia.
I want my journals
and I want 'em now!
And I know that you got 'em
and you're gonna give 'em to me!
You're not going to hide them
from me. I want them!
You're reminding me
of your father.
He was always screaming
for a photo album
even though
he never had one.
I'm so sorry.
A photo album?
- Photos.
- Evan?
The damage is irreparable.
Frankly, I'm surprised he still
has use of his motor functions.
Mum?
Um, did you remember to bring
those home movies
that we used to make?
Yeah, they're right here.
Good, because I really like
to watch them.
So that's good.
I think it's best we
transfer him to Bellevue
first thing in the morning.
'If anyone finds this,
it means that my plan
didn't work
and I'm already dead.'
He's not in his room.
Search the grounds.
'If I can somehow go back
to the beginning
of all of this
I might be able to save her.'
Evan!
Over here!
I believe he's in here.
Evan!
What's your name?
Kayleigh.
This is Evan.
Evan! Open up!
Evan!
Say hi, go on.
I hate you. You ever come near me again
I'll kill you and
..your whole damned family.
What happened sweetie? What's wrong?
Goodbye
Cracker!
Evan...
Kayleigh and Tommy!
I missed you!
I'll never let you guys
out of my sight again.
Happiness can only
be achieved through sacrifice,
like the sacrifices our parents have made
for us to be here today...
Whoo-hoo! Great! Tommy!
Are you alright?
Where's Kayleigh?
Who's Kayleigh?
Do you want me to take you to the doctor?
No.
No. I think everything
is going to be alright this time.
Sure about this?
I know who I am, I don't need
a bunch of stuff to remind me.
I'm running a little late.
Yeah, I had to finish up with a patient.
Get the soup or something.
Alright, love you Mom.
Bye bye.