Oh, you hopeless nut-case!
Please get your act together!
Jung-yeon... I'm sorry.
You've just made it
to the quarterfinals.
Do your best, Yong-gi.
Oh, Jung-yeon?
I know her well. We went to the
same elementary and junior high.
How many years ago was that?
Jung-yeon! Jung-yeon!
- I finally found out. I did.
- What?
- Your crush!
- Really?
I finally found out
where he goes to school.
Really?
Where? Where is it?
Whenever Jung-yeon got a chance,
she flew to Suwon to see him.
- Suwon? Not Seoul?
- It was Suwon.
I'm positive. I don't know how many
times I bought the ticket.
But wasn't his name Wonjae Lee?
Lee Won-jae... No, it wasn't that.
What was his name...
His last name was Kang or something.
I'm going crazy.
Who the hell is this guy?
Okay. Enough baking.
Let's go. Hey, hey.
- Do I really have to go?
- What?
You see, actually, there's something
I used to say to her all the time...
When I grew up, I'd become
a big success...
...and flip this country upside down!
So?
Well, forget about the country,
all I'm flipping is this here bread.
- So...
- I'm embarrassed to see her.
It's only nice to meet old friends
if you're doing well.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Is that so? Then forget about it.
Bro!
Why bring someone who doesn't wanna
see her? Keep flipping. Let's go.
Jung-yeon is doing well... right?
Welcome.
Have you been well?
You must be surprised to see us
here so suddenly...
We came here to say something to you.
No matter what,
you're our daughter-in-law.
Our only son's wife.
Actually, it was because
we didn't approve of our clown son...
...who wouldn't listen to us.
It wasn't because we didn't like you.
Forgive us for not treating you right.
The unpleasantness...
Let's forget about that now.
Sweetheart...
Yes?
Let's go somewhere together.
Hello.
A picture, all of a sudden...
Ready... Look here.
Sit down, please.
Mom...
Today, I took a family picture
with my husband's parents.
They both wore the sweaters
I knitted for them.
And now... they say they welcome
me as their daughter-in-law.
I really blamed you for not telIing me
about your illness...
... until you were about to die.
But now...
I think I know how you felt then.
Mom...
I feel so bad for my Yong-gi...
He's been so good to me.
My Yong-gi,
he can't do anything without me.
what is he going to do, mom...
I'm in trouble. I'm so nervous!
Let's start. 'How can this be?'
The President Kim missile... '
Your action is weak. When you enter...
Once again. One, two, three.
- Hey, I'll be right back.
- Where are you going?
I'll be back before the taping starts.
- Are you out of your mind?
- I just wanna see my wife, that's all.
What? See what?
- Hello?
- Ma'am, this is your husband.
- What...
- Well...
In a little bit, there will be a funny
show. Please be sure to watch.
- Okay.
- You have to watch. You have to!
I said, oKay.
Alright, ma'am. I'll see you later.
Jung Yong-gi, that dickhead!
Why isn't the idiot here?
- Well, it's not...
- Do you wanna blow the taping?
He said he'd be right back.
And if he isn't...
are you gonna take responsibility?
Don't worry. He said he'd be here.
- Shut your mouth, asshole.
- I'm sorry.
What the hell are you? Why I outta...
Get ready, dickheads.
- What happened?
- I'm sorry.
- Let's go.
- Hey, I'm sorry.
With 3 of our semi-finalists determined,
we'll an nounce our last semi-finalists.
- We only have one more slot.
- Yes.
And the winners are...
...the Yong-gi Jung and
Chulsoo Yang duo.
Congratulations.
Next week, we'll bring you
the 4 semi-finalist teams...
Hey, guys.
Do you know if Kwak Hyung-min
still teaches at this school?
- Mr. Kwak?
- Yeah.
- You know, octopus.
- Oh, you mean, octopus head?
Octopus?
Here, read this once.
They're poems Jung-yeon wrote.
She was a very sensitive girl.
Oh, we don't need to read this...
Actually, I feel weird when I'm in
a teachers' room.
- Shall we go?
- One second.
My hair...
'In my memories, there is only you.'
'Afraid if our eyes met,
the longing may fly away...'
'In my memories, there is only you.'
'Afraid if our eyes met,
the longing may fly away.'
'Afraid if we spoke, the happiness
may only be a moment.'
'I spent such a long time
hanging from a far, watching you.'
'In my memories, there is only you.'
Sir, aren't we gonna study?
- Is that so important to you?
- I need to go to college.
The person who wrote
on the bathroom wall...
...that Jung-yeon and I were dating.
- It was you, Hae-Kyung, wasn't it?
- No, she wrote that.
Hey! You wrote that
they slept together!
- You're full of crap!
- You said you saw them.
Quiet!
Grade school, junior high,
highschool...
Quite a faithful girl, alright!
Does she think she's Juliet?
- What?
- Never mind.
By the way, wasn't her crush
Lee Won-jae?
I don't know his name.
This is driving me up the wall!
- Well, let's get going.
- Please wait!
Why?
I'm sorry but I think it'd be better
if I didn't see Jung-yeon.
Now what?
Oh, that looks so good. Cheers.
Wow, with a famous hubby,
...you can take us to a fancy place
like this. How great!
That's why a person's gotta be
successful.
Now that he's famous, we can eat here.
If not, you think this stingy
would take us here?
- No way.
- You're right.
Don't be so tacky.
Slow down and eat up.
Okay.
My heart's in my throat.
I can't even swallow.
This place has great atmosphere,
right?
- Yeah. Wow.
- Really cool.
Jeez, talk about tacky!
How embarrassing.
I'm so embarrassed...
Hello.
How did it go?
- What about the people?
- Don't even mention them.
Do your homework before sending
someone off, dumbass!
We met with everyone
but they didn't want to see her.
What?
- Why not?
- No clue!
Then what about Won-jae?
He's in the U.S. on business
till next week.
Hey, forget about Won-jae.
Your wife has had a lifelong crush
on someone. Who's that?
- Lifelong?
- Yeah.
Who is he?
I don't know. If I did, I would have
dragged him here, stupid.
She never told me.
See, no communication
between the two of them.
In any case, forget about it.
Leave us alone.
We've done our best, okay?
This is it.
Over! See ya.
Hey, octopus head gave this to us.
Take it. Let's go.
What's wrong with you today?
Oh, I'm just surprised, that's all.
Getting married... With whom?
Oh, remember? I showed you
a picture last time. It's him.
That guy, he even has a kid.
You must be crazy.
His son's name is Dong-uk.
He's so cute.
Boy, you're totally into him.
I know, it's so great.
Jung-yeon, don't look at me like that.
Just like you love Yong-gi,
I love him and Dong-uk.
Welcome.
Please take it.
If I knitted better, I could have
given it to you sooner.
Wear it in the fall when it gets colder.
Oh, I'll just wear it now.
- It's too warm now.
- Who cares?
The colors are great!
- Do you like it?
- Yeah, I really like it.
- It looks good on you.
- But what's this?
Something's stuck.
- What is this?
- What is it?
Actually,
I bought this a long time ago.
Let me see your hand.
How do you like it? It fits, right?
Thanks for the sweater.
Man, I look so scruffy.
Mr. Scruffy. Damn.
Yes, yes, they're ready.
- Alright! Are we good?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- Yep.
Yong-gi, let's go.
Jung-yeon, wake up!
Jung-yeon!
What are you doing? We're up!
- She's not at home or at the store.
- Enough already. We have go!
What are you waiting for! Come on!
Yong-gi, let's go!
Jung-yeon, can you hear me?
- I was lonely so I had a fling.
- A fling?
You must be crazy!
Now you're calling me a man?
Hey, is there supposed to be a phone?
- That's not right.
- It's not in here.
What the heck? Who's calling...
Oh, darling. Let me just answer it.
Hello?
What?
Okay... I'll be right there.
Who is it? It's her, isn't it?
What are you looking at?
Why are you... looking at me...
Chul-soo...
I'm sorry! Good heavens...
- You're ditching me?
- Hey, hey... What's he doing?
Oh my goodness!
Jung-yeon, are you going
to be alright?
- Are you sure?
- We'll be right back.
What are you doing here?
Jung-yeon...
You... have to stay here
a little longer.
What are you saying?
It's nothing. Don't worry.
Jung-yeon, please...
What's wrong?
It's nothing, really. Go.
Stop it now!
- I'm fine. What's the matter?
- I know everything!
Everything!
Why can't you ask me, huh?
To hold you, to help you,
to comfort you...
Why can't you tell me the truth?
What... have you heard?
There's nothing wrong with me.
You've heard wrong.
It's not me so don't worry about me.
It's not me. I'm fine!
Please stop!
Don't do this. It's not me.
I told you...
Don't! Just go and do your work.
I'm fine. Please, don't.
Don't do this. It's harder for me.
You shouldn't. Stop!
I told you I'm okay.
It's not me, it's not me...
It's not me...
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- We'll see you later.
- Thank you. Bye.
You think this makes
you a good hubby?
- Did I say anything?
- You're really bad.
I know.
Get some sleep.
Yong-gi! Sleep here.
Are you asleep?
I'm sorry... Yong-gi.
Did you sleep well?
What are you doing standing there?
Go wash up.
Yong-gi.
I need a favor. Will you do it?
No matter how busy you are,
make sure you eat.
I know it's bothersome but
make sure you wear clean clothes.
Sleep at home.
Don't sleep just anywhere.
And...
I want you to keep making people
laugh no matter what happens.
It's what you're best at.
Is that all?
Is that all... you want?
The stew's getting cold. Eat up.
Don't worry.
Woo-jin...
Mom... is going there to see you.
Sorry, but we're...
Jung-yeon. Park Jung-yeon!
Ae-suk...
What brings you here?
Hey, Yong-gi.
Did you transfer to Seoul
in the 3rd grade?
Yes.
Right.
The person your wife has been
yearning for her whole life...
... is right here!
You made us suffer for nothing!
Don't bother us again, okay?
Oh, I see. So that's how it ended up.
- What about you?
- I already have 2 brats.
- The boys are 3 and 5.
- Wow!
I really missed you. Did you know that?
Same here, girlfriend.
I kept seeing you in my dreams.
So I felt like I had to see you.
- I'm glad we got together like this.
- So am I. I'm so happy!
Jung-yeon, I have to go.
- Why?
- Oh, you know, things.
- Still, stay a little longer.
- I'll visit again soon.
Stay a little more.
We have lots to talk about.
I'll come again.
Jung-yeon. Take good care of yourself.
Oh, I'm so curious.
Jung-yeon, who is he?
- It's a secret. Who's yours?
- It's also a secret.
- See, you won't tell me, either!
- It's because I'm embarrassed.
Then let's do this.
Circle his face in this picture and
we won't look until we get home.
Okay.
- No lying!
- And no telling!
Yong-gi. It's time. Let's get ready.
We're about to start. Please enter!
Yes, it's been a long wait.
Let's begin the finals
of King of Comedy.
- Hyo-jin.
- Yes.
For the final round,
we've moved to a bigger stage.
Yes, it's quite impressive.
Who are the first heroes
to grace the stage?
They've turned the comedy world
upside down.
Please welcome the Jung Yong-gi
and Yang Chul-soo duo!
Give them a big hand!
Look at them.
They even know how to mime.
Yong-gi...
I wish for you to bring warm laughter
even to those who are suffering.
In order to do that, they say
you need to know tears first.
It may be heartless of me
to leave you behind.
But I wish that even this pain
can become a present for you.
Just like you were the biggest
present the world had given me.
By the way, Yong-gi, do you know?
When it was I first started
to like you?
What treasure do you want the most?
I hid them over there
so go look for them.
This is what you're looking for, okay?
Alright, go!
I got one!
Here.
Yong-gi! They're having
a talent contest! Hurry!
Okay. Got it!
Hey, wait for me!
'Treasure: a box of crayons'
My heart grows tender...
Our fate twirls round-n-round.
With the fading time,
I'm afraid our love will grow apart.
What am I to do?
Our fate twirls round-n-round.
With the fading time...
Teacher.
May I have that picture, please?