There was a legend
that Kwok Ching and his wife Wong Yung
got the sword of Yeung Guo
They mixed it with fine gold
and made two swords
One is called To Lung
and the other named Yee-Tin
And they wrote what they learnt
together with Ngo Fai's many tactics
and the secret of the most powerful
Kung Fu Scroll the Lunar Secret
was hidden inside the swords
Whoever got it, whoever
could rule the world of martial arts
The supreme
of the world of martial arts...
Thus, no matter evil or virtuous
in order to get these two weapons
numerous fights were caused...
Two groups were thus formed
One, was headed by Shaolin
Shaolin
Wu-tong
Ngo-mai
Kun-lun
Hung-tung
Wah-shan
And their opponent was the Fire Sect
which came from Persia
They called themselves the Ming Sect
But, they were named
the Evil Sect by others
They're so mysterious
and always went against Yuen Dynasty
Ming Sect always caused riots against it
Their headquarters were located
at the Bright Summit
Branch leaders, Purple, White, Gold
and Green were all powerful
They were: Queen of Purple Dragon
King of White Eagle
King of Gold Lion
and King of Green Bat
Groups were strongly against each others
Their fellows couldn't make friends
with each other
Otherwise, they would be killed
Chang Tsui-san
the 5th student of Chang San Fung
was righteous and heroic
disregarded the unreasonable rules
fell in love with Yan So So
daughter of King of White Eagle
and he be-friended with
King of Gold Lion, Tse Shun
King of Gold Lion's master Shing Kwun
in order to help Yuen's Government
to destroy Ming Dynasty
he killed Tse Shun's whole farmily
Tse Shun risked his life
to seize the To Lung's Sword
to take revenge for his family
he killed many innocent lives
Tsui Shan and So So didn't want others
to know Tse's whereabout
they went to a nobody-land
Ice and Fire Island
to live in seclusion
Although he got the sword, Tse Shun
couldn't get the secret of it
until the 100th birthday
of Chang San Fung
Tsui Shan brought his wife
and his son Mo-kei to visit his master
Crab in sugar candy
I want it
Please give me one Alright
Mo-kei, enjoy it
Thank you, mom
Good boy
I asked you not to get off the cart
This is the foot of Wu Tong Mountain
I think it doesn't matter
It's hard to say
For To Lung Sword
they can do whatever in mind
Dad, why do they want
God-father's To Lung's Sword?
I have told you many times
Don't mention your God-father's name
don't you forget?
I won't do it next time
Remember, no matter who asks
about your God-father
No matter how they push you
don't tell a word, remember?
Yes, dad said
we can't betray our friend
Or, it'll be non-righteous
Good boy
I think Master will like you
Is your Master kind?
He is the kindest one among the kindest
Chang Tsui San...
It hurts
It's The Cry from Jinx
it'll affect one's mind
Resist it with your inner power
Or, you'll be hypnotized and lose your mind
Who are you? Show up now
Jinx's Palm?
Mo-kei
Mother
I think you're the notorious Jinxs
Chang, if you want your son back
tell us where the King of Gold Lion is
Stop dreaming
If we hit your son with our Jinx's Palm
What do you think?
How dare you?
The kid is innocent
Why do you ill-treat this kid?
If you let him go
Wu-tong and the Ming Sect
will appreciate so much
Are you threatening me
with Wu-tong and Ming Sect?
Even that old jerk Chang San Fung's here
I won't give it a chance
Won't you?
Master Master
I, Chang San Fung
beg you to let the boy go
I see, the famous Chang San Fung
isjust a fatty
I'm all eyed
Right, my name is being exaggerated
It's not a big deal
Fatty
if you're afraid of my Jinx's Palm
ask your student
to tell us where Tse Shun is
Right
Tsui Shan, told them then
Master, Tse Shun is my buddy
Right, how can I be non-righteous?
That's right
In this martial-world
how can you be non-righteous?
How can you face others then?
Please give us some faces then
Old bluffer
step aside if you're afraid of death
Or you'll die on your 100th birthday
It's useless to sigh
You assholes
I think today is my birthday
I shouldn't quarrel or get angry
But you two forced me to break my rule
I want to teach you a good lesson
Brother
How dare you beat my boy?!
If you hit him once
I'll hit him 100 times
Hubby, your master is so hot tempered
He's always hot tempered
OK, let's release the hostages together
OK, I don't think
you'd pull off a shunt
One, two, three
Mo-kei
Watch out Go!
Jinx's Palm?
Mo-kei
Take Mo-kei to Shaolin, no...
Take him to Wu-tong
I'll get the antidote from the bastards
No way, if we go on like this
Mo-kei will be killed
Cut
Mo-kei
Brother, how is he?
Jinx's Palm is so powerful
I think, we have to wait
for Master's antidote
Mo-kei he...
Mom, I feel so painful
Don't panic, Mo-kei
Here are some candies
If you feel painful, eat one
It's sweet
So you'll forget the pain, got me?
Uncles
Shaolin, Ngo-mai, Hung-tung, Wah Shan
and Kun-lun's representatives' approaching
they claim
to celebrate Master's birthday
In fact, they want Uncle Chang to tell
where the King of Gold Lion
Today is the birthday of my master
He asked us
not to make any grand celebration
So, he may enjoy a peaceful birthday
Thus, we appreciate your visit
and we'll express our thanks later
Please go back
We dare not disturb Master Chang
But he has to hand out
Chang Tsui San and Yan So So
and tell us the whereabouts
of the King of Gold Lion
Then we will leave at once
Master No-mercy
what do you think it is?
How dare you get anyone you wish?
To take revenge for the victims killed
by Evil Sect
We want to get Tse Shun by any means
If you do not hand us the wanted
I'll fight with you then
I've heard that you're great in kung-fu
I, Sung Yuen Kiu
would like to offend you now
Chang Tsui San, if you won't come out
your seniors will be killed
Stop
Master No-mercy, don't go too far
You're willing
to show up with your bitch!
Where is King of Gold-Lion?
I won't tell you my buddy's whereabouts
You deserve it!
You, be friend with that murderer
I'll wake you up
Bitch...
You?!
Damn nun...
You
Watch my powerful Yee-tin Sword!
It's no big deal
If not were your master Kwok Shang
my best friend
I wouldn't have given you face
Yee-tin Sword is with you
that'll only bring bad luck to the world
I'll keep this sword
for your master for 7 years
7 years later
ask a better student to collect it
Chang San Fung
how dare you protect your sinful student?
If we attack you together
I don't think you can kill all of us
When you're exhausted
you'll be in deep shit too
How dare you? Are you threatening me?
Master, I'll be wholly responsible
for this case
They come for me only
Let me settle it myself
OK. You may settle it yourself
but about fighting
I've never given a damn
Are you threatening me?
Seniors
you want me
to tell brother's whereabouts
In fact, you want his To Lung Sword
and to be the supreme only
I'll never betray my friend
But I don't hope my master
at his old age to risk his life with you
Well, I'll give you an answer now
Tsui San!
Dad!
Why do you kill yourself?
Mom, why did dad do so?
Mo-kei, recognize each face
remember them one by one
You've to remember all their faces
for each of them is stained
with your dad's blood
Did they push dad to death?
You have to take revenge for your dad
Don't let them escape
Miss Yan, we feel sorry
for the death of your husband
Now, you're the only one
who knows where Tsu Shun is
Master Hung Man, come here
I'll tell you
But will you let my son and I go?
Monks don't take his words back
OK. I'll tell you only
Miss, can you make it clear?
Master
King of Gold Lion is living there
Wish you to get the Sword soon
Madam... Where is he?
She didn't tell me
No? You do want to get the sword alone
Mom!
Mo-kei, mom cheated them
See, how powerful
is mom's cheating skill?!
Remember, don't ever trust any woman!
More beautiful the woman is
more capable is her to tell lies
Remember
Mom
We've to take revenge for brother
No, save Mo-kei first
Mo-kei...
Master
You have terrific inner power
So what?
These years, I've never got a way
to cure you from feeling cold
If the Shaolin monk
hadn'tjumped from here
he'd have cured you
with his Great Solar Stance
Great Solar Stance?
Great Solar Stance
is the mysterious kung-fu of Shaolin
It's as powerful
as the Great Lunar Stance
But the Scroll has been lost for years
Accidentally, a cooking monk in Shaolin
discovered it inside sutra
After he learnt the kung-fu
he defeated over monks and escaped
then he came to challenge me
Chang, you're really great
Great Solar Stance can make you famous
in this world of martial arts
But I think, you're not virgin
before practicing such kung-fu
Otherwise, I couldn't have defeated you
I can't imagine this kind of kung-fu
isn't invincible
Why should I try so hard
to practise it then?
Chang San Fung, see you
Nuts
If he wasn't dead
his kung-fu would have saved you
My dear boy, no matter how
you've to be virgin to practise kung-fu
So, your kung-fu would be more powerful
Don't think I'm a 100—year old granny
My dicky erects every morning
What's that?
Why isn't mine do the same?
You're weak
Master
What's the matter, Ching-su?
7 years passed
Ngo-mai's Master No-mercy
sent her student Chow Chi-yu here
to get back their Yee Tin Sword
Chow Chi-yu?!
How do you do, Master Chang?
Is No-mercy's temper better?
She's studied Buddhism in recent years
she's great improvement
You're a polite girl. It's lucky for her
to get such a good student
Mo-kei, return the Yee Tin Sword to her
Brother Mo-kei, are you the son
of Mr. Chang Tsui Shan?
Yes, Brother Mo-kei
is the orphan left by my uncle
I'm Sung Ching-su
My dad is the eldest brother
of Wu-tong's Seven Heroes
Thank you, Brother Mo-kei
Chi-yu, why not stay here for few days?
Let my student Yuen Kiu
teach you our sword stance
as present
Thank you Master Chang
Brother Mo-kei
Are you watching them?
Master Chang loves you so much
I think you'll be his successor for sure
Don't worry
Mo-kei can't practise kung-fu
We'll take care of him
Sister Chi-yu, why not practise together?
He was hurt by Jinx's Palm 8 years ago
he can't practise Kung-fu in his life
Dad
Ching-su, Master wants to practise
Tai-chi Sword for 3 months
We have to stay with him
in the secret cell
In these 3 months, you've to take care
of everything in Wu-tong
Thank you, Dad
Ching-su, you have to work hard
In the 3rd generation of Wu-tong
Mo-kei can't practise kung-fu
You're the only one
that we have to depend on
Master Chang specially made
100 Heart Strengthening Pills
Give one to Mo-kei per night
so it can stop him from feeling cold
Ching-su will take good care
of Brother Mo-kei
What are you doing?
Go... Go
Brother Mo-kei, what's happened?
Someone peeped at you
Really?
They're so bad. I'm so scared
They've all gone
But I'm scared too
Why not come and accompany me?
I know you wouldn't accompany me
Let me accompany you
I know you care me most
Are you hot? No
You're sweating
How dare you!
Chang Mo-kei
you think you're a lady killer?
Brother Ching-su
will there be any accident?
Don't worry, I'm in charge now
You jinx
you dragged your parents to death
You only know
how to flatter Master Chang
So he passes you his inner energy
to keep you from coldness
If he'd passed me his inner energy
I'd have been top graded kung-fu master
Your mom isjinx
You can insult me, but not my mom
I wonder are you the blood of my uncle
Maybe you're a son of a bitch
Go to hell
Brother Ching-su
Catch him, I wanna chop his hand off
I see, Wu-tong is not heroic at all
My friend, who are you?
Friend? I'm not a friend of yours
Dress
Bitch
Come down if you have guts
Wu-tong's kung-fu is nothing special
The kung-fu of Ming Sect
is much more powerful
Sister Chi-yu
attack her with your Yee-tin Sword
You bitch
Yee Tin Sword is really in Wu-tong
Aren't you leaving?
Watch out
don't let the dogs of Wu-tong kill you
I don't allow you insult Wu-tong
You must be insane
I'll chat with you after the fight
Bitch, I'll let you see
how powerful my sword is
Thank you, I come for this Sword in fact
I want to break
this non-breakable Cold-chain
Wu-tong's Sword Stance
Escape
Here... run
Your kung-fu is so bad
Forget about me, go now
No, they'd kill you if they catch you up
Kidding, you bring me to this dead end?
Chang, you allied with the Evil Sect
and mess our temple
Now, with the name
of Acting Manager of Wu-tong
I exile you
Wu-tong students have my order Yes
Kill with no mercy Yes
Miss, I've cragged you down
Call me Siu Chiu
How dare you seduce man
in such critical moment?
Where can you go?
It's soft?!
Why do you loosen your hands
without any notice?
For I touched yours...
Dumb-bell, you must be educated
by your dad
My dad died years ago
You're called Chang Mo-kei
Is your dad Chang Tsui-san?
My Chang, I'm your maid Siu Chiu
Get up first
Siu Chiu
is the maid of King of White Eagle
I offended King of White Eagle
so he locked me up
I went into fugitive
I've heard Yee Tin Sword is in Wu-tong
I wanted to make use of it
Luckily I met you and you saved my life
Get up first
I'm not your Mister
You touched me again
You're the grandson
of King of White Eagle
so I have to greet you Mister
In fact, I haven't seen my grandfather
since birth
What kind of noise is it? Monster?
Go...
This way
That way...
I can't imagine
there would be visitors for me
You are...
I'm the soul of hell
Are you the student of Wu-tong?
I'm Chang Mo-kei
Chang San Fung made me suffer here
It's not too much to eat
one of his student, right?
Are you the cooking monk?
You remember me?
The girl after you is so attractive
She must be more delicious than you
She isn't Wu-tong's student
Come and eat me
You're heroic too!
Mister...
Mister Chang, how are you?
It's cold
What have you done to him?
Kidding!
He's already been serious injured
Hey, who hurt you?
I was hit by the Jinx's Palm 8 years ago
Nothing can cure it
It must be Master Chang passes you
inner energy in these years
He loves you so much
Senior, I know you can cure him
I beg you to cure him
My Great Solar Stance
is the only solution
But why should I cure Chang's people?
Chang Mo-kei, unless you scold
your Master Chang as asshole
Then I'll teach you Great Solar Stance
to cure you from coldness
Impossible
You don't save him. That's OK
Why did you hit him?
Just scold Chang as Shame-less asshole
for three times
Then you'll be free
from this kind of suffer forever
and you'll have invincible power
This is a piece of cake
Follow me
Chang is a shameless asshole...
Shameless asshole...
is you
OK, I'll see
how can you get through this night
Mister...
It's cold Cold?!
Mister how are you?
It's cold Still very cold?
So cold...
Will it be warmer?
I can't imagine Chang
has such a brave student like him
I'm still living...
Mister are you alright?
Siu Chiu
Mister
are you having any weapon with you?
No
Why do I feel
something solid pointing at me?
Really?
Erected?
What is it?
Nothing
Shit, will that make her pregnant?
So soon?
What did you say?
Nothing, I said I wake up soon
Mister, you could stand last night
I think you'll be alright
Stop dreaming!
You're lucky last night
You'll feel ice-cold 2 to 3 times a day
If no one uses inner energy
to keep your life
You'll die
You hard-hearted
Chang Mo-kei
if you don't learn my Great Solar Stance
You'll suffer coldness
for the rest of your life
Leave Wu-tong, and be my student
Master Chang is so nice to me
I can't do that
You're sick
Why do you push him
to learn your kung-fu?
10 years ago
I was defeated by Chang San Fung
I'm so furious
I want my student to be more superior
than any of his student
Why not teach me?
If a woman practices Great Solar Stance
one year later, she'll have flat chest
with hairy hands and legs
with beard and man's voice
Do you want it?
Forget it
Mister, his backbone is broken
he moves with that ball
Why not promise him now
after learning his kung-fu
then we can take our words back
Wu-tong's student
is always righteous and virtuous!
I'm a Wu Tong's student
but he forces me to study his kung-fu
there must be trick
I won't learn it anyhow
I don't think you can force me
to get your kung-fu
Can't I?
Siu Chiu
Let me help you
I don't allow you to do so
Great Sun appears
the blood flows backward
Don't press my head with the ass
Air from belly goes through
the whole body
It's breaking
Blood sea
Top of the back
Solar Pool
Door of life
Ken-su k. ..
Chang, you have the 1st grade
of the Great Solar Stance
You have my kung-fu now
You can never get rid of it
I'll push you to learn the 2nd grade
Unless you die
or you're betraying Wu-tong
I'm useless
to let that evil bitch
hit Mo-kei down the cliff
I was late
I could only killed the bitch
but couldn't save Mo-kei
Please kill me
as compensation to Uncle Chang
I'll kill you now
Yuen Kiu, you can't save Mo-kei anyway
It's useless to kill him
Brother Ching-su tried his best
Mo-kei is such a poor boy
Death may be a release to him
Shaolin invited us
to launch a raid to Bright Summit
We'd maintain peace and righteousness
of the world of martial arts
Yuen Kiu, lead yourjuniors, Ching-su
and Chi-yu to go with you
Yes, Master
The 9th grade Great Solar in the Sky
Chang, you've got all stances
from Great Solar Stance
From now on, you're full of mysterious
and powerful energy
Your wound is cured too
From now on, it's hard for you to die
Master, you made it!
Thank you Master
Aren't you unwilling
to learn my kung-fu?
It should be a suffering instead
I know you didn't mean to teach me
You just want
to lose the face of my Master
So, I just tricked you
to teach me your kung-fu
I have to take revenge for my parents
I wished to learn it most
You're cunning
Not only pretty women
aren't trustworthy
You can't even trust
those seem to be kind-hearted!
I wanna kill you
I have the same kung-fu as you
How can you kill me?
Watch out, he's so powerful
Senior, please forgive me
You cured me by your kung-fu
Thank you for your lesson
You cunning guy
If I can make my revenge
I'll come back to save you
You'll die terribly
Let's wait and see
Let's see who'll die first
Let's go
See how long will you two get together!
You'll not have happy ending!
I've made it
Shaolin, Ngo-mai, Hung-tung
Kwun-lun and Wah-shan
All of you're stained
with the blood of my parents
I want you to repay it
Your look is horrible
If you were me
You kept every hatred
inside your heart for 8 years
to be bullied and insulted all the time
When you have a chance to release
you'll act like me
Are you going back to Wu-tong?
Sung Ching-su
is the only son of my uncle
I can't take revenge to him
No way
I won't go back to Wu-tong
With the help of my Great Solar Stance
I can go everywhere
I'll go to Bright Summit
to see my grandfather
And I'll beg him to unlock you
Thank you
We risked our lives together
don't call me Mister anymore
I love to serve you
Will you let me serve you forever?
You're so nice to me
I'll always remember it
Now you're so powerful
I think you'll attract many girls
I think, you'll soon forget me
No, once there is sun
I won't let you leave me
Mister
Crab in sugar candies...
See, there're candies for sale
These were the last thing
that my mom bought me
After I was hit by Jinx's Palm
she gave me 3 candies
She asked me to eat when I felt painful
When they were dead
you ate the first one, right?
I dried these two
So, I've to keep it properly
Take us some wine and food
Yes...
Schools of martial arts are
launching a raid to the Bright Summit
I'm sure they'll destroy the Evil Sect
If we're late
we'll then miss the great moment
So what if you can catch them?
It means more people
will be sent to hell only
There are branch leaders
and the invincible Elements Flat
Don't you think a small potato
like you can destroy them?
How ignorant are you!
She must be somebody in the Evil Sect
Arrest her
Let's hide up first
You're putting a quart into a pint pot!
Is she somebody in the Ming Sect?
I've never seen her
Let's deal
about the raid to Bright Summit
I'll try my best
Do you know them?
Of course, they hit me
with Jinx's Palm 8 years ago
Don't panic
Many powerful kung-fu masters are here
we can't compete with them
Mr. Deer
How do you do?
Master, we all depend on you
Please send my regards to his Majesty
See you
Who is hiding here?
Come out!
What are you doing here?
Kid, what are you looking at?
He seems to be familiar to us
Forget it
a couple is enjoying chatting here
Let's go
I just wanted...
Luckily you didn't move. See
This guy must be somebody
Even Deer Man and Crane Man
seem to be his fellows
Guy? This is a woman
Woman? She's like my mom
She's pretty
so you said she's like your mom
You're like my mom now
Still kidding?!
The Bright Summit is surrounded
by the schools
Let's hurry there OK
The Evil Sect is well prepared
The Elements Flags are all in position
Even Wai Yat-Siu
King of Green Bat has come back to help
Even though he's against
King of White Eagle
If Queen of Purple Dragon
and King of Gold Lion are back
It'll be difficult for us to fix them
If King of Gold Lion is back
that's perfect
We can seize his To Lung Sword
Do you want my Yee Tin Sword too?
That's what I want
I dare not
She can read my mind
Luckily she didn't know
I wanted to rape her too
You rape her
I'll take her students instead
What a hand job for you, pal
My pleasure
What are you two talking about?
Well, we decided to donate
the treasure of the Evil Sect to the poor
Queen of Purple Dragon is the Holy Lady
of Persia's Ming Sect
She's disappeared for many years
It's believed that she's gone to Persia
After a severe fight
King of Gold Lion were blind
It's not difficult to handle him
But King of White Eagle and
King of Green Bat are difficult to handle
Uncle, I have an idea
Go ahead
King of White Eagle has a grandson
He's the son of Chang Tsui-san
He's called Chang Mo-kei
He died few months ago
King of White Eagle doesn't know it
And old man
if he meets his grandson again
he'll be very happy
If his grandson attacks suddenly
sure he'll have a great chance
to kill him
Great idea
So we can kill King of White Eagle
and King of Green Bat easily
And rob all the money of them
Sell all the woman to be hookers
We're from decent schools of martial arts
how can we do so?
You're using my passed nephew
I don't agree to do so
Isn't it good?
Wejust want to help the poor only
I agree with Master Yuen Chun
You asked someone to act as Chang Mo-kei
Who is the most suitable person then?
The son of Mr. Sung is the best choice
I won't allow our Wu-tong student
to do such thing
You cunning bastards
are discussing evil traps
Watch out for being hit by thunder
Bat's down
It's King of Green Bat, Wai Yat-siu
Wai, let my wife go
Your wife is so fat, it's no big deal
for me to suck her blood
Damn it
No-mercy, you killed my wife
If anyone is bitten by Wai Yat-siu
one will lose one's mind
and obey Wai only
If I don't kill your wife
we'll have one more enemy
You can't compete with her
Wai doesn't know how powerful
Yee Tin Sword is
he used Mrs. Ho to be his shield
I believe that he's hurt
by the energy of my sword
Your Highness
Have the schools arrived the hillside?
Your Highness, they have arrived
Set the elements position
When they come half way
I want half of them to die
Yes
I'm back
Your Highness
Bat, I'm glad you come to help
That means, you really love our sect
Old man, I've got some information
and I fought with No-mercy too
Her Yee Tin Sword is really powerful
Are you alright?
Of course, I'll be alright
Set the position now
Someone who claims himself
the grandson of King of White Eagle
named Chang Mo-kei, just kill him
without a warning
Yes
What did you say? My grandson?
They'll send someone to act as
your grandson to assassinate you
If our Holy Fire Table is still here
I won't scare her Yee Tin Sword
Bullshit
If our Master Yeung didn't disappear
With his Magic Stance
he'd have killed them easily
It hurts
Are you hurt?
Of course
But I can't lose my face
in front of them
Never mind
I'll help you to cure your wound
It's useless, you've to suck the poison
out the wound
No problem
Really?
Yes, I didn't take my words back
What a good buddy
See, the wound is on my ass
It's alright if you don't suck
but you shouldn't kick me
So many people
They don't seem to be the man
from Ming Sect
Why are there so many flags?
This is the code of our Sect
They've rushed into the forbidden zone
of the Elements Flag
Elements Flag?
Don't retreat
We're from decent schools
we can't be cowards
If you want to be coward
you'll be killed
You're right
You go first
Chi-yu, give me the Yee Tin Sword
Yes, master
Go
Retreat
Let's chase