Having been misunderstood by her lover,
Cho Yi Hang,
Lien Ni Chang went on a killing rampage
and slaughtered everyone in Wu Tang.
She broke up with Cho Yi Hang.
Her hair turned white overnight
and she vanished from the land.
Cho Yi Hang heard about
a majestic flower in Mount Shin Fung.
lf he could pick the flower when it
blossoms and give it to Ni Chang,
her hair will return to its original
color and her evil ways will cease.
Cho Yi Hang guarded the flower
on Mount Shin Fung
and vowed to remain until it blossomed,
in hopes of reuniting with his beloved.
Ni Chang, as soon as
the majestic flower blossoms,
l will come for you.
THE BRlDE WlTH WHlTE HAlR ll
BRlGlTTE LlN
SUNNY CHAN
CHRlSTY CHUNG
JOEY MEMG
LlLY CHUNG
RUTH WlNONA TAO
HEUNG KAM LEE
KWOK LEUNG CHEUNG
RlCHARD SUN
and LESLlE CHEUNG
as CHO Yl HANG
So many are dead already,
don't push me any further!
Save your breath! Let's kill the witch
to avenge our ancestors' death!
lf you insist,
l will kill every single descendant
of Chung Yuan's Eight Clans.
Students of Wah Shang Clan,
burn your incense.
Students of Ching Shing Clan,
Student of Wu Tang,
burn your incense.
lf we don't kill
this white hair witch,
tombstones of the Eight Clans
will soon pile up to the roof!
So, we must unite the descendants
of the Eight Clans
to destroy the evil witch!
My elders, l would like to know what
really happened on that fateful day.
How dare you ask!
He should know what happened.
That day, rivers of blood and bodies
of the Eight Clans were everywhere.
When l woke up,
l saw Cho Yi Hang let that murderer,
the white hair witch go!
Then why didn't we bring Uncle Cho back
and ask him what happened?
- Don't you mention that coward!
- Don't mention the coward's name again!
l feel that at a time like this,
when there are so many
more important things to tend to,
why must we dwell
on past hatred?
Fung Chun Kit!
We must avenge our ancestors' deaths.
lf we don't kill the witch, the next
tombstone may have your name on it!
Knock on wood,
knock on wood.
Master Lui,
aren't you overstating just a bit?
Kit's wedding is coming up soon.
Please don't say such unlucky words.
l just worry that Wu Tang
may have no descendants left!
That's simple enough.
Marry him off.
When he has babies,
Wu Tang will have descendants.
Apologize.
Yes.
l'm sorry l misspoke.
My elders, please forgive me.
Thank you,
masters.
l'm delighted to
see you get married.
l'm sure your ancestors
would have been happy for you.
lt would have been even better
if Uncle Cho were here.
During the old days,
we would have thrown you a big wedding.
But now..
We just have to make do.
lt is unfortunate.
l appreciate the love
and concern all the masters
and my brothers have shown me.
l am very content.
Kit,
we brothers have something for you.
A jade lyre!
That's right!
Your wife's name is Lyre.
Bridegroom,
you want to take the bride so soon?
No way.
Hey girls, it's his big day,
give him a break!
Good luck!
Lucky money, lucky money!
Catch!
Hey, this little brother's
kung fu isn't bad.
Don't mention it.
But we're here to tease the bridegroom,
not the best man!
Doesn't matter.
As long as were all having fun.
- Just enjoy yourselves.
- Yes, you're right!
Cover your eyes!
Lyre is your beloved. Be good to her.
The party's in full swing.
You think the white hair witch
will come to give her blessings too?
What a bad omen.
String snaps, owner dies!
Go wash your mouth with soap!
Meng,
you watch the main hall.
Yes.
Tak, you watch over the other side.
Better safe than sorry.
Don't worry, Kit.
We'll take care of you.
Right.
Yes, don't worry.
This is your wedding night.
l bet Lyre's hair is turning white
upstairs waiting for you.
Shut your big mouth.
Do you have to mention white hair?
So,
you said it too!
Kit.
Sister-in-law.
Don't worry.
l'll be right there.
l'll be right there too!
Don't talk to your sister-in-law
that way!
Tonight is your wedding night.
l'm sure the white hair witch
won't spoil this special night.
Yes, but we better be extra careful.
You know..
Yes, we know..go!
Wait!
lf you have any questions about
what to do on your wedding night,
just ask me.
l am an expert
when it comes to making babies.
Finally some peace and quiet.
How did you know
there's a secret passage here?
This is for taking out the garbage,
didn't you know?
That's right.
Are you happy?
Yes. Are you?
Yes.
lt's too bad
What?
lt's too bad that my master, uncles
and brothers have all passed away.
l wish they were at my wedding!
l heard you still have an uncle.
His name is Cho Yi Hang.
But no one knows
where he is now.
l don't even dare mention his name
in front of the elders.
Why?
Just mentioning his name
gets them angry.
They said he shamed Wu Tang
and the Eight Big Clans too!
Are we going to chat till dawn?
l just want to know the truth
about this whole thing.
Have you ever met
your Uncle Cho?
No, but l've heard that
because of the white hair witch,
he's gone mad.
No one recognizes him anymore.
He sounded like a real romantic.
But was it worth it
for a cold-blooded murderer?
l don't know.
l only know that if
l can't be with you
l would be like my Uncle Cho.
l'll go crazy for love.
What if l become as horrible as
the white hair witch?
Don't be silly.
You're from an orthodox clan.
She was from an evil clan.
How could she even
compare with you?
Uncle Cho was bewitched by her
evil spell. That won't happen to me.
What if l really turned into someone
like her? Will you still love me?
Then l will have to sacrifice our love
and personally slay this ghastly witch!
Don't come out!
Lieu!
Meng!
Tak!
You're the last descendant of Wu Tang,
aren't you?
l won't let you die so soon.
Kit!
Lyre!
Why do you have to
destroy our clan?
Kit, are you all right? Kit!
Kit, don't scare me!
Does your heart hurt?
Go ahead, kill me.
l am not afraid of you.
You are willing to sacrifice
your own life for this man?
Yes!
Why are you so foolish?
Why do you suffer for such a bastard?
Because l love him,
forever love him.
All right.
Then l'll beat you to your senses so you
won't trust those heartless bastards!
Lyre!
You are tough.
We'll see how much of this you can take!
l'll just go over
to kill him now,
so the two of you will never
be together, even in death!
Lyre!
l want you to watch him die
with your own eyes!
Kit!
You white hair witch!
l'm going to kill you!
Damn!
Fung Chun Kit.
Hey, wasn't today your wedding day?
How did you get beaten up so badly?
l want you to know that
there is not one single good man alive!
l want you to personally kill
Fung Chun Kit.
l'm not afraid of you!
Yan,
give her the sword.
Sister, don't be like that.
Leave her to me.
Your hand is injured.
l won't hurt you.
Take a look at me
and you'd know l don't know kung fu.
Come on.
My name is Chen Yuen Yuen.
What is your name?
Lyre.
Lyre. What a beautiful name.
Befitting to such a beautiful girl.
Welcome to our big family.
Don't go.
l beg you. Please don't go.
Good and evil can never stand together.
There's no future for the both of us.
- Don't follow me. Go!
- Don't leave us,
don't leave your
daughter and me!
You be good and
practice your kung fu.
When you grow up, you can help me
kill all the bastards from Chung Yuan.
Then l'll love you.
Little brother,
not only do you want to love her,
you want to make love to her!
Too bad!
You'll have to wait at least 10 years.
Sister,
are you thinking sad thoughts again?
l know what you're
thinking about.
You're thinking about
those heartless bastards.
Yuen Yuen, you are luckier than me.
Only Wu San Kuei let you down.
But me, l was betrayed by my father,
Kei Wu Shang,
and worst of all,
that heartless Cho Yi Hang.
From now on, if we two stick together,
no one will ever hurt us again.
Men.
l see one, l kill one.
You should consider
yourself lucky.
Even though your wedding night
was ruined, at least you're still alive.
Lyre,
where are you?
l'm not your Lyre. l am Ling Moon Yee
from the Kwan Lun Clan.
You always call me a tomboy,
remember?
Wu San Kuei, you've betrayed yourself
and your country.
How can you say you
did it all for me!
Yuen Yuen,
don't leave me.
lf you would just change your mind,
l'll do anything you want.
You have done plenty
for me already.
You let in the Ching troops. You've
made me a traitor, a sinner in history.
How am l able to
face the world now?
l don't like this tune.
Play another one.
This one is no good either.
Laugh!
What are you trying to pull?
Play it yourself!
l was a geisha half my life.
l had to please you men every night
and l never complained.
You've only played one tune
and you're griping already.
Men can be killed
but not insulted!
Scholars like us
cannot be toyed with!
By that, do you mean women
can be toyed with and insulted then?
No. No.
Keep playing!
Lyre!
Lyre.
How are you doing?
l will avenge for you.
You're badly hurt.
How can you go anywhere?
You witch!
l'm going to kill you!
Take a look at yourself.
You can't even kill a cockroach.
How can you fight anyone?
Now lay down.
You're going to pass out.
lf you don't watch it,
you're going to pass out soon.
See!
l told you already.
The world may be big,
but paradise is right here.
A bride shouldn't be so filthy.
Let me help you clean up.
Why are you crying?
l miss my husband,
Kit.
Tears for love again.
You think he misses you too?
The more affectionate the man,
the more callous he becomes.
His love for you
will vanish overnight.
l was also hopeless
and in despair once.
But then l realized that,
without a man's love, l can still live.
Don't cry anymore. Cheer up.
Don't shed anymore tears for men.
Damn!
What are you doing?
Leave me alone.
Where are you going?
Get out of my way!
l want to kill that witch!
You want to kill the white hair witch?
With what?
Your kung fu is the worst amongst
the descendants of the Eight Big Clans!
Come back!
Moon, l really appreciate your saving
my life. But l must find Lyre.
l don't even know
if she's dead or alive!
You think you're the only one
who holds a grudge?
Everybody in Chung Yuan
wants to destroy her!
How are you going to kill her
if you're hurt like this?
Shit!
Almost got myself hurt too!
This witch is determined
to destroy the Eight Big Clans.
Now she has even kidnapped Kit's wife.
We don't know if she's even alive.
As soon as Kit recovers,
we'll gather all the descendants of
the clans and attack the witch's palace!
To redeem ourselves
and the reputation of the Eight Clans,
the white hair witch
must be destroyed!
But l'm afraid the descendants' kung fu
may not be good enough to kill her.
What, do you think
you and l should go instead?
l think we should turn this over
to old Granny of Au Mei Clan.
She would be best
to handle this.
Good idea!
lt's decided then.
You are the representatives
of the Eight Clans?
l am Ling Moon Yee
of Kwun Lun Clan.
l am Fung Chun Kit of Wu Tang.
l am Siu Lau of Wah Shan.
Lan Long of Shaolin.
- Yu Hin of Tim Chong.
- Tun Chai.
Liu Hang of Hung Tung.
You thought l was dead already.
Liu!
Kit!
l will help you
attack the evil palace
and cut the white hair witch
into a million pieces.
Don't be ridiculous.
Everyone is not here yet.
Yee of Ching Sing Clan.
How are you?
Your kung fu is more befitting
to join the Peking opera
than to kill the
white hair witch!
The world is so big.
Fate has brought us together.
Let's just try to get along.
Amen.
Watch out!
Someone is coming.
lt's the white hair witch!
You're dead meat!
lt's old Granny
from Ngo Mei Clan!
You blockheads!
Were you trying to knock out my teeth?
Damn!
Granny!
Granny,
are you all right?
Sorry,
l thought you were the white hair witch.
Just because l have white hair?
Moon, don't run around so much.
Go home some time.
And don't dress like
a boy all the time.
l am Yip Pak Chow
of Ngo Mei Clan.
Granny.
Ngo Mei does not
have any young pupils.
Therefore,
they have sent an old Granny like me.
lt's getting from bad to worse.
The white hair witch's base
is inside the Moon Lake.
Let me show you.
Judging from your kung fu,
there is no way you can fight
the white hair witch head on.
You must get in and out
as quickly as possible.
As soon as Lyre is rescued, take off
immediately using the four passage ways.
Do you all know
the Flying Stance?
Yes.
Does Air Stance count?
Get someone to
carry you over then.
Her evil palace
is heavily guarded on all sides.
But the west entrance
is the easiest to sneak through.
Oh no,
l've made a mistake.
This is called
the Virgin Stance.
Rebels!
You're gathering without the permission
of the Ching Palace.
Do you know that
this is punishable by death?
Hand over all your weapons now!
You rebels!
Tell me the purpose of this gathering
and you may be pardoned from death.
What?
Nobody wants to say anything?
Then my only option is to
follow General Wu San Kuei's words...
lt's better to kill a thousand innocent
men than to set a guilty one free.
Hey, big nose! Whats in your mouth?
Spit it out!
Oh God, l didn't want to kill you.
You made me. Amen.
You youngsters are too selfish,
didn't even leave one for me.
There's one left!
Guess which one is faster.
Your arrow or my dart?
ln a moment like this,
people should die glamorously.
No. Not glamorously.
lt's gloriously!
Fung Chun Kit married you to use you
to produce offspring for Wu Tang.
Fung Chun Kit,
you married me
only to use me
to produce offspring for Wu Tang.
Men. See one,
kill one.
Lyre!
Didn't want to look back
But didn't want to miss you
My mind was racing
l was mesmerized
When we meet again
Many seasons had passed
Was it passion?
Did its flame consume me?
lf you still remembered me
Then it was all worthwhile
Madly,
and recklessly l waited
Just to see your smile
Did you know?
l was crazy for you
Was it so wrong?
Did you love me?
Maybe hate was just as strong
l stubbornly lingered
While my hair turned to frost
Did you love me?
l dared not ask
My heart went out for you
l was losing ground
l lived and died for passion and love
Was that really so hard to fathom?
How come there's no message?
lt's been so long.
Maybe even the dove
has found a new love.
l know there was no tomorrow
But for now, your hands are in mine!
Found the perfect wife.
Are you happy now?
lt's more fun to sit under
the moonlight with someone.
Our destiny is predetermined
by the heavens. You actually saved him.
lf this had happened earlier, he might
have married you instead of Lyre.
Oh no, then you would have been the one
who was kidnapped by that witch!
Bite my tongue.
Listen.
There are so many birds in the forest.
Thousands of them, from phoenix
to rooster for you to choose from.
But you had to insist on one
and wouldn't let go.
Now you've even watched him
marry someone else.
Because he is a responsible man.
l know such a husband is hard to find.
But it's too late now.
l have been there before.
When l was young,
l was stubborn just like you.
Maybe even more so.
So what happened?
Like you,
l saw him marry someone else.
l am as old as an owl.
Not even a goose would want me now.
Then go find a crow.
We're back.
Come, let's find out
what's happening.
l am neither a phoenix nor a rooster.
And l don't ask for much.
As long as it's a female.
Now, Fung Chun Kit will lead
on the attack and destroy the witch.
Me?
Granny,
l thought you were going.
l'm good at defense.
Attack? l'm just so so.
Then why do you
sit in the middle?
lt's better to count on ourselves
than on others. Amen.
lt doesn't matter who leads, the
important thing is to die gloriously.
Don't just keep thinking about
failing and dying.
Do you think the white hair witch
has any children?
Why do you ask?
She killed all our ancestors,
and now we're going to kill her.
When we get old,
we will have no more descendants.
Ying Wai.
ls this the man?
No. Don't!
l want you to remember.
You're an animal. You're a pig, a cow!
You must obey my orders!
Before Sister rescued me, l ran away
from home because of this animal.
l loved him and suffered for him
with no regrets.
But for a mere 20 taels,
he sold me to the brothel!
l will never forget that.
l was nothing more than a pig, a cow!
Ying Wai, you let him know exactly
how a cold-blooded animal dies.
Kill him..
Kill him!
No.
Kill him..
Kill him!
Fung Chun Kit, you married me so l could
produce offspring for Wu Tang.
To restore Wu Tang's reputation.
Fine.
Go and get your dead Master
Tse Yuento do it for you!
Here we are.
Why don't we retire and pretend we're
dead. Do you think anyone would know?
The old windbags of the Eight Clans
are all cunning cowards.
They didn't even dare show their faces,
but sent their little prawns instead.
Let's put up a good fight
and show them what we're made of.
We won't die.
Ling, you go with Len Long
and attack from the east.
Liu, you don't know the Flying Stance.
Go with Yee and attack from the south.
Siu Lau, you attack from the west
and l'll take it from the north.
Everybody understand?
l'll give you two taels
to trade places with you.
Cut this nonsense!
Let's go!
You can't even give a good back massage!
You call yourself a man?
Come here.
What are you looking at?
Just do it.
Oh God.. l shouldn't look.
l have sinned!
Where is the white hair witch?
Where is the white hair witch??
Useless!
Women are for you to love,
not to hit!
l only love my mother.
That's a dead end.
This way!
Bastard!
You are such an ugly witch.
l will punish you for the heavens.
l'll strangle you!
Go to hell!!
Where is Lyre?
Take me to her..
Lyre!r
Fung Chun Kit. You married me so
l could produce offspring for Wu Tang.
To restore Wu Tang's reputation.
Lyre.t
The witch must have put a spell
on your wife.
Ask the others to retreat.
How can we? We haven't killed
the white hair witch yet!
Why are you in such a hurry?
Don't leave without saying goodbye.
Goodbye my ass!!
Siu Lau!
Go!s
Lyre?
Your beloved is over here.
Why don't you come get her?
Siu Lau.
Kit,
don't go over there!d
Whatever you do,
don't pull the hair out!
Go!a
Come here!
You damn witch!
Yee, run!
Don't!
Sister, you've fought and killed
for so many years.
Why don't we just leave here together
and find a better place to live?
No, l won't leave here until l've killed
every last soul of the Eight Big Clans.
That is only your excuse.
You're actually jealous
of Lyre and her husband.
What she has with her husband,
you never had with Cho Yi Hang.
That's why you want
to break them up.
You're still thinking about him.
You have been waiting for him.
Please don't forget.
He was the one who turned you
into who you are today!
Why don't you just forget about
this heartless man?
You don't think he
has hurt you enough?
So you think we'll be happy
if we are together?
Ni Chang, with your damn personality,
no one will have a good ending with you!
Whatever you do,
don't pull the hair out.
Moon was hit by the witch's
poisonous white hair.
As soon as the poison starts to work,
it will travel all over her body.
She must not use kung fu,
otherwise, her arteries will burst.
Are we just going to stand here
and watch her die?
You don't have
to be too worried.
As long as she doesn't use her kung fu,
she'll be fine.
Liu,
where are you going?
l'm going outside
to get some wood for the fire.
Maybe he's in shock.
l better go check on him.
Liu, l thought you were going
to chop some wood.
Liu,
l know you really like Moon.
But the husband of her dreams
is a hero with great strengths.
Even though you
aren't quite there yet,
if you study harder, practice your
kung fu and stop playing around so much,
in another eight to ten years,
it still won't be too late to court her.
Don't worry.
Moon won't die.
We should stop
lying to ourselves.
From the very beginning,
we were all destined to die.
You at least have a purpose,
to rescue your wife.
But what about us?
Just to avenge the deaths
of our old ancestors??
- Liu!
l am really getting old!
l misunderstood him completely.
l thought he cried only because of Moon.
l've spoken such nonsense.
Now l found out
the most immature of all was me.
- Liu.
Don't die yet!
Let me stab you a couple more times.
l won't have my turn
when we go back to the palace.
Let him go.
Let him go please.
Damn bastard!
Senile fool!
Granny!
What are you all
standing around for?
Go ahead. Go over there
and give it your best shots!
Little friend, isn't a little pain
invigorating? Pain builds character!
Then why don't you let me stab you?
Let's invigorate each other!
Please let him go.
Let the bastard go?
l won't die.
l am not going to die.
Moon!
Kit,
don't block the moon.
Don't worry, you'll..
save your wife.
Evil can never win over
good and righteousness.
Liu, don't always
hide behind a joker's face.
Be serious.
You have to help Kit.
l know.
Kit.. in the future, when you
and your wife look at the moon,
please remember me..
Liu Moon Yee..
Moon!
Why does it have
to be this girl?
l think you two will have to help me
to dig another grave.
Granny.
l am useless.
l am too old to be of any help to you.
But l know someone
who may be able to help.
Who?
Your Uncle Cho Yi Hang.
Uncle Cho?!
l have nothing to
lose or fear now.
lt was forbidden by the Eight Big Clans
to tell this secret.
But l am telling you now.
Your uncle is hiding in Mount Shin Fung.
Mount Shin Fung?
Yes.
Go and find him.
He may be the only one
who can defeat the white hair witch.
Liu!
Get up, Liu!
Let's keep walking.
Keep walking?
We've walked four days
and there's been no sign of Uncle Cho.
Who can live under these conditions
for ten years?
You don't want to come?
Then l'll go alone!
Kit!
Liu!
l must find Uncle Cho.
l have to tell him Ni Chang has turned
into an evil cold-blooded murderer.
Uncle Cho is the only one
who can help us to destroy her.
Do you understand??
Do you know where
Uncle Cho is hiding?
We will freeze to death
before even finding him!
lf we're dead,
who will rescue your wife?
lt's far better to
count on ourselves.
As long as l have one last breath left,
l will fight that witch!
Moon said: evil can never win over
good and righteousness!
Let's go!
ln one incense's time,
save Lyre and get out of here.
Should we fail, we'll take
the witch to the grave with us!
Those of you who don't want to die,
get out!
Lyre!
Sister-in-law.
l am Kit!
Lyre,
don't fight anymore.
This is from Moon!
This is from me!
Now you know what a real man is!
This is from Yee!
Forget about me.
Just go!
Don't!
Liu.
Kit..
l've done my best...
Liu!
l just have to see
how strong true love really is!
Kit.
Lyre.
You woke up from the spell?
l want you to kill him
with your own hands!
No.
l won't do it!
No!
Lyre!
Kit!
So you can't part from each other?
l will let you two die together!
Run!
Lyre, run!
Uncle Cho!
Ni Chang.
lt's all my fault.
Let them go.
Why didn't you say these words
ten years ago?
lt's too late now!
Go to hell,
you witch!
Uncle Cho!
Kit!
Why don't you fight back?
Ni Chang.
No matter what wrong l've done,
l just want you to know
that l didn't mean to betray you.
Don't move!
Once the hair leaves you,
you'll die!
Witch, to get you this flower, Uncle Cho
waited on Mount Shin Fung for ten years!
And you still want to kill him?
Yi Hang!
Don't move!
Ni Chang!
You paved your own road of destruction.
Do you remember what l said? No one
will have a happy ending with you.
l thought l'd never see you again
in this lifetime.
Have l aged much?
No matter how you've changed,
lt's not important to me.
l've become this way,
all because you did not trust me.
Forgive me!
Hate and despair
Who knew love could be so hard
Love and hate l cannot resolve
Passion faded and youth consumed
All at once l held in my hand
The past and the future
Can we call this
love everlasting?
l do believe when parting
your embrace will sooth my sorrow
Liu, that day at Mount Shin Fung,
we actually found Uncle Cho.
Let's go..
Kit, the other day
at the evil palace,
l thought l saw
the white hair witch's hair turn black!
Really?
lt doesn't really matter now.
The important thing is
that they are finally together!
SUNNY CHAN
CHRlSTY CHUNG
RlCHARD SUN
JOEY MEMG
LlLY CHUNG
RUTH WlNONA TAO
KWOK LEUNG CHEUNG
TAK NGAl YEUNG
CHUN FUNG NG
Directed by: DAVID WU