This is Chu Tu.
He's in his mid to late forties.
He's a nightclub owner, trader,
and property developer.
But we've found out all his companies
are losing money.
Hey, how are things up there?
This is Mad Wing, his bodyguard.
All of his employees
are actually hit men.
Be careful!
I'll see you at the dye factory.
Wait for me up there.
Yes.
This is Danny Chu, his nephew.
He's always surrounded by bodyguards.
This is John Ko, the brains
behind Chu Tu's organisation.
This lady's name is Salina Fong.
She's only joined Chu Tu recently.
It's hard to tell how much she knows
but she is involved.
Our mission is to arrest
all these drug dealers.
The code name is Operation Boar Hunt.
Have you got that?
Yes, sir!
Read your orders.
You all have specific duties.
Memorise then destroy.
It's crucial that you stay in position.
Hurry, come on!
Attention! Crime squad!
The Operation is underway!
Would you like a cup of tea?
Two teas please!
OK!
I'll be back for them.
There is a suspicious looking guy.
Two teas please!
Tell the others, I'll check it out.
Kim!
Are you buying me a tea?
We've been discovered.
What?!
Follow the guy in the red top.
What is it?
This is Salina.
There's a suspicious looking guy...
What are you doing?
Police!
It's the police!
The police are here!
Freeze! Police!
I just heard some gunshots.
They've opened fire!
What to do?
Let's break up the crowd first.
Leave this area now!
Crime squad.
What's happening?!
Police! Get out of here!
Go on! Hurry!
Quick
This way.
Listen! Mind the residents
and get the kids inside.
Hurry up! Go on!
This way.
Move in and help.
But we're supposed to stay out.
The situation's changed.
Move it!
Let me go!
It gets tighter if you move.
I'll keep you covered,
you make a break for it.
Protect the boss!
Go.
There's a female suspect up there.
Take her back to the station.
It's only me!
Why did they open fire?
Don't ask me.
Calm down!
Help me... Tak!
Cover me!
Tak!
You must stay calm.
It hurts.
Help me.
You stay here and take care of him.
They mean business!
Don't forget the warning.
Mind the villagers.
But will the bad guys
give a damn about them?
Who made you a cop?
Come here!
Be careful, Ka-kui.
These guys are really mean!
Boss! This way!
Get in!
You're blocking the road!
Get out of the way!
Reverse!
Not this way!
You OK?
This way's blocked, go back.
Go back! Quick!
Go back up!
The road below is blocked!
We're stuck, boss! Now what?!
Go that way!
Let's go!
Boss! Quick!
Quick!
This way!
Freeze!
Mind the civilians!
Where have you been?
They've all escaped.
We went up to help.
Who gave that order? They're gone!
You can't blame me for that.
Hurry, go!
Can I borrow this?
Tell them to get down.
Stop that.
Get down!
Don't let them see my face.
Tell the driver to step on it!
Quick!
Get down!
Turn here, turn!
Keep going!
Easy, boss, we'll make it.
Look!
Get up there, and get rid of him.
Tell the driver to go faster!
Come down here and get him.
Come down!
Turn the bus! Go down the hill!
What are you doing?
Police. Stay back!
Boss, the bastard's right in front!
Run over him!
Yes.
Step on it, run over him.
We'll be all right.
Freeze!
You're under arrest,
but you have the right to...
If you let me go...
this is all yours.
There is a lot of money here,
no one will ever find out.
Smart guy!
Stop!
Well done, you guys.
Give him credit if he praises you
and don't let it go to your heads.
I know what to do. Ka-kui is the one
who needs your advice.
I didn't do it alone.
It was a success because of careful planning.
That's a great line.
Don't forget to say it
when the Super comes.
He'll be very happy to hear that.
Operation Boar Hunt
was carefully planned.
You were told to go in
and make the arrest.
You almost let the prime suspect
get away.
What happened?
Didn't he give you clear orders?
Yes, but he said the operation
was very well planned.
What?!
This operation was carefully planned.
But it had a few flaws.
Why were there flaws?
That's because Ka-kui
couldn't handle the woman.
Before we even got to the store,
they heard her screaming.
How did Chu Tu get through
your men, then?
What do you mean by that?
Don't point your fingers at each other.
What?!
The PR lady is here.
Let her in.
The press is here, Superintendent.
Tell them no comment!
Hold it. I asked them to come.
Then, tell them to wait.
Ka-kui, you'll be our spokesman.
Me?!
I can't possibly.
The speech is ready, just read it.
Learn your lines.
You can go now
and don't botch them.
The Chief is well pleased
with Ka-kui's performance.
A promising lad.
After the speech, take him
to do a police recruitment poster.
And arrange for him to appear on TV.
A role model?!
The Chief thinks
he's a model policeman.
He'll be really good for it.
What are the charges on Salina?
Drug dealing, resisting arrest
and assaulting police officers.
Drop all the charges.
Really?!
You played a big part
in this operation.
The success of this operation
depended on skilful planning.
He means you.
Will you get a promotion?
As a police officer,
I don't fight crime to get promoted.
I'm not worried about promotions.
Did Chu Tu try to bribe you?
He sure did, with millions.
He could have bribed the whole force.
Just kidding! Don't put that down.
Can you two sit closer?
What are you doing?
Just saying hello.
Don't sit too close.
Let me sit here.
He'll come this way, right?
Yeah!
Let's start!
Straighten up your back.
Open your eyes a bit more.
Open your mouth. Wider.
Wider still!
More.
Forget it,
just be yourself!
Ready?!
The handcuffs in the middle.
Try to be more energetic.
Your plan wouldn't work.
Why not?
Remember, she's Chu Tu's secretary,
not just anyone can get that job.
Chu Tu's been arrested
and once he knows
his secretary is going to be a witness,
what will he do?
He'll do everything he can
to stop her appearing in court.
Whoever we send to protect her
will be in danger.
Don't be a cop if you're not
willing to risk your life.
Put that line on one of our
recruitment posters.
We don't have enough evidence to
prosecute him.
We must push him into a corner.
Then we can put him behind bars.
Who's going to protect her?
I suggest...
I have someone in mind already.
Great minds think alike.
Good luck to him.
You're the only one who got bail.
You're really lucky.
They're here to see the Super.
Please wait.
Please wait. Right.
You can leave after you've seen him.
You can go in now.
Thanks!
Please sit down!
You can leave now, Miss Fong.
Wait a second.
Please keep this subpoena,
you'll need it to appear in court.
What's the charge?
Nothing!
But you'll be acting
as our witness.
I'm sorry!
My client isn't going to do that.
We're not asking her.
According to law, she has to do it.
Inspector Chan!
Your job is to protect Miss Fong
until she appears in court.
Me? Protect her?
Why not?
Great!
I don't need his protection.
As long as he doesn't harass you,
you can't refuse.
Inspector Chan.
As an escort of the witness,
you must be aware that
the witness is often faced with threat,
disturbance, and assault,
or irritated
by the intentions of such.
It is your duty to see her safety
and personal rights are intact.
Yes, sir!
But can you send someone else?
You'll get expenses
for this assignment -
HK$32 per day.
It's an old tradition,
unchanged for years.
I know it's very little. That's all.
Can we talk to you alone, Miss Fong?
My client doesn't answer questions
without the presence of her lawyer.
We won't ask her any questions.
We just want some advice
for her own good.
You have the right to refuse this.
Let me see what they have to say.
Mr. Cheung! Please excuse us.
You don't have to answer
if they ask you any questions
about the case or others.
Get out of here!
I have to go, too?
What is your rank?
What do you want to talk to me about?
Nothing, you can go now.
See you in court.
Did they ask... Let's go.
Ka-kui.
Your tape recorder.
OK.
What did they say to you?
They didn't say anything.
I'm your lawyer, you can trust me.
They didn't say a word to me.
Why was it only her...
They're coming!
How's boss and the others?
I can't bail them out.
What about Salina, then?
She's their witness.
What? Really?!
They want me to do it.
You should have turned it down.
Stop bothering our witness!
Who are you?
I'm a cop!
My duty is to protect her.
If you keep doing that, I can charge
you with interfering with the police.
Salina...
You can only say goodbye or bye-bye.
One more word and you're under arrest.
I'll take you home.
That's part of my job.
I'll tell them nothing!
Now what, Mr. Cheung?
I'll see your boss this afternoon.
All right! Let's go!
It's dangerous for you
to hang around outside.
Let's go home, shall we?
It's none of your business.
It's for your own safety.
I don't need your protection, you fool!
You know what happened to the last
witness who said that?
What happened?!
Were they shot?
Don't try to scare me.
It won't work.
You're right!
They were fine in the end.
You can say whatever you want.
You can't scare me!
All the evidence
points to the defendants.
Only your situation is better.
We're depending on you, Mr. Cheung.
I'll do my best.
You'd better be prepared for bad news.
The chances are slim.
If I walk away free,
I'll take good care of you.
There's still something
we need to worry about.
Salina is their witness.
Is she really?!
She's been granted bail.
The police even gave her an escort -
the guy who arrested you.
Salina doesn't know much.
She's new.
That doesn't concern me.
But she could say something bad
about us in court.
I don't think she would...
All right.
Call Danny for me.
Tell him to take care of Salina.
All right.
Thanks a lot!
Keep the change!
See you later!
It's dangerous to stay home alone.
I always live dangerously.
John? I just got back.
The phone is tapped.
All right, I'll meet you later.
I'm really scared!
You think you can scare me like that?
Help!
I'm going to kill you!
Don't go.
I'll get you!
You have to die!
I'm going to kill you!
Go to hell!
I got you!
I'm going to kill you!
Don't run away!
I've got you now!
Go to hell!
Here I come!
Hide no where!
There's no way out. You're finished.
I'm going to kill you!
Don't worry! I'm here!
She's terrified. Can I go now?
You can leave right now.
Hold on to him, I'll call the police.
I knocked him out!
Not yet! He's still conscious.
He's fighting me!
Keep away from us!
Please go now.
You can't stay here any longer.
Don't faint!
Go!
I go...
He's passed out!
No! He's still conscious. See?
Look at me.
Don't!
Please leave here right now!
Go now! Go on!
Go! Hurry!
No more acting. Let\92s go!
Leave him to me!
He's fainted.
This time is real.
Let me hit him one more time!
Stop, or we won't be able
to identify him.
I don't want to do this any more.
I don't know him.
They'd use a stranger to kill you.
Why kill me?
Of course, Chu Tu's a ruthless man.
Inspector Chou, it's Ka-kui.
I just realised this is a tough case.
Can you send a replacement?
No?!
I'm not risking my life
for a few thousands.
I've had enough of her!
I don't give a damn about her any more.
I quit! Enough is enough!
Where are you going?
Home!
You're supposed to protect me!
But you're not cooperating.
How can I protect you.
What if I cooperate?
It's too late! I quit.
I can't believe it!
You cops have no sense of duty.
I have.
But there's nothing I can do.
If I stay here, I'll get killed, too.
I'll cooperate.
I'm not forcing you.
I'm doing it of my own free will.
You should come to my house,
it's much safer there.
Great!
Look at you!
I'll get changed!
Chu's men could be back any time.
I won't change my clothes, then.
Now what?
What is it?!
I'm checking to see if everything's OK.
Go back!
Come out.
Why are you holding that?
This is your jacket.
I told you to put it on.
Yes.
Follow me!
Use my car.
Which one is yours?
Over there.
Why are you not nervous at all?
I'm used to situations like this.
I told you to stay quiet, didn't I?
Now what?
My son!
Yours?
Close the car door!
It's me!
Give me my gun!
It's in my jacket pocket.
Help!
I've got you!
Freeze!
Stay calm! Give me the gun.
Stay calm! Keep away!
Go.
Give me the gun! It's me!
Are you all right?
Where are they?
You scared them off with that shot.
We must get you away from here,
those guys are for real.
Who was the guy at my house, then?
He wanted to kill you, too.
But these are professionals.
I see why you're nervous now.
Get in the car.
You're crying?!
How could Chu Tu do this to me?
You can't be that naive.
Your boss is capable of anything.
He can't have you in that courtroom!
What should I do then?
You should tell the judge everything
so he can put Chu in jail
and then you'll be safe.
What should I say to the judge?
What rackets Chu Tu's involved in,
who his contacts are,
who the dealers are.
Why are you taping this?
It's for my own reference.
How long have you worked for him?
Four years.
He's a family friend.
He used to give my mother
money to buy me food.
Now you help him deal drugs.
I hardly know anything.
You can still tell me what you do know.
If you remember anything else,
don't forget to tell me.
Do you have enough to prosecute him?
That's for the court to decide.
What you've told me is very useful.
Come in.
Let me turn on the lights.
It's May.
I almost forgot today's my birthday.
Are you all right?
Let me introduce you,
this is Miss Fong.
Let's go.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
May!
They've all gone? That was quick!
It's all my fault.
She wanted to surprise you,
but you brought me here.
And I'm dressed like this.
Of course she's angry.
I'm angry, too.
I didn't even have the chance to explain.
She dumped the cake on me!
I won't answer
if she calls to apologize.
I doubt she will.
I knew she would be back!
What so happy about it?
I saw May. What's wrong?
She saw me with our witness.
I'll go and explain to her.
No need. Tell her to curb her temper.
Why do I have to explain everything
to everyone?
I'm sick and tired of it.
Do you want some cake?
What about a drink, then?
Orange juice, please!
Help yourself!
Do you live alone?
It's too big, they'd get me
for corruption.
I rent it with a friend.
And he's away.
I'm really sorry.
Your girlfriend was furious when she saw me.
Don't worry.
I was doing my job.
Come on! Come in!
You'll be all right. I'm leaving.
See you!
I'm just a cop now.
But I might become a movie star
and have to kiss ladies passionately.
What would she do then?
She loves you, so she's jealous.
I'll explain to her.
What for?
She'll never understand me.
Aren't you going
to say something nice to her?
No way!
If I started sweet-talking,
I'd have a million girls.
You love her a lot, don't you?
To be honest, I do love her a lot!
But loving her is one thing,
apologizing is another.
When she gets home,
she'll call and apologize to me.
What a waste of food!
Am I right?
She couldn't wait to call me.
Hello.
Hello?
Is that your girlfriend?
It's her. She's crying!
Stop crying. You shouldn't
humiliate me in front of people.
What?!
If I was with a man,
you'd think I was gay.
You're so childish!
Curb your temper!
Let me explain to her.
No need!
Curb that temper of yours!
You should show me some respect.
Stop crying. Talk to you later.
It's time to teach her a good lesson.
When did she come back?
Right after you went in the shower.
So she heard everything?
The phone call?!
Not again!
May!
Let me explain.
She's our witness,
my job is to protect her.
I'm mad about what you just said!
I was just kidding.
Don't be mad.
Why are you angry?
Why?
You just insulted me in front of her.
How dare you?!
Go away!
Please listen to me! May!
May...
Are you all right?
No! Are you happy now?!
I hurt.
Of course I'm not.
I didn't mean to do that!
Your shoe.
Here, put it on.
Go away!
May, please listen to me!
No, I don't want to!
Don't be so childish.
Listen to me, will you?
Let me go.
Be careful!
I hate you!
Where is she?
I accepted her apologies,
and she went home.
Oh, you! That hurt?
What did I do?
You really poked me!
You're breaking it!
Don't push too hard!
What an ugly thing!
Go away!
It's the only one I got. It's broken.
You got me all wet!
Let me wipe it for you.
Please, no more! No, don't!
Not there, here.
Here?!
Be gentle! That hurt!
This sofa's hard, it's not very comfy.
Let's go to bed now.
Let's go to bed.
But where can I sleep?
On my bed.
And you?
Next to you.
You're so protective.
It's exciting!
I'm going to bed.
Don't wake me up.
Women are weird!
Hello?
Ka-kui? Wait!
He's on the line.
You're late. We're waiting for you!
He's not here.
I know it's you. Quick!
Get that witness here.
What was your duty on that day?
I was observing the squatter huts
behind the site.
The suspects were trying to escape,
and I arrested two of them.
Thank you!
Can I ask the witness a question?
Inspector Kim,
you said you saw the suspects escaping.
Did they pass in front of you
one by one?
Or did you have a special device
to allow you see them
escaping at the same time?
I object!
I object! The question played
with the witness's wording.
Overruled!
Thank you! No more questions!
Bring on the next witness.
That's my spot.
I'm in a hurry!
I want that space!
Nice parking, though.
What?! She's gone?
What have you been up to?
Now what? We might lose.
I don't know.
We'll lose.
How could you be so sure that one of
the escaping suspects was my client?
He had the same clothes.
In other words, you didn't have a
clear view of the suspects' faces.
I would say so.
Are you short-sighted?
No, I'm not.
All right. No more questions.
Next witness.
I swear to tell the truth.
I was at the squatter huts
for the operation.
The first, second, third
and fourth defendants opened fire.
I saw them jump on a bus.
So I took a short cut
and went down the hill.
A citizen helped me
to stop the bus with his car.
After the bus stopped,
I arrested the first defendant.
He tried to bribe me,
but I refused.
That was very clear. Thank you!
You were at the squatter house.
What time was that?
About 6:00 a.m.
What time exactly?
5:55 a.m.
Let's say 6:00 a.m.
In December in Hong Kong,
sunrise is at 6:23 a.m.
Did you know that?
I didn't know.
Is that true?
I don't know.
Do you know the saying
Darkness before dawn?
No, I don't.
The saying means that it's dark
before the sun rises.
I might have heard of it.
All right.
If there wasn't much light,
should we believe
you could actually see my client?
Believe what you like.
I did see him.
It's your business.
You shouldn't ask me.
You said you ran down the hill
to stop the bus.
Was the bus always in sight?
Yes.
Why hesitate?