Five minutes.
Where is Frank?
Lenny Drake
8 YEARS
VIV Batista
12 YEARS
Brodie
LIFELONG
James Lacey
7 YEARS
You've got yourself a friend.
Bets are over.
He's a handycap.
This one's missing a leg.
- I'm going for two on red.
- Too late, Frank, the runners are on the track
- Well give it back.
- Sorry, Frank, you owe the bank.
- Transfer?
- I'm out, Frank.
Just like that?
Alright.
Where's Hedge?
You don't see him?
He's out the door.
- Is he?
- You're next Lenny.
They were soft on him, things
will look good for you.
It's not likely they're going to split up such
a formiddable partnership, now is it?
Drake!
Get your fucking hands off me!
Hedges!
Catwalk!
Hello, brother.
Come on, let's get them.
- You smoked.
Give me one. Come on.
You have them all.
Someone takes care of you.
- Of course not.
Are you sure?
- Yes, I want one of them pussies.
Come on, come on.
Give me one.
Pussies!
Hey, you!
Look good to me!
The next time I see you
stand with your face against the wall!
- Against the wall, yeah!
- You bet.
Pussies! Pussies! Pussies!
This is your cell. This is your bunk.
This is your cellmate.
James Lacey.
Perry, mail.
Frank Perry
Prisoner Number 23401
Stare at someone else.
Thinking about me Muschi
I know you are.
Prisoner 24484 Brodie, absent from Cell
Prisoner 27103 Lacey, absent from Cell
Prisoner 23410 Perry, to your cell!
- Prisoner 26432 Drake absent from Cell
Prisoner 135 Batista, absent from Cell
You come at the wrong time,
chapel is closed.
Perry!
Well...
It's been a wee while.
I'll be right outside.
This is very hard.
But...
I'v got something I have to say to her.
It's nearly time, Batista.
Book!
Book.
Magazine.
Give me a card.
Come on, I want a card, Batista.
Just give me one.
Just give it to me!
Go beg your brother.
Do you get to wait awhile.
He's getting cocky, Rizzi! he's laughing
at me! You know he does it, you know he fucking does it!
Get out.
You heard me, now get out.
Batista!
Come with me.
Your choice.
Tony said it was...
Tony...
Checkmate.
That's the first time in 11 years.
Another game Frank?
Lacey, have a wonder.
- I'm not really in the mood.
- Have a wonder.
Hey kid.
Five minutes.
What?
The air vents in the laundry.
Would they connect to a sewer?
- Come again?
- The back of the dryer's.
Would they connect to the sewer system?
Frank, what's going on?
My first letter in 14 years.
Telling me our little girl's
a junkie.
Her heart stopped twice.
- She's a... she's not comin'...
- No.
Before it happens again...
I gotta see her.
- I gotta make things right.
- Frank!
I want out, Brodie.
Not in a month,
not six.
Now.
- The air vents in the laundry, do they connect?
- Frank, your not thinking straight...
Does it connect?
I'm not asking again.
Yeah.
But the air vent, it'll be capped.
You won't go through solid steel.
- Lenny Drake can.
- Lenny Drake? his walking in a few.
His parole's been revoked.
Hedge's grassing him for early release.
Suppose you get past the door cap,
the vent'll only take us as far as the perimeter.
as soon as your there you'll be picked up.
That's why I'll go deeper.
- No, I'm not going back down there.
- I'm telling you, you don't have to.
Jesus, Frank. You know why I'm in this dump.
- Would you listen?
- I want you to tell me, not take me.
- I can't tell you.
Fuck.
I can't even even draw you a map.
Is your mind made up?
Frank!
Without me, you'll be lost in minutes.
Stare at someone else.
- I'm not in the mood for a chat today.
- I can understand that.
Cunt snitched me out.
Well I tell ya, nobody was
more surprised than I was.
He walks early and I
go out for Gomez?
So I murdered a guard,
Hedge's... Fucker was holding him down.
When walk out that door...
Suppose I could get you
out the door, with me?
Don't fuck with me, Perry!
I told you I'm not in the mood.
What would you prefer to smack? that
bit of leather, or your number two?
Smack?
I had something more brutal in mind.
You walk through walls, Lenny.
and that's useful.
Is it?
Say we talk...
and you're not interested,
Well it goes without saying
we never talked.
Yeah, goes without saying.
Domino.
Three players.
Alright. Barriers.
One.
Two.
Three.
- Locks?
- Bolt and key.
No chance.
I'm a thief, not a magician.
- There is another way.
- How?
Shower drain.
Directly above.
There's the same problem above.
And more barriers.
Only one. The chapel wall.
- It'll take all night.
- Ever considered confessing?
Back of the confession room...
panels... loose.
And the chapel door?
What about the tools?
The Lord...
Provides.
Domino.
The first time we hit a tile,
screws'll come running.
- Alarm's would be louder.
- Who sets them of?
- We do, when they caught on to us missing.
- It's an obstacle course as it is.
If they're onto us from the off...
We'll be over the drains when the alarm goes
by the time they leave the spar...
- We'll be in the laundry.
- How long have you got before you're in the laundry?
Five minutes... tops.
That's enough.
Alright.
Next piece.
The dryer.
- Locks?
- Older than me.
What about the cap? on the vent.
You don't worry about that.
- I'll sort my end.
- Yeah, yeah I do worry.
Have you got something that cuts through steel?
I'v got whatever it takes.
Five minutes of your time.
I think I may have found
you a challenge.
Domino.
From the minute we're inside,
you don't breathe, you don't talk.
That far underground, banter echo's.
Ignore your thinking,
it'll only be playing tricks.
Things are different down there.
The laundry vent'll take us to here,
top of the sump.
Then we go deep.
There's a drainage tunnel.
Now were gonna need to get through
that... after that,
as far, as the river.
- What river?
- We're south, remember?
I can't swim.
No? We go under it.
There's a reservoir under the embankment.
it connects to the rail network.
Once we're on the tracks,
All roads, lead to Rome.
Charing cross, that's where we surface.
- Why so far? There's got to be stations closer?
- Plenty of exits.
- Easy to disappear, if we head for rush hour.
- No, before rush hour.
Track goes live at five.
630 Volts.
If we're not on the platform,
by then, we're tap-dancing.
How do you know all this?
How's he know all this?
Because I shovelled shit down there
for 12 years.
Prosperous holiday for you then.
Ok. How much time?
The night bell rings about 9.
That gives us eight hours into the AM.
- When do we go?
- How much do you need?
Three days.
That's good for me.
On Friday...
we away.
Oh, one more thing,
Just make sure you don't get
murdered that night.
There you go, proof that David
and Goliath, is cock... and bullshit.
Wouldn't be to sure.
Did you drop something?
Didn't see you there.
No, you didn't.
Fancy yourself do you, Frank?
What?
You got permission?
You done.
Fuck.
Fuck... that's not gonna make
Rizza happy.
The trouble is, if I open my
mouth,
he'd like to piss in yours.
I could sort somethimg out,
avoid any trouble.
What?
Time out, Frank.
With Len gone.
I can run faster.
To find out Rizza's gonna,
make sure you don't go anywhere.
Unless you sort me out.
Yeah, that's right.
You won't get enough?
First bill tomorrow, Frank.
In your cell, Frank, yeah?
First bell.
Drop it!
Don't you do this, I will not let
you fuck this up!
'Fish and Chips " with salt and vinegar?
how about that?
You got to be looking forward to that.
Yeah?
Park bench in the sun...
A beautiful large portion
of... fresh battered cod,
wrapped in a newspaper.
Watching beautiful girls jog by...
You know what I mean?
No.
You alright?
What?
Tony.
- Fuck.
- What?
How the fuck, did he find out?
- What does he want?
- Half a key
- Half a fucking key? That's more than a little grounds worth.
- We've got options.
Yeah, I suggest the option,
that murders him.
And have Rizza on our backs.
Not a chance, Tony's untouchable.
Not, Tony, Batista. We get
rid of him and pocket his stash.
Where do we look, under
his mattress? Check in his pockets?
The guy's got an operation going on,
don't you think his smarter than that.
Prick's not made of fucking, kryptonite!
Nobody's getting their hands
bloody for Tony. Nobody!
- Are you killing him?
- No.
So?
What if...
A ticket out, is worth something to,
Batista?
Half a key?
- And you want me to give it to you?
- No.
It's a trade.
Who else is going?
Brodie.
And Lenny Drake.
Lenny Drake?
Half a key of CAT,
cleans me out for a month.
Tony knows that.
So...
Tony's got a taste for it.
He think you kill me for it,
or steal it.
Which puts me in a coffin, or worse
if I don't deliver it for Rizza.
Besides...
If Tony knows, then Tony know's.
He's the devil on your back now.
But you will not trade,
I give out trade.
CAT's, are dangerous drug,
but deadly when poison.
You get me?
If it looks,
smells and tastes like CAT's...
- Who will know?
- No one touches Tony.
- Rizza will...
- Rizza?
Who's gonna tell Rizza?
Junkies die, every day.
Alright.
That's a trade.
Shit.
Brodie, wait!
Brodie...
Lights out.
You smoke?
That was the last time I saw her.
She'll be 21 tomorrow.
# He took a knife and he cut her down. #
# And on her bosom, these lines he found #
# Oh, what a foolish girl #
# was I, to hang myself,
for a butcher's boy. #
# Go dig my grave,
both wide and deep. #
# Put a marble stone
at my head and feet #
# And on my grave... #
# ...I die for love. #
This is cozy.
You should wrap a blanket,
'round him, Frankie, he's cold.
- Give us a minute.
- No.
No, he stays.
I like his company.
Got something for me have you, Frank.
What's Sykes doin' here?
Call it a peace of mind.
How do I know, you'll keep
your mouth shut up?
- Your lucky your still fucking standing.
- I need a guarantee.
- Anymore?
- It is trade.
I want a guarantee that you'll keep your mouth
shut, otherwise there is no deal.
You don't, make rules.
Yeah.
Have a burn.
Rizza! Ri... Ri...
Rizza!
It's okay kid... it's okay.
It's okay.
Open the door's.
Do it, Perry! Now
Frank...
Frank.
- I see something.
- What?
Well he came out of nowhere.
wh... you couldn't do a thing?
- Well he's a walking corpse now.
- We all are.
Why?
Little kid did the job for us.
As soon as he finds Sykes,
Rizza will hit wind, with the palm.
Rizza's upwind.
The only thing he knows,
is that Tony took a fall.
And Lacey?
What happens to him now?
He will not be in the hole for long.
Rizza, will make sure of that.
Will he hump the Rizza?
Which weigh's more, Frank?
a tonne of bricks...
or a ton of feathers?
He is a dead man,
with or without us, Frank.
So we leave tomorrow,
as planned.
- Where are you going?
- It's been awhile, since my last confession.
Listen... leave it.
Follow him!
Let's move, we've got one hour
before the tracks go live.
Listen!
- They've found us!
- Let's move!
Keep running!
Hello, Frank.
Hello, Rizza.
- I was sorry about your brother.
- Why's that? Did you kill him?
- Well, I had no reason.
- Well, there's always reason's.
He was a junkie,
a cunt, nobody liked him.
I don't smoke, Frank. I don't
like smoke around me.
You got family, Frank?
Yeah.
Any young?
Aww, she's a gorgeous one.
Do you love her?
Family is important.
But the only important thing.
So I'll only ask once.
I won't ask again.
He was talking to the lad.
He had a thing for him.
Tony, was over by the doorway...
Making moves on him.
Sykes...
Pulled him from the doorway.
I heard them Arguing...
Fighting.
After a minute.
There whole, spur was quiet.
You don't have much...
- yet you just subtracted, from what's left.
- Rizza...
You lie to me one more time...
They're bringing your boy out tonight.
I want him in my cell, before
closing time. You bring him.
You got one thing kind for you, Frank.
You're too old, to die young.
- You alright?
- No.
He's alright.
Stay with us, Frank!
Are you ready?
Perry?
Batista, Mitra,
Parkhurst.
Visiting room.
Wait... Frank.
Let's move.
Before these tracks go live.
Frank!
Frank, move now!
Help me.
Go, go, go!
Go!
Hurry!
Sit down.
Where you from, lad?
London.
- Old Street.
- Old Street?
I can't remember my street.
Rizza's, waiting for you, in his cell.
Want's me to take you there.
Go to the chapel, lad,
Before the end bell.
And make your confession.
Give this to Brodie.
- I don't understand.
- Yes, you do.
Why me, Frank.
You remind me of someone.
Five minutes.
Where is he?
You know...
I must have read this book,
about a dozen times.
If I had my time again, and I could
start over like, Rereading this book.
It'd be someone, I'd sit down
and talk to.
I'd talk some sense into him, tell him
how things really are.
But I can't.
That man's long gone,
and I'm all that's left.
- Where is he?
- But do you know something?
I'm free now.
- Like my little girl.
- Free?
- You've got an imagination.
- Imagination's what protects us.
It's what keeps us alive.
But, your still living,
but less and less.
Inside, you own this place.
You run things,
you're the king,
but look around you, what do you see?
It's all prepared.
It's all made up.
You own nothing.
Nothing except cells, bars
and a rusty metal staircase.
You'll never live... because outside,
you don't exist.
- No one will remember you.
- You, behave yourself.
Behaving myself, it's what's
kept me living this long.
- You tell me where he is.
- Lacey?
He'll be alright.
- He's gone, Rizza.
- What did you say?
Gone.
Where's Frank?
The lad's free.
Don't you walk away from me!
It's like you said
I'm too old...
Alarm!
Frank...
Frank!
I got no air.
Brodie...
Frank.
- Frank.
- Frank!
There's no air.
I can't breathe.
...can't breathe.
You stay with us, Frank
- Stay with us!
- Come on, Frank!
Come on, Frank.
Come on.
We are Free
Subtitles edited, by Scooby