Be careful!
Hey, mister.
Mister...
Mister, move over a bit.
Cut it out.
This seat isn't just for you.
Move over a little.
Cut it out.
- Have a seat, please
- It's okay.
Excuse me!
Sit down.
Excuse me.
Damn, I said stop it!
I'm waiting for red bean cakes...
If you follow this alley to the end,
there's a place that
sells hamburgers.
The food here doesn't agree
with you?
Here it is.
Sung-ho, today I...
Don't worry.
It's not a difficult club.
- I don't know history well.
- So you should learn.
Hello, sir.
Did you find the book I requested?
Sure, I've guarded it well for you.
Really?
I think the book you want is
way back there.
Wow, things have really
deteriorated since I left.
Gesturing at me with your chin?
Where's the club president?
The new president's policy is,
you get your own book. Sir.
If that's your policy, then, I shall follow it.
You're back!
Who's this?
I'll introduce you.
A freshman, SUH In-ha...
A gift to the club on my return.
The No. 2 in this book club,
med student Choi Jung-ran.
More a sacrificial offering
than a gift, perhaps.
But you'll have no regrets
or retreats once you're in.
- Good luck
- Yes, sir
We'll need everything on
Chosun folk painting,
so let's look for books first.
Yes.
Okay! Let's go.
However Confucian the society
was... look!
This is all voyeuristic eroticism.
These were drawn because
there was an audience for them.
The nobility bans the
Songs of Physical Love,
while they order and print these
among themselves.
The Chosun Era is nothing.
In the history of Koryo,
...was it the 16th king?
He was negligent of his rule
due to a homosexual affair.
- Really?
- In where?
You mean our country's gay history
goes that far back?
Then if the king was gay,
the queen was a man?
- Why?
- Hey, move, move!
When you people come,
even I get a bit distracted.
- Am I really a book seller?
- Yes.
You get prettier each time I see you.
- What's up?
- Thank you.
Wait, if they're gay,
then it must be the
Songs of Gay Love.
Put this in your mouth.
Eat a shrimp chip.
Sung-ho, what are the
Songs of Love... What was it?
Please understand him.
He went to high school
in the U.S., not here.
Oh, America...
He seems to speak Korean well.
How long were you there?
Hey, I like guys who speak English.
You didn't take entrance exams,
did you?
Wait, everyone.
I'll introduce him properly
over drinks later.
How about sorting though
- the books we found today?
- Yes.
Yes!
You grew up in America,
so you had no chance to learn
about our history or culture.
- Is that it?
- What?
Hui-jae!
Wherever you're brought up,
isn't it a good idea
to learn about your roots?
I'm sorry.
No need to apologize,
but if that's your attitude, go...
Hui-jae... No, President.
Wait a sec.
We know your style,
but you may have startled him.
You think so?
Excuse me.
Sorry to inconvenience you.
I'll study first, and then come back.
Forgive me.
Are you okay?
Forgive me. Goodbye.
He's going to destroy my book shop.
Attention, please.
I'm going to say something very moving.
What's that?
- In this beautiful season...
- Yes.
Buy books with hard cash!
She always spoke her mind
with great certainty.
Though I felt like I'd had both
cheeks slapped,
it was good incentive for me.
Oh, anatomy class is
such a headache for me.
You always do well anyways.
What a great day!
Why?
- Hui-jae
- Huh?
Wait a sec.
Hey.
You're working hard.
Jung-ran!
Was your head spinning there
at the book club?
It was fine.
President said it's okay
to come next week.
Then, see you around.
What?
Oh, but one thing...
This isn't next week's text.
We're not doing the Chosun Era?
The President is the one
who chooses texts.
Don't hate me.
Excuse me!
Thank you. Thank you.
In-ha! Put those here,
and can you get Hye-mi's books?
Sure.
Wow, sir, you could change
your profession.
I'm sorry, ma'am!
Good work, SUH In-ha!
Shoot, shoot, shoot!
In-ha! Pass!
- Hui-jae
- Pass!
She's not on our team!
You idiot!
- One to six!
- Six to four!
- Four to three!
- Three to two!
- Two to six!
- Six to two!
Try again...
It's no use. You all go ahead.
When In-ha comes, I'll take him.
The new guy's slacking off, huh?
Sung-ho, I'll wait with you.
No, you go and guide the group.
Jung-ran, go and get dinner ready.
Why, are you planning to give
In-ha a beating?
No, Sung-ho.
- Okay, let's go.
- The ship's leaving. Go.
Don't worry. He can take it.
Hui-jae!
Oh, I'm sorry. Did everyone...
- Ahh!
- You know what time it is?
But I left early...
So?
Everyone said to come to the wharf.
So what?
I didn't know "wharf" and "harbor"
were the same.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
Hui-jae!
You look so comfortable there!
This is great!
There's so much water
in this country.
When I took the bus
from the airport,
it was impressive seeing
the Han River
next to the highway.
Is it inconvenient for you,
having so many of us here?
Not at all! Having you here
brings the place to life.
Sorry for the trouble!
Oh, it's no problem.
So, should we read
"The Fox and the Crane?"
Yes!
Open to page 20.
Who wants to read?
- Me!
Will you do it, Min-jung?
Yes.
A few days later, the crane invited
the fox home.
The fox went happily
to the crane's home.
But the food was served in
bowls with tall necks.
I made this specially for you.
- Hey, Dong-hyun.
- Shit!
Keep reading...
Hey, KANG Dong-hyun!
Stop!
Dong-hyun!
Hui-jae!
Are you okay? What's wrong?
Catch Dong-hyun for me.
Hey, Dong-hyun!
Let me go!
Let me go! Shit!
- Shit!
- Dong-hyun!
Shit!
It's a spank for every swear word.
You have two now.
If you want to swear,
make noise and run away,
then you should quit camp.
But I'd rather that
you stayed at camp.
At camp you can read books
and even win prizes.
Huh, prizes?
Speak politely!
If you read the whole book,
I'll give you a special gift.
You'll give me whatever I want?
Sure.
Do you promise?
I promise.
Be sure to stir it well,
so it doesn't stick together.
Okay.
Save some for us.
That rice wine is great!
Work hard, In-ha.
I'm envious, seeing your life here.
Move here after you get married.
Rice wine.
Thank you.
Enjoy it!
Hui-jae, you want a cup?
You go ahead.
This is beautiful!
You could make a great
picture book with this.
Sure. It's a bit expensive, though.
Because it takes a lot of work.
Honey, we're almost
out of lime and glue.
When you go out this weekend...
Sure, I was planning to
go out with Sung-ho.
That new member is a good worker.
Oh, I heard there was a fuss with
Dong-hyun this morning?
He caught me by surprise...
Is he always like that?
Ever since his mother ran off.
She said she'd be back in two days...
But I think someone told him that
she ran away.
Kid's behavior is determined
by parents.
His mother lying like that, well...
He doesn't believe anything
that adults tell him.
Hui-jae looks much stronger
than she did as a freshman.
Leading the children,
presiding over the club...
Words like enthusiasm,
sincerity and responsibility
all fit her perfectly.
You sound like a man
bragging about his wife.
KANG Dong-hyun! Come up.
Good for you!
Nice job.
- KIM Tae-hyun!
- Yes!
Come on up.
- Nice work, Tae-hyun.
- Thank you.
Teacher, you'll keep your promise?
Sure, what is it?
Swim up to there and back.
You see the red flag? To there.
What?
Dong-hyun, why are you so bad?
You know that she can't swim.
That's right, your teacher's
afraid of the water.
She fell in as a child.
Dong-hyun
do you want to play soccer
with me instead?
Yeah!
I'll go.
I promised.
Hui-jae...
In-ha, stop her.
She fell in the water
during 1st year
and nearly drowned.
Open your eyes.
Open your eyes, Hui-jae!
Look at me, not the water.
It's okay up to here.
It's not deep.
Slowly... I'm here,
so don't worry.
Good.
- Out of the way!
- Just a sec.
Dong-hyun, is that okay?
A bad compromise makes it worse.
Hui-jae...
Is that okay?
Answer him, quick!
Is it okay?
He said it's...
- She hasn't woken up yet?
- No.
But doesn't she need to go
to the hospital?
It's just a combination of
lack of sleep and stress.
She didn't faint,
she's just sleeping.
Hey, why don't you eat something?
You missed lunch.
I'm okay.
In-ha...
Do you like Hui-jae?
If she wakes up she should eat
something, so tell me.
Do you feel okay?
Before... was that you?
Did everything go well?
Yes.
Lie down.
I'm okay.
Have some water.
Stop, it's embarrassing having
a younger man care for me.
If a younger man said
he loved you...
Would you laugh at that too?
You really are laughing.
What's up with you?
Hey, SUH In-ha!
I'll forgive you only because
you saved my life today.
I understand, it can happen.
As a freshman, you can be
attracted to
older women.
It may sound trite,
but you'll thank me later
for refusing you.
So you're refusing me now?
Hey, SUH In-ha.
Why are you so serious?
Let's stop this.
We'll feel awkward later.
I'm tired. I want to be alone.
Your attitude now
seems more awkward.
I can't feel moved
by the confession of
a 20-year old.
People always say love is this
or love is that,
but this is what I think.
Love should include the will
to take responsibility.
Being overwhelmed with passion
like a sudden fever...
that's not to my taste.
Your hair has the
scent of chrysanthemums.
What?
I first saw you in the subway.
You spoke your mind freely,
even if you felt shaky.
I was standing behind you.
And when I picked up the coin
in front of the coffee machine,
the wind blew,
and I smelled chrysanthemums
from your waving hair.
I'd never smelled
such a thing before...
At the time, I thought
it a passing fancy.
So I didn't speak,
couldn't speak of it until now.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
I've a favor to ask.
I don't want to lose a...
I've got a strong punch.
When you feel better,
then come out.
She punched my stomach,
but it was my heart that felt pain.
My chest ached from a thin
but deep wound.
When the physical pain healed,
I thought maybe I could forget her.
Hello? Hello?
Mister, has the last train left?
What? Soon, the first train
is going to arrive.
- Hello!
- Hi.
Hi.
What's this?
A gift from the male members
of the club.
So no flowers.
Oh, who's this?
In-ha?
Happy graduation.
Who is it?
The student that Hui-jae and
I told you about last time.
Who grew up in America...
Oh, right.
I wanted to see you
after hearing their stories.
Happy graduation.
You're so congratulatory.
You already said that before.
My 20-year old passion
didn't vanish with the next year.
Rather, it gained the weight of time.
Yes, sir! Yes, sir!
- It's beautiful scenery.
- Uh...
Mom, it's great, huh?
Mother, Father...
It was good of us
to leave today, right?
In-ha!
The hardest thing for me to endure...
Because of me,
she's had to suffer
so much hardship.
That's the most difficult.
She was mine.
But I let her go.
And if I come now to try to win
her back,
I could hurt her even more.
In-ha...
If...
If another chance comes to me,
I'll never...
But I'll wait for her to accept me.
Many days passed
since I said those words.
Each morning
I'd pray, by some miracle,
to meet her again.
Like a bookmark
placed in a book she set aside,
...a person to remember for her
where to start reading again,
I pass another day.
This letter was sent
by Mr. Bookmark,
who sends a postcard
every Thursday.
Many listeners now wait
for his messages on Thursdays,
myself included.
Waiting for his love
to re-commence,
with expectant hope, I play
his request for you now.
This is JUNG Eun-ah.
Push a little more.
Like a person trying to
avoid the light,
or as if bright colors no longer
existed for her,
the works she produces
for this world
are like a darkness
crushed by sorrow.
Whenever I see her colors,
my heart still sinks.
I thought that time
would heal her wounds,
but I worry now that
they only become deeper,
and I feel more troubled.
It's me.
Come on in.
Have you had dinner?
Dinner? You know what time it is?
Isn't it around 8:00?
You want some coffee?
How about a drink?
Did anything happen?
Me?
What about you?
I'm so-so.
You shouldn't be just
so-so anymore.
You should let them go.
Your parents and Sung-ho...
What? I'm okay now.
Hui-jae, you're not okay.
Your wounds haven't healed,
they still hurt.
You just accept it
and live with the pain.
Your sensitivity doesn't suit a doctor.
We ought to switch professions.
Hui-jae!
I don't know if I have unhealed
wounds or not.
If I do, it's not a disaster.
I'm living fine as it is.
You call this living?
I haven't died.
This is the program
produced by In-ha.
It's Thursday, so shall we hear
from our tragic love?
A letter from Mr. Bookmark.
Is In-ha doing well?
I'm hungry...
Hui-jae, what are you doing?
You want something?
No, hurry back.
Her favorite drink was
half a glass of cold beer,
or a glass of cola, lemon,
and ice mixed with gin.
Whenever she drank,
she'd say she was hungry.
She'd say a banana
was better than
eating bread or rice.
Perhaps because the banana
was more filling...
she said, unlike a fruit,
it would stick to her throat.
I'm going crazy.
If Hui-jae eats fresh yogurt often,
it sustains her, and
makes her feel secure.
You know the convenience store
by her home?
She buys it there.
On Wednesday, she stops
at the bookstore for design...
Jung-ran.
You said it. You want her consent
through fate.
I'm telling you how to do it.
It won't happen just because
you two live in Seoul.
First, run into her as if by chance.
Then if fate doesn't bring you
her consent, it won't work.
Even if you spend the
same time together,
a person you're not destined
for won't be the same.
What are you scared of?
How long will you send letters
she doesn't hear into the air?
Young people wasting their time
this way is a crime.
Someday she'll hear it.
No, she won't.
She knows it's your program,
so she surely won't listen.
Why not?
She's decided not to let
anything enter her life.
Hello?
Oh, yes. No, I wasn't sleeping.
I was just finishing up.
Yes. Tomorrow? Okay.
But sir, we don't usually
work this way.
Sure, I know you're busy.
I need it fast without
any loss of quality,
so who else can do it besides you?
If it's popular, you can make books
with handmade paper.
Really?
You said it would be hard
because of the price.
This is very popular these days.
If all goes smoothly,
it will be a bestseller!
You'll get a bonus and
herbal medicine if you do well.
This series will be broadcast today,
so be sure to listen.
Okay.
Goodbye.
My trust is in you!
Taewon Publishers here.
Yes, I gave it to MIN Hui-jae
as you requested.
Today Mr. Bookmark
sent a letter about his first kiss.
He asked us to read it
at the start of the program.
For most people, a first kiss
comes with the start of love.
But for me,
my first kiss was a farewell instead.
In a dreamlike bliss,
I watched over her sleeping
and then she woke up.
I confessed my love for her.
I told her it was love,
but she said it was foolish passion.
I told her it was forever,
but she said it was momentary.
Now seven years have passed.
I want to say this to her.
Even still, she is my only love.
Now I want to call her my wife
and be called her husband.
Oh my god!
Isn't this from the woman on
Producer Suh's program?
- Right?
- What?
- Is it a prank?
- It's real! Look.
Wait.
I feel thankful that
someone has kept love in his heart.
But I refused him long ago,
and have been living
without his memory.
I feel so sorry, my heart is sore.
However, now I want him to let me go.
Please give him this message.
- Hello.
- Yes, come in.
Do you have any yogurt?
Oh, we're all sold out today.
Thank you, come again.
Oh, hello!
I will give you everything
you need.
- Please go.
- Hui-jae!
I have nothing to say
to you. I'm sorry.
I didn't wait this long
to hear that answer.
Now you can forgive yourself.
You can. It's okay.
Are you listening?
Stealing glances at you
in the boat on the way to the camp,
do you know how happy I was?
But now, I want to look you
straight in the eye.
Not from steal a glance at side
I barely survived after three operations.
A lot was broken in me.
Thank you for surviving.
Why do you love me?
Because it is you.
You were engaged to another man,
and he died. Your parents died,
and you're two years
older than In-ha.
I didn't want to refuse you
for such reasons.
None of this was your making,
and it must have been painful.
It's not right to hurt someone again
for such reasons.
But I didn't like that
your heart was wounded.
A wounded person...
doesn't know how to give
and receive love,
or how to express thanks
with a pure heart...
So I refused.
I said this to In-ha,
and he sent me these.
Your designs.
He said, because you are
naturally so warm,
he was confident
he could bring you back.
Do you believe you can?
You don't answer quickly.
Good.
You aren't a person
to speak casually.
So I will trust you.
Thank you.
With such a strong-willed husband
you'll have twice the joy
and twice the trouble as others.
Remember that marriage is
the biggest promise of your life,
and if you have difficulties,
good times will also follow.
Hui-jae, have some breakfast.
What time did you go to bed?
Your eyes are red. I think
you should sleep more.
I can't. This is for
tomorrow's meeting.
What do you mean?
You read it 5 times yesterday.
In-ha!
If you read with those eyes,
you'll see only red print.
Sleep just two hours, okay?
Just two hours...
Not two hours and a minute,
just two hours.
- All right...
- Let's go!
Ahem...
The book to be read...
No, the man reading is SUH In-ha.
I'll start from page 45...
Barthes said mythology is a
...transmission... right?
Transmission system,
springing from a form of...
a semantic process,
which in the issue of Echo...
capturing... There are so many
Chinese characters here...
Hui-jae, you really understand all this?
Wow, you must be a genius.
Are you okay?
Come fight!
What is it, In-ha?
Are you hurt?
Did you fall and hurt yourself?
I'm just thankful.
What do you mean?
It's the first time.
Since we married, it's the first time
I heard you laugh.
Thank you.
It's very healthy.
When it starts to move,
it'll drive you crazy kicking.
It's amazing, huh?
Are you that happy?
Hui-jae...
In movies, they say something
impressive now.
What should I say?
Say congratulations.
- Congratulations
- Jung-ran!
In-ha will be so happy.
You know that the normal regimen
doesn't apply to you?
You need a check every week.
Don't work hard, sleep well
and eat good food.
All right.
Don't just laugh,
it's a miracle you're pregnant.
You need to care for your body.
You're not having lunch?
I'll eat with In-ha.
The other mothers will be waiting for you.
Mothers?
Okay, I'll yield to In-ha, then.
- Go ahead.
- Okay.
These are In-ha's baby clothes.
I thought I'd save them
for when In-ha had a child.
After 3 years, I thought
I couldn't give them.
Thank you.
You should be happy,
for the baby's sake.
Don't think of others,
only of your body,
only move as it is
comfortable for you.
Look, I wore this once.
- Does it suit me?
- Give it to me.
What a lucky baby!
Your grandmother sent clothes.
Be healthy.
Hui-jae, are you okay?
Why do you keep vomiting?
All pregnant women do.
When I vomit,
don't stand so close.
You don't want to ride
in the car, right?
But what can I do?
We can't leave it here.
What are you doing?
Tomorrow morning?
How do we get home?
I can't walk that far.
I can. Let's go.
- Oh, great!
- You're not cold?
Okay, good.
Here's the heart,
these are the hands,
and the legs.
It's all there.
Of course.
It feels things too.
It feels, but mothers
aren't aware of it.
- I can feel it.
- You can?
Sure, when I'm comfortable,
my baby is, too.
If my baby is uncomfortable,
I feel uneasy and tired.
Parents can't change their kids,
but kids change them.
What do you mean?
You've become much gentler.
More talkative, too.
Really?
- Jung-ran.
- What?
Is it possible to have a
Caesarian a bit early?
Of course.
If the mother's in bad health,
or if the baby...
- Why, is something wrong?
- No.
Oh, look at me.
I'm so happy about the pregnancy,
I wasn't thinking.
Get up. Let's go to internal medicine.
Don't worry.
I did it the last time I came.
What?
Everything's fine,
but the kidneys may be
pressed a bit,
so they said it'd be best
to deliver the baby at 8 months.
Sure, you be the doctor.
What's wrong?
Lucky you. You've got
a well-prepared mother.
At birth, your mother will have
your schoolbags ready.
That's not a bad idea.
I can just imagine it.
Bye.
- Go on it.
- Yes.
Dr. Choi.
Do you have so much time
in Internal Medicine?
Do you know the person
who just left now?
- She's my friend.
- Your friend?
What kind of friend?
Are you close?
No wonder you're single.
You can't tell she's married?
Keep your eyes off her,
she's even pregnant.
So I wanted to ask...
- is she having the baby?
- What?
Nice work, everyone.
Young producers these days,
they're too serious.
- Ah, yes...
- Eun-ha
- We should go out for soju sometime.
- Oh sure, goodbye.
Are you that opposed to it?
It's not that...
What can we do?
It's been decided above.
It's not like this program
isn't popular.
Do we really need to
broadcast this?
Well listeners like it,
and do you really think it's a lie?
I think it's genuine.
Cheer up, producer Suh.
For the past few years,
I've been so anxious about
not conceiving a baby.
I could have spent that
time in anticipation...
Now, amidst my joy,
I face a situation I never expected.
Thinking back now, I so regret
not enjoying the time I had.
In the time left to me,
so as not to feel regret,
I want to enjoy my life
as much as I can.
A letter from Ms. Paper Village.
Hui-jae!
You're not in bed yet?
I slept this afternoon.
You should lie down.
I read that at the beginning of
pregnancy, you sleep a lot.
I rested until early evening,
then I came out to hear your program.
- You listened to the program?
- Yeah.
Don't listen anymore.
Why not?
Just, it's late at night,
there are lots of depressing letters.
Listening when you're alone
isn't good.
It's not good for the baby, too.
It's because of that letter?
I didn't want to broadcast it, but...
Oh! I read that depression is
much more common at pregnancy.
You believe everything you read?
I'll get washed up,
then I'll massage your legs.
What would you do in her situation?
What?
Like that woman.
If I had stomach cancer,
with no time for treatment...
Hui-jae!
Just curious...
I want to know your opinion.
This is what I mean.
Don't think about that sort of thing.
I don't like that woman either.
Why not?
How can she do that?
Hiding it from her husband
as long as possible.
Later, with no options left to her,
her husband finds out?
She should think of others.
- I think I understand her...
- I don't.
She should give up the baby
and get treatment.
No man would give up his wife
for a baby he's never seen.
She'll only live a
couple months anyway.
Two months, one year, 10 years...
how can you tell?
Medicine is never 100% accurate.
She's not giving her husband
any chance.
Yes... I suppose.
But in my opinion,
I think she wants to live too.
If there were a way,
she would want to live.
Let's stop this.
Okay, let's stop.
- Who is it?
- It's me.
Just a minute.
One minute...
You're here early.
On your way to work?
My morning sickness is lasting
longer than the others...
I was just sick now, sorry.
What are you sorry for?
What's wrong, Jung-ran?
I'm sorry.
You're crazy.
You're bad.
You're really bad,
you always have been.
In-ha's sleeping.
I wasn't going to see you anymore.
Hui-jae's not my friend,
Like an incantation,
I repeated it all night.
In-ha went through
so much for you.
Hui-jae.
Let's do an abortion.
You may not know it,
but I've always liked In-ha.
If you just go like this,
I might snatch him away in anger.
I don't know?
You think I don't know?
We like the same ttokbokki stand,
the same singer, the same friends...
We're so similar...
How could I not know?
When I found out about this, I thought...
Knowing that you like him,
I should bring you two together.
In-ha... In-ha is yours.
You think I was the only one
who liked him?
But he picked only you.
You know that.
Hui-jae.
Let's live.
You're a doctor.
Between the baby and me,
we should choose
the one who will live.
As for In-ha...
Don't tell him about this.
Please...
You won't be able to fool him,
it won't be possible.
I don't want...
to cause him pain because of me.
It will be too hard for him.
Hui-jae!
Jung-ran stopped by.
Oh, you did?
So early?
She wanted to give me nutrients,
but I never stopped by
to pick them up.
Why, is something wrong?
Pregnant women should be careful.
She's too thin.
In-ha takes such good care of me.
Yes, but is there anything else
I can do for her?
How about taking a year off,
and going somewhere nice
- until the baby is born?
- Jung-ran!
That's a good idea,
but we should earn a lot to
bring up the baby well.
- It's late. I'll walk you to the car.
- Where are you going? I'll do it.
Don't worry. I won't steal your husband.
- In-ha, you use cologne?
- Yes.
I haven't put it on today.
Can you smell it?
If you use it a long time,
it becomes part of your scent.
But living with a person
who vomits a lot,
it might be better not to use it.
Hui-jae said she likes it.
I never used it before marriage.
Hui-jae is more sensitive now.
You should take great care
with everything.
I understand.
I feel secure having you around.
Thank you, Jung-ran.
His friendly voice is...
a great trength for the baby and me.
From long ago, he called
my name and soothed me.
The voice I waited for...
Today too, I lean on his voice
to ease my worries.
- Did you sleep well?
- Yeah.
- What is it?
- Nothing...
Hurry, aren't you late?
Yeah, I should go.
- Do you have the next letter ready?
- Yes, it's ready.
- Oh, how's your wife?
- Not bad.
Has she been to the hospital?
If you're so worried about her,
then visit the hospital.
She's already been.
Her best friend's an obstetrician,
she said everything's fine.
- I'm relieved.
- Yeah.
But do I look so worried?
You do.
You look so tired these days,
I feel tired too.
Go on in.
- Yeah
- The letter...
Yes, here it is.
- Ms. Paper Village...
- Good luck.
Hello? Oh, Mr. Park.
Yes, how are you?
Oh, nothing special.
I enjoyed the handmade paper book.
Yes, it was really nice.
Just a minute.
A letter from Ms. Paper Village.
Yes.
I love his scent.
He uses a cologne
which matches his bright gaze.
The cologne mixes together
with his own scent.
It smells its own scent.
But these days, the scent
is difficult for me to bear.
At first, I blamed my baby
For not liking the scent.
But I discovered it is not
because of my baby.
Hello? In-ha...
It is because of the cancer
in my stomach.
I wanted to remember
my husband's scent a bit longer,
Now, even worse than
the pain I feel each morning
is losing my husband's scent.
But she hasn't started
receiving patients!
It's okay.
I'm sorry, In-ha.
In-ha.
Pretend that you don't know.
Hui-jae wants it that way.
If my mother were alive,
do you know what she'd say?
What?
That you were caring for
a cracked chamberpot.
A cracked... what?
What's a chamberpot?
If it breaks, you will be in big trouble.
So you should always be careful.
Great caution.
You look happy, Hui-jae!
I am...
I have my husband, and my baby...
The breeze is nice...
Should I skip work
like this every day?
Sure! You think I'll refuse?
Let's do it, then.
I can leave from next week.
You were fired?
Sabbatical.
One guy from each department
gets a year off. With pay.
The radio station adopted it too.
Really?
Of course! Why would I lie?
Where shall we go?
Is there a place you want to visit?
We can really go?
It's paid vacation?
- You'll be cold.
- I'm okay.
I got a call from Park a while back.
They're having a paper exhibition,
so they'll be away, and they said
we could stay there.
- Oh, you're serious.
- Hui-jae.
- It's because I'm so happy.
- Are you that happy?
- I am.
- Kiss me.
Hello, this is JUNG Eun-ah
for Nighttime Music.
Today is a sad day
for the staff of this program.
So this will be the final night
with Producer Suh.
He will take some time off
for a while
So today will be the
last Nighttime Music
with Producer Suh
Hello, this is SUH In-ha.
I'd like to thank all the listeners
who have shared
their joys and sorrows
together with us.
I'm sorry.
In particular... the letters
by Ms. Paper Village...
have led us to think about
our lives and families.
With thanks and encouragement
I'd like to read her letter
in place of a goodbye.
The intervals between my bouts
of pain are shortening.
At first, this strange feeling was
frightening and painful.
But now, the tranquil gaps
between the pain
are more precious to me.
I am thankful to still have time
when I can laugh, gazing at him.
My precious body,
that feels the warmth coursing
from his fingers.
This long time, which
I thought would last forever,
was not enough to
express my love,
not enough to express my thanks,
and I want to say
that this lost time is
my heart's biggest regret.
White flag up!
Blue flag down, white flag up!
What's this?
Blue flag down, white flag down.
You try it.
Okay, white flag up.
Blue flag down.
Not that way, this way.
- What is it?
- Just a minute.
Okay, to the right.
- I'm curious!
- Okay, open your eyes.
One, two, three...!
Have a seat.
I hid this from you
in our luggage so we could have it.
And this too.
It's okay to have a little.
So that's why you were so busy.
Yeah.
Cheers!
Are you still scared of the water?
Why should I, when I have you?
It's chilly. Do you want to go in?
No, let's stay longer.
I'll do what I want,
like your mother told me.
I'm a good daughter-in-law.
You do that.
If you don't want to do
something, tell me.
I'll do it.
When the baby's born,
you change the diapers.
Okay.
You wash the baby, too.
Yeah.
You should mix the milk as well.
All right.
As for teaching numbers and letters,
I'm ill-tempered,
so I don't think I can do it.
I'll take care of it all.
I'll have a hard time
watching her get injections.
So you take the her
to the hospital for shots.
Yeah.
I said I'll take care of it.
Don't worry.
There's nothing for you
to worry about.
Hui-jae!
It's nothing.
It's the television. Stay there!
Okay, I see...
Is it a couple fighting on TV?
Hui-jae!
Hui-jae, are you okay?
Look at me, Hui-jae!
Hui-jae!
Hold on.
Hold on. Just a minute.
- Don't!
- It's okay, Hui-jae.
- No!
It's not bad for the baby.
It's morphine.
Jung-ran gave it to me.
Please Hui-jae...
Please, please...
Don't!
I'm O.K.
I'm sorry.
Why? What are you sorry for?
- When I go...
- Hui-jae!
At first, I was really angry.
Why me?
Why me now?
But come to think of it,
I was much happier than others.
This time together,
being loved by you, was enough.
But...
If I go...
what about you?
You can't find things
right in front of you.
Who will get you the nail clippers?
You always liked tumbling
in the thick blanket in winter,
don't use a thin blanket
when summer passes.
I wasn't a wife to care well for you,
but when I go, the empty room
will be so large.
Later, later,
much later,
when we meet again,
I'll compliment you.
Don't feel too stressed,
don't give up on anything.
Promise me, okay?
I promise.
Hui-jae, I love you.
I love you.
What you think about Jae-in?
Jae-in?
Jae-in means...
...pretty, smart, and sincere,
just like you.
Jae-in... SUH Jae-in.
Good.
Vital signals?
She's very unstable.
- What's her blood pressure?
- 90 over 50.
Hui-jae!
Hui-jae! Hang on a little longer.
First knife.
Scissors.
My dear Jae-in...
I hope you can express
your love openly.
To your father, in place of me.
Your mother could only say it once.
Jae-in, say I love you very often.
To the trees, to the sea,
to the sky, to your father.
- Is the baby okay?
- Yes, she's fine.
Hold this.
Suction. Hold it tight!
The placenta has passed,
let's do the uterine suture.
- Chromic one-zero.
- Do the suture now.
The cancer has spread.
Her blood pressure is falling.
Oxygen saturation is falling.
Oxygen level at 85%!
- Reverse I.V. And oxygen!
- Reverse I.V. Completed.
Damn, hurry with the CPR.
Hui-jae, please open your eyes.
Open them.
Hui-jae.
If you don't wake up,
you can't see Jae-in.
Please open your eyes.
Hui-jae.
In-ha... Our Jae-in is so pretty.
But what can I do?
I can't go home with her.
But I'm relieved you
don't have to go home alone.
Because I leave Jae-in beside you.
You can forgive me, right?
You've been so good to me,
and I was so happy.
I will carve all this in my soul
before going.
I love you, trees.
I love you, sea.
I love you, sky.
I love you, mom.
I love you, dad.
I love you very much too, Jae-in.