Over those years...
I wrote many novels on weird topics.
Everyone I met asked me.
"Did you get these ideas
from imagination? Or real experience?".
This is actually a silly question.
There are always happenings to people...
around you every day, and...
these can be concocted
into a strange story.
If you regularly drink with friends.
You can especially get out of them
good themes for an intriguing story.
Tonight, for instance,
I'm meeting two friends.
- Wesley.
- Mr Yi.
How are you, where's Yuan Chen?
He's over there.
What a pair of beautiful
glasses you have.
Mr Yi.
Congratulations on winning
the titles of Miss Asia.
Thank you.
- Cheers.
- Thanks.
Yuan Chen, you had a darling adventure
with Wesley some time ago, didn't you?
Tell us about it.
Mr Yi is a good storyteller.
Let him tell it.
Thus a good story begins
with good wine...
Hound calling Thunderbird...
Are all units ready?
I'm Thunderbird. Inside are six bandits.
One of them is a sharpshooter.
They all carry heavy weapons.
Tell everyone to be alert.
Hound, are you all right?
Hound, how are you? Hound.
- Cease fire, at once!
- Listen!
You gunned down a hostage!
He's having a serious heart attack.
Send a doctor before he dies!
The doctor's coming.
You've been surrounded.
You stand no chance of escape. Give up!
- What is it?
- Miss.
I'm a reporter of Western Daily.
Don't go in, it's dangerous.
Please keep away!
- Please, I only want to take one photo.
- No! I already said "No"!
What? Wonder Woman.
They won't let me in.
I'm Dr Yuan. Are you Captain Ho?
The hostage's inside.
He has heart attack.
Why have you chosen me?
We've long known your bravery.
We hope you could go in to plant a bomb.
to help us save the hostages.
I'm not too experienced.
- Inspector Chiang.
- Yes, sir!
Dr Yuan.
Let me play the nurse to follow you in
and I'll defuse it.
- Go and prepare everything!
- Yes.
The bomb's in a layer
of the first aid kit.
Well, okay?
Dr Yuan, remember it's 12 o'clock sharp.
We'll break in at this hour.
The doctor's here! Don't open fire!
Scatter!
Stop!
Bitch, stop!
I'm female too. Go now.
Get going!
Sonny, don't play any tricks!
- Where's the patient?
- Stand up!
Go...
Give me the stethoscope.
Calm down, I'm the doctor.
The heart-stimulant injection.
What are you doing?
Boss, a gun!
Bastard, how dare you?
Start!
Halt!
- Who are you?
- I'm a reporter.
Don't you know nearly ruined us?
Sorry!
Where's my camera?
I want to take a few photos!
What?
Thank you, Dr Yuan.
We're now in control.
- Good, I'll leave now.
- Good, retreat.
Are you going to arrest me?
I've never met a
more fanatic girl than you.
Don't you know
you could get a few years?
- Well...
- Go now!
Thank you!
- Dr Yuan, thank you!
- Don't mention it!
Captain Ho!
We must thank you for your bravery.
Aren't you that sexology writer...
- Dr Chu?
- Danny Wong?
They say you've recently
written an essay
on the climate's effect
on male sex potential.
This is merely a ratio in mathematics.
The temperature and time
constitute a ratio.
The length is one hour in tropical South.
Half an hour in the central part.
About 2-3 minutes
in the low-temperature North.
I remember you come from South Sea.
According to your inference
I should've come from North Pole.
Impossible!
Some beautiful girl over there.
Dr Chu, take the wine.
Leave her to me!
- Isn't it funny?
- Funny...
Don't you believe in stars?
I can readily see your star's Virgo.
Well, explain it.
- Anne, let's sit over here.
- A Virgo girl's best mate...
is a Taurus boy like me.
Your star must be Cancer.
I've many collections at home.
Including a human head
made by the New Guinea tribe.
It was shrunk to the size
of a monkey head.
So horrible!
And these are toes
chopped down by spacemen.
So nauseating! Anything else?
- And...
- Me! Adventurer Yuan Chen.
I have something important to tell you.
What are you up to?
Miss, don't be fooled by him.
Frankly, he's already married.
Don't talk nonsense!
I must go away for a while.
- Bye-bye!
- Anne...
- Stay for a little while.
- What on earth are you up to?
Sorry...
for the intrusion.
but I need you on something important.
- What is it?
- Okey.
I'd like to feature you in Western Daily.
to introduce your heroic deeds.
Let me take a naked photo of yours.
I assure you it will
have a sense of beauty.
My technique's not bad. Believe me.
- Sorry, it's no concern of mine.
- Idiot.
Idiot.
- Stop!
- I don't care for you.
Idiot, I thought I couldn't keep up.
You're cheap, dirty.
and despicable.
I'm sorry.
You really scared me!
How can you get in?
Where's your servant?
I gave her $1,000.
And said you let her have a day off.
Oh! I see!
You're great!
- Yuan Chen.
- Who are you?
Go with me to Thailand.
You must help yourself and Betsy.
What?
Your blood spell has reached one year.
You may soon have a relapse.
And she's got ghost spell.
We need your help.
What are you talking about?
Stop acting.
Here's my address in Thailand.
I'll wait for three days.
Don't go away!
What's your name?
I'm Heh Lung.
Listen, keep away from sex.
or you may have a quick relapse.
Who's that guy? I'm so scared!
That's all right, no problem.
Mr Wei,
you're my best friend and master.
Only you can help me.
Have you ever been
to the North of Thailand?
Su, bring us two cups of coffee, please.
Okay.
Apparently you've been under blood spell.
Tell me how it happened.
One year ago, I went with.
a medical team to North Thailand.
to get a kind of herbs for treating AIDS.
- Morning!
Professor, I'd like
to take a walk over there.
Be careful,
it's near the Yunnan miao tribe.
They say a kind of worm tribe
specializes in witchcraft.
I only believe in science.
Sorry for breaking your gem.
Never mind. Keep them.
- Are you serious?
- Yes!
I must leave.
Keep away from that girl.
Their tribe's cruel...
and knows witchcraft.
Professor, if they cast
a spell so easily.
They must nothing to do?
I'm the Captain,
it's my duty to protect you.
Sounds of the drum?
They come from the worm tribe
and signal offerings.
They're offering to God then.
Don't ever go and see it.
We won't...
What a big procession!
Go over!
It's her!
Who?
- The girl I was talking about!
- Who...?
I don't know.
Have you made up your mind?
I won't!
Probably you've been chosen for offering.
When Old Ancestor wakes up, you'll die.
You deliberately sent Heh Lung away.
and picked me.
I love only him.
I won't submit.
My people.
As in previous years,
when Old Ancestor wakes up.
Someone honored by God...
will be chosen.
Betsy is the daughter of the ex-Chief.
Please don't offer her to God.
This is the will of God.
But we've never tried.
Anyone else refusing to do it?
Send them to the grave.
I must go and help her.
You must be mad!
You may get killed!
I'll be flexible. Bring weapons.
- Don't...
- Don't go!
What now?
Run!
He's our Old Ancestor, he won't die.
Run! Leave me alone.
Help me...
Hurry up!
Run!
Intruders! Go and see.
Sounds of the drum again!
He's pursuing you for your intrusion!
Run!
Professor.
You brought the mess
because you're naughty.
Go back to the camp and pack up at once.
Run! Run quick!
Run, quickly!
Betsy! Betsy!
Run!
Get in!
You've blasphemed Old Ancestor.
I'll punish you on behalf of God.
Professor, you...
Yuan Chen, help me!
The worms are highly prolific.
But I won't use them against you.
I've let you down!
Run! Don't let them
get hold of you. Run!
You...
I'm now using my own charm to help you.
but...
When I woke up, Betsy had left.
And the bloodstains with me were gone.
So I left alone.
I'd been well in Hong Kong for one year.
But now...
Why didn't you take Heh Lung's advice?
I don't know him,
and didn't know what he wanted.
Right!
What are you...
What are you doing? Yuan Chen.
Su, bring the first aid kit.
The 2nd blood curse has burst.
When did the first burst occur?
More or less the same time.
It means one burst every 24 hours.
When it spreads to the heart, you'll die.
Mr Wei, you know witchcraft well.
Is there any chance of survival for me?
Blood curse is the most mysterious.
And complex of its kind in witchcraft.
Betsy used a spell to protect you.
But it worked for one year only.
That's why Heh Lung
wants you to go to Thailand.
You want me to go there then?
Yes, only the doer
can undo a damage done.
Okay, I'll see Heh Lung tomorrow morning.
Give me the scoop on this!
You again?
Cousin, do you know him well?
Mr Wei.
Tsai-hung is Mr Wei's spoiled cousin.
Please don't blame her.
You really are meddlesome.
I know him well.
Yuen Chen,
I don't want you to take my naked photo.
Let me go with you to Thailand. Okay?
I'm not going there for pleasure.
It's a serious affair. You can't go!
You mean I'm not qualified.
I went through everything with Dr Yuan!
Is it true?
I won't let you follow me.
I'll rush to help you
the day after tomorrow.
Call the Thai police if anything happens.
I'll get in touch with them.
Thank you.
Don't mention it!
Cousin, aren't you going to help me?
A reporter mustn't
go too far in coverage.
This is a matter of life and death.
You're only in for kicks. Stay out of it.
Mr Yuan Chen.
I'm here!
- Please follow me.
- You're...?
My boss told me to pick you up!
Your boss?
Mr Yuan, please sit down for a while.
Thank you!
- Idiot!
- You again!
I came on the earlier flight.
Why so many weapons here?
We're entering a primitive jungle!
It's unsafe without them.
This is the latest laser-guided gun.
Can you afford it?
My daddy's Tung Tai-ping.
Property magnate Tung Tai-ping?
I couldn't care less.
But he's given me...
a Gold Card for an unlimited sum.
Beautiful, ignorant, young, hell-bent...
And rich.
That makes you the most troublesome girl.
I always pay for info
out of my own pockets.
We're not going to war.
And these can't overcome witchcraft.
Let's get back to business.
I've already made
a promise to the editor.
And got in touch with the United Press.
If your info can be
front-paged in world newspapers...
I'll split the profit with you.
I'm in no mood for your frenzied ideas.
I don't care,
I'll go anyway.
Are you going to tie me up?
Let me go!
Don't ever underrate a man!
You've come at last.
You seem...
I was being pursued immediately returned.
Who did?
The sorcerer.
Knowing I'm here to see you.
He conspired with
the underworld against us.
So they're all of a kind.
I was assaulted immediately I returned.
Let's leave at once!
- Is this the worm tribe?
- No,
a good tribe working as farmers.
But they're often
attacked by the worm tribe.
Lung, it's nice to see you back.
Chief, what happened?
An eerie affair occurred here.
All the children here
disappeared this afternoon.
- Disappeared?
- Yes.
What happened?
Our children have
mysteriously disappeared.
The sorcerer must've abducted them.
For casting "Little Ghost spell"?
Yes! It's made of 100 children's blood.
They can fly, suck blood and kill.
The spell has to be
remade after three years.
How cruel he is!
Right, I saw that
little ghost that night.
The Chief wants me to bring men.
- to save them.
- Good!
I'm going too.
What a quiet night!
Right!
Not even chirps! Something wrong!
Watch out!
Run quickly...
Don't run!
Don't run! Come back at once!
It hurts!
I warned you against following us!
I've already followed you all the way!
Don't you know it's booby-trapped here?
Don't worry! When I studied in U.S.A...
I read many books
on the Vietcong tactics.
This shows I can take care of myself.
No more nonsense!
We must work against time.
Let me go up and see. Hush!
Tsai-hung, Where are you going?
To take photos.
I'm now responsible for your safety.
It's dangerous, don't run wild.
I don't care! What a male chauvinist!
Tsai-hung, please take my advice.
It really is dangerous.
I've experienced it.
Things are sometimes beyond your control.
Let go!
I warn you, if you touch me again.
I'll tell my cousin that you molested me.
though with your reputation.
few people will believe that.
I don't care.
Take my advice.
Or I'll spank you without pants.
How dare you?
You're dirty!
So what?
I don't care.
I'll leave and won't return.
Okay, it's up to you.
I won't return.
even if I were bitten by snakes.
hit by arrows or...
I won't care for you anymore.
Don't regret.
You really have the nerve!
Bye-bye!
So she's away in a twinkle.
The children are all caged and guarded.
We'd better go and save Betsy.
Okay!
Where's Miss Tsai-hung?
She left in a fit of temper.
Never mind her. Where's Betsy?
Betsy!
Heh Lung.
I've brought Dr Yuan too.
I'm here.
Betsy!
Keep away.
Don't let anyone
see me in my present state.
Forget it! Her looks scared me!
Betsy,
my 4th blood curse has burst.
Something must be done
to save you and me.
My dad told me before his death.
Some holy ashes can break
all kinds of spell.
I consulted the records of the tribe.
And have found their hiding place.
Where?
A large Buddha in a cave.
It's out of reach.
And no one can climb up for it.
So they're unobtainable.
I believe you're my saviour from Heaven.
So I've told Heh Lung to find you.
Try.
You must, you only have
three days to live.
I go to inform them
to bring all the equipment.
Besides, the ashes
will wither in six hours.
You must fight for time.
Help! What are you doing? Let me down!
I'll pay you! Let me go!
Let me go!
Let her go!
You must be his boss!
You're really nice.
Excuse me. Bye-bye!
I lost my way and fell into the trap.
Did Heh Lung bring you here?
No, I'm here to collect specimens.
You look brave,
let me take a photo of you.
Go to hell!
Okay, I know.
Men and equipment are coming soon.
Tsai-hung haven't come back yet.
Why don't see her so late?
Where's she going?
She may either be dead or captured.
Where could she be, if captured?
A foreigner like her...
would be taken to the sorcerer.
Rescue Betsy first!
Rescue Tsai-hung!
A good friend.
Miss Tsai-hung.
Well, is Tsai-hung all right?
Her temperature's a bit abnormal.
Let me go and see
if any men have arrived.
Tsai-hung.
What is it?
She goes berserk and is herculean.
Tsai-hung... how do you feel?
Get hold of her.
What bas become of her?
She had been captured by the Chief.
And was in such a state
when we brought her back.
I think she must be under "black" spell.
She kills anyone at sight.
How can we break the spell for her?
Let me!
Betsy?
Black is needed to break a black spell.
Mix the blood...
of black sheep, oxen...
dogs, cats, snakes, eagles and lizards.
Boil it and bathe her with it.
Immerse her till she wakes up.
Ghost!
What happened...?
She was scared by my sight.
It's all right...
That sorcerer brought her this.
She saved your life.
She's all right now.
Time's running out.
Go and get the ashes.
Heh Lung.
Come back by every means.
I'll go with you.
Tsai-hung, don't be naughty.
You must return by all means.
What happened?
Mr Wei, my 6th blood curse has burst.
But there was not much bleeding.
When your 7th blood curse bursts.
All your blood will spill out.
Mr Wei, tomorrow's
my last day in the world.
Yuan Chen,
I don't believe in fate.
I think man conquers Heaven.
Heh Lung.
What's the name of that sorcerer?
Sorcerer Aquala.
Aquala? The witchcraft of this clan is...
the most mysterious
and cruel in the South.
Did he practice Little Ghost spell?
Yes.
Get a pregnant cow at once.
Slaughter it and get her placenta out.
Also, kill a black dog and get its blood.
Okay.
Why, Mr Wei?
To break the Little Ghost spell.
A friend of the Aquala clan
taught me that.
I'm not sure if it will work.
Yuan Chen, it's all up to you.
Old Ancestor...! Give me strength.
Use blood strength
to turn into blood ghosts.
Kill Yuan Chen first.
Where are those two grains of ashes?
Inside the eyes.
We must climb up slowly. Okay with you?
I've even climbed the Himalayas.
They say no one
trying it has ever come out.
It all depends on us!
Watch out!
Be careful!
Yuan Chen.
Masters.
We try to get them to help someone only.
Please do us a favor, masters.
Run, quick!
Duck it!
Yuan Chen...
Swallow it now to break the blood spell.
Swallow it at once!
We must rush back in two hours.
Or the other grain
will become ineffective.
Go and rescue Tsai-hung and Betsy.
I'll join you later. Go now.
Old Ancestor must be delighted today.
To have three man
and three girls for food.
God will punish you.
Yuan Chen will come to kill you!
I'm waiting for them.
We're already here.
I said he would come.
Old Ancestor!
Aquala, you did many atrocities.
I'll make you pay for them now.
Old Ancestor!
Let's go!
Watch out!
Tsai-hung.
Heh Lung!
Let loose the little ghosts.
Where's that grain?
Over here!
Bad, already outdated.
Betsy can't restore
her original looks then?
Would you love me
if I look like this all my life?
Our tribes can lead a new life now
with the sorcerer's death.
I can help them live better.
Isn't that a pity?
Beauty lies in one's heart,
not in one's face.