I'm not available at the moment.
Please leave a message.
I'll get back to you as soon as possible.
Have you called the police yet?
It's not my fault.
Have you called the police?
It's not my fault...
Have you?
It's not my fault.
I have.
He rushed the traffic lights.
Hold on, bro.
The ambulance's coming.
Help!
How're you, bro?
Cell phone...
Here you are.
Battery?
I'll fix it for you.
What's the number? I'll dial it for you.
Kirk... What's wrong?
The driver of 1314 has an accident!
What should we do?
Where's Elvis? I don't know.
Call him now!
Man, I was so worry about you.
Where're you?
Man...
Man? Hello...
Who are you looking for, ma'am?
Man Liang.
What's your relationship to him?
Fiancée.
Wait a minute.
Is that her?
He had brain bleeding.
We tried our best but can't make it.
No... no.
I think you've made a mistake.
He just gave me a call.
I think you really must've made a mistake.
Sorry.
No... This can't be... it cannot be him.
He just called me.
It must be you guys who made a mistake...
Please check it again, will you?
Ma'am, please stay calm.
C'mon.
I'm calm. But you've made a mistake.
That guy is not him!
Why are you here, Hale?
How is it?
It's alright.
Let's go there.
Here.
Doctor... Who are you looking for?
The driver of 1314... we're friends.
No... impossible...
He's just given me a call.
Ma'am it's the destination.
Isn't the North Street your destination?
How do you know that?
I usually give you a ride.
You're so "ugly". Who would forget you?
I wanna listen to this song.
Can I get off later?
Sure.
I can give you the CD,
OK? Great.
Maybe it's not such a goof idea.
You can listen to the song whenever
you catch my ride anyway.
What's the matter?
You ran away from home?
It's dangerous for a girl
to wander around so late.
Tell me your address. I'll take you home.
Isn't it... more dangerous?
Though I look like a playboy,
I'm a good bloke.
Look at my face...
Wait a minute. I pick up my boss home.
Hello.
You're off? Yes.
Thanks.
What's wrong?
Wanna eat something?
Let's go.
Do you like kids? You may play with him.
Whose baby is this?
Stupid question.
This smart baby must be my son.
Spacious!
Definitely.
You wouldn't believe this...
An old lady who usually catch my ride.
She walks like my mum,
so I helped her to get on and off.
Later we became friends.
When she knew I wanna rent a flat,
she showed me this.
Guess the rent.
How much?
Just three thousand something.
So nice guys always get rewards.
It's near the stop.
It takes less time for you to travel.
But it costs a lot.
Money is not a problem,
as long as this is a nice place.
Where should we put our sofa?
This kind of difficult design work...
it's better to leave it for your decision.
Sofa in beige colour
and wall sky blue.
Colourful curtain. Like a rainbow.
It makes you happy when you look at it.
You own my minibus.
You keep my passbook.
After getting married,
you can't return them to me.
When will you tell your dad?
I don't want to get into a scrap with him.
What?
Well... I’ll invite him to come
for a dinner later.
It's me who tell him
about our wedding, OK?
Talk about this later.
Or let's try... the new room.
There's not even a bed.
No problem. I've never tried new poses.
Laurie. Time to go to school. Get changed.
I'll take you to a restaurant for breakfast.
Get changed.
I'll take you to restaurant
for breakfast, okay?
Laurie, remember... work hard.
Put the books into the bag.
Listen to the teacher, OK?
You can't be late for school, Laurie.
Get changed.
Where's your bag?
I've told you... don't put the bag
in the wrong place.
Where're your slippers?
Wash up. Be quick!
Ma'am, your money.
Have hair cut or washed, ma'am?
It's moved?
It's the next shop.
Hello. Miss Lam.
Please sit.
I give you a bag, Miss Lam.
Thanks.
Hello?
It's mum.
I've told your dad that
You and Man will come back
for a dinner tonight.
Do come back.
He's only long-winded.
Hello... are you listening to me?
Man's dead.
What?
He died in a traffic accident.
Holly...
How are you? Are you OK?
Come on.
Don't stay in the street. Go back.
Jesus...
I can't cry.
It's exgratia payment.
Thank you.
I gotta work. Take care.
I was just on the scene.
It was me who called you that night.
I hung up as I saw you
come to the hospital.
It's me.
What's your name?
Laurie.
Sir?
Just call me Hale. I go now.
Thanks Welcome.
Laurie.
What's that?
Laurie the good boy,
let's put it into the niche together.
Don't open it.
It's daddy.
Yeah, he's dead.
Dead?
What is 'dead'?
It's... going on a trip.
Are they all going on a trip?
Why don't they take us with them?
Don't ask this kind of question.
Holly, I don't think it's good for you
to take care of Laurie...
It's alright, dad. Please take care of mum.
You also take care of yourself, Holly.
Mum, don't worry. I'm fine.
Come in.
Come here, Laurie.
It's pretty good.
Honey, come have a look.
Grandma.
Good boy...
Your dad and sis come see you.
We've worked together
for a long time, Peter.
It's not about the problem of trust.
Ye know... there're a lot of deceivers.
If you aren't firm,
don't get me into the troubles.
Bankruptcy is possible!
Laurie's a good boy.
Congratulations.
When did you become a grandma?
OK. That's it.
What's up?
Tell Helen: Don't send him the cheque.
Your friend's not reliable.
What are you going to do now?
Go back to your room, Laurie.
I'm talking to you!
Fine.
What?
I mean what will you do?
Calm down.
Are you gonna raise that kid?
Yeah.
You've made up your mind.
No need to care about you, right?
Any problem?
We may go then.
Stay calm. Let's discuss this issue.
Sit down...
There's no need to discuss any more.
Let's go, dad.
Sharon...
Holly, how can you go on like this?
Anything to be discussed? She's great.
No need to worry.
Or talk about Laurie's issue with his mum.
Ask her to take care of him.
Let's go. She doesn't want us to interfere.
I'll wait for you downstairs.
Wait a minute...
Honey...
Keys, mum.
Don't be like this.
I'll make some soup
or do the cleaning for you.
Keys.
NO WAY!
I got it repaired, Hale. Have a look.
The mirrors and walkie talkie
have been removed.
The worn tyres are also replaced.
You're truly a vampire.
This minibus's useless.
Excuse me. Who's Charles?
Yeah.
Miss Lam? Charles
I want to get this minibus repaired.
How much is it?
Get it repaired?
It's better to replace it.
Maybe the engine still works.
But this minibus isn't lucky.
Don't bullshit.
Go to work...
Charles
Can you make it the same as before?
Well... miscellaneous included...
a hundred and ten thousand or more.
So expensive?
No.
Isn't there insurance?
Yeah...
But you have to pay
thirty thousand something first.
And thirty thousand something
for loading next year.
Maybe no insurance company
will accept the application.
It doesn't make sense.
Charles, how about eighty thousand?
Eighty thousand? No way.
Eighty thousand. No more bargain.
No way.
Well I'll call a tow company to tow it away.
Alright...
This time it's me who bear the cost.
I'll give it a try
Thanks and I want it to look
just the same as before.
Master! Please adjust the clutch pedal
to a higher position.
I have to fully step on it
to shift the gear. Too slow.
You car-racing?
Let me have a check first.
Hurry up. Gotta work.
OK. It's alright.
What's the matter?
Forget to bring the tea leaves.
You go to restaurant first
and I'll take the tea leaves.
I got it repaired. It's like brand new.
Thanks, Charles.
Thank you.
Lease it out?
No, I'll drive it on my own.
Well...
You are in the gear...
And fasten the seatbelt.
Which horse should we bet on?
Have a drink.
Thanks.
Welcome.
Who's this?
A woman.
Stop!
Hale, you're in "good luck".
Loudmouth.
Sorry. I didn't hit it on purpose.
I know. It doesn't matter.
That night... thanks.
It was a petty matter.
You're looking for somebody?
Yeah, I want to see Elvis.
Elvis, can you do me a favour?
Sit down.
What's the matter?
I want a place for the route
from this terminus.
Are you kidding?
I have a minibus driving license.
But you've never driven minibus.
I can manage.
I know...
But somebody has taken Man's place.
Just an extra vehicle.
If I had say, I wouldn't be
the terminal co-ordinator.
Well I'll talk about this with the boss.
But you have to pay for the place. It's a rule.
Man's paid for it.
But the sum is by head count not vehicle.
It's around a hundred thousand something.
But I don't have so much money.
You can be a freelancer.
You can run any routes.
See it as paid training sessions.
Thanks.
Welcome.
You go?
I reverse to make way for you.
Go away or she might hit you.
What?
Two inches left...
Tell all the bros:
Stay away from this woman.
Look. What's she doing?
Ma'am, you stole the minibus?
Got a driving license?
Need some guidance?
Come with me and I'll teach you how?
Come have a chat. C'mon.
Wait!
Have a chat!
Laurie, c'mon.
Eat them all. Don't waste them.
Enough? I give you more.
You're hurt?
Wear daddy's gloves.
Good boy. Now finish it.
Laurie, work hard.
And aunt will earn more money
and buy you more toys, OK?
I'm late.
Bitch. How come you overtake
in this way!
Ma'am, the sign's wrong.
Thanks.
Christ, late again!
Can you hurry up a little bit? I'm in a rush.
Look. The tram's faster than you.
Yeah, Please hurry up.
Got it.
How do you drive?
Sorry...
I don't have any change.
It doesn't matter.
Clearway! What?
Get off!
What's the matter, sir?
No stopping.
No stopping?
Clearway!
Here's a clearway?
7 a.m. to 12 a.m.!
Driving license.
Give me a chance, sir.
Driving license!
Still here? Forty-five minutes passed.
Poor.
Five hundred. Fuel, miscellaneous...
and a ticket.
Three hundred and twenty... My God.
Bastard! That bloke in suit...
What's the matter?
What're you doing, Laurie?
You break the pipe.
Get up. Quick.
Laurie, go to bed on your own.
Be a good boy.
I'm not available at the moment.
Please leave a message.
I'll get back to you as soon as possible.
Daddy, I'm going to bed.
When'll you be back?
I miss you so much.
And aunt's driving is really poor.
She drives very slowly.
Goodnight, daddy.
You look familiar, ma'am.
You used to run taxi service?
I seldom see such a young girl
running minibus service.
You like driving?
I want to hire a driver.
Want to work with me?
That's enough. Sit down.
So annoying!
I really want to hire a driver.
Be my driver...
Leave me alone!
Get off now!
This is too much!
You throw up on my bus?
Why are you so fierce?
Go!
Cross the harbour? Get on the bus.
Cross the harbour? Yeah.
Get on.
Hey...
You can't load passengers here!
I'm going now...
Sorry.
Please catch the next ride back.
Next ride back. Sorry.
Are you crazy?
If you'd been a man, I'd have hit you.
Go away!
Go!
I'm not available at the moment.
Please leave a message.
I'll get back to you as soon as possible.
Man...
I miss you.
Can you hear me?
Laurie...
Good boy. Help dad clean the vehicle.
Look at your grubby hands.
Give me your hands.
You'd said it's easy to run minibus service?
The passengers scolded me...
The cops gave me a ticket...
those gangs kicked me out...
And I received a fake note.
Why can't I take the passengers
at the terminal?
Tell me... what to do.
Well... Goodbye.
It's only the first day. Not used to it yet
I can manage.
It won't be late.
Wait for me at the terminal.
Take a rest. Tomorrow's another day.
I can manage.
That woman is really unbearable.
She has no ideas
about the signs and signals.
The taxi driver behind
blew horn to rush her.
She's nearly got lost.
She's so skinny and
still worked for two shifts.
She did?
Sure
Big Fool saw her last night.
Even us feel exhausted
after driving twelve hours.
How can she stand a job like this?
That's the point.
Do me a favour. Help her.
Crazy.
His fiancée’s died just recently.
Women need comfort.
Don't say this, OK!
Her boyfriend's just died.
She needs to pay the minibus mortgage
and raise Man's son.
Isn't she the mother of the child?
No. Man was divorced.
This lady's pretty good.
Sorry. May I ask you a question?
You were on the scene
of Man's accident, right?
Did he tell you anything?
Not a word?
He seemed to tell me...
He said, "tell her to be stronger.
Don't be too sad."
Maybe he wanted me to tell you these.
Then he asked me
to pick up the cell phone.
He might want to call you.
But he didn't make it.
How was he at that time?
Was he very painful?
It was just a short while.
I don't think he suffered much.
Thanks.
Not at all.
Excuse me. Please make way for me.
I need to drive the vehicle away.
There's enough room.
I'll help you.
Thanks.
These roads are narrow. Give it back later.
Why do you start with second gear?
It's too slow to use bottom gear for start.
We normally use it on the slope...
or for our own vehicle.
Bottom gear start reduces
the vehicle depreciation.
If you're on the same row with an 'enemy',
waiting for the green light
to hunt for the passenger,
you have to use second gear.
Hunt for passengers...
No hunt, no passengers, right?
That's true.
Remember: Wait for the amber light
but do rush when it's alight.
And don't brake hard.
Otherwise, the passengers get hurt easily.
And this makes the vehicle behind
brake hard too
or it may crash your vehicle.
Running minibus service isn't as easy
as I think.
Have you learnt how to run the service?
I... caught Man's ride before.
Well...
I show you once. Be careful.
As a beginner, you must learn the signs,
recognise the routes and
remember the clearways and loading zones.
This sign, no loading during
the periods of 8 a.m. to 10 a.m...
So many restrictions.
But rules and practice
are different.
Do remember this sign.
No stopping at any time.
No loading at any time in this zone.
Turn to another street
for loading and unloading.
But those old passengers
should know this.
Be hawk-eyed.
Unload passengers if needed.
No loading, then accelerate.
The faster the ride, the more the rides.
The more the rides, the more the earnings.
Watch out!
It's always for the giant to bully the tiny.
No need to fear those taxi drivers.
Just drive close to them.
Scare them and they must make way
for you.
Just give them a scare
but don't really crash into them.
Otherwise, you're wasting time.
Look...
Crazy!
That idiot calls a minibus in the red routes.
If you wanna load this passenger,
look the mirrors first
to make sure there're no cops.
No cops. It's safe.
Then go for it.
Hurry up, it's red route.
Take a seat...
Look out!
Are you OK?
Get off in the next mouth.
Please alight beyond the clearway.
Loading only in the clearway.
It ensures an earning.
Unloading may bring you a ticket.
Too risky.
Who pities you?
A passenger.
Hey... you've missed that!
Sorry. Only a bit farther.
Forget about the horn and
complaints.
Why do you run your service like this?
Passengers will understand
your difficulties.
They won't make any troubles for you.
Anyone get off ahead? Gotta paid first.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Any one get off before the red route?
No stopping there
And if there are cops stopping you,
pretend you're not seeing them.
Gamble on fleeing the chase.
If not, beg for a chance.
It's easy for a woman to make it.
Soft tone and sweet smile.
You'll surely make it.
But I failed every time.
Weep then.
Weeping is the best weapon of women.
The cops let you go if they pity you.
Thanks.
Your profit is three times more than mine.
I'm lucky this time.
I broke the record when
I started to run minibus service.
No passenger for whole-day rides.
Hello? Yeah.
I'll come over now.
My son has a fever.
I must pick him up now.
Then your turn.
No, you're faster. It's near the terminus.
OK. Thanks.
Are you OK, Laurie?
Why are you so late?
Take him to see the doctor.
Sorry.
Aunt.
Come here!
I gotta work.
I got something to tell you!
Can you take care of him for a moment?
Just tell me what you want...
once and for all.
I don't want you drop in so suddenly.
Are you crazy?
You really run a minibus service?
Can you stop it?
How can you go on like this?
Man's gone and the story's over.
You still keep his son?
That's enough. Don't say this, OK!
If Man had been alive,
we would've got married
and Laurie would've been my son.
I'll do my best. I'm not that kind
of person like you.
You can't live off on your own.
How can you keep the kid?
So what?
Leave him or
send him to an orphanage?
How about his relatives?
His grandparents only live off
social security. Besides, his grandma's sick.
How about his mum? Where's she?
To be pragmatic, Holly.
You're an adult.
Don't play this kind of romantic game!
Look at you.
You look pallid!
None of your business.
I don't bring any troubles for you, right?
Just as I don't think in the same way
like you do.
I don't need any luxury cars
nor clothing.
I'm still happy.
Is money the only thing on your mind?
Don't talk about me!
I earn money not just for myself.
Who supports dad after he retired?
You spend on the monthly instalment,
rent and the kid.
Have you given a buck to the family?
You think of the kid.
Why don't you think of your parents?
You're selfish!
I tell you, don't ask mum for money.
That means she can only
give you the money?
I take the money for investment,
not spend it.
What 'spend it'?
What're you looking at?
She's so fierce.
You know it?
Yeah.
Then am I fierce?
Yes or no...
He really has a fever.
Need to visit the doctor now!
Who's he?
If you go on like this,
both the kid and you will die.
What's the matter?
OK. Just park it aside.
Alright.
Let me carry him.
It's alright. He's heavy. Let me carry him.
Thanks.
Good boy...
Good boy, take some medicine...
Listen to me, good boy...
Don't move or it spills out.
Meal's ready, Laurie."
Come.
Eat the soup. Thanks.
It's hot. Be careful.
Salty and sweet... is it OK?
How's the soup? Seems a bit salty.
No, it tastes good.
Your clothes got dirty.
Is that... I help you.
No, I can do it myself.
Eat it.
Go to bed yourself after dinner, okay?
Your sink pipe got blocked.
Yeah. I've cleared it many times
but still can't fix it.
Buy a drain cleaner.
What? Drink cleaner?
No, D.R.I.A.N. Drain cleaner.
I can help you clear it when I'm available.
Thank you.
I take you to the terminal.
No.
I live in the place nearby.
Take care of the child.
He goes to bed on his own. It's OK.
You leave him alone at home?
What's wrong?
Oh... I forget to make him some milk.
You may go first if you are in a hurry.
He isn't a baby any more.
Still use baby milk bottle?
Yeah, it's his late night refreshment.
I think...
it's difficult... for you to go on like this.
I know you have sentiment on the minibus.
But if you lease it out,
you can put more effort on Laurie.
No, I'm not familiar with any drivers.
What if they crash the vehicle
or go away with it?
Frankly speaking,
do you know how to calculate?
I guess you repay the mortgage
of the vehicle.
Even if it's your own vehicle.
Renting it out is a must.
Two shifts a day. A thousand.
Rent, fuel and tickets...
How much can you earn?
And also the license fee, insurance,
maintenance...
Brake system replacement
at 3-month interval
and tyres 4-month.
Everything needs money.
If you don't do the calculations,
how can you make a profit?
And also the tickets.
If you got more points incurred,
you're disqualified.
You can't count on running
a minibus service then.
With money, you can pay the rent,
tuition and food.
Your sis may be right.
Why are you all the same?
Why do you all...
do calculations on everything?
I believe I can manage.
I don't need your help.
Sorry,
I'm loudmouth.
I'm leaving now. Bye.
Boss, prosperous business?
See. Buy two more fishes.
You really sell the biz to me?
Yeah, I've told you.
So, you do? Keep your promise.
I do. No reason to deceive you, right?
It's more comfortable here.
It was like in the jail just now.
C'mon.