I know
Out of battery
Hello
Great, I'm about to get to see my dad
Cut the crap it, let's go, come
They're bringing Tony back
The phone got cut off half way
I'm afraid that Chiu will try something
stupid
I think he will play tricks
What are you doing? Let go of me
Uncle Cheuk
Go to hell
Uncle Cheuk, help me
Tony
Wait for me
I'm in a hurry
Stupid
Help
Catch it
Tony, are you Okay?
I'm fine Come
We have received news from
the airport
The escaped criminals have taken
the kid away
Stop them, I want them here
Tell the snipers to get ready
Yes, sir
What?
They turned me on light and alarm
what for?
He wants to get my attention
Kun, watch the back door
Headquarters, the suspects are on the
move
What should we do?
Stop them
Alpha, take action
Copy
Don't come here
Why don't you believe me?
I didn't want to hurt anyone
I only want to have my son back
Why?
Uncle Cheuk, take the boat
It'll be faster this away
Uncle Cheuk, are you hungry?
Yes, a little
I have some peanuts in my pocket
I wanted to eat it until we get on
the airplane, eat it
Okay
Thanks
Be careful
Are you okay?
No problem
Sit down Thanks
Go
Be careful
Sorry
Uncle Cheuk, help me
Help me
Who is fighting?
No, no one is fighting
Uncle, over here
Are you okay?
Damn you
Welcome
Mr. Brian Cheuk, I'm from Organized
Crime Bureau
What?
Something happened at school
We need you to come with us to give
us a report
School? What happened?
I don't know the details
I only know that there was an explosion
Where is my dad? How is my dad?
Little friend, don't worry, your dad is
fine
Mr. Cheuk, we are just doing our job
I came here to take you back to the
headquarters
I can tell you the details later
Let's go
Wait, it's better for Tony to stay with
me
Feel free, this is way please
Mr. Cheuk, over here
Here
Help me check on these files, it's urgent
Got it
Come in
Officer Leung
Mr. Cheuk, please sit down
Officer Leung, that lady just said
There was an explosion at the school
How many people are hurt?
The place is in a mess
Our colleagues have brought your
friend back to help us
He is in the next door giving us a report
I heard that your Chief Hui Chi-on is
at the scene too
Yes, he is a good boss
Tony, didn't you say that you want to go
to the bathroom
Yes, I want to go to the bathroom
Uncle, take me with you
Officer Leung, where is the bathroom?
Outside
Thanks
Uncle, be careful
Now you know how to sing "Pain"
don't you?
Is the chief of Hong Kong police force
Hui Chi-on? Stupid
You are not as foolish as
I thought
the reunification of HK with China has
been over
And you still have the Queen's picture
on the wall?
Isn't this the office of the Organized
Crime Bureau
How come all the documents are blank?
Also, people should be busy here
But the phone didn't even ring once
This is ridiculous
You really think that we didn't notice it?
We have so many men here
You think that you can beat us?
Don't worry, let me help you
How many can you fix?
How about you?
7, the rest of them will go to you
That's not fair
This world is not fair
Kid, shut up
Shut up and fight
I have seen it, let me see it
Why are you chasing after me?
You look ugly
Ghost?
Come
Go after him, Freeze
I know
Why are you still here?
Come back
What are you doing?
You guys get on the boat first, I'll go
start this boat
Hurry
Any trouble?
None of my business
Wait
Hurry, come over here
What are you scare of?
Come down
Please, you can't do this
I need to borrow your car
Okay, take it
Thanks
Let me drive
What? This is of no reporting value
If I rape you, will it be a great news?
Hurry up
Get in
Take the back seat
Don't move
Sir, I just want to take my son home
Let me take him home
he is my only son
Please
I have a son too
Even if you are not going to let me take
him back
At least le me see him
I only want to know if he is okay or not
Please, I beg you
Do you know that you almost lost your
life?
Who is your son? Which class is he in?
He... he is in second grade, room A
Cheung, turn off the ray of B zone
Crawl in slowly
Don't move
She only wants to see her son
She will leave soon
Take her there
Let's go Thanks
You are not keeping your promise
7 o'clock
I'll blow this place up after seven
The kidnap at the primary school is not
settled yet
5 minutes ago, an unknown person
sneaked into the school
and started a gun war with the criminals
Right now there is no injury report
The criminal claims that if he can't see
his son before 7
he will detonate all the bombs
Asshole, it must be done by Chiu
You'll get tired
I thought that you are an ironman
I can't take this anymore
If little Pun was not at the scene
I could never have held on this long
Sorry for all the troubles
Don't be silly, this is not your fault
Are you guys going to arrest my father?
Tony, don't worry, if no one gets hurt
your dad will be fine
Don't worry
Don't lie to me, I understand it
Good boy
Well, Tony is such a good boy
when you report this incident
I hope you'll be fair
Maybe the judge will go easy on his dad
I want to make it good too
but you must know one thing
My boss loves to make things up
Sometimes the press must be blamed
Just to make a little more money
They will make lots of shit up
What good will it do?
I am only a little worker, I have no say
You are only a little worker
but why do you have to work this hard?
Just joking, you don't have to be this
mean
Come on, I'll drive
Don't touch my steering wheel
I've told you, what a bad luck
They are here
Stop the car
Right...
Left...
Do you know how to drive?
None of your business
Right
No, left...
Go to the right, just listen to me
Left or right?
Left or right? Damn it
Your mouth stinks
Take care
Shut up, stupid
Go left, hurry
Tony, come
Come and help
Can't get out
So?
Help me
Are you okay?
I'm alive
Take it easy
Run, it is going to explode anytime
It's almost 6, can we make it?
Just three more blocks, we are almost
there
I want a rest
Uncle, you are bleeding, are you okay?
We will not make it if we don't go now
Take the short cut
We only had a little fun on the boat
Now we can really have a fight here
Martial artists use their fists and kicks to
prove themselves
Before you punch, you should really
think about it first, what is it for?
I want to defeat all my opponents
Wrong
You want to help those who didn't
receive fair treats
To tell you the truth, I'm doing this for
money
If I defeat you, I'll get $500,000
Can you make it?
Tony, go there yourself
I'll be there soon
Uncle, you are bleeding
If you don't go now
more people will bleed, hurry up
This is what you have?
I'm... in... a... hurry
Tony...
Are you okay?
Yes, but I'm tired
Come on
Excuse me
You can't go in
This place has been sealed off
This is Mr. Chiu Chung-tin
He is the father of the child who
the criminal requests for
I want to talk to your head
stop washing my time
If anything happens
you will be responsible?
Wait, I'll get my superior
I'm in charge of here
A nutcase turned this place upside
down
My son has been captured by a fellow
of the nutcase
What is wrong with you police?
Have you reported it to the police?
I'm doing it now
Mr. Chiu, many violent incidents
happened on their way from the airport
to the school
I hope this has nothing to do with you
If you have anything to do with this
no matter how rich you are
we will carry out justice
Of course this has nothing to do with
Mr. Chiu, watch your mouth
Shut up
Please follow me
Charles, will that fool bribe the cops?
No
This case is widely watched, no one can
hide anything
Hello
Charles, why are you doing this?
Surrender now
Even if you get Tony back
Can you get away?
Okay, even if you can escape,
you must live in fugitive
Can you stand having Tony going all
over the place with you, he'll never have
a chance to go to school
You forced me into this
I've discussed it with Chiu already
If you surrender
we will hire the best lawyer for you
After Chiu gets his dad's money
you can have Tony back
What we want is different from yours
I won't trust anybody
Tell him Tony is coming
Tony is here
Is it bomb?
Shit Yes
Don't move
Do you have a problem?
What are you talking about?
You asked his wife to make him
show up, so you could shoot him
Crazy, what does it have anything to do
with me?
Stop lying, look
Let's go
I don't know them
don't set me up
Who is the nephew of Brian Cheuk?
I'm exhausted
Come on
Uncle Cheuk, are you tired?
What do you think?
Can you take on 4 people yourself?
No problem
I wonder
Looks like you can't make it
The suspects are taking action
everybody standby
You guys are not sincere
Trying to ambush me again and again
From now on
I will kill a child every 3 minutes
He's going to kill, what should we do?
Son, leave this place to your dad
Don't come over here
I beg you, don't come any closer
I've been a Buddhist for many years
don't fight with me
Don't force me to break my oath
Break it
Uncle Cheuk, they're more powerful
than you
Of course, they are my masters
No time left, let's go
Excuse me, thanks
Sir, this is the injunction from court
I want to see Mr. Chiu
Excuse me
Sir, your boss is calling for you
Really? Thanks
You can't going...
Mr. Chiu, this is an injunction from
court
This is an injunction from court
please give me my son
Can't you see the situation right now?
Can we wait until he release all the
hostages, okay
You crazy, should we let him eat first?
This is an injunction from court
are you going to execute it?
I don't mean it
I don't care
Just give me back my son
What are you doing? Stop it
Stop it
What's wrong?
Mr. Chiu
Who hit me?
Sir, there is a fight going on
What's the matter?
Didn't you see who hit me?
I was working
Why aren't you two fools helping me?
We don't know how to fight
Super tag team
This is called side kick
Honey
Damn, luckily I practiced kung-fu before
3 minutes are over
No
Tony...
I am Pun, not Tony
Tony is almost here
You are lying to me
You all lied to me
He is not coming
Tony won't come
Dad
Tony
Dad Tony
Dad
Charles
I've brought him here
Let other people go now
Thanks
I always keep my promise
Uncle Pun
Don't move
You go inside and take a look
Yes, sir
Cheuk, please take good care of
my son
I will
You are a nice and tough man
They won't punish you severely
After you come out from jail, take good
care of Tony
Tell him that violence is not good
solution
Tony, listen to uncle
Relax
Take him away
Yes, sir
Let's go
Son
Mom
Are you okay?
I'm fine
That's good
I've fixed those bastards
You are something
I've to meditate for a long time for this
wrong doing
Cut the crap, let's go
Let's go
This quick?
What?
You dad died in America
Where is my share of heritage?
He donated all money to the charity
fund
You assholes, I'm going to kill you all
You asshole, how dare you hit me
when you become poor
Although I'm not good at fighting
I should get it a try
Come on
Brother-in-law
Are you okay?
I'm fine, after this couple of days
I realized one thing
that I've not potential to learn Kung-fu
I've decided to study kung-fu from
Cheuk
You have to try hard
Forget it
Forget it, bitch
Charles, are you okay? I didn't mean it
Sorry, Charles
Be careful, brother-in-law
Tony, be a good boy and come to your
mother
Uncle, let's go
Did you hear me, let's go
It is not my fault, I'm innocent
One picture please
Miss, are you a reporter
Interview me, I'll give you exclusive
news
But you have to pay me
Exclusive
What do you want to know?
Maybe I'll tell you about my sex life
with Charles
Damn, I've to teach you a lesson
I can't believe after I stayed with that
dummy for hours only
but I've learned some useful skills
Dad, where are you going?
Going out to eat
Eating out
Yes
But I need some medicine
Uncle will set up a date for you with
a beautiful girl
Yes, really beautiful
Right, she is really pretty
No way
Really? It is really pretty
Hello...
Where are you going? Come back
I have to run to Shenzhen
He will be useless wh