Shangkuan, your Eagle's Claw
has destroyed my Snake's Fist school.
Damn you for killing my students!
The Eagle's Claw and Snake's Fist
are mortal enemies.
It is God's will that your diabolical sect
has been destroyed.
As grand master of my school,
I must avenge my dead.
Surely you realise that
your technique is inferior to mine?
I do this to honour my ancestors,
and though I may die today -
- my descendants will ensure
the Snake's Fist doesn't die with me.
Yes, and as long as
Pai Chang-tien lives -
- the flag of the Snake's Fist still flies!
After I've killed you,
Pai Chang-tien is next!
- Where's Pai Chang-tien?
- He's very sly. You won't find him!
Pai Chang-tien...
GUEST HOUSE
I told you not to bother me.
Do you want to die?
No flies on me!
- He owes a month's rent!
- Inn-keeper, be reasonable...
So, he won't pay...
I'll pay you, just give me two days.
See what's in the basket.
What are you doing?
- That's just my snake.
- A snake!
Stop him!
Remember, always use your head!
I can't jaw away all day.
It's hard to stomach, I know.
So, there's no chance of some grub.
What does my kick taste like?
My teeth!
"Cicada's escape."
One, two, three, four
and again, damn it!
You've been bowled over!
Bowl... chopsticks...
bowl... chopsticks!
- I'll... kill... you!
- Using a weapon? Really, brother...
- I must run.
- Come back, you scoundrel!
Excuse me...
Come back!
- What's up?
- That damned rascal had a snake!
A snake...
HUNG-TAI SCHOOL
- Chien-fu, don't neglect your chores.
- I'm... I'm not!
- So, you're splashing me...?
- Sorry. I'll wipe it up.
Damn fool!
- I didn't mean...
- Simpleton!
Clean it up.
That will teach you
to take more care next time.
While the master's away,
Li and I will be in charge.
Today, I'll teach you "dragon-tiger fist".
- Then you'll be able to beat ten men.
- Ten eggs maybe.
And don't forget to pay your fees!
Master Li and I will demonstrate.
Watch closely.
- Dragon-fist!
- Tiger-fist!
- Nice going!
- Impressive, huh?
- Stop laughing!
- What's so funny?!
What are you laughing at?!
- Chien-fu!
Why laugh at your teacher?
- What's so funny?
- What?
Ah, Chien-fu...
Fighters must be fast,
accurate and ferocious.
I'll now demonstrate
"golden dragon's claw".
Ready... Observe how
the abdomen is now exposed.
- A hit!
- You see, a hit!
The next stance is "preying-tiger".
Stretch out your hand.
No, no... the other one.
Exposed again...
I didn't tell you to resist.
An irresistable attack.
- Well, was it fantastic?
- Fantastic!
Remember what you've learnt today.
- Carry on with your practice.
- Come on, get moving.
Were you used as
a human punchbag again?
Shall I apply some balm for you?
HING-WEI SCHOOL
I'll rest here.
Here is your drink, magistrate.
It's an honour to welcome the owner -
- of so many restaurants,
pawn shops and funeral parlours.
Although your son is as fat as a pig...
More evidence of your prosperity.
But if he doesn't train his muscles -
- they'll lose the strength
so evident in his father.
Yes, there's truth in what you say.
It's for this reason
that I want my son to learn kung fu.
It's true that there are many
martial arts schools in our province...
Really? So why haven't I heard of it?
If you don't believe me,
believe your own eyes.
I've seen guys in the street
break bricks with their bare hands.
- Can your students do that?
- Such feats are simplicity itself for us.
Demonstrate your brick breaking
for young master.
Breaking stone with your fists
is a marvellous feeling.
Wait! Hold it...
Feel up to it?
Sure, no problem.
That's superb!
- That was marvellous!
- Not at all...
One of our students is competing
in the Three Provinces Championship.
- Really?
- Sure!
- You'd like to study here?
- Yes, I want to join this school.
It's agreed then, he'll start tomorrow.
One moment...
The magistrate's leaving!
I'm coming!
Say goodbye to our new pupil.
His hand looks crushed!
I'm not staying here.
Father, let's try Hung-tai School...
But magistrate...
Magistrate! Magistrate!
Get inside...
The sight of this layabout
is driving away business.
- Get rid of him!
- Yes!!
- What...?
- Who said you could sleep here?
Sorry, I'll leave at once.
Stop! You can't beat an old man!
- He's got guts. Who is he?
- He's from Hung-tai School.
Hung-tai School? Beat him!
Get him!
- Are you hurt?
- No!
Not my hand again!
My back!
Brothers, in the name of God,
don't fight! Brothers, stop fighting!
- Don't, brothers...
- Why not?
If a man strikes one cheek,
offer him the other.
That's your advice?
You dare... God won't forgive you!
- This way.
- Are you hurt?
- No, I'm used to blows!
- You're used to them?
This is the back door
of Hung-tai School. Come in and rest.
This is the back yard.
Very few people come here.
I live in this store room.
Cat, cat, cat
speak to our guest in the hat.
There...
Have a seat.
- Have a bowl of hot tea.
- Thanks.
- Why don't you drink?
- I never drink hot tea.
- I'll get a cold one.
- Good...
Chang, finished your shopping?
Old man, he's our cook.
His cooking is very tasty.
Save your flattery. And this is...?
He's my relative.
Chang, I haven't eaten yet.
Help yourself.
I've kept your meal warm for you.
I have to serve the guests.
Magistrate, I assure you...
The students here
find it's only a matter of time -
- before they become invincible.
Mr. Li, you must be a great teacher!
Is that so? Wei-wu School has
sent students to the championship.
Can you say the same?
What's so special about entering
students for the competition?
Although our Mr. Hung will be present
for the contest - he's the judge.
If he's the judge,
then his kung fu must be splendid.
Naturally, he was the best in his day.
- How many bricks can he break?
- Bricks?
I don't teach party tricks,
I teach real kung fu.
Young master, you were obviously
born to be a good fighter.
You're clever and tactful. Study here,
and you'll soon be an expert.
- Really?
- Of course!
Chang, bring Chien-fu here.
- What's your name?
- I'm Chien-fu.
- Your father was called Chien?
- No, sir.
I'm an orphan. The school took me in.
They say Chien is a good name
for someone simple-minded like me.
- What's your name?
- Oh...
Chien-fu... Mr. Li wants to see you.
You take it easy, old man.
I'll be back soon, so don't go away.
This is the young master
of Chin-san Bank.
He has been here a month,
and his progress is remarkable.
You see this big guy?
He's one tough cookie, I assure you.
Chien-fu, fight with Bean
for the benefit of our guests.
But don't resist, got it?
Be careful.
Begin.
Good! Beat him... Beat him!
You dare to fight back
and disobey Mr. Li?
Hit him!
Stop! That's enough!
Chien-fu, rest up
and you'll be better in no time.
Father, I want to stay here!
Chien-fu, are you okay?
- I'm alright.
- Alright... You've been fighting.
I haven't... It was...
You don't understand.
He's the school's human punchbag.
A punchbag?
Mr. Li forces him
to take the punishment.
Chien-fu, can you grab the bowl?
I don't think you can.
Old man... Old man?
Shabby cat...
"Twist and turn, in a blur
of hands and feet. Writhe like a snake"
"Be supple like a willow before the wind"
What is this...?
"Twist and turn..."
The old man's showing me
his tricks... Well, here goes!
Show some mercy
for the poor beggar.
I bring the message of the Lord.
Only His words can save you.
Have mercy on me.
What's the idea of begging at this hour?
Get out of my sight!
That's one fierce lady.
Wretched sinner, ask for
God's forgiveness before it's too late.
just who do you think
you're calling a sinner?!
jesus Christ wants to save you.
Save me? You mean fool me!
Take that, and that! And be
more careful who you call a sinner!
Thanks, lady. You're very kind.
Believe in God and eternal life,
for this is His gift to man.
- Anyone home?
- Why call so early?
jesus Christ died for us, so that
we might experience heavenly joy.
Come in if you want joy! My girls
specialise in bringing it to you!
BROTHEL
Don't be shy, come in!
Chun-hua, Chun-yuen! Foreign meat!
You sinners, you'll all go to hell!
Anyone here?
Leaving already?
- Are you looking for Chao Chi-chih?
- Who? I'm looking for food.
What a sad sight you are.
Let me end your misery!
You want to flee, Pai Chang-tien?
Renounce violence!
That's right!
Good!
- Marvellous!
- Your hand should be straight.
- Ah-Kuei!
- Father!
Finished work for the day?
Please sit, sit...
I've come to check on
Ah-Kuei's progress.
You son is a genius,
and he studies extremely hard.
He has good muscles,
fine posture and rock-hard fists.
He has a very bright future before him!
Is this true?
- Have you fought with others yet?
- No, I haven't.
You want to fight?
That's easily arranged.
Chien-fu, come here.
Chien-fu, let's see what
the young master is made of.
You know what I expect.
Young master, don't hit too hard.
Begin!
- Your son fights marvellously.
- So it seems!
Come on!
- Stand still, damn it!
- You have to be faster!
You've asked for it!
My dragon-tiger fist!
Lord in heaven!
Magistrate, are you hurt?
Here's a new move for the great guru
to teach his students.
Ah-kuei, let's get out of here
and go to Wei-wu School.
Magistrate, please!
just allow me to explain...
Well, smart guy, you've succeeded
in ruining my reputation.
Now, get out of my sight!
Old man!
- Old man, what happened?
- I was ambushed...
I... I must get help.
Chien-fu... just find a safe place
for me to rest.
Old man... Old man!
PHARMACY
Old man...
Boss!
Chao Chi-chih has been living here.
- How long since he left?
- A month.
Pai Chang-tien is wounded,
he'll seek out Chao Chi-chih.
He's bound to leave a trail.
It is your task to discover it.
The picture is ancient,
but the words are new.
The man you seek
awaits you in heaven.
You're awake.
How are you feeling now?
I'll be alright.
That's good news,
I've been very worried about you.
I'll get your medicine.
Drink this, it will give you strength.
Chien-fu, I am indebted to you.
It's nothing. We're friends, aren't we?
And you taught me
how to avoid being hit.
- Well, has it proved useful?
- Yes...
But I irritated Mr. Li and he beat me.
- Do you want to learn kung fu?
- Yes, then no one can victimise me.
You must promise me three things.
I'll gladly keep a hundred promises.
Firstly, you must never
refer to me as your master.
- Why not?
- Because we're good friends.
Secondly, don't reveal what you've
learnt, unless conflict is unavoidable.
Okay, and third?
Promise that you will not come
to my aid if I fight with my enemies.
How can I promise not to help
if you are losing?!
You must promise me this.
Okay, I promise.
- What will you teach me?
- The Snake's Fist.
Shabby cat,
are you missing your master?
You must eat or you'll waste away.
So, smart guy, you want to take me on?
You're becoming crafty.
You're slipping.
- Mr. Li, be careful.
- I'm always careful.
- Son of a bitch!
- I said take care.
- Are you hurt?
- Damn it!
Are you here looking for trouble?
I've won the Three
Provinces Championship.
Every kung fu school has
congratulated me, except yours.
“flu-w
- You need to learn respect.
- You're challenging us?
Yes! Who's first?
You're too sure of yourself,
my friend. Therefore, I...
- Yes, he...
- ...nominate my pupil.
You're in big trouble!
- Mr. Li, I defer to you.
- Not at all.
You must have this privilege.
I can't deny you this golden opportunity,
you lucky fellow. Go right ahead.
- Please, Master Li, after you...
- No, no, after you...
Shut up! I'll take on both of you at once.
- You go high, I'll go low.
- We'll attack front and back.
He's trapped now!
That was a textbook attack!
My braid!
- I won't use my hands.
- That's more like it!
The champion is fantastic.
Let's join Hung-wei School!
Go somewhere else. We're closed...
Master Hung... Master Hung!
Hung, why aren't you
giving classes to your pupils?
If you've nothing to do,
you can be my assistant!
I came here to fight.
Master Hung, no one forced
your students to join my school.
You took advantage of my absence
and stole my students.
- You can't deny it.
- The boys study where they please.
Then we will settle this by combat.
So, that's it? Well,
I fancy my chances against you.
Chien-fu, stand aside.
You posture like a hero,
but you fight like a dog!
Master!
Remain where you are.
My brother's coming!
Master Hung, as I caused
this dispute, I will settle it.
- Be careful, he's very powerful.
- Get back.
- You're the so-called champion?
- I have that honour.
Under no circumstances
use the snake's fist that I taught you.
Master!
- That's enough, okay?
- You clearly have a death wish.
Don't come closer! I won't fight...
This is for throwing shoes...
- Get up!
- That's enough, okay?
So, you're not a total novice....
- What stance is that?
- This is the "angry mantis"!
Mantis, beware the snake!
"Mantis catches a cicada".
"Reverse snake".
- Chien-fu...
- Stay back!
Looks like Chien-fu just got angry!
I said I don't want to fight.
You can't move now?
Your kung fu is quite good,
but a little unreliable.
All that waving your arms...
You use bricks now?
- Why use a weapon?
- To impale a snake!
A snake with fangs!
This is "finding a snake".
Master, let's go.
Well done, Chien-fu!
Let's rejoin Hung-tai.
Chien-fu, I have had to leave
at very short notice.
Study this book on Snake's Fist
kung fu, until my return.
He's gone...
Old man!
Where have you gone?
Who are you?
- Were you looking for the old man?
- I... Yes.
- I'm looking for him, too.
- Why do you want him?
- Who are you?
- What's it to you?
He's my mas...
So, he's your master?
Then you should call me uncle.
- You're the brother of old man?
- Yes!
- I don't believe it!
- You don't believe...
"Standing snake."
- "Snake at the front."
- just like my mas...
It looks right, but I'm not convinced.
You still don't believe me?
- Very well, let's fight.
- Fight? Why not?
Uncle, take it easy! I'm choking...
You've practised hard,
but not hard enough.
Stay down,
or I'll convince you some more.
You think so? Watch out!
- What else can you do?
- I can roll!
I writhe!
You missed me.
I've been using kid gloves with you,
but now they're off!
"Finding the snake."
This snake is too fast.
"Snake taking a pearl."
That's too obvious.
Un... cle... it... hurts.
- Are you okay?
- Uncle...
- Did you pull your punches?
- Of course. After all, I'm your uncle.
Your attacks seem different
to my master's.
That's because your master
didn't teach you everything.
Will you teach me?
I must have your master's
permission. Where is he?
- He just left.
- Left?
- Where has he gone?
- I don't know, but he'll be back.
- When will he return?
- He didn't tell me.
But I'll inform you when he does.
Good! But don't let him know
that I'm looking for him.
- I want to give him a surprise.
- Okay.
Why does uncle
fight so differently to my master?
Where's the book?
It must have been the cat.
Catch it!
Your claws are very fierce, cat!
Cat's claw with snake's fist!
Chao Chi-chih!
So, old man,
Shangkuan has snared you both!
Yes, Chao was in the hills, near
heaven. But heaven is still far away.
The two of you can rot here.
Hsiao chin, you must be dreaming
if you think I die so easily!
The weather is cool,
I don't need fanning.
Hold that pose...
Old man!
- Where were you?
- I had urgent business.
- I missed you. Why take so long?
- I missed you too.
- Chien-fu, the tea's ready!
- Coming.
Ah... thanks!
It's hot!
A man came looking for you
after you'd left.
- Who was he?
- You'd recognise him.
I'd recognise him? Who was it?
You sit here, I'll tell you later.
Uncle, the old man's back.
I'll take you to him!
Hurry! It's not far...
I haven't told him about you.
This way!
Hey, wait for me!
Preacher?
What did you call me?
I follow the Eagle's Claw, not God.
What are you saying?
I don't understand.
We will wipe the Snake's Fist
from the face of the Earth.
And the man you call uncle
is our leader. He has fooled you.
You really are scum!
I almost lost my feet!
Pai Chang-tien,
running any further is futile!
Shangkuan...
Are you so sure that the eagle
will always triumph over the snake?
Today marks the end of the war
between the eagle and the snake...
The end of the Snake's Fist!
I will oppose you with the last breath
in my body. I do not fear death!
Then allow me to take your life!
"The eagle swoops."
I'll rip out your heart!
Pai Chang-tien,
time for the snake to shed its skin!
A stone to sharpen your claws on!
It was dishonourable
to pretend to be my uncle -
- so that you could trick me
into leading you to him.
You've got guts, hero...
I'll tear them from your body!
You can't hurt him. I swear to you
he isn't my student.
Even if he disowns me,
I am proud to call him my master!
You follow the way of the snake.
All who wield the Snake's Fist
will be hunted down and slaughtered.
Slaughtered...
Master, he's dreaming!
Chien-fu, you can't beat him. Run!
Master, do you expect me
to flee from this wretch?!
It seems that to shut your lying mouth,
I'll have to remove your tongue.
And I'll shave your moustache!
- This isn't Snake's Fist... What is it?
- Cat's claw!
Chien-fu!
- What fighting prowess!
- Chang!
Why are you here?
- Where did you learn to fight like that?
- My master taught me!
Good... fantastic!
It's okay, your master's here!
Don't be so pleased with yourselves.
The tea that you drank was poisoned.
You're both going to die very soon.
No one can resist
Poison Eagle of Eagle's Claw.
Master never drinks hot tea.
I changed it!
Chien-fu, that was brilliant!
You combined Snake's Fist with
cat's claw to destroy the Eagle's Claw.
Such an elegant solution
deserves an elegant name.
- Master, you name it.
- How about...
- "Snake in the eagle's shadow."
- "Snake in the eagle's shadow" it is!