- Hi, Johnny. How are you?
- Hi.
- Can we do a picture together?
- Thanks.
- Hi.
- Ehi, how are you, Johnny? How are you?
- Well, Pupi.
- Always good, Johnny, eh?
- Hi, Cleo.
- Finally!
- Hi from Giorgia Surina
We are in the lobby of Principe di Savoia Hotel
Together with one of the biggest stars of Hollywood,
Johnny Mark.
- Welcome in Italy Johnny.
Comes straight from the airport
so he has seen nothing yet.
But there will be time to do
many things in our country
- Do you know name of some famous monument?
- Milan Cathedral, Colosseum ...
Good morning, Good evening
- Good morning, Good evening...
- Well just a few words to....
< Receptionist: Good evening, Mister Marco.
< Chocolate, strawberry,
pistachio and vanilla.
< Well, Mister Marco.
Thanks. < Please.
< RacheI (from TV):
Ross kissed me!
- No!
- Oh, Oh my god!
- Yes, Is not it amazing?
- Oh, my god, my god!
- Tell us something
- Monica, take wine
... and disconnect the phone
- Ok.
< Phoebe: Rachel, Has it nice end?
or must I cry!
<I cannot repeat same thing for 5 days
Okay, I explane you again reasons.
I do not feel I can
give something to this character.
< I think is better to stop the movie
Ok. Seeks to protect me, this is your job
Ok.
I wait for your call later.
Thanks. Bye.
< Pupi's wife: Beauriful!
- Did you called mayor's secretary? < Yes.
- Welcome back to ''International
television Grand Prix'',
- The magic night of television awards (telegatti).
- It's time to proclaim
- Dear Nino, The next winner is collengue by you.
- Not only collengue,
is more than collengue. < Sure?
< Frassica: is a friend,
is more than a friend. Is a sister. < Ah ah!
- A director from Milan DOG.
- DOC Nino.... and not DOG
- (ITALIAN WORDS).
- And the winner is
- Maurizio Nichetti.
< Ventura: Well! Maurizio Nichetti
is the winner for this year.
Congratulations, Maurizio.
This is your award (Telegatto).
Did you wants to great someone?.
I want to dedicate this to my public
Because this award is also
your, your and your.
...and thanks to my family
Thanks to all.
- Thanks to Maurizio Nichetti,
- Director of the year.
Go ahead,
now it's your turn Marina
- No, my name is Simona.
- Did you changed?
Simona is my name.
(ITALIAN WORDS)
Is now the international guest moment.
< Ladies and Gentlemen he comes from USA.....
- He worked with bigger stars of Hollywood,
Dustin Hoffman, Meryl Streep,
Sharon Stone and AI Pacino,
- Most important directors works with him.
Ladies and Gentlemen. Johnny Marco!
- Congratulation.
Congratulation, Johnny.
This award (telegatto) is for you..
You are a great actor.
..... And a very beautiful boy too
- Is your moment, tell something to the public
- Thanks.
Good evening.
Thanks to all. It's an honour.
Thanks.
(VALERIA MARINI sings)
< Driver: No, no.