Happy Birthday!
Give me five.
This is Malhotra speaking,
using STD on my personal line.
Are you all coming tomorrow?
Yes! As soon as we reach Delhi,
we'll take the Faridabad train.
The one at 4 O'clock?
- Yes! What are you doing?
Me? I was just... nothing.
No... sorry not you.
These Mumbai butlers
are something else.
Okay then, I'll pick you
up tomorrow.
Sure? You forgot last time.
Last time... this time
I'll be there
...by the way, the requirements
forthe death anniversary...
Yes! I am getting it all
with me. Don't worry.
Okay then, bye.
- Bye.
Hi Guys!
This is Neelam and you're watching
your favourite show, The Neelam Show.
Like always we are going to
do something new...
We are going to play a game.
Would you all like to play
this game?
Lt is said that this game gets
matters of the heart to the fore.
I will say a word...
...and you have to say the first
word that comes to your mind.
But you get no time
to think.
We'll start with you, Clouds?
Sorry. Times up. Clouds?
Rain.
Beautiful?
- Neelam.
Thanks!
Heart?
- Love.
Okay... Love?
- Seema.
What? You love me?
- Yeah!
This game really works.
You saw how real feelings came
rushing out. Now you try this game...
...and we'll be back
after a break.
Stupid game, stupid Neelam.
- Don't call my Neelam stupid.
Okay! Let's play your game.
Okay! Ready, start, go... Sexy?
- Granny.
Papa play seriously.
- Okay.
Clouds?
Papa you can't take so long.
I'm having water. Okay, now
we'll start. Tell me.
Clouds?
- Air.
Mad?
- You.
Home?
- Us.
Love?
- Friendship.
Anjali?
- Sharma.
Sharma?
Who is Anjali Sharma?
Who is she?
Nobody.
Papa, it's my birthday...
Okay. Anjali Sharma studied
in college with me.
In your College?
She was my friend.
- Friend!
My best friend.
Her name's very nice,
what was she like?
She was unlike any other girl.
She was like one of the boys.
All the other girls spent
time on make up...
...but Anjali played
Basketball.
She wore clothes like me.
Yeah! Really.
Anjali was mad. Dressing
up and looking beautiful...
...was just not her scene.
Enough or do you still
want to hear more?
Papa where is she now?
- I don't know.
Anjali, I can't believe that
you are getting engaged.
By the way, Guruji has come
to fix the wedding date.
Show me that one.
How much will you adorn yourself,
Aman's getting impatient.
"Your groom has been
waiting for long"
"Don't delay anymore
come soon"
"I've come to your doorstep
I've come to take you away"
"I've come to exchange
my heart for yours"
"My every heartbeat has a message
for you... listen to my heart"
"The Bridegroom has come home..."
"Why's the bride shy?"
"The Bridegroom has come home"
"Oh! Dear heart you can't make
excuses... no more"
"Now the bride will have
to go with her groom"
"What's her vermilion
whispering to her?"
"I've got hooked in
his net of love"
"Dear friends, how
did this happen?"
"Tell me, tell me"
"Oh my darling! Your friends
too have a crush on me"
"They won't have much to say
Ask them"
"Go, go, dear liar
Why do you make self praises"
"Your love has something to say
Will you listen to my heart!"
"He is innocent and oblivious. I've
done him a favour by accepting him."
"Someone please convey to him."
"She teases me deliberately I've given
my heart in return of her favour"
"Do convey to her"
"You're not aware of heartbreak"
"Your love has something to say
Will you listen to his heart"
"With henna on your hands
bedecked with jewellery"
"Teary eyed you will make us all,
and leave in the morning"
"We will miss you lots,
We will miss you lots"
"I've come to your doorstep
I've come to take you away"
"I've come to exchange
my heart for yours"
"My every heartbeat has a message
for you... listen to my heart"
"The Bridegroom has come home"
"Why's the bride shy?"
This is the old address.
Where do I get the new one from?
What Grandpa, you can't even
do this much for me?
I can do it for you but...
- Really!
The college principal can't even
do this much.
One minute... She would definitely
know where Anjali Sharma is.
I'm sorry. I had promised
Anjali that...
...I would not give her
address to anyone.
We were hopeful that...
I understand sir, but I made
a promise to Anjali.
Rifat bi, I'm also Anjali,
you won't tell me either?
Sir, she's getting engaged
today...
...and herwedding is within
this week.
Her Guruji will finalise
the date today.
The preparations forthe
wedding are underway.
You have come very late.
I am also going by
tomorrow afternoon's train.
This marriage cannot happen.
Mummy said so.
Guruji, we need to finalise
the wedding date.
Yes dear.
This is Aman's horoscope.
- Yes.
Aman wants to go to
London this month.
If you could find a date this
month itself?
This month?
- Yes Guruji.
Sir, if you would have
come earlier...
Yes, but we didn't know...
Anjali's stars have a negative
influence right now.
Until it changes she
cannot get married.
What about next month Guruji?
- Not even next month.
Not before December.
I had heard of God's grace,
today I've seen it.
The child's prayers
have been answered
Anjali's wedding is
postponed to December.
Anjali, can I ask you something?
- Yes.
Are you happy?
What sort of a question is that?
Of course I'm happy.
I've got engaged.
Aman's really nice, he
loves me a lot and...
But do you love him?
Anjali...
I have already loved mom.
I'm not sure I can do
it again.
Just think of this
as a compromise.
Compromise?
I neverthought that my daughterwould
marry out of compromise and not love
I'm your mother and I want
you to be happy too.
But a home based on a compromise
is a house, not a home.
The rest is upto you.
Oh! I can't handle this
religious stuff... Yes I can.
Today Guruji is going to chant
hymns and read the sacred book.
Wow! How exciting. This
Guruji will get a...
Why? He has delayed my wedding.
I can't stand these hymns any more.
Even God gets fed up with
so many hymns.
Why? Don't you want to ask
God for anything special?
I've got you...
what more could I ask for?
Well I do want some kids but that
I'm afraid I'll have to do myself.
Behave yourself!
Aman I saw you bare bodied,
exercising this morning.
What are you saying?
- Kammo... even in your old age?
Old! Old must be you.
Don't trouble him.
Do you have a brother?
My Gurpreet is also very pretty.
- What are you saying?
Forget Gurpreet,
My Jaspreet is Ms. Chandigarh.
Ms. Chandigarh or Ms. Sector 11.
Okay come on now, Guruji
has started.
Okay, bye Aman.
Anjali, there is a call for you.
Thanks a lot mother-in-law.
- Welcome son-in-law.
Hello!
I love you.
Huh... Aman!
- Listen, I have a problem.
What?
- Don't leave me like this.
Aman I don't know who is
on the line.
And anyway you are going to
Shimla for your summer camp.
You're going to Bombay as well.
For24 hours and you're
going for a month.
Aman, I go there every year
to teach singing and dancing.
Those kids are part of my life.
Even they are a part of
your life.
Only I'm left out.
Why do I get the feeling, you
don't love me?
Because I don't.
And that you don't want to marry me.
- Right, I don't.
Hey! Any tantrums this time...
...and I'll drag you by the
hand to the marriage pandal.
You'll force me?
- If need be.
You have the guts to do it?
Try me.
L'll stay here with
your aunts.
You go to Shimla
for your Summer Camp
Summer Camp!
Shimla!
Summer Camp? Shimla?
No way. Too much snow there.
Papa, it's a summer camp.
- Whatever... Is this okay?
Yes. Papa they teach singing
and dancing there...
...and you know I am fond
of that.
Since when have you been fond
of singing and dancing?
I've said no means no.
Papa not fair.
- Let her go.
All kids go to camps. She'll also...
- Mom! L'll handle this okay.
But Rahul try and understand.
L'll also go with her...
Papa I want to go, I want
to go, please papa.
No Anjali.
Shut up. I said no. Now
neither of you will go.
You felt bad? I'm sorry.
It's okay.
This doesn't mean you're going.
I'm going to the conference.
We'll talk when I get back.
Papa.
- Now what?
You haven't worn your pants.
It's okay, you wear it
if you want to.
Drivertake out the pant...
the car.
Anjali... How will we make
your father come to the camp?
Oh Granny! Rememberwhen dad was
in London and I fell sick.
Yes my baby.
Granny. Papa left everything
and came back immediately.
- Oops sorry!
- Don't worry about it man, it's okay.
Indian Exporters Conference,
good evening!
May I speak to Aman Mehra please?
Whom shall I say is calling?
- Anjali.
Indian Exporters Conference,
good evening!
Hello! Can I speak to papa?
- Papa?
Your father's not a film star.
Tell her his name.
Sorry. May I speak to
Mr. Rahul Khanna please?
Whom shall I say is calling?
- Anjali
Certainly, Anjali.
Quickly tell him we're going
and put the phone down.
Hi! Rahul Khanna.
Hello! Aman, I can't hear you.
- I can hear you. Tell me?
Hi sweetheart!
I'm really missing you.
Listen, I'm off to the camp tomorrow.
- Where to?
- Summer camp.
Again summer camp. I said
no once to you, didn't I?
Listen. I'm feeling very...
give me a kiss.
This is your mother speaking.
- Look. I don't like these jokes.
My mother passed away
10 years ago.
Why is everyone trying to
pronounce me dead today?
No summer camp, no summer
camp. Understood?
Aman why are you screaming?
That's because I've told you,
you're not going.
If you say one more thing,
I'll get home and... slap you.
Aman you've gone mad.
Anjali?
Your dad's gone mad.
- Anjali?
Hi! I'm Rahul Khanna.
- Aman Mehra, how're you doing?
I guess because of the same
name she got confused...
Bet you, my Anjali is
prettierthan yours.
No! My Anjali is very beautiful.
I'm sure but not as
beautiful as mine.
My Anjali is my 8-year-old daughter.
Shit! You're right.
Your Anjali is prettier.
Dear Papa, How are you? Sorry
we left without informing you...
...but you know how much I love
singing and dancing.
Don't miss me too much.
Love Anjali.
That's not possible for me to do...
Good Morning kids.
I am Col. Almeida, the camp manager.
L'll now measure your height
and weight.
24 - very nice, 30 - very good.
80 - very... what child is this?
Hey! Who are you?
Me? I am Granny.
- Whose Granny?
Anjali's. Who are you?
Col. Almeida. Camp Manager.
No grannies', mummies' and
daddies' allowed on this camp.
So I should've let Anjali
come here alone?
What?
Have you seen Ms. Anjali?
Ms. Anjali!
What? What?
The British flag in India...?
L'll sort him out. Almeida...
You have no shame?
You've hoisted the British flag.
I love England.
My fatherwas an English tailor.
He made this flag.
Britishers went away and
left you behind.
You fool, you should teach
the kids "My Bharat is the best".
Here you go.
- Thank you.
Hey! What's your name?
Sorry. What's your name?
- Anjali.
Hey that's my name too. Hi!
Why is your name Anjali?
Perhaps my parents liked
the name.
Why is your name Anjali?
- Perhaps my parents liked you.
Where is this Almeida?
Namaste.
Almeida...
I need your blessings mummy.
- Almeida.
Stop following me.
- Where is the kitchen?
I want to see how you cook food.
- And where is the prayer room?
- Puja has not come on duty today.
Prayer room, where one prays
to the lord.
We don't do that here.
What? There is no prayer
to the lord.
Lord? Who is the Lord?
Counting stars?
London Bridge is falling
down, falling down... up
Dear God, How are you?
Please keep papa happy and see that
he doesn't miss me too much.
You know he can't do anything
without me. Okay.
Caught you.
All prayers for papa,
nothing for mama?
Why ask God for anything for mummy?
Why?
- She's with him.
Whatever she wants,
she can ask for it herself.
Hey! Now go to sleep.
Sweet dreams.
Miss you papa.
Hi guys! Welcome to the
Neelam Show...
...and today we are coming
to you live.
There's so much noise here,
so check it out...
Hi Guys! This is Neelam and
you're watching...
...The Neelam Show.
Like always we're going to do
something new and different.
Today's theme is love messages.
Messages anyone?
I have a message.
- We've got one here.
Whom is your message for?
- Superna.
Who is Superna.
- My girlfriend.
Your message?
Look Superna. Don't call me.
I've found someone else.
Hey! Another message.
I want to give a message too.
Like the one he gave...
- And his message is for...
For Anjali.
I love you Anjali.
Why have you left me and gone?
You know I feel lost without you.
Come back or else... just come back.
Please come back.
Who is Anjali?
She's my 8-year-old daughter.
She's gone to some camp in Shimla.
Neelam can you tell herto come
back? She'll listen to you.
Anjali... Papa really loves you.
Come back soon. He misses you.
Come back home. Okay.
Mr. Khanna, meeting fortomorrow
at 11 a.m. Is confirmed.
Hi Rahul! Party at my place
tomorrow. See you there.
Papa... aachoo.
- Cold...?
Are you feeling okay?
Yeah. Why?
No. You're looking... beautiful,
that's why... Saree.
I didn't know about Tina.
I'm sorry.
How could you know? You just
disappeared.
We changed our residence.
- You changed your friends as well?
When I needed my friend the most,
you were not there.
You didn't marry again?
Couldn't find you... or else would
have married you.
We live once, die once, get
married once and love...
Only once.
You didn't get married either?
Couldn't find you.
Hey! Look a shooting star.
- Still believe in it?
No. You?
- No.
What did you wish for?
Granny.
What news?
- Bad news.
They are behaving like they're
meeting forthe first time.
Good night Rahul,
Good night Anjali.
Now what do we do?
You have any idea granny?
The solution now lies in
prayer and devotion.
Oh Granny. Now you only
tell me what to do?
What are you doing?
Have you gone mad?
Ls this what I have taught you?
Big boys don't fight, she's a girl.
- Why are you fighting?
She hit me first.
I just said that girls can play
Basketball and he said...
Boo girls can't play Basketball.
He said the truth and you
fought with him.
Why! In college Ms. Anjali beat
you everyday in Basketball.
Shh! Quiet!
Not everyday, sometimes.
- Rahul, you lost everyday.
- Remember Anjali, you lost everyday.
Rahul, you lost everyday.
- No Anjali.
Yes Rahul.
Don't lie in front of
the kids.
What I'm lying?
- So am I lying? Liar.
What?
The truth is you could only
Hey! Don't call me a cheater.
That's what you are... a cheater.
Anjali, not cheater.
- Rahul is a cheater.
I challenge you right now,
let's play.
Don't be silly Anjali.
Why? Are you scared Rahul?
Rahul Khanna is never scared
of anyone.
We will see.
- We will see.
I'm sure Rahul will win.
- We will see!
You'll lose again Rahul.
I've been practicing for
8 years, I won't lose.
Listen, be careful
with your saree.
Don't hit me.
What was that!
Hey! Lf you can't play
atleast don't cheat.
Hey! Don't call me a cheater.
That's what you are -
a teacher... cheater.
"There is a strange girl,
she is a dream..."
"Is she for real or a story"
"Look at this mad one,
she's not changed"
"She is still the same
crazy one"
"There is a strange boy,
he is a dream..."
"Is he for real or a story"
"Yes, yes, this mad one has
not changed"
"He is still the same
crazy one"
"We were close and yet so far
those were strange circumstances"
"Those were strange times
when you were so close"
"Where are you lost, I'm right
here if only you would look"
"I was lonesome even in a crowd"
"You were forever in my memory"
"If someone stops me now
my heart will brim over"
"I can't stand steady
only you can help now"
"There is a strange girl,
she is a dream..."
"Is she for real or a story"
"Yes, yes, this mad one has
not changed"
"He is still the same crazy one"
"You gave me dreams"
"I am neither awake
nor asleep"
"Somethings happen in my heart..."
Mamata here's your letter.
All your mothers are
complaining that...
you all are not writing to them and
I have complained to your mother...
...that you don't say anything.
Everyone is going to write
home, in front of me.
Here pass these on.
Anjali, come on write a
letterto your mom...
If you were here, you'd be proud of
Anjali being your daughter.
Because she's so nice.
She has to be, her name's
Anjali after all.
But the best thing about
her is that...
...she looks just like you.
The same eyes, the same face.
I don't find this family
incomplete anymore...
Hello kids! Good morning.
Are you ready?
Say cheese.
Taking photographs without me?
Anyway I'm here now.
My saree looks nice?
- Beautiful.
Shall I sit there?
- Come sit please.
No not there, a little higher.
Where is he sending me? Higher.
Little higher. Yes.
- Shall I sit here?
How do I look?
- Fantastic, beautiful.
What happened?
I don't know. Something
is missing. Something wrong.
Okay now?
Lt's perfect. Shoot it.
Excuse me. Now one of
just the 2 of you.
No Mr. Almieda, enough.
Anjali, just one.
Colonel, please colonel, really.
- Come on Anjali.
Wow! How can anyone look
so good?
Yes! Anjali is looking
very nice here.
Really, I didn't even
notice her.
Liar. She's not here so you
What to do mother-in-law?
Aman, Since the wedding is
in December...
...why don't you go back
to London for a while?
I'm not budging from here.
- Why?
I don't trust your daughter.
She's taken forever, to agree
forthe marriage. Till we don't...
Tie the knot...
- Yes!
Tie the knot I'm not
going anywhere.
You love her a lot don't you?
No... Yes.
But I get the feeling
she doesn't love me.
She doesn't, right?
Hey! Mother-in-law...
she doesn't right?
Aman, you've gone mad.
She didn't answer.
Today we are going to play
a new game.
It's called Dumb Charades.
In this game there are 2 teams.
This is team A.
And this is team B.
One team will secretly tell
1 or2 members of the otherteam...
...the name of a film
The players have to act
out the film
And make theirteammates
guess the name of the film.
You can't say anything.
Simple! We'll start with team A
Yes! But how do I do this?
Now look, it's like...
You can't say anything.
Cheating...
This is cheating,
you are a cheater.
Come on! Can't you do this much.
Come on.
Yeah! Everybody yeah!
She's doing it.
"The Colourful One"
Yeah! That's right.
- "The Colourful One" yes.
You were really sexy!
- Thanks.
No, no, no,
I can't do this.
Come on granny...
At this age kids! No. No
Even I don't see Hindi films,
you know.
I like"Gone with the wind"
- Shut up!
Okay son.
But she's my mom.
You go there.
- Where?
Go there...
- Why?
Becuase I'm telling you that's why.
- Granny gone mad.
Yeah! Now bend.
- Bend.
Like this?
Mummy... Madhuri...
"How Are We Related"
It's my turn.
There's no such film.
There is papa.
- No there isn't.
There is.
- But I haven't seen any such film.
But, hey wait a minute.
Ofcourse, it's a film.
I've seen it myself.
But what is the name
of the film.
Three... three words.
Yes I've understood there
are three words, what else?
Rahul, what are you doing?
- Your son has gone mad.
Rahul I can't understand anything,
what are you doing?
What is it?
I love you...
Do it again...
I love you.
You couldn't do that much?
- No.
I wish you would've,
we would have won.
Come on kids, hurry up get into
the barn...
Hey give me that, thanks.
Have you gone mad?
I'm feeling very cold.
Come with me. L'll take you
to a place.
No music.
I love you.
Hey! I love you too.
Almeida you can't even
fix a leakage. Go on, go up.
Mom, did Anjali come here?
- Her she is.
No... not this one,
the other one.
Here hold this and help.
I want to talk with you.
You call this sty a summer camp?
Hi guys! Hey, I know you from
somewhere.
Telephone man.
What's up dude.
What're you doing here?
Ls that your Anjali?
This is my Anjali.
And this, is my Anjali.
You're just like Michael Jordan.
You're too good.
L'am not that good.
I've been beaten.
I don't believe it... Who won?
Anjali.
- Your Anjali.
No, your Anjali.
- My Anjali...
She played basketball?
Tell me, what kind of a girl
was she in college?
She was the life and pride
our college.
Everyone came to herwith
their problems.
Well, nothings changed.
Even I've come to herwith
my problem.
What problem do you have?
My problem is that
I love hertoo much, you know.
I know.
What kind of friend are you?
You didn't even come
for our engagement.
You're engaged?
Yes, but with great difficulty.
The wedding is in December,
hopefully.
Hey! Tell your friend...
If she doesn't marry
me in December...
I'll... marry this basketball.
We live once, we die once,
we get married once and
love...
Men are very weak...
They make principles but
don't realise that...
...no principle can override
the heart.
And we remind these stubborn
weak men that...
...bonds of the heart are based
on feelings not principles.
But these bonds are created...
...by telling the other person
about one's inner feelings.
Tell him what you feel Anjali.
Sometimes saying what one feels
can break one's heart.
But by not saying it you won't,
be happy.
Congratulations and
celebrations...
...we wish Ms. Anjali a
happy wedded life.
Congratulations and
celebrations...
Anjali, you didn't even
tell me.
Aman told me that you
are getting married.
Are you happy?
You are happy, aren't you?
Having heard this, are
you happy?
I'm very happy.
Then how can I be happy?
I don't understand.
Somethings happen Rahul,
you won't understand.
Somethings happen Anjali...
Uncle, May I ask you something?
- Sure
Why are you marrying Ms. Anjali?
What? Why? Ls something wrong?
Yeah! Lt's simple.
You're so handsome.
What happened?
- So good-looking.
Oh! Thank you so much.
But Ms. Anjali is not
that good looking.
You're right. She's dark,
fat and short.
You know, you can get anyone.
Anyone?
- Yes!
Then will you marry me?
- Me? No, no, no...
Why am I that bad?
Then you'll have to find
me a nice girl.
Found her.
- Who?
She.
This MTV one? Hi!
This is the Neelam Show... Yo!
Then what about this Anjali?
You'll have to find someone
for hertoo.
Found him.
- Found him?
Shall I tell you?
- No, no, no...
Please, let me tell you.
I want to leave tonight itself.
Goodbye Mr. Almeida
You're leaving?
Please don't go.
You gave this to Tina when
she was beginning a new life.
Today you are going to begin
a new life...
...and I am sure, you and Rahul
Start preparing forthe wedding.
I don't want to wait anymore.
But Guruji said that there is no
auspicious date before December...
Mother, dates don't bring
happiness, destiny does...
...and no one can change that.
Look! Aman's here and
that too on a mule.
Bindya... Panditji has come. Leave
everything and look after him.
You are Rahul, right?
- Yes, Anjali and I...
I know.
Anjali is getting married today?
Yes. She decided to get married
so suddenly that...
...I didn't get any time to
prepare...
Yes, I'm coming.
Please sit, I'll just be back.
Anjali!
They say if you make a
wish on a shooting star...
...it comes true...
The auspicious time is running
out, please call the bride.
Anjali.
The auspicious time is almost
over, please call the bride.
Anjali, let's go.
L'll drag you to the marriage
pandal, I told you so didn't I?
You know, I always wanted to see
that love in your eyes...
...that I have in mine.
Today, I've seen it,
but it's not for me.
You're mad Anjali.
You've always loved him
Eversince you've known love,
understood love...
...You've loved only him.
Rahul is your first love...
...and no one understands
first love more than I do.
You were going to give this
all up for me? Stupid!
How can I come between
this love...
...that was never mine
in the first place?
And anyway, someone told
me that...
...I'm so handsome,
I can get anyone.
Aman I...
- What are you saying...?
Go...