Lady, it's you?
I'm Ling.
I'm the one who gave you your name.
Do you remember me?
Did I scare you?
Lots of thread.
It's getting longer and longer.
What do you get?
This dragon is nicely sewn.
The Dragon matches the Phoenix.
Go on,
see what else can be pulled out!
I've made a mistakes.
I'll help you.
There are 2 dragons now.
Dragon against dragon,
here comes a jealous phoenix.
I didn't come for you actually.
But I do want to look for you.
Now, I've found you.
Is this your room?
Are you married?
Someone's coming.
We'll take a revenge for Chimp.
Maybe Dawn's discovered me.
So he sends somebody for me.
Now you are in danger too.
It's hard for me
to talk to you like this.
Why not take advantage of that.
Let me take you out.
Let's check in different direction.
Disguise yourself.
As they have not yet arrived.
Let's go with the hookers,
so they can't find us.
Just relax, I've looked around.
No one is coming, let's take a rest.
We can have a good look of this moon.
I'm bringing along with your bottle.
Why don't you talk?
Are you Japanese?
Human's language has
too much meaning.
Someone likes flattering!
This is what trouble come from.
The men!
How you know what I'm talking?
We are grown in the troubled world.
When we join in the troubled world,
we grow older and older.
People love to seize their power.
But I prefer drinking!
I don't think you'd understand it,
now or in future.
So we'll never have hatred.
If everybody is like us.
We don't have to leave for peace.
I'll fix it.
Chief, what's the matter?
I came from the capital city.
What are you trying to do?
There's a cliff over there.
Miss.
Where are we?
Fortunately,
it is not made with fine steel.
Oh no.
Time to eat.
Is that you?
Don't talk
or there won't be a meal for you.
Sun Moon Sect conquers the world.
Long live the Sect.
Long live the Sun Moon Sect.
Why don't you kill Ling?
I have my plans.
He came here to look for one person.
For her?
For her!
For me?
Not moving.
Here's some meat.
Wu!
Master Wu!
I've found you finally!
God blessed!
God really helps!
How dare you fool me! Go to hell!
You don't dare to kill me.
Make fun on me? Go to hell.
Wu?
Master Wu!
So terrible!
You are Master Wu?
Don't be scared!
Dawn locked my bone...
to forbid me using martial arts.
He only gives me water.
He just tortures me!
Stop! Let's go out and continue.
Wu!
You know him? That's great!
Kneel down! Betrayer.
Don't be scared!
He can do nothing to us.
Cause Damn locked his martial arts!
Take him to get our reward!
Lock him up!
Master Wu!
Ling, I'll kill Wu, if you come near.
Essence Absorbing stance?
We're forced by Dawn.
Please forgive us.
They are forced.
You can't call me Chief.
Just let them go!
I'm back!
- Brother.
- Ling?
Father.
Welcome back.
Long live to Chief!
Zen.
Tell all my fellows now,
I'm back.
Tell them the truth
and arrest the betrayers.
Chief!
I'm afraid it'd be useless.
What's justice then?
Justice depends on power!
Someone believes that,
Iike Cloud,
he didn't come for 10 days.
His legs were broken by Dawn,
and was thrown to Regret Cliff
to guard the graves.
Bao objected
the cooperation with Japanese,
he was forced to admit guilty
and was poisoned.
Tung disappeared over 20 days.
I think the copse towed
by the wolf was him.
Chiu was executed.
His crimes were written on tombstone
to be scolded by the fellows.
And Young, your loyal fellow...
Young?
What did they do to him?
He was the first one to follow Dawn.
He is in-charge
of the execution dept now.
He keeps on investing us.
The fellows are all scared.
These 2 hooks,
are designed by him...
to lock you up.
Chief, The Martial Arts of Dawn
improved a lot.
Compare with us, I think...
Stop!
Are you scared?
Chief. In order to find you.
Zen ruined his face and voice
to get into the gypsies camp.
Tried so hard to contact with Ying.
He just wanted to save you.
Wu is always a hero.
I'd never say surrender.
Dawn, I'd kill you one day.
I'll cut your body into pieces.
I won't let you die so easy.
I want you to become a cripple!
Ling!
What's the matter?
It's our holy job
to kill the bad eggs.
We'd co-operate together.
To kill the bastard!
If you promise me...
I can share reign with you.
Wu, I'll go to Ox Mountain.
With my brothers.
I think, I can't help you.
No justice at all!
But our blood lost would be revenged.
Dad!
I'd return these hooks to Dawn,
I swear!
- Someone's coming.
- Watch out.
Dig... l want your eyeballs!
Your heart, your lung.
I've got it.
Who's it?
Come here.
Sacred Volume!
Give it to me.
I'm in your side, Wu.
Same side? I was betrayed
by the one in my side.
Ling, you deserve it.
It's you who make such trouble.
We break even.
I'm not the one who is going to lose.
We'll leave tomorrow.
I'm not involved
in any of your business.
I won't disclose your secret.
I swear.
Brother, what's the matter?
Dad!
Ling, come to me in midnight.
To ask Ying to marry him.
He decided to stay,
so he is on our side.
Kiddo, something's wrong.
You must be kidding!
Ying, won't go with me.
I won't get involved
into world business for Ying.
I won't tell this joke to anyone.
So you can relax.
Luckily, it's a joke.
You know we will
get out of the world business.
Martial art is meaningless to me.
If you don't trust me.
Destroy my martial arts.
Destroy your martial arts?
Wu, you heartless guy.
Don't get close to me!
He knows Essence of Absorb Stance.
Well! I'll destroy your martial arts.
Dad, don't think that
I'm fallen in love with Ling.
I use him to work for us only.
I'm the Chief.
If I marry the stranger,
I'll suicide before you.
Brother!
Don't be scared, the joke is over.
Kiddo, since we can't sleep.
Pack up and sing.
We'll leave at dawn.
I've got it.
It's difficult to walk at night.
Ling, you'd go first.
I can't see you. I cannot your heart.
I'll accompany Wah's students
to go at dawn.
- What happened just...
- I know it!
I offended the Mainlanders.
Thank you for saving my dad.
I won't see you off.
I understand.
Take care.
Chief...
Why don't you ask him
where he is going?
He won't come back.
If you don't, I'll go and chase him.
So you won't be regret!
Wine! I've forgot to bring it along.
There'd be mine!
I've got it!
I'll go and search for good wine.
It's over!
Chief,
I'm instructed to draw the map.
To celebrate your attack
in 3 days later.
Wish you'd become our new emperor.
Your look?
Don't be scared!
Your voice changed!
Isn't it because of Sacred Volume?
No matter what I'd be changed to,
I won't forget you.
What a beautiful world.
Making heroes compete for the world.
You'd understand now.
Why I don't sleep with you.
Give me the Sacred Volume.
I will burn it.
Take it to me.
I'll give you my treasure,
the Sacred Volume.
You want to burn it?
Murderer.
Volume!
You are just the same
as the common people.
You're heartless.
Chief, I'm wrong.
- I'll follow you forever.
- You won't.
Go now!
I'm puzzled now.
I prefer dying
to be abandoned by you.
Who is it?
Ling!
You can speak our language!
I'm bored
so I want to drink with you.
But I can't guess you're...
What a coincidence.
I'm bored
because of the unpredictable world.
Since it's unpredictable, let's stop.
Will leave here tomorrow.
Leave the business to somebody else.
You are willing to die for me?
No!
I want you to stay with Ling for me.
Life is like morning dew, it's hard
for me to find a true friend.
Come on.
Don't let him discover
that your take.
Remember me always.
I am coming.
Where are you?
I am here.
- Wine, please.
- Ling!
I didn't know your name.
Cici.
Cici?
You've crying.
Life is so short
and so hard to predict.
We're in the same boat.
All I want is only one night,
please stop asking.
Long live...
I'm so glad that the outsiders
and fellows are all loyal to me now.
Chief, your voice differs...
I've been successful
in practicing the supernatural power.
Our invasion to the North.
And our kingdom will come true soon.
Invincible Dawn?
Wu, that old fox is useless now.
He'll ruin my plan only.
I've to kill him
and his followers all.
Yes, sir.
Stab the needle into the artery.
Close his sinus.
"The seas laugh,
lashing on both shores."
"Carried in the waves,
we have only the here and now."
"The heaven laugh at
the troubled world."
"Only they know,
who is to win and lose."
"The mountains laugh,
the rain is affair."
"When the waves grew old,
the world still goes on."
"The clean winds laugh,
such a feeling of solitude."
"My sentiments remain
laughing still."
"The earth laughs, solitude no more."
Those swordsmen treasure
their swords more than their lives.
Why don't you treasure your swords?
We'll retreat tomorrow.
So there is no use for us to have it.
Why don't you take the garlic
and season the food?
Don't be that anxious!
Drink less!
Don't miss our trip tomorrow.
Anything else you don't think
its convenient to say?
No.
I just want to sing "Hero of Heroes"
with you till dawn.
Come!
Let's continue.
"The seas laugh,
lashing on both shores."
"Carried in the waves,
me have only the here and now."
May I ask, who is the hero of heroes?
Blue Phoenix!
Blue Phoenix,
aren't you chasing Ling?
Go!
It's the wind
Dad!
- I smell blood!
- Blood?
There is trouble with Blue Phoenix.
"The Slaying Sword".
"The Whirlwind Blow".
"The Flying Bomb".
Don't you want to escape?
- Go out and have a look.
- Where is Kiddo?
- He is outside.
- Where is my sword?
The sword's so hot.
Take Blue Phoenix to leave first.
I know you are here, Dawn.
Wu, we haven't seen for half years.
You must be upset for
being defeating by my trap.
When you discovered
I'd got the Sacred Volume.
You afraid that I'd be successful
in practicing supernatural power.
So you must kill me.
Therefore, I'd take this risk.
To take action before you,
seize your position.
And establish
my own kingdom of Highlanders.
I'd be a historical hero,
I'd thank you Wu.
Your voice told me you were not Dawn.
Who are you?
Supernatural power
from Sacred Volume.
Hot sword!
Your sword is stabbed into the hen.
It's edible now.
You've mistaken my sword.
- You said you don't want it anymore.
- Take it here.
How can you be so scared
when facing the enemies!
All rubbish!
Chief, come! We have company.
Blue Phoenix.
She is seriously hurt!
Take her in quickly!
Chief!
Cici...
Ling?
Long live to Japan.
"The Flying Bomb".
"The Whirlwind Blow."
"Essence Absorbing stance!"
Zen.
Blue Phoenix is seriously hurt!
- Master Wu.
- Luke, don't go there.
Japanese Gypsies,
it's a mistake to follow Dawn.
You are defeated by the Chief.
You are not qualified
to challenge him.
Chief, I think Dawn has come.
He maybe nearby.
We can drag the Wah students down.
Don't stay with us, go quickly!
Let's go together.
Our feud is too deep.
We can't leave like you do.
Blue Phoenix is seriously injured.
Please take her away with you.
You had better go now,
find some herbs to cure her.
Or, it'd be too late.
Blue Phoenix, if you come back
and see our corpses.
You'd take a revenge for us.
Go! Hurry up!
Well, let's depend a fate.
Let's go!
Take care.
"The Slaying Sword".
Essence Absorbing stance!
"The Flying Bomb".
"Powerful Hand stance".
"Division"
"Essence Absorbing Stance".
Timber.
Tell us, where is Dawn?
I won't tell a word!
Dawn, come out!
Kill! I want to kill...
Dad! Stop! you've not yet recovered.
Chief! There's a long way ahead,
why not revenge later?
For Sun Moon Sect,
just swallow your pride now.
I beg you!
I've enough!
Hurry up!
Wu, I'm coming.
Did she hurt you?
I'll take a revenge for you.
Take Blue Phoenix away,
don't let brother come back.
Go! Kiddo!
Are you retreated?
- Bull shit! Sword position.
- Yes...
Isn't it lnvincible Dawn?
Dawn should be a man.
Scum bag.
You are trapped! Wu has gone.
Brother.
There is fire over the lnn.
Shit! Would Wu do anything
to our brothers?
I got to go back and check that out.
Cici, I'll come back for you at dawn.
I want to go with brother.
I don't go to Ox Mountain.
If you see Ling,
tell him not to wait for me.
I've broken through my sinus.
The poisoned blood is
running through my whole body.
I can't be cured.
I want to die together with Dawn.
Blue Phoenix...
Should we stop singing
"Hero of Heroes".
Blue Phoenix! We'd be hurry.
I'll find a doctor to cure you.
I'll take you to Ox Mountain.
Let's retreat.
Chief, I haven't left you.
I'm happy.
I've waited for your return.
Sing, let's sing!
"The seas laugh..."
Brother.
You are already secluded.
Goodbye.
Ling, you can't even
understand the world.
Your enemies
are afraid of your revenge.
Even you hide yourself,
they won't let you go.
Dawn!
30 thousand of Dawn's fellows
has been sent to Blackwood Cliff.
They are waiting for
further instruction.
He wants to be emperor.
We'll go to Blackwood Cliff
may be we won't be back.
Dawn has the power
from Sacred Volume.
How deep is his Martial Arts?
You should understand other.
Ling, do you want to
look at the Sacred Volume?
What is it?
Would you let me have a look?
Take it.
We are in the same boat now.
Great!
I've got this Sacred Volume...
together with Dawn.
I knew he was aggressive.
He wanted to own it.
I copied one set.
"To practice the supernatural power,
one'd cut his penis off."
Cut his penis off...
Wu!
Dawn is so smart and clever.
He torture me.
But at last, he won't let himself go!
To practice the supernatural power,
he's willing to cut his penis.
He isn't a man now!
For this Sacred Volume.
Our Master betrayed us.
Thus we decided to leave for peace.
Leave for peace?
Ling!
If your next generation can't stand
the Martial Arts temptation.
And leave you
to be the sword man again.
Can you stop them?
Next generation?
I've never dreamt of it.
Swordsman! Once there is people,
once there is feud.
With feud,
there is another troubled world.
Eventually, man is troublesome.
How can you claim you want peace?
Sun Moon Sect conquers the world.
Long live the sect.
Long live the Sun Moon Sect.
Long live the Sect.
Wu is going to attack...
Blackwood Cliff.
The guards have been killed.
They'll soon be here.
They are just small potatoes.
They have arrived.
I'm going to destroy those betrayers!
Only those
who obey me can keep their lives!
Swaying sword!
Cool's sword!
Attacking sword!
Cici!
Ling!
Are you Dawn?
Sure.
Kidding!
Ying!
Why don't you greet your uncle?
No, you'd call her auntie.
The Mainlanders bully the Highlanders.
Now you bring Mainlanders
to Black Wood Cliff...
to interfere the internal business
of Sun Moon Sect.
How can you face your ancestors?
You allied with the Japanese Gypsies
to kill our fellows.
And you dare to
mention our ancestors!
If the Highlanders can
rule the Mainlanders.
Dawn will be famous forever.
Shut up.
But before the duel, I want to know.
Did you sleep with me that night?
Brother, you...
You slept together?
Smile!
We are grown in the troubled world.
But we are getting older and older.
The people want to compete for reign.
Why not drink instead of fight?
Sacred Volume is a big joke.
You are now famous.
What is the guy, man or woman?
How can you sleep with him?
Kiddo,
let's end up all the thing today.
You know it's our Sect's business.
Why you go against me with them?
I take the revenge for my brothers.
Take revenge?
I haven't killed
any of your brothers.
I saw you kill them.
Actually, the Wah students
are not linked with you.
They were killed of no reason.
You'd pay for your life.
Be careful!
Essence Absorbing Stance.
Your dog is killed by you.
Time to pay back.
Kiddo.
Chief!
Your honour.
Watch my hook!
Take it back.
I thought you learned
this because of the throne.
Indeed you do it because of a man!
You are jealous
because I can take both.
Do you think that
all people would listen to you?
It's a pity
that Ling's his Ying and Carol.
You'd be the third if he wants you.
Betrayer!
Father!
Ling, life is really unpredictable...
and so, we don't need to predict it.
Let's get out of here tomorrow.
Essence Absorbing Stance.
Father!
Danger.
Ling, I'm sincere,
so I'm not in full strength.
How dare you try your very best
to hurt me?
Answer your lover!
Stop attacking your allies.
Why didn't you attack
his weakest point?
You don't want to, do you?
Don't talk about love between us.
We've hatred only.
Hatred?
For revenge, or for the girls?
You heartless guy!
I want you to see them die...
in front of you.
Supernatural power
from Sacred Volume.
The wall will fall soon.
Hurry up, to the roof!
It is not safe here!
Dawn!
The whirling sword!
Merciful hand!
Attacking sword!
The reverting sword!
Who can you save?
Combination on 4 stances.
Kiddo!
Why do you save me?
I want to ask you...
Did I stay with you that night?
I won't tell you,
I want you to remember me.
I want you to regret
for your whole life.
Cici!
- Cici!
- Ling...
Tell me, you are Cici.
Sun Moon Sect
will unite the whole world.
Long live...
Wu, our Chief!
It's another Dawn.
- Hang Dawn up!
- Yes.
Please forgive us
- Yang, kneel!
- Yuan, kneel!
- Lee, kneel!
- Chi, kneel!
Seto, kneel!
Bring the betrayer of Dawn here.
- And kill!
- Yes!
Those betrays me should be killed!
- Zen!
- Chief Wu.
Anybody else in the list?
Fan, Ching, Lin,
Lui, Hoi, Cheung,
Lee, Kan, Win...
Wu, Tung, Yang, kneel!
- Ling!
- Ying.
Ling, go now!
What's the matter?
You are on the list.
Dad trusts no Mainlander.
Dad holds the power again.
He won't let you go.
I'll lead you to the exit.
Who else can be trust?
Ling, follow me, quick!
Run!
The boat is leaving.
Take the tea to the boat.
Ling, you can't go to Ox Mountain.
He won't let you go.
The gov't is going to arrest you.
You want to retreat.
The only way is to go to Japan.
What? Japan?
What are you going to do?
This is brought by you.
I cannot play your favorite song.
Take it back.
Ling!
Zen!
Ling, our Chief wants you back.
If not, leave me your head.
I'll do it!
- Ying!
- I'm fine.
Willow sword.
What do you mean?
If I lose, I won't blame anymore.
Come on!
I'll stop playing any competition.
Zen!
Ling, I can't arrest you.
I can't finish my job,
I'd cut my arm.
But I envy you,
for you can leave here.
Go now! Someone's coming.
The ship is ready.
Please leave me alone.
Go!
Ying, let's go together?
Your father won't let you go.
But I am his daughter,
I'd stay with Sun Moon Sect.
The ship'd leave, hands off.