''From Arthur Kahn to Tom Sanders.
''Product Name: Arcamax CD-ROM.
''Considering the merger, l thought
you should get this at home:
''Arcamax production lines running
at 29% despite all efforts.
''Spot-checks on dada dada....
''Speaking of the merger, are
you rich and famous yet?
''Congratulations in
advance on your promotion.
''Arthur.''
Dad, you got E-mail.
l`m not a pain in the ass,
l`m being a lawyer.
There`s a difference.
No more computer games, Matt, it`s time
for school. Eliza, where are you?
You got E-mail.
Tom, Matt`s got toothpaste
all over himself!
lf you can`t get them ready for
school, don`t say you`ll do it.
You`re welcome.
l`m here.
- And Liza needs a jacket.
- l know she needs a jacket!
A jacket doesn`t go, dad.
Wear a sweatshirt.
That`s for girls, a white sweatshirt.
Since when?
Leave me alone.
Put your jacket on.
Ariel doesn`t have a father.
She has two mothers.
That`s interesting.
He`s in a hotel with his secretary
patched in from New York...
...while l`m brushing Cheerios
from my file folders.
lt`s insanity.
Put your jacket on.
Put this on, sweetie.
You can take it off at school.
Listen to your mom.
Matt, did you pee?
l don`t know why you said you`d
help me today, with your promotion.
What`s dad got around his neck?
You don`t know what this is?
lt`s a tie.
Dad`s getting a promotion.
- Dad, you got an E-mail.
- Thanks, honey. Let`s go.
We`re late.
Did you get the Disneyland tickets?
With everything l have to do?
lt`s just one call.
Who are they for?
Mohammed Jafar. He`s foreman
of the Malaysian plant.
You`re the one person l know who
sucks up to the people below you.
Matt, don`t kick the seat.
- What`s on your tie?
- Toothpaste.
- Let`s go.
- Your tie shouldn`t look like a bib.
Hi, Cindy, what`s up?
Garvin came by the office this morning?
About the promotion?
Matt, will you stop that?
He was surprised l was late?
What does that mean?
Did he say it in passing,
or like he really meant it?
l wonder why Garvin came by
the office at 8 in the morning?
To congratulate you.
He treats everyone like dirt--
Except the top guys.
When this merger with
Conley-White goes through...
...and they spin off our division...
...we`re going to be rich.
We`re already rich.
No, l mean...
...really rich.
My grandmother used to say:
''Don`t climb up there too close
to God, He might shake the tree.''
Tom!
Thanks for this morning.
Smaller, faster, cheaper, better.
Remember
lugging the first ones around?
People were amazed. lt was like
showing a Polaroid to a bushman.
Now, if it`s bigger than a credit
card, it`s too inconvenient.
Keeps you on your toes.
Eddie, it`s Tom. Cindy said you called.
Sure, l can hold.
How`s the job search?
28 years at lBM. Did l
tell you what they told me?
l was ''surplussed.''
Ever hear that word?
What`s going on down there?
What? That`s crazy.
They should`ve said, ''sodomized.''
They`re not going to sell the
Austin plant. That`s just a rumor.
You don`t see it coming. You go along,
and then one day there`s no room.
No more room for you.
Smaller, faster, cheaper, better.
l won`t mention names. l`m just telling
you, it`s not true. lt`s a rumor.
l was making 150 a year. Big money.
lt`s probably what you make, huh?
Hang on.
Why don`t you call Cindy...
...make an appointment.
l`ll see if l can help.
Eddie, they are not
going to sell Austin.
lf l`m telling you, who else
are you going to believe?
Cindy.
Pretty name.
Used to have fun with the girls.
Nowadays they want your job.
Good morning.
- What did Garvin say? Should l see him?
- He didn`t say.
He growled.
He was flirting. Did you get Arthur?
He`s standing by on the DVL.
Lunch with Conley-White is at noon.
We`ll probably have those
sandwiches with the crusts cut off.
Their jaws were wired shut
at the same prep school.
The merger`s still happening?
You heard something?
No.
Just, l....
What`s on your tie?
Garvin didn`t mention my promotion?
You said you`d be early today.
People from ''Father of the Year''
didn`t call?
No.
That`s a joke.
5 seconds to Malaysia.
Should l close the door?
Do l ever ask that?
Never.
Malaysian video linkup.
You look good. Awake.
What`s wrong with Arcamax?
The drives are very slow. We`re
getting seek times in the 140-160 range.
140 isn`t a sexy CD player anymore.
Everyone has 140.
My guys think there`s a
compatibility problem...
...between the controller chip
and the driver`s software.
That`ll put us back a year.
The screen flickers. The current cuts
in and out. lt`s a design problem.
What do you mean?
All laptops have the same design.
l sent you out some drives.
You should get them today.
This is bad, Arthur.
How could this happen?
Going to bury it until the merger?
Don`t you say anything.
Does anyone else know?
l`m a grave. What,
are you kidding, Tom?
l still think, really, that
Arcamax will be a major, major hit.
l`ll call you when l see the drives.
Did you get the macadamia nuts?
Good night, Arthur.
They are so good.
He`s off the phone. l got to go.
Do you know a Meredith Johnson?
- Yes, years ago.
- She wanted to see you.
She`s here for the lunch.
The entire company came for this lunch?
Garvin brought up the Operations Group.
Meredith is in Operations?
What should l tell her?
Bad day, in-laws in town?
l`m going to see Lewyn about
the 900s. Stop worrying.
lf there was bad news Garvin
would`ve sent Phil Blackburn.
Phil.
Are you coming to see me?
No. Why?
Nothing. How are you?
How are you, Tom?
You look all beat up.
l do?
You`re letting it get to you.
Don`t take it personally.
Take what personally?
Maybe it`s just a rumor.
What`s a rumor?
l don`t want to spread rumors.
That`s how these things get started.
You mean Austin?
Who said that?
What am l missing?
l can`t believe he didn`t tell you.
He`s so perverse.
Tell me what?
So, how`s Susan?
Susan`s good.
- How`s Lonnie?
- Great.
- Did you know she got tenure?
- That`s great.
Here`s my stop.
l tried to explain to Garvin.
You know him, he`s like a child.
Fuck your feelings if they
interfere with his surprise.
- What surprise?
- Rumor is you`re getting passed over.
So l`m not getting the VP job?
That`s the rumor.
Rumors are always true.
Garvin didn`t say anything?
Came by the office. l was late,
Susan had a conference.
- You were late? Today?
- Why`re you in Seattle?
Good to see you again.
Somebody tells Garvin l was talking to
you.... You know how he is about leaks.
Leak? l thought it was a rumor.
lt was different before.
l could watch your back.
Who gets the job, Stephanie Kaplan?
Rumor is he went outside the group.
You`d still head up Manufacturing...
...presumably.
Wait a minute.
l might be out of a job?
Don`t get paranoid.
l`m a quick learner.
You wouldn`t make someone VP and
not let them appoint their own team.
How would that look?
Am l out of a job?
Come on, Tom.
l`m already out on a limb.
Are you okay? You want a Prozac?
No, l`m fine.
l`m disappointed, but l`m fine.
You sure?
Don`t worry about me. l`m a
stockholder. Whatever`s...
...best for the company...
Leave a message for Susan, Tom,
Matt and Eliza, after the beep.
Thanks for calling. Bye.
- Obviously, he`s disappointed.
- But he took it well?
Overall, l`d say yes.
No bumps before the merger.
l don`t want him quitting.
lt`s up to you.
Just one big happy family.
You got that?
l have to say, going down to see
him this morning was a masterstroke.
lt really put him on the defensive.
l`ll keep an eye on him.
He`ll get on the program.
When push comes to shove,
he has no guts.
Let me ask you something.
You know Susan.
lf l heard a rumor about the...
...future of the company...
...my future...
...you know, nothing crazy,
a real rumor...
...what would Susan say?
You think she`d say to see Garvin?
Here`s someone you should meet.
Tom Sanders. He heads up Manufacturing.
Steven Chase, Crescent Capital.
John Conley.
You`re John Conley?
Junior. Dad`s coming on Friday
with members of the Board.
- Catch you at the lunch.
- Tom, come in.
You wanted to see me.
Yeah, sorry about this morning.
You know how kids are.
Have you met Meredith Johnson?
What`s wrong? That`s a
hello you`d give to a rash.
l`m preoccupied. lt`s not you.
We go way back. He broke my heart.
She`s making that up.
l thought your heart
was made of plastic.
He said l could be anything l wanted.
- He was right.
- lt was a line.
- lt wasn`t a line.
- l didn`t know you were acquainted.
Wilde said, ''l like a man with a
future and a woman with a past.''
l heard you were in Operations.
l don`t know. Am l?
The last few years l`ve been cleaning
up the mess Bob made of this company.
lf it`s such a mess, why am l so rich?
Yes, but you`re a lot richer now.
We should catch up. Get together.
l`d love that.
Plenty of time now.
Flying over Wyoming, l
thought the merger was dead.
Conley was choking on the valuation.
The spin-off was Meredith`s idea.
Conley thinks it was their idea.
- Really?
- Lit them up like a Christmas tree.
She saved the merger.
You have money now.
You can even buy a new tie.
So, what was it you
wanted to see me about?
Meredith-fucking-Johnson!
Son-of-a-bitch. Goddamn Garvin.
- What happened?
- l didn`t get it.
- You`re not the new VP?
- He announced it?
lt was a secret. He`s got
her installed in the office...
...bouncing quips back and forth.
Who?
- Who`s she?
- Will this affect the spin-off?
She doesn`t know the difference
between software and a sweater.
What aren`t you telling us?
l might be out of a job.
You know what it`s like out there?
What about the spin-off?
They didn`t tell me about me!
Would they tell me about the spin-off?!
l`m sorry.
This is the worst day of my life.
All right?
Who is she?
Let me guess: attractive?
What does that matter?
Nipples like pencil erasers?
She`s attractive. Very attractive.
Sleeping with Garvin?
That`s why he got a Nordic Track.
lt`s a curse to be me.
Life holds no surprises.
This is such a cliche.
How do you think a
cliche becomes a cliche?
You mean like, ''Size doesn`t matter''?
l have a thing for you.
All right, please, can
we get some work done?
We got a small problem with Arcamax.
- lt`s not the design.
- lt`s not the code.
Any woman must be twice as good as
a man and work harder for less pay.
Cliche grande.
How does a cliche become one?
lt is very weird. We know
nothing about this woman.
l do.
l had a thing with her.
You are amazing.
lt was years ago.
You`ve seen more ass than a rental car.
Get a few more women in your
life so you can be a census.
Maybe you can sleep your way up.
Right.
Wait, why? Why her and not Tom?
He`s not attractive?
Men and women are different.
Not in a way that matters to you.
Are you saying l`m a virgin?
Meanwhile, you were asking
me about the spin-off.
Garvin said it was her idea.
lt`s always such a
pleasure to come here...
...and be with the
Advanced Products Group.
l feel such a warmth
for the people here.
l feel a kinship. And l`ve
always wanted to give you...
ls this seat taken?
...the most advanced original
leadership that l could.
How are you?
- Sorry you didn`t get the promotion.
- l`m sorry you didn`t get it either.
How long have you known?
Really? That long?
Every time l`ve wanted
to promote a woman...
...to break the glass ceiling...
...it`s always the same story:
''But, Bob.... But, Bob....''
l`ve thought about it often since my
daughter`s death, that had she lived...
...it would be extremely rare...
...that she ever got to run a company.
So it has a special meaning
for me when l tell you...
...that when we announce the merger...
...we will also announce the new VP
for Advanced Operations and Planning...
...in Seattle...
...will be Meredith Johnson.
Unbelievable.
Thanks, Bob. Can l have the lights?
The Advanced Products Group has been the
heart of DigiCom for the last 10 years.
Advanced Products has historically
consisted of 4 divisions:
You seem to be spending
more time up here.
My son`s a freshman at the university.
This way l get to see more of him.
l thought it had to do with the merger.
This merger means everything to Garvin.
Give a man a $100 million and you
create a frustrated billionaire.
The new compression algorithms
will shift industry standards...
...to full-res digitized
video at 60 fields a second...
...with platform-independent
RlSC processors supported by...
...a 32-bit color-active...
Conley`s a conservative company.
ls Meredith conservative?
l don`t know.
l thought you knew her.
ls there anything you don`t know?
We offer, through technology...
...what religion and revolution
have promised but never delivered:
Freedom from the physical body.
Freedom from race and gender...
...from nationality and personality,
from place and time.
Communicating by cellular
phone and hand-held computer...
...PDA and built-in fax modem...
...we can relate to each
other as pure consciousness.
Smart, touching base with
all the division heads.
She didn`t name them in her speech.
Does it mean something?
Only if she plans to make changes.
Phil said she wasn`t planning
on making any changes.
You know Meredith.
Wait a minute.
l must know, am l out of a job?
What was she bending your ear about?
Stephanie? Nothing. Just small talk.
What, all of a sudden
there`s Stephanie Lite?
She was talking about her
son at the university.
Sorry l didn`t get to mention you.
That`s fine.
l`m jammed all day but why
don`t you come up at 7?
We`ll have a drink and
catch up on business.
Great.
l remember how you liked a good
bottle of wine. l`ll get one.
What`s she want
to see you at 7 about?
Probably the Arcamax problems. We must
discuss it before Conley asks questions.
She doesn`t give you a boner?
Because, you know,
l definitely have lift-off.
What about you? You got a woody?
She`s very nice.
- l`ll let you know what happens.
- Don`t do that.
You have a sexual urge every
20 minutes. lt`s a physical certainty.
lt`s hard-wired into your brain.
You can`t fight it. Why would
you want to? Live a little.
Ten years from now you`ll need
a forklift to get a hard on.
l`ll call you.
l`ll count the minutes.
Where`ve you been all day?
l didn`t get it.
No, they went outside the division.
Someone from Operations.
What can l say? l got passed over.
What can l say?
So, did you get the
tickets for Disneyland?
No, l know, but l promised
the guy and it`s...
Mohammed Jafar.
Thanks a lot. Probably won`t
be home for dinner tonight.
l love you too. Bye.
Are there any asset sale triggers?
ln the indenture?
Will you do me a favor?
Alan, Brown will go 250 on this, easy.
Let`s just do this thing.
Not a bad idea for a girl.
Let`s talk first thing.
`91 Pahlmeyer.
l`ve looked all over for it.
l like all the boys
under me to be happy.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
l brought the files up for
Arcamax if you want to see them.
Show me your pictures.
The diagrams?
Your family. You have pictures?
Yeah, sure.
Here`s.... Here.
That`s Matthew.
That`s Eliza at Halloween.
And here`s Susan with the kids.
She looks like she always
has food in the refrigerator.
- She never lost the baby weight--
- She doesn`t look like a refrigerator.
l mean, she`s made a home for you.
ln my fridge l`ve got some
champagne and an orange.
Doesn`t Eliza look pretty?
She looks like Susan.
lt can be inhibiting.
- What`s that?
- Domesticity.
You`d be surprised.
You can`t jump her from behind...
...because you get excited by the
way she bends to pick up the soap.
Remember that?
l remember that.
And you miss it.
There`s compensations.
Of course. Life`s a
series of trade-offs.
l wouldn`t trade what l have.
l wouldn`t want you to.
That`s exactly why l can trust you.
You have more to lose than l do.
l`ll bring you up to speed on
the problems with the drives.
You kept in good shape, Tom.
Nice and hard.
Thank you.
lt`s different now.
You`re my boss.
lt`s different.
Okay.
Rub my shoulders and l`ll
listen to your problems.
The specs and the seek times
call for 100 milliseconds.
We have that on the prototypes.
But the drives coming off-line--
- Are the drives here?
- lt might be a chip.
- Answer my question.
- l`m trying to.
Understand the controller chip
positions the split optics.
l`ll show you the schematic.
No, no, no, no. Rub.
You can`t understand the problem--
- Do you have the drives?
- Arthur sent 5--
- l said no calls.
- lt`s Mr. Garvin.
But after that, nobody.
ls it all right if l leave for the day?
That`s fine, Mrs. Ross.
You`d rather talk about other things...
...than answer my question
because you don`t know.
You don`t know what the problem is.
But you can`t say, ''l don`t know''...
...because in your mind that means
you lose. You`re worthless. Men!
- What will you tell Conley?
- l can`t lie to them.
Talk about the prototypes. They work.
Focus on the positive.
We`re on-line. lt`s not
about the prototypes.
- They want to know if you can build it.
- l understand that--
Do you have a problem working for me?
No.
Hi, Bob.
You don`t want to hear
about my hard day.
Yes, that`s hard work.
Let me get my docs together.
The merger is about people, not Arcamax.
They`re comfortable with me and Bob.
This isn`t about some CD-ROM
that`ll be obsolete in a year.
lf they ask, then you
tell them you don`t know.
Hi, Bob, l`m here.
l`ve got a great idea about that.
Go ahead.
Lewyn, this is Sanders.
l`ve discussed the drives with Meredith.
She says don`t tell the Conley people...
...until we know exactly
what the problems are.
That is the line for the 8 a.m.
meeting tomorrow--
Let`s get down to business.
Wait a sec, wait a sec.
Meredith, wait a second.
- There, was that so bad?
- That`s not so bad, it`s just--
Come on, while there`s still
a chance we might get caught.
No, no.
Oh, yes, l think so.
Some things never change, and
some things just get better.
Meredith, come on.
- Remember all the things we did?
- l remember.
Things nobody knows about you but me.
All our secrets.
Just lie back and let me take you.
l could have anybody and l picked you.
Now you`ve got all the power.
You`ve got something l want.
Doesn`t that make you feel good?
Don`t stop me. Come on.
Don`t worry, l`m not going to bite.
Let me do whatever l want.
You just lie back and
let me be the boss.
Wait a second. Wait a second.
Wait a minute.
What?
Look, nobody has to know.
Nobody gets hurt.
lt`s just a meeting
between two colleagues.
Just another dull day in
the computer business.
No, honey.
Don`t!
Here.
- Want to get fucked?
- Do it.
ls that what you want?
Come on.
You just stay hard.
Oh, God.
You bad boy.
Come on, baby.
Come on. You going to fuck me?
You going to fuck me?!
Put it in.
God, look at us.
Go inside me.
Come on.
- l can`t do this.
- Do it.
l won`t.
Now!
- l`m not going to do this!
- Now!
You can`t just stop!
- Come on.
- No! Goddamn!
You stick your dick in my mouth
then get an attack of morality?
This never happened.
You never used to be this way.
l have a family now.
A family made you stupid.
You take those two champagne
bottles in your refrigerator...
...and fuck them.
You son-of-a-bitch.
You get back here and
finish what you started.
You hear me?
Do you?
Come back and finish what
you started or you are dead!
You are fucking dead!
Shit, it`s dead.
You are hereby notified that we
will hold your client liable--
l didn`t hear you come in.
l`m going to take a shower.
- No kiss?
- l just feel kind of shitty, you know.
Screw them.
- They don`t deserve you.
- Can you get me a beer?
Thanks. Before l forget,
could you do me a favor?
The cellular`s battery`s dead.
Sure. l thought they were
supposed to last all day?
l thought so.
Who`s Meredith Johnson?
What?
Meredith Johnson.
She called just before you got home.
She called?
Yeah, about 10 minutes ago.
She said the 8 a.m.
had been pushed back to 8:30.
- Who is she?
- She`s the one, the new VP.
She`s the one?
She came from the Valley.
How old is she?
l don`t know. 33, maybe.
That`s young for that job.
- Had you ever heard of her?
- She`s a face guy.
She made the merger happen. Now
she`s Garvin`s fair-haired...whatever.
Where`d she come from?
Has she any technical background?
No. That`s the thing with the merger.
Everything`s changed.
That`s not the worst thing in the world.
She`ll crash and burn.
Then they`ll appreciate you.
Things aren`t easy out there.
So quit...
...rather than let them treat you badly.
We might lose everything,
including the stock options.
l don`t care about stock options.
l`ll work full-time.
l`m capable of supporting our family.
Just trying to help.
You`re too nice sometimes.
l don`t need you to fight
my battles for me, thanks.
Right now some lucky girl in
the building will come after me.
l deserve that, but ask yourself...
...why does a man go with another
girl? He`s unhappy at home.
Because he`s lonely.
But that was before you, Fran.
l`ve stopped running.
Why are you wearing a T-shirt?
You never do.
l don`t know. Just a little cold.
What are you going to do?
Grin and bear it, like l usually do.
And hope it doesn`t get worse.
Morning.
Morning, Bob.
That`s a nice suit.
Nice fabric.
Can l feel it?
What is that? Wool?
With a little bit of viscose.
That`s what makes the
pants drape so well.
You work out?
When l get a chance, Bob.
lt`s been busy lately.
l`ve always liked you.
Now you have the power.
You have something l want.
Come on.
The computer takes the
information from the database...
...and constructs an environment
that is projected in the headset.
When the user walks on
the pad, he or she...
...feels like they`re walking in a hall
with drawers of files on all sides.
The user can stop, open any file...
...and look at the data. The laser
scanners are for body representation.
- That`s amazing.
- lt`s cool, isn`t it?
Where is everyone?
They left 15 minutes ago.
Don Cherry`s demo-ing the Corridor.
The meeting`s at 8:30.
No, 7:30. lt got pushed up.
Nobody told you?
lf someone wants to log on with a
regular computer, what they`ll see...
...is a model of themselves with a
photo that`s pulled up from a data file.
Hey, l know you.
The photo bears some
resemblance to me, l admit.
An inside joke here at the company.
We`ve also constructed virtual help.
Users always need on-line help.
We created an angel to help you.
Welcome to the Corridor.
The same face.
Angel...
...how do l open this drawer?
What`s the angel saying?
That`s between them.
We don`t see the Corridor as a
product in the marketplace now.
This is something that we worked
up to demonstrate the potential...
...of virtual reality technology.
This looks good.
Hold on. What`s that?
l believe it`s your financial records.
Turn that damn thing off.
Sorry.
ln the final system there will be
safeguards that will control access.
So glad you could join us.
That was a sweet entrance, my friend.
Did the ferry hit an iceberg? You were
going to call me after meeting Meredith.
l called you from her office.
Left a message.
There was nothing on my machine.
Then you`re late again.
Thank God Meredith
led the discussion.
Hey, pal, l left a message
on your machine, all right?
Check it out.
Did you get my message?
You told Susan the meeting
had been moved to 8:30.
l said 7:30. lf your wife can`t take
a fucking message, get a machine.
- There you go, Mr. Sanders.
- Thank you.
You`re welcome.
Full house today.
Meredith has been getting us
up to speed on the Arcamax.
We`d like your read on it.
Meredith said there are problems.
You might have to go back
to the drawing board.
l`m sorry if l conveyed that
impression to Meredith.
l`m convinced we can
manufacture them.
How many of the drives meet specs?
l don`t have that information with me.
Meredith told us the line is running
at 29%. ls that approximately right?
The seek times are off-specs.
There`s a power flicker in the screen?
- Right?
- That`s right.
With the merger impending,
shouldn`t you have told someone?
The merger isn`t about a CD-ROM
that might be obsolete in a year.
lt`s about people.
- lt`ll be obsolete in a year?
- The promise of the Arcamax...
...was a central factor in this merger.
l may be at fault. Tom said the
problem with the drives was serious.
Not so serious.
Don`t cover up.
- l`m not covering anything up.
- Give us worst case.
We go back to the drawing boards
and we`re down for 9 months.
Nine months?
Meredith said 6 weeks.
Nobody likes to go back to the board,
but it can be an advantage.
ls there a problem?
This isn`t an inquisition.
l feel like l`m pulling teeth.
John just wants to get a handle on
what the problems are with the lines.
- l don`t know is the honest answer.
- Wait a minute.
You are head of Manufacturing.
You are in charge of Arcamax.
There are problems with it...
...that could take 9 months to fix,
which l assume means a year.
And the bottom line is...
...you don`t know?
Goddamn it!
Jesus Christ!
l wanted to see you. lt`s not
going to work out with Meredith.
- Evidently not.
- She set me up.
l saw.
- Sit down.
- Why? What`d l do?
- Please, would you just sit.
Meredith told me about
your meeting last night.
What?
What`d she say?
She wants to handle the intervention
internally, which is best.
- She still cares about you.
- Wait a minute.
What`d she say?
Not to put too fine a point on it,
she said you sexually harassed her.
l sexually harassed her?
- What would you call it?
- She jumped me.
She jumped you? You`re in denial.
That`s typical.
She almost raped me.
You need help. You must
accept responsibility for--
What about this?
What about that?
Looks like she defended herself.
Defended herself? The woman can
kick the shit out of both of us!
- lt may have seemed different to you.
- l didn`t harass her.
She harassed me.
l`ve never heard of a
woman harassing a man.
Why`re you here?
- l`m here as your friend.
- My ass, you`re my friend.
When Garvin finds out about this, he`ll
want to throw you out on your ass.
Let`s keep this quiet.
That`s what Meredith wants too.
Resolve this quickly and quietly.
Want your wife to find out?
We`ll have to tell her at some point.
They`ll get the whole thing and it`ll
be on the front page of the paper!
l`m offering you a chance
to make a new life.
Keep your family out of this mess.
Keep your job.
Obviously, some kind of lateral move.
When you say lateral, you
mean out of the division.
You can`t stay here.
She`s scared out of her wits.
l`m not leaving this division. l spent
10 years here. l built this place.
Now, we got a spin-off going on--
We`re thinking, you know, Austin.
Austin?
l told him what she said.
He said the opposite happened.
He said she harassed him.
What?
He denies it?
You know, the man always denies it.
ls he crazy?
l offered him a move to Austin.
To Austin. That`s like a duck making
a lateral move to '' l`orange.''
He`s too smart for that.
Let`s hope he`s smart enough
to see he has no options.
Take care of this.
This is a bomb we`re sitting on
that can blow everything sky-high.
Meredith is key to the merger. l can`t
have her involved in a sex scandal.
And l won`t say good-bye to
$100 million. You got that?
l get the picture, Bob.
10th floor. Down the hall and right.
There were no witnesses?
Her assistant left earlier in the night.
A cleaning lady was outside the office.
l don`t know what she heard.
- Did you report that to anyone?
- ln the morning, yeah.
What was the company`s response?
They believed her.
They suggested l transfer to Austin.
l heard they`re selling Austin.
The point is, if l go to Austin,
l lose everything, all right?
My stock options,
everything that l worked for.
Did you call anyone
after the incident?
No.
Did you tell your wife?
Oh, boy.
Why not?
l didn`t want to upset her. l felt
guilty being in that situation at all.
How would you characterize
Miss Johnson physically?
She`s very pretty. She was
Miss Teenage New Mexico.
So you kissed.
Yes. And then she began to...rub me.
Rub you where?
You know....
Your penis?
Yes.
And?
l`m uncomfortable talking about it.
- Because l`m a woman?
- You act like it`s a game.
- Why are you here?
- l want to know what my options are.
What your options are?
l want to know whether l can
sue her for sexual harassment.
To do that you must convince a jury...
...you were alone with Miss Teenage
New Mexico and you said, ''no.''
Sexual harassment...
...is not about sex.
lt is about power.
She has it...
...you don`t.
lf you sue, you`ll never get
another job in computers.
lf you don`t, you`ll go to Austin. Sue,
and it`s news. Don`t sue, it`s gossip.
lf you sue, no one will believe you.
lf you don`t, your wife won`t.
They`ll make your life hell for the
3 years until the case goes to trial.
And, for that privilege, it`ll
cost you a minimum of $100,000.
Do you not think it`s
a game, Mr. Sanders?
lt`s a game to them.
How do you feel about losing?
That`s what Meredith wants.
To resolve it, quickly and quietly.
They said she`s not going
to press charges. Why?
She`s accused me. Why stop there?
Why not press charges?
Meredith didn`t press charges...
...because she couldn`t.
DigiCom is planning a
merger with Conley-White.
lt is supposed to happen Friday.
They think that we are as
conservative as they are.
With a scandal, Conley goes to bed with
Katie Couric, wakes up to Jessica Hahn.
Garvin is out $100 million.
l think we might make a
plaintiff out of this guy yet.
No, a potential plaintiff. l don`t
have to sue. l just threaten to sue.
That`s a dangerous game.
Are you willing to play it?
Fuck them.
Now you`re talking my language.
For the next 3 days...
...this loose cannon is in a
position to apply a lot of pressure.
And they on you, Mr. Sanders.
They on you.
Call security. Throw
him out on the sidewalk.
We have to appear to be impartial.
Keep him in his job, keep
paying him, no hassles.
l made Tom Sanders.
Who the hell is he to sue me?
Sexual harassment, under Title Seven.
He`ll file with the Human Rights
Commission if we don`t fire Meredith.
lf he files, it becomes public.
lt`d blow the deal.
We realize that. So does he.
He`s blackmailing us.
This is America, goddamn it.
The legal system is supposed
to protect people like me.
lt gets worse.
His lawyer is...
...Catherine Alvarez.
Great. She`d change her name to ''TV
Listings'' just to get it in the paper.
l`m trying to get them to mediate.
Keep it quiet.
Mediate?
l want you to cut his balls off.
Did he say mediate or
split the difference?
l`m just hoping he`ll agree.
Alvarez will tell him not to.
He`ll agree.
He doesn`t want this public.
We pushed him too hard.
He has nothing to lose.
Really? He hasn`t told his wife yet.
How do you know?
l know Sanders, remember?
He likes secrets.
- l`ll be in diagnostics.
- Where were you?
They`re pulling the drives apart.
- John Levin called.
- John Levin with Sematach?
He said it`s important.
- Why didn`t they come this morning?
- Susan called about the benefit.
- Call her and say--
- She said don`t try to cancel.
- The Lewyns paid for the tickets.
- l`ll be there at 7:30.
Ask her to bring me
a shirt and jacket.
ls everything okay?
Everything is fine, thanks for asking.
l`ll kill Arthur.
We must solve this before Friday
and you just got the drives?!
What is Arthur doing over there?
All he does anymore is give
macadamia nuts to people.
ls he a manager or a stewardess?
- He gave you nuts?
- What`s slowing it down?
Over here.
Let me show you something.
Arthur was right.
There`s a compatibility problem
with the controller chip.
ls it a bug?
Don Cherry debugged Arcamax.
There are no bugs.
Fabrication problem?
What`re you doing?
This is a sophisticated piece of
electronics, not a pickup truck.
How bad is it? We have 4,000
of these. Should l junk them all?
l told Arthur to send 10 in heat-sealed
plastic bags. lt`s a hunch l have.
Do what you can.
l don`t understand it.
ln prototypes, no problem.
ln manufacturing, it falls apart.
Mr. Garvin wants to see you.
He said not to tell anyone.
Catherine Alvarez on two.
Thanks. Could you close the door?
How are you?
Let`s agree to mediate.
l don`t want this getting out either.
lf we get this all over in a week,
my wife needn`t know.
l do not want to tell my wife. l don`t
want to upset her if l don`t have to.
Wait a second.
Guess what?
They locked me out of my computer
and cleaned out my files.
l guess it`s starting.
Come in.
l`m not interrupting?
No, not at all.
Going down?
Don`t tell me you`re scared of me.
l don`t want it to be this way.
Yeah, we could be fucking right now.
- l think of you as a friend.
- Oh, come off it!
You called Blackburn--
Only to beat you to the punch.
l knew you`d play that card.
l wasn`t playing a card.
You were the one that--
Alarm.
This isn`t a game.
You`d have a great job, the spin-off
would make you a millionaire.
We`d have fun.
lt`s not like breaking rocks.
You don`t get it.
Poor Sanders. You have no
idea what you`re up against.
As usual.
By this time tomorrow you`ll
wish you took the Austin job.
We`ll see.
l`m trying to figure out whether
to get a fat Barbie for Eliza.
Mattel makes a fat Barbie?
lt`s called ''Happy to Be Me Barbie.''
Does she come with the
''Happy to Be Divorced Ken''?
l`m serious.
Which is more stigmatizing?
Yeah, Barbie`s stigmatized.
lt`s that whole male,
36-24-36 image of beauty.
Women are oppressed.
Women are oppressed?!
80% of suicides are committed by men.
They`re dropping from heart attacks.
- You`re not as tough.
- Sorry. We`re just fighting the wars.
You start the wars.
l`m sorry. l don`t have
my own crisis hot line.
- You`re taking the Meredith thing well.
- That has nothing to do with it.
What was today`s rumor?
She was once a man?
Just tell her.
Tell her what?
Tell her a lot of us have
worked as hard as you...
...and you`re blowing this merger
for all of us because you fucked up.
What happened?
Who got to you?
lt`s not that simple.
The thought of losing millions happens
to stick right here in my throat.
This was my big shot. lt`s not
like l`m being scouted by the NBA.
What happened?
Who knows? An old girlfriend, a
bottle of wine, a late meeting...
- Fill in the blanks.
- Thanks.
You`re like women who think they`re in
the hotel room, drunk, to watch TV.
Could you possibly be more lame?
For your information, Mark,
Tom told me everything.
Everything that happened.
And l support him 100%.
That is so sweet, but l don`t think--
Let`s not discuss it.
Let`s just enjoy the evening.
Obviously, something happened.
Did you have sex?
- Think first. Because if you`re lying--
- No, l said, no.
She kissed me, and she unzipped
my pants, and-and-and-and-and--
And?
And that was it.
How did it get that far?
- You think l encouraged her?
- Her hand was in your pants?
- Nothing happened.
- How did that happen?
Then she accuses me of
sexual harassment--
- She harassed you?
- You don`t believe me?
Mark doesn`t believe you.
He`s got stock options on the brain.
He`s back-stabbing.
Everybody`s sure you`re
having an affair with Cindy.
- We`re not having an affair.
- How could you let this happen?
- Nothing happened.
- Something happened.
She`s an old girlfriend of yours.
Like l`m surprised. That club`s
as exclusive as the white pages.
- l was going to tell you.
- l can`t believe everyone knew but me.
- Nobody knows it.
- You`re so naive. Of course they know.
l`m old-fashioned. l greet my
inferiors with a handshake.
l`ll handle it.
Jesus.
What does she look like?
She`s attractive.
One to ten.
Eight.
Nine.
What does the company say?
They want me to transfer to
Austin, do some therapy.
Austin?
l`m not moving there.
We`re not moving to Austin.
- l`m pressing charges.
- For what?
Sexual harassment.
We have a mediation tomorrow.
When were you going to tell me?
That`s brilliant.
Show up without your wife.
- l`ll handle it.
- Are you crazy? They`ll destroy you.
- lt won`t go that far.
- lt`ll take over our life.
Depositions and whispering and legal
fees for some damn personal vindication.
And all people remember is that
you were involved in something sleazy.
- Do you have a lawyer?
- Catherine Alvarez.
Great. When are we on Hard Copy?
But if it had happened to you--
You know how many times
it`s happened to me?
- You never said this ever happened--
- You`re so narcissistic.
Nothing happens until
it happens to you.
- You should`ve said something.
- l do what women always do.
l deal with it. Now go in
there tomorrow and work it out.
Right. l should shut up and fuck her.
Apologize and get your job back.
Apologize?!
The children are sleeping.
Wait, l got a better idea.
Why don`t l just admit it?
l`ll be the evil male you all complain
about. Then l can fuck everybody.
Tom, stop it.
Come, l want to dominate you!
You`re scaring her.
l have a urge!
The children!
My children that l
provide for and protect.
They can come between me and my
wife, move us, take my job...
...and take the house we have made! ! !
And l apologize to them, Susan?
They call me a rapist and l
apologize. This is a joke.
Sexual harassment is about power.
When did l have the power?
When?
Good morning, l`m Judge Murphy.
This is a mediation.
Our proceedings are confidential.
Maintain a civil and courteous tone.
Our goal is to determine
the nature of the dispute...
...and how best to resolve it.
The parties have agreed that
Mr. Sanders will speak first...
...and be cross-examined
by Mr. Heller.
Ms. Johnson will speak next, and
be cross-examined by Ms. Alvarez.
Any questions?
Let`s get started.
l had my cellular phone with me,
so when she called Garvin...
...l called Mark Lewyn to give
him the upshot of our meeting.
Then she approached you?
Correct. She took the phone
from me and she kissed me.
Where?
She kissed me in my ear...
...on my neck...
...on my mouth.
She put her tongue in my mouth.
When you asked her to stop, did she?
No, no.
She unzipped my pants...
...and massaged my penis.
- Were you aroused?
- Yes.
Then she slid down...
...and she...
...put my penis in her mouth.
Did you climax?
l grabbed her by the wrists.
l threw her on the ground.
Then l wanted to leave.
Then what did Ms. Johnson do?
She threatened me.
She said, ''You`re dead.''
And then, the next day,
Mr. Blackburn told me that...
...she said that l had
sexually harassed her.
Mr. Heller?
- Mr. Sanders, would you like a break?
- No, l`m fine.
You say the bottle of wine
was Ms. Johnson`s idea?
Yes.
But when you were living
with Ms. Johnson...
...didn`t you discover wines together
on trips to the Napa Valley?
Yes.
Romantic trips?
But you didn`t expect any
romance in her office?
Did you have a conversation
after lunch about how...
...seeing Meredith gave you a...
...boner?
Someone else said that.
lsn`t the term ''boner''
a slang for erection?
You had a conversation about...
...having an erection? A boner?
Yes, but l didn`t say it.
But you laughed.
Yes.
So you condone it.
lt was harmless.
lf it`s harmless...
...why are we here today?
Well, it was just...
...what guys talk about.
About their boners?
Not generally, no.
Yet you expect us to believe that
after having a sexual conversation...
...you weren`t thinking of sex?
That`s correct.
How would you characterize your
prior relationship with Ms. Johnson?
Highly sexual?
l don`t know how to rate it.
Every day?
Sometimes twice a day.
Sex in public places.
Sodomy.
Viewing of pornography.
Vibrators and
other mechanical devices.
Sometimes we sat on the
couch and watched television.
But when you became reacquainted, you
no longer saw her as a sexual object?
- She was just your boss now?
- That`s correct.
And do you admit having an
erection during your meeting?
She had her top open.
lt was an involuntary reflex.
Reflex.
Do you think her gynecologist gets an
erection when he examines her breast?
That`s completely different.
Do you admit putting
your penis in her mouth?
She did.
Oh, l forgot.
You resisted.
Mr. Sanders, during your
rather fantastic testimony...
...there was one moment
that rang true.
You said, and l quote:
''l was angry.
l felt l was being pushed around.''
Correct.
The truth is,
you felt that way all day.
You`d been expecting a promotion and
she got it. You got angry about it.
l felt l deserved the job.
You took that anger up to her office.
You`d show her who`s boss.
That`s not true.
Did you tell your wife about your
7 o`clock meeting with Ms. Johnson?
l had a meeting and l`d be home late.
You expected to be late?
No, but if l got home earlier my
wife would be pleasantly surprised.
So you make it a rule
to lie to your wife?
l didn`t lie.
When you called your wife,
did you tell her that...
...Ms. Johnson was a
former lover of yours?
When you got home, did you
tell her what happened?
No, l hoped it would go away.
You hoped you`d get away with it?
Do not debunk the illusion that this
dispute might be settled amicably.
That`s okay.
l have no further questions.
l asked to see pictures.
l thought if we put it on that basis...
...it would be clear that
things had changed between us.
Do you have those pictures now?
l`d like copies for my file.
You can continue.
He said his wife hadn`t lost all
the weight gained from pregnancy.
His children were beautiful...
...but they made him feel old...
...and seeing me reminded him of
what it was like to be young...
...and marriage was a tough trade-off.
Go on.
My assistant, Mrs. Ross,
asked if she could go home.
l wanted her to stay, but felt guilty.
l`d kept her late for weeks
preparing for my new job.
And where was Mr. Sanders
at that point?
He began to rub my shoulders.
And you let him?
lt was awkward...
...but l thought we`d end the
meeting and leave it at that.
Then he tried to kiss you?
No, Mr. Garvin called and
then l came back to Tom...
...and said that was it, and
then he began to kiss me.
Did you try to stop him?
Yes. l struggled with him and
told him to stop. But he didn`t.
Did he attack you physically?
Yes.
He grabbed me by my hair...
...and forced me down on my knees.
And...
He put his...
...penis in your mouth?
This is making me uncomfortable.
Want some water?
Thank you.
He put his penis in my mouth...
...and said that he was going to...
To fuck you? Were those his words?
He said, ''Do you want to get fucked?''
And then he reached down
and tore off my panties.
What did you do then?
He threw me down on the scaffold
and l kneed him in the groin.
And that was the end of it?
lt`s strange. l`d think my instinct
would be to run, but l became angry.
l yelled at him. Called him names.
Told him l`d kill him.
Just yelling.
How did he react?
He seemed to realize what he`d done.
He pulled up his pants and left.
Did you call anyone afterwards?
No.
l didn`t know what to do.
l kept going over the day in my
mind trying to figure out...
...if somehow this thing was my fault.
You reported it the next day?
Yes.
But you didn`t bring
formal charges. Why not?
l talked to Phil Blackburn.
l knew he was Tom`s friend.
l didn`t want to destroy...
...Tom`s marriage or career, but it`s
clear we couldn`t work together.
l would be too scared.
l`m scared just sitting here.
Nothing further.
Ms. Alvarez.
Ms. Johnson, l just want
to be clear on one thing.
Mr. Sanders suggested
the bottle of wine?
- That`s right.
- But you bought it.
l sent my assistant Mrs. Ross
out to buy a bottle.
That afternoon?
Did you tell her what kind?
l said to get a nice Chardonnay.
l knew Tom liked white wine.
From those trips to Napa that
he was an amateur connoisseur.
He`d be impressed by a nice bottle.
Yes.
Do you remember the wine?
No.
The `91 Pahlmeyer?
That`s right.
Do you know where your
assistant got that wine?
l assume she got it at a liquor store.
Would it surprise you to know...
...that no liquor store in
Seattle carries that bottle?
Mrs. Ross is very resourceful.
Very resourceful?
A bottle of wine you can`t find
within 500 miles of Seattle.
l have no idea where she
got the bottle of wine.
lsn`t it true, Ms. Johnson, that
you told Mrs. Ross 3 weeks ago...
...that you wanted a
bottle of `91 Pahlmeyer...
...for this meeting?
That`s not true.
And when she couldn`t
find it, you said--.
What was that? lt had
such managerial brio.
Here it is.
''lf you don`t find the wine...
...find a replacement.''
Do you have testimony
from Mrs. Ross?
Yes, l do.
Ms. Johnson?
The fact is Mrs. Ross
has personal problems.
She has a drinking problem.
She makes up stories to make
herself seem more important.
l told Mrs. Ross to go buy a bottle
of wine after Tom and l spoke...
...at the luncheon.
Maybe she had that bottle at home.
Maybe in her wine cellar.
Any more questions?
No, not for now.
l think this is a good time
for a break.
l got some information on Meredith.
You won`t believe it, or maybe you will.
Alan gave me a list, we
can`t verify any of this.
- You said you didn`t have sex.
- l didn`t.
l didn`t have sex with her.
What is it, Tom?
She`s trying to quit smoking?
- lt`s true.
- How could you do this?
She did it. That`s the point.
You saw this woman alone.
You had wine, a back rub, you kissed.
And then this non-sex sex thing.
You took off her panties.
Those are facts.
So what?
- That doesn`t happen unless you want it.
- l was cornered.
- You let it happen!
- l did not!
How could you? How could you
let that woman into our lives?
Get this.
Ten of her subordinates transferred
in the last 5 years. All men.
What a red flag!
Can you see them?
Yeah, but no one will talk and we can`t
subpoena them just for a mediation.
- Do you want to have lunch?
- l must go back to work.
How about you? Are you hungry?
How are you holding up?
Are you married?
Chandler, Hogue and Alvarez.
- l married Chandler.
- You married your boss?
Classic case of sexual harassment. He
asked me out 5 times before l said yes.
Today, if l had said no once, he
would have been afraid to ask again.
Tom said you`re a lawyer.
Ten years.
- Let`s switch hats. What do you think?
- l don`t look good in hats.
You`re afraid she`s telling the truth.
Yes.
What he did, he did out of weakness.
Hardly makes it better, does it?
l can`t get in the middle of
your relationship with Tom...
...but she did break the law
and that makes the difference.
Ms. Alvarez, 48 hrs ago, my husband`s
penis was in another woman`s mouth.
There`s nothing in the law
that`ll help me deal with that.
When did these arrive?
Came in an hour ago.
Garvin had me send the Corridor to the
hotel for the Conley people to use.
lt`s at the hotel?
Yeah. The Conley people had
such fun with it yesterday...
Getting anywhere with the drives?
l`m counting on you.
- l have a hunch.
- What is it?
- l don`t know.
l don`t know.
She got to you, didn`t she?
What else? They`re stronger, they`re
smarter and they don`t fight fair.
lt`s the next step in
the human evolution.
Keep some of us for
sperm and kill the rest.
What do you have?
lf l know something for a fact,
l won`t withhold it.
But l can`t go out on a limb,
it`s too intense around here.
l`m 23. l can`t wake up tomorrow and
find l`m out of the computer business.
Why aren`t you at the mediation?
l just came back to--. This was
the last thing l needed this week.
Come in.
Something`s come up.
l need to know exactly
what happened that night.
Well, it`s exactly like l told Phil.
You`re not talking to Phil.
We have Sanders` phone records. lt`s
possible someone overheard you two.
John Levin called again.
Find out what it`s about.
He must talk to you personally.
l don`t want to talk to him now.
Can l talk to you?
Cindy...
Are you ''a friend''?
A friend?
You know...
...''a friend.'' A friend.
l depends on what you
mean by ''a friend.''
All right, never mind.
He`s heading for the elevator.
Heading back to the mediation?
- Yeah, l must get back.
- l`ll give you a lift.
Don`t you think it`s time we talked?
l understand you both had a
chance to get it off your chest.
Your version of what happened.
Now l want it to stop.
What l got off my chest
was not a version.
lt`s always a version. That`s
the legacy of the modern age.
We have information but no truth.
Flashes of electrons in a grain of sand.
l`m telling the truth.
- You must look at this from all sides.
- How many sides are there?
All right, let`s say she
made a mistake. So what?
She made a pass, that`s all.
You could have decided
it was flattering.
You could have handled it many
ways, but this vindictiveness...
...l must say, l`m surprised.
lt`s against the law.
l work for her.
l`m employed by her.
No. You work for me.
That`s what l`m saying.
After all these years, why didn`t you
come to me? Not hire this lawyer!
Maybe l should have.
l mean, why can`t you just forget it?
Work together like adults and
everyone makes a pile of money.
- What`s wrong with that?
- lt`s gone too far.
Things can go back.
Why would he offer to settle now?
He realized how much they got to lose.
No, it doesn`t add up.
Maybe there`s a vulnerability
we don`t know about.
l`m still getting messages from
''a friend''. l printed out the address.
Maybe you can check it out.
l hope DigiCom doesn`t find him first.
Remember the cleaning lady?
She`s out of town. No one knows
where or when she`s coming back.
The Bahamas, probably, with
Mrs. Ross soon to join her.
These guys play hardball.
Did Mr. Sanders ever touch you in a way
that makes you feel uncomfortable?
He`s not aware of it.
Just answer the question, please.
Yes.
How?
He`ll pat me on my behind or...
...rub my shoulders.
Rub your shoulders?
l don`t think he means
anything by it.
You don`t like it.
l just feel it`s inappropriate.
l don`t see the relevance of this.
We`re trying to establish
a pattern of behavior.
Sexual harassers generally
follow a pattern.
l`ll allow it.
Do you have chiropractic problems?
Any neck problems, or your back?
No.
So you would characterize
this behavior as flirting...
...or sexual?
- l suppose so.
- But you never said anything.
He`s my boss.
You didn`t report it?
He`s your boss. l understand.
Your job is at stake. Rumors.
Whether people would believe you.
And if l ask you if you ever had any
sexual relations with Mr. Sanders...
...same answer?
No, l didn`t.
Didn`t report it?
- lt never happened.
- l understand.
l have no more questions.
Barbara called...
- about the Disneyland tickets for...?
- Jafar.
He`s got the tickets and
an upgrade at the hotel.
Thank you, l appreciate it.
They gave me your photos.
l`ll see you later?
Yes, l`ll see you later.
You know...
...it`s funny how you always
assumed you`d get the job.
Lewyn assumed
it would be him or you.
But nobody ever thought for
a second it might be me.
lsn`t that funny?
That`s not true. You were on the list.
Really?
Let me guess: ''Hunter, not
someone you`d follow into battle.
A team player. No killer instinct.
Doesn`t have those tools.''
What is that all a code for?
What, you on Meredith`s side?
l studied engineering for eight years.
l was the only woman in the
department. You know what l did?
l worked. You think
l`m on Meredith`s side?
What do you want to do?
What?
Their offer ends midnight. lt`s what
Garvin said. You get your job back.
She`s your boss.
Everyone goes back to work.
Did you find ''a friend''?
Did we get the address?
Dr. Arthur Friend, a chemistry professor
from the University of Washington...
...who`s been in Nepal
the last three weeks.
You got messages from
a locked office.
l`m glad we got that one solved.
Shit, l have to call Lewyn.
The drives we`re having
problems with came in.
Only you.
Anyone else would be sabotaging the
company, not solving their problems.
lt`s Adele and Mark.
We`re not home, leave a message
and we`ll call you back.
What?
Mark`s wife`s voice is on the machine,
but on Monday it was a man`s voice.
Then the next day Mark said
he never got the message.
l dialed the wrong number that night.
So?
That`s why the battery was dead.
What are you talking about?
That`s why Garvin wants to deal.
He`s got my phone records.
l`ve got a 10 minute phone bill
while l`m in Meredith`s office.
She took the phone away.
l called the wrong number...
...but l never hung up the phone.
The phone line is open.
Somebody`s got this whole
thing on an answering machine.
lt`s Levin, not Lewyn.
What`s going on?
l`ve been getting phone calls.
Some creep has my Visa...
...then, at the office,
everything`s turned upside down.
Have they got the tape?
What l`m saying is, it`s
good l brought it home.
- My girlfriend and l listened to it.
- Where`s the tape?
lt`s all here?
l`ve been trying to get
a hold of you all week!
You know what this means?
Do you have any idea
what this means?
Thanks, pal.
No deal. No, no deal, Catherine.
We`re going to bury them.
Everything is on tape.
Yes, everything.
Put it in.
God, look at us.
Go inside me.
l can`t do this.
- Do it.
- l won`t.
Now! Come on, now!
You can`t just stop! You can`t!
No! Goddamn it!
You stick your dick in my mouth
then get an attack of morality?
This never happened.
You never used to be this way.
ln any judicial proceeding,
this tape would be inadmissible.
l`m worried l`m going to drive to
work and hear it on Howard Stern.
ls she threatening?
l don`t know how many copies
of this tape there are.
l didn`t put it out there.
This tape just shows consensual
sex between adults...
...however it may have
appeared the next day.
Mr. Sanders` regret is not
my client`s harassment.
Ms. Johnson,
is that your position today?
Yes, it is.
Ms. Alvarez?
Just so l`m clear on
what today`s story is...
...would you define for
me ''consensual sex.''
Sex where both parties
are willing participants.
How many times did we hear
Mr. Sanders say ''no''?
l don`t know, l was busy listening
to my panties being torn off.
31.
31 times.
Doesn`t ''no'' mean ''no''?
Sometimes ''no'' means that person
wants to be overwhelmed, dominated.
The way we`re supposed to have sex
nowadays we`d need UN supervision.
''No'' means ''no.''
lsn`t that what we tell women?
Do men deserve less?
When he really wanted to stop
he had no problems doing it.
And you got angry.
Of course l did. Anyone would.
We tell women they
can stop at any point.
Haven`t you ever said
''no'' and meant ''yes''?
Until the moment of penetration--
He was willing. That tape
doesn`t change anything.
You controlled the meeting. You
set the time, you ordered the wine.
You demanded service and got
angry when he didn`t provide it.
So you decided to get rid of
him with this trumped-up charge.
The only thing you have proven
is that a woman in power...
...can be every bit
as abusive as a man.
You want to put me on trial?
Let`s be honest about why.
l am sexually aggressive. l like it.
Tom knew it and you can`t handle it.
lt`s the same thing since
the beginning of time.
Veil it, hide it, lock it
up and throw away the key.
We expect a woman to do a man`s
job, make a man`s money...
...then lie down for a man to fuck
her like it was 100 years ago!
Well, no, thank you.
You won`t believe this. l think
the Howard Stern thing got to them.
- What did Phil say?
- You get your job back.
You get $100,000 in pain and suffering,
and l get fees and expenses.
Meredith?
She stays through the merger,
then they say...
...she has to leave for some
whatever emergency. She`s out.
This is total and
complete vindication.
lt`s over!
l almost feel sorry for him.
He has no idea, does he?
l`d like to read this over again before
we sign. Not that l don`t trust you.
Just as long as it`s done
by midnight tonight.
Garvin wants this off his screen.
We want you to make a
presentation on Arcamax...
...at the merger announcement
tomorrow.
Nothing technical, 4 minutes.
Fine.
Great.
Now l`ve got to go break it to her.
lt won`t be easy.
l thought you enjoyed
that kind of thing.
You go after one of our people,
we`ll put the wagons in a circle.
Once you made your case,
the company behaved appropriately.
Right?
- You don`t want to know what l think.
- lt`s terrible.
Way a thing like this can...
...tear a company apart.
l told Bob we really need
to take a look at it.
Friends?
What?
l hope you still think
of me as a friend.
Good night, Phil.
Sign it now and l`ll read it later.
Where will you be?
Here, working on the presentation.
lf not, l`ll have somebody
run this by your house later.
Let me ask you something.
Why`d she do this?
You`ve seen her in action.
She`s cool, smart and in control.
- How`d she lose control like this?
- l don`t know.
You`re attractive. Maybe.
- But not irresistible.
- l`m serious. She`s here one day.
There`s a merger going on.
Conley people are touchy.
She thought you`d go along.
- There`s more to it than that.
- Come on.
You think too much.
You need to go home...
...open a nice bottle of champagne...
...make up with your
wife and get some sleep.
lt`s over.
Thank you.
Absolutely. You`re welcome.
Good night.
Hi, Stephanie.
Must be difficult, nobody
giving you information.
lt`s been a crazy week.
l had a friend. She was one of
the first women to move high up.
You know what it`s like,
every day putting out fires.
lt turned out the job
wasn`t what she thought.
She was looking the wrong
way when they fired her.
lnteresting.
Truth usually is, once you get to it.
lt`s you.
Where is everyone?
Mr. Garvin came in an hour ago.
Said they were working too hard.
Sent everyone home.
- What if Sanders doesn`t bring it up?
- He will.
l talked to him about his
presentation on Arcamax.
He has no idea.
When he brings up the line....
You must pounce because we
don`t have the harassment.
lt must be that Sanders
is incompetent.
lt`ll be in public. With reporters.
Bob`s counting on you.
Let`s clean out the database.
And any backup.
Catherine,
can you hold on one minute?
Has my contract gone out already?
Shit.
What does it say about firing me?
They can fire me for cause,
can`t they? For incompetence?
The problem with the drives is not
with the programming or the design.
lt`s with the production line
and that`s my responsibility.
This whole thing tomorrow...
...they`re setting me up.
Housekeeping, please.
This is Mr. Conley.
Could someone come
and turn down my bed?
My room number? lt`s on
the phone here somewhere....
That`s right.
Thank you very much.
- When does your dad arrive?
- Midnight. They stopped in Houston.
l`d love for him to get a
chance to see the Corridor.
You know...
l stayed up late last night, fooling
around with it up in my room.
lt`s really incredible.
l`m sorry, sir.
Here, thank you.
- You`re welcome.
- Good night.
Have a nice evening.
You`re in the Corridor, our prototype
for a virtual reality database.
Enjoy the demonstration.
lnformation accessed during this demo
is for entertainment value only...
...and should not be duplicated
to another database.
lf you have any questions,
ask the angel.
Malaysian Operations.
Searching Malaysian revisions file.
Why don`t we go up to my suite?
Give my colleagues a chance
to try out the Corridor.
Good idea.
''Reduction of air handling
capacity from number 7 air handlers...
...to a more appropriate
and cost-effective number 5.''
You can`t put number 5 handlers in
there. You`ll have dirt in everything.
My God, she`s in the system.
Angel, l need help.
Help is here.
Can l stop files from being deleted?
l`m sorry. You`re not Level 5.
You`re supposed to protect the files.
Sysop controls are
restricted to Level 5.
Show me all communications
with Malaysia.
Telephone or video?
Video.
Show me the last transmission
involving Meredith.
Sooner or later, Tom will figure
out the changes at the plant.
He`s not stupid.
Tom will be out of the picture
by Tuesday.
l don`t like to gamble.
l love Tahoe, but l think the risk--
Think. Who`ll believe him?
He`s married, with a family.
He`ll have no choice but to
take the settlement and leave.
Then we say Sanders made the changes
at the plant? He`ll deny it.
He won`t know.
He`ll be gone by then.
These things are so darn complicated.
l think it`s upside down.
There we go.
Who`s first?
Must have left the system on.
Give it a try. You`ll love it.
l`d love to try it.
l am totally screwed.
l`ll make my presentation...
...Meredith will ask me questions.
She`ll make me
look totally incompetent.
Are you sure there`s not
another system somewhere?
The system
has been completely deleted.
So l`m a sitting duck.
l`ll be walking around like
a ghost with a resume.
lt`s Mohammed Jafar.
How are you?
l don`t mean to bug you,
but we`re departing Monday--
lt`s my fault. Susan got the
Disneyland tickets for you.
The E-tickets?
You`re comped for all the rides and
at the hotel they`ll upgrade you.
Magnificent. l can`t
wait to tell my wife.
She said you were full of shit.
You know how women are.
Yes, l sure do.
l miss your face.
Talk to Arthur. He sees it
enough on the DVL. l`m always--
Tom, are you there?
Mohammed, on this end,
we back up our files on DAT.
Do you do the same over there?
l don`t know what we have.
l`d have to check it out. Why?
l got a real problem here.
l`m up against the wall and...
...l need you to do some
things for me, Mohammed.
l hope we have what you need, Tom.
Daddy?
l never believed what
they said about you.
Thank you, honey.
Come here, big guy.
Thank you.
Those from Malaysia?
l can`t believe it`s still coming out.
lt started at 7.
Testing.
Put these in one of the files.
Yeah, there`s a real talent to fishing.
First you must choose the right bait...
...then you must know
when to reel it in.
About the other day, l didn`t mean...
Yes, you did.
l apologize, and...
...thank you.
l accept.
Which brings us to our
Advanced Products Group.
Tom Sanders heads our
manufacturing department.
Tom, can you come up here...
...and review for us the revolutionary
new product we call Arcamax?
Thank you, Meredith.
Arcamax is our own stand-alone
CD-ROM drive player.
Now, for a CD-ROM drive to be
effective, it must be portable...
...it has to be fast.
Arcamax is twice as fast as any
CD-ROM drive in the world today.
We`ve had our problems,
but we are solving them.
And were the problems
with the design?
No, there are fabrication problems
involving the production line.
What sort of problems?
For example, we should be using
automatic chip installers to lock...
...the control chip on.
The Malaysians have been
doing it by hand...
...jamming the chips
in with their thumbs.
And the quality of the air is dirty.
We should use level 7 air
handlers, we`re using level 5.
And we`re ordering our
components, like...
...hinge rods and clips, not
from our Singapore supplier...
...but from someone who`s a lot
cheaper but also less reliable.
l`m confused. You set up this line.
You didn`t anticipate these problems?
The line was changed.
The specifications were altered.
How is that possible? We know
you to be a competent manager.
You should know.
You ordered the changes.
l don`t know how you got that idea.
You were in Kuala Lumpur last year.
To settle a labor dispute.
l`ve never even seen the line.
You haven`t?
No, l don`t know who told you l--
You`re watching Malaysian Channel 3.
Perhaps instead of digging
up Malaysian video clips...
...we should discuss
the problems here...
...the problems in your department
with the line you set up.
All right.
The 1st memo in the file being handed
out is signed by Meredith Johnson.
lt states that manual labor will
be used to install the chips.
That made the Malay
government happy.
lt also meant voltage irregularities
and memory allocation--
The Malay government
insisted we fill those jobs.
The Malaysian government does
not own shares of DigiCom.
These people here do.
The second memo...
...reduces the air handling
capacity in order to cut costs.
And that`s why we`re getting dirt in
the split optics, the drive arms.
The resulting delays will actually
increase the costs by more than 70%.
- The third memo regarding--
- The drives are your responsibility!
These problems were created
because of your incompetence.
That`s what`s wrong!
Passing the buck!
Back stabbing!
l`m not done.
This so-called evidence of
yours is fooling no one!
You can protect your turf
and think it means something.
You weren`t told of these decisions
because they`re over your head.
This merger is about synergy...
...between hardware and software,
between cash flow and capital needs.
That`s a language
you can`t understand!
l don`t either.
We`re buying this company
because they build things.
You understand what she means?
l`m trying to convey the
sentiments of everyone here.
That`s what l meant to do.
Could you step outside
for a moment?
Can you build the darn thing or not?
Yes, sir, we can.
They`re replacing Meredith.
Garvin`s announcing it in 10 minutes.
Ten minutes?
l`m surprised you didn`t come to gloat.
Gloating is underrated. l actually
came here to pick up the Arcamax files.
Some smart people underrated you.
Thank you.
Not including myself.
l beat you. l beat you fair and square.
Garvin lost his nerve.
lt was his brilliant idea to
fire you for incompetence.
Him and Phil.
Now l`m being fired.
l`ve never seen you play the victim.
lt`s the only good quality you had.
l`m playing the game men set up,
and l`m being punished for it.
lt`s fine.
l`ve had calls from ten
head-hunters with job offers.
Don`t be surprised if l`m back
in ten years to buy this place.
Did it ever occur to you, Meredith,
that maybe l set you up?
- This is my son, Spencer.
- How you doing?
- Good.
- You`re at the University of Washington?
That`s great. Very good.
What a week!
The Chinese say:
''May you live in interesting times.''
This merger is the most
interesting merger l`ve had...
...since my 2nd marriage.
The merger is complete.
The question now is...
...who do we find to run
things up here in Seattle?
And what l realized during this...
...very interesting week...
...is that l have probably
focused too much on...
...breaking the glass ceiling,
finding a woman to run things here...
...when l should have been
looking for the best person...
...to run things here.
Someone whose...
...long service with this company
has established a record...
...of creativity...
...sound judgement...
...and hands-on expertise.
And that person...
...is Stephanie Kaplan.
Congratulations, Stephanie.
l tell you something,
she`s the greatest!
Thank you.
First, l`d like to take the opportunity
to thank the department heads:
...Mary Anne Hunter
and Mark Lewyn here...
...and Don Cherry, where are you?
There he is.
And particularly, Tom Sanders...
...who epitomizes the
inventiveness of this division...
...its past and its future.
l`m counting on you to be
my right-hand.
Thank you.
We are heading
into a new millennium...
...a new time.
You a chemistry major, Spencer?
Yeah, l am.
l know a chemistry professor there,
Arthur Friend. A. Friend.
l don`t know if he teaches freshmen.
l`m his research assistant.
So if Arthur Friend was
in Nepal, for example...
...you`d have the keys to his
office and computer password.
We all work so well together
and it`s exciting...
...and it`s wonderful to see.
Thank you.
Your mother`s
an extraordinary woman.
You just figured that out?