Yeah, I'm back from the hospital.
I'm ok.
Did you put the book in the mailbox?
Okay.
I'll go get it.
Seung Hyun.
There are 3 things a person can't hide...
...coughing, poverty and love.
The harder one tries to hide them,
the more they rise to the surface.
But there are times when you still want to hide them.
I just sit and cry...
...and cry until I can't anymore.
Love is a self-inflicted pain.
I hope you'll find peace within you.
Il Mare looks like a lonely place.
But its warmth and comfort comes from the love within.
Love comes to us in different ways
but underneath all those ways,
I believe there is only one love.
It's been delivered a little late..
but I hope your father's book
helped you to understand him.
Hye-gi!
Auntie!
- Have you been good, kiddo?
- Yes.
Are you ok?
Yes, how's dad?
He's at a seminar in Seoul.
Let's get in. Come on.
/ Let's go.
Eun-joo,
Everyone I loved
were always out of my reach...
...and I think I ached for them.
I was 7 when my father left me.
Cola!
It's dinner time.
You like Mr. Fish?
Cola,
I'll be right back. Be good now.
Gosh, it's freezing...
Excuse...
I saw you at the station tonight.
White sweater, black muffler,
and very long pretty hair...
Haven't heard from you in a while...
I'm anxious to hear from you.
Il Mare can make you feel so alone.
I felt like that when I was there.
Sung-hyun, wanna have some fun?
Go inside a convenience store and grab a beer.
Drink it down...
Now start running!
Go for a ride on the Viking.
The adrenaline rush is amazing.
This is the moment when...
It's my turn!
Take a bus to Bomunri.
Get off at Mulmok near the tree-lined boulevard.
Do you like to take walks?
It's a beautiful place to just walk alone
and think things through.
You'll feel better.
Just when you start to get tired,
You'll see a little cafe.
I go there to drink wine sometimes.
Do you like wine?
I heard that wine drinkers are lonely.
...but it doesn't matter to me.
I reserved a bottle of wine to be opened
in the year 2000.
How is it?
Wine is supposed to get better with age.
Thanks to you ...
I had a great time.
How about you, Eun-Joo?
I did too.
But I felt a little sad coming back alone.
I'd really like to meet you,
if it's ok with you.
Hey, Cola.
You really think we'll meet?
Can you come down to Cheju lsland?
I'm going home next week.
Cola, Cola!
Cola, I'm going to meet Eun-joo.
What'll we do for the next two years?
Are you looking at the photo?
The coral beach is where I want to live.
Once you see it you'll want to build a house on it.
Oh, our rendezvous date is March 11, 2000 at 3 p.m...
on the coral beach.
March 11, 2000...
It's a Saturday.
Don't forget. I only have a week,
...but you still have over 2 years to go.
Eun Joo, aren't you going to sleep?
I'll be right down. Good night
Go to bed, dear.
Can I help you?
No, I was just...
Are you building a house here?
Yes, we are.
Are you going to live here?
No, I'm here for the construction.
Why do you ask?
Just curious...
A friend of mine designed it.
Isn't it perfect for this beach?
He dedicated it to his true love.
I see...
I gotta run.
Good luck.
I waited for you a long time.
I know 2 years is a long time
but I still hoped you'll show.
I guess I expected too much again.
I know I shouldn't...
because it always leads to disaster.
But everyone I care about is so far away.
What happened to you in those 2 years?
I hope you just forgot.
I wouldn't forget a promise like that.
This is breathtaking.
Sung-hyun's letters were little pieces of happiness.
But there still is this sense of emptiness.
Is it because of losing Ji-hoon?
Or not being able to meet Sung-hyun?
There's a technical problem...
so let's take a 30 min.
Let's get some coffee!
My treat!
More animation, the better. It means more work for us.
And it's great that are many big projects in the works.
That's true.
Sorry, I'm late.
No, not at all, I just got here too.
Ji Hoon, about our engagement...
Yeah, let's do it this month.
Really?
How about 2 Wednesdays from now?
Ok!
It's about time.
But why do you want to rush this?
I'm not rushing. You're the one who's stalling.
Just be patient...
until my animation project's finish.
ok.
I thought I could forget him...
...but when I heard his voice again,
everything fell apart.
I know he loves someone else...
...but I can't help it.
I can't stop thinking about him.
Please help me stop him from leaving.
I'm sorry..
I'm really sorry, Seung Hyun.
Hi. -Sorry, I'm late.
It's ok. Are you hungry? -No but dinner is on me.
What should we eat? -Whatever you want.
Was I just a stranger to you?
Am I only a meaningless faceless stranger to you?
Jung Sook!
Was it the right decision not
to go with Ji-Hoon to USA?
and become a radio-performer?
Of course.
True love comes from true independence.
Forget all about Ji-Hoon.
I want to believe it too.
All I want is career and love.
My happiest moments were opening my mail
under your Christmas lights.
Eun-Joo.
It was really hard studying in the USA alone.
I just got too tired and lonely...
...and I wanted someone there.
I'm sorry...
We should have went together.
Please help me stop him from leaving me.
I'm so sorry,
I'm asking you for this.
I'm sorry, Seung Hyun.
I'll help you.
Why didn't you tell me how you felt before?
We don't have much time.
Eun Joo, do you remember your first letter?
You wished me good fortune at Il Mare.
Knowing you has been a blessing.
This time I want to return this good fortune to you.
Best wishes to you.
Thank you for everything.
Good bye...
Excuse me. Where's the department of architecture?
That's over there...
Thank you.
My Lord, you're the biggest whiner these days...
You are complaining about your room again?
Well, life isn't fair.
He dedicated it to his true love..
May I help you?
Sung-hyun dedicated it to you. Eun-joo.
It was a car accident.
Help me...
Help me stop him from leaving me...
He was on his way to Youido to meet someone.
The driver didn't see him.
Seung Hyun! Don't go there.
It's that house over there.
Please...
Please... hurry...
The letter has to reach him.
Seung Hyun, please don't go there.
It's all my fault.
The letter has to reach him in time...
Our last date was at a cafe called morning.
in Youido on March 25, 1998.
Cheer up, Eun Joo.
I'm not going away forever.
Don't be so down.
I know, I just feel weird.
I asked you to come with me.
It's not easy becoming a voice actor.
Not many people pass the exam.
It's only 3 years... right?
It will be alright.
I just feel so uneasy.
Please don't go.
Don't go there.
Don't die.
Seung Hyun... I'm sorry.
The fact that I don't show up 2 years from now...
...must mean that we weren't meant to be.
And you are...?
I hope you're ready to hear
a long and magical tale.
Can you trust me?