Senator Carroll is here
to celebrate Independence Day.
He is so independent,
some say they don't know
which party he belongs to.
Austin Tucker is with us today
as a political adviser to Senator Carroll.
Austin, we hear that you wanna get
the nomination for Senator Carroll.
We're jumping the gun there,
Miss Carter.
He's not running for any other office.
Here come Senator Carroll
and Mrs Carroll. He looks terrific.
Happy Fourth of July!
Happy Independence for us all!
He is the ideal father.
The ideal husband if you're old enough.
And I guess the ideal leader
for our country if you're any age.
- Lee, how are you?
- Fine, thank you.
Welcome. You look just as wonderful
as in all the photographs, always smiling.
I'm happy to be with my constituents on
this wonderful day, Independence Day.
- Thank you very much, everybody!
- Thank you.
Thank you!
You need a ribbon.
- I'm with her.
- Ma'am, is he with you?
No.
All right, we'll try to make it.
Schedule it some other time...
How are you?
How are you, sir? Good to see you.
You're looking very good.
Hello, how are you?
But I fouled up on that one.
I know a bit about your background,
your lovely family. Scotch and water.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you
very much for inviting us today.
Independence Day
is very meaningful to me.
I've been called
too independent for my own good.
Move back, everybody.
You are here
for the official announcement
of the inquiry into the death
of Senator Charles Carroll.
This is not a press conference,
therefore there will be no questions.
A transcript of the investigation is being
prepared for publication on March 1 st.
At that time, the committee will hold
a full-scale press conference.
After four months of investigation,
followed by nine weeks of hearings,
it is the conclusion of this committee
that Senator Carroll was assassinated
by Thomas Richard Linder.
It is our further conclusion
that he acted entirely alone,
motivated by a misguided
sense of patriotism
and a psychotic desire
for public recognition.
The committee wishes to emphasise
that there is no evidence
of any wider conspiracy.
No evidence whatsoever.
It's our hope that this will put an end
to the kind of irresponsible speculation
conducted by the press
in recent months.
The complete text of the hearings,
which provides the basis
for these findings,
will be published March 1 st.
When you have
examined the evidence,
you will have every opportunity
to ask those questions which
remain unanswered, if there are any.
That is all. Thank you.
You could win this! Take a look.
We are just starting with you.
The package you pick might contain...
Excuse me, but my parrot is loose
on your back porch.
- What?
- My parrot. I wonder if I could...
- What are you talking about?
- My parrot. It's very sick.
Let him go look.
- I haven't seen any parrot.
- He's hiding.
Freeze! Police officers.
Where's the stuff?
- Wendy hits the $25,000....
- Check that, will you?
You've won an all-expense-paid trip
to British Columbia!
All right, Frady, you're under arrest.
- You didn't see us, did you?
- I did, but I've never seen those two.
- What are you talking about?
- You looking for dope?
Maybe one of your men
could tell me what I'm here for.
- Destruction of property...
- Me, destruction of property?
- I can't believe I...
- Terrifying people, trespassing...
Hold it, goddammit!
I wanna get something straight.
Is there anybody here who can say
I broke into that house,
I was waving my gun around,
I threw his wife on the floor?
If you can, do it in front of
your watch commander.
- Shit!
- What were you doing there?
- What was I doing there?
- Yes, Joe.
These assholes have been after me
for my sources and you're...
So he told perfect strangers
he was looking for his parrot.
- My parrot, that's right.
- Can you imagine that kind of nerve?
You're saying
can I imagine that kind of nerve?
- Can I imagine it?
- Thought you'd teach 'em a lesson?
I don't think I could teach 'em anything.
Why don't you go out
and do something worthwhile?
You're not only dumb, you're dirty.
- Look at your shirt.
- Get your goddam...
- Hold it, hold it.
- You're not even...
- Do I post bail?
- What the fuck for?
Malicious mischief, obstructing justice.
Good enough?
I'll forget the whole thing, Bill,
if you shut him up.
- Malicious mischief...
- Come on, Joe.
- It isn't good enough.
- Joe, come on.
You're enjoying yourself, aren't you?
- You gotta admit it's funny.
- It makes me laugh.
But I don't think it's funny.
What's that supposed to mean?
Ever laughed at a comedian
pretending to stutter?
There's nothing funny about stuttering,
but people laugh. They're amused.
But they're not happy about it.
You're not gonna print this?
You're not gonna print it?
Not only that, but this is the end
of your series on local drug problems.
We're in the business
of reporting the news, not creating it.
Joe.
Joe, we went through all this
six years ago.
When I agreed to take you back,
I made two suggestions.
One was about your drinking.
You seem to have licked that.
The other was that you curb your talent
for creative irresponsibility.
You can start working on that right now.
You're really tired, aren't you?
Joe... go home.
Go to a movie. Relax.
Tomorrow you can do a nice dull piece
on the Parks and Recreation hearings.
That is, if you feel this job
is interesting enough to stick with it.
Hi, Joe, I got a hot one for you.
Lee Carter called.
Four times. She must want it pretty bad.
- Did you clean up the room, Schecter?
- Sure. I got some mail for you, too.
I hope I'm not interrupting.
- You've been calling me?
- A lot.
Any particular reason?
- Somebody's trying to kill me.
- Somebody besides yourself?
I've never tried to kill myself successfully.
Last time you were here,
I think you lost your cat.
- I haven't lost my cat.
- The time before, it was your husband.
You may find this difficult to accept,
but I'm terrified.
You were always terrified
about something.
- That some guy might attack you in bed.
- Not as long as you were there.
OK.
Here. Now, why are you here this time?
- I told you. Somebody's trying to kill me.
- Jesus.
I don't think I should be looking at this.
- Just look.
- What?
Come on, I looked at this
three years ago.
Six of these people
have since died in accidents.
Four. Look, nobody's trying to kill you.
These people were killed. Whoever
killed them is going to try to kill me.
Austin Tucker thinks that
maybe we all saw something up there.
- We did see something.
- I mean something else!
What do you mean? Has he ever
indicated what he means by that?
Did he see anything other than
what was in the Commission report?
- Did you see anything?
- No.
Neither did I. Believe me, I looked.
We all looked.
- If you didn't see it, it's not there?
- I know all about these accidents.
Ralph Scaletta hit a piling,
killed three other people.
Joy Holder died of anaphylactic shock
from an antibiotic.
Herbert Moon burned up in bed,
smoking. Harry Lutz had a heart attack.
Harry Lutz was 40.
It's too young for a heart attack.
He was in terrific condition.
He found out his wife
was banging her psychiatrist
and a bulldozer knocked over his house.
That's future shock, Lee.
You no longer believe
there was another assassin?
People were crazy
for any kind of explanation.
Some nut was always knocking off
one of the best men in the country.
OK. OK.
But there's 6 out of 18 dead.
- Four.
- That was the last time you looked.
Since then, Norman Lomax has died.
- Now Arthur Bridges.
- What are you talking about?
A fishing accident?
Where the hell is Salmontail?
Salmontail is where Austin Tucker
is now. I tried to reach him.
Why don't you call him?
Looks like a small town.
Take me there. We could catch a plane
and be there this evening. Please!
Call him up. It's a fishing accident.
I got some real problems.
You son of a bitch!
You don't care!
Lee, don't do this.
Hey...
Lee...
The alcohol and barbiturates
would have killed her in bed,
let alone at the wheel of a car.
Would you call that a possible homicide?
Face it, some people wanna die.
Excuse me.
Wait till the cars
come to a complete stop.
That's it. Hop right in there.
Separate seats.
I want you to read
what is over the cars.
- "Please keep hands and feet in cars."
- Right.
OK, Frady, what do you know?
Will, tell me something.
You still got access to FBI files?
I'll tell you how the FBI feels about me.
Recently, they took my name
off the roster of ex-agents.
So now, not only am I not an agent,
I'm not even an ex-agent.
Is it possible to kill somebody
and make it look like a heart attack?
Sure. They got a pill for it. PEP.
- PEP?
- Pulmonary Embolism Pill.
It creates an embolism, but
the actual cause of death is biochemical.
The man ends up
looking like his heart attacked him.
- What do you know?
- I don't know.
Come on, what do you know?
What I know is I need a good alias
and a good ID.
What kind of ID?
- I've gotta be a hostile misfit.
- For that, you don't need an ID.
- Still got friends on the El Monte force?
- Before we get to El Monte...
The minute you know what's going on,
I wanna know. Promise me.
I promise.
All right, I think I got a guy for you.
Sunshine Homes
hired me to investigate him
when he was doing a night-watchman
job for 'em. He's a real nut.
- Richard Partun.
- Richard Partun?
Get a fake ID for him, too.
Make it look like
he's hiding something.
If they investigate the first,
they'll be less careful on the second.
You should look like a guy
who's ashamed of something.
- Let's make him a weenie wagger.
- A weenie wagger?
Anybody would be ashamed of that.
Besides, you look a bit like a flasher.
Hold on to your neighbour,
it's happy hour in Salmontail.
We're here to play a little music
and have a lot of fun.
This boy goes into a bar
down in Texas, see.
He goes up to the bartender and he says,
"Give me 12 bourbon and waters."
The bartender goes, "That's a lot
of bourbon and waters." He says...
No, I'll catch it.
- Think your date just come in.
- I think you're terrible.
- Hi.
- My name's Gale. What can I fix you?
- I...
How about a Martini?
You know what they say about Martinis?
A Martini is like a woman's breast -
one ain't enough and three is too many.
- That's an amazing joke, Gale.
- Yeah, it is. What can I get you?
- Just a glass of milk.
- You're the healthy type, huh?
How are you?
Can I buy you a drink, Miss?
For a moment,
I thought you were a man.
- But you aren't, are you?
- No, I'm a girl.
Why don't you go over there
and tell those people, real loud?
Don't touch me unless you love me.
I told you to go over there to that table
and tell those people who you really are.
You don't want me to ask you again.
Come on, get up. I'll buy you a drink.
Come and sit down. You're all right, son.
You wouldn't be offended
if I call the police?
No, but you don't have to call far,
because Red's a deputy.
I'm the sheriff.
You got some interesting ideas
about law enforcement.
Shoulda stopped the fight. I would have,
but I dearly love seeing Red get stomped.
- He's your deputy?
- He's my sister's boy.
He's so damn mean,
he can't get along with anybody.
He's a real turkey. You move his plate
five inches, he's gonna starve to death.
He's all right. He does that all the time.
This is Gale, this is Shirley.
You met Red.
Now, where you from, son?
Jesus.
Your friend Austin Tucker's long gone.
Did he think that Bridges' drowning
wasn't an accident?
- I don't know. What do you think?
- That's the river, that's the dam.
Open that dam and that water
comes down like a wall.
If you're standing where Bridges was,
you're gonna drown.
Isn't there a warning system or does
the power company love a surprise?
They got sirens and bells and signs all
over the place and they got a watchman.
- There might be just something there.
- Where?
The watchman. Buster Hinton.
Nah! Hell, I've known Buster
for a long time.
I got no reason to doubt him.
No, go ahead.
This might not have
anything to do with anything,
but old Buster showed up
with a brand new shotgun.
- Maybe we ought to talk to him.
- I'd like to do it kinda casual.
He's up at the dam in the afternoons.
I'll take you to where it happened.
You could do some fishing.
- Come up with anything?
- Nothing but fish. You?
I've found out a couple of things, but...
Here, I've brought you some lunch.
You are aces with me.
Look at this! What did you find out?
- That's the warning, huh?
- Yeah, that's it.
Bridges couldn't hear that?
My mother could've heard it
and she's dead.
LD, what's the news
on your friend Buster?
Actually, there is no Buster.
Yeah? Gale! You want LD?
Drowned in what?
The car's right out front.
You gotta be kidding.
Who found the body?
Charley, somebody's broken into
LD's house and stole his car.
Get to the intersection and cut him off.
OK, Red, we're on our way.
We got him cut off.
You've been drinking again, haven't you?
Tell the truth, Joe.
Come in, Stanley.
The thought of covering that council
meeting was too much for you, wasn't it?
Close the door.
Somebody's systematically knocking off
witnesses and you don't care.
Sure I care. I care about my kids' future,
this newspaper, my golf handicap.
I've even been known to care about you,
you ungrateful bastard.
Drink your coffee.
Here. Take it! Shit.
Joe, what evidence have we got?
A girl who died of pills and booze,
a sheriff you say tried to kill you
- And the poor bastard drowns.
- I got a bank book with $107,000 in it.
- The police are after me.
- Why is there no APB on you?
I checked. They say it was an accident.
- They don't wanna answer questions.
- You're damn right.
Sheriff LD Wicker and two deputies
were indicted three months ago
on a utilities scandal.
It was in every paper in the North-West.
He knew you were a reporter,
but it wasn't any national conspiracy
he was covering up.
Remember catching the state senator's
bagman and it was his nephew's bookie?
You're gonna make
a real horse's ass of yourself.
He didn't know I was a reporter. I didn't
tell him, I didn't give him my name.
- Did you register at a hotel?
- Yeah, under a phoney name.
Boy, you amaze me. You go expecting
these things to happen and they do.
Just advance me two weeks' salary.
- For what?
- I gotta find Austin Tucker.
If anybody knows about this, he does.
I won't advance you a dime.
I don't care if your self-serving ambition
gets you the Pulitzer prize.
I'm not gonna have
anything more to do with it.
- Joe...
- Can't help it.
I know.
Good shot. Good shot. You got a point.
Not bad, Riggsy.
- That's good. Hey, babe, you're all right.
- Winning, huh?
Winning? I'm beating the shit out of him.
I'm Schwartzkopf, this is Riggs.
Harry Nelson. The Psych department
gave those vocational tests to you?
I'll go and get those tests.
We establish a centre for the study of
violence, they send us every nut in town.
- They get mean?
- Yeah. Vicious.
One of them bit the ear
off a colleague of mine.
It was OK, though,
we sewed it back on. Most of it.
I'm glad about that.
I'm not sure whoever made this
knew what they were after.
How you doing, Ernie?
It seems to be directing at...
...trying to pull out anger, repression,
frustration, stuff like that.
Could it pick up
potentially homicidal characteristics?
You mean a killer? Yeah, sure.
Would you be willing to go through it
and tell me what answers would come
from a highly violent personality?
Yeah, but it probably
wouldn't do much good.
This stuff's pretty sophisticated.
It's a lot different than my stuff.
It's not any better,
but it would be a difficult...
Fuck it. We'll let Ernie take it.
He'll blow 'em right off the graph.
He hacked up his great-aunt
and killed two ticket-takers.
Ernie?
Come here, boy.
I'd like you to meet somebody.
What's your name again?
Nelson. Harry Nelson.
Harry Nelson, Ernie.
Joe Frady? Looking for Austin Tucker?
D'you wanna see him?
Leave your car here.
- I have to do a skin search.
- A what?
You're gonna strip
and I'm gonna search you.
- Are you out of your fucking mind?
- That's the way Mr Tucker wants it.
And if I don't see you,
you don't see him. All right?
All right, Mr Frady,
who sent you to look for me?
- Nobody sent me.
- Now, look...
I've come 1,300 miles to get
a straight answer to that question.
- My life is in danger just being here.
- Who really sent you?
- Nobody sent me.
- Keep your voice down.
Nobody sent me. I'm a writer...
Stop acting like
you're on The New York Times.
You're a third-rate journalist from Oregon
or wherever the hell you're from.
You've been asking about things
you know nothing about.
There were two attempts
made on my life.
I don't know what you want,
but if it's money...
...l'll give you
$10,000 to keep me out of it.
You don't mention my name
or come looking for me.
All I want is to stay out of it.
Money means nothing to me. This story's
gonna mean more to me than $10,000.
Fella, you don't know
what this story means.
We better talk.
Have you seen this photograph?
It was taken
on the Space Needle that day.
There's me, Lee, Bridges...
You know that man?
- The waiter?
- Yeah. You know his name?
- No, why?
- Just curious.
Lee, Bridges, Joy Holder. Lutz.
Herbie.
Who would have thought?
Sorry, Bill, I didn't mean to scare you.
You're supposed to be dead.
Goddammit. You could have called me.
I was scared shitless
they'd think I was still alive.
- You mean nobody knows?
- Nobody but you.
- Hey, Bill, what's that?
- Tomorrow's lead.
I'm demanding a reopening
of the Carroll investigation.
- Who are you calling?
- The police, FBI, CIA, somebody.
Bill... don't do it.
You suggesting they're involved?
Or that they covered up?
There is a bureaucratic tendency
to cover up mistakes,
but I got no reason to think
any governmental agency was in on it.
Or if they were, that they knew it.
You don't have to infiltrate
the whole agency.
It's not only to do with
the Carroll assassination.
Whoever's behind this
is in the business of recruiting assassins.
Recruiting assassins?
I think I got some of their entrance
exams. If I'm right, I'm gonna enlist.
If you print anything now, I'll be exposed.
You alone can uncover
what all the agencies couldn't?
Maybe. I'm just asking you not to print
anything until I get more evidence.
You'll blow my chance
to find out who's behind it.
- What do you expect me to print?
- My obituary.
I wanna pre-date a will,
name you as executor.
Pick up my things,
give them to the Salvation Army.
Make a big show out of it.
I'm dead and I wanna
stay that way for a while.
It's about $340. It's all I've got here.
You're gonna need the money.
Hope you know
how to take care of yourself.
I hope you do. You're gonna be the only
person who knows what I'm doing.
- Who is it?
- Richard Paley?
- Are you Richard Paley?
Who?
Who wants him?
Congratulations.
You had some very interesting scores
on the first series of tests for Parallax.
- Testing for what?
- The Parallax Corporation.
You did apply for our training, didn't you?
Oh, Christ, that.
As you know, Parallax receives demands
from all phases of industry.
Demands for unusual personnel.
If you qualify, and we think that you can,
we're prepared to offer you
the most lucrative and rewarding work.
- What do you get out of it?
- We receive a sort of finder's fee.
As I said, the jobs are difficult to fill.
- How tall are you?
- Six-two.
- What kind of jobs you talking about?
- Whatever you're cooking is burning.
You might as well come in.
I'm Jack. Jack Younger.
But we like to be on a first-name basis
with potential candidates.
You look taller than six-two.
What does my height
have to do with anything?
Put some ice on it.
It'll stop the sting and the blister.
Your tests suggest
that you have remarkable talents.
- What do you mean by "talents"?
- You have difficulty holding on to a job.
I just don't like to take a lot of shit,
so people say I got antisocial tendencies.
Has it ever crossed your mind
that it's everybody else's problem
that they don't get along with you?
- Why?
- The very quality that gets you in trouble
makes you potentially invaluable.
- What's that?
- Your aggressiveness.
I don't wanna intrude on you
while you're eating.
Get in touch with me personally
if you'd like to go further.
It's been a pleasure, Richard.
Welcome to the testing room
of the Parallax Corporation's
Division of Human Engineering.
You will now please cross to the chair.
And you will sit down.
Make yourself comfortable.
Be sure to place each one of your hands
on the box on either side of the chair,
making sure that each one of your
fingers is on one of the white rectangles.
Just sit back. Nothing is required of you,
except to observe the visual materials
that are presented.
Be sure to keep your fingers
on the box at all times.
All right. We hope you find the test
a pleasant experience.
Will you please proceed to our offices?
Thank you for your cooperation.
Senator, here's an editorial
even you can't figure out.
Your drink, Senator Gillingham.
This comparison between
you and Carroll is nonsense.
Sorry, sir, you'll have to
go back to coach.
Point is, he doesn't like Hammond
any better than he likes you.
Your name, sir?
- Paley. Richard Paley.
- Is that P-A-I-L-E-Y?
- No, it's P-A-L-E-Y.
- Will you be returning with us?
- Is Denver your final destination?
- Yeah.
That'll be $68.64.
$68.64?
Out of $70.
- What would you like to drink?
- Just a Coke.
Excuse me. Ma'am?
Would you like something to drink?
Attention. Due to technical difficulties,
we will be returning to Los Angeles.
We regret any inconvenience
this may cause you.
Passengers disembarking
from Globe Airlines flight 451
will be met by airport security.
We regret any further delay
that may be caused by the investigation.
All efforts will be made
to have you airborne again quickly.
Passengers disembarking
from Globe Airlines flight 451
will be met by airport security.
We regret any further delay
that may be caused by the investigation.
Hello.
We've already received an offer
for your services. $25,000 a year.
- Who from?
- Manufacturers Intelligence Group.
Never heard of them.
They work out of
the Hammond building in Atlanta.
- What do they want me to do?
- Work in their security programme.
- Sounds good to me.
- Good.
Just one more thing.
What's that?
Who are you?
- Who am I?
- You're not Richard Paley.
Your service records don't check.
They don't?
There was a Richard Paley
in the 1 st Air Cavalry, but he's dead.
- Gee, I'm sorry to hear that.
- So were we.
Who are you?
I don't have to tell you. You're not a cop.
I was getting attached to you.
I wouldn't step outside that door.
We simply have to know.
All right.
My name's Richard Partun.
Why did you want us to think
you were Richard Paley?
I needed a job. I got into a little difficulty
in El Monte a couple of months ago.
What kind of difficulty? It's important.
I was drinking in this bar and...
I used to drink a lot.
Next thing I know, I'm running around
a laundromat with no clothes on.
Some old lady
claimed I was trying to...
- You know, molest her.
- Were you?
I don't know. I don't remember
what I was doing there, nothing.
All I know is that they arrested me for...
indecent exposure.
A thing like that follows you around.
Try to get a job, you're a sex offender.
- I'm no sex offender.
- No, I'm sure you're not.
I think they put something in my beer
that made me take off my clothes.
If that's all there is to it, we'll check it out
with the El Monte police.
It'll be no problem... Richard.
I've tried to be a friend to you, haven't I?
At Parallax, I've found that people
who have had real trouble in their lives,
so-called antisocial people,
if I can earn their loyalty, I can give them
a sense of their own worth.
That's very rewarding, believe me.
I honestly think, with your nature,
you're more reliable for security work
than any semi-retired ex-FBI agent
they can come up with.
In a risk situation,
I believe you'll go right down the line.
That's something money can't buy.
You're invaluable, Richard.
- ... ex-FBI agent they can come up with.
- Oh, come on, Frady.
... I believe you'll go right down the line.
That's something money can't buy.
You're invaluable, Richard.
Come in, Stanley.
There you are.
You're new, aren't you? Thanks.
It must have been 5.30.
That's when I come to clean the office.
- There he was.
- All the signs of a massive coronary.
- D'you know if he had a heart condition?
- I don't know.
Trusting man. He didn't even
lock the drawer he kept his money in.
I'm very pleased with you.
Tomorrow, you'll meet with the other
member of your team, Ben Harkins.
He'll have your assignment.
I just...
What name am I supposed to use?
Richard Partun.
Don't worry, he knows all about you.
Good.
Good afternoon. 803, isn't it?
The guy that just checked in,
is his name Ben?
I can't remember his last name.
Harkins. It's Mr Ben Harkins.
816, right down the hall from you.
Ben Harkins, please. Ben Harkins.
Ben?
I got a message for you from Jack.
Don't unpack.
There's been a change in plans.
How much money you got left?
- I don't know, maybe $700.
- There'll be another $200 at the desk.
Go back to the airport and
take the 510 American to Honolulu.
- Honolulu?
- Not bad, uh?
When you get to Honolulu,
take the first flight to Maui.
When you get there, rent a jeep and
drive to a hotel called the Hana Ranch.
- Yeah, Hana Ranch. Got it?
- Right.
- Is Jack Younger here?
- Mr Younger isn't here.
Richard Partun was here. The guy
he sent me to meet didn't show up.
People, let's work now.
Would you please
check your cards for sequence?
Check your cards carefully
for sequence.
Work smoothly
and it'll be a clean, clear picture.
I'm gonna give you a warning,
"One, two, three" and a command, "Pull".
Get your concentration here.
Make a good, clean, sharp picture.
Here we go.
All right. And one, two, three, pull!
One, two, three, turn!
One, two, three, lift!
Applause, applause. Here he comes.
Here's the man himself, Mr Hammond.
- Quite a surprise.
- Nice to see you.
This is Pat Fairfield,
Student Body President.
Marilyn Puttnam,
Student Federation President.
The youth is rallying, sir.
We're at that point
where you'll be coming in.
- If you would make your entrance.
- What I'm here for.
- Where do I enter?
- Round the table, up the stair.
- Right to the speaker stand.
- OK.
Card people, we have a tape of the
address Mr Hammond's going to deliver.
We're gonna run that
so you can learn your cues.
I'll be giving cues for applause.
When he comes in,
greet him for everybody here.
Here he comes, making his entrance.
Let's hear it! Come on!
That's the man we're working for,
the man people are coming to see.
This is gonna be on television.
Wanna thank you kids for being here,
and the band. See you tonight.
Thank you.
I am proud to be here tonight.
I can think of no occasion
that has given me more pleasure.
We all ache for the chance
to be proud again.
I promise you I will not stop,
I will not falter,
till that march
has reached its destination.
Until, like Moses, I've returned to you
the promised land of liberty
our forefathers created.
I cannot take the honours
you bestow on me as a personal tribute.
You are here to honour me
not as a man but as a representative...
...they're all talking about Jack Nicklaus,
Palmer.
Our cause must become the country's.
I am proud...
My life has been blessed with success,
but that is not why you are here.
My life has been blessed with...
There he is! There he is!
I see him!
Ladies and gentlemen,
you've been invited here
for the announcement of the inquiry
into the death of George Hammond.
A complete transcript of the investigation
is in preparation.
This committee has spent
six months of investigation,
followed by 11 weeks of hearings.
After careful deliberation,
it has concluded that George Hammond
was assassinated by Joseph Frady.
An overwhelming body of evidence
has revealed that Frady was obsessed
with the Carroll assassination.
And in his confused and distorted mind
seems to have imagined that Hammond
was responsible for the senator's death.
He was equally convinced
that Hammond was plotting to kill him.
It is for those reasons
that Frady assassinated him.
Although I'm certain that it will do nothing
to discourage the conspiracy pedlars,
there is no evidence of a conspiracy
in the assassination
of George Hammond.
Those are our findings.
The evidence will be available
to you as soon as possible. Thank you.
This is an announcement, gentlemen.
There will be no questions.