"Was that you or was that
just a fragrant wind"
"Was that you or were there
colours everywhere"
"Was that you or were those
shining pathways'
songs resounding in the atmosphere"
"Was it you I found,
or was it my destiny"
"Was it you or was there
magic in the air"
"just for two moments, the caravans of
our dreams made a stop"
"and then you went your way
and I went mine"
"just for two moments existed
the story of our hearts"
"and then you went your way
and I went mine"
Today's my wedding day abbaji
aren't you going to give me away?
Aren't you going to put
your hand on my head and bless me?
Please forgive me, my child
I don't know whether this
is my obligation or my weakness
Please forgive me
This is a holy amulet.
This will protect you
The moment you cross the border,
take out the coins...
and give them to someone needy
My religion does not permit,
but still from now on...
I'll pray to allah everyday and ask Him
to give you zaara in every other birth
I'm leaving...
Listen...
Sign here
What's this?
It says here that my name
is rajesh rathore
I work for the Indian Intelligence raW
...critical... political... secrecy...
sending Pakistani secrets to India...?
That's correct
No way. My name is Veer Pratap Singh,
ex-lndian air Force
I'd come here just two days ago to
visit somebody and now I'm going back
My passport's in my bag, you can check.
We've found this in your bag
Your name is written clearly
as rajesh rathore
Let me see
We have witnesses also
who can recognise you
What's going on,
why are you doing this?
Okay... you were just saying that
you were here to meet somebody
Tell us their names,
we'll call them
Yes... I'm...
I'm here...
Tell us
I didn't come to meet anybody
Wow, what love
If you take her name
she will be disgraced?
You'll ruin yourself
but won't let your love be damned
Yes Mr. Veer, this's exactly
what I expected of you
Mr. Veer, there's one thing that is
very special about both our countries
On the basis of power and money
anything is possible. Isn't that so?
What were you thinking?
That you could come here...
and declare your love for my wife-to-be
in front of everyone and leave...
and I'd stand aside
and watch the whole show...?
Mr. Veer I'm about to live my life
with a woman...
who's in love with someone else
and it's my bad luck that I can't even
back off from this marriage
can you imagine...
can you imagine... everyday of my life,
will be a living hell
You and zaara were the ones who dared
to love... why should I be put to test
Either your life should
be a living hell...
or zaara's,
Not mine
You take great pride
in your love, right?
So now you're being tested
I can make zaara's life heaven or hell.
But it's all in your hands
as long as you sit silently
within the four walls of a prison...
till then zaara's life
will be more beautiful than heaven
The moment you open your mouth
zaara's life will become worse than hell
Veer Pratap Singh's identity
has to be destroyed...
in order to give zaara a good life
Now this... is the true
test of love
I'll take your leave
It's time for the wedding
Either you disgrace the names of zaara
and her family and buy your freedom
Or else sign on those papers and ensure
life time of happiness for zaara
The decision is in your hands
Goodbye
"Why is there a tradition of cruelty"
"Why is the society the way it is"
"These traditions of this world...
I am completely overwhelmed by them"
"do not ask what my complaints are
Or why I've been given this unhappiness"
"What can I tell you,
Why is love a crime"
"Why does one cry
Why does this happen"
"Why is everyone a stranger
to his heart"
"What turn has this story taken"
"What sort of world is this
that we live in"
"Where sorrows
wear the face of happiness?"
"Whom do I call my own
and who is a stranger"
"What turn has this story taken"
Miss zaara Hayaat Khan
daughter of jehangir Hayaat Khan
Your marriage has been fixed
with raza Shirazi...
son of abdul Malik Shirazi at a dowry of...
five million rupees.
Do you accept this marriage?
"What turn has my story taken"
do you accept that your name
is rajesh rathore or no?
I accept
The bus that left from Lahore met with
an accident before it reached India
Nobody survived
My name was also on the
passenger list
I was happy that Maati and Bauji
would hear about my death
If they got the news
that I was missing...
then they wouldn't have been able
to live or die in peace
Now in India Veer Pratap Singh
was dead and in Pakistan...
there was no sign of
Veer Singh left
Now his only identity was...
Prisoner number seven eighty six
Prisoner... number,
Seven eight six
My country owes you, twenty two years
of your life
I can't bring back
these twenty two years
But I take a vow...
that I won't put flowers
on my father's grave until...
Veer Pratap Singh doesn't get his name,
his identity and his country back
So Miss Saamiya Siddiqui,
this is your first case?
Yes. - Congratulations
Thank you sir
and you're defence counsel on behalf
of the Human rights commission...?
That's right sir.
- Good that's good
No one representing the prosecution?
Well Sir they should be coming.
May I come in sir?
Oh it's you Mr. zakir...
Good morning sir.
- Morning. Come in, take a seat
That's Mr. zakir ahmed
I know. I know him very well
Sorry Your Honour, you know
the traffic of Lahore...
zakir sa'ab, are you presenting the case
on behalf of the Government of Pakistan?
Yes Sir. Actually, I've not been
to court since many days
People may be thinking that zakir ahmed
has forgotten how to fight a case
and anyway, I think this case is
very interesting
What do you think Saamiya?
So you both know one another?
Of course! Saamiya was working
for us earlier
But perhaps she didn't approve
of the way we worked...
so she went over
to the Human rights camp
She's a very capable lady,
it'll be fun to fight the case opposite her
There was a special purpose
for calling both of you here
It would be better if both the parties
can have an out of court settlement
Otherwise the court has fixed
the date for day after tomorrow
But yes, if the case does not start
day after tomorrow...
then the next date could be
after six months or maybe even a year
We're ready Sir. But if the defence
needs more time then...
defence is ready Sir.
- But Saamiya...
Sir you can fix it for day after tomorrow.
My client has waited...
for twenty two years to get justice.
I can't make him wait any more
Okay then that's fixed
I thank you both for coming here
Good day.
- Good day, Sir
Okay Saamiya I'll see you in court.
Good day
This was an impossible case
right from the start
and now with zakir ahmed's arrival
there's absolutely no chance
But this case is too small
for his portfolio... I don't know why
I can't understand anything. Listen, just
make any excuse and drop this case
This is your first case and the way
zakir ahmed insults the opposition...
he'll ruin your career.
That's exactly what he wants
What do you mean?
Saahil, do one thing,
you go back to
the office & make a list of the witnesses
I'll be there in a while...
But where're you going?
- To meet zakir ahmed
What...?
Miss Saamiya Siddiqui you'd sworn that
you'd never step into my office
Then how could you bear
to come here today?
There's nothing like that Sir, just
my principles differed from yours
and I thought that if I could not
respect working by your principles...
then it's better that I leave.
- Interesting, very interesting
You've developed great principles
at a young age
My principles have been passed on
to me as my father's legacy
do you know that you're
the first person, Saamiya...
who refused to take a case
offered by zakir ahmed
Here people wait for years in the hope
of getting their first case
But I recognised your capability,
I chose you...
I ignored your age,
your inexperience...
and even the fact that you're a woman.
And what did you do inspite of that?
You threw the case back in my face.
It would've set a criminal free, Sir
and according to me
that would've been wrong
It's not a lawyer's job to decide
what's right or wrong. It's the court's job
a lawyer's duty is to win the case
under any circumstance. Nothing else
Well, that's the difference
between you and me, Sir
Your principle is to fight to win
and my principle is to fight for the truth
Interesting, very interesting!
So now you're giving me lessons in law
This was all that was left
for me to experience
Let's forget the past, otherwise we'll
keep opening up old wounds
If you've taken the trouble
to come all the way here...
then it must be something important.
Sit. What can zakir ahmed do for you?
Look Sir, being my first case
it's obvious that...
I will make some mistakes...
and now that you're the opposition
the problems will increase
Because of some trifle on my part...
I don't want that Indian prisoner's
freedom to be revoked. Because...
he's completely innocent.
That's true. A great injustice...
has been done to him Sir
and he truly deserves his freedom
Finally you've stooped down
to our level
Basically you've come asking for help
to win your first case, right?
Defeating zakir ahmed takes your career
off to a flying start! No...?
Have you forgotten that zakir ahmed
has never lost a case as yet?
And now it's very important for me
to win this case...
because I want to teach a lesson to
headstrong youngsters like yourself...
the repercussions of not following
zakir ahmed's principles
What's the matter
Miss Saamiya Siddique?
Lost faith in your principles of truth
that you come begging for a win?
Please forgive me Sir, for a while
I thought that you were almost human
I just came to discuss
if there's any possibility of...
giving this man his freedom
without taking this case to court
But you mistook my humanity
to be my weakness
Now we'll meet in court.
Be prepared to lose your first case...
because now prisoner 786
is being sent to India... and...
neither you nor the
State of pakistan is stopping me
Interesting
Very interesting
can I ask you one question...?
You hadn't spoken to anyone
in all these years...
then why did you tell me your story?
You called me by my name
What...?
You're the first person
who didn't doubt my innocence...
that I am Veer Singh
The truth is that in all these years
I'd forgotten my own identity...
you reminded me of who I am, you gave me
respect by calling me by my name
Veer Pratap Singh
For a prisoner who has been insulted
for the last twenty two years...
this was a great thing!
Great thing
Now I'll eat some more, okay?
Tomorrow is our first day in court.
You remember your promise, don't you?
That you're going to change out of the
garb of seven eighty six and come as...
Squadron Leader Veer Pratap Singh
No. - What?
Do you remember your promise?
- Of course I remember it
Under no circumstances am I to mention
name of zaara or the Hayaat Khan family
You keep your promise
and I'll keep mine
Your Honour, defence would like
to call its first witness
defence calls its first witness
defence rests Your Honour
I call upon the prosecution
to present its case
Your Honour...
a man has been in prison
for the past twenty two years...
and that prison is in Pakistan.
And that man...
who was imprisoned in a pakistani jail
since twenty two years is...
an Indian
Hearing this, you, me, and everyone
sitting in this courtroom...
will have tears in their eyes.
And we'll hope for some way...
that man can go back
to his country... to his home
Because we are human
and we've been taught...
to respect all human beings.
But Your Honour...
in a court of law what man can't
see the law can...
and according to the law
the State is bigger than the individual
and for a person who works against
the interests of the country...
even being sentenced to death
twenty two times is less
This case is as transparent as water
There's no question of any doubt
prosecution will in a matter
of just thirty minutes...
and with the help of just three witnesses
prove without a doubt...
that the defendant rajesh rathore
is not worthy...
of going back to his country
or his home until his dying day
That's all Your Honour
Now I call upon the defence
to present their case
Ms. Siddiqui, best of luck
Your Honour, prosecution counsel
Mr. zaheer Khan was very quick to...
zakir ahmed
say that this case
is as transparent as water
But Mr. zaheer Khan forgets...
Ms. Saamiya Siddique...
My name is zakir ahmed!
- Being called by another name once...
has infuriated you to such
an extent? Then just think...
if you were called by another name every
single day for twenty two years...
can you imagine, what would
it feel like then?
Your Honour this case is not being
fought to send an Indian back...
to his country or his home. This case
is being fought to give a man back...
his identity, his individuality...
Someone is asking you...
to give him back his name!
He's telling you that...
I am Veer Pratap Singh
ex-lndian air Force Officer
Squadron Leader Veer Pratap Singh
just give me back
the respectability of my name
I don't want anything else
Maybe not in thirty minutes
like the prosecution counsel...
but I will definitely prove that
this man is not rajesh rathore...
but he is Veer Pratap Singh.
Then whether you send him to India...
or keep him in Pakistan,
that is in your hands
That's all Your Honour
Now prosecution may call upon
it's witnesses
I'd like to call upon my first witness
police Officer dilbaaz Khan...
who had arrested rajesh rathod
twenty two years ago
could you tell the court without
any doubt or hesitation...
who this man is?
Yes Sir, I remember very well
This man is an Indian spy.
He's an agent of raW, rajesh rathore
Some twenty two years ago,
anwar ali and myself...
we forced him to get off a bus going
from Lahore to India and arrested him
We had received an
intelligence report...
that this man was
conspiring against Pakistan.
Good
Mr. anwar ali, can you tell me,
if you found in his bag...
a passport identifying him
as rajesh rathore...
then how is it possible that
this same man's ticket...
was booked in the name of
Veer Pratap Singh?
But Sir, that was the thing...
Honour, this person also had a passport
in the name of Veer Pratap Singh
and how could one person
have two passports?
For this reason our suspicion
changed to certainty
and after we questioned him,
he himself signed the affidavit...
I, rajesh rathore
I've being seeing him
for the last ten years
He was always quiet
and kept to himself
He never communicated with any one
But whenever a prisoner
was ill or upset...
he would go forth
to heal him and comfort him
I don't know if he is
Veer Pratap Singh or rajesh rathore...
for me he's just 786
God's own man
Yes Sir, this Hindu here is
allah's noble servant
He spent twenty two years in prison.
Can't be greater punishment than this
Send him back to his homeland...
send him back
Looks like you, Mr. Majid Khan, have no
great love for your country Pakistan
If it were up to you then every person
who had spied upon Pakistan...
every conspirator, should be set
free by the court?
Sir, that's not what I meant...
just reply with a yes or a no
Mr. Majid Khan, only with
a yes or no
No.
Good
Your witness
No questions Your Honour
The next date for this
case is after a week,
Before me, on Monday, 21st March
On that day I will hear
the defence's case
and immediately after that
I will give my judgement
defence should be ready
with their case
adjourned
I'll have to mention
zaara's name...
No...
please... for once...
let me bring zaara or any one person
from the Hayaat family to the court...
and in a moment the verdict
will swing to our favour
absolutely not...
Why don't you try and understand?
We're losing this case
The court does not have time
for prisoners like you...
in this country there are
too many prisoners and too few courts
a lot of prisoners' cases
come up after they're dead
You'll never get
such an opportunity again
You'll die lying right here...
you'll die! Don't you understand?
Zaara must be the mother
of two by now
She perhaps has a 21 year old daughter
and a 19 year old boy
She must've passed through all the
good and bad times of her life
Her days, her evenings must've
settled down to a fine rhythm
Must be a peaceful life now for zaara
and tomorrow you'll drag her to court
and in front of everyone...
you'll ask her
who's Veer Pratap Singh?
Questions will be raised, what is
the relationship between Veer and zaara?
And no one will be able
to understand the answers...
no one will understand
In an instant that raza Shirazi
will divorce her. Zaara's life...
will be ruined. She must be
living peacefully
For the last twenty two years
I have been guarding her honour
Today how can I trample upon
her honour and go home?
I can't do this Saamiya
and I know you won't
be able to do it either
I'm sorry, for a while being a
lawyer made me forget my humanity
I forgot...
That Veer and zaara's names
can never be taken together
Now there's only one way out...
I'll have to go to India...
to bring Veer Pratap Singh's
identity from his country
Time is short
I'm leaving.
Take care
Saamiya...
Until now this amulet has protected me,
now it will protect you
If I lose...
will you forgive me...?
On one condition...
every day you must bring me...
laddoos
Take care
Excuse me...
can you show me where
chaudhry Sumer Singh's house is?
Yes... the largest house
at the corner there...
that's chaudhry saab's house.
- Thanks
But who're you looking for?
For Mr. Singh and his wife...
It's been years since
both of them died...
But if you want to see the house
you're most welcome
That house is always open
I'm in a bit of a hurry,
please forgive me, goodbye
zaara, oh zaara...
I'm not sparing you
Hey who're you, what d'you want?
Hey why're you crying?
Say something, are you
deaf or what?
Hey Shabbo, look here's a visitor
and you jassi... come here
Oh you'll be the death of me
I'll tell your Ma,
you aren't studying...
Yes... tell me...
what do you want?
You're Shabbo...?
Who else can I be?
And she's...
zaara?
You came asking this?
Is she zaara Hayaat Khan?
How do you know this name?
She's jehangir Hayaat Khan's
daughter from Lahore?
Who are you?
After hearing about Veer's death,
zaara called off the marriage
abbaji himself got her divorced
zaara came here to help Bauji and Maati
...to make Veer's dream come true
raza settled overseas.
Abbaji left politics
He died two years afterwards,
a few years later Ma'am also died
The Hayaat Khan name
no longer existed
Today Bauji and Maati
are also no more
But she won't go back. She says...
My soul is embedded here.
Now I'll live and die here
Which century are these
people from Shabbo?
There's a Veer who so easily sacrificed
twenty two years of his life...
to protect zaara's honour...
and there's zaara who spent
twenty two years of her life...
in a strange land
to keep Veer's dream alive
are they humans pretending to be Gods
or are they Gods disguised as humans?
This...
was my mother's
Twenty two years ago Mariam Hayaat Khan
had tied this amulet on an Indian...
while bidding him goodbye
so that it would protect him
That person did not reach India
but for twenty two years...
this charm has been protecting him
That person's name is...
Veer Pratap Singh
He's in prison, in a jail in Lahore
I am his lawyer
and I've come to take you to him
For the last twenty two years
God has been testing you both intensely
But now not even God
can separate zaara and Veer
Not even God
Mr. Saahil Farrouqi I'm asking you
where is the defence counsel?
Your Honour, she must be on her way
Looks like she has decided to
give up the case
Please begin with the proceedings
Irresponsible...
absolutely irresponsible of the
defence counsel not to have arrived
Mr. Saahil Farrouqi, do you have
anything to say?
Your Honour, Saamiya... I mean my
learned colleague should be here soon
There's no problem...
There is a problem Mr. Farrouqi,
there is a problem
It's no small matter to waste
the court's time in this manner
Especially when
I had clearly specified...
that this day has been reserved
for the defence's case...
then what is the reason
for her absence from the court?
It's obvious that the
defence does not have a case
Silence on the defendant's part and no
one appearing on behalf of the defence...
"For you, I have lived all these days"
"With my lips sealed"
"For you, I have lived all these days,
with my unshed tears"
"But in my heart,
the flames of love"
"Have always been burning for you,
only for you"
"Life has brought me..."
"a volume of old times"
"and I am surrounded by
countless memories"
"Unasked, I have now found
all the answers I sought"
"Look, what I yearned for"
"and what I got"
"But in my heart, the flames of love"
"Have always been burning for you,
only for you"
"How can I describe
the cruelty of this world"
"I was ordered that I have to live
but without you"
"Unwise are those who say that
to me you are unknown"
"So many ordeals, were heaped
on me by this world"
"But in my heart, the flames of love"
"Have always been burning for you,
only for you"
"For you, I have lived
all these days"
"With my lips sealed"
"For you, I have lived all these days,
with my unshed tears"
"But in my heart, the flames of love,
have always been burning for you"
"Only for you"
zaara Hayaat Khan's testimony...
and photographs and documents
presented by her prove that...
this man is not rajesh rathore
but that he is Veer Pratap Singh
and to prevent disgracing
the honour of a pakistani girl...
Veer Pratap Singh signed
that affidavit
Squadron Leader Veer Pratap Singh,
this court exonerates you
Go on Veer Pratap Singh, go on
You have the right to return to your
country with your head held high
and for the precious twenty two years
of your life wasted in prison...
the State of Pakistan and this court
asks your forgiveness
If you wish to speak, you may
I prisoner number seven eighty six...
Look through the bars of the jail
I see days months years
change to eons
From the soil of this land comes
the fragrance of my Bauji's fields
This burning sun reminds me of
my Maati's cool buttermilk
This rain brings along with it
the swings of my seasons...
this winter fills me with the warmth
of the fires of my Lodi
They say that this is not your country
then why does it feel like mine"
He says that I am not like him
then why does he look like me...?"
I prisoner number seven eighty six
look through the bars of the jail"
I see an angel
who has come down from heaven
She calls herself Saamiya
and she calls me Veer"
She's a complete stranger
but treats me as her own"
Hearing her truthful words
I feel like living once more"
Hearing her promises and vows
I feel like doing something more"
They say that she is no one of mine
then why does she fight the world for me?"
He says that I'm not like her
then why does she look like me...?"
I prisoner number seven eighty six,
look through the bars of the jail"
I see my zaara wrapped
in the colours of my village
In making my dreams come true
she has forgotten her own..."
in serving my people
she has left behind her own"
Now I feel like filling her
being with happiness
I feel like living
another lifetime for her
They say that my country is not hers
then why is she staying in my home"
He says that I'm not like her
then why does she look like me..."
I prisoner number seven eighty six,
look through the bars of the jail"
Saamiya
congratulations
Thank you
This was my last case
I'm giving up law
Because you've taught me that
I'm not fit for this work
I always thought that
a country's progress is measured...
to it's judicial system.
But now I understand that...
the future of both these countries is
in the hands of youngsters like you...
who do not measure humans as
big-small, man-woman, Hindu-Muslim...
who don't rake up bitter war memories
of 1947-1965 and 1999 on every pretext
Who wish to address the future
with the truth and only the truth...
and there's no stopping a country
where Truth prevails
Thank you Saamiya
Thank you for teaching me
the value of truth and justice
Your father would've been proud of you,
he would've been very proud
I am
Goodbye
Veer had lost zaara in Pakistan.
So Veer and zaara...
will be joined together
on pakistani soil
Here take this...
make our zaara yours forever
You said, Veer and zaara's names
can never be taken together
Now Veer and zaara's names
have been joined together forever
What Veer says is true
You're an angel...
sent only for us by God
Go on...
Iook your country awaits you
come zaara
Let us go home