CJ Entertainment Presents
A CJ Entertainment Production
In association with
Ikyoung Film, Sidus HQ
Produced by Lee Kang-bok
Executive Producers
Lee Kang-bok, Choi Pyun-ho
Co-Producer Seok Dong-jun
Producer Song Chang-yong
Lim Chang-jung
Kim Seon-ah
Directed by Oh Sang-hoon
I don't know what I was thinking
maybe I wasn't thinking?
Maybe thoughts
just went out of my mind
I can't believe this!
Why is this happening to me?
- Number 35
- Yes
- Number 36
- Number 37
- Yes
You guys are up next
Miss, what number are you?
- I'm 34, Jang Mi-young
- Jang Mi-young?
You missed it
You'll have to wait
What do you mean
I missed it?
Sit down and wait
I had a call from nature
Wait till you're called
I can't afford to wait
Look, lady
This isn't your playground!
Please, let me go in
I won't be long
- I must go in
- Go sit down
Go!
You can leave now
Those that I've called go in
and sit to the left
Relax and do your thing
Next!
Excuse me!
I'm 34, Jang Mi-young
I had to go to
Sorry
Hold on!
Give me a sec
I had diarrhea so I had
to use the ladies' room
I couldn't help it
I'm just saying
Please, give me a chance
Let go!
You took my man
How dare you
You took my
Sorry, but
Can I do this later?
The Greatest Expectation
Let's go, number 3!
I'm hungry
You had a hotdog earlier
I'm still hungry
Are we buying all these?
Do you have money?
Do I?
We're putting them back later
Why?
It's just what you do here
Too much meat isn't good
for your system
Dumplings!
Remember it's called a buffet
Wasn't it fun today?
We saw lots of animals,
didn't we?
Tell Jang-mi so, okay?
Your grandma's not home
Don't forget the word,
'buffet'
- Say it for me
- Buffet
Tell Jang-mi we ate
at a buffet, okay?
Grandma
You scared me
What was that for?
Bastard!
Where on earth
have you been, son?
Grandma,
I'm not your son
What's this then?
Tits?
No, it's a penis!
He's the seed you planted
So take care of him!
Okay, okay!
Grandma, I'm thirsty
Are you, my pumpkin?
Come on, I'll get you
some water
- Where are you going?
- To make money!
It's changed
Mom?
What are you doing?
It's so upsetting!
I can't believe this
Don't you wanna know
how the audition went?
I know you failed it again
You sure you're my mom?
I found you under a bridge
No!
This is so frustrating!
I never win
Shitty game
- Can't stand it anymore
- Where are you going?
Playing cards again?
I need to practice
in real life
I'm starving!
Collect the late fees and
order some Chinese
You're so young
You don't even have a man?
Always coming home for meals
Hey, wanna play cards?
Look who's here
Shoes!
Where the hell did you go?
What?
I was at Jang-mi's
Jang-mi's busy with work
So I baby-sat the boy
Some cartoonist she is!
She made a bum
do her volunteer work?
Okay, that's fine
What's this?
'Sympathy for Mr. Vengeance'
Why haven't you returned it?
I was going to
Don't watch videos or eat
unless you make money
Did you think I'd flee the country
over this lousy video?
Why the hell did you call?
My mom told me to
Better be nice
to your biggest patron
The late fee comes to 1,500 won
Tajja 2' is still out?
Who the hell rented it?
'Tajja 2'?
He should here soon
Here comes your meal!
Did you bring it?
Sure did! I didn't come
empty-handed
That'll be $3.50
I meant 'Tajja 2'
Oh, that!
Darn, I forgot again
I'm so stupid
It's him?
He rented 'Tajja 2'?
Mr... Chinese Food
Don't you have any etiquette?
Return what you rent on time
Who's this wise ass?
I know you're all busy
but it's been a week
What do you care?
You don't pay my late fees
Do you have any idea
what emotional trauma
others go through
waiting on that book?
I've had to endure the pain
of waiting for that book!
What are you babbling on about?
Read Part 3 first then
That's what it's there for
The story doesn't connect!
You reconnect it then
You corn-headed asshole!
What are you gonna do about it?
Please, return it ASAP
What the hell!
Did I stain it
with noodle soup?
Did I tear off a section
and wipe my ass?
Who says deliverymen
shouldn't read the funnies!
Should I just fucking
deliver all day!
Can't a girl eat in peace!
What was that?
Leave it,
or take it outside
Even with a mouthful,
you're still so pretty
Not so fast, wise guy
Finish what you started
Come on, make my day
What's your problem?
Return it soon, please
Or what?
You'll pay late fees
Stupid asshole
Hey, pay your late fees!
Change the part
in your hair!
Leave!
Shit!
He eats like a pig, man
Took him to a buffet
He cleaned out every dish
in the restaurant
Time to pay out, girl
I'm hungry
Eat this
Wait till I get paid for this
I don't understand
Why are you helping
the less fortunate?
Nobody's worse-off
than you
No crumbs, okay?
I'm working here
and you're watching TV?
Losing your focus?
What? The breath of a man
distracts you?
Wanna get laid?
You took my man
How dare you
I'm gonna kill you
- Aaaaah!
- What are you doing?
You scared me!
- Dinner?
- I ate!
No, for me?
What am I, your maid or something?
You're a bum
You should've cooked
It's on the table
Go stuff yourself
Wasn't I scared!
Mi-young, you're dead!
You wore my clothes again!
No, I never wore that leopard panties
So stupid!
How'd you know
I was talking about it then?
Stupid idiot!
I just tried it on
It's all stretched out!
I told you a hundred times
Your ass is way too big!
Maybe it was made loose
God!
Go get me
a pack of cigarettes
You go get it!
Don't want the change?
You smoke 'Time', right?
Shit!
What's the point?
You're dying soon anyway
God damn it!
Hey, you!
What?
I'm missing a dime
So?
It was $1.40,
but now it's only $1.30
So what?
- Give me a dime
- Why should I?
You bumped into me
You weren't looking
where you were going
I was
That old man in red
Don't be a tightwad
Give me a dime
Why should I?
You're not going home
until you find it
Or give me a dime
so I can buy my cigarettes
You choose!
My legs hurt
What a freaking girl!
What?
What's your problem?
Please, spare me a dime
I'm begging you
I need it to buy cigarettes
I'll take it
off your late fees
What does that have
to do with this?
Making me crazy
Why should I give you
any money?
What took you so long?
Shut up
That bitch!
Hey, why is this open?
Merciless bitch
That merciless bitch
I can't believe that bitch
Brother?
I'm home
Oh, hey
I'm hitting the sack
- He's going to bed
- Get off of me
Come on, we can't stop now
I said, get off
Damn it!
I've got a fucking demon
for a brother
Twenty years of age
M&A
The revolutionary movement
that was in Czech?
Prague Spring
Fucking stocks!
How can she not know that?
Independence Editorial
Ojak Bridge
Spinoza
Hi
Fuck me!
You don't have a penny
In that account
Right, what a stupid thing to do
Maybe I should
go to your wife
Wait outside
I helped you make money
Give me ten more
- $10 my ass! Ten? Ten? Ten!
- Fuck!
I'm still down $8 Gs, man
You don't have any right
to ask for anything!
Don't hit me on the head! Fuck!
It'll bounce back
If she finds out that
I touched that account
I'm as good as dead
So, stop bullshitting me
- Keep your mouth shut
- I got sources telling me
When a flying saucer
lands at the airport?
Don't be such a wuss
You gotta look ahead
No wonder dad always
- beating the crap out of you
- Shut up!
For 12 bra and panty pairs
it's only $39.80
What an incredible price!
And we give you
a sexy ivory nightgown for free
On our last broadcast
I was so tempted
So I bought my sister
this set of lingerie
Let me tell you
She absolutely loved it
That lying bitch!
When'd you get me any
freaking panties?
You're so two-faced
Go!
Come on, decide your move
That!
Lose that one
Shut up
He might take it
Trust me on this
If he takes it,
he gets more points
I bet he doesn't have it
Do as I say
You sure?
He doesn't have this?
- Shall I?
- Of course
- Maybe you're right
- Yes, of course!
Trust me
Go ahead
So stupid
Why is that my fault?
- Shut up!
- Why are you hitting me?
Stop hitting me!
I've had it! Don't expect
to see me again!
What are you doing here?
Reading the funnies
You have a lot at your shop
Why pay to read them here?
You can't always eat at home
Sometimes you eat out, right?
Leave me alone
Don't get fresh with me, girl
Jang-mi!
Why is the door locked?
Eating pork, or something?
We're out of lettuce
Why aren't you eating?
Help yourself
I couldn't care less
if they starved to death
I will love you
- until the end of time...
- One two, one two
God, I peed on myself
Why does that old fart
jog at night?
What's wrong with him!
Man
- Damn!
- Let's go!
We're fucked, man
Let's get out of here
Come on, Drive!
God damn it!
They're taking him
to the hospital, right?
I guess so
They know we saw it
You got the plate?
- What?
- The plate number?
Yeah
Fuck!
Fuck! Is he dead?
Heaven doesn't help those
who helped themselves
Nothing in life works
in my favor
Should we bury him?
- Bury what?
- No, we shouldn't
We'll get life for that
That's too long, isn't it?
Way too long
Why the fuck now?
This is a bad sign
What do you have
for eyes?
Marbles, asshole!
What boss Drives himself?
I gave that money to you
to get a fucking
driver's license!
And you drank it away!
- You're doing it!
- No way!
What makes you think
I can teach?
Why the hell not?
You didn't go to college
to be a bum, did you?
She's right
A bum with a degree?
That's too much
It's been 2 years
You can't freeload off of us
forever
Yeah, that's too much
Hush!
Maybe I should get married
and move out of here
Dream on
What girl wants to marry
a piece of shit like you?
She must be mentally ill
Zip it!
Decide now
Will you teach, or move out?
Show some respect
I'm your brother-in-law
- Look, Mister
- What?
Earn some respect
Then I'll be nice to you
Where are you going?
Get off my back!
Stop it before I Drown
myself in the river
You get fined for dumping
garbage in the river
Yeah, no garbage dumping
in the river
- That expensive?
- One Go!
No, let me think about it
- I was on the phone
- What was that?
A herbal diet program
Why don't I beat you up
to lose some weight?
Herbal dietso ridiculous
My ass is huge
What about my thighs?
Actresses nowadays are
all toothpicks
You should take a look at one of them
I saw this actress
the other day
She was so skinny
I thought she was dying
She looked like this
You like that?
That's in lately
Looking as fragile as a willow
Willow my ass
Keep playing cards
I'm so hating you, mom
I'm not your mom
I told you I found you
under a bridge
- Stop distracting me
- Some mom you are!
Two Go!
One more Go, and I win!
It's so unfair
You have a big mouth
So does my sister
But look at me!
I have a hard time
getting a hotdog in
Come here
I'll rip it open wider
When I get some money,
I'll have a DNA test done
It'd be a waste of money
Where are you going?
To find my biological mom!
Three Go!
Wanted: Eyewitnesses
Reward: $5,000
Yeah, I saw everything
Now? Where?
Yeah, I know that place
I was wondering...
Did anybody else call?
Because this girl
Oh, I see
Sure, I'll be there
Five thousand dollars!
Excuse me
You called, didn't you?
I'm so glad he's okay
He got hit pretty hard
He's healthy, isn't he?
I know he jogs every night
Right
Going to the police?
Yes, by the way,
did you see the plate?
Of course!
I saw everything
The plate, make and
model of the car
- Get in
- Okay
Thank God I witnessed it
Otherwise, you wouldn't be
able to nail those bastards
Oh, you have company
Should I sit in the back?
Sure
Hey, wake up
- Hey!
- Who the fuck are you?
It's me The video girl
From the video store?
What are you doing here?
In the trunk of their car
I came for the reward and
ended up in here like you
You mean that
They put up that sign?
I think so
Mannothing good left in this world
What'd they hit me with?
It hurts like hell
Shut up and
let's untie ourselves
Turn around
- What for?
- Turn around!
Oh, our hands are tied
Don't pretend to be
so sensitive
Let me untie you first
Done?
What are you doing?
Untie me now
Hold on
Let me catch my breath
What are you doing?
What shampoo do you use?
Stop fooling around
Untie me now
This is important for me
What do you use?
What are you, a pervert?
It's 'Dove'
'Dove'?
I thought so
Don't move
Stop wiggling
- Come on!
- Stay put
Okay, hold on
Okay, done
God, he's slow
What?
What are you doing?
It's too dark in here
We need to find a weapon
It uses up the oxygen
Give me a break
We're not in a coal mine
I need to fix my makeup
What a girl!
What are you doing?
Pop the trunk!
Can't even do that?
You go
I told you to go
- Move aside
- Don't hit me!
- You're so useless, It's right here!
- Where?
Can't even do this?
- Please, don't kill us
- Don't kill us
Move your arm
- Roll it down
- Okay
Don't kill us
Let us go!
Stop right there!
Go get them!
So the hit-and-run Driver
tried to kidnap you?
You don't get it, do you?
It wasn'tjust an
attempted kidnapping
They tried to kill us!
- Plate number?
- Give it to him
What?
The plate number is
- I don't quite...
- You forgot the number?
How could you!
It was too dark to see it!
You told me you got it
when I asked you
Stop yelling at me!
Quiet, both of you!
So
You witnessed a hit-and-run
and almost got kidnapped
But neither of you remembers
the plate number?
How do you expect me
to bust these guys?
At least
Give me the city
it's registered to
Seoul!
And it's a 'Potentia'
Yeah, that's it!
Potentia! Potentia!
What about you, Miss?
- 38!
- What's that?
- Last two digits of the plate
- You sure?
I'd bet my big ass on it
You're so dead
Stop it!
I struggled to open this bar
And you tell me to run
like a chicken?
So you can take over
this place?
Yeah, I mightjust run
Only if I first get wasted
But I can't and won't
We might catch them
Who knows?
We have to!
You're a novice
I'm God of this game
- Should I help you?
- Can you?
My ID is 'Cicinnurus Regius'
When I see you on line
I'll make you invincible
Cicinnurus Regius?
Yeah Yours?
'Wandering Monk'?
- Don't forget my ID
- I won't
Do you know the legend
of 'Cicinnurus Regius'?
Of course, I do
What is it then?
Why the hell should I
tell you?
What is it?
I've placed an APB on the car
You can go now
Go where?
You're sending us home?
What, you wanna play
soccer with us?
Our lives are at risk here
Don't you have a witness
protection program?
Witness what?
You've seen too many movies
He's a bum
with nothing but time
You should protect us
Our taxes pay your salary
Do yourjob right
I doubt
you've ever paid taxes
Hey, Video!
Whose side are you on?
That's the truth
You can't even afford to
pay your late fees
You ran like a chicken earlier
You call yourself a man?
Yeah, I'm a girl, dick!
What?
What an annoying couple!
Couple?
Stop fighting
with your girlfriend
- What?
- Girlfriend?
Who?
- Hey, Video!
- What?
Stay out of my way
from now on
Don't even think about
renting videos from us
What are you, a moron?
It isn't the
only video shop in Korea
We don't need bums
for customers
Watch your back at night
Watch your back
during the day
Bitch!
I warned you
The interview is at three
Don't be late
I don't have a suit to wear
Can we do this later?
You can borrow mine
I didn't wanna worry
you guys, but
- My life is in danger
- I won't kill you if you show up
I'm notjoking
You think I am?
If you don't show up you're dead
and he's divorced
What?
I've been waiting for you
What for?
I'm off today
Let's go see a movie
Why should I see a movie
with you?
We're neighbors
and business partners
We can discuss ways to develop
our neighborhood over coffee
How about it?
I'm not in the mood, okay?
Turn me down, and you will
never see that book again
Suit yourself
You'll run up your late fees
Wait!
Hello?
I'm so busy
What do they want?
Why ask me?
I didn't call you here
Here they are
Hi I'm the lawyer
for the late Mr. Hwang
- Mr. Hwang?
- Who's that?
- That old man in red?
- Him?
How much will it be?
What?
The reward
Come on, the man is dead
You don't like money?
Fine
I'll keep it all to myself
Says who?
We'll split it in half
I was gonna go
but the police
- No more excuses!
- I'm not lying
Call him right now
and apologize!
I don't even know him
I don't fucking care
Call him you idiot!
If you don't call him now
I'll starve you to death
You never keep your word,
you piece of garbage!
- What's the number?
- Write it down!
If I drop dead today,
it's all your fault
You're so full of shit!
- Shoot
- 992-3285
- Worthless idot!
- 3285?
- Yes, son of a bitch!
- I'll call him, damn it!
- Right now!
- Fuck
What?
Guess I'm not the only one
who wants a piece of you
It was my sister-in-law
Is that how you talk to her?
Don't get started
You've got no manners
for anybody
My sister-in-law and I
We went to school together and she's
the daughter of my mom's friend
We go way back, okay?
Sorry to keep you waiting
Please, sit
Without you, we couldn't
have recovered his body
We owe you a lot
Thank you
We just wanted justice
to be served
That's all
I feel so sorry for him
and for his grandchild
Oh, that picture?
That's my sibling
Your sibling?
It was taken long ago
The child went missing
on a family picnic
My father had wanted
to find his lost child so badly
Please, take it
It's a token of my gratitude
You don't have to do this
You really don't
7, 8, 9, 10
5 Gs!
That much?
Look at the size of the house
This is chicken feed
for them
Should we be happy
about this?
We didn't kill him, did we?
If he'd made it, he would've
given us twice more
Let's go eat
It's my treat
Have you decided?
Yeah
- Why don't you order first?
- Sure
I'll have what she's having
Excuse me?
Get me the same thing
she's getting
Okay, sir
Go ahead
I'll have the same
This is pretty good
By the way,
we haven't met, have we?
- We shoulds stop swearing first
- I'm Mi-young, Jang Mi-young
Jang Miyoung? Got it!
- What's yours?
- Chang-sik, Kim Chang-sik
Chang-sik?
What?
My name's tacky?
That's not it
People always say their
names twice
It's a subconscious way of
letting themselves stand out
Is that right?
I'm a psychology major
I see
Speaking of which
- Let me ask you something
- What?
I always wondered
Do they teach you hypnotizm?
That's a piece of cake
Anybody can do it
- Stop lying
- Want me to prove it?
Here?
Close your eyes
Open both your hands
I'm dropping a feather on your
left hand, It's very light
I'm putting a metal bracelet on your
right hand, which is very heavy
The feather is so light
while the bracelet is
quite heavy
Open your eyes now
I can do this trick, too
What'd I say?
Anybody can do it
Keep eating
You're such a cheapskate
No matter where you drink,
it's the same beer
Stop bitching, just drink
What are you gonna do
with that money?
Get your face redone?
Anyway, this is on you
Right?
Waiter!
I studied psychology
so hard
But I failed to read her mind
I loved her so
'Dove'!
She used that shampoo,
didn't she?
I hear body odor is harder
to forget than faces are
Right?
Mi-young
You know what rules
in a capitalist society?
That is
A rich guy took 'Dove'
from you, huh?
- Mi-young, say 'Dove'
- Why?
- Say it slowly, Do...
- Do
- ve
Your mouth reminds me
of something
An asshole
What an asshole?
What the fuck!
Do I wanna be a bum?
Hell no!
You must know how I feel
I'm like the black goat
'Black sheep,' fool!
Zoo sings this, right?
When I was little
I lost my mom at the zoo
And the next minute
I was at this fucking orphanage
You're not listening,
are you?
Are you listening?
One minute you're a bitch
the next, you're an angel
Stop confusing me
You're trying to dump
the tab on me, aren't you?
Hey! I thought I was the one
to be carried home
God damn! She's heavy
I paid for dinner and beer
And now a piggyback!
What do I get in return?
What do I
Bingo!
The table's set
All I need to do is eat
No, slow down
Yeah, I know
You're horny too, huh?
Let me go wash up
No girl wants to kiss a guy
with bad breath
This is so disgusting!
You call yourself a girl?
I think not!
Look at these
Oh, it's a snowman
Kind of cute
I'm not the black goat
I'm not
Forget it
I've lost my appetite
Mom, get me some water
I knew I couldn't trust
this fuckface!
You son of a bitch!
Come here, asshole!
You asshole! Fuck!
Come here, you bastard!
You son of a bitch!
- What'd you do to me?
- Jesus Christ!
You slept on the wrong
side of the bed or what?
You touched me, didn't you?
What the hell did you do to me!
You have no fucking clue
what I went through
I shouldn't have trusted you!
I knew this would happen
Do you have any idea
what you did last night?
I don't even wanna go there
Look at that laundry!
You shitted in the bed
you disgusting bitch!
You fucking liar!
You're dead, shithead
You didn't call him
I might as well kill you
No name calling, please
What the hell is this?
I know you need a new bag
Bribery won't save
What's this?
A complimentary coupon
Do some shopping
Where'd you get the money?
What do you think?
I stole it
I'm going to bed
Hey!
Don't I get anything?
Catch it
Asshole!
What's up with him?
You staged this, didn't you?
Hell no!
I'd rather buy rat poison
and put it in his rice
Oh, God!
What time is it now?
- Mom
- Where'd you sleep?
At So-jung's
She asked me to sleep over
So I did
Why'd you turn your cell off?
- Chinese medicine for you
- What for?
It's supposed to be good
for menopause
I'm not menopausal
What is it then?
Puberty?
Where'd you get the money?
She owed me some money
and paid me back yesterday
Where'd you get the money
to lend her?
I know this is expensive
Just take it, okay?
Why can't you look me
in the eyes?
You lap-dance at private
parties or something?
You're unbelievable!
Where are you going?
You're very
close to getting it, girl
Is that my wallet?
My jacket's gone
That's my jacket
Why'd you do it?
Give it back
Confiscated
I risked my life for it
You need some dough?
Then ask me
Why take what's not yours?
Why?
Why in God's name!
Why are you doing this to me?
Why? Why? Why?
I even hooked her up
with my brother