Sonpyong 1975
I'm not supposed to be wasting
my time on a rabbit drumstick.
Here, have the front legs then.
Eun-ji.
There's an old saying that says
send horses to an open plain,
and send people to big cities.
In short, whether
you're human or animal,
you need to get out in the
open and mix with the crowd.
So we're going to Seoul?
Catch what I'm saying here.
Not us, me.
I don't know who said it,
but I sure have respect for the guy.
And that's why I need
to get out of here.
This place isn't
for YOUN Min-jae.
You understand, right?
Why do you always have
to cry like that?
I swear on this snow.
I'll be back in a year on
a snowy day like today.
You trust me, right?
Look. You trust me, right?
You know how true our love is.
How do you do?
Go home.
The shades aren't too dark?
They're just fine.
I told you.
What are you doing?
Your collars are up.
Get with it.
This is a fad in Seoul.
What?
I'm just worried.
About what?
Girls in Seoul will
all chase after you.
Eun-ji, you're more beautiful
than most girls in Seoul.
All they have is make-up.
Have a good day.
Go home now, I'll see you.
I'll see you soon, okay?
You have to let go.
There's nothing in it.
Let go.
The train's here.
I'm leaving to better my life.
What are you doing?
Come on, please.
Eun-ji, let go.
Min-jae, Min-jae.
Don't worry. Just go home.
I'll come back looking good,
- Min-jae
- so don't worry and go home
Eun-ji, don't worry
and just go, okay?
I'll be waiting for you.
Just go now.
Hey Axe, didn't I tell you
to get out of my way?
Come on, just let me go.
Let me go!
Boss, I'm here.
Boss!
It's me, Min-jae.
Relax. Calm down and come sit.
What did you tell me
when we first met?
You said you wanted to
live in style, right?
And that's why you said you
wanted to become a gangster.
And now you want out?
You'll just leave us?
Why?
I thought I'd live in style
if I worked for you.
But evidently, there's no style.
I want to end my thug life here.
So then what? What will you do?
I'm going to become a philanderer.
I'm going to seduce rich women
and get them to pay up.
You may go now.
- Boss!
- Just go.
Thank you, boss.
One more thing, Min-jae.
I could careless if you become
a philanderer or a playboy.
Just don't tell anyone
you worked for me.
It's a goddamn shame.
Boss, you sure you should
let him go like that?
He's a catch, but he's
no thug material.
The kid has too much heart.
Sister dear...
Love is eternal.
Imagine if there were
no love in our lives.
I just can't stand people
that try to buy love.
- Sister.
- Yeah?
You believe in love, right?
- Thanks.
- What for?
You're right.
Love is eternal.
I must've lost it.
My husband didn't
hit me out of hate.
It was probably all out of love.
And he probably stomped on me
without knowing that it was me.
He probably knew.
Thanks to you,
I regained my rationality.
Thank you so much.
- No, you see...
- Have a good life, honey.
Sister.
It's way too late.
I need to go fix him dinner.
Wait, I didn't have dinner either.
Fuck.
You're no good as a philanderer.
You should become a
marriage counselor.
Shut up.
You need to stop
that love bull shit.
Just get straight to the point.
And look, if you're trying
to play the game,
You don't want to be all nice.
Get to the point.
I got some good stuff.
Wanna check it out?
Thought I almost had it this time.
- It doesn't hurt to look.
- Hey, Dong-shik.
I'm just trying to be a
humane philanderer, you know.
I mean, being a philanderer is a
service-centric profession.
But then we got all these
inhumane suckers, you know.
Especially for you two, I'm
willing to offer you the best,
and the most advanced, you know?
- Get out.
- For almost nothing.
I said, leave.
Good day.
Just watch.
I'll get another chance.
Sure.
That's what dreams are for.
I'm telling you.
I'll find someone, hit it big,
and live in style.
You'll see.
Hey, Dong-shik.
I'll show you how it's done today.
She's mine.
It'd be great if you could help,
but if not, I have a plan.
Just remember when you
first came to our store.
If I blurt it out, you know
your old man won't be happy.
We'll talk over a drink.
What an honor to be getting
a drink from Hae-mi.
That's for your medical bill.
If you're thinking the
old Hae-mi, think again.
I make a call, you're dead.
Keep calling if you want
money for medical bills.
I can't pay you a penny
other than medical expense.
You bitch!
Since when did you...
turn all arrogant and
condescending.
You fuckin' whore!
Who the hell are you?
Fuck...
Let's run, ma'am!
Get him!
It should be safe here.
This place is temporarily closed.
You're all wet.
Ma'am, if it weren't for me today,
you would've gotten in big trouble.
Choi back there... he's known
for beating women.
Anyway, he must've
really loved you, huh?
Stupid bastard.
Ma'am, love is eternal.
Imagine if there were
no love in our lives.
You believe in love, right?
Ma'am!
Well... uhhh...
You!
All you do is rip off women?
I don't rip off anything.
You said you would go
hit it big in Seoul.
And all you are is a philanderer?
What did you used to tell me?
Wait, because you'll be back?
It's been five years since you left.
Eun-ji. It's really you, huh?
Wait a second. Is it really you?
Was it that hard to make a call?
No...
I never crossed your mind?
Of course, I did.
I thought you were dead.
You know what, it would've been better
if you were dead. What's this now?
Well... I thought of killing myself.
But it's me we're talking about.
You know, YOUN Min-jae. Remember?
I wanted to hit it big and live
with you till death do us part.
Has it really been five years?
One thing though, do you have
to be that rude to me?
What's wrong, Eun-ji?
I'm OH Hae-mi. The Eun-ji you
know died five years ago.
What? Eun-ji?
Hey, Eun-ji.
Eun-ji, you can't just
leave like this.
Let's talk and catch up.
Hey, Eun-ji. Locked, huh?
Hey, roll down the
window for a sec.
Eun-ji!
Come on, roll down the window!
I swear on this snow.
I'll be back in a year on
a snowy day like today.
Eun-ji!
Don't worry. Just go home.
I'll come back looking good,
so don't worry and go home.
Eun-ji, don't worry
and just go, okay?
Let me get another bottle please.
That's enough.
I won't put it on the tab, don't worry.
Sir, how about a shoe shine?
No thanks, I'm good.
Come on, I'll shine them
real good. Give it a try.
I said, no thanks.
Come on, you know you want it.
I got some good stuff here.
Want to take a look?
- I'll make it shine like a mirror.
- It doesn't hurt to look.
You bastards. Don't you see I'm
trying to get some reading done?
Hold on, who might this be?
Do you know me?
I had dreams about you,
and you don't remember me?
I think you're mistaken.
You're Gwang-pal from
Kyungsang province alright.
It's me. WANG Do-chul from Cholla.
I'm not CHO Gwang-pal.
Hey, low-life.
You ruined my life and
you don't remember me?
You stinking bastard.
Relax, Do-chul, will you?
It really wasn't my fault.
I got the stuff all for you.
I didn't know that it would
have side-effects like that.
Do-chul, I'm trying to
move on with my life now.
I even have a wife
with a baby inside.
So you were living happily while
my family was getting screwed.
No, man. I'm barely getting by.
You bastard!
Do you know what happened to my dick
after I took the pills you sold me?
It won't get hard and it's
been sleeping ever since.
It's sleeping?
- It won't get up.
- Really?
- No more erection.
- None?
I turn impotent overnight.
My wife hits it off with
this guy next door.
I'd have to kill you to make up
for what I've been through.
Anyway, you're dead today.
Come here!
Hey, drugs cause different
reactions on different people.
What?
Don't come near me.
I'm gonna run.
How fast do you run
a hundred meters?
Thirteen seconds.
I can do that in twelve seconds flat.
I ask for your mercy, man.
That's not happening.
Fuck!
You stinking bastard!
Congratulations, sir!
Colonel, it's about time you
find the right woman, sir.
Your nephew's had enough hard work.
That's right. That's right.
Tell him to come in.
Is someone here?
They sent someone from
the 32nd division.
Isn't that the Samchung Revival Camp?
I guess he's in a
hurry for relocation.
Captain Hwang from
32nd division, sir.
Happy birthday, sir.
Leave your gift there and leave.
Hey, where are you from?
What, sir?
Where were you educated?
United Armed Forces academy, sir.
UAF?
No wonder he's running errands
with a captain rank.
I don't think where you come from
is important as a soldier.
- How dare you...
- Wait, wait...
Then, what do you
think is important?
It's one's patriotism
for his country, sir.
That's respectable.
I should have someone
like that under me.
Since you came, have some
dinner before you go.
This is no place for him to join.
No, no.
Since you're here already,
eat before you go.
Wash your face with this.
There's a guest.
He said he was a hometown friend.
Eun-ji.
Holy cow.
What brings you here?
You can go now.
This house is awesome.
What's this here?
Are you crazy?
Where do you think this is?
What? I'm just here to
visit an old friend.
What happened to you?
Did you find a gold
mine or something?
How did you find me?
It's not too hard.
How many people in Korea do you
think drive fancy cars like that?
Hey, Eun-ji, those are all
expensive stuff, huh?
Are theses antiques?
Eun-ji, are these real gold?
You found a gold mine, didn't you?
With just a few of these,
you could live in style.
You want them?
Of course.
Then take them.
Really?
You sure I can take these?
As long as you don't get caught.
Who's going to catch me?
Don't you want to know
who the owner is?
No.
It's someone that can easily
kill any one of us instantly.
Then don't tell him.
Then take them.
I'm really taking them, okay?
What the hell, why not?
Fuck it. I'm not taking them.
If I take them and go into hiding,
they'll never find me as you said.
But then, what's going
to happen to you?
You said the guy can kill any one of us,
so that includes you too, right?
I'm okay, but you shouldn't
get hurt because of me.
You look really good.
Look at where you're living.
You have a slick car and everything.
Don't get in trouble because of me.
You need to learn, girl.
Anyway, this is some
style we got here.
What brings you home at this hour?
I was nearby.
Just wanted to get changed.
Ummm... the thing is...
Take my clothes first.
Are you still smoking?
What did I tell you?
I said bad habits are
better rid than done!
Once you taste something new,
you forget the value of the old.
Don't go anywhere and stay home.
Eun-ji.
Eun-ji, look, you okay?
Just go.
What's going on?
Talk to me.
Just go.
Eun-ji, wake up.
What's going on?
Please go.
You're in danger, go.
Eun-ji.
I'm begging you.
Just leave.
You can't stay here.
Just go.
Eun-ji.
Please.
Come on, go. Please go.
You gotta go.
Go.
Min-jae, go.
So you're home, huh?
Remember me?
You know, the day you threw
noodle soup at me.
Look at what you did.
How is it?
Looks good, right?
Why don't you try running again?
Now that I know where you live.
Couldn't you forgive me?
You little piss ass.
My dick's dead.
So now it's your turn.
You dog!
They call me bulldog.
Dear...
Stop right there!
Stop, you fool!
Stop!
I said, stop.
Stop.
Get him!
Hey!
Move!
Sir, listen.
Please help.
What are you two?
Excuse me.
I just need to get him.
So just do as you were.
- Come here.
- What?
I just have a personal business
with this guy to take care of.
Come here!
Crazy fucks.
I think your expression
is a little excessive.
Don't you know where
this bus is headed to?
This bus is going to
the Samchung Revival Camp.
Fine.
Just take me anywhere, but here.
I don't care what camp it is,
just take me.
Revival sounds good.
You bastard.
Either you let the both of
us go, or take both of us.
I'm not leaving this bus without him.
Fuckin' assholes.
Kill them!
Do you like it?
You can never leave
me unless I dump you.
Eun-ji!
Are you crazy?
What are you doing here?
Follow me.
I'm sorry.
Only if I hadn't showed up.
It hurt a lot, right?
What does he do anyway?
Why do you have to live
with a guy like that?
Two years after you left for Seoul,
everyone in town left because
an army base was moving in.
That's when Butcher Pal-bong offered
to find you for me in Seoul.
And?
The day we came to Seoul, Pal-bong
sold me to a Geisha house and left.
Pal-bong... fuckin'
asshole... fuck.
It's all my fault.
Then I was introduced to this soldier
who said he could find you.
He said he could find you for sure.
I was stupid for believing him.
If I had known the shore was this
close, I would've came already.
It's great here.
Thank you god for
finding Min-jae.
Eun-ji.
Hey.
Eun-ji!
Are you here for Hae-mi?
She's been shocked by a
sudden external impact.
She needs to rest.
What now?
What about it?
Isn't it pretty?
It doesn't sting?
For me.
I'll go with this one.
Get him the butterfly just like me.
Butterflies aren't for men.
But it's something to remember
me by when you go to Seoul.
Christ... Well then.
This one's okay, I guess.
Happy?
Why do you have to cry like that?
Okay, okay.
Let me get the same one.
Min-jae.
They said you'll be okay
if you get some rest.
I'm really not the old Eun-ji.
I've changed a lot.
That's okay, Eun-ji.
Can you forgive me?
You didn't do anything wrong.
There's nothing to forgive.
I'm the one that should be
asking for forgiveness.
Can you keep a promise?
Don't go anywhere and
let's run away together.
Okay, okay. I won't ever leave
you until death do us part.
You said you liked the sea, right?
We'll live in a place with a sea view.
I'm talking about where
we're going to live.
With huge palm trees and a hammock,
sipping freshly squeezed juice.
That's right!
We'll put up a camp fire and
cook up rabbit like before.
Let's do that, okay?
Let's live like that, Eun-ji.
Sit.
Yes, sir.
Why did you want to see me?
I want to become one
of your men, colonel.
What did you say was the most
important thing as a soldier?
I said patriotism, sir.
Then, where should you be
showing your patriotism to?
My country, sir.
Your country, huh?
Let me ask that again.
Where should you be showing
your patriotism to?
You, sir.
Hey!
You're really giving me
these clothes, right?
Yes.
Are you serious about leaving?
You don't need to know.
I'm going to go live in style
with Eun-ji in a remote place.
Live happily ever after,
you son of a bitch.
I'm out.
See ya.
YOUN Min-jae.
Take him.
What's wrong?
What is it?
What the hell?
Get off of me.
What are you doing?
Let's go.
Hey, Dong-shik.
What's wrong? Off of me.
Dong-shik, Dong-shik!
What is this?
No, I'm not.
YOUN Min-jae.
Odaesan crime family member.
Okay, okay.
I'm one of them,
are you happy now?
Now let me go.
Eun-ji's waiting for me.
I said Eun-ji's waiting for me,
you son of a bitch!
Hey, Do-chul, I guess this is it.
I feel like I'm back in the army.
It can't be as bad as the army.
You never know.
I bet this place is way
worse than the army.
As far as I know
it could be worse than the army.
Look at their eyes, man.
Did I ask you?
I'm just trying to be
nice to you boys.
Show some respect, will you?
- Who do you think you are?
- What?
Hey, dip shits.
Just shut the fuck up.
What are you on a picnic?
Fuck.
You suckers.
You'll repeat what I say.
Trainee rule of conduct Number one.
I'll do as told.
One, I'll do as told!
Two!
I'll take all beatings.
Two, I'll take all beatings!
Three!
I'll eat as served.
Take off everything you're wearing
except your skin and bone.
You have ten seconds.
Execute!
Take off your watches,
necklaces, and rings.
Freeze!
Freeze! You will salute the
commander with 'Allegiance'.
Salute like a man, and bellow
forth your 'Allegiance'.
- Got that?
- Yes, sir!
Now only put on your pants.
Execute!
Salute to the commander.
Allegiance!
At ease.
Most of you were delinquents
in the real world.
Our society will no longer
tolerate people like you.
With regards to this, the army
has decided to help you revive
into a worthy human being.
The program will last for weeks
with its focus on rebuilding
your body, spirit, and mind.
I'm Captain HWANG Gi-duk,
your unit commander.
I hope you'll follow your
instructors' lead without trouble.
Salute to the commander.
Allegiance!
Stay still!
Can you please leave that?
Shut up.
Can't believe you're cutting it.
I said, shut up.
It hurts.
Next.
You don't have anything
to cut, asshole.
Dreaming of Miss Yang from
Daemyung adult barbershop.
Shut up and get out.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You're dead once
we're out of here.
You think they'll
let us out to eat?
How can you be fuckin'
hungry right now?
You stupid bastard.
I'm cold and hungry, man. Shit.
Patience, Reflection,
Hae-mi?
Who are you?
I'll explain that to you later.
I have something to tell you.
You know Min-jae, right?
You know, YOUN Min-jae.
That's right.
A bunch of soldiers dragged
him away that day and
next thing I know, I get
this notice in the mail.
But you see, the Samchung Revival
Camp is supposed to be way more
than four weeks of
revival training.
They say it could take anywhere
from six months to a year.
Once you're in,
they don't let you out safe
can prepare about ten grand,
he may be able to work something out.
You know, that's the money.
For about a thousand, he said.
But I just can't afford for that money
so I come here to...
Get out.
If it's too much
five is good.
I said, get out.
Well then
maybe two grand?
Get the fuck out!
Want me to get out?
I should've gone with two
grand from the start, shit.
Man, I was too greedy.
Is this a butterfly?
That's a pretty
sorry butterfly.
Stay still. Boss is trying
to take in the art work.
Go away.
Go away? You fuckin'...
Do you have a death wish?
You disgusting flab of meat.
Hey, why would you wanna
bother this scrawny kid?
Get off, you fat fuck.
You okay?
You don't look like
you belong here.
What brought you here?
No way.
You were a gangster? You?
How scary.
What's your name?
YOUN Min-jae.
I'm WANG Do-chul. Think of me
as your big brother from now on.
As long as I'm here,
you don't need to worry.
I got your back.
Hey, listen.
If any of you gets near my boy here,
I won't leave you alone.
You got that, or what?
What's wrong with
those guys? Fuck.
Come on, move.
Wash what you can for
the next one minute.
Come on, hurry up now.
Over there, sir.
How are you
Captain Hwang?
Sorry for intruding like this.
That's okay, Hae-mi.
What brings you here?
My cousin's in the camp.
Oh, so he's a soldier?
No, the police had some things
mixed up and brought him here.
I was thinking maybe
you could help.
If it's your cousin
wouldn't it
be a lot easier if
you ask the colonel.
Well, the thing is...
The Corp commander is
paging you, sir.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I need to be excused.
Hold on, wait.
What's his name?
Min-jae. YOUN Min-jae.
He should be out safe
in four weeks.
Can I see him now?
I'm sorry.
Visitings are prohibited.
But, let me see what I can do.
Thank you. And one more thing...
I would appreciate it if you
don't tell this to the colonel.
Yes, ma'am.
Count, One!
Two! Three! Four! Five! Six!
Seven! Eight! Nine! Count over!
Numbers one to three
may go in and eat.
Enter!
The rest of you,
get on your heads!
On your heads, shitheads!