The universe...
So full of wonders...
I could spend hours and hours
looking up at the sky.
So many stars,
so many mysteries...
And there's one very special star
that makes me think
of one very special person.
Now let me tell you my story.
At the dawn of time,
from the chaos,
came an exception.
One of the most mysterious secrets
of the universe.
You see, I come from
that very mysterious and unique place.
We are the only known solar system
with double gravity.
Two twin planets
whirling together around one sun
but each with its own
and opposite gravity.
Now, in our world
it's possible to fall up
and to rise down.
But... my story,
it's about love.
Some people say
that true lovers are one soul
that is separated when it's born.
And those two halves will always yearn
to find their way back together.
Well, to understand my story,
you're gonna need to know the three
basic laws of double gravity.
All matter, every single object
is pulled by the gravity of the world that
it comes from, and not the other.
- An object's weight can be offset using-
inverse-matter.
After a few hours of contact,
matter in contact with inverse-matter
...burns.
All these laws are as old
as the universe itself.
They're are unchangeable,
and there are no exceptions.
Gravity...
They say you can't fight it.
Well, I disagree.
What if love
was stronger than gravity?
Now let's go back
to the dark times
when any contact between worlds
was extremely dangerous
and totally forbidden.
Up top had grown rich
and prosperous
while here, down below,
we stole inverse-metal from up top
to heat our homes and to survive
risking everything,
even our own lives.
I think he's dead.
Hey! Police!
They only authorized contact
between worlds is through TransWorld,
a giant corporation up top,
created to take cheap oil
from down below
and to sell back to us
overpriced electricity
that we couldn't afford.
Because of TransWorld,
I grew up in an orphanage.
You see,
my parents died in the Big Blast,
a TransWorld oil refinery explosion
that destroyed much of the city.
Fortunately,
there were the weekends.
They let me visit
my great aunt Becky,
my only surviving relative.
- As well as Becky, there were-
model airplanes
and Becky's flying pancakes.
Going to have to get me
some more pink pollen tomorrow.
Okay, sweetie?
Becky also initiated me
into an ancient knowledge
passed down over the generations
to the women of our family...
Now catch!
The secret of the pink bees.
Becky, how do they do that?
It's all in this book.
It was passed down
to my mother from hers.
And, of course,
I would have given it to your mother.
One day, when you grow up, it'll be yours..
Becky would often sent me to gather
pink pollen from the Sage Mountains.
This was the only place,
and a forbidden place,
where pink bees could be found.
Bees that fed of flowers
from both worlds
and without whom this story could
never have happened.
But I have a little secret
of my own...
I used to go chase inverse-rain
from up top.
One day
I went much further than usual,
climbing higher and higher
above the cloud line.
And that day... that day...
changed my life...
...forever.
Hey!
Hi!
Hey, where have you been?
I've been waiting ages for you.
Our neighbors got robbed.
They're saying it was a thief
from down below.
There's hunters with guns
and border patrol trucks.
Are you serious?
Don't make that face!
I made it here, right?
Look, as long as you're okay...
Hey, look, I'll throw it up!
- Alright, ready?
- Alright right, Adam!
Are you tied on?
- I'm done!
- Yeah?
Okay, I pull you down!
Don't drop me!
You know,
these ones from up top are so good...
- They're the best.
- Yeah, they are. They're amazing.
Oh, wait.
I got something for you, too...
And this is from both worlds.
What is it?
I can't tell you.
You gotta close your eyes.
Close your eyes!
Come on, like 'closed' closed!
- I closed!
- Alright.
- Are they closed?
- Uhmm.
Okay, open your mouth.
I can't reach!
Mmh...
How is that from both worlds?
I don't know, you should
probably ask the bees.
I don't know.
Imagine if we could
go anywhere we wanted to.
I mean, really...
I can imagine that...
- Hey, you know what?
- What?
Well, we can.
Come on, let's imagine we can,
let's go down!
Are you holding on?
- Ready!
- Three, two, one...
Go!
Alright, I go down.
- You're holding on?
- Yeah.
Don't you let my legs go!
I got it, I got it!
- Okay, let it spin! Whoa!
- Whooo!
I've got my eyes closed.
Look at the branch, whoa.
- We gonna go again?
- Uhum.
- It's the biggest one ever.
- Alright, I'm ready.
- You hold on?
- Yeah.
Coming down!
Alright.
- Are you okay?
- Uhum.
Okay, mind if we go
for another spin?
Yeah, let's get really high,
let's get even higher than that.
Okay, yeah. Ready?
Did you hear that?
Yeah.
- We should go.
- He's there!
- Let's get him!
Quick, Adam!
Eden!
Oh no!
No! No, please!
- Becky!
- No!
- Becky, I'm sorry!
- - No!
Becky!
No, no! No!
- Becky!
- Adam!
You did nothing wrong!
Nothing!
Becky!
No, Becky!
Please, no! No!
Becky!
10 YEARS LATER
Adam, come on, stop!
Come on, make us a plane!
Oh, I can't.
I can't.
I gotta go to work.
Come on!
I'll do it later!
Hey, Mr. Jones!
- TransWorld...
...you've got to play to win!
- Hello, Albert.
- Mrs. Nathanson.
- What do you have for me?
- Inverse-matter to pay my debts.
Will this cover it?
My husband says it's stainless steel.
From the main pipeline.
Oh...
Pablo, it's ready.
Okay, don't start it till it's
fully applied.
Okay.
Okay, here we go.
Wow, that stuff is amazing!
Is it for sale?
Oh...
Not great yet.
Nah.
- We're all settled, darl.
- Thank you.
And, uh... can you keep me
posted on that beauty cream?
We'll do. You take care, no?
Do you hear that, Adam?
We have got to finish this cream.
Well, I would love to,
Albert, you know, but...
with this equipment, you know,
it'd take years.
...TransWorld will fulfill
everyone's dream
and transform his life working
for TransWorld.
We're live down below with our
nine finalists feverishly
awaiting the results.
I'd like to welcome
Ms. Eden Moore of Trans Publicity,
a division of TransWorld.
- Hi, how are you?
- Hi.
Welcome!
Now, she'll tell us more
about what she does.
But more importantly, let's hear
about our winner's new job.
Well, our division handles all of
TransWorld’s graphic designs.
Right now, we're going to work on...
Uh... that sounds fascinating
but our audiences are dying to know...
just what job will our winner begin?
Well, today we're offering the winner
a job in our department.
Okay, here we go.
Let's choose our lucky winner.
It's her.
Number 2.
- Pablo, it's Eden.
- Are you sure?
I'm probably sure.
She... she's alive!
I can't believe it!
I couldn't find her,
and she works at TransWorld!
Attention,
this is a final call.
Doors will be closing in five minutes.
Stay in line, prepare jackets and
personal objects for weighing.
Please, remove
your jacket and empty
your pockets of personal
belongings for weighing.
Place your jacket in the bin as well.
Stay in line, prepare jackets and
personal objects for weighing.
165 pounds.
- Don't move.
- New?
- Yeah.
- What floor?
- Floor zero.
- Name?
- Adam Kirk.
Thanks.
Need some help?
Uh, yeah, yeah. I... I'm looking for
a station 15, sector 8.
Third aisle down.
Thank you.
"WELCOME"
Welcome aboard, newbie!
- Cheers.
- Goddammit!
I'm so... so sorry.
I... I... I had no idea...
- I was gonna...
- Don't worry, my friend.
They do that to all the newbies.
Oh, great...
My name's Bob, Bob Boruchowitz.
And you are?
I'm Adam, Adam Kirk.
Mr. Kirk?
Please, follow me. The managing
director is waiting to see you.
Right, sure, uh.
Okay, thanks.
Psst! Hey, hey!
Your back...
Your back, check it out.
Oh...
Right... that's, uh...
That's pretty funny.
Oh ho.
Mr. Kirk,
we don't have much time!
Come see me on your way out
for the list of materials
you require for your work.
I need you to complete
your security clearance form.
I'll also give you your various
access badges and meal vouchers.
Come in, Mr. Kirk.
Come in, come in.
This anti-aging cream idea of yours
seems to be quiet promising.
Your application has been approved.
But this is strictly on a trial basis,
you understand?
O... Of course.
Have a seat, please.
Thanks.
Fasten your seat belt, Mr. Kirk.
I'm sorry?
Your seat belt.
Seat...
Oh, right.
Are there any questions, Mr. Kirk?
Yeah, I was just wondering what
all these people up my side do?
Mmh...
They're merely adapters.
They adapt our products
to your world.
You on the other hand have
a real opportunity here.
Company policy
doesn't normally allow
for someone from... 'down below'
to hold such an important position,
but were making an exception
in your case.
Sign here, please.
Now then, a word of warning...
We scrupulously observe a full
separation between worlds here.
That means there is to be no
unnecessary contact with those up top.
Just stick to your job
and all will be well.
One last thing...
The rules are quite strict here.
As you know, you'll be working
with upper world materials.
This means that you will be
thoroughly searched and weighed
every time
that you leave the premises.
If they find
any inverse-matter on you,
you'll be fired
and jailed on the spot.
But I have a feeling that
this won't happen in your case,...
will it, Mr. Kirk?
No, sir.
Try not to prove me wrong.
Right then...
Dismissed!
Another massive
oil leak has developed,
following a metal robbery
from the main pipeline
forcing TransWorld to
double their security.
The three thieves from down below
arrested last week were hanged
this morning at dawn
raising interworld tensions.
Here's the senior TransWorld
executive with a statement...
They got what they deserved.
We don't go down to their world,
we certainly don't want them coming up to ours.
- Hey.
Nice boss you got there.
And that's tonight's news on TTW7.
Thank you for watching us.
Adam,
you did not have to do this.
I could have gotten you
that patent.
TransWo... TransWorld is the worst
thing that ever happened to us.
And what now, you're...
you're one of them?
Come on, Albert...
Those people are vultures.
And you're gonna give them
your golden goose for peanuts?
We have nothing!
Yeah, we're from down below.
I mean, that's just the way it is.
I mean, we have nothing.
Don't you tell me I'm nothing!
This isn't nothing,
this is everything!
And I gave you everything,
treated you like you were
my own son!
And you know what
you're gonna do?
You gonna go out there and
you're gonna get yourself killed!
That's all you're gonna do...
get yourself killed.
Shit...
What?
Al... Albert, come on!
I didn't mean it like that.
Albert, please, come on!
Alright...
Don't you dare to think
that I have forgotten
that TransWorld took away
my entire family!
Alright?
Look...
If I could use TransWorld...
and... and aunt Becky's
pink powder just to...
I... I... I don't know...
Just to give my life
some kind of hope.
That's how I'm gonna do it.
Come on, Albert, please!
Come on, I need you your help.
Albert, please!
Come on!
Alright...
Alright, I'll help.
Okay...
Today we have someone joining us
for the first time.
Hello, Eden.
Hi.
Eden. Eden Moore.
Uhm...
I had an accident
when I was a teenager.
Uhm...
Everything before that is gone.
Sometimes things come
back to me in dreams.
But I'm never sure if they're real
or if I'm making them up.
It's frustrating.
You know, I...
I know that whatever is missing,
it's in there.
Uhm...
But it scares me.
Mostly it just feels like
something's missing.
Mr. Kirk?
Yes.
Here's the key to your
personal refrigeration system.
And here's your very first allocation...
of inverse-matter.
Okay, great.
Be careful. Without cooling
it gets hot very fast.
Err...
Thank you.
Hey...
Not exactly a charmer, is he?
- Oh!
- Lunch time.
- Lunch time!
I usually go to the smoking room
after lunch break.
Why don't you drop by,
and we have a little conversation?
Okay, sure.
- Hey, Bob?
- Mmh?
Mind if I come in?
Come in, come in,
sit down, hey!
Want a cigar?
- Smoke?
- No, no, thanks. I don't smoke.
Okay, fine.
See? Empty.
"No one smokes in TransWorld anymore..."
pfft.. Well, I do so.
Hell, people have a funny way
of seeing things here.
Anything or anyone different is...
well, they say...
'frowned upon'.
Can I ask you a favor?
Yeah.
Yeah, sure.
Can you get me some stamps?
Some stamps?
Yeah... stamps.
I, uh...
I don't like to boast, but...
I got one of the largest known
stamp collections up top.
And if you can get
me some from your side...
Oh, boy...!
Right, yeah, I mean, uh,...
I mean... sure, I guess.
Great... Great!
So, you're saying...
anti-gravity...
Yeah, you know, I... I've...
Well,
I've been working on this, uh...
- Well, it's an anti-aging cream.
- Uhum.
Oh... well,
I'm here if you need me,
expert in conductivity,
in computer programming,
anything you need, anything,
just ask.
Well, then, uh...
I... I... I guess there could be
something you could help me with...
uhm...
I was wondering if you might be able
to get me in touch with an employee...
...up top.
Up top?
Yeah.
Her name's, uh...
Eden Moore.
Sure...
Sure.
So, what's your plan?
I don't know yet.
Working on it.
I mean,
but you've seen her, alright?
No, I mean...
I... I haven't actually seen her, but...
...but she's there, Pablo. I mean,
she's just like a... fifth floors above.
Are you sure this is worth it?
I mean it's been like ten years
since you last saw her.
Yeah... it's worth it.
It's amazing!
The ma... The man with no hair!
I can't believe it!
So what kind of shirt you want?
- You want like a sport shirt?
- No, no...
T-shirt?
One of of the button-down collars?
- Yes, like a normal button-down shirt.
- You want a jacket?
Yeah, like... I don't know...
a suit jacket.
Stay in line...
You may proceed, Mr. Kirk.
Thank you.
Now, this should be happening
any moment now.
You watch carefully.
Here it comes.
How long does the effect last?
Well, right now really
only like a few minutes...
...but I...
we've been working on...
It's been working long enough.
Soon we'll begin clinical trials
on human subjects.
Obviously, we start with a sample
of women from down below.
I need quick results.
I'm counting on you.
Is that beauty cream
for Halloween?
No, they got different
standards of beauty down below.
The... uglier the better.
Hey, don't let those guys
get to you.
They're just jealous,
that's all.
Are you... staying late?
Yeah, you know, I thought I stay and
finish up a few things, you know.
Ah, yeah. Well, I take the dog
back to the kennel.
Come on, girl.
Hey, here!
You realize they don't pay
overtime, right?
Yeah, I know.
Okay, alright.
See you tomorrow!
Don't work too hard!
I won't.
Hello?
Yes, it is.
No, I'm sorry,
she's got home for tonight.
Yeah, you can come by tomorrow.
Okay, what's your name again?
BO-RU-CHOWITZ.
Thank you.
Okay, see you tomorrow.
Believe me, Adam,
it's gonna burn.
And the pinch... just use a little
water to cool it down.
Please, remember, you won't last
an hour with these kind of things on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I know, I know...
Alright, Pablo, what?
What is it?
Alright, what's your plan, huh?
You dress up in disguise, you show
up to meet her, and then what?
Then what? I...
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
No, I don't know.
Alright, let me
get this straight, okay?
She sees you, alright,...
she throws herself in your arms,
says she loves you, and... and...
she never forgot about you.
- Yeah, yeah, maybe.
- Okay...
Since you're starting
to burn up...
you tell her you love her too,
but you really have to go.
And if you don't get
caught or shot,
maybe you see her again
in ten years.
Besides, what... y... you...
You really think she, uh...
she just waited for you?
- Yeah, I do.
- You do?
Yeah, actually I do.
Adam, you're from down below,
okay? Don't you get that?
Besi... you know what...
I bet she calls the cops
the second she sees you.
- She's not gonna call the cops...
- Adam, you're so delusional.
Hey, why are you so obsessed
with those people, anyway, huh?
You know,
my brother was the same way...
when he went up there and...
well, he never came back.
You wanna end up like him?
"Hey, Eden. It's Adam!"
"It's Adam."
Who's there?
Possible breach.
Ah!
Eden.
Eden, it's... it's... it's me!
Oh, yes, Mr. Boruchowitz, right?
I'll be with you in a second.
Wait...
Come on, Eden.
Hi.
I'm Paula.
We spoke on the phone yesterday.
I didn't realize
you guys knew each other.
Yeah, yeah, yeah... no, we do.
I mean, I can't believe she would
just ignore me like that.
No...
No, she just forgets things.
What do you mean?
It's her amnesia.
W... wait, she has amnesia?
Yes, since her accident.
- - Will you get these two?
- Yeah.
You wanted to see me?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, no, I did, uh...
Look, look, you know,
I thought that we...
I... uh,...
I... I thought...
that, uh...
...that this product
that I've been working on...
I... I thought it might be of...
...some interest to you...
- ...professionally speaking.
- Uhum.
Yeah, I... I... uh...
Oh, would you...
Can I, can I show you...?
Yeah, sure.
That's just a mock-up.
You know, it takes a...
second to work, so...
Okay.
You know, uh...
I've, uh...
I've been working
with this, this...
young man...
who's just recently started
here at TransWorld.
But, uh...
He had like a trouble childhood.
Yeah, he grew up in a, like a...
like an orphanage.
Oh, that's terrible.
Yeah, you know hi...
his aunt Becky...?
Who's like his only
real family?
Well, you should've brought him.
Yeah...
Well, uh...
Th... the truth is...
that he couldn't come.
Oh, why not?
Well, 'cause...
...he's from down below.
- Oh... sorry.
- Sorry, I'm sorry.
I just don't know why
you tell me this.
- Anyway, I thought that...
- Oh...
...the product might
be of some interest.
- That's amazing!
- Yeah.
It's perfectly straight.
What is this stuff?
It's top secret, actually.
I like secrets.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- No, I'm good.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, oh, yeah. I'm good.
- Wait, you're sweating.
Oh, really?
God, look at that...
- Do you want Translenol?
- No, no, really, I... I'm good.
I'm pretty good.
You know what,
can you just, uh...
excuse me for like...
just one second.
- Okay.
- I'll be back.
I'll be right back.
So funny.
Ohh, ahh!
Ahh!
Uh!
Hey! Stop!
He's not coming back?!
Can you believe it?
No, I don't.
But he is cute though...
- I know.
- Uhum.
You know I hate to say it,
but I told she wouldn't remember you.
Pablo... please.
She got amnesia
...after all of that.
Boy, you sure know
how to pick 'em.
You burned yourself
pretty good there too.
Put some more of that on,
tonight when you go to bed.
Okay.
Everything alright, Mr. Kirk?
Yes, yeah, yeah, yeah...
everything's fine, just uh...
you know,
cleaning up a few things.
Here's the list of candidates
for your clinical trial.
Oh! Oh, great!
Thank you.
I'll come by at the end of the day
for your selections.
Psst! Hey!
May I see?
Sure.
Uh-ohh... man, Geez,
models like that...
Your goose is cooked, man!
What are they trying to do,
get fired or what?
Show time!
- It's showtime, honey.
- What's that?
Oh, you'll see...
You just started here,
you'll be on to a lot of fun.
Your attention, please.
Before we begin
handing out the bonuses...
- we have a list of individuals whose-
Albert Midwall
Susan Gonzalez
John Phelps
Believe me, my friend...
Your things works out.
- You got nothing to worry about.
- - Jimmy Scotch
Beatrice Amuchastegue
Bob Boruchowitz
- Nah, that's not me.
- Alexis Vonarb
That's a mistake.
Edvan Soumache
Uhm, excuse me...
I'm sorry,
did you said 'Bob Boruchowitz'?
Well, uh, I think that's
a mistake, yeah?
There is no mistake,
Mr. Boruchowitz.
You lied of your seniority,
you will be given...
a retirement package,
...but your TransWorld contract
has been terminated.
Jeff Duhaim
Emiliano Grassi
Dimitri Rassam
Oscar Lopez
Steven Craig
Don't ever trust
anyone here, Adam.
All a bunch of snakes.
That's it? I mean, you just
pack up your things and leave?
31 years... They toss you out
like a bag of garbage.
Yep, that's the TransWorld way.
This is for your collection.
Some things in here
may come in handy.
You're ready?
Yeah.
Okay, and...
I got it... I got it.
Hey, Bob.
I'm really sorry.
Don't worry about me my friend.
It's their loss.
Right.
Take care of yourself, right?
Right...
Come on, old girl.
We're out of here,
you're comin' with me.
All these jerks...
...wind me up in a tin can.
Come on, girl, come on.
Hey, Bob...
Thank you.