- It's apt. 108.
- Okay.
- Hey!
- Yes?
You're such a cute little thing.
Thank you.
- Thanks for everything. Bye.
- Good night.
- Bye. Take care.
- Thanks for tonight.
Where have you been?
Apartment meeting.
Look at him. He looks
like a sleazebag.
Yeah, he really does.
Looks mean as well.
What did you tell them?
How can you do this to me!
See you later.
Shit, why am I such a loser.
I envy you.
You've got a husband and a boyfriend.
Next, next.
No. 2, Hulk,
No. 3, Tiger Woods,
- No.4 Zidane!
- Okay, Zidane!
Zidane, Zidane!
What is it?
Aw shit. You should've knocked...
- Uh! Jisoo...
- Jisoo...
You're here. I have your assigned
internship schools.
- Sangmin is Dongin High.
- What?
- Dongin High.
- Shit!
What is it? What's wrong?
It's Boeun's high school.
Idiot!
Boeun...
Huh?
- You know...
- What!
- Speak, I'm late for school!
- Okay.
We'll talk at home, okay? Bye!
Excuse me, but where is
the faculty office?
Faculty office? I don't know.
I loathe that place.
Wait for me!
Hey, who told you to dye your hair?
What a funky hairstyle!
Come here.
Excuse me!
Hey!
Your tea...
Thank you.
You should have told me.
You seemed too attractive
to be a pervert.
Working out?
Sir, this is the new intern Park Sangmin.
Hello, sir.
Miss. Kim, you may be excused.
Yes, we'll be seeing a lot of each other.
- How have you been, sir?
- Good.
- Take good care of Boeun.
- Yes.
- No one knows except for me.
- Right.
Last night I was at a disco club,
you know who I met there?
- Who?
- Our room teacher.
What?
She must've gone there to pick up men.
Old maid syndrome!
Quiet!
We have a new intern here.
- Wow, he's so cute.
- He's really cute.
Doesn't he look familiar?
Yeah, he does look familiar.
He's cute, though...
I am Park Sangmin who will be
teaching Art.
- I hope we get along.
- Yes!
Don't even think of playing tricks
on Mr. Park, okay?
Yes, ma'am...
You all have a bright future,
you know what I mean!
- Anything else?
- No, that's all.
Quiet!
Now, let's make a toast!
Cheers! We'll spend
the entire night toasting.
Mr. Park, bottoms up!
Mr. Park!
Now one from your supervisor.
- Here you go~
- Just a little bit.
- How is it, Mr. Park?
- Excuse me?
- The kids are hard to deal with, huh?
- No, I can handle them.
- Are you busy tonight?
- Yes, a bit...
Aw~ come on!
What a great coincidence
we're teaching the same class.
This calls for a celebration together!
No thank you!
It'll make your internship much easier.
One more round, okay? Okay...
Mr. Park, let's go! The second round.
When I first met you in Jeju Isle,
I felt weird inside.
Miss Kim! Wake up. Please!
Don't take me easy cause
I'm a spinster!
I'll kill you if you do!
I don't believe this is happening!
Mr. Park. You know, I went to
a fortune teller early this year.
I'm supposed to marry a younger man.
What do you think about this?
What do you mean?
We talked about this before!
Don't take me easy!
I'll pound you with a brick
if you do!
Miss Kim... Miss Kim! Miss...
Miss Kim, Miss Kim...
Where're you going Mr. Park?
Nowhere... drive on, mister.
Why are you up?
What?
Why didn't you answer your phone?
Your teachers all drink like fishes!
I couldn't keep up.
- Why of all schools is it mine?
- I know.
If the school finds out,
I'm going to die! Be careful!
I'll be careful. Don't worry.
There won't be any rumors.
Don't worry. Go to sleep.
Wash up! You stink of liquor.
Okay. Sleep.
Why should I be the only one
to be careful?
- Hey!
- What!
I'll be careful.
What?
Sorry, but can I pee next to you?
- No!
- I'll turn around.
Boeun, I can't hold myself!
Oh my god!
What are you doing?
Hey! Park Sangmin,
what are you doing!
Didn't I warn you not to
drink too much!
I feel like shit.
Now, focus!
Mr. Park.
Huh?
Get a grip on your wife.
Mr. Park!
Ah, yes, Miss Kim!
Isn't this adorable?
Mr. Park, what are you doing after school?
Well, my grandfather's sick.
- You must be the first son.
- I'm the only son.
Your family must have a weak male line.
We're all sons except for me.
Isn't it funny?
I'm just joking.
Mr. Park...
- It's okay.
- A bright smile.
- The kids are watching.
- Let them watch.
What's with the old maid?
She's caught her prey.
The old maid's pathetic.
She made the phys. Ed teacher
transfer to another school.
- Hello, sir.
- Hi.
Was it good?
Were you watching?
You seemed to really enjoy
the cosy lunch together.
It was great. Better than
the school store's stale bread.
Jealous?
You're such a loser!
- Hello, sir.
- Uh, yeah.
- Hello, Mr. Park.
- Uh, yeah, hi.
- Is there a Lee Jungwoo here?
- Yes, that will be me.
- Are you Lee Jungwoo?
- Yes.
- So you're Jungwoo...
- Yes, I am Lee Jungwoo.
- Jungwoo, was the Kimbap good?
- What?
You look good.
Keep it up!
Shit!
- Having fun?
- Yeah.
Hey, I was getting to the fun part!
They're all naked.
How could you say it's fun?
- Don't say that about my hobby!
- You call that a hobby?
- Give it to me!
- Forget it!
It's educational. Give it back!
You should be ashamed of yourself!
I'm studying!
Then close the door!
- Stop watching!
- Shut up!
- Alright, so give it back.
- No.
- I'm sorry, so give it back.
- You're sorry?
It won't stop you from
watching it again!
Gimme. Okay.
Hey! Do as you wish!
Hey! Someone's at the door!
Jeez.
Boeun. Boeun
Miss Kim's at the door!
Miss Kim?
What did you do to make her
come all this way!
I don't know. Hurry and
clean this up. Hurry!
Underwear, underwear!
Mr. Park~
- Mr. Park!
- Oh god!
- Oh, the door's open~
- Yes...
Oh, your place looks cozy.
- A woman could just fit in.
- Miss Kim, what brings you here?
Mr. Park, I came to do
your dirty laundry.
- Is that your bedroom?
- Miss Kim!
- What's that?
- An automatic vacuum cleaner.
Auto, it does everything by itself...
- Someone's here, Mr. Park.
- No!
It's a ghost, a ghost!
Who was that? Who was it?
- It's my sister, she's a bit crazy...
- Crazy? It does seem like it...
Munch is a Norwegian painter.
A pioneer of expressionism, whose
paintings were of angst and grief.
- Then there was...
- Mr. Park.
- Huh, what?
- Forget Munch...
Tell us about your first artwork
in the dept. Of romance.
- First artwork...
- Yes!
Let's continue the class!
- Your first love!
- Mr... tell us about your first love
Okay.
My first love was
the only visitor during my
two years of military service.
But that person doesn't
know how much I like her.
She still do?
It must be Jisoo.
She may or may not know.
Now back to class.
How's the internship?
I'm so unlucky being stuck
with a boys' high school!
How could you be lucky when
you're not with the girls?
How about you, Sangmin?
Everything's great, thanks to you.
I felt that you two needed
some time together.
The dude's having ball.
He goes to school where
he can meet his pretty wife,
and be surrounded by
young high school girls.
How could he get bored there?
I'm bored out of my brains.
Seeing my bossy wife at school
and at home...
Dude, you've got nothing but luck.
Take this.
What is it?
Military service...
It's tomorrow, so don't be late.
And bring coins to play coin games.
Your husband's off
to serve his country!
Allegiance!
- No, it's "Victory!"
- Victory!
See you later.
Oh, and don't forget
what I asked you to do.
Have fun.
Thank you.
Morning training's over!
Time has passed, but I still
got the form, don't I?
Your beer belly is destroying
the form.
- They're lining up.
- It's the lunch ration line!
Morons...
Thank you.
Hey, Sangmin, it's noodles...
- Fried tofu noodles?
- Yeah.
Can I have another bowl?
No, it's okay.
You're not eating, right?
Is that Kimbap?
- Victory!
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- I'm sorry. I just brought only one.
- Don't worry.
It's okay. Is it good, dude?
Don't talk to me. It's delicious.
At least you could offer some.
- Want a piece of kimchi?
- Kimchi, kimchi...
Another piece would be nice.
A big piece! Let go!
Aren't you marine Park?
Victory...
Victory!
- Invincible!
- Marines!
Once a marine, always a marine.
What do they want?
Marines are all like that.
- Do something!
- Ah, delicious.
Stop! Don't touch anything!
Invincible... Marines...
Mister, what do you think
you're doing!
- Get up!
- This won't take long.
A feisty one, aren't you?
Are you his wife or what?
- Yeah, I am his wife!
- Sorry, she's my little sister.
What's there to hide!
How dare you push my hubby
around? Apologize!
- I'm a marine.
- Now!
- My grandpa's a marine, too!
What's your year rank!
What year!
Hey, Boeun...
Now, I'm leaving for the sea.
Casting a net to catch fish~
I am the romantic cat~
Meow~
My hot lips wish to touch your soft lips.
So my feelings can reach your heart~
If you still don't know.
More than anyone, I will love you ~
- I will love you~
- Forever~
- Like this moment,
More than anyone, I will love you ~
We can't meet~
The feeling's important~
That's what I think~
I don't want things to be too simple~
Even if it may be just this once~
The feeling's important~
That's what I think~
I don't want things to be too fast~
I still don't know what love is~
Wait a little longer~
If you really love me~
You can wait a little longer~
I still don't know what love is~
Wait a little longer~
If you really love me~
You can wait a little longer,
even if it may be just once~
The feeling's important ~
I can't meet you, I can't~
Stop it.
Stop.
- Tickle, tickle~
- Stop~
- Nice picture.
- Hullo, hullo!
- Who are you people?
- We're hoodlums.
You're her sugar daddy, aren't you?
- Cute.
- Really cute.
You want to die by my hands!
Hey, I'd love to be her sugardaddy.
Sangmin, Sangmin, shit!
You're all dead meat.
Let go!
Can't you file a paper, right?
How can this high schooler
be your wife?
They all say they'll marry the girl
when they're caught.
It's true.
I'm no sugardaddy.
You can check my record then.
Mister, it's true. We're married.
You're both fucking with me,
aren't you?
What is the world coming to?
I'm so pissed. How could you
get beat up like that?
How will you live in the real world!
How come everyone you meet is a bully?
I really worry about you.
- Stop...
- Keep rolling...
How will you go to school
with a face like that?
I'm worried about school...
Everything will be okay.
Yeah...
Hello.
Attention!
For this year's school festival,
our class is assigned to decorations.
No!
Quiet!
Stage decorations will be done by
No. 1 to 15.
The stands and stairways,
No. 16 to 21.
The Entrance, No. 23 to 32.
- And No. 22!
- Yes?
No. 22 will do the hall wall. Alone!
That's all!
But, Miss Kim!
That's unfair. How will Boeun paint
that huge wall by herself?
Right! I told her to do it herself!
So what!
With my luck with men,
what was I thinking?
You are huge.
Have you thought about
what you'll paint?
No.
What do you mean?
Even if I wanted to help you,
I can't, for fear of starting rumors
at school. I'm really worried.
I really worry about you, Boeun.
Do you know what I'm thinking?
Do you?
- Cut it out.
- Boeun!
Shhh!
Follow me.
Oh my...
I must be a lesbian.
I like my friend better than a boy.
If you're a lesbian,
I'm a cheating wife.
Hey~
Your husband is so cute.
Stop talking about that loser.
He keeps staring at you during class.
He has a cool side to him.
Cool my ass!
Suh Boeun!
I know you're seeing Jungwoo
with romantic feelings,
but have you ever thought about
Sangmin's feelings?
I really think you like Sangmin.
Am I right?
No. Sangmin's just like a big brother.
Since we were little.
- Stop fooling around.
- You're always on my back.
- Hey, sew her mouth, shut.
- Uh?
Wow, look at all this food.
The table's barely holding up.
- Eat.
- Thank you for the meal.
Thank you for the meal, mom.
Easy. Have you been skipping meals?
I've really been busy.
I missed your cooking,
it's delicious.
You shouldn't say that,
your wife's right here.
You'll hurt Boeun's feelings.
Mom, don't worry. I'm undernourished.
When Boeun reaches twenty,
you'll totally forget mom's cooking.
Boeun, I've put food in the fridge,
don't forget, okay?
There'll be more when you're
done with it.
Yes...
Okay, it's late. I'm leaving
after dinner.
Yes.
Mom, it's raining.
Sleep over at your son's place.
Yes, mom.
Is it okay?
Sleep over, sleep over.
Eat, mom.
Oh, okay.
It's your son's place.
What's the big deal!
Oh, great. So comfortable.
Turn around.
No, not this way, but the other.
Okay.
- Stay in that direction.
- Okay, pest.
- Are you asleep, Boeun?
- No...
You can't sleep?
- Sangmin, I thought about it...
- Yeah...
It's not fair to you.
Look at me, Sangmin.
What?
Did you know?
That you're really cute?
You're pretty yourself.
- Sangmin.
- Yeah, Boeun...
Boeun...
Sangmin, what are you doing?
- What do you think?
- Stop!
Wait, Boeun.
Uh, stop it!
Sleep.
Did we paint that much?
Let's hurry with this. There's not
much left till the festival.
- Hurry!
- Okay.
Hey, wait!
Gotcha, gotcha!
I see you've been working hard,
but can you finish at this pace?
The festival's coming up.
Don't worry. We'll be done by then.
Yeah, and it'll look great too.
Really? We'll see about that...
I've seen enough...
Whatever...
The hag has appeared.
To find fault in our wall painting.
Miss Kim,
with her nasty tone, she will...
I hate to admit it,
but we've done a horrible job.
- It's okay.
- Really?
Let's wash our hands
and grab some snacks.
Are you taking care of Sangmin's meals?
It's really hard to be an intern you know.
It couldn't be that hard!
Hey, but he's your husband.
Hey, I'm busy myself.
And he'll never skip a meal.
What kind of wife are you?
Then you be his wife.
Mrs. Park Sangmin.
Forget it. I don't want it.
- Why the sudden interest!
- Shut up.
Hey, Park Sangmin! Where are you?
Shouldn't you be helping me?
I couldn't believe it myself!
- Coke.
- Thanks.
- Good?
- Yeah.
- Eat up. We'll be painting until dawn.
- What?
Hey, isn't she a babe?
She's the queen of Sunil Girls' middle school.
- Hey, let me see.
- Hey!
I'm going to make a move on her,
so nice shots, please.
Okay.
Just don't get blown off.
From this day on, she's
Suh Dongku's woman!
Excuse me, but, aren't you
going to Sunil Girls' middle school?
Hey! Over there. Isn't that
Dongku's sister?
Where? It really is his sister.
Her husband looked older than that...
Then, who's that?
She must've fallen for a younger dude.
Nice.
The whole family's fooling around!
I got her number.
Did you get a good shot?
Here.
COME TO THE MONTHLY FAMILY DINNER
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
Jungwoo, I have to go home.
Already?
Hurry in and sit.
Can't you be more early?
Leave her alone.
It's okay. Let's eat.
The chilli squid was great...
Attention, please.
I'll now show you my girlfriend!
- Do you have a girlfriend?
- Yes, of course.
- Now take a good look.
- That's her?
She's better than your sister.
- Hey, look... look...
- Who's that? Huh?
Hey, Boeun!
Hey!
Boeun!
When you were little,
I always pushed you on
this swing here. You really loved it.
But one day,
you fell off the swing
while I was pushing.
I actually did it on purpose.
I'm sorry, Sangmin...
Everyone will be worried.
Let's go.
This marriage...
it seems like your grandpa
forced you into it,
but in fact we wanted to have
Sangmin as our son-in-law.
Do you remember?
How often you would cry?
But whenever Sangmin came,
a smile would spread on your face.
You would fall all the time.
Scraping and breaking yourself.
Sangmin felt worse than I did.
He carried you on his back
all the time, that Sangmin.
Anyway, I envy you.
The way he spends more time on your school
festival than his graduation exhibition,
I guess he's gone to paint the wall
with Yongju and Youngchul...
Sangmin! Sangmin!
Sangmin!
I came with the family to see you,
but an emergency at your squad
forces me to turn away.
Are you doing well?
A few days ago,
heavy snow came down in Seoul.
The Han River is frozen as well...
It's colder here, right?
Don't catch cold.
And this is a secret
but my mom says that
I've become a woman now.
I'm a bit behind than the other girls,
but being an idiot that you are,
you won't understand what I mean, will you?
It's strange but when you were around,
I hated your guts,
but your absence has me missing you.
Are you feeling the same?
Then be good to me
from now on. Stupid.
The disappointment of not being able to
meet you has your mom crying.
Anyway, this letter,
I hope it reaches you.
Where have you been?
I've been looking all over for you.
The wall's great.
- I... have something to say.
- Yeah, what?
I'm sorry. I've been so selfish.
To you and...
What's got into you?
I'm breaking up with you.
I'm sorry, Jungwoo.
People laugh and dance
but I hate to laugh~
While we drink and search for love,
we forget about the truth~
Why are you late?
Did you see him?
Who? Your husband or boyfriend?
I'm not kidding!
There he is.
I like the smiling clown~
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah~
I like the clown who embraces sadness~
Aren't they great?
Now, intern, Park Sangmin will
share a few words with us.
I thank everyone,
the principal, all the teachers...
and all the students for helping me
finish this internship in one piece.
It may have been a short time,
but personally,
it has left me with precious memories
I will carry for the rest of my life.
Mr. Intern, cut the boring crap
and show us some honestly.
Mr. Park Sangmin is a married man.
Didn't you know?
Of course, it's not a sin to be married.
But in fact you're married to a
15 year old high school girl, right?
To Suh Boeun who's sitting right there...
Correct. We are married.
But Boeun had no choice.
The only crime she's committed was
granting her sick grandfather's last wish.
It was against her will to marry me.
She may be married, but she's still a
15 year old high school girl.
She goes crazy over a bowl of
chilli and spaghetti.
She loves cute stars and
Kimbap-loving attractive baseball players.
Everyday, she's stressed over exams,
and applying to university.
I hope you won't persecute Boeun's
school life over a marriage document.
I beg you all.
Sangmin,
I'm not a kid anymore.
Since I was little,
you were always at my side.
I was never aware of the
strange feelings... inside...
but... I think I'm in love with you...
Our poor Dongku. She's the end of
all your fun and play.
Fun and play...
I knew it since he was fixed on
that school queen or whatever...
I can't believe grandpa fell for
her grandmother.
- I can't believe it...
- She looks bright though.
Just consider it starting early! Do it!
Do it!
Oh, shut up and peel the garlic.
I'm in no position to say this, but
you can hide a lop-sided butt,
but not lop-sized balls.
Anyway, congrats.
It's good that she doesn't have a clue.
Who would marry a lop-sized ball man
if they knew, right?
Right.
Oh, you're here!
Oh, dad!
You're here.
I'm really getting into
peeling these things...
Did you get married to peel garlic?
Mom!
Okay!
Say cheese. One, two, three!!