Project A
Your recent operations
have been failures.
I have doubts about
your present proposal.
Governor, in my opinion,
these sea battles are risky.
Why not save all this precious
money and spend it on the police?
We can capture the pirates this time.
According to your records,
this is what happened two years ago.
You couldn't even find
where the pirates were.
And with the wind...
two ships were lost.
- A sudden typhoon came!
- How do you explain last year?
You were so certain
that you could capture the pirates,
but you got lost in the sea
and ended up in Bangladesh.
You were almost starved to death.
Can you explain that?
- I was never good at geography.
- You've wasted most of the budget.
We've not had a pay rise
for two years because of this.
Do you know that my officers
are complaining?
That's your problem, it's not mine.
You'd better think again.
I'm against taking unnecessary risks.
And so am I.
All right, if you're confident
it'll work, then go ahead.
Dragon! You're wanted immediately.
Dragon!
- Go get these papers signed.
- Thanks.
Morning.
Are you in a hurry?
Captain Chi, please sign this.
All this ammunition, is it necessary?
Is this another world war?
We need that much
to fight the pirates.
Aren't you aware that
we have to deal with street crime?
OK, you take all the ammunition,
we can still manage to do our jobs.
Corporal.
Tell our men to practise running.
No shooting at criminals,
we'll run after them instead.
Does that satisfy you?
If you hit the target every time,
a bullet can kill one pirate,
and a cannonball can kill
a few dozen pirates.
Then you won't need
so much ammunition.
Captain Chi, if you don't want to
give it to me, just say so.
How dare you
talk to your superior like that?!
Look at yourself.
You coast guards
can't even stand correctly.
You've been at sea for too long.
Do they ever teach you
what discipline is?
You may go now.
Once I sign this, I'll give it
to the armoury department.
Wait a second!
Lucky for you
you're not in my department. Dismiss.
Are you writing to your mum?
Tell her not to worry,
we'll be back real soon.
- Don't forget your life jacket.
- I'll sleep in it.
Why are you all so sad?
Grin and bear it!
You all look so gloomy!
We're not dead yet.
The cops are watching us.
Show some spirit, can't you?
Dragon.
- Is everybody here?
- Are we leaving?
Sure. We're sailing tomorrow night.
Why have you got such long faces?
Waiter, beer for everyone!
Thank you, sir.
It's very busy tonight.
Tzu, over here.
- Beer for everyone.
- You're late.
Sit down here.
This is my girlfriend - Chu.
- Waiter, here.
- Coming! OK.
You have to drink this.
Waiter.
- Who keeps the sea safe?
- The coast guard!
- Who's the toughest?
- Coast guard!
It's them again.
Drink to the greatest!
Don't your customers get served?
- They're going to die.
- Don't be like that.
- What did you say?
- You're going to die!
- Forget it.
- I'm coming.
- Hurry.
- Your order, please?
- Beer.
- Four beers.
- May I join in?
- Winnie. Sit down.
Are they celebrating something?
They're celebrating going to capture
the pirates. They may not come back.
A glass of milk, OK?
- Not milk. I'll buy you a beer.
- All right, then.
No wonder we don't get a pay rise.
These bums waste good money
chasing after pirates.
Actually, they couldn't even
locate where the pirates were.
Come on, don't get upset.
Even now, they have no idea
where the pirates are.
- Say that again!
- No trouble. Stay calm.
Tai-po, get the check.
Get the check.
Sha, taking a vacation soon?
- That's right.
- Are you going home?
To Canton.
The sea's full of pirates,
don't take a boat.
- How can he get there, then?
- He can always walk.
Do you feel safe
walking on the road?
Mind your own business.
Ladies and gentlemen, we admit the
sea is not safe now and we apologise.
My uncle is coming to Hong Kong and
he's walking all the way from Canton.
But he's blind,
how can he manage it?
But his ears are very good.
When he hears someone
selling cookies...
He's reached Yuen Long!
- When he can smell roast goose...
- He's in Shen Jang!
- And when he can hear whistles?
- Whistles.
He's in Hong Kong Island!
That's right.
Even children know this song.
One, two, three, four,
A, B, C, D
The cops whistle
when the criminals run away
Whistle...
The cops whistle
when the criminals run away
when the criminals...
- Whistle...
- Bastard!
Easy!
No fighting!
Stop it. Stop fighting.
Do you hear me? Stop it.
Come on.
Can nobody take a joke today?
We're sorry.
Let's toast to friendship.
Let's not fight each other.
- Why are you so rude?
- Shut up!
- What are you doing?
- Let's go.
- Are you OK?
- Are you all right?
I'm OK.
I spilt some beer,
but I've made my toast so no matter.
Let's go.
You dirtied my best suit.
- I apologise.
- But I don't forgive you.
You have two choices, pal.
You can say you are sorry or...
I won't say sorry.
I choose the second one.
Get him.
Get the truncheon.
- We're all friends, aren't we?
- Not any more.
- Come on.
- You come on!
I'll give him a mouthful.
Where is he?
What are they doing?
The cops are fighting
with the coast guards.
This one first.
Stop fighting.
Stop this at once. Police!
We're all for law and order here!
I'm going to get you.
I'll get back to you later.
Sorry, I didn't mean it.
Why did you hit me?!
I'll get him, be sure of that!
221! I've got your number.
I'll give you all this spaghetti!
- 221!
- I'm here. What is it?
Nothing.
You are supposed to represent
law and order. Arrest them.
Come on, get up.
Uncle.
Get yourself out of here.
You know we're sailing tomorrow,
you really can't detain my men.
Only some are detained.
You have all my navigators locked up.
Just because
you don't want us to sail.
I informed the governor.
I suppose you informed him
your nephew started it.
Can you let them go now?
My thanks to the captain.
All right.
I want no more trouble.
- Father.
- Go home.
Admiral, sir.
Sorry about the trouble we caused.
Don't apologise. If I was in your
position, I'd beat them to hell.
I never could stand
the smell of cops.
Get out of here!
Fall in.
Our mission
is to capture those pirates.
When you see them,
what should you do?
We will never let them go.
What if you are wounded?
We won't feel the pain.
And when you're captured?
Well?
What is it, then?
Guard, come here.
Talk...
Talk or you'll be shot dead.
Good. Keep silent if you're captured.
Dismiss.
Ready for inspection.
Listen up, boys.
If you can fight the pirates
like you fought the police,
then you're sure to win.
We're sure to win.
We built five ships,
why are there only three?
Governor, the other two
are submerged.
I thought we couldn't see them
because they were submarines!
Three ships will be too crowded.
They may be overcrowded,
but it shouldn't be a problem.
They won't be crowded when returning.
Ready.
What's that?
Put the fire out.
- Two ships are on fire.
- Then get water. Get water!
Those pirates!
I'll arrange for a ship
to take you to Vietnam.
Don't worry about it,
I know what to do.
Excuse me, I have some business now.
Chiang, the cops are looking for you.
You keep out of trouble.
Thanks to your information,
we've blown up their ships.
They're better off this way.
If you had blown them up at sea,
they would have had to swim home.
- Thank you very much.
- Don't mention it.
All my ships travel safely now
thanks to San-po's protection.
I should really thank him.
I'm happy to hear you say that.
San-po would like a favour from you.
He needs 100 rifles like this.
- I'll see you get paid well for it.
- Sure, I know what to do.
Cho-kou...
it won't be a problem.
We're counting on you. Bye now.
Take care.
But Boss, those are police rifles.
Where can we get that many?
It'll be tough,
but we'll manage it.
- We need a good man for the job.
- What about Chiang?
No. He's a wanted man now.
Contact Fei.
- Are you sure? He's expensive.
- Don't worry about it.
We can always kill him afterwards.
West. Full house.
On what?
- On a West.
- Where did you get that?!
He threw away a Circle.
You're blind.
The West was discarded ages ago.
- Now what?
- You should be fined.
- Pay the fine.
- Pay up.
- I'm finished.
- Fine.
- We need one more player.
- I'll join you.
"Ten Cent Stake"
"One Dollar Stake"
- Banker.
- Coming.
- Price it.
- Fei, I'll make it quick.
Can you take a look at this?
A broken rusty watch.
Three dollars.
It's Fei's watch.
You can be sure it's real gold.
100 dollars.
Yes.
- Hold on.
- No!
Not this one.
- 40,000.
- Wait.
It's time we saw
the colour of your money.
- Place your bets. Today is my day.
- Nothing I can do.
Can't you be more careful?
Eight Circles.
- What are you doing?
- Sorry, Fei.
Your turn.
Six Sticks.
You're not going to win this game.
- 20,000 thrown away.
- No. Honestly.
Are you accusing me of being blind?
Am I right?
- He discarded Five Circles.
- Right.
- Do you believe me now?
- No. Will you swear to it?
Sure. I will swear to it.
Everybody, on my life I swear
I've just discarded Five Circles.
I didn't throw away 20,000.
- Five Circles?
- That's right.
Let's see.
I won!
I won this game.
- You are good.
- Thank you.
Come on, give me my money.
- That's it.
- Hold it! I saw you cheating.
I saw you cheating.
Wait.
Sorry.
Don't worry. It's my turn now.
- Get up.
- Please, no!
What's the hurry?
Maybe I can win again.
It's my turn now.
It's a full house.
Nobody can argue with this.
Hello, Fei.
We want a favour from you.
Do you know how much money
I was going to win?
This is my new plan
for capturing the pirates.
It's called Project A.
First of all,
we need to buy new ships.
Go home and get some rest.
I'm not in the least bit tired.
Secondly, we need more new recruits.
Let me tell you,
your men have disappointed me a lot.
I'm turning them over to Captain Chi
for some hard training.
Now you're in charge of fundraising.
A British ship has been sent
to capture the pirates.
I want you to get out now!
- Change into these uniforms.
- Why?
Captain Chi's orders.
These are police uniforms.
- Are you kidding?
- The governor disbanded our squad.
I don't care what I wear,
as long as I still get paid.
It's better than fighting
the pirates.
Congratulations.
Congratulations on your new status.
Now you don't need to endure
the hardship of the sea.
- And you, sir?
- Me?
Didn't you hear about my promotion
to chairman of fundraising?
- What exactly is that?
- Go change your uniforms. Come on.
Change uniforms at once.
That's my last order.
I think it's time to report in.
Go on.
Reporting for duty, Captain Chi.
From the coast guards. Sergeant Ma?
We've been disbanded, sir.
I don't care what
you did in the coast guards,
you're in the police now.
When you answer an officer
in this force, answer yes or no.
Just look at you.
You call that attention?
I'll teach you how to stand.
Stand to attention.
Stand up, chest out, stomach in.
From the nose to the toes,
there's a straight line.
Is your number 213? Answer me.
Do you think you're stupid?
Answer me!
Not bad at all.
- Captain Chi.
- Just in time. Meet Sergeant Ma.
This is our new inspector, Hong Tin-tzu.
Inspector Hong
is an excellent officer.
He'll be your squad leader and train
you to be a Special Mission squad.
You may leave. Dismiss.
Sergeant.
For the last time,
what is the correct salute?
We're in trouble.
Start training them tomorrow.
If you want them to listen to you,
be sure to give them a hard time.
Come on, fall in.
You, come here.
Salute, Private.
Stand up, chest out, stomach in.
Do it 500 times.
I don't care how sloppy
you were before,
you're in the police now.
- As a policeman you have to be fit.
- Look at that chick over there.
- She's got a crazy figure!
- She's a bit of all right.
209 and 214, come out here.
What were you talking about?
- He said look at that chick.
- He said she had a crazy figure.
Go repeat it 500 times.
1000!
- Look at that chick over there.
- She's got a crazy figure.
- Look at that chick over there...
Who was laughing?
- It was me, sir.
- Here.
- Laughing on parade.
- Yes, sir.
- Were you the only one laughing?
- Do you know the punishment for it?
- To laugh 1,000 times.
Shoot him dead.
- Look at that chick there.
- She's got a crazy figure.
- She's got a crazy figure...
Sir, we've finished.
He fainted before the execution.
Then he can clean the toilets.
Look at that chick.
She's got a crazy figure.
Look at that chick. She got a...
What's up?
That was some dream.
I hit Tzu really hard.
Let me sleep!
- Why is there an emergency call now?
- There must be an emergency.
- Nonsense.
- Put on your uniforms. Quick.
You drank too much soup last night
so you need the toilet now.
Sergeant.
Take them to the toilets
and then dismiss them.
Stand by. Into attack. Forward.
In our squad, speed is essential.
It's very simple.
You have ten seconds. Stand by.
Go.
One, two, three,
four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine, ten.
You must understand that I'm training
you to be alert day and night.
- OK, my turn.
- Do you have ten seconds, too?
Instructors are allowed 45 seconds.
Give me a water ladle.
Give me one. Hurry!
Give it to him.
That's an order.
We might have to use some
deadly weapons on our missions.
This is the latest hand grenade.
You might not know it.
I will give a demonstration.
Pull the pin out
and throw it within ten seconds.
Bang! It's just exploded.
Got it, boys?
Big Mouth, get the grenade.
- Did you switch them?
- Yes.
Sergeant,
did I say you were outstanding?
Step back in line.
Let's take turns at throwing it.
Sergeant, you.
- Sir, he doesn't know how to use it.
- Yes, I do.
Can you show us again, sir?
OK. Watch carefully this time.
Firstly...
- Do you think I'm stupid?
- No. But that's a real grenade.
Pull the pin. This time I'll throw
it towards you. So watch out.
Quick! It's a real grenade. Look out!
Squad, sit down.
We've been given orders
to arrest Chiang.
We've heard that
he's hiding in the Hoover Club.
One problem is that
important people use this club.
We must arrest Chiang discreetly and
not disturb the members in the club.
Do you all understand?
Understood, sir.
I can't do it alone. I'll let you
know when I've made my mind up.
- You better make it quick.
- The quicker the better.
Don't cause a disturbance
until we find Chiang.
We all know what to do.
You cover here. Come on.
Membership cards, please.
Police.
Can I help?
That's not a membership card.
We suspect you're hiding
an escaped criminal.
Wait there.
He said our members
are rich and famous people.
There are no criminals here.
- Front door's there.
- Can't we come in for a drink?
No disrespect,
but how much do you earn a month?
Even a glass might be worth more
than your savings.
Stop!
I said stop.
- Calm down.
- He was trying to tip them off.
- Lucky I didn't break any glasses.
- Do you know who my boss is?!
- I don't need to know.
- We want to have a look around.
Fine.
Take a look.
Leave when you've finished.
You've seen everything.
That's the manager's office.
Stop! Come here.
It's the cops.
Chiang, coming out quietly?
All the bad guys are here.
That'll save me some work.
We're arresting you
for murder and drug trafficking.
And for insulting a policeman.
This is the warrant.
You know the charges!
We've come for an arrest,
not a fight.
Beat him up!
- You can't go up.
- Get lost!
Speak Chinese!
You have to pay
for all the damage here.
Get him.
- Keep out of sight.
- Go on.
Look at this mess!
Stop it. I said stop it.
- Captain.
- Do you have a warrant for this?
- No.
- Sergeant Ma.
We were informed
the murderer Chiang was here.
- So where is he?
- Upstairs.
How dare you!
You're trespassing on my property.
Captain, your men
should join a demolition squad.
Do you know what you're doing?
You are more experienced than Tzu,
you should have known better.
- Uncle...
- That's enough.
- Sergeant, apologise to Mr Chou.
- To him? But we did nothing wrong!
They're hiding criminals
and have assaulted us. Apologise?!
Captain, I'll tell the governor that
you allowed these men to slander me.
Come back.
You'll see if it's slander.
I said apologise to Mr Chou.
There's a punishment
for disobeying an order.
So be it, then. I quit.
I am no longer a policeman.
No more orders.
How dare you!
Stop him.
Everyone stay where you are.
You take the credit.
I'm always the bad guy.
Dragon.
You almost hit my nose!
How are you?
You don't treat friends like this.
It's not my fault
if you have the hump.
Were you in the club?
When I saw you guys move in,
I knew something was in the air.
In this world of evils,
no man stands alone.
I won't join your thieving ways!
Don't mention that word. Since you
joined the force, I've gone straight.
How else could we be seen together?
I guess some
are delighted that you quit.
Why?
You want to get rid of the pirates,
but not everyone is like you.
- Really?
- Yes.
Why did your ships get blown up?
Someone betrayed you all.
- You're guessing.
- I'm not.
The pirates are getting rifles
from somebody inside your force.
News! Read all about it.
Pirate San-po strikes again.
Three dead, 24 injured.
Read all about it.
- Who'd sell to pirates?
- Why do you want to know?
I want to know
who would be so cold-blooded.
Thanks.
Why do you know so much?
Are you thinking of stealing them?
In life there are four
kinds of people.
I don't qualify as a rich man.
I don't like being poor.
The cops don't want me
so I have to be a thief.
As you're my friend,
I'll try to be a good thief.
In this rifle deal,
everyone is a bad guy.
You can get your man
and I'll get my money.
And we both win.
Tell me where.
At the jetty.
Are you ready?
Get them on board.
- The pier's moved!
- Get him up here.
- Quick!
- Someone's there!
It's me.
Do you know you're committing
a serious crime?
And selling arms
to the pirates is a crime.
- How shall we punish him?
- Chop off his head.
Yes! We'll chop his head off.
We're surrounded by water.
I can't find an axe.
So... we have to let them go.
We'll kick them in the water.
- Why didn't you jump?
- I can't swim.
- Really?
- I can't.
- Now what?
- What now?
Why can't you swim?
It's never too late to learn.
Give this to him.
Now swim and swim!
- Thank you.
- Don't mention it.
- Help! I can't swim!
- Let's go.
Help me!
- What will you do with them?
- Find some buyers, of course.
Yeah, they'll make good money.
You're not going to sell
them to just anybody, are you?
- These are guns, not toys.
- Don't worry.
I'll sell them back to the army.
Are you happy now?
Then I'm glad I helped you.
What's that for?
We have to identify which log it is.
Remember, it's only
you and I in on this.
Have you finished, Fei? This way.
- Have you got the money?
- Here.
And the rifles?
I wouldn't keep rifles here.
Do you think I'm crazy?
Now, where are the rifles?
They're in the log yard.
I'll take you there in the morning.
- There's so many. Which one is it?
- Easy. I fixed a red cloth on it.
Right there, see?
- They all have a red cloth.
- Which one?
What now, Fei? Which one is it?
Looks like we'll have to turn
them all over.
OK, guys, get started.
Listen, Fei,
be smart with us. We can get rough.
Mind your manners.
You guys get soft
living the high life.
You double-crossed us.
Do you think I'm crazy?
Tell us right now or we'll kill you.
Everyone leave. This place
is closed to the public today.
Come on, split.
You sold us out to the cops.
It's not my day.
Why are you still here?
I'm an undertaker.
His father is going to die and he's
looking for a nice log for a coffin.
It's better to do it early.
This will make a nice one.
You're a good boy. But it's closed.
Come some other day.
All right, we're leaving now.
See you. Bye for now.
- There's a lot of cops.
- He won't get far.
We'll deal with him back in town.
Let's go.
Admiral, it's all clear.
Dragon said it's the log
without a red cloth. Find it.
- I'm sorry!
- What are you doing?
What? Wasn't Captain Chi going to
sell the rifles to the pirates?
No, he was collecting them
for the government.
- It's Fei.
- Womaniser!
If it wasn't for you,
they would never have found the guns.
How did you know the rifles
were there?
How did I know? I eavesdropped!
But they discovered me.
- What happened then?
- I was surrounded by 20 thugs.
- No other man can compete with me.
- So...
I jumped on one and kicked three!
There was only one fat guy left.
What a fight we had!
We were fighting for three minutes,
until I used this move.
Then he was defeated.
Then I told him
if the pirates got those rifles,
many kids would be killed.
That's right.
He decided to tell me
where the rifles were hidden.
Dragon, I think you're wonderful.
Traitor! So the price
for betrayal is one little kiss?
And nothing else!
- Look...
- I'll deal with you later.
Have you seen a fat guy?
A fat guy? He's gone that way.
Don't expect me to thank you.
You! I just heard his voice.
He's right there.
Many thanks.
Don't block my way.
Why are you chasing me?
Ask him where he's put the guns.
- Dragon.
- Let's go!
Get him.
Come on.
Where are the guns?
- Ask him.
- Talk!
- They're in the police station.
- What?!
Do you know how to handle that thing?
You conned me!
I thought you were a friend.
Double-crosser!
I was doing it for you.
How many times have I saved you?
- Never.
- Liar.
What about that axeman?
Who saved you then?
I don't remember that!
Bastard! I'll teach you a lesson!
- Let's go.
- Come on.
This way. Hurry, follow me.
There!
Cut them off.
- Wait! Where's Winnie?
- How do I know?
If you get away,
we'll meet at the usual place.
I can't walk.
Hold on.
They went that way.
Go on, jump.
It's not so high. I'll go first.
Jump, go on!
- Impossible!
- Don't be scared. I'll catch you.
If you don't jump,
you'll end up a gangster's moll.
Come on.
Hide in there.
Stop.
- Come on.
- My leg hurts!
You'll be all right. Quick.
Quick.
Watch out!
Run for it.
I'm up here!
Give me your hand.
Come on, run.
Just follow me.
It's easy, you see. See?
Come on.
- I'm still up here.
- You'll send me mad!
Can't you even jump?