Dinner is at 6.
Good job, guys!
BONG?
Mi-jin.
I got little something
for you.
You shouldn't have...
You've come a long way.
I guess our practice
at Karaoke paid off.
I was so embarrassed then.
Quite an experience
for me though.
BONG...
Please.
You're warm.
Mi-jin, I love you.
BONG...
The movie isn't done yet.
It needs editing.
Mi-jin...
How do you feel about
your new life?
It's so refreshing.
Let's have a party
of our own.
Sure. Why not?
Why'd you choose me?
You were so helpless
like myself long ago.
When were you chosen?
100 years ago.
I couldn't be more
confident now.
Who will do the editing?
An assistant director.
He's good.
Here, cheers.
Cheers.
Didn't it hurt?
I was in so much pain the first time.
Not really.
I was drunk.
Your blood was so fresh.
BONG's blood was
a bit salty.
You'll get used to it.
How old are you?
120. Age is just a number.
It's delicious.
That part is good
for your skin.
What if I get hooked
and crave it?
Control yourself. But you must
eat it once every 2 years.
Cause there are many men
who need to go.
Jane... Jane...
Don't talk.
In the End is My Beginning
Remember me?
My daughter tutored you
in high school.
I even cooked for you.
How dare you show up here!
Stop it.
You're nothing but a whore.
Get out of here!
Honey?
Get up.
Breakfast is ready.
Let me sleep some more.
Come on.
Let's eat together.
You know we can't.
Why not?
I'm dead. Remember?
It's a plant.
"Water it and
what you need will grow."
What are you doing here?
How'd you get in?
I've been here for a while.
Get out of here.
Now!
No point kicking me out.
Cause I'll be back.
What's going on here?
Did you call her?
Get out.
- No.
- Now.
Please.
Get out.
Let me stay here.
I'll do anything.
Shut up and leave.
I'm begging you.
Let me stay.
- Please...
- Get out!
Let me stay.
Let me stay...
Please.
Why don't you?
No way.
Give her a break.
I said no!
Let me stay.
Please.
Let her or I'll leave.
Hi.
You can't get over him?
Searching for his memories...
It's not that.
Save it.
That's what you're here for,
isn't it?
I won't touch his things
if it bothers you.
You sure?
Change into that.
It'll bring back
vivid memories of him.
You're killing me.
Make it tighter.
Am I pretty?
You're still so pretty.
What'd you do
after high school?
A lot of things.
I delivered. I cleaned.
I gave manicures.
Then I acted in a few plays.
I did magic, too.
You know what you're best at.
Like what?
Recognize this?
You could've been a porn star.
You were a slut
back in school days.
I wasn't.
You know that.
I thought I did.
Eat it.
Eat it all.
So you can cherish
such a precious memory.
It's some sight to see.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
Come in.
Hi.
She's just a maid.
Don't mind her.
Draw the tub for us.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Stop it.
Hey! Come up here.
What this is for?
You... favor?
Tie me.
You are for real?
Tie me up.
What are you doing?
Tie me like he tied you.
Tighter.
Come on. Tighter.
Oh, come on.
Are you sure you want...
Tighter! Tighter!
Come on!
You can do better!
Tie me tighter.
Make it tighter.
Tighter.
- I'm get going...
- Where are you going?
Get back here!
It's no fun.
Oh God...
What's wrong with me?
What's that?
In case I couldn't stand
this punishment.
Jung-ha...
It feels weird.
What?
A wife and a lover celebrating
his birthday together.
What a lucky bastard.
Leave now.
What?
Leave.
Stop saying that.
I'd rather kill myself.
I mean it.
It started raining that day
unexpectedly.
All my dad did was magic.
So I didn't expect him
to pick me up.
You stole me an umbrella
from a store.
Right then, a raindrop...
It fell on your forehead
like a God's voice.
And it exploded
over your eyebrows.
So did my heart.
If I could get near you...
...I would've done worse
- than seducing him.
- That's enough.
He might hear you.
Don't make him upset
on his birthday.
When we first kissed...
Stop it.
I don't remember.
My tongue...
When it got into your mouth...
You told me
you heard a bell ringing.
Was it the same
when you kissed Jane?
Yes.
You truly loved him.
Tie me up.
Stop.
I said stop.
Am I not better than him?
You don't arouse me.
Stop it, will you?
Can't you see?
I'm you, Jung-ha.
Awake?
You can leave now.
Thanks.
I have to ask you.
Yes?
Did you know?
Naru didn't...
I know.
Be good.
Hi.
Hey!
You're 30 minutes late.
Why the hell are you late?
God...
Did it hurt?
You're buying.
Excuse me?
You haven't changed.
You either.
We'll have fun today.
Just like we did.
Just today?
Can't a girl eat?
I've never seen a girl
eating like a pig.
The beautiful eat a lot.
Here, eat some.
You won't get it?
Wanna see something funny?
What about Su-jung?
Going together?
We will.
If she decides to.
Is that why
we're doing this?
I just wanted to know
how she feels about me.
What about you?
I wanted to make sure, too.
Make sure what?
What Ji-woon means to me.
I know you like him.
What about him?
He will find out today.
I wonder how it will end.
You've done that before.
I know.
I'll do more today.
What else are you gonna
show me?
Show you?
I don't think so.
I'm sleeping with him today.
You suck in bed.
He's way better.
You're crazy.
You think so?
You don't think you are?
How long have you been
with an art teacher?
Beats me.
I can't remember.
I just can't understand you.
What?
Can you understand
what we're doing then?
Who is it?
It's Yoon-jung.
She's sounding you out.
I don't know.
This is pathetic.
Why'd you suggest this?
You're a fool.
If this will break you up,
you're not meant to be together.
So naive.
What'd he say?
"Do as you please."
He doesn't mean it.
He's just pretending to be cool.
Like you?
I know how I feel
about Su-jung.
What about her?
Tell me.
Is Se-eun ok with this?
How'd you guys hook up?
Sang-min.
Do you wanna...
...kiss me?
What are you trying to pull?
See you tomorrow at school.
I can't believe he did that.
He hasn't called you?
By the way,
where are we going?
We have a thing to do.
We do?
What?
You okay?
Huh? Yes.
I like it better with Ji-woon.
Of course.
He's your boyfriend.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
Should I walk you?
No, it's okay.
Yoon-jung,
we should take a picture.
Oh, right.
Wait, wait.
What?
Tell me honestly.
Is this your revenge
against Sang-min?
You don't wanna do it?
No, I wanna do it.
You like being with me?
You're no different.
"Do as you please"?
That's me?
Let me see.
It's you.
Let me draw you.
Don't look.
- What is this?
- Wait.
You're making it worse.
Fix mine then.
- Long legs...
- Make them longer.
## #~##...
- Why?
- Draw it again.
Stop it.
You're so good.
Don't let it go to your head.
I won't let you win
this time.
Wait.
Let me gather my Ki.
Let's go.
Thanks.
No way.
You're going down.
I wish I could be cool
about this.
I don't think
I can see you again.
Ji-woon.
Let's not do it again.
Yesterday, I couldn't...
You're not supposed
to tell me.
Right.
I love you.
Ditto.
You! "Do as you please"?
What was that?
Get back here!
Ji-woon!
I love you, Yoon-jung!