I promise you I'll never see her again.
Don't go.
Trust me.
Say no more, let's get a divorce.
Mom.
Did I do anything wrong?
I have never seen dad again ever since.
I then asked mom
why she parted with father.
Mom says I might love someone
at the beginning...
but then I would soon
get tired of that person.
She says I will understand this
when I grow up.
Mom, will you get tired of me in future?
Of course not,
I'll give you the best care.
No matter how tired mom is...
...she teaches me how to play
Bach and Beethoven every night.
But what I want to sing the songs
by Danny Chan and Leslie Cheung.
Mom won't get married again
just for my good sake.
I know she really loves
and pampers me as well.
Therefore I can never stand against her,
though I sometimes disagree with her.
I always ask myself.
If I fall in love with someone,
...I wonder if I can treat him
like the way my mom treats me.
...Will I love him
no matter what happens.
Hong, Mimi speaking!
Please cut your hair short.
Please leave your hair long.
It's not easy to keep hair long.
Sir, what would you like?
One order spaghetti...
Come back...
Angie, I haven't seen you all day.
Haven't you?
I've reserved seats for you.
I have already turned down many people
who asked for this table.
Didn't you say
you loved that Bossini watch very much?
Bossini?
It's a Bulgari!
More or less the same, man.
Yeah, more or less,
just a difference of $18,600.
What if I send it to you as a present
when I have enough money?
You can surely make it,
I have confidence.
Get some food for us.
Thanks...
Stupid!
Don't be this way, you'll hurt him.
Hey, tell me about yours first.
What is he like?
He is tall, slim, big eyes, high nose...
Then he looks like you.
Yeah, as good-looking like you.
Not as good-looking as you,
but a fatty loves you very much.
Not necessarily,
I've read a psychological book.
People will find themselves
better-looking as time goes by,
and soon they'll find a lover that
resembles themselves, this is called...
Narcissism.
No, just the perfect couple.
Watch out!
Hot... Kid... Mini... Sundae.
What do you mean?
We're "Kid Mini Sundae",
she's also "Kid Mini Sundae",
why are you so biased?
About the same no difference, man.
What? Man, get me another one.
Hey, you want to stir up trouble here?
What if I do?
Stop fooling or I'll kick you out!
Shit!
Sorry...
Go pick up the ball!
Dad, are you OK?
We'd better call for an ambulance,
Uncle Wing.
What's wrong? Serve now!
This way, come on.
Go, go...
Yes! Yeah!
Why is it under-cooked?
Not even any vegetable?
They're in the refrigerator,
not yet washed.
Why don't you wash them now?
What? I'm your guest anyway.
Brother, I must tell you something,
don't tell father.
You're pregnant?
Of course not, I never will be.
Why?
I am Les.
What Les?
I am Lesbian,
I'm interested in girls only.
Why?
When I visit the bathroom,
I have the urge to peep at other girls.
Do you find me abnormal?
There's nothing wrong to be homosexual,
but it's bad to be a horny lesbian.
Am I abnormal then?
You're normal.
Anyway, you're not in love with cats,
dogs or this vegetable.
Even if you fall in love with them, that
doesn't mean you're abnormal, right?
Many people are like this too.
Let me tell you, your brother and I...
Nuts!
What shall I do if others laugh at me?
Hit them!
Even if others laugh at you,
you can tell them sincerely...
- I'm homosexual.
What can they do to you?
They can't do nothing to you, right?
What's "gay"?
Are both talking about homosexual?
Eat!
Have you seen any meteors?
I did borrow two porn
video cassettes from you...
I was going to take them back,
but I dropped it into the ditch.
Can you get me something
so that I can pick them up?
Don't tell me you're trying hard...
...to get a degree or a master degree.
Anyone can tell
you've given up studying.
What do you mean? You're nuts!
Don't you have lust?
Nuts!
I mean seduce girls.
Dad, it's not that simple
to seduce girls.
I remember being a kid of 19 years old,
I had seven girlfriends
at the same time, I'd court even a sow.
What? You had seven snows
at the same time? Blind sows?
You're strong!
You bastard!
OK... I'll seduce one tomorrow.
Let's cross fingers.
Nuts! I can't just go seducing,
not before I find someone I love.
I'll ask Fatty Lan
to play mahjong tomorrow.
You can get to know each other then...
Nuts.
We've serious work tomorrow, to earn money.
OK?
Where can you make money?
Being a gigolo?
Being a slave,
a school is holding a show.
He and I will help with
moving and transporting.
How much can you make?
$70 an hour.
Why do you go to school then?
I can't hold on anymore.
Can't hold on... anymore...
This must be hurried...
help me massage a bit.
Start work now, don't play on.
Start work.
Watch the cart carefully.
Shrimp Dumpling, Pork Dumpling.
Rice Rolls.
What?
Man, sorry... excuse me...
Excuse me...
Watch out where are you going next time?
What is you say? What is you come from?
Don't you watch where you're going?
How to say "challenge" in English?
"Heat"
Heat!
Stop that "heat", come on.
Excuse me.
BBQ Pork Buns.
Rice Rolls.
Shrimp Dumpling, Pork Dumpling.
Which one?
I say this one.
You say this one, and that one,
which one exactly?
I say this one.
We can make close-up with this one.
Excuse me.
What are you talking about?
Disguise as foreign singers?
You move the things to back stairs now.
Why point with your fingers?
- What do you mean?
- What?
What...
- What are you doing?
- What?
- What are you looking at?
- Looking at me?
- What?
- What?... What?
What?
- What?
Nothing, those bastards threaten me
as they fail in the reasoning.
What do you want then?
- What?
- What
- You What?
What?
What do you want now?
How come I know?
- What?
Forget it... OK? We're sorry, OK?
Let's go.
Go?
Why shout on? Do you know who they are?
What did you say?
What?
- What did you say?
- What?
What?
Have you finished shouting?
Why don't you work up there?
Go working now.
Mind your steps, I tell you.
Do you see me now?
Mind your steps.
Man, excuse me.
Just never mind me...
Have you eaten yet?
Can't you answer me?
Yeah!
- Hey, you're smart.
- Yeah!
I'll donate $500,000.
How much will you?
$1,000.
Hong, come up here, set one more
microphone next to the piano.
Coming.
OK.
Thanks.
Hey, you want someone?
Is the guy who set up the microphone
the David you met in MTR?
None of your business.
But I saw him being scolded furiously.
He's as poor as a dog, didn't you see?
You won't fall in love
with such a green-horn, will you?
You guess.
Excuse me, have you got facial paper?
Oh... no.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
I... I've seen you.
Have you?
You were wearing school uniform.
Go away...
Why are you so ugly?
Wooing girls? I'm leaving.
Bye.
What is it?
Will you come to the show tonight?
I don't have a ticket.
Hey, I have an extra ticket with me.
Take it if you want to see.
Don't waste it.
Bye-bye.
Don't forget me if you make a fortune.
What do you mean by this?
I mean if you become rich.
Nuts! How come I become rich?
About the tall girl with big eyes
whom you just met.
I saw her wallet
with many gold credit cards inside.
What credit card have you got?
You don't even have a single card.
Do I?
I think you can become a pimp.
What are you saying about?
You're aged, behave yourself.
No handicap.
You mean you want me to suffer?
Sorry, I said it wrong.
Go seduce her again,
take more with you...
I'll pay... let me pay...
I'll pay!
You're chicken-hearted?
You're chicken.
It's good you've got guts.
We're two of a kind indeed.
What? Just like a prince and princess?
One of the prettiest princess.
One of the poorest prince.
The two are the perfect couple.
Shit! Take your hands off me.
Cut your dirty finger nails first.
Then you can seduce girls, come on.
What?
Come on, let's play games.
Good-bye everyone, I'm leaving.
You're leaving, Tap?
It's late, you're not leaving?
No, I've booked a table, come with me?
Sorry, Chris, mother is waiting for me.
I've taken some photos for you,
keep them.
Thank you.
I'll leave now, good-bye.
Quick, catch up with her,
don't wait for me.
Girl... go chase your girl!
You have no luck at all.
Brother, your call.
Who is it?
A girl.
A girl?
Hello?
This is IRG surveying company.
How much time do you spend daily
in the bathroom?
How do I know?
Do you keep track of the time yourself?
I've an incoming call, got to hang up.
Hello?
- Hello?
I've found that guy.
Which guy?
The one who set up the microphone.
Yes!
But, what did you just say? Which topic?
Nothing, heard his voice,
felt scared and just hung up.
Did you?
OK, let me call him up for you.
I'll ask him to call you up,
then you can talk on.
Really? Thanks.
What's his number?
Hello?
Hong, Shum Chi Hong.
Speaking... you are?
I met you at school last time...
I'm the friend of the girl who made your
saliva water and your eyes pop open.
Do you want to call up that girl?
Yes, I do...
Yes, then please copy down the number...
2-3-3-5-2...
0-0-0
- Hello?
Is it Tap?
Hong Speaking
I am...
the one who asked you for the tissue...
Do you remember me?
Yes, I do.
Your friend gave me your phone number.
How did you get my phone number?
I've a friend
who works at the audio company.
Tap...
Will, why are you called Tap?
My name is Stephenie,
my classmates nicknamed me Tap.
So now everyone calls me Tap.
Which school did you attend?
And you?
I'm a F.7 student in St. Marynold.
A famous school.
What about you?
I'm also a F.7 student.
Which school?
La Salle.
OK... why don't we exchange
our school prospectus?
Sure, how?
You decide.
Let's meet this Sunday afternoon.
OK, it's a deal, bye.
- Hello?
Where shall we meet then?
Your choice?
Someone going to commit suicide!
Who? Where?...
Isn't it suicide to have affairs
when you're broke?
Let me rescue you...
If you become king of Noodle,
you can win $7,500.
Then you can seduce girls.
Damn it! What is it?
The more you can eat,
then more you'll win, start.
Hey, did you cheat?
You're disqualified, come with me!
What's going on?
Mentor, if you manage to eat
this last bowl,
You'll win the super prize.
Eat on.
Yeah!
Go on! Be confident!
Go on! Courage
Louder... shout more loudly!
Right, one mouthful,
one more mouthful, eat it!
Quick!
Go on, courage!
Enough...
Someone has won!
Yeah!
Congratulations,
you've won our super prize, you get $750
What? Say it again?
Are you alright? It's $7,000, not $700...
Are you alright?
Quick... take photos for him...
take photos...
What?
- What?
- Quick...
What are you taking?
$20 for a snapshot.
Sir, may I help you?
I'll have...
This... "Never Loved Like This Before"
OK.
Add in some chocolate.
Sure.
No thanks, I'll just watch awhile.
Hi
Hi!
This is my friend Angie, this is Bell.
Hi
Much neater this time.
You look alike.
You're so tall.
Don't be like this.
Am I?
Why you're so shy?
You needn't be shy, we'll leave now.
Yeah, we just here to see
if you suit her.
I say... as a couple, it's a good match.
We know... what to do...
Let's go
They're always like this.
It's OK...
You're really very tall.
Miss, please.
Thanks.
I want this one, please.
"Never Loved Like This Before"
Sir.
I've brought my school
prospectus for you.
My school prospectus...
I've forgotten to bring mine.
I'll bring it the next time.
It's alright.
Composition champion, javelin champion.
Vice-Chairman of Music Group...
You're competent.
Not really, my classmates
played a joke and elect me.
What are you? Joining any activities?
Football Club.
Football Club? Football Team?
Yeah.
La Salle Football team?
Do you know Johnny and Stephen?
I... played football with them
only yesterday?
Didn't Johnny emigrate to the US?
Johnny?
Johnny Koo.
Not him, I mean Johnny Chan.
Right, Johnny Chan has gone to the US.
We keep in touch with each other.
Do you have time, later on?
...why don't we meet another day.
How about going to eat something.
Time's up... OK...
Can we go inside now?
The 7:00 p.m. show is full house,
but I've got tickets for 9:30 p.m. show.
What is it?
I promised mom
I'll be home before 9:00 p.m.
It's OK, let's see it next time.
Let's not waste the tickets,
wait for me.
Hello, is it Angie?
You've turned bad.
But luckily you've got me as friend.
OK, just count on me.
Hello? Aunt, Angie speaking.
Tap will be at my house tonight
for a project,
so she won't get home until 11:30 p.m.,
Ask her answer the phone.
Tap.
Kid, please show me your tickets.
You showed us to these seat.
Are we sitting in the wrong place?
No, but you've come too early.
Your tickets are tomorrow evening show,
not today.
Come again tomorrow.
Shouldn't we leave?
Hello?
Can't stand it anymore, lied about toilet
three times, bought snack four times.
I even lied that you had three baths.
If you don't go home, I afraid your mom
will call up the police.
Hello...
You're rushing home?
Let me see you home by taxi.
Let's take a bus.
Then we can spend more time together.
Bye-bye.
OK, let's count three, and then...
Let's part after saying good-bye.
One, two...
I must go home.
One.
Two.
Three.
Bye-bye.
You're back so quickly?
Mom.
5 minutes ago Angie said you're taking
a bath, but you're back so soon?
Did she really say so?
Yeah.
It's like this... mom,
we have a lot of pressure at school.
And Angie must finish
an important project.
So she's recently...
What kind of is so important project?
It's vital, not finished yet,
it's about my happiness.
Good-bye mom.
What is she up to?
Why don't you sleep?
Mom.
In fact, I wasn't at Angie's place
for the project.
Where did you go then?
I went out with a friend.
A boy?
My daughter has grown up, she's in love.
Bring him home for dinner on Saturday.
What are you doing?
Got sand in my shoes.
Want to take your shoes off?
No, thanks.
Hello, come and sit here.
Mom.
Hong.
What are you doing?
I want to photo as souvenir.
I want to take photo for Aunt.
Help yourself, come on.
Come on...
Good appetite, Aunt.
Let's eat.
What's her name?
Eat now.
Have you got an English name?
Shum Chi Hong
S-H-U-M C-H-I H-O-N-G, Auntie?
Which school do you go to?
La Salle, F.7.
You're attending university this Autumn,
any faculty in mind?
Any Faculty is fine with me,
I haven't decided yet.
But... I prefer studying football.
Studying football?
Can you give an opinion?
No "connon"
What?
No "common"
How can a La Salle student
be so ignorant?
I'll get some drink, you want one?
Mom.
What do you think of him?
No "common", lily no "common"
- Let me do it.
- OK.
I'm sorry... Let me do it...
It is OK.
No... let me do it... please take a rest...
You go... you take it easy.
What are you two doing here?
Nothing. I'm washing this glass,
and will wash the rest too.
Well, come next time
when our maid is on leave.
OK...
Thank you, go take a rest.
What a big sitting room?
Is it the Governor's House?
You're ignorant.
Is she pretty?
Your girlfriend? Very pretty.
That "Old Bag" is her mother?
She's called Tina.
Tina, the "Old Bag"?
I warn you,
don't mention this remark if she's here.
Don't worry,
I won't call her that if she's around.
You're mean...
Where shall we go?
Le Se Wa Sai Si Si
What are you saying?
Can't hear a damn thing.
- Let me teach you this S-language.
- Sure.
It's for exchanging secret message.
Whenever you speak...
...add an "S" between two syllables.
Raise the tone
if it's a unstressed sound.
For example: Put your legs on the floor.
Then it becomes:
Fong So Fan Sa Le Sa Ja...
It's hard to learn or hear.
How to say: I love you?
Caw Saw Chun Shun Yee See Lai Sai
Oh... I see.
What are you saying?
I'm speaking a Dialect-language.
Stupid, can't you learn S-language?
S-language is too hard to learn.
Is it very hard?
Oh... say I'm stupid in S-language?
Do you really mean I'm stupid?
I'll tickle you if you say I'm stupid.
No... help...
I'm bored, I'm leaving now.
The weather is nice today,
I must seduce you.
I'm going to seduce you,
so what are you afraid of?
Come on, I'm mighty,
you haven't never tried this before...
Stop that.
You don't look like a La Salle boy.
What? You don't believe me?
No...
Then let me kiss you again, come on...
Open your eyes...
You're Angie!
You again?
Stephen?
Having a wild game?
If I break up with you,
why should you be depressed?
Kid, what are you talking about?
None of your business.
You're both from La Salle,
don't quarrel!
You're La Salle?
I'm from La Salle.
I'm really from La Salle.
You're from La Salle?
You mean you're from La Salle?
I'm from La Salle.
You're from La Salle?
I'm really from La Salle.
Where's Stephen?
Let's talk over there, come on...
Where has he gone?
Stephen
What happened to you?
Nothing, someone just beat me up.
You got robbed?
Not a robbery, they just beat me,
still have my money.
Who is he?
Stephen, it's your classmate.
You are from La Salle too?
No, got beaten up twice? Oh, God!
Stephen
You live here?
Dad says the fengshui is good here,
he won't move.
We called this "Gold House", you know?
"Gold House"? Keeping a concubine?
Keeping a concubine?
I'll take you as my concubine.
Open the door.
My sister is really cute,
I love to pamper her.
Hello
Meet the sister.
Very cute!
Where did you sleep?
I must fire the maid tomorrow.
Don't be like this.
What shall we do now?
Revising lessons.
Really?
Revising lessons!
You sleep when I'm asking you to study?
Get up.
In fact, we're doing nothing
but studying all day.
So we should relax from time to time.
Want to relax?
What! Messing around here.
Dad... welcome, don't bullshit...
Dad, Stephenie, daddy.
Hello
How are you, Uncle?
Just call me Wing.
How are you, Uncle Wing?
How are you?
It's fate we meet.
I've been so busy recently.
I've just arrive from L.A. ... and Africa,
just got off from the plane
Did you?
I'm an easy going person.
In deed, a rich man doesn't need
to showoff he has money.
Have you ever told others
we have properties worth of $40 million?
Quietly...
Yeah...
- Dad.
- Yeah.
Please eat, I cook one more
OK, you eat yourself, thank you.
Give me a massage, I'm aching all over.
Quick.
Massage harder.
Are you weak from starvation?
How's this?
OK, no, thanks.
It's all right.
- I find you very naive.
- Do you?
You must be ignorant if not naive,
you believe all that I say?
Believe what?
I don't want to cheat you anymore.
I'm a taxi driver indeed.
Hong is not from La Salle,
he only studies in the college nearby.
We've been living here.
We're poor people,
I mustn't blame Hong for this.
He boasts just cheer you up.
I know he loves you very much.
I don't know
what you rich girls have in mind.
But if you only want to play with him,
I beg you to spare him, he can't
take this kind of disappointment.
What are you talking about?
Nothing, the Arab Prince Wasabie says
he wants to sell oil-wells.
Right, Wasabie?
He always cheats in business deals.
- Don't do business with him in future.
- OK.
I remember that Mr. Misubishi
mentioned about the car...
...that he won't sell it
for less than $3 million.
I remember now, my classmates
wanted to borrow our yacht, can they?
OK, don't lend it, just give it to him.
Why?
- Have you ever cheated me?
- Cheat what?
I mean it.
I'm indeed not a rich guy,
I don't study in La Salle either.
Why must you lie to me?
I was going to tell you earlier.
I was afraid that you'll leave me
if I told you the truth.
I will.
If I didn't do this,
I'm afraid I can't get you.
Don't leave me.
You mustn't cheat me anymore.
Never will I cheat you again.
I know many La Salle students,
none have heard of a Hong.
Did he really studying in La Salle?
I can tell you,
but you mustn't tell my mother.
No, I must tell her.
Don't tell her.
No, I must tell...
Then I'm not going to tell you.
It means he's not from La Salle.
Chris
How are you, Aunt?
You want to invite me to tea?
Aunt, I've something to tell you.
But I don't know how to start.
Just go ahead, why hesitate?
- Aunt, you know I pamper Stephenie a lot
- Yes.
I treat her like my sister,
I don't want her to be cheated.
Go ahead.
Have you had enough?
It's aerated, pour slowly.
Angie, Stephenie's mother
is boss of the cosmetic company.
She's here for tea
with a guy called Chris.
That Chris kept saying bad remarks
about Stephenie's boyfriend...
...saying he lies that
he's from La Salle and is a rich guy...
...and also he tries to cheat Stephenie
for money and sex, aren't you worried?
Shit, Angie told me that bastard Chris...
...called up Tap's mother,
and said Hong is not from La Salle.
Say something, OK?
Do you know Tap told me
all of this two hours ago?
Don't you remember we're both in love?
I think I'm bit loss!
No, don't worry, we have a solution.
What solution?
Dad.
I've joined an opera group
at the community centre,
I've learned how to play act.
It's time for me to perform.
Will you really help me out?
I haven't any sentiment for this school.
I've been your buddy for decades.
It's my last day here as I'm emigrating
to New Zealand day after tomorrow.
So I must help you out this time.
Still taking my $5,000
and you're my buddy? Mind your greed.
- Hello.
Excuse me,
are you Stephenie Wong's mother?
Yes, I am, who are you?
I'm Father Ng of La Salle College.
I discovered your daughter is in love
with our student Shum Chi Hong.
You know this...
Our school rules
forbid students to have love affairs.
As this will affect their studies.
I agree with you.
I'll ask my daughter
to concentrate in school.
I'll discourage her from love affairs.
No, I don't think this is a solution.
Sometimes if the two
can help each other...
...a little love affair
will do them good.
Mrs. Wong, if we have spare time...
...why don't we meet
and talk more about it?
When will you be free?
OK, I'll see you at the college
at 3:00 p.m. today.
OK today, this afternoon.
Let's meet at 3:00 p.m.
Our first plan is a success.
- Good!
- Yeah!
Hey, what's the name of that "Old Bag"?
Don't ever call her "Old Bag".
But she is an "Old Bag".
She's Tina.
Tina? God!
How are you? Are you Stephenie's mother?
Yes.
Shum Chi Hong
is a very hard-working student.
He has been awarded "Competent Youth",
but he's humble,
he never tells others about this.
He doesn't give me a good impression.
Are we talking about the same guy?
Yes, but you misunderstood him.
Did I?
You don't believe me? Let me show you.
OK.
God bless you.
Watch out,
there's a curb in front, brake now.
Quiet.
Sir.
Quiet, don't shout.
Good morning, father.
Good morning, class!
All are God's children.
Father.
Oh my son.
My father.
Come, come.
Yes.
Go on with the lesson.
Let's not affect their lesson.
There's a stall nearby, let's have tea.
Right, we can eat pork bun.
Sure...
How long do you both plan to cheat me?
What... Cheat?...
What is your relation with him?
I'm his father.
Did you really study here?
Right...
- Hi! Tina Wong.
- Hi!
You're father here?
Yes...
What's the name of this sister
She's... called Sister.
She is Sister Mary
She's Sister Ivy indeed.
Aunt, sorry,
we didn't mean to play a joke on you.
We act this way because we're afraid
you'll know we're not from La Salle.
I didn't mean to reveal your secret.
But now I know my daughter's boyfriend
is not honest.
What? My son is not honest?
Wait, madam, do you mean your daughter
is pregnant and can't face others?
Like father like son, you're both sly.
I never expected
Stephenie's judgement to be so poor.
How can she get along with these guys?
I must teach her a lesson.
Aunt, I'm not from La Salle,
I'm not from a rich family.
You can look down on me,
but you mustn't say this to my father.
Good boy.
You think you're special
because you're rich?
What did you say?
Apologize to my mother at once.
Sorry. Now I've said it, so now
you must apologize to my father too.
I didn't do anything wrong,
why must I apologize?
Madam, you must be fair.
Just a "sorry"
and we can all forget about it.
It doesn't make sense, let's go.
My ball, please.
It's bad.
Mom, are you alright?
Sorry, I didn't mean that.
Are you alright, Old Bag?
What?
Hong, take the shortcut, come on.
You know I love my mother the most,
it's wrong for you to insult her.
I've been doing all this for your sake.
What are you laughing?
Sorry, I recall the name "Old Bag",
sorry again.
You're always like this,
you never study hard when I ask you.
When I speak seriously to you,
you just laugh.
You're not serious at all.
When I'm laughing...
how do you know that I'm not serious?
I can sense that you're not serious.
I'm always like this.
I just don't like your behaviour.
I can't change.
Don't change then.
Start driving.
They've reported to the police,
let's go.
You're useless, no one can see you here.
Look, you stink,
even flies are coming to smell you.
Get up at once.
Take a bath and I'll take you to dinner.
Go take a bath, now.
Dad, don't touch brother.
Take a bath, why are you pretending?
You got dumped?
Your whole body stinks.
What a tragedy!
The Tang family is quarrelling again.
Come back, I'll give you a house.
What do you mean by this?
You're so love-sick, I'll shave your
head then you can be a love-sick monk.
Asshole! Men can always
get a wife anytime.
Look at how ridiculous you are now!
Teach him a lesson,
no need to use force.
You're not human,
I'd better castrate you.
Quick someone report to the police.
Look, if I had known,
I wouldn't have helped you seduce girls.
You'd better become a gay,
like your sister.
Brother, you told Dad? What's
the big deal that you're love sick?
I haven't told Dad anything.
If you hadn't, Dad's stupid,
how did he guess it?
I know everything, Mimi told me that.
Why did you betray me?
You promised you'd keep it a secret.
And you told others? Do you've manners,
how can you teach your children?
Why not?
If I've no manners, then I would have
chop your head off, and throw it out.
I'd lock your door and burn your place.
Pay back $300 before you burn my place,
pay me back now.
You mean you're breaking off with me?
Wait.
I'll pay back the $45 I owe you,
Hong, let's go.
Why are you shouting?
You're all nuts.
I don't know what I have done wrong.
My son is girlish,
and my daughter a lesbian.
You gave birth to a lesbian.
I'm going to play mahjong,
don't care whether you come back or not.
Hello
- This is for you.
- Thanks.
Sorry, I didn't realise
I'd stir up so much trouble.
Forget it, it's not your fault.
Let's skip school
since we're so depressed.
Ask your mother to give you money
for a world tour.
No, mom will die if I ask her.
Right, don't think about it anymore.
You'd better study hard,
and take the exams.
I'm not thinking about it anymore.
Stop crying, please.
I can comfort you if you need help.
I don't know why Hong loves you,
you're such a mess.
Concentrate and study,
or I'll bully you.
Come and play, we need one more player.
I'll play mahjong with Mrs. Tang.
Brother, have a cup of coffee
to refresh yourself.
I'll have a coffee and a cake.
No... I don't want anything.
What do you want?
I know I'm poor,
but we're honest people.
I'm stupid, and naive,
but I'm a good guy.
What do you mean
by telling me all of this?
Like father like son.
Hong is a good son,
he's obedient, a real good guy.
I do hope you'll let Tap and Hong
keep their friendship.
I've never stopped Stephenie
from seeing your son.
But Stephenie
doesn't want to see him anymore.
Stephenie is studying for A Level exams,
she must concentrate.
If you son really loves Stephenie...
...he'd better leave her alone.
I can't help.
I find you more and more elegant.
You're so different,
even when drinking coffee.
Then... we can become friends?
We can go out for a movie or a dinner...
I don't think so.
You don't need tell me so honestly.
Sir, your cake.
What? Didn't I cancel the order?
I cancelled your order of coffee
- Smart!
- Good.
Stephenie, I want to see.
Where is her?
Stephenie is at her mother's
birthday party.
Thank you.
Why you're so quiet,
not smiled all night.
Laugh out loud,
I've practised a long time.
Why has my cigarette disappeared?
I can't tell it. It's a secret.
Why... you're hiding it here?
You come to disturb Tap again?
Where is she?
Why are you here again?
She'll cry when she sees you.
I want you to show your maturity today.
It's my birthday,
please don't stir up trouble here.
Tap.
You'd better go outside.
If Stephenie wants to see you,
she'll come out.
There are some things you can't help it.
What did you tell him?
I know how you feel now.
First love is never easy... to anyone.
It's hard to take a balance
between judgement and sentiment.
Think about yourself
whether you'll see him or not.
Tap.
Why did you come so late to see me?
I promise myself I must study well.
I've achieved flying colours
in my exam this time.
Congratulations.
What about you?
I didn't study well because of you.
I'm going to England tomorrow.
You're going to England tomorrow?
Can't you stay here?
I've promised mother, I must go.
Which flight?
At 9:30 a.m.
Only 12 hours from now on.
Stephenie!
Come and cut the cake with me.
Happy Birthday Aunt, Happy Birthday.
Thank you...
You're so pretty tonight.
Let me kiss you again.
Aunt, your glasses looks very sexy,
long, square and thin.
What are you doing?
Aunt, never mind them.
Where are we going now?
You haven't eaten, let's go and eat.
What are you laughing at?
Mom.
I... I promise I'll come back
for the flight tomorrow.
Sorry...
Happy Birthday.
Do you remember how we met?
Why, I don't remember.
Wow, you father has blisters...
Isn't this the song?
You're not singing a song.
I recall now.
Since you left...
Will you forget me soon...
after being far away?
No, will you?
Tell me, who will you miss the most?
My mother.
I know my mother is lonely.
And now... I'm leaving her.
You're the culprit.
If you hadn't disturb my studies,
I wouldn't be going to England.
Promise me...
If I marry, its with my mother,
you must accept her.
OK, I'll start my "savings" tonight.
I'll support one wife
and a mother-in-law.
I mean it.
I'm most happy... when my parents
took me to amusement park.
I remember... my dress was wet
after riding the roller coaster.
You pee?
No, my father did.
You mean it?
Horrible, isn't it?
He pee? He's a grown up.
When did you last go to amusement park?
I don't remember.
Let's go there now.
It's closed at this hour.
Come on... I'll ask them open it.
Can you?
You two are nuts.
You should be making love madly
in motels on this last night together.
What did you come to amusement park for?
Bastard, why are calling me up so late?
Come and help me.
My boss will fire me
if he learns about this.
I'll cancel your debts.
You're nuts.
You should be making love madly
in motels on this last night together.
What did you come to amusement park for?
Sorry to bother you, please help me.
Uncle, please.
I'll treat you to tea.
No thanks, tea will mean
I'll have to pee all day.
- Just a few rides and leave.
- Sure...
Sit still, ready...
One, two, three!
What's going on?
Shit... I'm going to lose my job.
You've been working here for so long,
can't you do something?
Dad... sorry.
Stupid boy, you haven't accompany
your Dad for a long time.
Haven't I?
Very warm.
I don't long for daylight.
You're back.
Mom...
Sorry.
Time for boarding, say your last words.
Let's count to three and say "goodbye".
If we say good-bye here
it means we'll meet here again.
One.
Two.
Three!
How to say it and mean "good-bye"?
This way.
Let's count to three.
We then turn around and go.
If not, we'll become lizards.
One.
Two.
Three.
Lizard.
Mrs. Lizard.
Bye-bye.
Move.
They got married one year later.
My mom made the right decision.
My step-father is great too.
I have four days off and came back to HK
for my mom's wedding.
Stand close... let's take photo...
Relatives and friends of the groom
stand that way.
Relatives and friends of the bride,
say "cheese".
Employees of the groom's company
go that way.
One, two, three, OK...
It's done, who hasn't taken a photo yet?
Yes, not yet.
My daughter.
Mom, you're very pretty.
You must be good to my mother.
I will...
You must be treat my daughter well.
Sure... I will...
Two.
Three.
Who are you?
Her boyfriend.
Her boyfriend?
I'm her boyfriend indeed.
I'm her boyfriend.
Her boyfriend?
Where're you going?
You're her boyfriend?
That fatty is from La Salle too?
Oh no...
I'm happy to see my mom
believing in love again.
But if he was here...
I think I'd be happier.
Sorry, I'm late.
What time is it now? You're late again?
My father's car broke down on the way.
I don't care, don't touch me.
Let's take a photo with the bride.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Don't you want to take photo with Aunt?
What is it?
Kid.
I don't care about you,
go away, don't follow me.
Sorry.
Damn you.
- Don't run, please.
- No way.
Go away.
Unless you buy me a super teddy-bear,
it's a deal.