BRAKE
What is this?
Oh come on. Morgan
Oh Jesus, Morgan
Morgan?
Please, man
You're taking this too far.
Okay?
You're making it worse.
I have your money
What do you think I'm
doing in New York?
I swear to you I came here
to settle up with you
Fuck. Please, man
Just talk to me
Can you hear me?
Okay. Alright, just calm
down and just breathe
Breathe
Help! Please, is anybody there?
Please, help me. Is anybody out there?
Somebody, anybody. Please
- I can hear you, can you hear me?
- What the hell is this?
I'm trapped, I can't move. - Fuck
I don't know who's doing this or
I don't know who you are doucebag...
Anybody can hear me?
Hold on
How long I've been here or where I am.
I just want to get out
- Something's here hold on
- What you want
because I didn't do anything
Help me, please, just
let me out of here
Please, somebody, anybody
Hello, can you hear me?
- Yes, yes, I can hear you
- Who is this?
Who are you?
I mean why are you doing this to me?
What do you want? I haven't
Alright. Take it easy.
Tell me your name
Henry, Henry Shaw.
Who the hell is this?
Okay, Henry. Do you have any
idea ​​where you are?
No, I have no idea
it's dark place, I can't see a thing
I can't sit up, there's barely
enough room to move around
I can't breatheee okay
I'm having trouble breatheeing
and I hurt my hand trying to get out.
I think I might've broken it
Are the walls smooth?
Yes, there's like a glass okay
and they're these numbers
Please, stop asking me all
these questions just let me out
- A countdown?
- Yes, they're counting down
- What do it mean? Am I going to die?
- Just
- Is this some kind of a
- Stop. Just read me your numbers
Okay. Fine. fine. 2:22 - 2:21 - 2:20
God. Jesus Christ. Is this it?
You got to get me out of here
Wish I could pal
Looks like me and you
are in the same boat
What? You're trap too?
What is this?
Pitch black. Tight space. Numbers here
We're going to die, are we?
Because the number is still going down
Don't think about that now. Alright?
We need to try and relax.
I going to get you out of there
Relax? What, are kidding me?
You're trap too.
How the hell are you
going to help me?
I need information to help us both
Talk to me, Henry
Are you a gambler?
No, I do not know. Yes, a little
sometimes, maybe Atlantic City
I played some Keno
What does it have to do with anything?
Keno huh?
At least lose  your
shirt on a real man game. Jesus
Oh okay, I'm sorry,
What is the real men game?
Cards, Henry
Real men screws up playing cards
and is that what you
think this is about?
a gambling debts?
Listen, I don't what
kind of trouble you in
but I don't owe anyone anything. Okay?
Do you know a man named
Detrick Morgan?
Who? No, no, no, look look
I done playing 20 questions
We running out of time here.
This is bullshit
Come on, man. The name, Detrick Morgan
You ever heard that name before?
Just think hard. Okay
this is important
No, no, no I don't anyone
by that name. I'm positive
Listen, you got to figured
this out. Okay?
I don't know how much longer
I can last in here, do you hear me?
Just try and relax, Henry
This radio is old, it's ancient
It's frequency can't travel very far
We got to be close together
Okay.
so then why is this happening?
Shh. Hold on.
I think I could hear something
- What is it? What did you hear?
- Shut up
Help! Help! Somebody
Anybody if you can hear me. I'm trap
Okay. Let me figure this out
good, good. Let's go
Oh shit
Henry, Henry,
what's going on in there?
I'm moving. What's the hell?
Are you inside the trunk of a car?
Because I am
Yeah, I think so, I'm in a car too
Ah man this can't be happening
Please, this can't be
Listen to me. Okay?
Do you remember anything?
Do you remember anything about
where you were before you woke up?
I was in New York
Manhattan, I was at a Clarion Hotel
on Park Avenue, that where you were?
Wait. Were you in New York?
I can't tell you that right now
Okay. Whoever doing this to me
wants us to communicating
I got to watch what I say
I can't explain it to you
but I need to know what are
you doing in New York?
It was a business trip
Okay, that's great
I get that, what kind of business?
You a broker? Real estate? Lawyer?
Just business
Alright, stop stone walling me man...
We're on the same team here
Okay, listen I work for
the state department
I'm a foreign service officer
sign in the diplomatic
in the White House office center
Fuck me. Henry?
Slow it down. Asshole
Henry?
Henry, are you stopped?
- Yes
- Okay
Turn the radio off for ten seconds
yell as loud as you can. I want to
see if I could hear you
That's a good idea, okay. Here goes
Come on
Do you yelled?
Yeah, you didn't hear me?
Did you hear me?
Oh my God. Oh my God, what is this?
The lights just turned on
Its a vault I'm in a
god damn plastic box
It seems so bright I can
see wires and tubes
There seems to be no way
out of here
What is this?
Somebody fucking with us.
That's what this is
Why?
That what I want to find out
Hold on
You got to be kidding me,
thanks a lot
What the fuck?
"The White House"
Give us the location of Roulette
Jesus
Jeremy?
How do you know my name?
I never gave you my name
No, I've got a piece of
paper and it says the
man in another car has the
answer to the question
It says your name is Jeremy
Listen, Henry
- I can't answer that question
- You can't or you won't?
It doesn't matter I can't say anything
No Jeremy, please
If this will get us out of here
I need you to tell them. Please
I have a family, Jeremy
a wife and two kids, please
I want this to be over
How do I know you are not
the one that put me in here?
How do I know that you're the
one who's driving the fucking car?
If I were driving the car,
you would hear me, won't you?
I didn't put you in there...
and I'm not driving the car
Look I'm stuck in a trunk too, remember?
I'm not the bad guy here, Jeremy
I'm sorry
I can't trust anyone
or anything right now
Jeremy, you have to believe
What the hell is going on?
This wire goes here
Tube goes through there
Oh Jesus
What's this shit for really?
Yes
Okay
Want to fuck with me?
Channel 19. Let give this a try
Hello, hello. Can anybody hear me?
Can anybody read me on this frequency?
If anyone could hear me
please. Please, help me
Come on
Sir, are you okay there?
Who am I talking to?
- You can hear me?
- Barely, you're kinda breaking up
The name's Bob. Who's this?
It's Jeremy, my name Jeremy
You sound a little agitated son,
What seem to be the problem?
Look, this going to sound nuts alright
Somebody lock me in the trunk of a car
I think I'm close to you because
you can read my signal
Okay, hang on a second
I heard some crazy shit before
But you would want
to run that by me again
I'm being held captive inside a trunk
of a car. Alright? I'm serious, man
I need some help here, please
Where are you?
South bound, on the rig
on the I-95
I-95? Okay
Alright. I'm in a car moving. We must've
be heading in the same direction
Do you have any clue,
what kind of a car?
I don't. I don't know what happen here
Have you been drinking?
Because if it was a
joke, it is not funny
No, listen to me
This is not a joke
I swear it on my life,
I'm in real trouble
Okay. Okay
What do you need me to do?
Okay. I need you to blast
your horn three times
That's it. I need to know
how close are you to me
Okay. Alright
- Here it goes
- Good
I can hear you, man
Fucking ace. I hear you alright?
Sounds like you're behind me
you need to speed up and catch up
Copy that, I been out of the fourth
lane now heading your way
Yes. Okay. Alright
What kind of car in front of you? How many?
I'm in something with a large truck
a big cylinder engine
You got to get write down the plate
write down the plates please
I'm driving a truck, son,
I can't write down shit
Okay. What do you see?
What's on the road?
Directly in front of me,
I got a red Hyundai
I see a green SAP
No, no
Wait a minute
I hear something
I hear a Harley, man
I hear a bike right on top of us
Do you see anything like that?
Yeah, yes, there it is
About a 100 yards ahead
Get to that bike. That's us man
Come on, hurry up
speed the fuck up, please
Sounds like we're taking an exit man
They're trying to lose you, please
I'm trying kid, I'm trying
- Can you hear me? Hello?
- Hello?
Bob, What's up?
You're getting closer?
- Hello?
- Bob?
Are you there?
Ah come on. Please hear me man. Bob
Bob
Stop it now!
- Hello?
Jeremy?
Is that you?
Molly? Molly
You got to be kidding
me and now call me?
- I don't have time for this
- Molly
I going to be late for work
I'm hanging up. Goodbye, Jeremy
No, no, no
don't hang up, please
Look, I'm in trunk of a car okay
I'm trap, I'm in a box
I need your help
Why am I not surprise me,
it's the first time we
talk in three months
Are you drunk dial me?
No, I'm not 'm not drunk.
I swear to you, Okay?
Somebody dialed your number.
I'm in this fucking box
You're on a speaker phone okay
Why do I keep getting caught
up in your shit, Jeremy?
this is right where we left off
- The gambling, more gambling
- No, this is not Morgan
trust me he will not go this far
Listen to me, please
Do you remember the number?
Remember the number that I gave you
in case of an emergency?
- What number? Ben cell number?
- Yes
Yes. You need to find him
you need to find him
Okay. I don't know
what I'm looking for
What does it start with?
I don't the number by hard.
It was programmed into my phone
Where is your phone,
Jeremy, what's going on?
That's what I'm
trying to figure out okay
Here's the deal, find the number,
call Ben please
Tell him what happened
to me, and tell them,
they need to secure POTUS
In those words, exactly
Can you do that for me, please?
Yeah, yeah,
Okay, where is it?
My computer, the desk the top
drawer in the folder
I emptied the desk drawers when
you moved out. I don't know, Jeremy
Look I don't know how much time I have
Please, just find the number
Okay
Molly, did you get it?
Molly?
Molly, where are you?
Come on, babe
- There's someone at my window
- What?
What? No
Oh please, fuck no
No
Molly
Hey! Let me out of here
You better not fucking touch her
You got to fucking calm down
Do you have your attention now?
- This can all be over very quickly
- Fuck you
- Or we can leave you in there
- Okay
Yeah, I'm here
you want to talk, I'm listening
Tell us what we want to know
So you guys sending me postcards
You know what we want
Yes, I may know what you want
Yes, sure
I can't really think in here
I can't even breatheee
I got an idea why don't pull
over and we make a deal
You want information and
I want out of here, okay?
Lets pull over and deal
You're not in controls
of the situation, I am
Now, tell us what
we want to know or
Molly suffers with the
lack of your cooperation
No, no, no
No, listen to me. Okay
You don't want to do this, alright?
You want to stop right now and
I will forget the whole thing
I want to location of Roulette
Look just pull over the car
and I talk to you. Alright?
I said lets communicate. Please
Hello?
Fuck!
Alright. Alright
Okay
Jesus Christ
You got to be fucking kidding me
Help! Stop! Please
Shit
Somebody out there?
Help Somebody!
- Jeremy, are you okay?
- Henry
They put bees in my trunk man
I know, they told what
they're going to do to you
They said that I'm next
I need help
I'm going to go in an
anaphylactic shock
If I'm not shot in 2 minutes, I'm done
Jeremy, I can help.
I think I know the answer
to question they asked you
What are you talking about?
You don't know anything
They have my wife, Jeremy
They have my kids
Give them nothing.
There's nothing to give
How the fuck?
Center, 10-9
38 - 25
3845 - 14
- Center-98
- 98-Center, go ahead
Center we contacted the RP
and ask for Tina. She still have
no visuals on the suspects
Area checked
north and south to the alley
10-4, 98. stand by
10-98 disregard, we have visuals
five males
south bound from the
alley on foot. Suspect...
Hey man let go
Let go of my arm
Fuck
What is this?
- You should say thank you
- What?
We saved your life, you're welcome
Why give me the shot?
Why keep me alive?
Why all of this?
Agent Raines
Special Agent Jeremy Raines
Current assignment
a National Security Adviser
connection detail
nice job
I don't know what you're
talking about man?
Don't play dumb. We know who you are
We know who you work for
We couldn't afford lose you
You are a valuable asset Jeremy
If you know me so well you know
I'm not going to tell you anything
No, Agent Raines you will give
us the location of Roulette
How much you suffered before that..
Look man I can't help you, alright?
I don't know what you're talking about
If you want to play roulette
you go to Vegas, right?
Try  Atlantic City, if you don't like
to fly. I don't know what to tell you
I'm glad you still have
your sense of humor
but I'm on a schedule Agent Raines
and very soon, my patient will run out
God damn it
Fuck
Henry, are you still with me?
Jeremy, Is that you?
I thought you're gone
No, I'm still here
They gave me a shot.
They save my life
Why would they do that?
I do not understand
Look
if we going to find out
what's going on here
I want to know
everything you know
All I know is that this is something
to do about Roulette
What do you know about that?
I know its an underground bunker with
the President and Vice President
and National Security Adviser are all
taken if there ever were
an attack on Washington
after 9/11 they built
a series of bunkers
Go to the bunkers changes
randomly without notices
Only a hand full of people ever know
which one of this on an any given day
That's why they call them Roulette
How do you know that?
I told you earlier I'm with the
State Department Jeremy
- No, you never mention that to me
- Yes, I did
I assigned the National Security
Council at the center of operations
I worked in the White House
I was in New York for a briefing
at the United Nations
you never mention
that to me before man
Yeah, I tried to tell you earlier but you cut me off
You didn't trust anything
I said, remember?
Please Jeremy. Look I'm just
Okay
Alright, is Dave Lau is still the
senior NSA rep in the Ops Center?
What? You're quizzing me?
Brian Nolan replaced him in the
center of operations two years ago
Dave Lau went to the Pentagon,
the Minister of Defense office
Okay, you're working in
the operations center
I want to know what painting
hanging on in the conference room
That's a trick question
There are no paintings there
Jeremy, please. Come on
I'm just a State Department Attaché
I'm not cut out for this
I just trying to stay alive
and keep my family safe
stop talking
best thing you can is be quiet
They know where my family lives
Do you think that I'm going to lay
here and fucking give up? No way
Look I'm not going to do that
Yes you are.
Because that is your duty
Your duty is to keep your mouth shut
When you joined the State,
you took an oath
Don't forget that
Do you have any kids, Jeremy?
No. No I don't... we are
Me and my wife got
separated three months ago
We were just about to try
it's definitely in the card
- I'm sorry
- Yeah, me too
I was just trying to make
things right between us
That's why I was in New York.
That's why I went there
to set things straight with this
guy who I owed money to
How many kids you got, Henry?
I have two, 7 and 9, boys
and are we supposed to go out on
vacation in after few
weeks to Disney World
the boys love rock
and roll roller-coaster
I can't stand roller-coasters
but right now
Right now all I think about is
getting out of here in one piece
So I can ride roller-coaster
with them, you understand?
Yeah
I hope you get that chance,
I really do
Do you hear sirens?
Yeah, sounds like
they just passed me
- They passed you?
- Yeah
Pull over with the break
Damn it, I told you to stay down
on speed limits, we're screwed
Just relax and stay cool,
as long as he stay quiet back there
You so much as sneeze
I cut your wife's head off
and mail it to her parents
What are you doing?
You suppose to stop
You make this problem now fix this
Come on, think
Act normal. Let me do the talking
We just get  a ticket
and we'll be out of here
Shut up, here he comes
- You gentlemen in a hurry?
- I'm real sorry, officer
We're late for a meeting and
I wasn't paying attention
- Is this your car?
- Yes, Sir. It is
Here's my driver's license
and registration
Hang tight okay?
Remember, not a fucking
sound or she dies
Come on, come on
It's your luck day, take it
a little slower next time
- It's my lucky day.
- Thank you, officer
- I'm in here
- What the?
You two put your hand
where I can see them
Now! Now!
Run for it
This 5-90, I need back up now
Officer down! Officer down!
God damn it
Oh shit
Okay, Okay
Okay
Fuck
Come on fucker
Come on
I got it
Incoming Call
Restricted
Marco. Marco, where are you?
I need an answer, an update.
Give me an answer
Marco can't come to the
phone right now
Who is this?
Who the fuck is this?
Agent Raines
I don't how you got a hold on a
phone but I'm glad you could join us
Molly send you her love
Fuck
Come on
Come on, answer
Hi, Molly. Can't get into
this phone right now
Leave a message and I'll you back
Molly. Molly, I got a phone back here
Please, call me at this number
as soon as you can
Fuck
- You been asked to hold
- Wait. Wait I'm
Oh shit
You have Reached the U.S.
Secret Service
Fuck
- Okay
- 911
- 911, what is your emergency?
- Hello, listen to me carefully
My name is Jeremy Raines
I'm a special agent for United
State Secret Service
I'm being held captive in a car.
I need help
Okay, Jeremy. Just stay calm.
Where are you calling from?
Listen, lady I just told you I
calling from inside the trunk of a car
Okay, Sir. I understand, I'm going to
help you. Are you injured?
It's doesn’t matter right now, look
my phone is about to die
I my called office several times
I can't reach them
Please, reach the Secret Service
and tell them what's happening
Sir, do you know where you were
when you were put in the trunk?
I was in New York city, I was
coming out of a restaurant
It was night, it's late
that it, that's all I remember
- Did you say New York city, Sir?
- Yes, why?
This is The Baltimore
Emergency Communication Center
you're calling from
inside our response zone
Baltimore?
Well, look. you got to find me
find out where I am please now
- Right now
- Sir, I need you to try and stay calm
Can you tell me what kind
of phone are calling on?
It's an LG, it's old.
It's an old flip phone
Sir if your phone GPS
capability has been disabled
We going to have to
triangulate your location
through the cell towers to
pin point your location
How close can you get?
Depend on the signal
strength of 3 to 6 miles radius
Three to six miles?
I could be in fucking
Kansas for all as we know
Sir, We going to
do the best we can
Just stay on the line with me,
and I'll be right back
Okay
Fuck
Hello? Can anybody hear me?
Hello
Where's your owner buddy?
Who you with huh?
Sir? Sir, are you alright?
Jeremy, are you still with me?
Hold on
- Hold on one second, are you with me?
- Jeremy?
- Hold on, hold on
- Holding, sir
One second
- Okay
- Jeremy?
I'm in the alley way, okay?
I can see some abandoned buildings
- How can you see that?
- I can see through a bullet hole
Did you say a bullet hole?
We got pull over by the
police, it was a shootout
Are you injured? Are you in
need of medical attention?
Well I lost a lot of blood but I
tied it off, it should be alright
Do you see an
emergency trunk latches?
Or anyway you might able to
escape into the back seat?
Yes, I see it. I see it.
You don't understand, I'm in
a box okay. I can't get to it
Are exactly sure?
Are you sure?
Is this exactly accurate?
Great! Great! Okay, great
Jeremy, I have very good news
we triangulated your position
Where am I?
You're in Severn Maryland
I'm sending up a police
unit to the general area
Hey
- Do you say Severn? Severn Maryland?
- Yes. Yes, that's correct
Look, listen to me
I need you to call Anne Orandl
with the County Police Department
I need units at
22, Green Valley lane
Do you hear that?
Twenty-two Green Valley lane
- Now
- Sir, what is at that address?
My wife
I think who ever doing
this to me holding her
Look, you have my number
- You get that done. Call me back
- Sir, don't hang up. I need...
Here boy
Hey get out of that trash
Come here
- Help me, sir
- Come on buddy
Sir! You in the robe
Sir!
Doggie, doggie. Come here
I'm in trunk of a car
Please help me
Yeah, closer straight ahead
Come here, boy
Yeah, man. I see you
What the fuck are you doing in there?
I been held hostage I have been
here for hours, please
Get me out of here alright, there
got to be a latch on the front seat
- Hey is this kind of a  joke man?
- No, man. It's not
I'll give some money, I'll
give you what ever you need.
Just open this
fucking trunk please
Okay. Okay. Hang on
I don't need money, I'll get you out
Oh God, thank you
What the hell man? There's a guy pass
out here back here, what's the deal?
Yeah man he's dead.
They shot him
What're you talking about man?
I don't know if they going to be
cool if I let you out. This is fuck up
Forget it man. Alright
- Yes baby
- Right, hang on
Open it
- Open it buddy
- Alright
No! Fuck!
Get me out of here
Oh fuck
Come on, man
Come on
What are you doing?
Oh Jesus
Where's the phone?
- Hello
- Jeremy?
Hey. Did you get to the house?
What happened? Tell me
We sent a unit to the address
you gave me, sir
I'm sorry but there
wasn't anyone there
Well I need they to check again
Just send them back, and
look again. You hear me? Check again
They searched the entire
property sir. She wasn't there
Look, is there something
you're not telling me?
Did they find something?
They did, didn't they?
Just fucking tell me honey please
Sir, We're doing everything we can
for you and your wife
Tell me what they fucking found
a note on the door way sir
It said you get her in one
piece if you cooperate
Jeremy, We dispatched unit to your
area, they're checking the cars
we're going to locate you
I'm already moving
I'm already gone
Jeremy?
Yeah, I'm here
The numbers are back
Yeah, I know. Mine too
They timing everything here man
This is complex plan of work
We got derailed a bit when we got
pull over by the cops but
I'm moving again
I'm running out of time, Jeremy
There's something going
to happen soon, I feel it
What do you mean?
What're you talking about?
The number they started at 15,
15 minutes
Read me your numbers to me
11:34 - 11:33 - 11:32
11:31 - 11:30
The President was arriving
at Washington this morning
I know, I know, Air Force One was
touched down in Andrews, at 9:40 am
I'm sure of that time,
because I will join
national security
adviser this morning
to brief the President prior his
speech on EU expansion
10:07 AM
It's a little after 10 now
How do you know that?
I got a phone in here now
Don't ask me how
Jeremy  I'm begging you. Please.
You got to call my wife
I want to know she and
my boys are okay
I don't know what's going
to happen to me, please
You got to do this for me
please, Jeremy
Come on, man
I'll do this for you
What's the number?
757 - 765 - 4321
75 - 77 - 65 - 4321
Tell them I love them, hurry
I got it. I'll get back to you
You Special Agent Ben Reynolds
U.S. Secret Service
Recruitment Division
What the fuck?
You reach Special Agent Dale Carter
US Secret Service of America
Fuck
Where is everybody?
What is going on?
You may have heard already
they're unconfirmed reports
explosion from inside the facility
With me is Amanda Aesmond
A freshman at Princeton
Community College
She stopped to get gas on the way
to school this morning when
explosion occurred.
Amanda, what can you tell us?
I was just standing over
there filling my car
when all of the sudden I heard this
2 big boom right near the road
I thought it was an
earthquake of something
When I looked over it was a smoke cloud
just like they're now
Those people are like a ghost,
they disappeared
I didn't know what's going on but
I knew that it's not good
Thank you, Amanda
Right now, a huge cloud of smoke still
cover the road entrance
road around Andrews are grid lock
Norman. Back to you in the studio
and we end up bringing to you
right now on our breaking news
All of this just unfolded
Associated Press and a local source
confirming now 2
separate explosions outside CIA HQ
in the Langley suburb of McLean
2 Blasts occurring within just
minutes of each other
One explosion at the National
Highway Testing Center
which adjoined CIA HQ
Then a second larger explosion
has collapse apparently of
Portion of George Washington
Memorial Highway
which runs directly
along CIA property lines
There are unconfirmed reports at this
moment, that this were car bombing
but we don't want
to speculate just yet
because of course the
situations isn't very clear
To get more information, by the minute
So we stay on top until
we have more information
Incoming units, be advised..
every floor of the west
parking structure has falls
additional paramedics units
10-76
Center we got a 10-79
If you can give us a
bomb squad units
Controls, multiple casualties
Okay, come on
Oh please. Pick up man
Pick up
- Agent Reynolds
- Ben, Ben. It's Jeremy Raines man
- Jeremy
- What is the hell is going on?
I called every extension at the
office, I'm not getting anybody
Jeremy, you're alive
Where are you?
What? What? What do you know Ben?
Please, don't tell me you
inside the trunk of a car
How do you know that?
You're not the only one
Seven others of the four Secret Service
Two FBIs even the Deputy
Chief of Staff, maybe more
We had several 911 calls, we're
trying to locate their position now
One just detonated outside of Langley
Jeremy, I have to go. We're last ones
in the building, we're evacuating
We could hit next
Whoa
Detonated?
What're you talking about?
Bombs, car bombs
and you're lying inside one
I'm sorry, Jeremy. I have to go
I call you back at this number
Hey, Ben I need your cell
Ben. I need your cell.
Hello?
Jeremy
Molly?
Oh my God I'm in a trunk of a car
- it's moving
- What?
- I can't get out
- What? No, no, no, no. Fuck
I'm so scared
Tell me where you are.
What's going on?
I'm in a car, and it's moving
and don't know what to do
- Alright. Just stay with me, alright
- Okay
I'm here, I'm here. Let think with
each other for a minute, okay?
Okay
Did you see who put you in the car?
I don't know. It's happen so fast
Okay, alright. I need you to stay calm
alright babe? We need to think
Stay calm, just try to relax, okay?
Why is this happening to us?
What do they want?
This all part of the terrorist attack
They want information
about The President Bunker
I got the information
they're trying to get out of it
Oh my God this can't be happening
- Jeremy
- Listen to me, Molly
- Molly, can you hear me
- Yes
- Jeremy, I'm so scared
- I know, I know
I'm going to get you out of there I'm
going to get you out in one piece.
I promise you
- You believe me?
- Yes
Listen, there's something
I want to tell you
Something I been meaning
to tell you for a long time
I'm sorry
For anything I did with Morgan
for not being trusting
and for let you down honey
I'm sorry
Why didn't you...
- Hello? Molly? Molly?
- Jeremy
Molly?
- Jeremy?
- Hello?
Please. Hello?
Oh fuck
What're doing to me?
Fucking damn crazy
Oh gods damn please,
please. Please help us
Jeremy?
Jeremy, are you still there?
Come on, Jeremy. Please
answer me if you still there
Jeremy?
I'm still here
Do called my family?
What happened to them?
Are they alright?
I haven't call them, Henry
Jeremy, please. Come on
I'm begging you, please
Please, damn it, you got to call them
I need to know that they're okay
- I don't have much time
- I'm calling now
Thank you, thank you
757 - 765 - 4321
- Who's this?
- I'm looking for a Mrs Shaw
Who the fuck are you?
Just put her on the
god damn phone. Now
- Bring her to me
- No
Shut up
- No, please, don't
- Now you talk
They said they're going
to kill my husband...
they're going to
kill us all, please
Just give them what they want
Now you listen to me
Agent Raines
Give us the location
of Roulette,
or I start executing
these people, one by one
Tell me, now
No
Jeremy
Jeremy, help
Help me, something's happening
What's going on, Henry?
What's wrong?
Jeremy, the trunk is filled
with some kind of liquid.
I don't know what it is
Liquid? What?
Just keep talking to me, Henry
Just don't stop, keep talking to me
Jeremy, it's filling
I-I think I'm gonna drown
There is no time left
on the clock
What's going happen to me, Jeremy?
Are they really going to let me drawn
Jeremy, please.
Give them what they want
This is my life, man
Just tell them.
I'm sorry, Henry
But I can't do that
I'm so sorry
Our Father lord of heaven
hallowed be by name
Thy kingdom come, Thy will be
done on earth as in the sky
Give us today our daily bread
and forgive us for trespasses
We forgive those trespass against us
lead us not into temptation...
but deliver us from evil
Henry?
Henry, are still with me?
Henry.
Fuck!
We are experiencing an
unusually high call volume
- Please try call again later
- Shit
This is not a test
The state and federal
authorities has
activated the Emergency
Broadcast System
Please do not use your telephone
Stay tuned to this station for
news and official information
I repeat this is not a test
we are standing by for an announcement
from The President with
the additional bombing at
Andrews Air Force Base and
other locations around the capital
it is clear, we are under attacked
The President and first family
has been taken to a secure location
Air Force One touch down at
Andrews Air Force Base
just minutes before the
three bombs exploded there
Smoke can now be seen from
miles all around Washington
and more explosions
may be imminent
Please, stay off the
highways and roads
emergency vehicles
need to get through
Stay in your home. We're waiting
for the president address
as soon as that happens
we will go directly to it
Right now though, lets go to
Susan Gibbs in the capital
and Susan, you've got a front row
seat to see what's going on there
as long as....street
- Hello?
- Jeremy, It's Ben. You there?
Ben. Ben, what do you know?
What's going on?
Car bombs are going off
all over the district, if we can't
locate them before they detonate
There got us at a god damn time
Ben they have Molly
They have her in the trunk of a car
I talked to her
- Oh Jesus, Jeremy. I'm sorry
- Listen to me...
They're targeting the President
Well I'm getting this all second hand
but the Vice President safe
I don't know about POTUS
and the first family
my guess is they're already
off to locate them
But I can't get confirmation
I out of the loop when I took over
the loop since I took over recruitment
That's what the terrorists wants
They want everything to go underground
What are you talking about?
How the bombing has there been?
Five confirmed
Andrews, Langley
Toll station on 395,
Reagan National
and now the 14 Street Bridge
that's the mass, the district
is completely paralyze
That's what they're doing
They've taken away all the avenues
They taken away all our sources
They're contain the fucking city
So nobody could get in or out
- Even The President
- He's definitely been secured
Yeah, Roulette
That's why I'm in here
They want to
location of Roulette
That's what they're
trying to get out of me
Jeremy, listen to me
They may already have them
from one of the other captive
We have to warn the protection detail
No, it won't work man.
He's already in the bunker
God Damn it, Jeremy
There's an imminent
threat to the President
His location may have been compromise
I'll go myself just tell me where
Why you asked me that Ben?
You know I can't say anything
They're listening to me
What about Molly? You never
told her anything, do you?
No. No, nothing
she's know nothing
They are using her as
leverage against me
Jeremy, just trust me on this
We're tracking the cell number,
we will find you
.. Listen to me, you find Molly first
You track her phone
and you find her
I'm begging you man,
you do this for me, okay?
Do not even think about coming for me
- You find Molly
- Hey somebody get on that other line
Jeremy, is there anything else you can
tell me? Anything at all?
You're running out of time
We're doing what we can as
fastest we can and now listen
You going to have time reaching me
because we're on the move
But I promise, I call you
back as soon as I can
- Hanging there
- Yeah
Okay, Ben
For those who just joining us now
We are on the line with
someone calling himself Jeremy
That maybe involved in this attack
- Sir, this is Real Time Morning News
- What the fuck?
Are you still with us?
Hang up the god damn phone
Okay, can you confirm what's
taking place? Are you one of them?
I said hang up the god damn phone
You're doing exactly what they want
You're live on the air, sir
I don't give a shit, you
know what you're doing?
So, I want to repeat our
viewers right now
Can you confirm whether
or not you're involved in this?
No. I'm not a terrorist
Then are you a hostage?
We have report
that they're taking
hostages as well
Who's this? What's your name?
This is Jack Stern anchor
for Real Time Morning News
Okay, Jack. Let's have a
little conversation. Alright?
The best thing you can do for everyone
is to disconnect this call. To hang up
because right now you're
doing everything to their plan
They want to install fear and panic
You're doing that. They want paranoia
You helping the bad guys man. So stop
Can you tell us anything?
Anything at all about this attack?
You know what, you're an asshole
you fuck-head
How much do I have to
tell you to turn me off
Stop this please
Had enough?
If you want out, give us Roulette
Go fuck yourself
You know
I'm sorry. Alright?
I'm sorry! I'll tell you, I'll tell
you what you want to know
I'm sorry
Listen, I'm sorry. Alright?
I'm ready to talk
I'm ready to deal
I know you can hear
me in there, alright?
I'm listening
You're an American, man
You're fucking American,
Why you doing this?
Why are you part of this?
Just tell us where Roulette is
or this conversation is over
No, It's not because you
need me, remember?
You need me!
not the other way around
I'm ain't telling you shit
You fucking fail man
You fucking fail miserably
You do all of this, all this
effort and you got nothing
You got nothing out of me
How about that huh?
You fucking idiots
5 minutes huh, 5 minutes till
what motherfucker?
Until you die
Goodbye, Jeremy
No. I said when this is over. I do
You don't turn me off,
I turn you off!
Get it?
Fuck you
Hello? Hello?
- Jeremy
- Oh thank god, Molly
- I was trying to reach you
- Well baby
What is happening?
Where are you now?
Emergency broadcast system in effect
I've been calling you, babe
I can't reach you, are you okay?
Jeremy, I think I know where I am
I think I'm in an ambulance
How do you know that?
It's dark in here, but I can hear the
siren, it sound like it's on top of me
Hold on
- What?
- Something happening
Okay
We're stopping, of traffic
Are you moving, Molly?
Barely
Please, Jeremy.
this time should get us out of here
I promise you, baby
I got the whole team on this
The whole office is looking for you
They're going to find you
I promise you baby. I promise
Okay. Good
- What?
- Molly, talk louder
What happening? Jeremy,
Are you okay?
Holy fuck
you're right.
You're in an ambulance and
I'm in the back of a
fucking police car
- Jeremy?
- Molly, Mol
Jeremy, I can't, I can't,
can you hear me?
Molly
Fuck
Come on, hold on
- Hello?
- Ben?
Hold that and get to her
as fast as possible
Jeremy, listen. We've located Molly
and we are on our the way
Where is she?
- DuPont Circle
- DuPont Circle?
It is a mile from
the White House
I know, I know.
We're working as fast as we can
- Well work faster
- We're trying, it's chaos out here
Road are grid lock, I don't even
know how they're transporting her
Look, she's inside of an ambulance
and I at the back of a police car
That's how they take
us through traffic
Jesus
Guys, she's inside of an ambulance
Let's go, let's go
I'm not moving right now
As far as I know, she's not either
- You're running out of time, man
- How much time?
You got about 3 minutes
You need to clear the area
and keep the roadblocks in
place, don't let any cars through
Not even emergency
vehicles, you hear me?
I'll do what I can
Now, you promise you don't
let any cars through
Look, Jeremy. I can't promise anything
Ben? Ben?!
Ben?
One last chance, Jeremy
Give us the fucking
location of Roulette
I'm not giving you anything
I'm not giving you a god damn thing
Then good luck to you, Agent Raines
I'll tell Molly, good bye for you
You lay one hand on her,
I'm going to fucking kill you
Oh come on
Please pick up
Please. Please pick up
- Jeremy?
- Hello, Molly
- Oh thank god. Are you okay?
- I'm moving again
God fucking roadblocks. I told them
to keep them in place
What roadblocks?
Jeremy, what the hell is going on?
What's happening?
- Listen to me. Do you trust me?
- Jeremy
- Do you trust me?
- Yes, I trust you
Okay
- We're together, baby
- What
We're traveling right
next to each other
What? Do you tell them
what they wanted to know?
No. I can't do that
I took an oath, Molly
Jeremy, Please
I don't want to
die today, please
Just give them what they want.
Please, for me
I never want to do anything
to let you down there
I know that I done things to you
I never wanted to in my life
Jeremy
I hurt you and I'm sorry
I can't think about those things now
I can't do anything about it
but I ask you now to accept me
to accept me for who I am
Of course, of course baby
I accept your
I love you, no matter what
- I love you so much
- ... I love you
I love you so much
Molly
... It filled up. Molly
What the fuck?
- Hello?
- Jeremy, it’s Ben
Ben
Bin, it almost fill up to the top man
I know, it's binary
explosive, liquid bomb
and you're dead either way
but I can save Molly
So tell us what we want to know
We?
You're part of this, Ben?
- It's just business my friend
- It's not business
Give us the location of Roulette
You're a coward, man
You're a fucking traitor
You were my friend
- Enough, give us Roulette
- You were my friend man
Goodbye, Jeremy
Molly
breathe, Jeremy
breathe, take it easy
Jeremy
Whoa. Easy, easy
You're safe now
Jeremy
It's Henry
... I'm Henry. It's Henry
Put the gun down. Okay?
everything is cool. Alright?
Jeremy? Jeremy, I'm here
- Molly
- I'm okay
You did good, real good
Are you kidding, boss?
He did fucking great
This guy is fucking hardcore
Ben, don't fucking moves
Jeremy. Stop! It is over
Stop what? What's over?
What the fuck is this?
It was merely and exercise
and you pass, Jeremy
You pass with flying colours
I don't understand
Stay back
I didn't transfer to
recruitment last year
I'm the protection detail training
coordinator, and you're in Towns ville
This is AOP training ground
You did all this?
You set all this up? Why?
Yeah, we have done a lot of
stress tests since 9/11
It sure beat a hell out of
polygraph don't you think?
and it was important, Jeremy
It was crucial for your transfer
to the presidential detail
starting next month
you're on the asian trip
Congratulations, you're on
your way to the show
- Keep it up, Agent Raines
- Nice work, man
Congratulations
- Nice job
- Awesome
911, what is your emergency?
My outer ego, great great
work Agent Raines
Heading the I-95
Agent Danielle Wade, retired
Great job
I had to, you can know my inner
actress in my high school drama dates
We told her about the
importance of this exercise,
and Molly agreed to help us
- I'm so sorry
- No
This guy has lost a lot of blood,
we got to get this leg patch up
Sorry about that hot weld ammunition
We probably made it way too much
We visit that in the next exercise
Yeah, that'll be a good idea
Meet you at the hospital
for debriefing
Hey Ben
You really had me man
Yeah
That was the idea
Alright, ladies and gentlemen.
Great job, let wrap
it up and go home
Give us the location of Roulette
Hey. Hey, hey, it's okay. I'm here
- Where am I?
- Better be careful
you going to wreck this
thing out of your arm
You're in an ambulance
You pass out, they gave you
a sedative and a new IV
- Hi
- How long have I been out?
- About half an hour
We pull out into Walter
Reed in about 15 minutes
Thank you
How did they get
you involve in all of this?
They paid me
I mean I'm not taking it to
the cleaner or anything, but
I got what we needed
- I paid off Morgan
- Really?
Yeah. Clean slate
You're done with him
You know what? I didn't make
a bet since south Green Park
I know, I know
The bastard said he
lost his best client
Has anybody else knows?
Just Ben and his team
and he knows you're done with it too
He's the on that clear
you for the presidential detail
that ain't better half
of crazy son-of-bitch
What happen is extremely awful huh?
Yeah
Well that's Ben for you
Well at least you get
the rest of the day off
and it's beautiful outside, look
- What's so funny?
- ... Nothing
Really?
The Washington Monument that's it?
That's where it is?
It's not important now
Wait
Will you marry me?
We are married
Marry me again
I've just got a big ass promotion
What are you doing?
What the fuck is this?
What's this for? What're you doing?
- Who're you talking to?
- Did you get that?
Washington Monument.
We got what we need
What are you doing?
You still playing with me?
Come on guys. you're still testing me?
Molly, you're scaring me... Look at me
Where do you want us?
Abort plan C and dismantle the ER
Operation can commence on schedule
- and the subject?
- Molly
He's broken, eliminate him
- What the fuck are you doing?
- Copy that
I trusted you, what are you doing?
What the fuck are you doing?
What the hell is that?
I trusted you
I tried change for you
No, what the fuck is this?
- Fuck you
- Stay down
Sub edited and synced by: PEEAN91