Only a white man would make a fire
for everyone to see.
Maybe there is more than one.
There might be three or four.
They won't be going home.
We have nothing
to show for this trail.
We have no rifles.
The white men are sure to have rifles.
We can't see how many are down there.
Let's forget about this and go home.
Then go.
I'd rather die
than argue about some smoke.
He won't quit until we're all dead.
Kicking Bird has been keeping to himself.
I do not like to see
our medicine man going around alone.
What does his wife say?
She says he's keeping to himself.
That's not what I asked.
- Well, what did you ask me?
She says he's keeping
to himself these days.
That's what she said.
Make sure that my meat is soft.
My teeth hurt.
May I come in?
No, he can sit with me.
Our country seems good this summer.
But I have not been out to see it.
But the buffalo are late.
I'm always worried about
the bellies of our children.
I was thinking of a dance.
- Yes. A dance is always a good idea.
It would be good to have a sign.
It's a funny thing about signs.
We know when they are bad or good.
But sometimes they are strange
and it's hard to understand them.
A wise man will think about these things.
If he is still confused,
he will tell somebody.
You or me, for instance.
A wise man always does this.
I have seen such a sign.
Really?
I saw a man.
A naked, white man.
Are you sure it was a man?
I saw his sex.
Did you speak to him?
No.
He might be a god.
Or a white chief
with special abilities.
We should talk to him.
Don't talk like that
about a white man.
He is not a Sioux
and that makes him less.
When I hear that more whites
are coming, I have to laugh.
We took 100 horses from them.
There was no honor in that.
They ride badly,
they shoot badly, they're dirty.
Their soldiers couldn't even make it
through a single winter here.
And these people are flourishing?
I think they'll all be dead soon.
This fool is probably lost.
Wind In His Hair's words are strong.
The whites are a poor race,
and hard to understand.
But make no mistake.
They will come.
Even our enemies agree on this.
When I see one man in our country,
alone and without fear,
I don't think he is lost.
He may have medicine.
I see someone who might speak
for all the white people who are coming.
I think treaties can be struck
with a man like this.
Kicking Bird is always looking ahead
and that is good.
But this man cannot cover our lodges
or feed our children.
He means nothing to us.
We will shoot some arrows
into this white man.
If he has medicine,
he won't be hurt.
If he hasn't, he will die.
No man can tell another what to do.
But killing a white man
is a delicate matter.
If you kill one,
more are sure to come.
These are confusing questions.
It's hard to know what to do.
We should talk about it some more.
That's all I have to say.
What's the matter?
- We don't think this is a good idea.
If we take the horse of a white god,
they will write songs about us.
Maybe.
- They will let us go on raids.
Who gets the horse?
- I do.
But we share.
Isn't that a great plan?
It's always the same.
We will be heroes.
They will write songs about us.
What happened?
What's wrong?
I don't know.
I can't move my arm.
You shouldn't have fallen off.
We're in trouble now.
It was your idea.
My idea was to take the horse,
not fall off.
Otter hurt himself.
What are you looking at? It hurts!
My father will beat me up with his bow.
I am Wind In His Hair!
Do you see that I'm not afraid of you?
Do you see?
The party that went
against the Utes is coming back.
Many have died.
You are not welcome here.
Go away. Go away.
Go.
You are not welcome here.
Stop! The soldier
did not come here to fight.
He is going away, and we'll let him.
I agree with Kicking Bird.
We will go
and talk to the white man
and find out why he is here.
If this is what the council decides,
it will be so.
But it's not right
that a great chief like Ten Bears
should talk to a puny white trespasser
who has only a smart horse
and a few clothes.
I'm not going. You're going.
And you.
That will be all.
He has lost his mind.
Stands With A Fist.
Let us talk a while.
Are your wounds healing well?
Yes, they are.
Are you happy here, with my family?
- I'm glad to be here.
I am missing my husband.
Perhaps you will marry again.
- Perhaps.
We get word from many places
that the whites are coming.
They are coming to everyone's land,
and soon they will come to ours.
The white man at the old fort,
I have visited him.
I believe his heart is a good one.
I am afraid of him.
I'm afraid he will tell others
that I am here.
I'm afraid they will come
to take me away.
All our warriors would protect you.
I don't know the white man's language,
and he doesn't speak Sioux.
It has been a long time
since I spoke their language.
I want you to try.
- I don't know how.
Yes, you do.
- No.
Yes.
- It's dead in me.
I don't ask this for me,
but for all the people.
He knows many things
about the whites.
You must remember.
- I can't.
Will she make the white words?
She won't try.
She's being difficult.
She's crying.
Maybe the difficulty is yours.
We've been waiting for you.
We've been waiting.
Tell him that we are glad that he is here.
Ask him why he is at the soldier fort.
He's right.
Introductions should come first.
I found it on the prairie.
It's mine.
That hat belongs to the lieutenant.
He left it on the prairie.
He didn't want it.
Well, you can see he wants it now.
We all know that it is a soldier's hat.
We all know who wears it.
If you want to keep it
you have to give him something.
Please use the Skip-button
on your remote control
to skip the intermission.
You were right.
He is a very special white man.
He should have a real name.
You can keep talking in
the white man's tongue, if you like.
I like to talk.
What are you doing?
It's hot,
so we're sitting in the shade.
I'm hungry.
How is Dances With Wolves?
What do you mean?
- How is he learning?
He is a fast learner.
What did you think I meant?
You go to get water?
Let us take you.
You are not talking to him today?
- No, I'm not.
You make a few mistakes,
but you're learning fast.
So what can I tell you today?
About Stands With A Fist.
Why is she not married?
She is in mourning.
I do not understand 'mourning'.
She cries for someone.
Cries for who?
It is not polite to speak of the dead.
But you are new, so I will tell you.
She cries for her husband.
He was killed not long ago.
That's how you came
to find her on the prairie.
How long will she be in mourning?
That's Kicking Bird's decision.
He found her when she was very little.
People are talking about you.
What are they saying?
They are proud
of the medicine you are making
with Dances With Wolves.
I have hurt him,
and I should go and talk to him.
You can't. He's gone.
He left this morning.
Stone Calf, wait. I will follow you.
The Pawnee do not come for horses.
They come for blood.
Get your weapons and come to my lodge.
I will get them.
Wait. I have guns.
Many rifles, at the fort.
At the fort?
No. The ride is long
and we can spare no men.
Guns would make
one warrior like two.
Take one man and go quickly.
I'll take Smiles A Lot.
When we were young,
he always bragged about his courage.
And what a great chief he would be.
He thought I would be impressed.
Once we ran
into a herd of buffalo on the prairie.
This brave warrior
immediately ran for a tree.
He would have forgotten all about me
if he hadn't needed a leg up.
We sat up there all day
while an old cow circled the tree,
hitting her head against the trunk.
Where are you going?
There's gambling tonight.
Horseback's games are always good.
I'm tired. And he already
has won a good rifle of mine.
Good night.
How long will
Stands With A Fist mourn?
I don't know.
I hope it won't be long.
Has something happened? What?
She has found love again.
With who?
- Guess.
Tell me.
- Dances With Wolves.
Are you certain of this?
When you see them together, you'll know.
What are people saying?
- They've accepted it.
No one is angry?
It makes sense.
They are both white.
I suppose
I will have to say something.
She's your daughter now.
- I know.
Relax.
You can't see everything coming.
Quit your playing.
Stands With A Fist.
You will mourn no more.
Sit. Sit.
They say that you want to get married.
To who?
- Stand With A Fist.
It's her, isn't it?
- She's in mourning.
Not today.
Kicking Bird has released her.
He did?
What are you doing here?
Kicking Bird told me to wait.
You might have to wait a long time.
He saw Kicking Bird riding
on the prairie, talking to himself.
A medicine man takes it pretty hard
when he's the last one to know.
What do I do now?
You're pretty poor,
and a Sioux-girl is not for free.
I don't know if you can get married.
I have my horse.
- That's too much medicine.
Do you think my horse is too much medicine?
It is for a girl.
Wait here.
Maybe we can help you.
Wait.
- Alright.
Turn around.
You look good.
You know, the man she mourned for
was my best friend.
I didn't know.
He was a good man.
It has been hard for me to like you.
I'm not a thinker like Kicking Bird.
I always get angry first
I got no answers to my questions.
But now I think he went away
because you were coming.
That's how I see it.
This is a good day for me.
If you want this man,
take his hand in yours.
Did you hear what I said?
Have you heard all that I have said?
Good, then take her inside.
She is your wife.
Thank you.
We don't see Dances With Wolves
much these days.
They're having trouble making a baby.
I don't think so.
If we pull the smoke flap shut,
they're sure to come out.
Dances With Wolves,
are you in there?
Today,
I'm riding to a far away place.
I'd like you to come with me.
It feels good to be out.
- I can imagine.
We are trying for a baby.
No waiting?
- No waiting.
I was just thinking,
of all the trails in this life
there is one that matters most:
It is the trail of a true human being.
You are on this trail,
and that's good to see.
We call you the Busy Bee.
It is said that all the animals
were born here.
From here they spread over
the prairies to feed all the people.
Even our enemies agree
that this is a sacred place.
It's quiet here.
We must wait for these people.
No. They've been gone
a week, maybe more.
We will water the horses and go home.
You always ask
about the white people.
How many more are coming.
There will be a lot, my friend.
More than can be counted.
It makes me afraid for all the Sioux.
We should tell Ten Bears.
The men who wore this helmet
came in the time
of my grandfather's grandfather.
Eventually, we drove them out.
Then the Mexicans came.
They don't come anymore.
In my own time: The Texans.
They are like all the others.
They take without asking.
I don't know
if we are ready for these people.
But I think you're right.
I think they will keep coming.
When I think of that, I look at this.
Our land is all we have.
We will fight to keep it.
Tomorrow we will go
to our winter camp.
Enough.
We cannot wait for you.
Something has happened.
He is not coming back.
He must have trouble.
Pick two good men
and send them to the fort.
I am Dances With Wolves.
I have nothing to say to you.
You are not worth talking to.
Dances With Wolves
is very quiet these days.
Is his heart bad?
Killing those soldiers by the river
was a good thing.
I was glad to do it.
But the soldiers hate me now,
like they hate no other.
They think I'm a traitor.
And they will hunt for me.
And when they find me, they find you.
I think it would be wise
to move the village.
I will be leaving.
I must go and talk
with those who would listen.
Quiet. You make my ears hurt.
Leave us alone.
You are the only white man
I've ever known.
I have thought about you a lot.
More than you know.
I think you're wrong.
The man the soldiers are looking for
no longer exists.
Now there is only a Sioux
named Dances With Wolves.
Let's smoke a while.
It's all right.
Dances With Wolves!
I am Wind In His Hair!
Do you see that I am your friend?
Can you see that
you will always be my friend?