Long ago,
during the Ching-dynasty...
Shaolin-monks wanted
to overthrow the evil regime.
But the emperor
mounted his own charge.
They must die.
Many monks fled, with the emperor's
soldiers close on their heels.
That is where we join the story.
Burning Paradise
- Uncle, are you hurt?
- My ankle...
- Does it hurt?
- No.
The soldiers are coming.
We must leave.
Let me help you.
Egotistical beast.
- Go, save yourself.
- I don't run like an animal.
Then we must fight.
Maybe another time, uncle.
Tell that to them.
Fong, you forgot to mount.
Boy, what is your name?
Fong Sai Yuk of the Shaolin-temple.
And you, old goat?
I've been looking for you.
You cannot escape.
Where are you going?
Crimson?
You're finished.
Fong, run for your life.
So you want to run away?
Don't leave me alone,
I want to fight.
Next time I'll let you know in time.
Don't let them go.
We'll hide there, quickly.
Are you alright?
That damn animal
will be the death of me.
- Rotten beast.
- It's only an animal.
You're just too heavy.
That's because I do nothing
but eat and sleep.
Shut up,
you're a disgrace to all monks.
Show your old uncle some respect.
Damn it's windy.
Empty, like it was just
waiting for us.
Rather cosy.
Uncle, you must pay better attention.
Who is it?
We are hiding from the soldiers.
We leave as soon as I'm well again.
Uncle, let me massage your foot.
Miss, monks don't lie.
Don't be afraid.
Nice body.
- Nice legs.
- How can you tell with those pants?
I learned that from you.
And you're supposed to be a monk?
How dare you make fun of me.
You're a sinner.
Sit still, uncle. Don't move.
Comfortable?
The soldiers.
Don't panic, I'll protect you.
Don't be a hero just yet,
wait to see what they're up to.
Hide, uncle.
Quick, there they come.
- Go away, it's safer.
- I have to hide too.
Miss, it's not done
to stand so close.
- Show some respect.
- Piss off.
- Watch your tongue.
- Fuck off.
Stop yapping and hide, fast.
Don't lean on me, I can't stand it.
Search the cabin.
This hovel is falling apart.
Nothing, let's go.
Dear god.
Don't panic.
Don't think, just stay calm.
- Anything?
- There's nobody here.
They're leaving.
Who touched me?
Not me, I'm a Shaolin-student.
And Chi Nun is a respected
Shaolin-monk.
- We'd never do such a thing.
- I'll bet.
- We didn't do anything.
- You can't prove we did.
No proof? How about this then?
My hands are smaller.
- So it was me?
- You're admitting it.
You're both the same.
It was just an accident.
You're a good person,
please don't make a fuss about it.
Forgive us,
we'll be forever grateful.
- Fong, we must go. Come on.
- Very smart, uncle.
Watch out.
- Did you do it?
- Blame it on me.
- I mean this.
- My hand is not that small.
Say it was you, otherwise it was her.
Leave it, we have to go.
- Are you leaving?
- Yes, why?
- You still owe me something.
- You're right.
You must pray for my dead mother.
- I will. What's your name?
- Tou Tou.
- I'm Fong.
- Chi Mun.
- So you said.
- You might have forgotten.
Come, I will help you.
Some student.
Tou Tou, why are you here?
I escaped from a brothel.
I'm on my way home.
- A brothel?
- I'm a whore.
Famine struck in my village.
I was sold to a brothel, for food.
Now everybody is dead.
I don't want to be a whore.
So that's why you were so offended.
Uncle.
- Don't act so nervous.
- Aren't you nervous?
Don't be so secretive.
- Some kung-fu master you are.
- Just unlucky.
We don't stand a chance.
Every battle has winners and losers.
Shaolin is finished.
Fong, we must find a place
where we can live in peace.
Do you want to be a coward?
That's worse than an animal.
I'm testing you,
but you take it seriously.
In the Shaolin-temple
I fought in the Wooden Lane.
- I passed the fite test.
- You're bluffing.
You don't believe me? Look.
- A dragon left, a tiger right.
- Let me see.
Are you trying to burn me?
You afraid of fire?
What about the fire test?
I was prepared then, now I'm not.
I'm a Shaolin-student,
I must save my master.
- Shaolin-honour must be restored.
- Finished?
At this rate my mother
will never make it to heaven.
- Alright, go get wood.
- Okay.
I'll come along.
There's a wooden frame.
That way.
- Being a whore must be difficult.
- What about being a Shaolin-student?
Of course, look at my rough skin.
I have that too.
Who was your first customer?
An old man or a young man?
He was around 50.
The old bastard.
How can you do it
if you don't know them?
- I close my eyes.
- Are you afraid?
- Of course.
- And afterwards?
- I scream.
- Because you feel like it?
Aren't you Shaolin-elite?
Why do you want to know this?
Yeah, why bother about it.
I should worry about my country.
All I want is to go home.
- I'll visit you if I have the time.
- Okay.
Give me your address later.
- Is everything okay?
- Fine.
We're surrounded.
Quickly, we have to get out of here.
Fire.
Where is uncle?
Fong, this way.
Uncle...
Look at all those soldiers. What now?
Ready...
Fong...
Uncle, hang on.
Uncle...
The soldiers are coming.
Stop.
Fong, you will die,
unless you can fly.
Look after my uncle.
Come on then.
Show me what you've got.
Run, it's no use fighting.
Who comes close, dies.
Fong, if you want her to live,
surrender yourself.
- Will you let her go?
- I promise.
What do we do with the monk?
Take him away.
Crimson, let him live
or I will kill you.
Let my uncle live.
May god bless you.
No, uncle...
Thanks.
- Stop pushing me.
- Be still.
RED LOTUS TEMPLE
Stop working.
Everybody in line.
Kneel.
Lord Kung, Chi Nun is dead.
I have a gift for you.
Go on.
Prisoners of the Red Lotus,
you're lucky to be alive.
Kung-fu and praying are forbidden.
There are no Shaolin-students here.
Only prisoners of Ching.
Shut up, bitch. A Shaolin
never renounces his master.
What a beautiful voice.
Do you know any other tricks?
I'm ready.
Good, the Shaolin has got guts.
Bring him out.
Yes, Lord Kung.
Brother...
- Any more Shaolin-students?
- All of us, so what?
You've got nerve.
If you can appear before me,
you can be what you want.
Release him.
Fong, watch out.
Watch out, brother.
Get down.
Fong, look out.
Take my hand.
Brother...
Brother, hang on to my hand.
Don't let go.
Brother...
This temple has many pitfalls.
You must obey me,
even if you are invincible.
In the end, you will all die.
Then I want you to die with me.
Good kung-fu.
- But you will die young.
- We'll see.
The Grip of the Fantastic Tiger.
How dare you be so insolent.
Brother.
Fong, I'm no longer your brother.
I'm a foreman, you're a prisoner.
Traitor.
If you want to live, turn back now.
You've become their dog.
I'm through with you.
The killer has to die.
Come on.
Show me your Crane, come on.
Not bad. Very educational,
the Shaolin Tiger and Crane.
Go on.
- You're scared.
- Come on.
Do you repent?
Fong...
Everybody on your knees.
Any more Shaolin-students?
I thought so.
Good work, master Hong.
Luk shall be your reward.
Thank you, lord Kung.
Gather everybody who can work, the
rest goes into the Cave of the Dead.
Fong...
It's me, master Chi Nun.
Don't you recognize me?
Are you scared?
- What do you think?
- Of course you are.
Master, you must hang on.
I've come to rescue you.
Long time no see.
Have you come only to talk nonsense?
That's kind of you.
Cleaner.
A little kindness, please.
You're hurting me.
Are you afraid of me?
Why? Death is the worst
that can happen.
Women shouldn't talk about death.
Is everything to your liking?
Such a big bath tub,
what a waste of water.
It's water from a well. You'll find
no cleaner water anywhere.
That itches.
I just took a bath.
I always give a woman
a welcoming present.
What would you like?
Anything you want.
Just don't ask me to let you go.
I don't want to go.
I ask for Fong's freedom.
- What's your bond with him?
- He saved my life.
If this is the way you repay him,
you must be a passionate woman.
I like that.
Will you let him go?
I know your weakness now.
- Remember that, Boroke.
- Yes, master.
Master, how did you survive here?
- It wasn't so difficult.
- Master, you've gained weight.
I had no choice.
I ate too much meat.
- Will you eat me when I die?
- I only eat rat meat.
Somebody's coming.
Pretend you're dead.
Sleep with the dead.
Corpses are so filthy.
That's him. Take him away.
How can a corpse
change its expression?
Go on.
- Sister Boroke...
- Luk, get out.
Whatever you wish.
Hong, anything Luk can give you,
I can give to you too.
Tonight I shall be yours.
I'm not that strong.
I can't do it.
Don't be nervous.
Be my servant.
You're bewitched.
You are lord Kung's right hand.
What could I possibly mean to you?
O, shut up. I think you are a hero,
that's why I want you.
But you're not a man of the world,
so forget it.
I don't dare.
I'm not prepared.
You call me the dog of Manchius,
but dogs have passion too.
Send Luk back in.
Watch your head.
Your highness.
- How is he doing?
- It's not so bad.
I heard you saved my queen.
I want to repay you.
Then she'll owe you nothing.
I'm sorry you must suffer to save me.
Lord Kung is a gentleman.
I'm just doing you a favour.
- How are you?
- Better, but it's still painful.
Show me.
Can you bear it?
You are nice, but he is a killer.
I will save you.
That depends on your strenght.
You two have a lot to discuss.
I won't bother you any longer.
What do you want?
- I want to walk.
- That won't speed up your recovery.
Help me, it'll go quicker.
Easy. No problems?
Not at all.
Look, it doesn't hurt one bit.
I feel no pain.
- Let me lie down.
- I said: Take it easy.
Why do men always want to be heroes?
- How can you stay with that wolf.
- He hasn't touched me.
- He behaves like he has.
- Let's sit over there.
You must forget him.
Fong, that woman is Kung's pet.
Leave her alone.
Mind your own business.
This is the Red Lotus Temple.
It is forbidden to fool around.
Hong, you've betrayed Shaolin.
You will pay.
Shut the door.
- You're abusing the situation.
- I learned that from you.
Eat.
You're a nice person.
Lord Kung.
Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
You're pretty when you're scared.
You're disgusting.
If you want me, then take me.
Is this some kind of trap?
Damn it...
Why do you lie down so easily?
Speak.
- I want to obey you.
- Why don't you resist?
Did I tell you to undress?
What kind of a slut are you?
You must resist.
Can anybody take you, just like that?
That's not what I want.
You disappoint me.
I was a great general,
loyal to my lord and ruler.
Then I saw I was turning grey.
I knew I would die someday.
Even rich and fame
won't keep you from dying.
So you must enjoy life
as much as you can.
I want to enjoy life,
although life is unbearable.
For me, there's no other way.
So I asked my lord and ruler for
a transfer to the Red Lotus Temple.
Here I can do as I please.
Even the emperor cannot harm me here.
Here I am a god, and more.
What is the use of power?
Women, death...
I'm locked up in here.
The Red Lotus Temple is a horror.
- Aren't you afraid of death?
- Yes, don't kill me.
Tung Tak saw what I did.
You must keep my secret.
- I won't say anything, really.
- Really? Try it.
Does Fong want my woman?
I have released Fong.
So tonight you must do
what you promised me to do.
You're so pretty when you're scared.
Fong.
Close the gate.
Hit it.
Open it up.
Who is there?
Hong?
- Did you see anything?
- No.
- I'll go that way.
- I'll look over there.
Don't stick your nose in these
matters, or you will die.
- How dare you be lazy.
- Go to hell.
Stop.
Fong, drop that.
So he works slow.
Is that a reason to kill him?
In here, there are no laws.
Drop that if you want to live.
Dog.
Drop it, you don't have a chance.
Fong...
Kneel, all of you.
- Fong, you again.
- So what?
What's with the pride?
You owe your life to a woman.
And you dare call yourself
a Shaolin-student?
- Shame on you.
- What? Fight if you dare.
- With you?
- Are you scared?
Alright, you'll get your chance.
I'll see you on the podium.
Drums.
Go on.
Hurry up.
Move along.
What is this?
A theater for animal fights.
Who's going to fight Fong?
Fong has insulted the elders.
He must die.
Only if you beat the podium master,
you may live.
The podium master.
- Is that you, Hong?
- Hong, you filthy dog.
- Fong, kill that traitor.
- What? Shut up.
Crimson, you coward.
Fight with me if you have the guts.
You are a prisoner,
you cannot fight me.
Fong.
- Lord Kung, what is your command?
- The Tiger and the Crane.
If you win,
this woman will be yours.
Lord Kung,
I won't disappoint you.
Traitor. You are my brother,
but I will show no mercy.
Crane, I will show you how it's done.
- Your Tiger has lost some weight.
- You have no respect.
Fong...
Calm down, don't let go of my hand.
Fong, drop him.
No mercy.
I'll repay my debt at once.
Up with you.
Fong, look out.
- Why did you become their dog?
- I owe you no explanation.
To hell together or up together.
Fong, come up.
Up.
Hong, are you no longer loyal?
This map could endanger
the entire temple.
Luk is not only good in bed,
she's also a good informant.
Lord, these Shaolin-students
no longer have any purpose.
Fong, if you kill Hong,
this whore is yours.
What do you take me for?
Brother, you're trapped.
Let's save our brothers
and get out of here. Run.
Get the keys.
Fong...
So you want a rebel.
Bitch, you betrayed my brother.
Fong, come on.
Tung.
Fong...
- Are you alright?
- I see stars.
Fight.
Who squeezed my dick?
Stop it, we're on the same side.
- Let's fight.
- Wait for me.
Outside.
- Brother.
- Everything okay?
- Many soldiers.
- Are you scared?
Push the gate.
- Pull him away.
- Let me do it.
Careful, there are many soldiers
down there. And behind you.
Step back.
Jump, quick.
Upstairs, now.
Don't let them escape. Fire.
- What do you want from me?
- I want to play.
And when I'm finished, I will let
my servants play with you.
Until nobody wants to play with you
anymore.
Then I will keep you as a statue.
You're crazy.
Dead people are perfect.
They don't think. Perfect.
You're a monster.
If you like death so much,
why don't you die?
When we meet again,
you will appreciate my kindness.
Lord Kung, all prisoners
are locked up.
Those morons. If escaping was easy,
I would have been out of here.
Good dogs are rare.
Hong wants to deceive me.
But all he will find is death.
Boroke, keep an eye on her.
No more mistakes.
No way out here.
- What now?
- Jump.
God, what foul smell.
- You've been here before.
- Traitor.
Master.
So you recognize me, you animal.
Leave me alone.
Leave him alone.
You killed my students.
You must die.
- I will kill you.
- Master, you don't understand.
Why am I still alive?
Because I want to save my brothers.
Are you that kind?
There are many traps here,
so I help him.
I have to know the traps.
He drew me a map.
But lord Kung found out.
I'm not lying.
- Then I misunderstood.
- At least you didn't hit me.
- No, he hit me.
- You should have ducked.
- You're much too fast.
- You know it.
We must find a way out of here.
If we can find the gun powder...
we may be able to get out of here.
- But how do we get to it?
- I've not been idle in here.
Follow me.
- Here is a way out.
- How on earth did you dig that?
Aren't I wonderful?
I found it like this.
- Master, come.
- I'm safer in here.
Come and get me
when you're ready to escape.
The future of Shaolin
is in your hands.
- Quite a burden.
- Stop complaining.
Master, you're the greatest.
We'll come for you.
- There we go.
- Be careful.
The Rode Lotus is as dangerous
as the martial arts themselves.
Two parties will fight,
the winner is pronounced king.
Why do you want to leave?
If you leave,
the Red Lotus will cease to exist.
A new man will bring new leadership.
Wake up or die.
Tou Tou...
Fong...
Everybody stay here.
Sit down.
Go save the rest.
Fong, look out.
You again.
- Fong, let me do it.
- Brother.
- Boroke, let us go.
- A dog doesn't bite his master.
Fong, save me.
They're running away. After them.
Tou Tou says nobody may leave.
- I don't want to kill you. Go.
- I don't want to.
- Brother, are you alright?
- Yes.
You musn't be too nice.
Hold this.
Don't let it drop on me,
that would kill me.
Women are such a pain.
Wait. Hold on.
- Let's see if you can carry this.
- You bitch.
Dirty bitch.
Here it comes.
- My leg.
- I'm gonna kill you.
Fong, stop.
She's as good as dead anyway.
- Where were you?
- I was guarding the women.
You should have helped me.
But I'm so confused.
- Help.
- Who called for help?
Let's lift that thing.
- How are you?
- Will you take it easy.
- Tou Tou, are you okay?
- No.
- You've gained weight.
- Untie me.
You're so rude, it's unbelievable.
You let me go the first time.
Now I'll help you.
- How do you take this off?
- I'll do it myself.
Simple.
You should have done that earlier.
- I was tied up, you idiot.
- I'm such a fool.
When will that nitwit learn to be careful.
Fong, come back.
Hong, poison gas. Get out of there.
Come on.
- Let me be. You go.
- Why?
I probably won't make it,
and Kung will never let me go.
Everything will work out fine
once we get out of here.
It's working.
Where are we?
Rats.
That one's thin, he must be starved.
This is no time for jokes.
Who is there?
- Nothing but corpses.
- All because of that old monster.
- She looks like you.
- Shut up.
- A snake.
- Are you afraid of snakes?
At least it's quiet in here,
no fighting.
- Can't we avoid the fighting?
- How would we escape?
Will we get out of here alive?
- I'll make sure you get home.
- Really?
I've never lied before.
- Something's bitten me.
- Step aside.
- It hurts.
- Sit down.
Don't panic,
I'll suck out the poison.
- He bit in your toe.
- Let's be serious about this.
- It's smells bad.
- Aren't you going to save me?
Close your eyes.
No, that tickles.
Stop laughing,
I'm saving your life here.
- Are you okay?
- It doesn't matter.
- Are there any traps here?
- Yes.
Kung showed me
where the gun powder is.
- Where is it?
- Straight ahead.
Let me help you.
Turn it to the right
and the door will open.
It doesn't work.
But it will turn to the left.
- That was a mistake.
- Leave it, let's get the gun powder.
Hong, be careful.
- Did I land on you?
- No.
Hang on. Don't let go of my hand.
Don't let go.
Boroke...
Boroke.
Look, the door opens.
Turn the tap again.
- Come on, let's go.
- Let me put on my shoes.
Get down.
Let's get out of here.
I'm dizzy.
Snake.
- It's real, so don't worry.
- Drop it.
- Fong, do you dare to fight me?
- Are you kidding?
Let her go.
- Drop that or she dies.
- Don't trust him.
Tou Tou...
- Bastard.
- It works every time.
Run.
I'm going to kill you.
- Stand still and fight.
- Fong.
- You wait here.
- Be careful.
Stop, you.
So you want to escape? Where to?
I send you to hell.
Uncle, now you can rest in peace.
It's open. Climb out.
Tung, Tung, this way, quick.
Hong, master...
You are safe, that is so good.
How I've missed you.
What's gotten into you?
I'm not your wife.
- You're making my hand all wet.
- Master, I'm so happy.
- What are we waiting for?
- Master, this is a dead end.
- We must go that way.
- Why didn't you say so. Go on.
Tou Tou...
- Master, there's no way out.
- What do we do?
Buddha will have a solution.
Buddha, how do we get out of here?
- Master, he doesn't care about us.
- Maybe he's angry.
Hong, burn some incense.
Students, kneel down
and cite the sutra together.
- Are you done?
- Yes.
Get down.
Master.
Suckers. What good does your
Shaolin-kung fu do now?
You're even asking help
from a statue.
I built this statue,
it answers only to me.
When I say 'kill', it kills.
Don't you know
that Buddha has gone to hell?
Go and visit him there.
Take care of the master.
Hurry up.
Hong, you disappoint me. Shaolin or
Red Lotus, what does it matter?
You had a good life with me,
what more could you want?
Now you must die.
- Old monster, fight if you dare.
- Hong, what are you doing?
Beautiful, both of them are here.
Just when it was getting boring.
Show yourself, old wolf.
You want to see me?
Come down to hell.
There.
Look me up in hell.
Show yourself.
He must be here somewhere.
Master, it's just
a big piece of stone.
No, Buddha is testing your faith.
On your knees.
Bow down and say you're sorry.
All the way to the ground.
- Not that hard.
- Look out, master.
- Master, look, sunlight.
- A miracle of Buddha.
- The hole is too small.
- I'll talk to him.
Why don't we blow it up?
We must respect Buddha.
On your knees and pray.
- Nothing.
- Where is that old monster?
Leave it, let's save our brothers.
- The Floating Stance?
- Your kung-fu won't save you.
I was just careless.
You're not so tough.
De jeugd denkt dat ze alles kan.
Kun je ook verliezen?
Het zal snel gedaan zijn met je jeugd.
Tijger en Kraanvogel,
dat stelt niks voor.
Behold my Boundless Stance.
And my rainbow.
Boundless dimensions.
Boundless power,
boundless force.
A boundless world.
Tiger and Crane.
- What does it say?
- Boundless. I curse you.
Fong, now.
- Quick, disperse the brothers.
- Master, we're ready.
- How do I explain this to Buddha.
- Just light it.
- You do it.
- No way.
- You're young, Buddha forgives you.
- Are you mad?
Boundless creativity.
Fong...
He has gone to hell.
Watch the master, I'll go for them.
- Tung.
- Go now.
Where is Tou Tou? I must find her.
Fong.
- Tou Tou, where are you?
- Fong, I'm here.
Tou Tou, I'm on the bridge.
Where are you?
I'm under the bridge,
come and save me.
- I'm coming.
- Quickly, or I will surely die.
I'm coming, stop screaming.
- So high, I'll break my neck.
- What did you say?
Stop screaming.
Where are you?
- You scared the hell out of me.
- What did you yell?
That you should stop screaming.
- Now what? I can't walk like this.
- I'll carry you.
Numbskull, do you want to die?
That way.
- Is there a way out?
- With you it's always a dead end.
- What do you mean by that?
- Isn't love sweet.
Fire. Go back, quickly.
- Tou Tou, are you alright?
- Yes, no thanks to you.
Is anybody there? Come and save us.
You wanted to save me
and now we're trapped.
This wasn't even your fight,
you were innocent.
- Just like her.
- The people are suffering.
There's war after war after war.
Tou Tou, hold my hand, we're trapped.
I'll take you to heaven.
- Fong, enough already. Come on.
- It's too narrow.
- It breaks just like that.
- Quick, the temple is gonna explode.
Give me your hand.
Don't touch my butt.
- Why are you touching it anyway?
- It's hard to miss.
- What about me? Don't go.
- You jump.
What a pain in the ass.
That way.
Master, we must say farewell.
I'll bring Tou Tou home.
Fong, there are many temples
like the Red Lotus. Be careful.
Okay, master.
- Brothers, I wish you well.
- Come back after you're married.
Don't tease me,
I've never lied before.
- Brother, take care.
- Don't hurry back.
Give me that horse.
Goodbye.
What a couple.