When did you ...
When were you gonna tell me?
Soon. Now.
How am I part of the decision now?
What am I supposed to say now?
So, the daddy bear plants his seed
in the mommy bear
and it grows into an egg.
Is this about fucking?
Do you know what that means?
The boy puts his pee pee
in the girl's doo doo.
Well ...
Haven't you ever wished
you had somebody around to play with?
No.
You might like it.
What if I don't like it?
Then you get used to it.
Just because you're used to
something ...
doesn't mean you like it.
You're used to me.
Yes, well ...
In a few months we're all gonna
get used to somebody new.
Beautiful.
Hey Kev. Come on and meet your
little sister.
This is your brother. It's Kevin.
It's your big brother.
Yes, that's right.
It's Kevin.
Yes, yes ...
Kevin! Don't do that.
No, Kevin. That's not nice.
No problem dear.
We're getting snacks, okay?
Come on.
Christ! To Ecuador? For 2 months?
Why can't they send someone else?
I really wanna work this deal.
First he cries too much,
then he's too quiet.
Then he makes up his own little language,
and that is annoying.
He has trouble communicating.
A lot of kids do.
And you see this as some kind
of personal vendetta?
It's not good for him.
Franklin, pick up the god damn phone!
Pick up the god damn phone.
... 13, 14, 15,
16, 17, 18, 19 ...
... 20, 21, 21, 22,
23, 24, 25, 26, 27 ...
Please. Please. Let me have
a drink. Please
Kevin?
Kevin!
Honey?
Are you ok?
I'm sorry mom.
Not to worry, sweetheart.
You couldn't help it.
"By my soul," cried Gilbert.
"Aren't thou the devil in blue to shoot in that way?"
"Nay," posed Robin, laughing.
"Not quite so ill as that I trust."
"Then he took up another shaft ..."
Are you okay, honey?
Then he took up another shaft,
and fitted it to the string.
Again he shot.
Again, he smoathed the arrow
close beside the center.
The third time, he losed his bowstring
and dropped the arrow
just betwix the other two,
and into the very center,
so that the feathers of all three
were ruffled together
seeming from a distance
to be one big shaft.
And now a low murmur
ran all along the great crowd.
Hey champ. How are you doing?
Feeling better?
Go away. I'm tired.
Oh. Okay.
Sure thing, buddy.
You just get some rest, okay?
Don't stop reading, mom.
280 score shafts were shot in all
and so deftly were they sped,
that when the shooting was done
each target looked like the
back of a hedgehog ...
when a farm dog snuffed at it.
Good afternoon, ma'am.
I hope this isn't an inconvenient time.
Well, it is actually.
Well, we just have a couple
of quick questions for you.
What is it about?
Do you know where you are
spending the afterlife?
Oh, yeah. I do as a matter of fact.
I'm going straight to hell.
Eternal damnation.
Thank you for asking.
Okay?
Hey honey. Let me help you with that.
I can dress myself.
Can you leave?
Sure.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
Do you want some more of that
chowder for lunch?
Whatever.
- Or grilled cheese sandwich?
- I don't give a rat's ass.
Thanks Dad, this is so cool.
You're welcome, buddy.
Right. Here we go.
In the middle.
Ooooh. Almost. Here.
Take that one.
Try again.
Use your finger ...
Keep your eyes in the middle.
Good shot, Kev.
You're a natural.
Perfect.
Thanks Dad.
Right.
It's like this.
You wake up.
Then you watch TV.
You get in the car, then you
listen to the radio.
Then you go to you little job
or your little school
but we're not gonna hear about
that on the 6pm news.
Why?
Because nothing is really happening.
Then you go home
and watch some more TV.
Or maybe it's a fun night,
and you go out
and you watch a movie.
I mean it's got so bad,
that half the time
the people on TV,
inside the TV,
they're watching TV.
And what are all these
people watching?
People like me.
And what are all you
doing right now?
You're watching me.
Don't you think you would
have changed the channel by now
if all I did
was getting "A" in geometry?
Me and Kevin were plaiying
"Christmas kidnapping".
Kevin!
Kevin, you're my friend!
You're my friend.
Beat it, Celia.
Get me a soda.
Not that, you retard.
Get me a Root Beer.
What ?
Thank you, Celia.
I was thirsty.
Hey, you wanne know a secret?
Come closer.
Do you know who else is thirsty?
You don't?
It's the vacuum monster.
Cut it out!
- Hey troops!
- Daddy!
Ho, ho, ho. See what I got!
Kev, come here. Give me a hand.
Yeah, sure dad.
- You wanna dance?
- No thanks, Harland.
- Come on. Just one.
- I don't dance, really.
Where do you get off,
you stuck up bitch?
Do you think anyone else
is gonna want you now?
Come on. Stay for another drink.
Come on.
- Are you excited?
- Yeah.
Can we leave a carrot for the reindeer!
- Should we?
- Yeah.
Kevin!
Didn't I see you at the
bookstore today?
No.
Oh, I could have sworn.
By the way, are you doing
anything on Friday?
Why?
I just thought we might
do something together.
For fun.
Like, do what?
Maybe take you for dinner.
Or play around with
miniature golf?
Okay.
Why didn't you bring a coat?
You just can't get uncomfortable
enough, can you?
Uncomfortable?
With my own mother?
Whenever I see fat people,
they are always eating.
Dont' give me any of this "slower
metabolism thyroid gland" crap.
It's food.
They are fat because
they eat the wrong food.
Too much of it, and all the time.
You know, you can be
kind of harsh sometimes.
You're one to talk.
Yeah, I am.
I wonder where I got it.
Well, you won.
So. What next, momsy?
We're gonna go home. You're gonna get
changed into something reasonable.
And I take you to dinner.
Great.
We're going to dinner.
I was hungry.
I'm a growing boy, you know.
I'll have a calorie salad,
steak, medium rare,
and a bottle of Merlot.
Very well.
So, how is school going?
It's going.
on a course schedule.
How about the teachers?
Are there any of them ...
Right, right, what bands am
I listening to these days?
Next you can read all about if there
isn't some cute little cunt
in the front row
who's got me itchy.
Then you can segway into the whole,
it's all up to me of course
but before balling the chick in the hallway
I might decide to way until I'm ready.
Right around dessert,
you can ask about drugs
Real careful, like
cause you don't want to scare me
into, like, lying my head off.
So you have to say, like,
how you experimented.
Then finally once you've sucked
up that entire bottle of wine,
you can go all gooey eyed
and say how nice it is to spend
quality time together,
then scooch over and put your
arm around my shoulder.
Give it a little squeeze.
Fuck!
- Your computer is fucked, isn't it?
- Yeah. It's fucked.
And so are all the ones at work.
I guess I deserved it.
- Why would you let out something like that?
- I collect them.
Isn't that a weird thing to collect?
I don't like stamps.
But what is the point?
There is no point.
That's the point.
No, it really hasn't been any trouble at all.
Everybody is bringing a dish.
Oh. That's him now. I got to go.
You have a great day.
Bye, mom.
Merry Christmas.
Alright, Kev.
You're next.
Can you guess what it is?
That's a series 7. The guy in the
store said it was the best one.
- Gee, dad. Thank you so much.
- Merry Christmas.
What did you have for breakfast?
Had a good day, Snuffles?
Did you hear that thump?
That's a powerful thing, man.
Celia!
Come on, honey. Time for bed
Here we go.
I thought I closed the door.
Kevin said I was stupid,
and he was right.
You're not stupid, honey.
Don't you worry. We'll find him.
Now you scoop down. Come on.
Cozy?
I'm sure Snuffles has gone to
the big pet store in the sky.
- Don't say that! Don't say that!
- Yes. It's the truth!
Dearly beloved,
We are gathered here
to mourn mr. Snuffles ...
Stop it!
Who will ... tragically early ...
So daddy and mommy were looking for him
the whole night.
And you know why we couldn't find him?
Because Snuffles has gone
to live in the garden.
He's living in the garden now,
with a whole bunch of new animal friends.
Celia.
Okay, give me the spoon.
So, they're having a big party tonight...
with the chipmunks, and the squarrels,
and the racoons ...
and they're eating nuts, and berries,
and they're gonna have a whole bunch ...
Why did you leave the drain stuff out?
I didn't.
- I put it way.
- Then how did it get out?
Ask Kevin.
Kevin did it.
You need to go talk to someone.
Uhm Kev. Mom has something
else she wanted to tell you.
I wanted to ...
thank you for calling the ambulance.
And?
And ...
I was concerned that you might
be feeling responsible.
Why is that?
Because you was supposed to
be looking after her.
We just don't want you to
blame yourself.
No. I don't ...
I never said I did.
She's gonna need a glass eye, Kevin.
So, we would appreciate you
looking after her,
and any namecalling ...
You don't really remember being
a kid much do you, dad?
Celia is just gonna have to
suck it up.
I thought you didn't like those.
Well, they're a ...
Now what do you call it ...
an acquired taste.
I'm so sorry.
There you go.
Okay.
Thank you, mommy.
- Hey kiddo. You're going to practice?
- Yeah, you know it.
- Hey Celia, you wanna come collect arrows?
- No!
So ...
What do you want to do?
Let's wait for the school year to end,
and make arrangements for this summer.
At least the custody
is a no-brainer.
Is it?
You've decided?
Eva, there's nothing left to decide.
It already happened.
- I needed a drink of water.
- Hi, Kev.
Listen, buddy,
it's easy to misunderstand something
if you hear it out of context.
Why would I not know the "context"?
I am the context.
- You have to appeal to reject punitive damage.
- No.
You'll lose everything.
The business, your house.
I hate the house.
I always have.
You'll rot in hell!
A personal for Kevin Khatcha ...
dourian?
- Careful, it's heavy.
- It is?
- Have a nice day.
- You too.
What are these for?
You never ride your bike.
I got these for a song of the web.
You make a bundle on them at school.
Like Donald Trump, huh.
I'll take you back to my ship.
1, 2, 3.
Ready for the big dip?
I'm charmed to meet you,
young lady
- Yeah.
- Did you eat all your cereal?
- Yes.
Alright.
You're a little clammy.
Are you okay?
Never better.
Hey. Only three days to go
till you're 16.
We should do something.
How about Sunday?
I don't know.
I might be tied up.
Come clean up some of this mess
and then we're gonna get dressed and go.
I do not want to go to school.
I know, but daddy have to take a shower
and then we'll go.
Say goodbye!
Do you think we could make some time
later to talk. Just the two of us,
without the kids?
I really wanna work this thing out.
Doesn't Kevin go to Gladstone High?
Franklin ...
Pick up the god damn phone!
I have my son in here.
Kevin?
Kevin!
Lauren!
Franklin?
Celia?
You don't look happy.
Have I ever?
I'm almost 18, aren't I?
What is it?
Going to the big school making you nervous??
Nervous?
Do you know anything about
those places?
Well. You managed it all so well.
A child of a minor.
Out of your head on prozac.
You'll be out of here
in a couple of years.
Do you know what day it is today?
Why the let me come see you
on a monday?
Sure. It's my anniversary.
Two years.
Plenty of time to think about it.
I want you to tell me why.
I used to think I knew.
Now I'm not so sure.
Time is up.