Look, look! They're shooting at us.
Fire!
It's just a dragon dance!
Return to your posts!
Start drumming!
Master Wong,
watch out for the gunfire!
- Can you make it?
- Yes!
Give me the tail!
"Monumental Bravery"
"Limitless Trust"
Look over there, Wong Fei-Hung...
more and more foreign ships
are anchoring in our docks.
Britain was given Hong Kong,
Portugal was given Macao,
Russia occupies Hak Lung Gong.
Our country is divided
and I'm being sent to Vietnam
to fight the French.
How will the Vietnamese
react to this plaque here
that says "Our land, our people"?
- Step forward!
- Yes, Your Excellency!
Take it down! Quick!
Wait a minute!
Excellency, the Government
changes its policies so often
you could be called back soon.
The Government is factionalised,
and has reduced my army.
I fear that, while I'm gone,
the men that remain here
will be dismissed.
You're the chief trainer
of my Black Flag Army.
I hope you'll organise them
into a local militia.
So that if China comes under foreign
attack, they can defend it.
Master Wong...
Get up!
Excellency, don't worry!
I hope you'll return soon.
Wong Fei-Hung,
the unjust treaties forced upon us
are written on this fan.
When you see it, think of me.
When I return, I hope the treaties
will have been erased.
"Unjust Treaties"
ONCE UPON A TIME IN CHINA
Produced by: Raymond Chow
Starring: Jet Li and Yuen Biao
Also starring: Kent Cheung,
Rosamund Kwan and Jacky Cheung
Guest starring:
Wu Ma, Lau Sun and Yuen Cheung Yan
Co starring: Yau Kin Gwok, Yam Sai
Guan, Wong Ji Yeung and Yuen Kam Hui
Production Design:
David Law and Kam Yeung Xiang
Executive Producer: Li Yen Lin
Production Manager: Jeuk Bo Chu
Assistant Producers:
Chu Ga Yee and Lam Shu Kin
Writers: Tsui Hark, Yuen Zao Zhi,
Leung Yiu Ming and Deng Bik Yin
Martial Arts Directors: Yuen Cheung
Yan, Yuen Pui Yi and Lau Ga Ying
Art director: Hai Chung Wen
Costumes: Yu Ga Gao
Set designer: Lau Man Hung
Photography: Chung Chi Man,
Bill Wong, Arthur Wong, Ardy Chan,
Chan Dung Chuen and Chen Pui Gai
Edited by: Mak Ji Shang
Music: James Wong and Dai Lee Ming
Director: Tsui Hark
Pork buns!
Here they come.
"God Loves the World"
What are you talking about?
The town's full of foreigners.
You're very smart
to do business with them.
I couldn't make it in China,
so I went to England.
Let's take a photo
with Chu's pet bird.
What an honour
for our feathered friend!
Don't mention it.
- Let's take your picture, too!
- Thank you very much.
- Master Wong!
- How is everyone?
Fei-Hung!
Great Uncle, it's been a while.
You're looking good.
Thank you!
Fei-Hung, see who I brought with me?
Master Wong! Had tea yet?
Everyone's waiting for you.
- 13th Aunt.
- Fei-Hung!
- She wants to shake your hand.
- It's a foreign custom.
Let me introduce you.
This is Joanna.
"Do"?
She's asking how do you do?
- Say, "Thank you."
- Oh, "kill you."
You're welcome.
Fei-Hung, let's take a photo
with the bird. OK?
Sit down...
- Fei-Hung, taking photos is simple.
- How does it work?
Look there.
Don't move...
or the photo won't look good.
Ready! One, two, three!
What happened?
That's boiling water!
- Are you OK? Are you hurt?
- I'm all right!
This foreign game is too dangerous.
Too much powder.
- You told me not to move!
- Are you all right?
Grand Uncle,
I'm glad you asked me here
or you could've ended up
like the bird.
True.
Chu!
I'll go back to England
in a few days.
Yee was in England,
but she insisted on coming back.
At least this way, she won't mix
with those foreigners any more.
- Take care of her for me.
- Take care of her?
Chu, say something.
You're scaring me!
Anyone here?
I'm looking for Master Wong.
Is anyone here?
Who is it? What's up?
- I'm from May County.
- M... ay... May... May.
I'm Leung Foon.
I want Master Wong to teach me.
- He...
- He's not here?
- I...
- You?
- I am...
- You are...!
- Wong... Master Wong...
- You're Master Wong?
- No... yes!
- Ah, so you're Master Wong?!
I was practising kung fu on my cows,
when one kicked my arm.
Please take a look.
Good!
Not that one, this one.
Master Wong, why are you plastering
my leg? I only hurt my arm.
Too... late... now!
It's stiff, Master. Why is it stiff?
Are you... all right?
Oh, I get it!
You want to teach me kung fu?
- Roll? You want me to roll?
- I said no, not roll.
I'm good. Even in plaster
I can move like lightening.
Not a bad stance.
Still not good enough?
I'll keep trying!
I'll show you a few more rolls.
What's all this noise?
- Who's he?
- Master is teaching me kung fu!
Buck Teeth So
is teaching you kung fu?
- Who are you?
- Buck Teeth So!
You're not Master Wong?
Buck Teeth So? Who are you?
- He is Master Wong's student.
- And who are you?
I'm also Master Wong's student, Kai.
What happened to you?
Don't ask. I have to get back
to the theatre. I'm off.
I'm off before he plasters
my other side.
Foon, have you finished mending
that hole in the roof?
The show will start soon!
I'm here to act,
and you make me fix the roof.
It's not fair! I'm scared of heights.
If you can't play this role
how do I know you can act?
When I'm famous, I'll send you
up here to mend the roof.
What are you doing? Sommersaults?
What are you playing at?
I thought it was the ship's cannon.
You wish! It's only thunder.
Cannon fire is good luck.
Maybe we'll all go
and mine gold in America.
Then we wouldn't have to suffer here.
Country bumpkins... so stupid!
Don't move or you'll spoil it!
Are you ready?
A foreign woman speaking Chinese?
China will be taken over
by foreigners soon.
Wait for me!
- One, two...
- Wait for me!
Wait for you?
It's stuck!
- Foon, where the hell are you?
- I'm changing!
Hurry up! Don't be so lazy!
Foon, you brag about your kung fu.
You can't even climb the roof
to fix something.
You broke the stage
with a somersault.
You show me how to do it
if you're so good.
Miss, I had your dirty clothes
washed and ironed.
Thank you!
- Do you need fresh water?
- No, I'm almost done.
Who is it?
You're naked!
- I'll invite you to our new show.
- Thank you, Boss!
Take care, the path is slippery!
A Chinese pretending
to be a foreigner!
Miss, your umbrella!
Sir, what's your hurry?
Come up,
there are lots of girls here!
It takes so long.
A gunshot! What's the matter?
Who is it?
"Lam Chi Bo"
Master!
It's Wing. Open the door.
You opened the door just in time.
I nearly broke it down!
Have lunch with me sometime.
Excuse me!
- Kai, who's been shot?
- The greengrocer.
- Who shot him?
- I don't know. Ask Master.
Buck Teeth So, if I wasn't here,
you'd have broken that!
Por... ky... Porky...
My name's Wing. Call me Porky
again and I'll get mad.
Back so long and you still
can't speak Chinese.
- Por... ky...
- Bu... ck... Tee... th.
So, bring the medicine.
You can't handle the medicine!
What are you arguing about?
Master, I'm teaching him
how to be Chinese.
Give me The Magic Healer.
- The Magic Healer.
- 3, they're all 3 characters.
Master, you know I can't read!
And you laugh at those
who can't speak Chinese?
Come on, So.
Powder for Seven Cuts.
Blood-Clotting Powder.
So is from America.
He studied medicine there
and learns bone setting here.
Then he must be smart.
- Master, here's the water.
- Finally.
Take a rest, you'll be fine.
Master, this bullet
is from a shotgun.
Let's bandage him.
There are many ships, he can't tell
American and British flags apart.
He boarded the wrong ship
and got shot.
The country's being sold off
piece by piece.
When they argue, it's we who suffer.
We can't accept this kind of
treatment any more!
The Manchurians have taken our land.
Now they join the foreigners
and sell out our country!
Brothers of the Local Militia,
let's fight!
- Ca... ca... calm down!
- You're lecturing me?
Por... ky...
Watch your mouth! I'm your senior!
- Wing!
- Master!
You're too rash. Keep out of this.
This is a matter of life or death.
I must meet with the authorities
and the Westerners.
Otherwise how are we to survive?
- So, you explain to the captain.
- Yes!
How... come... your... English...
is... so... fluent?
Why so many daggers?
So, ask them to bring us
some dim sum.
Foon, your job
is to check tickets today.
I'm here to learn acting not check
tickets. It doesn't suit me.
It can't be helped. The others
have gone to America to mine gold.
America?! Gold mining?
Boss, is there really gold there?
Would I lie to you?
It's all in the newspaper.
I'd go too
if I didn't have to run this place.
Newspaper?! What newspaper?
They're here for protection money.
You haven't paid?
Yes I have,
but these thugs are from Shaho.
How dare they make trouble
so far from their turf?
If they mess with me, they've had it!
- What are you doing?
- I know you know some kung fu.
Didn't you say you
wanted to show off your stuff?
Here's your chance.
Boss, I'm not that good.
They've come to pay their respects
especially to you.
I'm being set up. Stop!
Boss, open the gate!
Boss, open up. Quick!
Oh, there's no daytime show.
No tickets left.
Thank you, Boss,
I'll come another time.
Hey kid, come on down!
I came all this way, and no show.
Next time I won't bother.
I know you're Foon.
You've got something to say?
- I'm just the ticket collector.
- We're the collectors here.
You must be quite a guy...
facing us all alone.
You've got guts!
You must be joking.
Let me buy you a gift.
No need.
No need for gifts,
just give me a hand.
Go on, chop it off.
Chop my hand off?
I'll chop your mother's head off!
Don't go!
Come on!
Me against all of you isn't fair!
Let's fight one on one another time!
Why not now?
Get him! Stop!
Someone's fighting in the theatre.
They're armed!
Stop! Stop! Get him!
Excuse me, excuse me!
- What's happening?
- A fight!
Fight outside,
we're doing business here. Out!
What is it, brother?
They want money,
and they want to fight me for it.
There are too many of them.
Kill that asshole!
- Sounds like trouble.
- Let's take a look.
That's Porky,
one of Wong's disciples.
Never met him.
Porky, out of respect for your master
I'll let you off.
- You're Master Wong's disciple?
- I am!
I saw this young doctor
at Lam Chi Bo.
That Chinese American.
- Foon!
- What?
I'm not kidding,
if you don't bring a hand to Shaho...
they'll be digging
your grave in Fatshan!
Let's go back to Shaho!
What? Turning chicken just
because Wong's disciple is here?
You want a hand?
This pig will donate one!
- Big brother, what shall we do?
- Do? Tear them apart!
Brother Wing. This one's for him!
He can have it for free.
You asshole!
Shaho's stupid, Shaho's dumb...
You want to mess with me?
I'll beat you to death.
Have some refreshments,
enjoy the show!
Take that! Hold it!
Add a little water,
make a perfect brew.
Who's throwing boiling water?
Find him! Go look up there!
Who threw the boiling water?
Out! Go!
You old bastard,
it must have been you!
- No it wasn't. I'm just eating.
- Really?
Wong Fei-Hung, this is General
Wickens of the British forces
and Mr Jackson
of the Sino Pacific Corporation.
They've kindly agreed
not to press charges.
So stop seeking damages
for the greengrocer.
This is unfair.
The people are outraged.
Outraged?!
Wong, you have no authority.
You are a mere civilian.
Who are you to negotiate?
This is a new age
of international cooperation.
It's better to keep the peace.
These rolls are made from our flour.
So you appreciate western food?
The foreigners draw boundaries here
and set up forbidden areas.
If we fight amongst ourselves
and keep bowing to them,
we'll lose more than flour.
I know you are friends with Lau,
Commander of the Black Flag Army.
He doesn't follow orders
from the Central Government.
I've been sent here to watch you.
I intend to set an example
here in Fatshan.
Are you all right?
Master, it's our Local Militia.
Master Wong!
Stop them!
Stop!
Don't fight!
Kai, I told you
to tell them not to fight!
He told you not to fight!
Put down your weapons!
You still want to fight?
Don't move.
- You're not bad!
- Of course!
Boss, that looks like Wong Fei-Hung.
Master Wong Fei-Hung.
He's outnumbered! Let's take him on!
Don't fight!
Did he hit you? Don't fight!
Don't fight, Kai!
I told you not to fight!
I said don't fight!
You're still fighting?!
Are you sure?
They're coming. Let me go!
Boss, are you all right?
- Who kicked me?
- I don't know!
- Have you taken them on?
- Yes, we have!
Carry on!
- Buck Teeth So!
- Stupid!
So, tell them
it's all a misunderstanding.
No need to explain.
If China had no forbidden areas,
we'd all be in danger.
Master, this alien can speak Chinese.
You still want to fight?
Don't call me an alien, you devil!
Listen, we're here to do business.
Don't let this kind of crap
keep us from making big money
Otherwise you'll get yourself
in real trouble.
Goodbye, aliens!
Shoot on sight. Run! Run!
The authorities are here!
Let's get out of here!
Stop! Stay where you are!
Drop your weapons.
Why are the Local Militia fighting?
Where's Porky? Gone?
Don't move or we'll shoot.
Wong, this area's administered
by the foreigners,
yet the Local Militia
dare make trouble here!
You're their leader.
Explain yourself!
Excellency, as trained soldiers,
these men wouldn't act
without a good reason.
Soldiers? They're trash
the government discarded.
They're under our command now.
Excellency...
Tell them report to City Hall,
or get arrested!
Excellency!
Master Wong will pay
for all the damages.
Yes, Your Excellency!
Beware of fire!
Beware of thieves!
Master, I've lost my appetite.
All this trouble was started
by a gang from Shaho.
Now we have to report to City Hall.
Are they going to arrest us?
Master!
Sit down!
City Hall's authorised
to look into this.
If it's a set-up, they'll find out.
So, let's eat.
Until the verdict is known,
this'll be our last meal together.
Let's eat.
Attention, Militia men,
prepare to eat.
Pick up vegetables!
Eat rice!
Swallow!
13th Aunt!
Don't worry, your men will be fine.
It's late, why aren't you sleeping?
I want to take your measurements
for a suit.
A suit?
Why would I want a western suit?
It's for when you go abroad.
13th Aunt, is the West
really so wonderful?
What do we have to learn
from the foreigners?
They invented the steam engine
and many other things.
We must move with the times.
When we have time,
you must tell me more
about the world beyond China.
13th Aunt,
if the western world was so great,
why did you come back?
There are still some things here
they haven't got.
Such as?
People.
I missed some people very much.
I was abroad for two years,
but my heart was here.
You were always in my thoughts.
You are very kind.
- 13th Aunt!
- What's wrong?
I thought... No, it's nothing!
Fei-Hung, you and I
are relatives by name,
not by blood.
We were raised together,
don't call me 13th Aunt.
What else should I call you?
I'll do it.
- What's this? It doesn't matter!
- It doesn't matter?
Of course it does,
one must be precise.
Chinese shouldn't wear suits.
Chinese are Chinese,
Westerners Western.
There will be railways
and a telegraph company soon.
Everything will change.
China will change with the world.
You're right. Western guns
and ships are already here.
Everything is changing.
What will we change into? Who knows?
I appreciate your gift,
but you keep it.
When all Chinese wear suits,
I'll wear one.
Come greet the God of Fortune!
Here I am, the God of Fortune!
Get out of my way, you bloody priest!
Fortune?
Sir, we already bought
the God of Fortune.
Come greet the God of Fortune!
Sir, we already bought
the God of Fortune!
Did you buy protection from me,
or the other guy?
He's rotting in a ditch.
Want to see him?
Just buy a new one!
If I pay him, what happens
when the other guy comes?
- Sir, do you need help?
- You should join us!
- Life is tough right now!
- Give it all
so we can take care of you.
Sir, don't clean me out,
give me a break.
And who'll give me a break?
Hand it over!
Robbing your own people!
It's Master Wong!
You're from Shaho?
Come with me to City Hall.
Save me!
Stabbing your own people?
Get going! Run!
Quick! Run!
Where have you cowards run to?
Damn you!
It's too high!
All right! That's amazing!
Did you see the speed of that kick?
- Did you see it?
- No, it was too fast.
Listen to me. This man is a gangster.
I'm taking him to City Hall.
Please come and testify against him.
Incredible! What a jump!
Boss, he demanded protection money
from you.
- Come with me and be a witness.
- Me?
And fear for my life,
like the theatre boss does?
You two were practising kung fu
in there, I didn't see any fighting.
In America, people
have to walk carefully.
Because they might
trip on all the gold.
- Is that true?
- There's more!
If you wash your face in the river,
you'll find gold.
- Is it really that wonderful?
- Of course it is!
One visit to America is worth
a lifetime of work in China.
Come on, take a leaflet!
There's one for everyone.
People in America wear
dark glasses day and night.
It's so bright it hurts your eyes.
You can't pick up gold
if you're blind.
My poor lost sheep,
God's Kingdom belongs to you.
You're promoting America, too?
Material things are transient.
Only Jesus is the truth.
Come to Jesus. He forgives all sins.
I arrested a criminal today.
Will Jesus be my witness?
Beware of fire.
Beware of thieves.
Boss!
- Boss, are you over there?
- I'm here!
Get ready!
Master! How are you?
Are you crazy? Fans in this weather.
So, the Governor has locked up
the Local Militia?
He won't release them
till the suspects are caught.
Master!
I can't be a witness
because I'm a suspect.
They even let Hung of Shaho go.
When will our men be released?
When a witness comes forward.
Master, what about Foon?
- Foon?! Do you know him?
- Yes.
You must be mixed up in this.
What are you hiding?
I...
Master, you don't always trust me.
So, I...
What? Speak!
Mas... Mas... Master... The... There...
- Calm down, So. Don't panic!
- Master!
So!
Master, what shall we do?
Those arrows came from the roof.
I'm coming!
Never mind me.
Gather... the valuables!
Kai, get your weapon.
We'll take them on.
- Wing, put out the fire. I'm off.
- Alone?
Damn!
So! Here!
Goddamn steps!
His Excellency's fan?! Here it is!
Wow, the roof's like a furnace!
It's like hell down here!
Someone's on the roof. Shoot him!
It's Master Wong. Run!
Lam Chi Bo is on fire!
Lam Chi Bo will be lost forever.
- What are you doing?
- Taking a photo of Lam Chi Bo.
- You'll be burned alive!
- You're blocking the sign!
A little more, I can't see you.
Should we wait for Master?
The... roof... is... is on fire!
So, look this way!
Kai, shift a little to the right.
I thought I had it with me.
But I was taking pictures
of the clinic.
You're just like the foreigners!
Don't ever bring this
into the clinic again...
or I'll throw it away!
His Excellency the Governor is here!
Wong Fei-Hung, you open kung-fu
schools, triad societies...
divide up the town
and run illegal businesses.
Now other triads take revenge...
The burning of Lam Chi Bo
is your own fault.
It's time to mend your ways!
Excellency,
mine is not a triad society.
If the authority
labels martial arts illegal,
then our grand tradition
will be lost.
So when we are attacked,
how will we defend ourselves?
Is that what you call
preserving the peace?
You can't even save your clinic
and you dare lecture me!
It's your job
to investigate the fire.
You tell me, who did it?
I don't know.
You don't know?!
You're hiding something.
Wing!
- Wing, what are you doing?
- Master!
Can I come in?
Foreign devil...!
- Wing!
- Master!
Go on like this,
and you can stop calling me Master.
Don't go.
You must have a complaint
against Fei-Hung. You can tell me.
Wong Fei-Hung,
I know who set Lam Chi Bo on fire.
I can be your witness.
Check if anyone's from Shaho.
- Hey, are you from Shaho.
- No!
So many people!
Boss, looks like
the Governor's going to arrest you.
Goddamn!
That Jesuit must have squealed.
Shouldn't we go and hide back home?
Never! We're afraid of the Governor.
He's afraid of the foreigners.
So let's find some
influential foreigners!
Wait for me.
We want to speak to Mr Jackson.
Damn, we've no English. Try harder.
Please, please let us in
to see Mr Jackson.
We all want to see Mr Jackson.
If I keep a dog,
it'll guard my house.
You are wanted by the Governor.
What good are you to us?
I'm not afraid of being arrested.
But I am afraid that
without a leader,
my brothers' talents
will go to waste.
You came all this way
to make money,
by sending so many Chinese
to America.
Why don't I give you some women
to ship over?
No, we don't allow
the labourers to breed.
Otherwise they'd stay for good.
Not as wives as hookers.
As many as you want.
It's Wong who's the problem.
Dare you kill him for me?
- Master Wong?!
- Yes...
I'll invite him to the show tomorrow.
He won't get out alive.
Wing, the Governor is after
the Shaho Gang.
Foon, where have you been?
I have to go back to the theatre.
Come with me.
- Wait, let me lock up first.
- OK!
- Hey, come out first.
- Oh, right!
This is Wing.
He'll solve all your problems.
Master Wong's students. Welcome!
Don't worry. I'll check the tickets
for you. I like gate duty.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Tickets. Show me your tickets.
Stay in line.
Do you have tickets?
Tickets? Do you know who I am?
Look at the poster.
He's Wonder Ho, I'm White Gent.
And I'm Wing! No ticket? Go!
The show's starting
and you dare tell us to leave?
OK, we'll go, you'll regret this!
We'll go! We'll go!
Tickets...
Brother Wing, let's go in.
- No hurry, the actors aren't here.
- Thank you so much.
Have you seen Wonder Ho
and White Gent?
They tried to barge in,
I told them to piss off.
What? They're the actors!
Then we don't have a show.
You stay here,
I'll go and fetch them.
Tickets...
My Master's coming! I'm out of here!
Excuse me!
- So you accepted the invitation!
- Please!
- 13th Aunt!
- Master Wong!
Why so formal?
Relatives must respect
the rule of seniority.
OK, let's just watch the show!
Please!
Wing, we're in trouble.
Master's here. I don't want to stay.
The actors are gone.
You're going. What'll I do?
- I can sing.
- So what?
I can act a little. Let's go!
You dare sing on stage
in front of your Master?
Who's going to recognise us
with make up on?
OK, let's take a chance.
Come backstage.
Lucky you got us
or the show would be cancelled.
- I'm amazed you recognised me!
- Isn't that Wing?
Who's Wing? Let's go! Come on!
The White Snake is now a Fat Snake.
Porky! Porky!
Hey, Porky Wing's changed profession.
Where will we buy our pork
from now on?
Wing, again!
Nonsense!
I made him do it, don't blame him.
Pack up and never come back.
Brother Wing, I'll join you
in the pork business.
Watch out!
Get down!
Seal all exits!
- Lead the foreigners out.
- Yes, sir!
There's fighting outside.
Foon, it must be the Shaho Gang.
Go after them!
13th Aunt!
Stop it!
Don't shoot at the audience.
Don't shoot!
Son...
Limestone powder. Close your eyes.
Stay down!
It's not Wong? Forget him!
Protect His Excellency!
Come on.
Gun!
Take cover.
13th Aunt, take the gun
and protect the reverend.
They're here for me. Keep away!
Master, take the pole!
Master, I'll help you!
The floor's too thin.