This is Salvage One!
We have secured the Sleeper sample,
but we're going to need
some additional support
to clear the Blue
from our escape route!
Salvage One we've got
our hands full down here!
Just leave the fighting
to the Armor Shrikes
and get the hell out of there now!
Copy that!
We'll move the Sleeper to the
recon point and meet you there!
Over!
I'm picking up some
bionoise at 10 o'clock!
Get ready!
Hey! Hey!
Don't touch me!
Please don't!
Salvage One! What's going on?
Report in at once!
The Sleeper is out of his
capsule and is now on the run.
What the hell?
Dammit! Go get him!
Yes sir! I'm in pursuit!
He won't get away!
This can't be? It can't!
None of this is real!
It's insane!
Stay back!
G-go away! Please go away!
So Sleeper, how the
hell did you wake up?
I don't want you to
cause me any more trouble.
So unless you'd rather die,
you will follow my orders.
Hey Marlene, need a hand!
Keith! Joey!
Yeah!
Hey, I got something for ya!
Come and get it!
That's enough Keith!
Leave the rest to Bull's Eye!
Now run!
Let's move out!
But leave 'em a present!
Copy that!
What are you doing?
Get in the jeep now!
Hey! How long was
I in that capsule?
I figure that it has to
be at least a year or two.
This may come as a shock to you,
but the year is 2031.
And that means that
it's been 22 years
since you Sleepers first
went into those capsules.
Wow? That long huh?
Those things back there!
They killed everyone but me?
Are you sure?
Maybe we should go back
and look for survivors?
That facility is really big!
There could be more people
like me all over the place!
Dammit! I want to know
where you're taking me!
His name is Yuji Kaido.
He was born in 1992.
Says his sleep treatment
began in 2009.
I heard that those Sleepers came down
with some kind of viral infection.
That's right!
They called it the Prophecy Syndrome.
The subjects went crazy and began
speaking all kinds of nonsense.
They claimed to be haunted by visions.
But why start moving them now
after they've been sitting
on the surface for so long?
I have no idea.
It's been a lot of trouble
retrieving these Sleepers.
I damn sure hope it's worth it.
It better be!
So, how's our Sleeper doing?
This may be hard to believe,
but I'm from the same
generation as you.
Yeah. Back then,
we lived the good life.
Then the Blue...
They changed everything
for us here on the planet.
Mankind has lived in terror
ever since their arrival.
The Blue?
That's what those creatures are called!
They've destroyed the civilization
that you once knew by devouring it.
The population that remains
has been forced into space.
As you've seen for yourself,
the Earth has become a
very hostile environment.
Those Blue creatures have
eaten away everything?
So it's all gone?
Everything I knew... It's gone?
This is Tokyo 22 years later?
So much has changed,
but to me it feels like
only one night has passed.
It's like a bad dream
that I can't wake up from.
And if this is the way things are
then I wish they never found me.
Where are we?
It's a spaceport.
They've become more common
since you went to sleep.
So you mean we're going into space?
That's right!
We have a base in orbit
from which we run our operations!
You mean a space station?
What're those?
Sleepers like you recovered
from other areas...
Only they haven't woken up.
There were a number of facilities
all over the country!
Stop!
Hey! Come back!
I'm not the only one! I'm not
the only one that survived!
Move out!
What's that?!
What's going on up there?
My god!
All Armor Shrikes on deck!
The Blue are invading!
They're coming up
through the ground!
Malcolm! Come on!
Get me over there!
No! I have to wake the others up!
Somebody! Smash its neuro-point!
Hurry!
Keith! What the hell
are you waiting for?
Hold it steady!
I'm going to shove our arm
so far up that bug's ass
it explodes!
Wake up! C'mon wake up!
You gotta wake up in there
or you'll all be killed!
Stop it or you're gonna be
the one that gets killed!
You don't understand!
We've got to wake them up!
Please! I can't go
through this hell alone!
Wake up! Please wake up!
You've got to stop this.
It's hopeless.
There's no way to
resusitate them down here!
Get in!
I'm picking up a lot of
bionoise on the scanner!
Get to the shuttle!
Wait! We've got to bring
the other Sleepers with us!
No!
Damn them!
Damn this world!
Damn it all!
Training?
Just enough for me to
look after myself down here.
I want to try and
help out if I can.
I don't want to be
a burden to anyone.
You gotta train me!
No way!
But why not?
My duty is to deliver
you to Second Earth.
And I intend to see
you get there alive.
I will not let you
jeopardize this mission.
We've lost the other
recovered Sleepers,
and you're our only
surviving sample.
Sample?
Hey Marlene...
Keith and Malcolm are dead,
and Robert's wounded.
That leaves the two of
us to pick up the slack.
Bringing on an extra pair of
hands might not be a bad idea.
I mean it's not like
we can't use the help!
If I teach Yuji to
drive the Armor Shrike,
and you teach him to shoot,
in a few days we might be
able to use him in combat.
I refuse to die
without a fight! Teach me!
All right, but you have three days!
Sure, it's a deal.
Let's get to work!
There! That's better!
The idea is to get close enough
to the Blue to use the grappler arms.
But don't forget they won't
exactly be sitting still,
so pay attention.
Let's go!
Damn that was fast!
Hey, ease up on the controls!
Right!
That's wrong!
You're too stiff.
Try keeping your right elbow bent.
That way your left
hand will be steadier.
Keep your eyes focused.
Concentrate!
We hit it!
I think you've got a knack for this!
Bionoise detected!
Confirm the enemy's number!
I'm reading three, no four!
I'm reading four of them!
Intercept! Marlene I want you
to assume tactical command!
I just took out one of the flying Blue.
I'll go get the other
two then I'll come up
and help you finish off the last one!
Until then, keep it occupied.
You got it!
Yuji don't do anything stupid!
Okay! Okay! I got it!
Come on!
Where the hell are they hiding?
Come out! Come out and show yourself,
you monsters!
Yuji! Hey Yuji!
Try to relax, but keep your eyes open!
The... The Blue!
Where the hell is it?
Yuji! Above us!
Yuji!
Go on! Blast it Yuji!
Oh god! It's right on top of me!
Come on! Blast that thing!
Yuji! Ready yourself!
If we keep going at this pace,
we should arrive at the
Korean Coast sometime tomorrow.
Have you made contact
with the recovery squad?
Unfortunately, there's
been no response sir.
I see.
You know, after all
the Blue we've seen,
I doubt there's much left
of the Korean recovery squad!
Joey! Stop right here!
We won't make it over
the bridge in this.
Joey! Take him!
Yuji stop!
Where did she go?
My god!
Hey! Hello?!
What's going on here?
Wait! Hold on.
Hey, don't run away from me.
I'm just like you.
I'm not one of those monsters.
Maru!
Oh? Maru! So that's
your name, is it boy?
Yeah I know, I'm glad
to be alive too!
Yung! Stay away from
this guy! Ya hear me?
But Daddy, I think this nice man
came here to kill all the monsters!
No! You know better.
You can't count on the
people from Second Earth.
They could care less about you
or me or anybody else down here!
So pal, don't try and
tell me you've come here
to take pity on us worthless folk!
What? Why are you
looking at me like that?
I just wanted...
I wanted to help.
Who the hell gave you
permission to go off on your own?
But you don't understand.
There are still
survivors in this city!
They're been keeping themselves
alive by their own means,
but they could use our help.
If we don't do something,
they're not going to make it!
You know they all hate us, don't you?
Look, it's time for you to face
the reality we're living in!
When the Blue took over the planet,
mankind was forced to
make some tough decisions.
The survival of our species
has come at a cost!
Only the intellectuals,
the problem solvers,
and the military minded
were taken into space
and enlisted to fight the Blue.
And the others...
The weak and the sick had
to fend for themselves.
It's the only way we could survive.
Yeah? Well that sounds more
like selective genocide to me!
No Yuji, you've forgotten this
is a different time and place.
Don't you see? There is no other way.
This is a life and death struggle
between the human race and the Blue.
And those who can't fight
don't deserve to survive.
If that's what you believe,
then I'd rather stay here than go
to Second Earth with people like you!
I'm a free man! I don't need
your permission to do anything!
Those who can't fight
don't deserve to survive?
Hey boy!
Yung?
Here.
Know what mister?
You're different from
all those other soldiers.
Like Marlene.
Well, that's because I'm from a
different time than they are Yung!
I was asleep for a long time.
But that was long
before you were born.
Back then I had hope
for the future.
But the future doesn't look
so bright these days does it?
I wish I could go
to sleep for a long time.
I bet you when you're asleep
the monsters can't get you!
Yung, don't worry.
No matter what happens,
I'm gonna protect you!
You will?
Hey, I'm your friend right?
You know you can't do a
thing for that little girl.
Damned liar!
This is a very dangerous area.
We have no way of knowing
when the Blue will come ashore!
What do you think we should do?
The closest shuttle launch
site is far away in Russia.
It's at Baikonur. We could go there.
By my estimation, it's at least 5000
kilometers that we'll have to cover.
Oh great! By the time
we get to Baikonur,
I bet the recovery squad will already
have left for Second Earth without us.
We've got no choice.
We have to keep going.
Our orders are to get the
Sleeper on board a shuttle
to Second Earth at any cost!
So we're going to sneak away
and abandon those people?
You're way out of line!
Even if we wanted to, we don't have
the extra resources to waste on them.
I'm afraid Marlene's right, Yuji.
They'll have to make it on their own.
The Blue will start
gathering on this island,
and we don't have the fire power
to save anybody but ourselves!
Well, if that's the situation,
can't we save the girl?
So you're saying that she's the
only one worthy of being saved?
Dammit! Hang on everyone!
We've got company!
Give me a hand up here!
Let's get this done people!
We don't have any time to waste!
Understood!
Alright here we go!
Joey! Get out of there!
Marlene!
Marlene...
Joey...
Pull yourself together!
You've got to be tough!
It's just going to be the
two of us from here on out.
We're going to move on,
to Baikonur base.
I intend to complete my
mission no matter what.
Do you understand?
What's wrong with you?
If you don't like what happened
in Seoul then just say so!
What happened in your life
that made you so cold?
They're all dead!
Joey, Robert and Yung!
And we couldn't do a
thing to save them,
and somehow that doesn't
bother you at all?
It doesn't bother you in the slightest
that your own people died
right in front of your eyes?
How can you think nothing of it?
What's wrong with you?
All over this planet,
people die every day.
And I've gotten used to it.
You bitch!
Are you even human?
Yeah, I'm human.
Yuji wake up! You're lucky!
You've come this far and you're alive!
Now don't push your luck.
Down here only the strong survive,
and to hell with the rest of them!
That's just the way it is!
If you're weak, you're no good
to anyone and you deserve to die?
You're right about one thing...
There is no humanity
left in this world!
I can hardly wait
to meet your superiors!
I'll thank them personally
for sparing my life!
I bet they're no better than the Blue!
All right, do you want me
to end this right now?
"The Sleeper took ill and died"
That's all I'll have
to put in my report.
My god! Yung!
Oh no, the Blue are here?
Oh my god!
Stay away you monsters!
I'll kill you all!
Yuji!
You should try and sleep.
Marlene, what happened?
Yuji...
Yeah?
The human race is almost extinct.
Civilization as you know
it is a thing of the past!
There isn't any room left for
sympathy towards others anymore.
Try to survive.
That's all you can do.
Turn your hatred for the Blue
into a passion for staying alive.
The past is gone Yuji.
You have to let it go!
I'm trying.
It's hard 'cause I know something
better is alive down here.
Even in you.
Yuji, I'm just doing my duty.
Yeah, somehow I knew you
were going to say that!
Marlene, you've grown up knowing
that you could die at any moment.
So I know it's hard for you
to show your true feelings.
But I think deep down inside,
you and I are alike.
It's hard for me to explain.
But when I found out I was sick,
that's when I realized
how precious life is.
And after all we've
been through together,
I feel it even more.
You must feel the same way.
Marlene, there must be a reason
why you and I are both here.
I know, there has to be.
Yuji.
What is it?
You still have a very good chance
of surviving your illness.
And if you don't want
to go to Second Earth,
then I won't force you.
I'll just change my report.
I'll say that you were killed
in a surprise attack by the Blue.
What made you change your mind?
I just want to give you
a chance to live the life
that you feel you're entitled too.
It's that simple.
Marlene!
Are you all right?
That was a close call.
I guess I owe you one, huh?
The thin air up here must be
starting to affect my judgement.
Hey, it's okay. I know that you
would have done the same for me.
You don't owe me anything.
This is all about survival,
and I'm going to take your advice
and do my best to
stay alive from now on.
I still don't
understand this world,
but I'm ready to leave my
past behind and move on.
So let's go.
If we waste time, we'll miss
our ride to Second Earth.
Come on!
You want to get past these
guys you gotta cut the power!
Oh by the way,
welcome to Baikonur space base!
There's a lot of Blue out there!
Don't worry!
The automatons will take care of them.
Unfortunately we've discovered an
abnormality in their A.I. programming.
As you found out for yourself,
for some reason they
can't tell the difference
between a human and the Blue!
Because of this glitch
we've had a hell of a time
getting to the shuttle
base's central area.
Luckily they've continued
fighting the Blue
that are nesting in
the surrounding facilities.
We're going to make another
attempt at launching the shuttle,
but we'll need to double the
strength of our advance team.
Time is running out, so we're
going to initiate an attack
on the Blue Nest ourselves!
Second Earth. Wow, I'm
actually going into space.
I wonder what's gonna happen
to me when I get there?
Yuji? What are you doing up?
I can't fall sleep.
You'll need your rest.
Tomorrow is gonna be tough.
If you're out here, the mission
briefing must be finished.
If it's not too much trouble,
do you mind filling
me in on the details?
An advance party will move in first,
attack the Blue, and smoke them out.
And then the next team moves in.
Their job is to debug the system
and get the automatons back on line.
Once that's done,
we'll move on to the shuttle.
That's our mission.
That's it? It sounds
like suicide to me!
As long as there is even
a slight chance of success,
we do as we're ordered.
That's what a soldier does, okay?
Yuji, our future depends on tomorrow.
Marlene.
Yeah, what is it?
Is there anything I
can do to help out?
No, we're okay here.
There's got to be
something I can do!
Let me help!
Listen, why don't you
just try and relax?
The journey here took a lot out
of both of us, but we made it.
And now everything is under control.
You're the reason
we're doing this Yuji.
This mission is all about you.
All units prepare for departure!
Here! Take this with you.
Before I went into sleep treatment,
a friend of mine gave it to me.
He said this would
bring me good luck.
I know it seems silly,
but take it with you anyway.
It's given me good luck so far,
so maybe it will do
the same for you!
No you should keep it,
maybe it's only good luck for you.
I'll see you when I get back.
Marlene...
Take care, and
please come back...
Alive...
Decoy One, I'll blast the Blue's Nest.
Decoy Two, you take the point
and keep an eye out for any attackers.
Copy. Decoy One out!
The advance team is nearing
the fourth barracks.
They're about to
commence the attack.
First strike complete!
Get out of there!
The Blue are coming out
of the 4th barracks.
They're in pursuit!
They will be within the attackers
effective perimeter in 90 seconds!
Decoy One, we're going
to begin our advance.
I want you to stand by in Sector 2.
Here they come!
The automatons are
nearing the perimeter!
The invasion route is clear!
Move out!
I expected to find the
power here operational,
but this is almost
too good to be true.
This should make it easier
to gain access to the shuttle!
Commander! Look!
Watch yourselves!
Those things are still programmed
for regular operations.
They will shoot to kill!
Unauthorized personnel are
not permitted in this area.
Withdraw immediately.
If you do not comply
with these instructions,
you will be forcibly
removed from this base.
Withdraw immediately. Withdraw...
Fire!
Han, get the control
system back on line
and run a diagnostic check!
After that, I want you to
debug those automatons!
Yes sir!
Can't you go any faster?
Back off. What I'm trying
to do is way over your head.
So get lost!
Hey? What?
I thought I told you
to stay out of the way kid!
Now let Han do his job!
Listen if you really want to
help your girlfriend out there
then keep your mouth shut and
maybe you might learn a thing or two.
Okay! The automatons
have been debugged.
All right! Let's prep the
shuttle for lift-off operations!
Thank god.
Okay! Let's finish these guys off!
Recall the advance
divisions to the shuttle!
They should be about done out there.
Let's pick up the pace a little!
Huh? What's that?!
Hit the emergency power!
Malfunction! Aw, dammit!
Base electrical supply
down 60 percent.
Launch procedures must be aborted!
That's impossible!
Huh?! What?
I'm detecting some
underground bionoise!
It's moving slow,
but it's getting closer!
There's a lot of them!
Evacuation code confirmed!
All units assume defensive positions
and return to base immediately!
That's strange, why would they
all of a sudden stop like that?
Something's wrong.
We got a large group of Blue
900 meters from the base perimeter!
Then order the advance team
to move in and eliminate them!
It's no use!
There are too many of them
and they've got us surrounded!
If we make one wrong move,
we could lead a whole horde of Blue
right into the launch center!
So what you're saying is the advance
team is on its own out there?
Dammit! There's too many of them!
Where the hell did they come from?
All right soldiers!
We're launching the shuttle!
Switch to manual control
and start the countdown!
Wait! You can't do that!
The advance team is still out there!
We'll have to abandon them!
What'd you say?
We have to lift off
before the Blue get here!
It's unfortunate,
but we have to do it!
I'm sorry there's no other way.
Minh! What's wrong!
It's too dangerous to try a
shuttle launch right now sir.
I think it would be safer
to secure a defensive line
against the Blue
and hold our ground.
Listen! I give the
orders around here!
You just get that shuttle ready!
Understand?
Stay here!
I'm gonna go out there
and help them!
No you're not!
Let's make a deal!
- I'll stop the incoming Blue, and you
wait for the advance team to come back.
- Do you think I'm a fool?
In the first place,
you're a Sleeper!
Secondly, you might
think you can fight,
but you have no idea what
you'll be up against out there!
So you stay right by my side!
Your little taste of combat
is nothing compared to this!
You let the professionals
handle this one!
I want you to sit tight
and do exactly what I say! Got it?
Now you listen to me old man!
You can't tell me what to do!
You got it?
I'm not going to Second Earth
just so you can claim me
as some kind of prize!
I'm going for Marlene!
You might think she's expendable,
but I sure don't!
Sleeper! Go!
There's an Armor Shrike
loaded on the trailer.
Go get the Blue!
Move! Now's your opportunity,
but remember you've
only got five minutes!
Damn you Han!
Disobeying orders is a serious offense!
I believe giving irrational orders
is also a serious offense.
I'm not trying to undermine
your authority sir,
but our first priority should be to
keep the Blue away from the shuttle.
When the advance team returns,
we'll be able to safely blast off.
Very well, but when
we get to Second Earth
there's going to be a court martial!
I guarantee it!
If we get there, that is.
Go to hell!
Get off of me,
you insect bastard!
Decoy One! Can you hear me?
I'm gonna take out as many of these
oversized cockroaches as I can!
This is your chance
to get to the shuttle!
Now get out of here!
The shuttle!
Scott! Hang on!
Please god,
don't let this be in vain!
No, it can't be!
Marlene...
Where are you?
Why won't you respond?
What? Look at the
size of that thing.
I've never seen a
Blue that big before!
Oh god!
D'you see that?
It's huge!
All right!
Yeah, come on!
The shuttle is ready sir!
Should I initiate
the launch sequence?
No! Not yet! We take off
when I give the order soldier!
We can't leave until we get
that Sleeper on board!
I guess, you saved
my life again huh?
Like I told you, no matter what happens
I'm taking you into space with me!
You did good out there, kid!
Once we get to Second Earth
I'll buy you a drink!
This is the commander of
the European recovery squad.
We are en route from
Baikonur launch site.
On board are the surviving members
of my team and one Sleeper.
E.T.A. to Second Earth Space Station
is approximately ten minutes.
Request a medical team
upon our arrival. Over!
Yuji...
Look at the Earth.
I'm here...
I'm actually in outer space.
How strange.
You know if I hadn't gotten sick,
I would never have seen this view.
Um, Marlene!
Please take this,
I want you to have it now.
Maybe it will remind you of
the time we spent together.
Please take it.
I won't be fighting anymore
so I want you to have it.
Okay?
Yuji...
Marlene...
Are you okay?
No!
Please save him!
Please...
Yuji...
Time has passed by so quickly.
It's been two months since we
arrived here on Second Earth.
During that time they've kept a
close eye on everything I've done.
Maybe I deserve all
this surveillance.
After all a Sleeper was injured
because I let my guard down.
And I haven't seen Yuji since then.
I mean, I haven't been
allowed to see him.
I have no idea what condition he's in.
I was brought before a court martial,
and my movement on the base
has been tightly restricted.
My military career is worthless,
and now I'm back where I started.
In order to maintain my rank,
I've been required to go through
an intensive retraining program.
All personnel! Saddle up!
Unfortunately,
the poor results of my most
recent battle excercise
gave them the excuse they needed to
suspend my Special A pilot certification.
Marlene Angel!
Your responses are way too slow!
Why did you hesitate? Take the
shot when it presents itself.
If you would have fired
through the groundling
in front of the Blue's core
you would have hit your target.
Decide what's more important,
the groundlings or the
success of your mission!
It doesn't seem to
matter to my superiors
that on my last tour of
Earth I went through hell.
I can't get Yuji
out of my mind.
I wonder where he is,
what he's doing.
I wish I could talk to him,
just one more time.
Look at that.
It's like it's trying to fuse
completely with the body!
It's evolution has accelerated!
Professor Miyagi,
we've transferred the
Sleeper you requested
out of the intensive care unit.
And that would be the sample
that unexpectedly woke up
in his sleep capsule
back on Earth?
That's correct sir!
Put him in the regulation room.
I'll go get the data
for the new Armor Shrike.
Yes sir!
For your sake, you had
better not fail me.
Sleeper...
Earth, it looks so
beautiful from here.
I wonder if they'll ever
let me go back there again,
or if I'll be spending the
rest of my days in this place.
It doesn't seem like this good
luck charm has any left in it for me.
I should have never
taken it from him!
There's no problem here.
I'll return to my station.
Hear me? I'll return to my station!
No! Don't leave me in here!
The room is full of them!
Let me out! Please let me out!
Uh! The bugs are everywhere!
Get them away from me!
They're going to get me!
Doctor, a problem sir!
One of the Sleepers tried to commit
suicide by chewing through his wrists,
so we put him in lockdown.
I think you should take a
look inside the room sir?
Gentlemen, I assure you this
new technology will work!
And what happens if it doesn't, Miyagi?
You expect us to believe
that this Sleeper Brigade
will give us the military advantage
we need to defeat the Blue?
We're running out of options.
We all know our current
military force is dwindling,
and the Blue have
gained the upper hand.
And a full scale nuclear
attack is out of the question.
That would leave the Earth
uninhabitable for centuries.
I know a way that we
can win this war,
a way to use those suffering
from the prophecy syndrome
to help us take back our planet.
I've prepared this demonstration.
This is the modified Armor Shrike
developed exclusively for Sleeper use.
The Mega-blade is synchronized
with the pilot's nervous system.
Interpreting the
Sleeper's thought patterns.
The prophecy syndrome is
a result of the B cells
that inhabit a Sleeper's body.
These cells act like antibodies
when the host comes under attack,
destroying the perceived threat.
Right! That's interesting but
there's still no way of knowing
how effective these Sleepers
will be on the battlefield!
By harnessing the
Sleeper's nervous system
to the Armor Shrike we have the ability
to activate the B cells at any time.
This will increase the subject's
perception and reflexes
and cause them to focus their
rage on our enemy, the Blue.
It's a perfect union
between man and machine,
and with it we can not lose!
You must never forget the
humiliation the Blue have caused us!
They have destroyed our homes
and taken everything from us!
Even as I speak, those disgusting
creatures are moving across the Earth.
I've heard some of you
in the barracks say
those things are demons
that crawled out of hell!
Well, you're wrong!
They're nothing more than insects!
Insects that must be exterminated!
And this battle will
make those pests realize
once and for all that
we are the superior species!
We will take control of
the Earth once again!
Onward fighters!
- Don't stop until you have eradicated
every last Blue from our planet!
- Alpha 1, launch.
That is your mission!
The fate of humanity is in your hands!
Glory goes with you!
Death to the Blue!
Alpha 2, you are clear
to go for launch.
Zaire! Tanzania! Gambia!
Landing operations are
proceeding as scheduled!
Control! This is the
Nest Demolition Corps.
We are 8000 meters
from the Nest entrance.
We are under attack
by a new type of Blue!
Request immediate reinforcements!
Move out!
Dammit! It's like
a maze in here!
Where the hell are
those reinforcements?
What's wrong?
There's a great deal of
bionoise ahead but uh...
What is it?
Well, everything is still.
I'm not reading any
motion on the scanner.
All right then, proceed slowly.
Holy shit!
Are those eggs?
What the hell?
Yeah, I think so.
You know, if this is the
Blues' spawning ground,
then I bet that the queen
must be around here somewhere!
I've lost an engine!
I guess you win.
Come on, do it!
Uh, wait!
This is Rick Ferguson of
the reconnaissance patrols,
somebody come in please!
Can you hear me!
Yes, its Marlene Angel!
There was some intense somatic magnetism
making communication impossible!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Look, I've set a bomb in
the Blue's spawning ground.
I'll meet you out front okay?
Okay.
I guess we got lucky.
Looks like we won this one.
I'm The Rick. I was
in the Nest with you.
Rick, have you ever
seen an Armor Shrike
with a Mega-blade attachment?
No, is it some kind of prototype?
I don't know.
If you ask me, it sounds like somebody's
been doing their own modifications.
Hey! Enough shop talk!
You free tonight?
I don't think so!
That was no ordinary soldier
inside that Armor Shrike.
A group of Blue have escaped into the
jungle from the demolished nest sight.
All units maintain your positions
and if you make contact fire at will!
It's so quiet.
It's as if there's no
life left in this jungle.
The Blue!
Huh?
What are children doing way out here?
Wait.
Stay in your Shrike!
We're on a mission remember?
Don't worry, I'm a friend.
Don't be afraid.
Are there any others here?
If there are, can you tell
me where they're at?
I see.
Here they come!
Hold your fire there
are humans out there!
You hold your fire!
What's wrong?
Can't you hear me?
They're everywhere!
What's wrong with you?
Stop it!
You bastard!
What? Are going to kill me too!
Stand down! What is your problem?
I'm unstoppable!
Yuji!
My god, Yuji!
Have you forgotten me? It's Marlene!
Marlene?
It's me! Answer me Yuji!
Yuji!
We're nearly at
the drop off point.
All pilots set your Armor Shrikes
to camouflage mode for urban warfare.
Upon completion of this
mission in the American district,
this division will be
returning to Second Earth.
In other words,
this will be your last fight!
Your job is to demolish the
largest nest in North America!
Do it! Destroy the Blue!
My god! Is that the Sleeper brigade?
The Sleepers have really
turned this war around!
Yes! Nothing can stop us now!
Soon we'll all be able
to return to Earth!
And a dark chapter of our
history will soon be over!
Yes, it's all played out
just as I predicted.
We've taken the Earth
back from the Blue.
But what difference will it make?
As far as I'm concerned mankind deserves
to stay in this giant coffin in space.
Where the hell are they?
Hang on, I'm coming!
Yuji...
Yuji!
You, you're Yuji Kaido right?
Answer me! You know me!
It's Marlene Angel!
Marlene?
The Earth...
The Earth is infested.
Humans are the same as the Blue.
They're both cancers that
are eating away this planet!
What the hell happened to
you on Second Earth Yuji?
What did they do to you
to make you act so insane?
Please tell me!
If there's any way
I can help you, I will!
Humans, the Blue...
They are both the enemy!
Come on, don't just sit there!
Hurry up and kill them, dammit!
Oh my god!
There's too many of them!
They're gonna kill us all! No!
What's that?
Yuji...
That's it, come and get
me you insect bastards!
I hope this still has
some luck left in it.
I'm the only one who can
rid the world of its cancer!
Remember Yuji...
Please remember...
Yuji!
Remember!
Marlene...
Yuji...
Can you hear me Yuji?
It's me, it's Marlene.
Do you remember?
Yuji...
Please don't leave me here.
Stay with me Yuji...
Please don't go Yuji.
I need you.
I knew all along that
the prophecy syndrome
was capable of stimulating
the Sleepers battle instincts,
but I refused to accept the fact
that it would cause them
to breakdown mentally.
I can't ignore it anymore.
I'm responsible for
all this suffering.
I'm no better than a mother
who abandons a child in need.
The Blue?!
I'm sorry Yuji.
I won't be able to
save you this time.
Please forgive me.
Yuji... Yuji...
What? The Blue...
They're gone.
Thank you, Marlene...
Seeking out a single ray of light
All I can do is wander on, no matter
how far, through the darkness
Clinging to a heart that is
governed by sorrow, and yet
As I breathe a sigh not unlike surrender
I don't want to fear
being hurt, all the time
Set me free now
Come on, let it all go,
to the far reaches of time,
From that which binds the soul
For my heartbeat
Make freedom your weapon,
and you are sure to attain it
The power to believe and dream is there
For you to go on living
From deep within your heart, you try
to call out, but the cry reaches no one
You have to keep on putting it into words
These chains that we call fate
bind us hand and foot, while you
Vaguely lament over the
weaknesses you have now
But unless you try to become strong,
you'll never change
Set you free now
Come on, let it all go,
while your heartbeat runs hot,
From everything that stands in your way
For your heartbeat
Even more than memories,
the future brightly shines,
To reunite you with the one
you love more than any other
Come on, let it all go,
to the far reaches of time,
From that which binds the soul
For my heartbeat
Make freedom your weapon,
and you are sure to attain it
The power to believe and dream is there
For you to go on living
Set me free now