Ask Wong to come in.
Feeling better?
Mr Wong, Dr Sun would like you
to help him.
- Where is he?
- He's in the reception hall.
OK, lead the way.
He said thank you. He's never seen
anything like this. He's amazed.
Not at all, saving lives
is what matters.
- What's happening?
- Aunt Yee, don't! Stay with me.
I won't leave you.
The children!
Watch out, Mr Luke. Get down.
The army have closed Telegraph House.
We've lost contact with Hong Kong.
Are we still going ahead
with our plans?
It's too risky.
We'd better lay low for now.
Let's split up and tell the others.
The telex at the consulate
is the only way we can contact them.
Mr Luke, you know
how to send a telex.
Stay here and keep contact
with the outside world.
- Sun, I...
- I've taken care of your family.
I'll go back to the villa now,
and then go on to the wedding.
If you don't get a message from me...
take the boat to Hong Kong
tomorrow morning.
Don't be late.
Take my watch with you.
If I fail...
carry on the fight.
I will.
- Dr Sun, are you leaving?
- I've got something to do.
- I'll see you out.
- Thank you.
- Stay here.
- Be careful, Fei-hung.
The White Lotus Sect will drive
the foreigners out!
Dr Sun, how will you get out?
It's easier to save men
than their country.
It seems my medical case and I
can't save them all.
Get them out of here!
Get out of here! Go!
See you later, Master Wong.
Sir, we just want
to expel the foreigners.
We wouldn't kill our own people.
I'm glad to hear it.
Leave the negotiating to us.
If you were so capable,
we wouldn't have lost so much land.
It's all your fault!
If you continue to make trouble,
I'll arrest you all.
- Take the altar away.
- Yes, sir.
General Lan is here, make way.
I see Mr Luke is hiding here as well.
Mr Luke.
- Let's go!
- Yes, sir.
- Sam Fok.
- Sir?
Cut the wire pole down.
I want to stop all communications.
An army without information
is a dead army.
As soldiers we are men of the world.
We must do what is best.
Sir...
- I know. Just follow my orders.
- Yes, sir.
Carry out the General's instructions.
Go on.
The British are trying to divide us.
Pick up the altar!
Let's go.
If you are all up for this,
let's practise some kung fu.
Once you have your stance, don't
move. This is the Hanging Horse.
One move and you're steady as a rock.
This stance brings unlimited power.
Perform the Unicorn Move.
Third move...
Hold the head, grab the hand, twist!
Watch carefully!
Return to your original position.
And again!
Not bad. Hold that stance
for two hours.
Foon!
Hold the head, grab the hand,
then twist... what do you do with it?
Grappling Hand?
Yes, I've learned it,
but I don't know how to use it.
That's easy. I'll attack
and you counter attack.
- Watch.
- OK.
Is it this way?
It doesn't feel right.
Foon, what are you doing?
Why are you holding Aunt Yee?
- I'm teaching her Grappling Hand.
- You teach her?
Do you think I can't teach her?
It's not right for you
to hold Aunt Yee. Knee bends, now!
- Master, I...
- Now!
Stop looking at me.
Carry on!
I'm going, Master.
What are you doing?
The stance.
That's not the way!
Fei-hung, don't be angry with Foon,
I asked him to teach me.
You did?
Why don't you ask him to come back?
Go on, then.
I'm punished for this? What would
happen if I taught her the Bear Hug?
These foreigners are really lazy!
If White Lotus came,
you'd be a goner.
Trying to scare me?
Wait for her to come down.
Mr Luke.
Have you seen Foon?
- White Lotus?!
- Help!
White Lotus is here!
They're here!
Wind and fire come together.
Kill all foreigners.
White Lotus, saviour of the world.
Eradicate all evil!
Go and hide and don't come out.
I'll be right back.
OK, come back soon.
Come on, come on.
- Who is that? Mr Luke?
- Yes.
- Upstairs.
- You go first.
- General...
- Be quiet.
Now you'll die, you little brats!
The stance!
Foon, tie them up.
I'll see if there are any left.
- Arrest them, go!
- Yes, sir.
Arrest the White Lotus.
Leave!
- What are you looking at?
- They are fighting.
Fei-hung, General Lan
killed the consul!
Don't move!
- Search everywhere!
- Yes, sir.
Nothing over here.
- Tell Sun to run for his life.
- OK.
I know you look on me as your aunt...
but you're the one for me
in my heart.
If we lose each other...
come and find me.
It's time to go.
Whatever happens,
we must survive this night...
so that future generations
can see a new dawn.
Do you understand?
Foon, you pretend to be Mr Luke
and distract the soldiers.
If you can, find the name-book
in the market for Mr Luke.
I will.
Leung Foon, take this watch.
Meet me at the pier at seven am.
It's down to you now.
Siu-qun.
You said my name!
It's the first time you've done that.
Who are you?
I'm the interpreter
from the consulate, sir.
Go on, then.
Foon, go now.
Mr Luke! Mr Luke!
- Mr Luke?!
- After him!
- General.
- Wong Fei-hung.
Sir, I want to destroy their leader.
That way I destroy the whole sect.
And who's that?
Foon, come and meet the General.
Sir.
He was injured by the White Lotus.
Sir, we can't predict
what might happen.
Please take care of the children.
OK, I promise you.
Thank you.
- Escort Master Wong to the temple.
- Yes, sir.
White Lotus, I want to join you.
The White Lotus Sect welcomes you,
our guests.
Master Wong, there are so many
soldiers, how can we escape?
The temple is so big, we can just
disappear. I'm sure we can get out.
Under the incense,
long live the White Lotus Sect.
Is it safe in there?
Don't worry, just relax.
- Anyway, we can't go back now.
- Let's go in, then.
The Goddess comes to save all people.
White Lotus will free the poor.
Our sect brings peace to the world.
Prepare for our initiates.
Kneel!
Wong Fei-hung, Leung Foon,
come to the altar.
Come forward to be purified.
Let the ceremony begin.
Swallow the lucky token,
become a child of the sect.
We are all brothers.
We share a common bond -
for better or for worse,
for richer or for poorer -
all are equal.
Drink this
and you'll be a member forever.
May lightning strike down
all those who betray us.
Master!
Be loyal before God. Drink it!
God in heaven, devils below.
Protected by God,
nothing can harm me -
A thousand knives are deflected.
A million blades are deflected.
The body is now as strong as iron.
Nothing can penetrate!
Master Wong!
Kill him now!
Seek the power within!
Wong Fei-hung,
how dare you make trouble here!
Priest Gao Kung's name is famous.
But I need to see him
before joining the sect.
I need to see him now!
We won't let you see
his righteousness!
You won't?
I'll fight my way in, then!
"White Lotus"
How dare you!
Leave here.
Surround him!
You'll have to look out for yourself.
Sky, wind, earth, fire,
eight stances to challenge you!
Surround him!
You're all frauds!
That's enough.
God...
It's all a deception!
God will protect us.
Gao Kung, why don't you come out?
This whole thing is a fraud.
I want to reveal the truth.
Protect the altar!
White Lotus brothers, kill him!
Come and fight me if you dare!
God will protect us.
Stop, or I'll shoot!
Can't you see this idol
cannot protect you?
You must stop believing in it.
- You...
- Mr Luke!
Come this way
and we'll see who doesn't die.
Let me through!
God will protect me.
Your gun doesn't scare me!
God will protect you!
The body is as strong as iron!
Little girl, you will lose your life.
Get back!
White Lotus is divine!
Power to the people!
Let's go, quick!
I've shot the girl!
Don't worry about that now.
You first.
- Stay there!
- Look at these people.
They're giving up their lives
for this idol.
Mr Luke, let's go!
If they're all like that,
how will they ever change?
They know nothing else.
Surround them!
There's nowhere to run to.
We can't escape.
Don't let them get away!
Beloved God, take over my body.
God will protect my body giving me
power to exorcise the evil spirits.
With God in my body,
I'll teach you the true way.
How dare you wake me to come here,
you fools!
Anger the gods and bring them
to earth. I'll teach you!
Come out, or I'll burn my own altar.
Gao Kung, the righteous, is here.
Welcome High Priest Gao Kung.
The invincible Gao Kung!
The universe is controlled by him!
All things obey his command.
The Goddess personally taught me.
She instructed me to set up an altar
to exorcise the evil spirits
and save us from this impure world.
Come spirit!
Come, spirit!
Here I come!
Come down here!
Be gone!
Trap him! Come on!
Yes, sir!
- Why do you need help?
- I'll do what it takes!
Come down!
Steady!
Yes, sir!
You set up a useless altar.
Come up here!
Supreme Being, come into my body!
I'll leave this broken altar for you.
Steady, steady!
How dare you!
How dare you wreck my altar!
Protect Priest Kung.
Use the cloth as an altar.
Do you want to die?
Supreme Being, four Guardians
of Heaven, come to my aid.
Destroy my enemy.
Guardian of Anger!
Guardian of Mercy!
Guardian of Evil!
Little girl.
Guardian of Defiance! Come!
Gao Kung, you've summoned all
the guardians! Are you ready yet?
If any guardian was of use,
one would be enough.
They will all punish you!
Death to you, the guardian's enemy!
Die now!
Wind somersault!
Mighty strike!
Evil being!
Priest Kung is invincible.
He will exorcise all evil!
Get down!
No Shadow Kick from Fushan!
Protect Gao Kung!
Killer Cloth!
I am not any sort of god.
I'm Wong Fei-hung!
Can't you tell gods from what is not?
Wong Fei-hung, prepare to die!
White Lotus opens up!
Put your feet on the ground.
It's all a deception.
Wong Fei-hung,
how dare you challenge the gods!
Gods don't burn!
If that's true,
there's no justice.
Solar explosion!
Gao Kung.
Your show is over now.
You demon!
You say believe in God
and peace will reign.
How many people have you killed?
Let's see you survive this!
- Nobody can stop me!
- I can.
Claw Knife!
A metal plate!
His magical powers amount to this.
Now they've no god,
they must look after themselves.
- God!
- Master!
How can this happen?
Let's go.
What kind of number...?
I can't even read it,
this is no use to me.
Master.
Good, we meet again.
It's six o'clock,
there's still time.
Hey, where is the name-book?
Name-book?
Oh, no! I was distracted
by the soldiers and forgot it!
Why are you so careless?!
I'll go back and get it.
Do we have enough time?
I must get it,
it's a matter of life and death.
Let's go.
"Gatehouse"
Mr Luke, it's well-guarded,
do we have to go in?
I must get the name-book.
The boat leaves in 30 minutes.
We can't be late
meeting Sun at the pier.
Wait there.
- Foon, see if Mr Luke is ready yet.
- OK.
I'll keep watch.
- Mr Luke, can I help?
- I've got it, let's go.
Soldiers, let's hide.
Search the building.
Master Wong, this way.
Hurry!
I'm going to die this time.
Help him up.
Where are you hurt?
It hurts, it really hurts.
Luckily they shot your watch...
Mr Luke!
You bastards!
Foon, you go first.
Mr Luke, I'll carry you.
This way, Master.
Don't move!
Master, there's a way out.
Let's go.
- Are you all right?
- I can't go on. Leave me here.
Let me help you.
The name-book is vitally important.
Don't let the Government have it or
many Chinese people will be killed.
Take me over there.
You can't burn this cloth.
Master Wong, I beg you,
deliver this to Sun personally.
Tell him I died for the revolution.
He must live for the revolution.
There's blood here.
They're over there!
Foon, look after Mr Luke.
General Lan?
We meet again.
- Arrest the rebels!
- Yes, sir!
Hold it. What are you burning?
Wong Fei-hung, this will be
our last chance to spar.
I wonder how many of my moves
you can withstand.
Give me that now!
Here you are!
How dare you!
The name-book?
Foon, stay where you are.
Carry on with what you're doing.
Master, take care.
Lan, didn't you want to test me?
Wong Fei-hung!
Come on, then!
Come down!
You come up!
You wanted to fight?
Son-of-a-bitch! This is too much!
Why aren't you down yet?
Mr Luke!
Time...
is vital.
Be on time... at the pier.
Meet Sun Yat-sen.
Mr Luke!
Mr Luke.
Wong Fei-hung, there's no way out!
Come back.
You killed the British consul,
everyone will know sooner or later.
There's no way out for you either.
Well... we're both doomed, then.
Foon, you can't burn that cloth!
- Master!
- Foon, go quickly. Time is vital.
It's a dead end, there's no way out.
Foon, what time is it now?
I can't tell the time,
but it's getting light.
There's not much time left.
Mr Sun must meet Mr Luke
before he sails.
Wong Fei-hung.
Please give me the name-book
so I can go back to the Governor.
He won't let us go.
Try and find a way out.
Quick! go!
Cloth Staff!
Foon, make the hole bigger.
Well done!
Thank you.
- Foon, get out of here.
- Yes, Master.
- Master, we can go now.
- Yes, you can go to hell!
Foon!
No Shadow Kick!
Master.
All aboard! Hurry up, everyone!
All aboard!
- Where's Mr Sun?
- Hurry up.
We've found him.
Don't move! You're coming with me.
Out of the way!
Grab the hand, crouch down and twist.
Master.
Fei-hung!
Aunt Yee!
Where is Mr Luke?
Dr Sun!
May a new dawn break
over our land.
May we never forget
our martyrs' blood.
Mr Luke, your spirit will always be
remembered in our hearts.
Don't worry, I'll meet
you at the pier!
Foon, are you missing Aunt Yee?
Are you, Master?
I asked you the question.
I think you're the one
who's missing her.
- Really?
- Yes.
DVD Subtitles by
European Captioning Institute