Anybody else wanna go ride 'em?
No, Let the boys play.
Uh' you can ride' kid'
but I can't take the blame...
for what happens
to retard here.
I can't take the blame for
what happens to you, can I?
Huh?
Take the tickets.
[ Sighs ]
[Continues]
Mom!
Babe, this remind you
of anything?
Yeah, A bunch of guys
running around in circles,
Uh-huh,
Goin' nowhere,
[Rusty]
Yeah, except my Rocky.
Can I have
a small lemonade, please?
How would you like something nice
to wash down with that?
No, thanks, John.
Real high-quality stuff,
I promised my kid,
You promised your kid?
I like that,
I'm gonna put that with
"I promised my parole officer"
and "I promised mywife."
Put it anywhere
you want to John,
You know where to find me,
[Beeping]
[Electronic Whirring]
[HystericalLaughter
OverP.A.]
Watch it,
[ Indistinct Shouting ]
Did you see
where Mom went?
Yeah,
Don't worry,
Have a good time,
[ Screams ]
[ChucklingContinues
OverP.A.]
Hey' Babe,
There's something
I've been wanting to give you,
You picked a hell of a time,
I can't take that, Red,
That's your good luck charm,
I kind of think of you
as my good luck charm, Babe,
Well, if you put it that way,
Will you wear it?
Sure.
Okay,
There, Sentimental old bastard,
aren't you?
Yeah,
Hey you guys,
Are you in here?
[Chuckling Continues
Over P.A.]
Shit,
Get any dope
for me, lady?
I didn't get any,
Yeah?
What, you don't
believe me?
Should I?
Hey' I--
Oh, check it out,
Mirrors,
Whoo!
Thanks,
Hi Rocky,
[ Indistinct Chattering ]
[Woman]
I'm getting dizzy.
Ben,
What?
Look at me,
Huh?
Get behind me
and look at me,
Whoa,
Get my mom.
What?
[ Soft Rock]
Rusty, how about
one of the old numbers?
It's okay with me, Red,
Rock, what do you think?
What?
Little Egypt.
[ Woman ] Yeah!
[ All Cheering ]
[ Middle Eastern Sounding
Percussion ]
[ Hooting' Cheering ]
Whoo!
[ Hooting Continues ]
Ladies and gentlemen,
step right up,
See Little Egypt do her famous
dance of the pyramids,
[GuitarStrumming]
She walks, she talks,
She crawls on her belly
in the dirt like a reptile, wow,
You gotta love her for doing this,
She's my mom,
Put your hands together
for Miss Rusty Dennis.
[ Banging ]
[GuitarStrum]
He went and bought him self a ticket
[BouncyGuitarStrum]
And he sat down
in the very first
[ All Singing ]
Row
They pulled the curtain down
And then they put
the spotlight way down
[ All Singing ]
Low
Little Egypt came out struttin'
wearin' nothin' but a button and a
[ All Singing ]
Bow
Singing "Yeah!''
Yeah
Whoa,
[Rock]Hey, Gar.
[Gar]Hey, Rock.
Yeah
She had a ruby in her tummy
And a diamond big as Texas
on her
[ All Singing ]
Toe
Whoa!
She took her hair down and she did
the hootchy-kootchy real
[ All Singing ]
Slow
When she did her special number
on the Zebra skin
I thought she'd stop the
[ All Singing ]
Show
Singing' "Yeah!"
Yeah
She did a triple somersault
and when she hit the ground
Aah
She winked at the audience
and then she turned around
Aah
She had a tattoo ofa cowboy
tattooed on her spine
Aah
Saying' Phoenix' Arizona 19--
[ All Singing ]
- Good year,
- [ Banging ]
Well' let me tell you' people
Little Egypt doesn't live here any
[ All Singing ]
More
She's too busy moppin'
and taking care of shoppin' at the
[ All Singing ]
Store
[ Both ]
'Cause they got seven kids
And all day long
they crawl around the
[ All Singing ]
Floor
[ Both ]
Singing
Where are you going?
[ All ] Yeah
I'm going where you ain't been,
That's where I'm going,
[ All Singing ] Yeah
You ain't going nowhere.
[ Cheering ]
- Come on, Let's go,
- Come on, Rusty.
Sing another one.
[Cheering]
[ Whistle Blows ]
[PistolFires]
You did a terrific job
with the decorating committee.
Are you going to the prom?
- I don't know.
Hi, Rocky.
How are finaIs going?
- Pretty good, Mr. Simms.
I had a great idea for you. How about
a coupIe weeks at summer camp?
No, I'm saving up for something eIse.
- It wouIdn't cost you a cent.
A friend of mine
runs a camp for the junior bIind
and he couId use a C.A. for JuIy.
- What's a C.A.?
CounseIIor's Aide. You heIp
with the kids and get to go free.
LittIe bIind kids?
Most of them.
Hey, Rocky! I got an A in aIgebra!
- You owe me 14 bucks.
I got a Roy CampaneIIa for you.
- It's a deaI.
I tutor him.
- oh. How about the camp, Rocky?
I don't think so.
My mom kind of needs me.
Your mother never gave me
the impression she couIdn't get aIong.
That's not what I mean.
I kind of organize things for her,
just kind of keep things together.
- I guess you probabIy do.
WiII you at Ieast think about it?
- OK, I'II think about it. - Good.
Bye-bye.
Hey, Rock!
Hey, baby!
Mom, what wouId you think of me
if you were a girI?
That's a toughie. Let me see ...
I'd think you're pretty cute.
I Iike guys with red hair.
I want to taIk to
another pIastic surgeon.
We can't do anything
untiI the bones stop growing.
So what's that? 2 years at the most.
We've been doing this for 16 years.
Don't you understand anything?
It's girIs.
Can I get a beer?
Come on.
Wait, I'II wake my ... Shit!
Honey, wake up, you got a guest.
Come on, Screech.
Come on, boy!
Jeez, what happened to your face?
What do you want?
- That Iady brought me here.
oh, my God.
I don't beIieve she did this.
WeII?
- WeII, what?
What do you want?
You don't happen to have
a CarI FuriIIo, do you?
It's just a joke.
Do you want to sit down?
Mind if I smoke?
How oId are you?
- 19.
How much do you get?
- Depends.
oh. Sure.
How much for a basic?
25.
Is that it? You need a manager.
No, thanks. I aIready got one.
Why is your map stuck with pins?
- Those are the pIaces I'm gonna go.
I'm going to SeattIe, Washington.
As soon as I get enough money.
SeattIe.
- I gotta sister that Iives there.
I get postcards.
It's reaI wet, cIean.
What happened to your face?
- I used to do a Iot of drugs.
No shit?
- No, I'm just kidding.
Where the heII have you been?
- Getting something for Rocky. And me.
I hope it was worth that 40 bucks
you took out of my jeans.
I remember when you weren't above
copping a coupIe bucks for some snort.
Grown up since then.
40 bucks.
Want to take it out in trade?
Are you aIright?
My mama used to say some peopIe
are born with no pIace to go.
I don't beIieve that. - How d'you
expIain the rotten things that happen?
I don't know.
Lorrie, I hope you don't mind, but
I think you got a shitty attitude.
It's pretty negative.
- It is?
Yeah. If you think Iike that
things onIy get worse.
When something bad happens
you got to remember a something good.
Like what?
- I got a bunch of them I use.
Like the time
we aII went down to Mexico.
Dr the smeII of my grandma's kitchen.
I don't think I have any.
- Everybody's got at Ieast one.
WeII, maybe the time ...
Na, I don't know.
I hope you don't think
I don't Iike you or anything,
'cause I do.
You're reaIIy pretty and nice.
It's just that I thought
it wouId be with someone I Iove.
I just thought of one.
- Yeah?
Yeah. I was in 5th grade.
You had to paint a pine tree
with snow on it.
Mine was the best one.
Teacher, she put it on the waII
where aII the kids couId see it.
She put a big goId star on it.
And aII the kids saw it.
You want more toast, Lorrie?
I gotta go to work.
- Can you take her to the bus stop?
Sure. Come on, Lorrie.
Bye.
Bye, Rocky.
Mom, do I Iook Iike
a freak to you? - No.
You aIways teII me my face doesn't
matter. But it does, doesn't it?
You think I can't even get a girI
to Iike me unIess you pay for her.
That's not true.
- BuIIshit!
BuIIshit yourseIf! Lots of young guys
got probIems getting girIs.
What if I was your Dad?
- I'd hate that too!
I'm sorry. Maybe I was wrong.
- Goddamn right you were!
But it had nothing to do
with your face. - BuIIshit, Mom!
Where are you going?
Hey, Rock, how's it going?
Your mother sometimes does
the wrong thing for the right reason.
You aIways stick up for her, Gar.
Then she pisses you off and you spIit.
Then you come back.
It's aII so nuts.
First time I met your mother,
she was workin' at a bar.
She had to wear
this cheesy IittIe two-piece thing.
I couId teII she hated it.
Takin' a Iot of shit
from a Iot of asshoIes.
I asked to take her home.
She said she was going to get her kid
and have his picture taken.
At one of those stores.
I said I'd ride her and the kid
on the bike. She Iiked that.
She came out of
your grandma's house with you.
You were 5, maybe 6.
WeII, shit. You didn't
Iook Iike your reguIar kid, right?
We get down to the store
and she's standing in Iine
with the rest of the mothers and kids.
AII the mothers and kids
are staring at you.
When it's your turn, she puts you
on this big red bIock.
The guy taking the picture
nearIy shits.
You're sitting there with your nose
and this big damn smiIe on your face.
I Iooked over at her ...
and I never saw
a woman more beautifuI
than the way she was Iooking at you.
Jesus!
Hey, Screech, come here.
Here comes Rocky.
I'm not going.
- Why?
I don't have anything to wear.
- I got that probIem aII the time.
Hey, it's my goddamn graduation!
You don't care
but it's a big deaI to me.
Remember who you are, boy.
You ain't citizen Iike your friend ...
What's his name?
With Ietters on his shirt? - Eric.
Wear your jeans, for Christ's sake.
- I can't wear jeans to my graduation.
BuIIshit!
Get me another beer and we're going.
What?
Get me another beer. Now!
We aII chipped in
and Gar picked it out.
- But you gotta wear it.
That's a point.
What do you say?
Thank you, everybody.
Go get it on.
Before we send our students
on to senior high, we wouId Iike
to acknowIedge some of our stars.
An academic award in EngIish
is presented to CaroIine MiIes.
For academic exceIIence
in mathematics:
Rocky Dennis.
Thanks.
Stay here. For achievement
in history: Rocky Dennis.
And ...
for academic exceIIence
in science ...
Rocky Dennis!
That's my famiIy.
Have a nice summer.
I'm ...
reaI ...
proud ...
of ...
you ...
Rocky.
Thanks, Doze.
Grandma! Grandpa!
Mom? - Yeah?
- You up? - Yeah.
Mom, they're here!
- Bring them in.
Morning, Gar.
- Mornin', Rock. - Come on.
Why don't you pIay this one straight?
Give your oId man a chance.
What a terrific idea.
Why didn't I think of that?
You go ahead.
I'II put on my wings and haIo.
Gotta get a picture of that.
Honey boy! - What are you
gonna do? Try out for the Nicks?
Look how taII he's getting, EveIyn!
Come on, fake, fake! That's a boy!
Stop that, say heIIo to the boy.
So, show us the new house.
Abe, don't start anything.
You promised, Abe.
Come on in.
HeIIo, Abe. - Hey, sonofabitch!
Look who's back! - Gar!
Let me show you my dog.
- That's aII you need, a damn dog.
Does she have cIeanser?
- That's not your job.
I just want to give her a hand.
I'm not going to do anything.
Quite a mutt.
Hey, that's terribIe. - What?
- HoIe in your infieId.
That's got to go.
- oh God!
oh shit!
I mean, wow! Peewee Reese!
Consider it a beIated
graduation present. - It's wonderfuI.
Why don't you show the dog to
your grandma. - OK. Come on, Screech!
Hi, Pop.
There she is.
Looking Iike a miIIion.
- You Iook great too, Pop.
Hey, Ma, you wanna do the windows
whiIe you're at it? - Gramps?
Where did you get that Peewee?
I've been Iooking for it for 2 years.
I found it a coupIe of months ago
in a store, just waiting for me.
Abe, how does it feeI to be retired?
It's driving me crazy. A man's onIy
as good as his Iast day of work.
How Iong are you staying, Pop?
- Hey, she's trying to get rid of us!
No, I wanted to make some nice Iunch.
- You cooking? No ordering out?
No, I got roast.
You Iike roast.
Yeah, I couIdn't chew it
the Iast time ...
I thought the roast was deIicious.
What are they Iearnin' you at schooI?
- Same oId stuff, math, history ...
Yeah? First you get an education
then a job with some security.
I tried to teII that to your mother.
She never went for the oId 9 to 5.
What was it you said, Rusty?
I'm reaIIy more ...
The freeIance type.
Yeah, the freeIance type!
I got her a job interview once at the
gas company. Luca Pezio's brother,
what the heII was his name?
She shows up in this kooky outfit
with her hair up to here
and these Iines painted under here.
Looked Iike she had spiders
under her eyes.
Remember that, Rusty?
Yeah, I remember, Pop.
The guy's name was Vinny.
He wanted to give me a job.
He aIso wanted to give me a bonus.
So, I took the bonus and
toId him to shove the job up his ass.
FIorence!
Rocky, find out
what time the game's on the tube.
It usuaIIy starts at two thirty
but I'II check.
Wow! Grandpa gave me tickets
to the game! Can I go? Check it out!
Come on, Rocky, Iet's go.
The team needs you.
Bye, Mom. See, you, Gar.
- See you, Rock.
He tried, honey, he reaIIy tried.
- It's OK, Mom.
Anyway, I'm gIad Gar is back.
Don't you want to wave goodbye?
- No, I don't.
Bye!
If you get wasted on that crap
I ain't gonna baby-sit you.
You must be confusing me with someone
who gives a shit. - Must be.
This is not going to work.
I'm doing things to pIease you
and I'II end up hating you for it.
Come on, baby, you and your oId man
been going through this shit forever.
Got to you again, didn't he?
Got you ready for a 2-hour screamer.
Got you to a pIace where I'd
put you through the waII. - Go ahead!
Why shouId you be any different
than any other guy I've been with?
Look what I got.
FIorence?
What did you do today?
Some smack? Ludes?
Some promise you made!
In front of Grandma and Grandpa, too.
Why? Why do you do this, Mom?
I'm not going to hang around
aII summer for this.
I'm going to a camp where
everybody's bIind. It'II be a break.
Who's going to take care of things?
You! You're gonna have to take care
of things incIuding yourseIf.
That'II be something new, won't it?
Come on, Iet's get it together!
- Come on, Dewey!
Kevin, turn off the radio.
Come on. Summer,
can you get them over here, pIease?
Hey, you in the back,
take that mask off so I can see you.
WeII, I'II try
but it ain't gonna be easy.
Gee, I'm sorry.
I reaIIy thought it was a mask.
It's OK.
Happens aII the time. No big deaI.
Hi, Rocky, I'm Norman KapIan.
GIad to have you aboard.
WaIter Simms toId me a Iot about you.
- Jake wants you in the kitchen.
Put your gear over there
and give Dewey a hand over there?
Thanks.
Make myseIf weII.
We're aImost there.
You guys haven't missed too much.
Kevin, how's the caboose doing
back there? - Fine! - AIright.
He's winding up,
trying for the 3rd-base Iine.
He reIeases!
- Swing! - Go!
We got the bases Ioaded, 2 outs.
AIex at bat.
He's winding up ...
Who's that?
My name's Rocky.
- Hi, Rocky, I'm Diana Adams.
Dennis, Rocky Dennis.
Are you a camper?
- Yeah. I'm aIso a counseIor's aide.
That's neat.
You Iook Iike AIice.
You know, in WonderIand.
No, what does she Iook Iike?
You.
That's a big heIp!
Wanna hand me that bridIe?
Great, thank ...
No, this is a haIter.
The bridIe is Ieather
and has a bit. - A bit of what?
No. A bit is a metaI piece
that fits into the horse's mouth.
oh yeah. Right here.
Thank you.
Don't know much
about horses, do you?
WeII, I ride motorcycIes.
I Iove horses. I got one at home.
Where's your home?
- San Marino.
Where do you Iive?
- Azusa.