Please breathe
Myungwoo... Please... Please breathe!
Please breathe. You fool. Breathe!
Please breathe!!!
Why did you save me?
I don't want to die after you
When a golf ball and table tennis ball
is thrown at same speed!
We went back to our ordinary lives
Me teaching students,
her chasing criminals
Who can report to jurisdiction 230?
Officer Yeo, coming to Nu Karaoke
Jurisdiction 230, this is line 2
Backup requested
The criminal is the notorious
jail-breaker Shin Changsoo
Block the entrance,
and wait until backup arrives
Kyungjin, this is dangerous
Let's not go
It's Shin Changsoo
We can't pass this up
This is our chance to get promoted
Jurisdiction 230.
This is line 2. We're in front
of Nu Karaoke, district 113
Backup still hasn't arrived
No, Kyungjin!
He's over there!
Put your hands up!
Weapon on the table, hands in the air!
Drop your weapon or I'll shoot
Officer Jo, are you okay? Yes
This is Line 2!
Nu Karaoke Changsoo Shin on the run
It is the notorious Changsoo Shin
Officer Yeo is chasing by herself
It's me. I discovered something
This is really special
Where are you? I'll help
I'm chasing a criminal now!
No, it's too dangerous
She sounded different that day
I could figure out vaguely
where she was
I know that she's stronger than me
But sometimes she acts without thinking,
so I was worried
Damn that bastard. I'll remember this
Shit! My big shot daddy
will not like this!
Oh, hello Get down
Quit smoking, punk
Got it
When the hell are they going
to use their guns?
Let's go. Where?
It's the jail breaker Changsoo
What?
Freeze!
Shit, we screwed up
Let's get away. Come on
Jurisdiction 230. Line 2, line 2
District 117, a citizen down at
the factory behind Evening Star Park
Call 911. Call 911
Jurisdiction 230, line 2
District 117, a man down
Please call 911!
Myungwoo
Don't die. Don't die
How can you die when
I saved you once already?
Don't die. Don't die
This is a dream. This is a dream
Jurisdiction 230. Line 2, line 2
District 117. A man down
Maybe I was destined
to die in that river
Don't do it
Don't do it! Let me die!
Let me die! Lie her down
Why are you doing this?
I killed him. I killed him
Hi, this is Myungwoo
Either my battery's out,
or I'm in a non-serviced area
Leave a message after the beep
and I'll call you back ASAP
Which non-serviced area is that?
Come back
Hurry and come back
No, never mind. I'll come to you
I'll come to your side
Hey lady!
What are you doing there, lady?
Why do you care?
And don't call me lady
I'm not that old
You're trying to commit suicide right,
lady? Jumping off?
She says don't call her lady
Ask her for some money. I'm hungry
Money? We're not beggars
Then what are we?
Hey lady! I mean, Miss
We ran away from home
Please give us some money before
you jump. We won't stop you."
What? Just 50 bucks
Aren't you a little out of line?
Or a credit card would be fine
You won't be liable after death
You guys are really something
Wanna see me get angry?
What's it this time? She seems angry
I'm hungry, dammit
Why can't she give us some money?
Hey, if you got something to say,
speak up. Don't whisper like cowards!
Give us some money before you croak!
Your guts will be sprayed
all over the street anyway
bucks will do. Or let's have sex
Make the most out
of your body before you jump
Let's get it on. You little shit!
You bastard, get over here
This is unbelievable. She's pissed."
You mongrels! You guys are dead!
Come on let's have a hot night!
Hey! Run!
You guys are dead when I catch you
She's wild
What? You rude idiots
Catch us if you can!
Hey, I can see her panties
Panties! Panties!
They're black! No, she isn't
wearing any! That's why it's black
It's purple, you dirty dogs!
Really, she's not wearing any!
No, how could she be
You're dead!
She's still following us. Take this
Shit!
Don't give me this. Take this yourself!
Why are you giving me this
It smells, I don't want it
Where did you learn
that kind of crap?
What did you say? "Screw till you die"?
You dirty bastards!
We were just hungry
We haven't eaten for three days
It's true
What do you want?
What should we have?
Pizza! Pizza?
Watch her eat!
I can't believe she was
just trying to kill herself
You said it
I haven't eaten for 3 days either
I need to eat to be a pretty ghost
What's the use of that?
If you jump off a building,
your guts will all burst open,
1and the pizza will spray in all
directions. What did you say?
Cut the crap and bring me more salad
No cucumbers or croutons
You go. No beans
Why do you always order him around?
You go!
Damn. Don't eat everything. Got it
More pizza, please!
This is cab fare to go home
You better go home
I'm going to check! Ok?
Thanks, Miss
We don't need to thank her
We're the ones who saved her life
What? Give me my money back
No. Thank you very much
You have to go home. All right?
You have to live, too
Excuse me!
Is this the way out?
Well then... Take care
If you feel the wind when
I'm not around, that's me
If I die, I want to become the wind
Myungwoo
Are you here?
Is this you? Or is it just the wind?
Tell me! Tell me, Myungwoo!
Myungwoo!
Did you become the wind? Did you really?
I can't believe this
This is the day you leave me forever
The 49th day after your death
But I'll come and find you
before that day. I'll be sure to
Come on! Get in!
This place is 30 years old... come in
Doing all right, guys?
Nice work
Hey, Park. The guy you caught
Get him in!
You can use the desk Min was using
Your locker is over there
Where's Kim? i @i @i @I don't know, sir
Oh come on
What time is it?
Detective Kim!
Yes, sir?
Not you guys
I'm looking for Kim Youngho
There are a lot of Kims here, sir
You're not even a detective
There he is
What time were you going to meet?
I don't know
Hey, Kim! Yes sir
She's your new partner
I'll see you guys later
Hello, sir!
It's nice to meet you
"I'd like to see you play piano
I'd like to see the real you"
Who are you? A cop?
Don't come closer, or I'll shoot!
I'll really shoot! Get out of here!
Detective Yeo!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go away!
Learn to shoot straight
Yes, Ma'am
If he resurfaces, call me back
And don't let anyone else know
I need to get Changsoo myself
Don't worry
Did you say Changsoo?
No, nothing
I have some other errands to run
I'll see you back at the station
I won't speed
I'll let you. Follow that car
Freeze!
Shoot him!
Call the ambulance!
Careful!
Myungwoo!
How can you die after
I saved you once already?
I must've been the wind in my
previous life
Please don't die
Be honest. You need a servant,
not a boyfriend, right?
A boyfriend should help his girlfriend,
shouldn't he?
Aren't you sorry for this?
If you want to hear me say 'sorry'
you'd better change your name to Sorry
Breathe, you fool!
Where are you? I'll help
He's my boyfriend, so don't you
dare try making eyes at him
I'm a three-peat offender
Murder, arson, rape...
Try this. It feels like I'm flying
There's a saying...
"Only the wicked see the wicked"
Am I late?
My name is 'sorry'. Call me now
Are you here?
Is this you? Or is it the wind?
Tell me. Tell me. Myungwoo
Did you become the wind?
Did you really become the wind?
Don't die, Myungwoo!
I can't believe this
I must have been the wind
in my previous life
Line 2 Line 2
Call the ambulance! Hurry up!
This is the day you leave me forever
The 49th day after your death
If you feel the wind
when I'm not around, that's me
But I'll go meet you before
that day. I'll be sure to
Call the ambulance!
Myungwoo... Myungwoo...
Is that you?
Detective Yeo, wake up!
Concentrate on anything
Just try to live
Keep talking to her
I can't, tears keep coming out
Do you remember that time?
You were like Robocop
Robocop can't die from one gun shot
I have a confession to make
I have to tell you something
I need to confess something
Be quiet, please!
They told me to keep talking
Check her vital signs. BP 60
Her pulse is weak. Connect the
monitor and call cardiovascular
Call cardiovascular
She stopped breathing
Get the D.C. ready! Intubation!
200 joules. Ready! Shoot
Check the EKG. No change."
300 joules! Ready! Shoot!
360 joules! Ready! Shoot!
Officer Yeo! Your night shift is over
Go home, okay? i @i @i @Yes, sir
Myungwoo!
It's you, isn't it?
You were alive
Why did you run away?
You know you can't run fast
I could've run well
But I only have one lung now
How could you pretend
that you're dead?
Didn't you think about
how much it'd hurt me?
I didn't want you to see me this way
Who cares? I love you no matter what
I'm not Myungwoo any longer
And you're not Kyungjin
Myungwoo. Myungwoo's dead
Admit it, will you?
Don't pretend I'm alive
But you're alive.
Myungwoo's dead!
Myungwoo
The EKG's back
She's trying to live. What?
She's trying to live. Connect all
the lines. Check her vitals again
Get the chest tubes ready
Prepare some blood
Hey, Kim. I can see that
you have the hots for Kyungjin
But you're a married man
No love confessions, OK?
You're awake
The operation was successful,
1and you're recovering quickly
Get some more sleep
What's the date today?
Today? The last day of October
Myungwoo
Somebody must've heard my prayer
I can see you
I need to go
I'm glad that I saw you before I left
No! Myungwoo
Myungwoo. Don't go
I'll follow you, if you go
No. It's not your time yet
You have many days ahead of you
No. No
Don't be so sad because of me
We'll meet again. Can't you feel it?
When we meet again,
tell me all the happiest memories
you experienced from this life
And when you hear me
whisper in the wind,
you'll meet someone
who has a soul like mine
Now, let me leave with
your love in my heart
Myungwoo!
Sorry
You don't have to call me that
My name is Myungwoo
I won't be so sad anymore
I'll believe that
you're always with me
If you miss me,
come back anytime
Even as the wind
Come back as the wind
Were you looking for me?
Oh, this
This just came in at the lost
and found. It's got your name on it
"To my savior Kyungjin, I'm yours"
Kyungjin, how are you these days?
I hope you're not hurting anymore
I'm always beside you
Remember I told you once
that when you hear me
whisper in the wind
you will meet someone with
a soul like mine?
Can you feel it? I am near you
You will meet him today
Do you know who brought this in?
Please stand back from the train
Please mind the gap between
the train and the platform...
I could hear his whisper
in the wind. I could feel it
It was him. Standing beside me
Let me introduce my girlfriend. She is...
someone who shed many tears over me
Her name is Kyungjin. Kyungjin Yeo
I feel strange just saying her name,
She has something special
that no one else can touch