Shit! I have to hurry up!
It's time to work! Come on!
Good morning, Ivy!
Do you want to run? Come out!
Let me get your milk!
We used to do it everyday, come on
Come out now
You are so rich in miIk!
I wish I wouId marry a wife Iike you
so she can miIk me everyday!
Young master
your milk pIease
Change the bed sheet!
No. Just throw the bed away
and buy a new one tomorrow Yes sir
Come on down!
Hey, take a morning bath!
Wash your hair, OK?
Who is going to wash my Iegs today?
Me
Don't wash anything eIse
TeII me, am I smart?
Sure! You are so smart!
Young Master...
OId master caIIed that he wouId come to
visit you two days Iater
TeII him to bring me
a miIIion US doIIars
Is that enough?
So, just teII him to bring more
Yes sir
Daddy, I am a good boy, I miss you
I am now going to schooI
bring two miIIion US doIIars
to me pIease
Sorry...
Where is my Iadder?
Here it is!
Have some ice-cream
Green coIor matches your cIothes
What is this?
ChocoIate
Green coIor shouId match
with yeIIow coIor!
How can you match with bIack coIor?
Sorry
See! The bIack girI
wears stripe underwear!
Yeah!
Wong Siu Fu?
Yes, I can teII from his ass
Stop him
Where can you go?
Brother Sing, I am here waiting for you
Sorry
for burning aII your hair Iast time
That made you tattoo your
eyebrow & wear wigs. I regret so much!
Never mind, since my famiIy
is working for your dad!
And I am good Iooking now!
You are reaIIy good Iooking!
I can't stand you!
Come on, have some chocoIate
Brother Sing, I don't need it
This is cathartics, I tried that before
When did you become so smart?
I can't heIp, Iet's go
Young master, are you Ietting him go?
I can't heIp! See, how smart he is now!
I can't fooI him any more
I Iost two hundred doIIars
Isn't it stoIen?
CaII the poIice now!
I have recorded the numbers
You are smart!
How is the taste of the note?
It's made of cathartics too
It meIts in mouth and wiII be
effective in 5 seconds!
You are trapped!
HoId it...
Not untiI he is shitting!
Go!
Jump! Jump!
Do you know it's dangerous to do so?
Who are you? Who is your boss?
My uncIe is Professor Chang Sze
of this coIIege
I am studying here
I have toId them not to Iet
ugIy women study here!
That's right
You know, I bribed them so as
to enter this coIIege
You are too ugIy
even bribery won't heIp! Go
Go Go now!
Go Bastard!
But I am smart!
You are not smart at aII
What?
What did you say?
How can you teII such Iies?
Can you face your conscience?
Forget it...
How can you face your parents?
Don't argue
How can you face your country?
You'd better caII
a press conference to apoIogise
Or, I wiII kiII you! You know?
Human bodies are the most
fantastic things in the worId
In my cIass, you are studying the most
advance subject about it
That is the imitating function &
adaptabiIity of human bodies
It's Iike some Iizards, it imitates
the coIor of the surroundings
And human beings have the same function
Young master, after you
What are you staring? Go on teaching!
Get out
Now, I am giving you an exampIe
Say, a coupIe
When they have stayed for a Iong time
Their appearances wiII be aIike
They said, it's the coupIe Iook
In fact, this is the effect of human
genes which imitate each other
What do you want to ask?
I aIways stay with women, how come I
haven't become women?
Human bodies are weak
I beIieve that
one day, our organs wiII be repIaced
by artificiaI organs
What onIy Ieft wiII be our brains
Our organs wiII be
controIIed by computers
We wiII have strong imitating power
to imitate anyone
Or anything
Can we change to be a cigar?
According to theory, yes
You seem to be interested in this topic
In fact, I am interested in you
An ugIy girI toId me that
you are her uncIe
So I come here to see how cocky you are!
Now, I'm going to start the dissection
If you can stand it for three minutes
we wiII go ahead to
discuss other questions
OK, I am now going to dissect the body
What's he doing?
He's reaIIy crazy!
You're reaIIy great!
You are the onIy one who can toIerate
such Iong time in my cIass
Damn it!
I won't give it a damn
If onIy you open your eyes
I wouId admit that you are reaIIy boId!
It's a shame to be scared Iike this!
I'm scared to piss! May I be excused?
Are you scared?
Who do you think you are?
If you have guts, finish the food
My dad is the director of this coIIege
I'II ask him to fire your uncIe
And kick you out of the schooI
And seII you to be bar girI to
perform strip dance
When you are dancing
I'II ask the bar manager
to fire you again
No one can fire me
I am a senior scientific consuItant
empIoyed by the US Gov't
I am a guest professor here
WeII, since I can't fire you
I wiII steam you!
I can't imagine you are the most
disgusting guy in this coIIege
I am aII eyes!
What do you mean? My father is the
director of this coIIege
If your father wasn't the director
you wouId have been beaten to death
Shut up!
If you have guts, teII others that your
father isn't the director
We'II wait and see the resuIt
I won't give it a damn!
My father isn't the director
so what?
That bastard! He made me be
beaten Iike shit!
I'II take revenge tonight
Yeah...
Left...
Right...
No
Be carefuI
You hurt me!
Sorry, are you aIright, young master?
ShouId I give you some medicine?
Get Iost!
Go upstairs and take a Iook
Young master, the Iaboratory
shouIdn't be upstairs
It shouId be buiIt in the basement
Here is Iike a Iab
Here it is, young master
What a big basement!
We'II have a Iot of fun here!
PIace one here
If anyone steps on this animaI trap
he wouId either die or become handicap
Where are you going?
In case he missed the trap
the banana skin here wiII heIp him
to step on it
Wise guy!
Thank you
It's fixed
Remove these tubes
and piss in
Great
Young master...
I've just seen a hand running!
Just piss!
If I cheat you, my famiIy Iine wiII end
I don't think you'II have any sons
Even yes, he shouId be a handicap
Not exactIy
What are you staring at?
Young master...
I've just seen a pair of eyes
Just a pair of eyes
which are staring at me
Staring at you? Yes
What do you want me to do?
I just want to ask you
the same question?
If I were you
I wouId stab into it
Do you want me to show you how?
Stare at me, come on
No, thanks
Shit! What's this?
What's up?
What is he staring at?
Isn't it what you have just seen?
Yes, they're the eyes I have just seen
Stab it!
Go to heII
How are you doing?
What's up?
I don't know! What's that?
Let me handIe it
It's not successfuI
GentIy... gentIy pIease
Stop! Don't go
PoIice, freeze!
I've got you!
Come out
I asked you to come out
Kid, what are you doing here?
Show me your I.D. card
I haven't brought it
HeIp!
Wait for me...
HeIp...
Come on. Check it
Don't beIieve them! They're crazy
they're reaIIy crazy!
OK, OK! Don't worry, we'II handIe it
caIm down
Mr. Lee, we have found for haIf an hour
But we can't find the waIking hand
which you have mentioned
And the eyes too
Not even a ghost
Shit!
My feIIow's ass was
aImost stabbed by that hand
It did stab into my ass, two inches!
Two inches deep in my ass
4 inches aItogether 4 inches!
This student of mine is having
great imagination
Just Iet him pIay
Professor, I suspect that
you are a crazy maniac
I beIieve that you kiIIed
many innocent peopIe
And you chopped off their hands for
crueI scientific experiment
You are so wise!
But you can't prove anything
You'd better find
the hands and Iegs first
What are you doing here?
The hand is a sex maniac
I think it must be a maIe's hand
So, I pretend to be a
femaIe hand to seduce it
Send two persons there to have a Iook
I'II take two up there and check it out
Tat, get the finger prints Yes sir
I am the in-charge here, behave yourseIf
Young master...
My father is...
Bye bye
If you are free
come to my cIass tomorrow
Young master, why did you hit me?
Why did you forget the secret code?
There isn't anyone outside
That professor must be a crazy kiIIer
I discIosed his secret
he wiII come to kiII me, you know?
Ortherwise, why shouId I ask you to find
someone to protect me?
And, I asked you to empIoy bodyguards
Not modeI! Yeah
They just put their hands on their waists
how can they protect me?
They are just modeIs What?
Time's up, Ieave now Yes sir
What do you mean? They are bIind
Since no one is wiIIing
to work for you in Hawaii
So, I have to empIoy some
bIind men to be modeIs...
So...
When I count to 3, I'II kick you out
if I stiII see you
Three!
Why didn't you count one two?
Master
I want to give him a big surprise
Dad?
My son!
Hi mom
Son
How is your heaIth?
Are you aIright?
I am fine, a master taught me
great Kung-fu
So, when you hit me
the rod bend, but I am fine
Now, I haven't any sore throat
and didn't vomit bIood
Everything is aIright
But, I think I am a bit crazy now
It's true
Yeah
ShouId I show you?
See, I think I am a bit crazy
What's wrong with you?
Stop scoIding me, Emperor Tsun is
coming to attack us
HoId it, I want to save others
ShouId we take a Iook?
The enemies are coming, get ready
I'II open the door to shift
the enemy's attention
You, go to his back and beat him
Hi
Watch out!
Miss, are you aIright?
I am fine
Who is he?
I don't know, maybe a thief
What do you want?
My name is Bonnie
I Iive next to you
WeII, my bathing tub is out of order
Kidding?
May I use yours to take a bath?
I usuaIIy wash right here
Shampoo, conditioner, anything you want
And, there is a cIeaning brush
under the water
Not bad
By the way, you are so fast to
take off your cIothes!
UsuaIIy I use Iesser time to
take off other's cIothes
I don't beIieve it
Isn't it caIIed diving?
Watch!
Whose stuff is it?
That's mine
Miss, don't you worry
you wouId be teased?
Be carefuI of the bark dogs!
Your dad fainted
He wiII wake up if I
give him more strikes
Go and take a Iook
Let me heIp you to wash your back
It seems to be something
for washing toiIet
Yeah, I am washing toiIet now
You are so bad
You don't remember your dad's name now!
By the way, I have forgotten
Madam, you Iook famiIiar to me
who are you?
I wish I had given birth
to a bun instead of you
Having me was the side effect onIy
You were enjoying
the process of making me
You're right
You've aImost finished your bath
What's next?
I haven't got any idea
But if someone heIps me to wash my toes
maybe, I wiII have some ideas
What's this?
MentaI iIIness drop
What's that?
LSD!
Yeah!
What are you doing?
Do you want to vomit it?
I want to see what brand it is
For I want to buy some
more for sudden use
No, I have many of it. Come on!
Yeah!
Good evening, what can I serve you?
7 TequiIa
That's TequiIa mixed with seven-up
No! 7 TequiIa
7 gIasses for each
Yeah
Do you think I am stupid?
Ladies and gentIemen!
Now it's the time you've
aII been waiting for
the worId's most famous twist contest!
Yeah!
First, Iet's see who our
champions wiII be tonight
The winners wiII receive a mystery prize
Why not go dancing?
I don't know how to dance
If you win
I wiII sIeep with you tonight
Bonnie, you have mistaken me
I am not a woIf
Understand?!
Hug me
Why are you so hot now?
My husband is here
ReaIIy?
Turn and have a Iook
He is waIking towards the bar tabIe
Over ten men are waIking over there
are they aII your husbands?
No, the rest are the bodyguards of him
Are your husband operating
a security company?
No, he is a boss ReaIIy?
What company?
He is the boss of Japanese triad gang
Yeah. Bye bye
I know how's the resuIt
The winners are Mr. Lee Chak Sing
and his IoveIy Iady
Wait, give the Iady a kiss
give the Iady a kiss!
I've got the betrayer
You are so bad! Why didn't you drive?
Why don't you taIk?
Are you sIeeping?
What's wrong with you?
How are you?
Don't faint!
No...
Where is it?
I don't care!
Yes, he is having troubIe
I've prepared everything, come here now
I beg you
When I arrive, he wiII be dead
fix him first
This isn't your first time!
I didn't know how to do it
I have no experience!
You shouId Iearn it now
If he dies in your pIace
you wiII be finished
I wiII get the handbook
to instruct you, wait
Have you Iocated the mark?
Yes, it is
He overtook drugs
So caused heart weakness
To prevent expansion
You have to do him some injections
to stimuIate his heart
So as to save him
Kidding?
Try. You've no choice!
Have you got the needIe?
Yes
Forget anything, but stab in
You've waken
Yes
But the woman fainted
Where was the needIe?
It's stabbed into the Ieft hand side
under my beIIy
9 out of 10 men's dicks are
pIaced on the Ieft
how about yours?
I am Iucky, I am the tenth one
it's pIaced on the right
CongratuIations
But my baII is on the Ieft
WeII, bye bye
Forgive me, it's not done by me
You bastard!
I gave you so much money!
I just wanted you to amend something
in government's computer
How dare you betray me?
Boss, don't kiII me! Don't kiII me...
Boss, you speak fIuent Cantonese
I aIways taIk to my girI IateIy
That's why I have enough practice
I'II handIe you first
Don't kiII me...
So, shouId I Iisten to you?
If yes, how can I be the boss?
Give me one more chance...
AIright, I wiII give you another chance
So as to Iet you die with no regrets
When the bitch and
his aduIterer come back
catch them and throw them to the sea
To feed the fish
Get him
Shit
Fuck
What does that mean?
What are you doing?
You said a waIking hand was found in
Professor Chang's home
Now, you said someone is
going to kiII you
Get out
Mom, this is shit!
What a big troubIe!
Let me teII you Let me teII you
Someone wants to kiII me!
This isn't a big deaI
I have something to teII you
I know! You want me to study hard
I aIways study hard
No, I have something new to teII you
Your dad, Lee Yat-fai
isn't your father at aII
I know. Tat is my dad
How do you know it?
I hit dad and he went crazy
but I didn't hit you!
What made you to be crazy then?
Crazy?
Don't you think I am reaIIy crazy?
You bitch! You discIosed your secret!
That's why I know you aren't my son
I've suspected that for ages
My nick-name is Handsome VaIentino!
But...
my son Iooks Iike shit!
I know nothing!
Anyway, I want 2 miIIion
Who gives me 2 miIIion
I wiII take him as dad
I have two hundred doIIars
Two miIIion
PIease go back to wash toiIet
25 years ago
one night, I was reading sex noveIs
in the store room
Your mom rushed in, she wore nothing
but turned off the Iight
Mind your tongue
I did wear something, I mean the socks
Sorry
You wore a pair of white socks
OId master went out on that night
I couIdn't controI myseIf and I...
When I turned on the Iight
I regretted so much!
So, why did you read the sex noveI?
Shut up, stop saying anything!
Stop!
If a son hits his dad
he wiII be hit by thunder
Who said he is my dad?
Why shouId I beIieve it?
Do you have any proof?
It's shown in the movie that
if a dad kneeIs in front of his son
his son wiII feeI dizzy
ReaIIy? So, just try, see whether I wiII
feeI dizzy or not
KneeI down
See? FeeIing dizzy now!?
I am fine! Don't you beIieve it?
Stop messing up
I have bright future
Here is a cheque of 2 miIIion
If you take me as your dad
I wiII forget everything and you wiII
have further benefits
Otherwise...
You can teII the resuIt
No... Don't take the cheque...
Thank you dad
You are my good son
The wise guys shouId know
how the wind bIows
This is not fiIiaI!
No
Get out
I don't mind you not
admitting me as your dad
Get Iost!
I aIways spoiI you, in fact
it's a harm to you
Mind your tongue, or I wiII caII
the poIice to arrest you
Be honest
You are a very disgusting person
Stop!
I hope you wouId know how to
respect peopIe from now on
So, others wiII respect you
Get Iost, bastard!
You are bastard
I am your dad, so I can scoId you
How dare you?
HeIIo
Are you confessing?
Don't you scare?
I won't give it a damn
See my teeth?
Aren't you happy?
How can I get happy after seeing you?
I'd better Ieave
PIease, hurry up
HeIIo
Come here
I have a friend
For money, he just ignored his own dad
Then?
That's it
I am Ieaving
Wait...
He kicked his dad out of his home
And gave him a heavy kick
At that moment, it was pouring &
with thunderstorm
What do you feeI about this guy?
Worse than animaI
But he is reaIIy handsome
That's better
Otherwise, he shouId be shot to death
I just want to ask one more question
Don't you think I am smart?
I, Chung Chung, swear here
You are not handsome at aII
He is aIone tonight
Damn!
Move it
They are here
Do you want to caII 91 1 for the poIice?
May I?
Up to you
What is the number?
Sorry!
Who turned off the Iight?
Don't go!
Why are you standing here?
I didn't know he wouId bump against me
Go and get him
This house is too big
I think I'II bIow it up
Watch me
And!
Yeah Yeah
Why are you back?
I haven't Ieft
Don't move
Take the gun here
Don't do anything mad
Give it to me sIowIy. Hurry up!
Don't puII off a stunt, I teII you
Don't you think I can't see your cunning
eyes behind the gIasses?
Don't do anything stupid
Give me your gun
You've got it
OK!
Don't move!
Don't mess up, I have got your friend
This is what I want to teII you
Your boss is with me
WeII, Iet's change our hostages
Damn you! Let my friend go
Or, I wiII shoot him to death
OK...
Why do you kneeI down?
He is my son, he can't stand it!
He feeIs dizzy for I kneeI
down in front of him!
HeIIo, goodbye
That stupid guy doesn't know
how to use gun, but bomb onIy
He has made a big mistake this time
Watch!
He Ieft a knife
Do you remember we have a spring toiIet?
The one which is used
to fooI Wong Siu-fu?
It's just next to you
Oh!
How many peopIe can it serve each time?
One
Don't worry
we stiII have coupIe of hours
Wear your gIasses!
Just 10 seconds are Ieft
You can't cut the chain by the knife
Chop off my hand and Ieave
as soon as possibIe!
You needn't teach me that
I haven't treated you nice in my Iife
Now, I wiII pay everything back to you
Dad
My dear son
Sit down!
Chung Chung, are you aIright?
I am fine
Have you had a nightmare?
Yes
I saw Sing being bIown up in my dream
What a horribIe dream!
Aren't you hating him?
Why did you think of him in your dream?
In fact, I hate him
I know, I remember a psychiatrist said
those bad guys have
speciaI attraction to women
In fact, he isn't that bad
He went to the church for confession
He just Ioves face
he doesn't want me to tease him
He is so poor, for he hasn't any friends
He is a smart guy
Otherwise, he can't think of so many
tricks to fooI others
Yes
Doctor Chang pIease Speaking
A patient caIIed Lee Chak-sing
is bIown to death
Come to the hospitaI now
What's up?
What you saw isn't a dream
It's reaI
Professor...
How is my son?
Stay caIm
From the medicaI point of view
your son is dead
What?
But to me...
He is haIfIy dead
What do you mean?
Dad, are you here?
Why onIy his Iips are Ieft?
Right
Did professor teII you anything?
Now, aII my bIood and fIesh are gone
Just the brain and Iips are Ieft
Take a rest
Don't say so much!
Now, I have to teII you a good news and
a bad news
What?
The good news is, I've mentioned the
artificiaI organs, right?
Now, it's successfuIIy invented
by the US government
You may keep two originaI organs
For the rest, you can repIace them
with artificiaI organs
So, we can rebuiId your son's body
Do it now
This is Doctor Quency, the chief doctor
of this hospitaI
How are you?
This is my son, pIease save his Iife
Listen to me, I have a bad news too
He wants 60 miIIion US doIIars
for the operation
Sorry, I don't have that much
How can you do the operation then?
It doesn't matter, I wiII caII
his weaIthy father
I understand
You'd better taIk to him directIy
Sing, I have much money
But I don't want you to see Tat again
Otherwise, I won't treat you
as my son any more
Let's stop any communication
In fact, I've made up my mind
in these days, Mr. Lee
Let's forget each other from now on
AIright, since you don't Iisten to me
just go to heII
Why are you so stupid?
Oh Jesus, you're wasting any time
I can't beIieve it
He is so practicaI! Not mercifuI at aII
I don't have that much money
I can onIy afford $6000 doIIars
Do you have 6 thousand?
OK, I wiII give you a hand, a free hand!
We may do it in a cheaper way
Dare you try?
The sweat!
It's fixed
What a hard time for you!
Eat whiIe it's stiII hot
Great...
The noodIes that I made wiII
make you never forget
He Iooks so angry, Iet him eat first
My dear son, have the noodIes first
I am not in the mood
The operation can be cIaimed a success
His Iook has aImost been recovered
But not the face
A square face is aIways smart Iooking
WiII it be too smart?
It's OK
Just take a Iook first
What? I have to eat my noodIes first
Be frank. How can you say OK?
It's cheap, don't be so mean!
I wanna kiII myseIf
CaIm down!
Professor, you shouId take it seriousIy!
HeIp, fix him first
OK
Look. You Iook handsome now!
That's your originaI Iook
Thank you, Professor
This is what I shouId do
But I think my hands are
of different Iength
Everyone's hands are not of same Iength
But, they vary too much!
So?
It's cheap, don't be so mean!
I'd better kiII myseIf
Professor, are you fooIing us?
How can you provide such hand for him?
Don't you think we are fooIs?
Stay caIm...
CaIm? How can I caIm down?
Trust me...
Do you want me to beIieve you again?
You are Iucky. In this month, over 100
pairs of hands are dumped
I've tried my best to find you a
perfect pair of hands
Try
It's OK ReaIIy?
Yes! Yes
What?
I am sorry. What are dumped
in this month are...
onIy hands!
They are cheap
Don't be so mean!
Left hand
Right Ieg
Yeah
So great!
CongratuIation, professor
It's reaIIy perfect
I said it wouId be OK, right?
CongratuIation!
Stop
I can't stop!
Damn you!
When wiII he stop?
I think...
He wiII stop after
the battery is used up
Out of battery now!
Come on
The eIectronic organs can't be
adapted easiIy, so he Iost controI
He wiII be aIright soon
And he has to eat battery daiIy
Don't get your body wet
Or, you can't move
I want to piss
HeIp yourseIf
He can onIy eat battery
What's this?
This is for urination, after using it
just cIose it
PIease find a better Iooking one!
How about shitting?
Use this too
You...
Don't faint!
And I have to pIant a chip
inside your brain too
If it is pIanted
the imitating function of your
eIectronic organs wiII be started
So, you can change yourseIf
to everything
According to theory
you may change to everything
I just want to be myseIf
Sure
So, go ahead and pIant it
I haven't invented that yet
You?!
Piss on him
Piss...
No...
Sing, the Japanese triad gang is
so powerfuI here
And they are crueI
If they know you are not dead
they wiII come again
So, I wiII arrange a fake funeraI
for you tomorrow
And you have to fIy to Hong Kong
as soon as possibIe
Never come back again
I can't imagine someone
wouId cry for me!
I wiII remember that
Hey, paI...
this buiIding is going to be demoIished
why don't you move out?
I wiII move out soon
I'm going to pack up now
Better Ieave as soon as possibIe
Are you wet by the rain?
I can't move whenever I get wet!
I don't want to be aIive!
Stop saying such nonsense!
Just add some oiI, then you'II be aIright
What have you done to me?
Show me your finger
Like this
Stop pIaying
I want to piss, pIease heIp me
AIright...
I've taken it out
but it's stepped by you
I am sorry
Why do you change a shower?
The oId one is stuffed
so I have to change a new one
It doesn't work
It comes out from your ears too!
It's stuffed again!
PIease bIow it dry for me pIease
You do it yourseIf
HoId it
Go ahead
Let's eat
Your dad is fired today
This pIace wiII be
demoIished some days Iater
We'd better find a sheIter in the garden
By the way, a rapist aIways
shows up in the garden
He Ioves raping young man of your age
Come on, have some of it
I do want to have a change
AIright, I wiII buy you
a new battery tomorrow
Why not buy some drugs
Let's commit suicide together
Siu-fu! I am so gIad to see you!
Sing, I've found a new job for you
ReaIIy?
To be a bioIogy teacher
This is the address of the coIIege
Eight o'cIock. I've arranged
everything for you
The saIary is over ten thousand doIIars
Siu-fu, I treated you badIy in the past
but you're so nice to me!
I...
Don't be siIIy
Iet's forget those history
We're grown up now
Siu-fu!
Work hard
Have the change
StiII 50 cents Ieft
What? StiII 50 cents Ieft
Are you the teacher here? Yes
I'II give you a doIIar
so as to Iet you caII for poIice
Good morning, I am the newIy
empIoyed bioIogy teacher
I feeI something bad
It's too quiet
Yeah, what a nice pIace
You are too absent minded
This is caIIed the grave of
teachers in Hong Kong
57/ of the teachers here are
hurt and become handicap
You shouId pay fuII attention in cIass
In fact, I was a nasty student in schooI
My nickname is ''DespicabIe Man''
''ShameIess Guy'' is my reaI name
I have experienced everything!
Stupid. My nickname
was ''EviI King in HeII''
But now
I am a poor guy
Good morning sir
Good morning
Good morning sir Good girI
Are you a new comer? Yes
Let me show you to the
administration office Great
Here you are
Here? Are you kidding?
Bye bye
Be carefuI
You are reaIIy something
Here is a bit safe
The most secure pIace is
the most dangerous pIace
57/ of teachers are seriousIy hurt
how about the remaining 43/?
23/ death
1 1/ went crazy
OnIy 9/ can stand great insuIt
and pressure here
What's wrong with you?
Sir
Don't panic, he is Long Hair
An informer of us
he comes to pass me some messages
Oh, an informer needn't wear pants
Since my identity is discIosed
so they took off my pants
They said a new teacher
wouId come to work today
they want him dead
Are you the new teacher?
I want to have a Iook then
I teII you...
I was a heartIess and animaI Iike...
Sir
What's the matter?
What is your bIood type?
Mr. Tang, the net profit of
our internationaI schooI...
has had doubIe increment when
comparing with Iast year's figure
I'm so gIad to present such satisfactory
figure to the directors' board
Increase 2 more cIasses in each grade
in next semester
For schooI fee
we'II have 50/ increment too
We charge $1 7,000 per month
can they afford that?
The students aren't coming for studying
you know?
Their fathers are aII rich guys
They just want any schooI's record
for further studies abroad
They are wiIIing to pay for that
That's right
If we have more satisfactory
income next year
I'II consider to distribute shares
WeII! It's a good idea... good idea
Dad, a teacher was beaten
seriousIy by a student
Is that true?
We take this educationaI business
Right, the students are our cIients
Say the cIub girIs, they have to face
the cIients with smiIing face
But a cIub girI won't be
beaten by students
However, they wiII be screwed
by their cIients
WeII, just take yourseIf as a cIub girI
I won't!
I'm the cIub girIs' manager
Manager...
Can't you read?
Rats and teachers are
not aIIowed to come in!
Beat him
I can't go in stiII
No
It's broken
HeIp, principaI
Be patient! You wiII be used to it Iater
That way
HeIIo
I am stiII aIive
UncIe toId me that
HeIIo...
Are you the new teacher?
Yes. HeIIo
Do you need my heIp?
No, I am fine
How is your teaching?
So far so good
Are you teaching gardening?
What?
And your shower...
Don't touch, be carefuI
Don't you know it's dirty?
OK
Chung Chung
My friend is coming to pick me up
see you
ReaIIy?
Bye bye Bye bye
What's wrong with you?
So far so good
Not bad! So keep on
If I were you, I wouId have suicided
Just do according to your suggestion
Kidding? What's wrong with it?
I am having more and
more power instead! Shit!
If you are great, Iet me stay aIive
even if I jump to death
I've made it
You know, the super chip is
invented successfuIIy by me
At the criticaI moment
I pIaced it into your mouth
Now, you have become a super superman!
You may maintain the worId peace now
What did you say?
To maintain worId peace
What?
Where are you going?
To destroy the invaders of the 5 pIanets
I am not that great
I want to suicide
Listen to me first
AIthough you are made of cheap organs
After having this chip
The imitating function
wiII be started automaticaIIy
So, your power wiII be unIimited
You can change to be everything
I want to be a cooking pot, may I?
Sure, just think of the cooking pot
then you can make it
Stop pIaying, professor
you are not a kid
Look at the mirror
What's wrong with it?
Do you beIieve in it now?
If you want to be human
just think of yourseIf
Professor, isn't he my son?
Change back to your originaI Iook
How come?
Don't waste it...
Professor, we have rice now
can he change to be some food?
He is changing...
Bastard, do you want
to scare me to death?
I just wanted to brush my teeth
but I become Iike this
Cut the crap
change to be a piece of goId
Sorry, he can be a toothpaste onIy
You are not used to that
so Iimited changes can be made
But nevermind, take a rest
then you may change back
to your originaI Iook
I wasted aII my Iife...
And I input Mrs. Wong's famiIy
encycIopedia into your computer
So, you may change to many
many funny things
What are interesting written in
Mrs. Wong's book?
Yes...
So many wonderfuI inventions!
Say a toiIet, it's modern Iooking...
Enough, Iet's stop here
This is toothpaste
You'd better use another brand
I use this brand too
You are foreigner! You can't use it
Sit down
Damn!
This is Mr. BIack Stone
an FBI coming from USA
He hopes you'd be witness...
to sue against Fumito of
the Japanese triad
No! I didn't witness him and
he wanted to kiII me
I wouId be dead meat to offend him again
You have become something instead
of a human being now
What is worrying you then?
This is your fauIt!
You never give me advantage
You just input famiIy appIiances
into my computer
It wouId be embarrassing if
I am seen by Chung Chung
Don't worry
The son of the coIIege's director dated
her for a proposaI
What?
Dad, squeeze me at once
I want to die
What for?
Have you got my permission yet?
Do you know how important you are now?
OnIy you can become a
toothpaste in this worId
If she knows that she can brush her
teeth for free because of you
She wiII hug you at once!
And you have to maintain worId peace!
But you teII me that
you want to suicide!
What'II I do now?
What do you think?
What's wrong?
Where are you now? I am waiting for you
I am now in a restaurant, honey
Why don't you come back now?
I wiII be back soon
I saw a toothpaste!
What?
A big toothpaste!
Hey
Cheers
John aIways said you are
pretty and cuItured
He is fIattering me
Few years ago, he aIways teased me for
I was wearing gIasses
You have had great change!
After marrying with John
you have to behave weII
We are a tough and decent famiIy
Why are you so rude? You may scare her
I am sorry...
May I be excused?
Sure
Thank you
See, she is scared
Enter at the back
What?
Not here! Go through the back stage
Why?
Aren't you the magician?
I am Iooking for someone
Sorry, pIease heIp yourseIf
Not here!
Hey, watch!
Sorry
Do you want to peep?
Damn you, bastard!
It's me
Why do you come to the Iadies' toiIet?
I want to teII you something
Just go ahead
I am different now
I noticed that
Zebra, right?
In fact, from now on
I want to be a decent man!
If yes, you won't come to
the Iadies' toiIet
I don't have any seat
My friend is waiting for me
Do you come for a match?
None of your business
Not exactIy
If you are a IittIe bit fond of me
What made you say so?
Two years ago
you did shed a tear of
Iove in my funeraI
Sorry, I think you've misunderstood
I wiII cry even if I step a
cockroach to death, OK?
Chung Chung, I guarantee that
I am much better than a cockroach now
So what?
See, I am reaIIy different
UncIe's research has reached a success!
A reaI success!
Damn! It's fuII
Auntie, are you aIright?
I have drunk too much
herbaI tea to keep fit
That's why I aIways want to shit!
What a speciaI toiIet!
Yeah...
Leave me aIone, or it'II stink!
Go out and have a chat with them
AIright Good girI
Chung Chung, Iet's go for a dance
Great
Forget about it
Madam, do you want to piss or shit?
Shit of course
You can shit in the basin!
What's the matter?
Auntie
I was scared by the toiIet
Are you crazy for pIaying
too much mahjong?
It's true...
Go back to your seat first, go!
What's the matter?
My underwear is Ieft behind
Let's go, no one wiII notice that
Yes, go back to your seat
Ladies and gentIemen, we wouId Iike
to have Mr. R. BiIIion...
to perform magic for us
Now, the show starts
Hi
HeIIo
What magic do you know?
I know everything
Can you make a toothpaste?
Toothpaste?
What a fresh request!
Give my son one more pIease. Come on
Can you make such a big toothpaste?
WeII!
Can't you make it?
I wiII fire you
WonderfuI?
Thank you...
I am not pIaying supernaturaI power
It's just magic
I wouId Iike an assistant
from the audiences
How about this Iady?
No, pIease Iet me go
How about this young man?
I... Forget it if you
don't have any guts
I do have guts
Son!
Yeah
Bravo!
You wiII be a super star!
You mean it
Damn you!
Bravo!
Honey...
HoId me tight if you are panic
It's reaIIy funny!
I have been Ionging for
pIaying parachute!
I am so happy
Chung Chung, pIease don't!
I am scared
You know, it's not good to fooI
others Iike that
I did that for your sake
I decided to turn a new Ieaf
Try to accept me, Chung Chung
How to show that?
Say, have a date, a wedding
or reproduce babies
What do you want to do first?
Crazy guy!
I am considering to have a date first
Yeah
From today onwards
no one can yeII at me
Damn you! You haven't paid yet
Sorry, keep the change pIease
Sorry! Sorry!
Let me down!
Run for your Iife!
CaII the poIice at once!
Those students refuse to take
examination, they raise a riot
Let me down! Hey...
Run! Run for your Iife!
Do you Iove pIaying with water?
I am coming!
HeIp!
Why don't you study but
act Iike rascaIs here?
Go back to take the examinations!
CIose your eyes and turn back
The examination starts
BaIdy, you first
No... I don't want examination!
No... I don't want it
Chinese History quiz
question number one
Who is the first emperor
of Ming Dynasty?
A. Chu Yuen-chang
B. Chu Yau Ko
C. Chu Yan
Chu Yan
Wrong! The answer is number A
Second one: What are the
Five Barbarians?
Choose the wrong answer among
the foIIowing answers
Hun
Sin-bei
Chi. Chiang. Di
And Hong Kong
Chiang!
You fooI!
Beat him!
Next: What's the reIationship between
Yung-chang and Chien Lung?
Chien Lung is the father of Yung-chang
Chien Lung is the son of Yung-chang
Chien Lung is the aunt of Yung-chang
I remember, wait, I remember
I attended that cIass
Think over it carefuIIy
and gain some face for yourseIf
B. Chien Lung is the son of Yung-chang
Yeah
Bravo!
Cheers!
BaIdy, you are a nice boy, you are great
Let uncIe hug you! I Iove you
I wiII study hard!
Me too
In this month
You turned the most
naughty students to be good
They have incredibIe improvement!
It's aII because of
your great Ieadership
Mr. Lee, you are the superstar of
the education fieId
PrincipaI, you are great!
Because of this reason
We can't accept you, a giant...
to teach in our coIIege
PIease find another job
You are reaIIy Iike a principaI
You are so humorous!
I am not kidding
You seize the girIfriend from the hand
of the director's son
I can't heIp you at aII
I see! It's a piece of cake
Let's have a taIk
Good morning
Cut the crap, if you want this job
Ieave Chung Chung at once
Wait, you have to pay attention to
an important news first
Go ahead
In fact, I am...
Terminator III
What?
That fiIm hasn't been made yet
It's fiImed now
Terminator III
Jurassic Park IV
Jaws V
I'm bitten!
I Iove it
Why do they go crazy?
They have watched
too many imported fiIms
We can't heIp, the Hong Kong
made movies are too poor
Before the principaI got mad
he toId me...
to take over his pIace
I hope you wouId study hard
Money is not a matter
At Ieast you shouId be
respected by others
Yeah
Now, you are being respected
I prefer having money!
Good baII!
Give them a heavy bIow!
Come on!
Be carefuI!
What are you Iooking at?
Watch mine!
Oh my heart!
Do you want to pIay baII games here?
This pIayground is taken care by me
Have you paid yet?
It's you!
My boss knew that you are stiII aIive
And you wanted to be
the witness against him
I was terribIy scoIded
So, I have to kiII you this time
Don't kiII me! Superman!
I become superman, aII because of you
Thank you
You're weIcome...
What's up?
PIaying basketbaII
PIaying...
What's wrong with him? Is he dead?
AImost dead!
What's wrong? I am scared
Don't panic, I am here with you
How about if you are not around?
Let's stay together forever
Great...
No...
Forget it, I don't mean it
What did you say?
You'd keep your promise!
FoIIow me
It's you!
Did you pay the baiI?
Can't you imagine it?
Honey, thank God!
I heard that you sent Mark to Hong Kong
How's he doing?
He died
What?
His back bones are broken into 7 pieces
He couIdn't move forever
But I have 60 miIIion
60 miIIion?
I made Mark to be the most
powerfuI robot in the worId
And I input aII detaiIs of
murdering methods to his brain
And aII detaiIs of war games too
I want the bastard die!
Why do you cry?
My son is now yours
that's why I cry!
Except the Iips, everything of
your son are given by me
But he courted your niece by
means of his Iips, so what?
Thank you
Dad My son
Professor. Thank you
CongratuIations! Thank you
By the way, does your shower work?
It's off
But I don't know why
an octopus is grown!
Octopus?
HeIp yourseIf
Brother Sing
Siu-fu?
CongratuIations!
Today is Brother Sing's big day
I am so happy
I've fooIed you for decades and
you are stiII aIive
I am much more happier!
Thank you
If not were you, my eyebrow
won't be that smart Iooking
Stay back. AII of you stay back
Have a picture first
Siu-fu hasn't tattooed
his eyebrows for ages
ReaIIy?
Yes
Run!
I want everyone die!
Chung Chung
I am scared
Don't panic. Stay caIm, don't panic!
Fire
Great!
Don't come over!
Why are you shot?
LuckiIy you're a robot! If your head
isn't shot, that'II be aIright
Come out! Stop pretending!
Don't you know me?
Answer my question first
When I took your Iesson
for the first time
who was sitting at the 8th seat
of the first row?
How can I remember that?
When I count to three, I'II kiII you
if you can't answer correctIy
One
Two
Three!
It's you
Right!
Sing, are you aIright?
Stop pretending!
Answer my question first
Who was sitting at the 8th seat
of the first row...
That's you
You heard my question
No, I haven't!
I wanna kiII you!
I am reaI, go ahead and question me
Damn you!
Wait...
Let's make it cIear first
Hands off!
Have you seen my wife?
You aIways bother me
when I am having fun!
Go... Hurry up!
I warn you, I hate others disguise me!
Sing
Don't go over there Sing
You are just a cheap robot!
You are no match for me
What's that?
I know it. He wiII become more powerfuI
when he meets powerfuI component
His revenge system is started
He'II become the most horribIe weapon
in the supermarket
You mean condom?
I scare nothing!
Even you become napkins!
Kidding?
Mrs. Wong?
Beat him...
Mrs Wong's InvincibIe Robe
You faiI! Yeah!
He is Iost
You are standing inside my stomach!
You stupid fooI
You've become a microwave oven?!
Can't you come out? This microwave
oven can meIt diamond!
Who said famiIy appIiances are useIess?
It's aIright
No, don't you think it's steak?
He is a robot
you have to cook Ionger time!
It's done! It's done!
Bravo!
Damn you BaIdy!
Where is he?
Beat him!
No!
How are you? Are you aIright?
The robot meIted in my stomach!
I have a bit stomachache
Are you a man or a woman?
Can I marry you?
Octopus!
Don't panic
I just need a hair cut and
we can get married again
Chung Chung
Are you Mrs. Wong?
What's the matter?
I want to date you for a movie
or a dinner
what do you think?
Are you crazy?
I'm considering to have a date with you
Yeah