LOVE IMPOSSIBLE
Produced by Jong-hwi Ju
In-sung Jo, Sa-rang Kim
Hyung-jin Gong, Young-ran Heo
Directed by Cho-shin Jung
Ancient tombs found
in Yanbian, China
Estimated to date from Goguryeo
Era, perhaps 2,000 years ago
North and South Korea to form
a joint-excavation party
Hi!
It's been a while, man.
Ah, the lovely scent of perfume!
Girls, here comes Chul-soo,
your prince!
- Let's go.
- Come on!
She looks hot.
'Blue Marine'?
How did you know?
Oh my!
You're the cutest guy
I've ever seen!
Where did you buy
that perfume?
I'd like to get it
for my girlfriend
She's your type.
Say hi.
Hi there.
She's way past her expiration date.
Hey cutie, where's your table?
Hey, good-looking!
Wow, Chul-soo, she's a fox!
She's mine, boys.
Come on.
How's it going?
What's this?
- What are you doing?!
- A piece of string!
So long.
Let's light it!
Let me set you on fire tonight.
They made it to the finals
through harsh competition.
Now the final round begins!
Let me read the question.
In 1975... our Great Leader,
Comrade Kim II Sung...
...visited an industrial site
and gave a speech.
What was his teaching
on that day?
A Great Leader of
the Korean peoples...
A forerunner that leads
the history of Asia...
A respected revolutionary...
The Sun of the race,
Lantern of Asia...
He got it wrong?
The order's mixed up.
- 'Lantern of Asia' comes first.
- That's right!
In the course of his life,
his only concern was...
...to make our lives better off.
He couldn't put more emphasis...
...on increasing the output
of cereals, and...
He's wrong again!
It's grains, not cereals.
You're joking, aren't you?
You're so funny.
I need to look for a job.
There's no way
I'm going to Yanbian.
Mr. Chul-soo Kim. Do you think you could
find a job in the real world?
What a mean thing to say!
You're too mean.
Hi. What's your name?
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
- Mr. Kim.
- Yes?
What do you want a job for?
What?
I'm not gonna be a bum
after I graduate.
- Mr. Kim.
- Yes?
You crack me up!
I know.
Forget about it.
Because you're not graduating!
What are you talking about?
A supreme commander
of the armed forces...
The almighty leader of
the Korean peoples...
General Kim Jong-il...
...has made our military invincible...
...on the road to completing
- the revolution.
- Not a single mistake!
The hardest part is over.
She's going to win!
The morale of our military
soars high to the sky...
...and our passion reaches
every corner of the world...
...like the violent waves
of the oceans!
- Mr. Chul-soo Kim.
- Yes?
This is your last chance.
- If you go to Yanbian...
- What?
...I'll let you graduate.
I'm not going!
You'll be the representative.
No way!
No? That's a shame.
I thought you might
be interested.
I've got to get going.
Bye.
Screw the tombs!
I'm busy enough trying
to dig up chicks in Seoul.
You'll be going with college girls
Our Great Leader,
Comrade Kim II Sung...
...designed this competition
for college students.
And the Kim II Sung Award goes to...
...an archeology major
at Kim II Sung University...
...Comrade Young-hee Oh!
You can't film here!
This is the National Intelligence Service!
No filming the NIS!
Dad!
Calm down.
You're totally mistaken.
Mistaken, my ass!
Dad... you really hit me...
in my stomach... hard...
I meant to!
I might as well disown you,
you pathetic Casanova!
Put it down.
Going to Yanbian for what?
To pick up girls?
Is that the latest hot spot for
hooking up or something?!
Dad!
Relax, okay?
Like I said, you totally got it wrong.
Save it!
I don't want to hear it.
I'm not lying!
Why did you take it off?
Because I'm hot!
If not for girls, what would
you go there for?
- Dad!
- Don't 'dad' me!
In this building,
I am an NIS director!
It's to graduate!
That's why I'm going!
To graduate?
That's right!
I'm shy of some credits
to graduate.
They'll give me credits
for going there.
I swear it's not about girls.
What are you doing?
Anybody there?
So, it's for credits?
Dad, let's have some tea.
Sure.
You must be really close.
I mean, hugging like that.
Huh?
You're a carbon copy of
your father.
So handsome!
He looks more like
his late mom.
Are you okay?
God, you've got coffee
all over your legs.
Miss Kim, get me
a glass of water.
- Yes, sir.
- Why don't you...?
Sorry I lost it there.
And I'm about to!
To graduate?
If you're lying,
you're dead meat.
Hi, Professor. Lee.
This is Chul-soo's dad.
How are you?
Let me ask you something.
Does my son have to go
to Yanbian?
What happened to that
glass of water?
Thanks. Bye.
Start packing!
If you mess up again...
I will bury you next to that tomb!
I should've sent him
to the military academy.
Young-hee.
I'm so proud of you!
Suitors will be
lining up after you.
You must be tired. Go to bed.
- Goodnight, father.
- You, too.
Why'd you bring it up?
She's still too young
to get married!
Don't be like that.
It's for her sake.
Have you forgotten?
When you proposed to me...
...you said love was all
that counted.
Give her some space.
Pipe down!
I'll make sure she marries
only the best.
Just watch!
'Screams echo away
as waves in the ocean...'
'A beautiful youth,
beautiful memories...'
Gosh, I missed it again!
I can't breathe, singing this!
This is way harder than
memorizing speeches!
Isn't that Young-hee Oh?
Right!
An archeology major
at Kim II Sung University
Who's going?
- Why don't I...
- No way!
Don't you have some things
with you from Japan?
You give it a shot.
She won't fall for them.
Every girl is materialistic.
It's a piece of cake.
Let me go talk to her.
Aren't you Young-hee Oh?
You won the Knowledge
Competition, didn't you?
How'd you know?
I thought so.
I was in the competition, too.
I didn't do well, though.
I see.
Young-hee.
This is for you.
Wow, isn't this Coke?
This is so hard to get around here.
No thanks. I can't take it.
Please, I want you to!
And... Young-hee...
Can I see you tomorrow?
Why don't we...
You pathetic player!
You gotta study harder.
Wow!
Young-hee!
Sorry I'm late.
What's that boy doing
on the ground?
Beats me, Hae-young. He was there
when I got here.
Is that true?
Don't be too excited.
I'd never send you to Yanbian.
But it's a direct order
from our Great Leader.
I couldn't say no to him.
I'll do my best as the leader
of the excavation party.
Keep this in mind.
There'll be boys from the South.
So behave yourself.
Okay?
Don't worry.
I won't let you down.
- Father.
- What?
Thank you so much!
What are you doing?
Stop it!
Don't thank me.
Thank our Great Leader.
Eat well
and be a good girl.
Where the hell is he?
What the...
This is... Aren't you hot, Mr. Kim?
Welcome!
We've been expecting you.
Thanks.
Girls of Yanbian...
Here I am!
Others are coming tomorrow.
It's small, but you'll find it
to your liking.
If you need anything,
call me at the embassy.
Thank you.
This is so exciting!
Let's unpack.
Do you like you room?
Let's go.
I've once dug up a tomb twice
the size of a mountain.
No big deal, though.
That's a primary school.
3 years ago...
...we found one, 10 times
bigger than a pyramid.
You can count on me.
You got yourself an expert.
In Yanbian, Il-Pyong is known
as Mr. Tomb!
Who's that?
Oh, I forgot to tell you!
My name's Il-Pyong Kang.
Look,
Il- Pyong.
Don't mind the tombs.
Your job is to dig up
chicks for me. Okay?
What, aren't you a guide?!
I am.
You can go home now.
I'm off to do market research.
What a self-absorbed ass!
That way goes to the park,
not any markets.
The scenery is breathtaking,
you idiot!
Help me!
Help!
I can't swim!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
He's here.
Come on in!
What do you want?
You ditched me like I was...
What on earth are you
giggling about?
Find a girl for me.
A girl?
That's right!
That's an attitude, man.
What girl?
I ran into her today.
She's gorgeous.
Where?
At the park.
Talk about a needle in
a haystack...
What does she look like?
Long-nosed like me...
Her thick lips were so sensual.
About 170-cm-tall...
Kind of slim, but graceful.
For instance...
Like this lady!
Let me see.
You've got unique tastes
in women, Chul-soo.
You're into middle-aged
Just the style, man!
She's my mom!
She looks so generous.
As you know,
this kind of thing costs...
- Right!
- the more, the better.
- Yes.
- Some more.
Don't worry about it.
What's this?
Am I looking for a dog?
This is a joke.
Let me give you some more.
Here you go.
This is like 30 dollars.
What is this shit?
Excuse my language.
You go find her,
you ignorant cheapskate!
I thought that was a lot
for you guys here.
What the hell...
This is what I'm taking about!
Fork it over, nitwit.
Hang on.
You want South Korean money?
It costs a lot of money
to find a person.
Hold on!
Yanbian isn't the boondocks.
This is more like it, dolt.
Stop calling me names!
This is Yanbian, and
I'm much older than you.
I can call you whatever
I want to. Okay?
I'll find her for you.
Don't you worry a thing.
Where the hell is she?
Hey!
Where have you been all day?
Sorry, Hae-young.
Have you eaten?
You haven't eaten all day?
Grab your bowl there.
Slow down, girl.
Happy to be away from
that 'get married' garbage?
Even rice tastes better here.
It's sweeter than honey!
The North Koreans are running late.
They'll be here shortly.
Just my luck!
I can't believe the professor
is the prettiest woman here.
Yes? Got a question?
Of course not.
I'm so getting back at him!
Oh, they're here!
Who?
What?
He's so cute!
Cute? Please!
We should've sat in the back.
Why don't you guys say hi
to one another?
It's a stone tomb from
the Goguryeo Era.
Relatively small,
but its historical value...
...can't be overemphasized.
This project is very significant.
Why is he staring at us?
He must have a crush on me!
This tomb...
very important...
My heart's pounding so hard!
He's looking at the professor.
I'm telling you!
He's checking us out.
You've got to be watch him!
Many ancient Goguryeo tombs
have been found here.
In this circled area alone...
...more than 10 of them have
been unearthed over the years.
Don't be shy,
you cutie you.
A military post stood here
during the Japanese rule.
So, be cautious at all times.
Chul-soo Kim from South Korea?
Yes, ma'am!
I'm the party leader.
He's the leader of the South?
Good for you!
Young-hee Oh from North Korea?
Yes, ma'am.
Let's work hard together
to find the tomb.
It will be a step toward
reunifying the two Koreas.
Step forward, please.
Shake hands.
Your hand is so soft.
Please...
Young-hee!
That's your name, right?
I was wondering...
- What are you doing?
- Huh?
You came all the way here
to hit on girls?
You think you're hot stuff?
You totally got me wrong.
As leaders of both parties,
we've got things to discuss.
Zip it up!
Zip up what?
Hey. You.
Don't forget what you're here for.
Later!
Young-hee, let's go.
I know what I'm here for!
Lord almighty...
The wind feels so creepy,
doesn't it?
- Look, Chul-soo.
- What?
You know the girl
you asked me to find?
- Yes.
- I found her.
Where?
Look straight ahead.
- She's the one, isn't she?
- Right.
I thought so.
Check out that bomb
next to her.
Getting rid of her
won't be easy.
You can say that again.
Any ideas?
No matter how bad,
there's always a way out.
Let me tell you.
I was with the bomb squad...
...serving in the Chinese
People's Army...
...defusing bombs...
Oh, that!
You're a fast learner, Huh?
I'm smarter than you think.
Whatever.
You know what?
It might look easy to you.
But a bomb like her is very
hard to defuse.
Yes. But...
Give me a little more.
You won't be sorry.
Can I write this off?
Just kidding!
This is enough.
This'll help me...
disarm her.
I'm counting on you.
Chul-soo, trust me.
We're compatriots.
I'll blow her into pieces.
She's done for.
They've got everything
here in Yanbian.
So do we in the Republic!
- Young-hee.
- What?
Look!
Isn't that a dance club?
Let's go there tonight
and have some fun.
Comrade, are you nuts?
That's a symbol of
corrupt capitalism.
Stop calling me comrade!
It's so embarrassing.
Stop yelling at me.
This is China.
Whatever I call you,
they don't understand.
Please, go.
Think of it as studying,
experiencing new things.
Over my dead body!
Fine! Let's not!
Don't be upset.
Hae-young.
Do this for me. Please!
Putting on lipstick is
harder than studying.
Everything is hard at first.
I'll help you put it on in a minute.
Get over here and help me
fix my lips now!
I thought you didn't want to go?
Okay, I'll do it now.
Look.
What's the matter now?!
What if diplomats or other
students see us?
No diplomats here!
And the others won't rat on us...
...because that means
they were here, too.
Forget about them
and let's have fun.
Still...
Stop being a party pooper!
Keep your mouth shut
and follow me!
So many cute boys here!
You call that dancing?
They dance like zombies!
I'll get you girls a table.
Even the waiters are cute here!
Right here, girls.
Have a seat.
What can I get you?
Chinese beer. You?
- Beer from Pyongyang.
- I'll be right back.
- Look who's here!
- What are you doing here?
Mind if we sit?
You already have!
Who would've imagined
running into you here!
This club rocks!
Yes, sir?
A bottle of whiskey...
Some beer?
- 10 bottles!
- You heard the man.
Shake a leg, okay?
On the double.
Bite it hard!
Let's party like there's no tomorrow.
Wow, that was quick.
How'd he do that?
Awesome!
Are you guys ready?
You bet!
Here we go.
Grab your...
She must be a drinker.
That's good for us.
What's up with you?
Slow down.
What a finish!
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
It's called a 'Cannon Shot'
in the Republic.
Go ahead.
Me?
My stomach...
I need to hit the head.
What a wimp!
Where are you going?
Is she okay?
Never been at a disco with a man.
I have, but not with a pretty
girl like you.
Let's get to know each other better.
Stop peeking.
But they Look so good.