Many years ago in Thailand
there is a temple that was called the temple of the Golden Buddha.
And there was a huge statue of the Golden Buddha.
And word came to his village where the
monastery was
that an army from neighboring country
was about to invade.
And they've got the brilliant scheme to cover the
Golden Buddha which is quite large with
mud and concrete so better look basicly
like a stone Buddha and the army would
perceive no value in it.
Sure enough this army rolled in with its ... arms and weapons
and as they passed by the monastery the
y saw nothing but a big stone Buddha
and they have no reason to plunder it
Well years went by because the army
continued to occupy
until there was a time in the monestary and the village when no one remembered
that the Buddha was golden until one day a
young monk was sitting on the Buddha
meditating on his knee
and as he got up a little piece of concrete
happened to crack off and he saw something
shiny. He realized there was gold under
there
and so he ran to his fellow monks and said
"The Buddha is golden, the Buddha is golden",
and they all came out and realized he is telling the
truth
they took the pics and harass. And
eventually they unearthed
the Golden Buddha.
So what's a metaphor here? The
metaphor is that each of us is golden by
nature were born golden
we were born high, we were born knowing, were born
connected to our bliss, were born knowing
truth, we were born knowing everything that every
great spiritual master has ever said,
we were one with the Christ, the Buddha, everyone
but then we went to school and they said you had to be just like this,
and they said these are sweat boys and sweat girls, white people and black people and on and on and on,
and so we developed the casing of stone
over the Buddha
to ... at a young age, maybe four or
five six or seven,
we believe that we are the stone Buddha, not the Golden one.
And then, something comes along that
cracks that casing,
maybe it's an injury, a divorce,
financial setbacks, our governmental change,
something that really scares us and bugs us (??HÃ)
and knocks off a piece of our armour,
and all in that moment that the armour is being
knocked off, they get a look inside
and see the golden.
Let me tell you
friend, that the moment you see that gold
the armour and the concrete will never
satisfy you again.
At that point you truly
enter to the true heroe's adventure
an all you want to do for the rest of
your life is pick away the stone because
the gold is so much more fun.
Finding Joe
- A film by Patrick Takaya Solomon
(suggested subtitle instead of this for SEO purposes):
The Hero's Journey Movie - Joseph Campbell
Who is Joseph Campbell and why
should we care?
(Robert Walter - President: Joseph Campbell Foundation)
A topic that comes up a lot.
Joseph Campbell was one of the leading
mythology experts of all time
Joseph Campbell is a philosopher. The
man who had this ability to see the
truth
in a world where we've lost sight of
that in many ways.
He has studied all of these classical myth
traditions
(Brian Johnson Philosopher/Entrepreneur, entheos.com)
and actually started by studying
Native American mythology. He fell in
love with it when he was a kid.
This was his bliss. He went on
studying the aboriginal cultures
he studied Greek mythology, he studied
Arthurian legend,
He dissected and really diagrammed
all of our stories.
He compared
philosophies, mythic stories
of the whole world.
All myths, all movies all novels,
all romances
He found this one story within
(Chungling Al Huang, Founder-President: Living Tao Foundation / Tai Ji Master)
all the stories, that we can relate to, no
matter where you come from.
He recognized that in spite of all the
different stories we seem to be telling,
there is really only one.
And He called it the Hero's Journey.
There must have been thousands and
thousands of hero's stories
(Gay Hendricks Ph.D., best selling author, The Hendricks Institute)
from every culture, but until Joseph Campbell
came along
certainly I never realized how they all
kind of fit together and how they were
basically the same story.
I was religion major in college. I was
taking my final exam.
(Rashida Jones - Actress/Screenwriter)
I had a moment where I've just gobsmacked.
It was just like
holy crap, it's all the same thing. I mean it
is really
all the same thing.
The hero's journey is a pattern. You can
almost think of it as an algorythm,
that has three basic parts:
separation, initiation and return.
Separation: you are in one kind of a
reality
in one kind of a place and you are separated
from it.
Initiation: you're put into another
place, where you are in some manner
initiated.
Return: you come back.
A SIMPLE VERSION OF THE HERO'S JOURNEY
is, someone starting out in their normal
protected world
(Catherine Hardwicke, Director of "Twilight")
and then getting a call to adventure.A call to adventure.
There's a vision, there's a quest.
(Deepak Chopra M.D.)
It's the story of the hero enduring some trials,
(David L. Miller Ph.D.)
various trials and ordeals,
meeting different obstacles along the
way.
People that hurt you.
People that help you.
Doors will open as
Campbell would say
for you where there are no doors
for others.
Dragons will appear that are your
your dragons alone.
you get to like ??? /meet?? the innermost cave where
you're really challenged,
like the greatest crisis, in which you find your
true self.
The achievement, the glory.
But then
that's not the end of it,
that he has to bring that back to the
community,
there's a return to tell the story.
That is
a heroic journey.
Separation, initiation, return.
All of the
adventures of the human story are in there.
All the heroes, all villains, all the gods and
goddesses and all of the nights and of all
the fantastic creatures we can conjure
up in animation, they're all in there,
Because they're all in here in the heart,
because they're all in here in the head.
This is
where they come from.
If you look at some of the greatest
pieces of literature
(Robin Sharma, best selling author, Sharma Leadership International)
the greatest works of philosophy, they
all have what
Joseph Campbell called The Hero's Journey.
And
if you look with a piercing eye
you can recognize his outline in just about
any move your story you would read.
Star Wars, The Matrix, Harry Potter.
Wizard
of Oz: that's a classic story of the hero's journey.
You first see Dorothy
and our natural environment and just
like out here in regular life
a person is operating in their natural
environment every day
and living in their house and that kind of thing.
And then something happens to shake
that world up,
And you go on a journey in which you have to
face certain tests and challenges
Storytelling is typically about
people
learning something.
You go to a place which is dark and
mysterious,
you are faced with yourself
there is a relationship between facing fear
and this kind of soul game.
You acquire a quality, a hidden strength, a value,
moments where somebody is tested
somebody moves to a place where
it feels like a crisis point and then
they are
restored, redeemed, made better
through that trial.
And we call them heros.
If all of these stories boiled down into one map, ???
we can use that map, because all
human beings are the same ???
whether they're going through
a war like World War II or going to a
war inside ???
it's basically the same kind of
process. ???
In other words we're not separate from the characters
we see
in our movies and our novels,
they are us, this one journey.
The whole idea of the hero's journey is a journey of
life,
clear patterns to guide you through. ]]]
You're born, you have a childhood,
you have adolescence
and you try to find the place for you to become an adult. ]]]
and you go through
adventures,
you struggle with the inner conflicts
and finally you become a hero: you slay
the dragons,
you succeed in conquering all the demons
and use them (???) to step over threshold ]]]
and finally you have arrived.
We're all born, we die but within this short
span
we have to have some meaning, some
reason for this existence. ]]]
Doesn't have to be higher mighty and fantastic ]]
You can have a very simple life
and still go through the very similar pattern
We've grown up watching great heros' journey movie,
it's that impulse within us
that seed of potential that wants to be
actualized.
It's being talked to during those movies
and being whispered to: ]]]
"It's time for you to do that!"
That's the story here, that's what it's
all about.
It is a wonderful narrative, iconography for how to live life.
The idea that "Try hard, you get", the little
engine that "I could, I think I can,
I think can, I think I think I can, I CAN!"
This idea that we really can do
better, be better
that our greatest selves are still hidden and
that the future is the prospect
of coming to terms with that self.
Dorothy had to confront her inner
barriers
and so the journey she went on was not
just a journey to
find out how to deal with the Wicked
Witch of the West, ]]]
it was how to deal with her own inner resources
,
how to claim her own inner resources ]]]
and at the end of the
movie how did she get back home?
Well, she cicked her heels together, so she
had it all the time,
the ability to get back home but it
didn't get mobilized for her
until she went through all of those
challenges and was able to kind of test herself.
It's kind of the ordinary moving into the
extraordinary.
Its going through the dark to come out
to the light.
Going from an
unsatisfying life to
a satisfying life
by pushing through
the scariest things you can imagine.
"The funcion of mythological symbols is to give you a sense of
Aha! Yes. I know what it is, it's myself" - Joseph Campbell
The most important thing that the myths teach us
is to go beyond
what we perceive as
the limits of our possibility.
So mythology
needs to be seen for what it is which is: ]]]
which is
a metaphor for our human existence.
It's not a history lesson. It's a
metaphor for life
and for universal experiences.
Lot of
people reading myths and they say
it refers to something historical:
the creation of the world or something like. But Joe didn't think that.
He thought that it's really a narrative
about the psyche.
What Jung called the self.
The problem is that many of us
are metaphorically impaired.
We don't realize that this thing that
they're talking about is actually a
metaphor
for a transformation process.
Just kind of
like the Holy Grail, where it's not the thing,
]]]]
it's not the
actual concrete Grail, it's an intangible thing,
that the Holy Grail is a metaphor for that in
tangible (???) feeling.
And so if you look at a book and it says
you will go to heaven,
and you don't realize that they're
talking about heaven on Earth,
heaven in our bodies, heaven right now, in the now,  ]]]
you might fall into a trance of
thinking that you're literally gonna go
some place else if you follow the rules.
Having been brought up in a mythical
culture,
I was very familiar with the different
motives,
and themes that were encapsulated
in say a mythical being.
Whether it was the Lord Shiva or Ganesh,
or a goddess,
just thinking the name of that person, the whole story was evoked.
Carl Jung called these archetypes.
Archetypes of primordial,
encapsulated stories or
mythologies and they are there
in this form of a seed in consciousness.
When you plant that seed in consciousness,
that archetypal seed,
that mythical journey,
in there the seed starts to sprout and as it sprouts,
the patterning forces create situation, circumstances,
events and relationships for the unfolding
of the story.
It's better to have a story to look
through life ]]]
than an explanation. ]]]
The reason for
that is the story is richer.
I say select two or three heros and heroins
either in mythology
or religion
or history and then ask these
mythical beings to incarnate through you.
And then don't be surprised when you see
situations ,circumstances,
coincidences, synchronicities,
relationships
sure suddenly show up,
that actually are part of the story that you
have been seeking to express.
Once upon a time in the forest there was
this little tiger cub
amongst the flock sheep.
And he ate grass,
and he wondered around with the sheep,
and when he tried to say anything all
that came out was a certain a little meow.
Not much of a roar.
And one day through the forest comes a
large male tiger
And he is just about to pounce on the sheep when he sees this tiger cub.
He says, what are you doing here?
And the tiger cub goes, beeee.
He picks the tiger cub up by the s??? of the neck,
and carries him over to pond and
he puts his face over and he says: ]]]
"Look, see that face?  ]]]
You're not a sheep, you're a tiger!" ]]]
The male tiger says, okay, we need to do
something.
He slays a sheep and he grabs a big runk ??? of meet,
and he shoves it into the little tiger's mouth.
And the little tiger gagged on it as all do on the truth. ]]]
But it went down. ]]]
And he got a little bit of energy, and pretty soon, ]]]
he had a bigger tiger roar.
And eventually he had a full Tiger roar and he went off with the male tiger.
I think the moral here is self-evident:
if you're a tiger living among sheep
you' rea a really poor specimen of a tiger
.
And we are all Tigers living among sheep.
We are all individuals with a self
that we don't even begin to understand
and.
And unfortunately, when you can open
the metaphor out,
the food we get from the culture around us is maybe food for sheep.
It's not food for Tigers.
"Your life is the fruit of your own doing.
You have no one to blame but yourself" - Joseph Campbell
We have to catch at least the spark
of what your life is going to be
or you may spend those dreary decades
in corporate America, climbing
the ladder only to discover its against
the wrong wall.
You get to the top, who cares?
If this path of the hero's journey is
fairly simple in design,
why then isn't it that everybody is a living
it?
Well the answer is that most people on
the planet live under a kind of a
mass hypnosis.
There's a tremendous pressure even in
the media
on really keeping people in their place
in the sense of keeping them happy,
tranced out consumers.
It's a trance of comfort, it's a
trance of
not sticking your hand up above
the crowd very much.
That keeps the enterprise going.
Most people
think it's a luxury and a great privilege
to stay home and look at their 800 inch
television
you're just spaced out, not developoing.
We're stimulated by some images, by some loud noise.
It's about collecting things and stuff,
and making a lot of money and doing a lot of
things and it's
impossible to enjoy that because you end up on that treadmill
and you can't get off.
And so most people, unfortunately, because
they are
so victimized by the environment, they
have no time to think,
or be themselves, they become bundles
of conditioned reflexes
and nerves that are constantly being
triggered by people and circumstance,
into very predictable outcomes and
predictable patterns of behavior, ]]]
there's no creativity
That's the trance, that's the wasteland,
where we're just guided toward this
weird sense of what's real on our
lives,
and those ideas that are imposed on us
from the outside
about what we should and should not do.
It usually starts out with something like
you shouldn't talk to that person
because they're from a different tribe,
you certainly shouldn't marry that
person ]]]
you should go to this school,
you should have a certain type of car
, you should live in a certain type of house,
you should have a certain number of
kids by this type age,
should should should should should. ]]]
What I experienced in my own life was I gotta have
the degree from this university, I
gotta have this advanced degree from this
University preferably either
a law degree or a medical degree or
something to that effect
some letters after my name which would
say that I have a stamp of credibility
I can go out and make my
six figures in society, ??? kind of deem me worthy ]]]
I have countless
examples of young people who
go to college because they are expected to
go to college
and they study biology because  ]]]
since the
time they were six they were supposed to be a doctor. ]]]
It's very difficult for a
person who was brought up in this
environment of instant gratification with
the media
and with advertising with all the promises
of instant gratification by
buying something, for example, or having
a certain
level of afluence that you lose
contact with this mythical domain
which is actually part of your soul. It's there in everyone.
It's their passion, it's their bliss, it's their unique skills.
it's their unique good ways of expressing
themselves,
is their soul / song ???, which if they think,  ]]]
they
could do anything.
If you look at every heroic journey, the hero
has been confronted with the fact that
the world that they thought was reality
was nothing more than illusion.
I go back to The Matrix... what
was the matrix?
It was just this big illusion, it
was the dominant values and beliefs
that the world had put around this guy
Neo, the seeker on the hero's journey,
and what did he do? He felt this longing
to go beyond the illusion, to go beyond
the matrix,
So he took the red pill, and he woke up to
reality.
And what was reality? Reality was he was full of
potential.
"The call to adventure
signifies that destiny has summoned the hero..." - Joseph Campbell
Separation begins with what we call "The
call to adventure".
Campbell tells us there's literally
almost a phone ringing. ]]]
It's like the universe,
the divine, god, whatever you want to call
it, literally dialing you up and ringing ]]]
and giving you a call
asking you to step out into what is your
journey. ]]]
Something breaks into the ???? reality
and makes it impossible for you to continue.
Well, you can hang up the phone, you can
run away.
But he'll ??? keep coming back,
it will keep coming back until you finally
answer the call.
If you're not paying attention, the wake
up calls come in the form of a
sledge hammer.
You know if you're paying attention, they
might come in a tical ??? feather.
So we don't always get the call as a
choir of angels
with trumpets singing ??? to his??? beautifully
warm sunny morning.
In Star Wars, Luke comes back as his house has been burnt down.
He's gotta go.
Often times it comes in ??? the depth of our
despair
in losing a job, getting fired,
getting divorced,
having your house foreclosed on... These
things that you would never
want to have happen are ??? often the
exact things we need
to catapult us, to catalyse us into that next version of ourselves. ]]]
Bad
things happen to good people
and when that happens to them they typically are
thrown for a loop ??? because they
frequently have felt everything's going along,
I'm doing everything right, what happened..
Well, you know, the universe has just up ended you
and it does do that.
The Chinese symbol for crises is too
symbols.
The first one is danger and the second one immediately is opportunity.
So crisis both enjoy an
opportunity
This idea that if one storyline
collapses that that's the end of the
movie is
not true in human life and never was true in human life.
I know people who have prospered in the most
extraordinary way
in the worst type of adversity, but actually it revealed something to them about
themselves that they didn't know
and that became the new journey they
took.
Let me put this into really
practical hundred-pound terms because if
the camera had been pointed
at me when I was 24 years old what it
would have seen was a person who weighed
320 pounds
you would have seen me puffing on two or three
packs of Marlboros a day,
a relationship that I didn't want to be in
and I had a job I hated,
everything was wrong in my life and so
those are ripe moment for a wake-up call
in life.
You know, if you haven't been paying
attention enough so that you end up with
a job you hate,
a relationship you don't want to be in, a a
body you don't like,
and you're addicted to a bunch of things,
you're ripe
for a sledgehammer blow from the
universe and I got it.
You step over a threshold, meaning you
move from one world into another,
sometimes you're shoved from one world
into the other.
I went out for a walk and I stepped on
the ice
on the road and my feet shot out from under
me and I smacked my back of my head
on the ground, frozen ground, and it
knocked me out just enough I wasn't
completely unconscious but I had a
vision
while I was semi-knocked out, I could
see down through all the layers of myself
to this pure consciousness inside
and I could see how all the fat I
had was organized around a whole ]]]
bunch of feelings I didn't want to let myself
feel,   ]]]
like sadness from childhood  ]]]
and lot of old grief in
my family and anger and things like that
and I realized that the fat was there to
keep me from
feeling those feelings and so as I began
to come back to normal consciousness
I made a vow that I was gonna change my
life
so that I could live in that state of
pure consciousness instead of having to
have all of that
armour around me.
Once you make the decisions that Joseph
Campbell is talking about,
about really hearing the call and being
willing to take on the challenges
of that new awakened life, once you do
that you begin to feel a power ]]]
that it's like nothing else I have ever experienced.
And I think a lot of us are just plain very afraid of that. ????? ]]]
I tend to think that people wake up to
the fact ]]]
that they're the hero of their own life
when they get tired of being the victim of their own life.
At the point that you
say "Enough", "I know", "I don't want to
listen to my parents anymore"
"I have had it with my boss", "I'm really
having problems perhaps
the sermon I'm being taught", you can
either surrender to victimhood
and a lot of people do, ]]]
or you can
surrender to a fundamentalism: you can basically give
your responsibility to someone else and
say "Tell me what to do and I'll do it"
or you can say "I have a choice here and
I'm responsible"
Now, what does it mean to be the hero of your own life? It means to be
responsible for your own adventure.
Campbell talks about metaphorical death
, where something dies ]]]
so the something can live
and in every hero's journey there is ]]]
some death-
moment where some old has to go on some new has to
stay.
He quotes Nietzsche and he says that "The snake
that cannot shed its skin must parish
the"
When death is a motif in a myth
it doesn't refer necessarily
to what happens at the end of one's
biological
and physical existence.
It's an indication that change has taken place.
I went through that process when I stop
ped being
[Joseph Marshall III, best selling author]
a travel administrator and started
becoming a writer
I put that aspect of myself away, it was
valuable
and I learned a lot and I draw on it,
but it enabled me to go on. ]]]
No death, no life. No death, no transformation.
No death, no change.
Than I said, okay, I don't want that anymore, I
want this, put that away
made myself into something else. In
essence, resurrected into being a writer.
The whole key to a blessing death is
recognizing that it is just the death
of one old form that has played itself out and has no use anymore,
which always, as the Phoenix, rises
and gives way to some new form that has new
intrinsic meaning and makes your life even bigger and better.
You want have new birth, new revelations
new insight into life as you grow as a
human being.
You will learn to keep dying.
"We must be willing to get rid of the life we've planned,
so as to have the life that is waiting for us" - Joseph Campbell
I think
its tricky
to afford a proof.
I think there are proofs in our
lives
I think the proofs exist in our ability
to transcend
the worst things that have happened to
us.
My proof is I was abused as a little
boy
not something I chat about typically but in this context,
it was the worst thing ever.
It went on for a very long time and...
It's who I am, in part, because I had to face that,
Because I had to wrestle with that,
because I had to accept that and acknowledge that and
forgive and all the terribly
difficult things
that come with that.
I had to tell my
parents... you know it's this...
and by the way it's one of the
things that you work with
for the rest of your life.
But from that
most difficult thing
also came a kind of
understanding
I get high marks on compassion.
I wouldn't wish it on anybody...
But it is part of what made me me.
So the truth is
it's not what happens to us,
it's what we
do with it.
The forest represents the darkness,  the unknown, the edge of your world.
And it takes the courage of a
hero
to go into that forest.
The people in your community don't
understand
why you want to go into that forest.
In fact, they are pulling you back, asking
"Why
can't you be happy with what you have here?"
But there is this urge that exist within
the hero to "Go and explore!"
Joseph often used the Knights of the Round Table.
When they behold golden chalice.
There's a story with King
Arthur,
and his knights.
After the Knights have seen the grail and
decide to go forward on a quest
the made a vow.
They decided the knightly thing to do, the
noble thing to do as individuals
seeking their own inner collective, was
to go in
to the force at their own points.
Each knight enters the forest where it was
darkest and there was no path.
They cannot follow other people. They
have to go in, find their own entry into the dark forest. ]]]
Campbell makes it really clear:
If you go into the forest
where there's already a trail, that's the
one sure sign that you're not on your path.
Because if you follow somebody else's
entry, it's somebody else's path.
That's not going into the forest. That's
not initiation.
You need to find your own path and that
kind of comes from that impulse within, to
go out and really
discover who you are, beyond just the narrow
confines of how you have been conditioned
what you have been told to do,
and go out and explore for yourself
which is true if it is and how you can
go out and rock it.
"Follow your bliss" - Joseph Campbell
The hero's journey for me is having the
courage to look within yourself and say
"What am I here to do?"
"What am I most passionate about in my
life?"
"What are my greatest gifts?"
"How do I give them to the world?"
Joseph Campbell captured it with the
phrase "Follow Your Bliss"
"Follow Your Bliss" - I don't think more profound teachings
have ever been given than this one.
"Follow your bliss" means listening to
your heart
and following your truth.
Just to be specific about the word "bliss", it's not ecstasy,
it's not happiness. There's a serenity
in bliss.
I like to talk about your bliss as "the
thing you can't not do".
So it's your authentic journey. I'd heard "
follow your bliss" but didn't know
where it came from
and what's cool is that it's grounded in
deep
Hindu spirituality and philosophy and it comes
from the Upanishads.
There were three launching points into enlightenment:
sat, chit and ananda.
So sat means beingness,
chit means consciousness and ananda means bliss or rapture.
Joseph Campbell said to himself "I don't
really know what my beingness is,
if I'm honest with myself, I don't really
know what my consciousness is,
but I do know what my bliss is and I can
follow my bliss."
And that idea of trusting ourselves and
trusting that deep impulse within us
to go out and follow our bliss, do what
makes us feel most alive:
that's the path, that's the key, that's
the essence of the hero's journey.
"Follow your bliss" does not mean: get
addicted to pleasure.
It's more than just something
you wish for. It doesn't mean escapism, it
doesn't mean hedonism.
[Lynne Kaufman, award winning playwright.]
It doesn't mean selfishness.
It doesn't mean listening only to
sensory pleasures
like having sex with anybody you look at or
sticking up a candy store if you want
candy...
Don't follow what other people think is your bliss!
Don't follow your wallet!
Follow the thing that's presenting
itself
as your most serene and fulfilling state.
Sometimes
it's difficult to let go of that
inner resistor and just say "Okay, I accept
the possibilities of the present,
I will follow my bliss, I will listen to
the call of spirit"
Huhhh, that's a very big deal!
Daddy said "What do you wanna do" I said "
I need to leave school.
I'm never gonna learn anything. I'm not
going to University.
I want to
play drums." I learned to play drums in the attic and
[Mick Fleetwood, founder: Fleetwood Mac]
That's my world and totally naive, like sshhhss...
So Dad sends me off to
London.
With the drum kit. So I went to London,
and all of it came true.
Of course, I'm not saying I gotta be rich, I gotta be famous,
but I have to be doing something I love
to do! And I have so much passion!
And I didn't even know what that was
really all about.
But I do now.
How do we find our bliss? This is what
everybody is asking.
The first thing is, ask yourself, "Where am I
passionate about?
What are the things I love doing?
What are the activities, when I engage
them,
it feels like hours go by in minutes?
That's one big clue about what your bliss is.
What I say is, find out what you most love to do!
And then do more of that thing.
Ask yourself right now: What was it that
made me
different as a child? What set me apart? What caused me to cry at night on my pillow
cause I didn't
fit in within the crowd? That is
probably
precisely where the door to your bliss
is going to open.
Go back and find it.
Let's say you never had to think about
money,
and you never had to think about dying.
With all the money in the world and all the time in the world
how would you express yourself and how
would that benefit
the ecosystem, the larger web of being?
We have to find a
a way of reflecting on those experiences
that we've had that engaged us in
where we became lost and totally absorbed in them.
So for some people a way to that might be to write these things down,
others don't think like that, they don't like to use words all the time,
so maybe collect some images or cut some images from magazines,
collect music that's always inspired you. But
some way to
bypass that apt of barrier to your own sense of energy.
It's not about
being successful,
it's not about feeding a family. Write
some bad poetry,
do something that gives you that Moment.
You can write in a journal,
because writing a journal is a conversation you
have with yourself.
You can get to know your gifts, your talents,
your weaknesses, your hopes, your dreams,
your lessons.
Joseph Campbell always gave the same
advice to his students
graduating Sarah Lawrence.
Don't do what Daddy/Mommy says!
Because Daddy/Mommy
has one interest in mind for you, and that's your
security.
And if you bargain away your life for security now,
you will never find your bliss!
I started skating because my older
brother was into it.
[Tony Hawk, professional skateboarder]
And I enjoyed it but
I didn't take it that seriously until the
first time into a skatepark
and I saw these guys literally flying
out of empty swimming pools.
I got so excited that that was even possible as
a person
to be flying in the air
with a skateboard in your hand. Once I saw
what was possible
and what you could do with this
thing that I would have come to enjoy
I had to keep going, I mean, I just want to fly.
I think is really important to do things
that make you happy and I know that
sounds very obvious and
you know, some reviewed viewers might
say, Well, now let's hold hands and sing
Kumbaya
but when you look at every great
inventor, every great business person,
every great scientist, you look at these
people who have got
to the so called mountain top and almost
every single one of them to a person
didn't do it for the money. They did it
because they were chasing their bliss.
If you're following a dream, then you're doing
what you love,
it's not always going to be a financial
success but it will be a personal
success because
you're still doing this thing that you love doing
and that's more important.
I would describe
[Laird Hamilton, professional athlete]
my discovery of surfing: exposure.
I was just watching surfers, watching
what they were doing and what surfing
was all about, and the routes that they
were taking and the ways they were doing
it.
I think I new subconsciously before I
knew consciously.
I think I knew that I was gonna do something in
surfing, that surfing was gonna be
a big part of my life so I wanted to
absorb all the information I could.
Just because you don't know what a call
on your life is right now,
doesn't mean play austrich and stick your head in the sand and
say:
"Well just because I don't know then
I guess I shouldn't move towards anything."
The very fact that you're
looking for you bless
means that you're in the process of getting
to your bliss.
A part of life and a part of the whole journey is exploration.
Human ???? .......... is often very deep. You don't know you're there.
And we don't know that we're there often because we
don't look for them.
We don't take the journey.
Some people found them. And many people have not found
them.
Because they have not found their talents they think they don't have any.
I believe passionately that we all have
deep talents.
Go looking. Try things you've never done before.
With the things you wish you had done
but you never did, well, why didn't you? Go do it! Try!
If you always go the same route to work,
take some different route.
The people you never speak to go, go and speak to them.
At least, put yourself out there, but don't
anticipate what you'll find.
Put yourself in uncomfortable situations
at least every seven days. If
at least every seven days people aren't
laughing at you or scratching their
heads,
wondering why you're dreaming so big or
doing what you're doing,
or have such a fierce resolve to
achieving your goalsn,
than I don't think you're stretching enough
and ultimately we grow the most when doing the
thing that stretches the most.
My personal journey:
I was bright enough I got in the best University but a part of me
needed the journey. I was interested in
the West.
So I jumped at the next opportunity to
get a scholarship
and get on the boat and then I saw my boat to
the west.
It took 14 days.
I landed in Portland, Oregon
and to be a foreign student. I stretch
ed myself.
I arrived, I knew very little English.
I went to a class called "English for foreign students", I learned English.
And I embraced a Western culture, I stretch my
self.
So suddenly I saw a part of me which
I never knew was there.
One of Joe's most beloved quotes about bliss
is that
"When you follow your bliss,
the Universe will open doors
where there were only walls."
What a wonderful image and in fact a lot of
people's experiences are so like this.
You feel like you're beating your
head against a brick wall
And then suddenly you shift just a tad
???? and low and behold,
there's a passage that opens up.
when you truly forth and trust
your bliss,
unseen forces
have the power to rearrange things to
accommodate your
step of faith.
I took the Robert McKee course, I
thought well, that's not that hard
and I wrote a screenplay and
I sent it to a friend of mine who was
somebody's assistant
who left it on his desk and some other agent wandered by and picked it up and
read it
and said, "Oh, this is good" and so than my
friend went "Oh, shit" and
ran to his boss and said you should read
this because that guy over there
who's a junior agent, liked it and his
boss was a senior agent and then
I got a phone call. It was fantastic.
It was the greatest thing ever.
And so it seems like I sold the first screenplay I ever wrote.
But the truth is, I kept writing untill I got
lucky.
If I stopped writing I would never got lucky.
got like
There's no luck coming to my
house
going, "Hey, here's a book deal."
"Hey, we want to buy it, that screenplay
that you haven't written."
Just keep doing it and then eventually,
you're likely to get lucky.
Why do most people not follow their bliss? One word: fear.
Right? We're literally
overwhelmed by fear and primarily we're
overwhelmed by the of what other
people would think of us.
Campbell says that "What will
they think of me,
must be put aside for bliss"
One the biggest inhibitors of following our bliss is
"What will they think of me?"
"Am I going to look like an idiot if I
follow my bliss and I fail?"
"Am I going to look like a fool?"
All
these different questions coming to our mind.
Your friends and family,
can be very well-meaning. But really,
will collude with you to create a story
that is hard for to get out of. For
example,
"Don't do music, you won't be a musician."
"There's no point trying to be a dancer,
because you'll never make a living there."
I think that's the first step to the
journey.
They're the demons, we often have to face them.
We are each our own greatest inhibitors.
People could say "oh yeah, this guy is holding me back" or "this situation", but really,
you hold yourself back.
You're deciding, hey, I don't wanna look bad in front of those guys,
or I don't want those guys to say some bad things about me so
I'm not gonna do that.
Who made that decision? You! "I'm not going
to do that."
It means you decided.
There's a poem of Rumi, the great mythical
poet from the Middle East, in the 12th
century,
who said "I wanna sing like birds sing Not worrying who listens,
or what they think"
But if you can do that, then you can achieve the impossible.
For me, one of the most formative
times,
the first, probably most formative time was when I
dropped out of law school.
All of my friends at the time told me at least
stay here for the first year.
I could make you the first master I was literally
noxious
at the idea of completing this,
I burned my
resume.
I had no desire to live within the
corporate world in any sense.
and in the same 24-hour period of time
ended my relationship of
five years and I dropped out of law school.
It was an incredibly gut-wrenching, soul wrenching
time.
Moved back in with Mom.
There were several months when I just layed in bed and slept and red.
It wasn't a pretty process.
But the
only thing I knew I wanted to do
was to coach a little league baseball
team.
A little bit of instinct that I had, a
little bit of bliss I had in my life at
that time
was to work with these kids.
And I had no
idea what would come out of it and then
3-6 months later I had an idea that wow
there's an amazing opportunity to serve
families and sports.
The internet was just getting going
, it was just 1998 and I had a vision of what I
could do to serve these families
and created a company that there's no
way I could have imagined when I dropped
out of law school.
No possible way. But as it turns out I
started this business we won the
business plan competition UCLA
be raised five million dollars I hired the CEO of ???? to be our CEO
and we hired the law firm that I would have
wanted to work for
before I graduated from law school so
this is beautiful, this sense of this is
it, this is what happens when we follow our bliss,
magical things happen
that we couldn't have imagined when we were
going through the tough
point of making the decision to take the leap to go for it and to make the
difference in our life. ???
There are two roads in life:
the Red Road and the Black Road.
The Red Road is the tough road because it's narrow,
it's winding, it's full of storms, it's full of obstacles.
The Black Road is easy.
It's straight and it's wide. Doesn't offer
any challenges.
The storyteller never says, you have to
travel this road or you have to travel
this road.
They end up telling you the story of the red and black road by saying this:
The choice is yours. Always the choice
is yours.
"Find a place where there is joy
and the joy will burn out the pain" - Joseph Campbell
I was living a spontaneous life with my
father
the bond, the passions that my father share
with me.
We got on a plane, seven in the morning on Santa Monica Airport,
flying towards Big Bear where I had won a
ski race the day before,
we were returning to Big Bear to collect my
trophy.
On the way
we hit a storm, we crashed head along,
right into this rugged out a $200 fee ???
its the level we crash  ???
I woke up,
our bodies were sprawled ??? in this
45-degree
icy chute. It was a blizzard was harder
find everybody took me about half hour
for from is peace everybody where they
were
My dad's girlfriend Sandra was still
alive
my dad was hunched over and I was
unclear
whether he was dead or just so
knocked out
three you know through like comatose or
something ???
I just told myself that he was
knocked out
At a certain point I had to admit that he
is not gonna ??? help me any more
that I was on my own
Sandra and I took shelter under a wing.
Many things happened. Eventually we started
down this
initial icy shoet. She slipt and was killed. ???
An hour later I came
across her body.
I covered her with twigs and leaves and
stuff.
Even though I knew she was, dead pretty much.
But her
eyes were open so it was a bit
confusing for me at that age I was 11
and then I continued down in
the varied terrain in all kinds of
things happening got stuck in snow I
had a get through Little Creek cultures
and and
broken rocking I E San I just wanted to
go away
more than anything in the world I want
the pain to go away now had I not
had I not him gone in there and seen
that
that thing that that thing I fear the
most
I would not have learned
to serve find the jam in the treasure
pain those answers that were there for
me and had I not
face up and i not gone and stared in the
eyes and think I feared most
that why one run promos I would not be
here now
this book which is really besides having
a kid
P not satisfying experience in my life
home
this
Campbell talks about the fact we go on
the hero's journey
there's a drag in we must slay world
now a dragon is the most challenging
fears creature they can ever be created
him mr. GV my
Joe Campbell describes the dragon as
being a beast
covered with scales and on every scale
it says either that shelter but thou
shalt not on
the
so this beach is a constructional all
love the
rules regulations social obligations
cultural creations that have
made you feel that you either have to
or can't do certain things I'm
no
slaying the dragon to me is the most
interesting
the final moment the time when you are
faced with the scariest thing you've
been faced with him
you get to take everything we've learned and
and not the guy I am that
no
if you were to ask you what's the one
thing that
keeps people from the mountain tops
what's the one thing
the keeps people small rather than
allowing them to present their genius to
the world
it's it's their fears are is Joseph
Campbell says its third reagan's
the mysterious anything that gets in you
the new it's a beast it's a monster the
name here
yes you know let me face every day you
know only fear that we can be
rejected that we're going to be you know
no one's gonna answer return our phone
call that no one's gonna like
well we made a while we did what we said
on
fear that isn't based om has a tendency
to
creep it moves through your
experiences it starts to talks if I
your perception cuba com scared
love is what web along with and fear is
what we learn
I think there's a great truth in that
I want to hold a player you know I had
this idea I knew it was physically
possible
million usually do it Hot Wheels do this
Labor Day
com and so I A presented the idea to my
sponsor the time
they said adding it to do this lizard
that sounds awesome
the around I designed around you know in
all this is
on paper and it was my idea and I'll
never forget driving up
and seeing it and this wave fears crash
early Ly coming
what tonight are you serious like I made
a loop
I'm really in it like and I'm the only
one that's even volunteering to do it
and at that point I felt like I was so
much at stake
to not do it you look at the time no was
building
extravagant Rams no one really had money
to do that kind of thing
and there was no psych and I just had
asserted
internalize and say okay you keep
telling yourself this is possible
this is the time we got to make this happen and little by little I figured
out my text heavy heavy hits that day
the
actually now we own one for Hutchins
tour the that we could do into every
single night but
but that first time
you know that was cells is frightening
but I had to I had to really step back
in OK
you can use
the mail fears are very interesting fan
first but we need to realize that fear
is an inherent part in the human
experience
but it's not about getting rid of fear
where's it going hours now there's
nowhere for it to go
the issue is to have courage to move
forward in spite
a few you feel the new the courage
is not a lack of fair the courage
is is dealing with a faint and nobody
would have a it's not as courageous you
didn't and from their own fair
and that's not going to tell that just
doing
summit if I'm relatively and challenging
Curtis when you know what to do
can you do it and lack of courage is
when you know what to do and don't do it
courage is is the ability did to get up
after your phone gigante exploring the
unknown
and and trying stuff the maybe people
have thought was impossible
is just like a muscle if you want to get
stronger you wanna run a triathlon to
run a marathon or do whatever you want
to do
physically you know you need to train
you need to get stronger
current is exactly the same thank you
think a bit like courage GM
you've got a consistently go up your
fears go one step past
one step past you'll find your comfort
zone expanse each time you do that
things used to freak you out won't freak
you out as much
and now you have the tools you have the
strength literally to lift more in your
life
as you face your fears one more
authentically
there is some
power monsters get by being dark in the
closet I'll
and there is some diminishment
arm by facing them facing them head-on
and are
are suggests Campbell talk to the
slaying dragons
and with most others do their lives
whether it's a difficult assignment at
work
when there is a difficult conversation
we know we should have with a loved one
whether something we're resisting we
leave can run in the opposite direction
rather than running away we should go
closer to you because once we can see
here
fierce the death here you know the
concern
do the things that scare you you know
courageous what comes after
it is
okay to be scared
shouldn't stop you
a healthy warning election stuff
the No
of mmm
over dragon that hordes all the stories
talk in those terms for several reasons
am on the one hand we could call a
projection tennis psychological sense
so we project out and we create
and antagonised that we have to slay
more but what's actually happening is
we're I'll
dealing with the energies inside
ourselves what he's outside is in fact a
reflection what's inside that it back
you've sorted shows n
your 10 the new
of course in Star Wars which wasn't
pretty much entirely based on
camels paradigm blue sky Walker
has to go into K where he does battle
with Darth Vader
the new we're finally he cuts of Darth
Vader's head
in the head rolls to his feet
and Darth Vader's helmet opens up
North Jersey City but his own face he
thinks that is evil outside of him
when the struggle between good and evil is understood to be going on inside of
us
it can be very beneficial this is part
is a personal transformation
overcoming I negative aspects
emphasizing are good ones
but what often happens of course we want
to feel that we are good
so we don't find the negative within
ourselves we're gonna find it
somewhere out there the great optional
for most
as ready as ourself you know if we can
overcome that basic fare
about what we might achieve and we take
that risk
I think all kinds of things open up in
and Campbell stands now we
we can all be heroes I'm
the hero encounters these obstacles
and Wales and the
and that's how we react when we find ourselves in a situation where we have
that and cognitive dissonance
how do I get out amid the nobel
first thing is you have to surrender you
have to stop fighting in the mood
are
the new
so slaying the dragon
is really coming to terms with that
inner part of Use
yourself that you think is bigger than
your and in doing that then you grow
bigger sent to your cell go
however I think dad its
loving your to hack that's the much more
efficient thing to do
it also feels a lot better
theme
when you do that then frequently
whatever the dragon was hiding
reporting this step away and give it to
me they give it to you because there's
no
began when you're fighting you find
yourself we stop fighting yourself
then you're no longer engaged in the
fight
in Europen to what might come true
though is a gift in battling demons and
overcoming
because that's what our soul's journey
is about its about facing fear growing
beyond
and as we overcome our fears regain
power
you look at our lives the best
most rewarding moment com after stroke
as such what we do with our allies
is what makes us Europe or not arm
and
there's grace in knowing and there's a
TF yeah
believing hey every minus
mishap a plus way the first row cover
article where Nash
in other words on one level to make it
here you had to deploy CA have that
health challenge a got fired in a kiln
arguing that
has not troublesome but one awareness
can you add to it
see get a far bigger picture helps you
master
at a certain point in the hero's journey
it's going to become a Down
you loving and accepting yourself
pension why
that's a powerful moment because that
line she worked directly with the
universe now there's no more war
going on inside yourself and as that gap
heels between your unlovable South
in your ability to montana lovable self
became an awesome power
life
the way we think the kindness as linear
I'm born I'm gonna go through these
things I'm gonna die
here's journey tells us know you're
gonna go here you can have this
adventure in uni come back and guess
what you gonna be right back where you
were now you can go over here have this
adventure you come back
you're gonna go here you can have this
invention unit come back and guess what
you gonna be right back where you were
now you can go over here have this
adventure you come back
and guess what you right here what did
you bring back I'm
what the hero brings back the No
is a story Gomes for example go
commission a big
he went out any look for the plan to be
more challenging
he went through all kinds it runs with
the feminine with her
the monster and so on but he finally
swam to the bottom of the sea and got
the plant immortality
he came up on the short put it down
while he was bathing
the snake serpent came and got that
plaintiff immortality
but he went home to o'rourke anyway and
he had this story to tell
for gil comish there was no concrete
objective thing widget
to give to the community no gold
no treasure and so on the story the
train getting the treasures
treasure
and so the giving this story
is the invitation for other people to
make the same journey
that's why it's a circle and never hit
love that idea that there's a circle
and the circle needs to be closed and
the way to close the circle
is to come back return with
something different than you started
with and to share that
not to me is like a perfect hero's
journey deaths
the ultimate in to the US Attorney's not
slaying dragons
not being the bad guy it's giving back
the essence in that journey
looks like about how can I make a
difference and who can I make a
difference
2&4 and then it gets really easy a kind
get a shirt for the future taking he's
getting more
here's more only my friends star
artistic said he's trying to make moving
he doesn't have the money
what can we do it visually all love said
we're doing things
that we are going to do anyway but down
so we can make money for him and make
him finish the movie
and then all since I will let's do that
again that was great
when I found this success in skating and
I never dreamed possible
the first thing I want to do is try to
help kids get a facility in and that was
the first thing I did I start a
foundation for public skate parks
it
today we've helped build about 500 skate
parks
it's my passion it's what I would love
to do is provide facilities for these
kids to
deserve a chance I love talking to young
writers about writing
there's a scholarship by primed which is
up screenwriting scholarship at Wesley
where I went to college
the away to up
everybody who wants to be what we are
with a crow
this if you speak to somebody at the
level of the mine
can you speak to them if you speak to me
a hot
you will speak to the hot work if you
speak
through your life in your life has the
story
then you changed that's what mythical
beings
and it's why stories are great because
my story
right now
which is my also my truth
may have an effect on you
and therefore
I'm picking the in trouble
I'm making an external and through that
I'm sharing experience
no matter how long you get to live life
is ultimately for sure
before all the silver in the dust and
the street sweeper gets buried next to
see
you know all that really matters at the
end of the day is how big
showed up and how courageous were
I think when we are on our debt that's
what feels are hurt integration crack is
not all
risks we talk not all the opportunities
he sees
and all the times we we don't live in
look silly
bushels are the bread at the
industrialized world
responded in taking all the
opportunities didn't
sees and it's really all you gotta do to
get to the next step
I believe we all have in this to think
to ourselves okay
a choice between our bob
is a story you're telling
nixon feel the morning
it if you like you can overcome and that
nixon deal
transcend
about a week ago
room
I'm
%uh