Burglar!
Catch the burglar!
Don't you run away!
Happy Birthday!
Happy Birthday...
Sammo Hung!
- You're not Sammo Hung!
- He's not Sammo Hung!
Burglar...
Get him...
Hurry up.
Don't run...
What a coincidence!
We do not wish to be
the parasites of society.
We do not wish to
live off other people's harvests.
We only want to give comfort
to the despaired.
Bravo!
Let me ask: Is it shameful
to be in hard labor?
Let me ask: Is it a crime to support
your husband and children?
No!
I hereby implore citizens of Hong Kong,
that there's no right or wrong
in the entertainment business.
Right!
It's everybody's responsibility
to legalize prostitution!
Curly, you were great!
We have to act like real men,
be free and go bravely forward!
- Alright!
Alright...
Brother Jack.
Want to buy me out?
My principle is never to be a two-timer!
Say no more.
We'll start demonstrating today.
Tomorrow we'll voice our complaints
at the Council's office.
Then we'll protest
at the Governor's House.
This is the situation.
You can think about the consequences.
Talking to you is a waste of time!
Even $3,000 can't buy him.
Junkie Ming!
Protest! Protest!...
Protest!...
Three in a row, three in a row!
More than three and we'll be booked
for an illegal gathering!
Line up now.
Three by three...
Line up, line up!
Right. Line up just like that.
We protest wrongful termination!
Wrongful termination!
We must persist to the end!
What?
What are you saying?
What are you doing?
What do you want?
Sure, sure, I know what to do.
Jack said we don't need
to respect the management.
Jack said we can tear down the factory.
Jack said...
Sure, sure, I understand.
Jack ordered me
to make a move right away.
I'll make a move on you first!
Sir, this has nothing to do with me.
It has nothing to do with me either.
Get in!
Pal, can you please
clean that yellow car for me?
Thank you. I'm leaving very soon.
Where's my car key?
Shit!
It's not your lucky day.
You've got some nerve!
Hold it!
No need to shoot me for stealing a tire.
We citizens are very cooperative
with the police, sir.
Do it yourself.
Done.
This will be evidence in court. Move!
Buddy, do you have anything
more expensive?
Yes. One moment please.
- Please look around.
- Okay.
Sir, I guarantee
you will be satisfied with this watch.
This one? It's not bad!
Chan! Long time no see!
Can't believe I'd see you here.
Why don't you ever call your old friends?
Now that you're rich,
you never look me up...
I told you...
I have nothing to do with that!
Never thought you would shoot me!
You...
What's going on?
Don't look. Just go!
I have nothing to do with it!
Please show me that diamond watch.
Sure.
I'm sure you'll be
satisfied with this one.
This one's not bad either.
- This one suits you.
- That's right.
Chan! Long time no see!
Never thought I'd bump into you here!
How's life?
I told you not to be trigger-happy!
I told you it has nothing to do with me!
Don't move! This is a hold up!
Freeze!
Don't move.
I'll shoot anyone that moves!
Don't look! On your knees!
Let's go!
Sir, how are you? Are you alright?
I'm fine. I go home,
put some antiseptic on and I'll be okay.
How can that be?
You're bleeding all over!
No problem. I'm used to it.
Sir, those robbers ran that way.
Follow me!
You can't move!
What's the matter?
He got shot!
Call an ambulance, quick!
No, don't call the ambulance!
Don't be scared, don't be scared.
- Be careful
- No, really!
I'm alright!
You're covered with blood.
What're you here for?
For a stick up, okay?
Of course it's not okay.
Otherwise you wouldn't get arrested. Come on!
Why are you still standing there?
Sir, this is such a narrow street.
We should go one by one.
Get on with it!
I'm in a good mood today.
Otherwise you would've bled to death!
Sir...
Sir what? Confess now!
Where did the counterfeit U.S. bills
come from?
I withdrew them from the bank, sir.
What? Those counterfeit bills
were withdrawn from the bank?
Sir, those aren't counterfeit money.
Can it be genuine then?
Yes...
I'm no longer in a good mood.
It's counterfeit!
I picked the money up from the street.
Smart. You just saved your own life.
You wouldn't have gotten a beating if
you told me sooner. Try to lie to me?
You asked for it.
7086.
Sir, he has confessed.
They're all genuine.
I went to the bank and checked.
He did take out $200,000 U.S.
You've beaten him senseless! You...
Sir, I know what to do.
Sir, he has agreed to accept today
as though nothing has happened.
Don't go yet!
7086, you are now off
the counterfeit money case.
I've already sent an undercover.
Sir, are there any other cases
for me to take care of?
Sure.
Go to the parks and catch litterbugs!
Why am I so down and out?
All because I'm so impulsive.
I'm the eldest, so I should be No.1!
I'm No.2.
I'm No.3.
I'm No.4.
Then I guess I'm No.5.
From now on,
we'll share both joy and pain together!
Who's willing to clean the toilet?
Him!
Even the air breathes differently
from the other side of the wall.
What's the matter? Asthma attack?
Just getting used to the air outside.
I don't think you'll get used to it.
Go back in.
Honest to God, please don't follow us.
Go, go!
Wait for Teapot!
No need to wait!
I said wait...
You're right. We better get going.
Is that how you guys treat me now,
buddies?
Let's wait for him.
Look at you. Put these clothes on.
Boss!
Daddy!
I've told you
not to speak English with me.
Father.
Good.
Are you still fooling around
with that chauffeur?
Not fooling around. We plan to
get married right after you're out.
Future Father-in-law.
No need to be envious.
We'll get a cooler reception
the next time we get out!
Maybe we have to use our legs
to hail a bus now!
Let me!
A flat tire.
Pal, it's your lucky day.
Even here you can get 5 passengers.
Bye!
When you're down in luck,
there's simply no escape!
Oh well,
better get some Palmolive leaves
to wash away all the bad luck!
Ah Sing, want to play poker today?
You can count me out.
Today isn't my lucky day.
You're kidding!
Don't believe me? Come take a look
and you'll know what I mean.
Each one of them has the word "convict"
sculpted on their foreheads!
What are you honking at?
Late for your own execution?
So, uh, Curly. Why are you in for?
Oh, nothing. I was on this minibus
and the driver was talking shit.
So I grabbed him off the wheel,
stabbed him a couple of times
and I got 3 years.
You think that's bad!
Some guy just kept staring at me, so I
cracked his eyeball with just one punch?
I got 2 years for that.
Then using sulfuric acid is better.
That time when I splashed it
on the driver's head,
I only got 18 months!
Then your luck is better than mine.
I used sulfuric acid too!
But I got 10 years!
10 years?? Where did you splash him?
I didn't. I forced it down his throat.
Doesn't matter how much time you get.
Whoever thinks he's tough?
He's gonna get it!
I wonder how much time one will get
for setting a minibus on fire?
Hey driver, got a light?
No! No!
Enough already.
I'm getting all fired up.
Curly, is there a minibus
that takes you straight to your place?
There used to be one.
I don't know about now.
Then how do we get there?
Make a left here.
Then a right.
Go straight and through the puddle.
Stop right here!
How much, man?
All men are brothers! No need, no need!
Thanks!
Hard to believe you have property!
It's not mine. It belongs to my uncle.
His whole family
is busy washing dishes in Canada.
I'm just house sitting for him.
But Uncle is already 79,
and has no children.
All of this will belong to me one day.
Help yourself, guys.
There's beer in the fridge.
Sis! Sis!
Want to guess
how Curly's sister looks like?
Just look at him and you'll know.
Thanks.
Not necessarily so.
Curly, come over here.
What's up?
We're going to ask you a question,
and you must give an honest answer.
Say it!
Do you and your sister
share the same parents?
Yes.
What about it?
Nothing.
Then it's hopeless!
What now?
What's the matter?
Nothing. Going to the toilet.
What happened?
Nothing. Just being scared by my sister.
All these years
and she still scares him!
We better have some mental preparation.
Cut the crap.
Just be polite when you greet people.
- Are all the guests here?
- All here.
Dinner's ready. Have a seat.
Actually, God is very fair.
A beautiful lady can never cook.
And a lady that cooks is never...
Say Hello to the uncles.
Hello uncles.
She's "helloing" you guys!
I'm Lin,
but you can call me Vaseline.
Sit down.
You all better not
let your imagination go wild.
Honestly,
let me ask you one more question.
What was your father's occupation?
Seaman.
No wonder.
Burglar!
- What is it?
- There's a burglar!
He's not a burglar. He is Teapot.
It's alright. Go away!
I'm Teapot.
Sorry.
No need to say sorry. It's perfectly
normal to think he's a thief.
Say, does your foot hurt?
Are you alright?
I'm alright, just feeling a bit cheated.
It's okay.
Just a misunderstanding. Come eat!
Come get some rice.
What's this? This is my house. No need
to stand in line for food anymore.
Thanks.
Make yourselves at home.
She can get it herself.
Thanks.
Is the stuff ready yet?
All set.
Boss, can you tell which one is real?
The middle one.
Wrong, Boss!
It's the one above.
Wrong again, Boss.
All three are counterfeits.
Come over here.
Don't fool me like that again.
But you've done good on this job.
I'm serious. Stop following me!
Hey man, it's all of you
who told me to wear this rag!
What rag?
Is it so embarrassing for you
to wear my dad's clothes?
I didn't say that.
You were the ones who said it's ugly.
It is a little ugly,
but it really suits you.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
It's the inner beauty that counts.
Jack was right. Your only flaw
is your awkward appearance,
otherwise you're fine.
Stop arguing. Let's go.
Don't touch!
That's no fun!
Not even a pat on the shoulder!
Of course. Curly Jack may think
you two are perverts.
Look what a bad mouth you have!
What do you mean "may"?
They are perverts!
Her brother is here. It's hopeless.
Think of a plan to get rid of him.
What plan?
Can't you think of one?
Tonight... we two...
brothers... are not selling...
...selling medicine.
How come I don't see Butcher Wing
and his sister?
Medicine!
We're... here to...
heal the sick.
And... and...
nourish the healthy...
and... and...
- Me?
- Of course it's you.
The smart ones talk
and the dumb ones act.
Strengthen...
- Strengthen your body.
- Most performers sell fake medicine!
The whole... whole...
body will be strong all over.
The pills... though they
are tiny,
but... they're... easy...
...to swallow. Three times a day,
morning, noon and night.
That's why I've... never...
gotten sick in the last twenty years.
Full... of... vitality...
Alright, folks.
Enough with the small talk!
I beg your pardon!
I thought it's something special.
See them all the time on those oldies rerun!
Look at you. Use some force!
Looks more like some old man pissing.
You've got guts!
How dare you hit Master Chiu?
- Don't go away!
- I was just kidding!
No! I was just kidding!
Brother...
Relax, sis. Your brother
is used to this kind of action.
He's run away from tougher battles!
Small matters like this are no big deal.
He'll be alright, sis.
We'll take a stroll over there.
Windpipe!
Are you going to compete with me?
Can't you tell?
Let me set the rules straight.
No need.
We'll use our own cunning ways.
Now what?
You like to pull men's pants off too?
You...
Look who's taken the gravy!
Come and get it!
Brand name Walkie-Talkie only $65!
Last chance!
Sis, can you hear what I say? Over.
Yes.
At this distance, anyone can hear you.
Got to move further. Give it to me!
This game is not for you and me.
Machinery is Windpipe's specialty.
This time you're right.
I can tell right away.
Even though it says "Made in Japan",
it's actually made in Hong Kong.
But its reception capabilities
are very strong.
I think its transmission radius
should be 51.4 meters!
How can you be so sure?
He's bullshitting.
Bullshitting? You can ask the boss.
My friend, you do have some knowledge.
See? Listen, sis.
I'll now talk to you
at the 51.4 meter spot.
Why am I hanging out
with a dork like him?
Windpipe, over, over.
Hi, sis. Over.
Are you at the 51.4 meter spot yet?
Not yet. I'm on my way.
Sis, can you hear me clearly? Over.
Vaguely, over.
What about now?
Sis asks you to sing a song for her.
What? Sing a song?
Yes!
"Baby loves me from the heart,
I love baby from the start.
And we wish upon a star,
till forever do we part.
Now the sea is in between...
Who knows when we'll meet again?"
Dad, someone has taken over our turf!
"Brief reunion can be sweet..."
It's a tough living, my child.
They'll sing theirs, and we'll sing ours.
"...can be sad."
"Past joys are hard to forget..."
Sis, sis. Can you hear me? Over.
Sis? Sis your ass! I'm closing up!
Get me back the walkie-talkie now!
Or I'll call the cops!
Teapot, go get some peanuts
so you two can eat.
I want some too!
Get going. Do you need some change?
No, because I don't have
any money at all.
God knows I tried hard
to preserve your dignity. Here!
My dignity is worth more than 10 bucks.
Then how much?
150 bucks.
That's too much!
Too much?
Then try and get rid of me too.
Alright. Let's get this over with.
Relax.
I will pay this $150 back to you.
After three years in the cell,
even a hooker is Princess to me now.
See ya!
Where's Ranks?
He must have sent him off!
I think he must've left on his own.
That's right.
He has to take care of something.
Very nice!
That's a ladies' booth.
Why are you standing there?
Nothing.
Even those with potential are gone now.
You should know what to do.
I know. I'm leaving,
but I want to say goodbye to Sis first.
No need. Just disappear.
No way! Sis was already asking me...
why they've left so suddenly.
I think it'll be beneficial to you
if I let her know.
Sounds like you want to help me out.
That depends on whether it's worth it.
How are you going to help me?
Alright. Here're 30 dollars for a movie
and a late night snack.
You can keep the change.
Remember, don't take too long!
Okay.
Then how long is "don't take too long"?
I don't know
how you can live for so long.
Fine. I'll give you a signal,
then you can go. Remember now!
Sis. Vaseline told us to leave first.
Why?
Don't know. He said he has to
take care of something urgent.
Why don't you go and ask him?
There's no need. Let's go.
TEAPOT!
So that's what you guys
have been fighting for.
That's right.
Turns out I'm the one
who has a chance to be with you.
Actually, you can just ask me out.
I don't dare. I know who I am.
Look at me.
Aside from being healthy, smart,
kind-hearted, hard-working,
sincere, and honest,
I have nothing else in my favor.
Besides, girls nowadays
only care about appearances.
That is true.
Even you agree. That's why
I don't dare to approach any girls.
So what if I get to know...
an approachable girl like you?
I am shy and no good with words.
Just one look from a girl,
and my heart would jump,
my knees would jerk,
and my hands get numb.
I'll just be like right now,
not knowing what to say.
You mean you've never
asked a girl out before?
Asking a girl out, no.
But paid a girl for a night out, yes.
I'm just kidding!
Where do we go now?
We can go to...
Go to hell! All those noises.
You even scared my fish away!
Have people been calling you Teapot
since you were a kid?
No. When I was little,
everyone called me Little Teapot.
Actually, you hardly look like a teapot.
Hardly? I am from head to toe.
There's even a song about it.
Song? Can you sing it for me please?
Right here?
So what? There's nobody around.
Promise me not to laugh if I sing.
I promise. Now sing!
"I am a teapot fat and short,
I am a teapot fat and short.
This is the handle, this is the spout.
Water is boiling, tea is pouring!"
Teapot, you are a charmer!
Teapot.
Where did you take my sister to just now?
Brother!
We went for tea.
That means you haven't eaten yet.
I've treated each of them
with a hard-boiled egg.
I even saved two for you.
- You bastard.
- No!
I got a beating because of you!
Where do you want to go now?
Anywhere.
Want to go see a movie?
Alright,
but I don't watch horror movies.
What do you want to see then?
Comedies.
Your turn, kid.
"Maxim's smart, Maxim's best,
Maxim's cakes beat the rest."
Answer one more question.
What's Maxim best known for?
Any tips?
I'll give you three choices.
Pancake, pudding, or pastry.
Pancake.
Wrong. One more chance.
Pudding.
Wrong again. One last chance.
Pancake plus pudding.
This is for you.
I would like 3 ham and egg sandwiches
and 2 hamburgers,
3 Cokes, and a coffee to go.
Also 2 pork chop over rice
and 2 orange juices for here.
Eat in, thanks.
What would you like?
You can get a table first.
Okay.
Chubby, lend me your girlfriend
for a while.
There's going to be a robbery here.
Don't worry.
You two will be safe as long as I'm here.
Chubby, sit down
and eat your pork chop over rice.
Just duck when I tell you to.
For you.
I want money, not prizes!
Kid, you...
I was a kid 30 years ago.
Now I'm a robber.
Give me your money now.
My gun has very little patience.
And don't you dare scream.
Keep cool, keep your mouth shut,
and put the money in this bag.
You'll soon forget about your fears.
Get used to it.
Better not scream
till you think you're safe.
Freeze! Get down!
Let them go or I'll kill him!
Chubby, you've got some moves.
Just so so.
Teapot, are you alright?
I'm fine.
I don't understand,
why do you let them bully you?
Actually, they should be glad
you're not bullying them.
When I was a kid,
I like fighting and bullying others.
And I ended up having no friends.
So now I treasure friendship much more.
As long as they are my friends,
I don't mind them bullying me...
once in a while.
Robbery!
Now she yells!
Don't move! Or this bullet
will go through your head, then theirs.
You fake!
How dare you rob with a phony gun!
You need some help?
Sure.
Not that! Call the cops for me.
Don't move!
Shoot!
1, 2, 3!
Next time we'll throw
when we count to 2.
What're you guys laughing at?
Don't tell, no matter what.
What're you two looking at? Sit down
and let's finish the game, idiots!
Invisible, sure. Even if the body is,
you still can see the clothes!
This time it'll work for sure!
- Shoot!
- You can't even shoot at the goal!
Shoot!
What a dumbass.
Just standing there and doing nothing.
Just shoot from midfield!
You think everyone is like that Zico?
"Just shoot from midfield"!
Don't just stand there!
Go after the ball!
You guys can forget about winning.
That No.9 just keeps punting around
and doesn't pass the ball.
Go! Shoot!
What a great chance and he still misses!
Can't just stand there
and wait for the ball, am I right?
That's why British soccer is much better.
Every shot is aimed for the goal.
What commercial is this?
Longine Watch.
You mean you haven't seen it?
This bald guy sure
looks like Sean Connery.
How can they win
if they don't even have teamwork?
This No.7 is always blocking the way.
No.8 is much better.
He has strength in every kick.
They're doomed if they kick like this.
What was that for?
Who has time to mess with you?
I can kick better than him!
Not too hard, man!
Why did you hit me?
You're nuts! Why don't you ask them
whether I hit you or not?
Go outside if you two want to fight.
We have a game to watch.
Hit me again and you're going to get it.
Forget it. I'll sit over there.
There's no escaping this one!
Blaming me again!
Luckily I am miles away.
You sons of bitches! You tricked me!
Move! Idiots!
Better let her take it off herself!
I'll be letting Curly down if I do this.
Nice!
How come it's missing something?
I think of you when I can't see you.
I'll love you more if I do!
If he goes out like that,
I'll die laughing!
It's possible!
He can't be. He's upstairs...
Sis!
He's coming down.
Pass to the right! Kick! Pass!
Shoot!
Get the door.
Let me.
Registered mail.
Pal, you sign for it.
You can see me?
I don't want to,
but my eyes aren't cooperating.
I can see even the smallest thing.
Are you sure, buddy? I'm invisible!
Invisible? I wish I was too!
Hurry up, pal.
I need to go home and get an eye-wash.
Sore eyes are a pain in the ass!
What are you all laughing at?
Windpipe thinks he's invisible
and we can't see him.
So?
He was there when I took a bath.
I just pretended that
I couldn't see him.
So, do I have a nice figure?
Remember.
Your contact person is a foreigner.
Both of you wear a red rose.
All you need to do is give him the case,
and bring the money back safely.
Then your duty is done.
Is that clear?
Clear.
Repeat it for me.
The red foreigner... no, no.
Rose... rose spray!
Father, what do you want him to do?
I've told you that women shouldn't...
barge in when men are talking business!
Go back to your room!
No!
I want to know what you want Chai to do.
Is it tough?
Relax. Nothing is as tough as
relying on a woman for a living.
Go now.
Bill, Pat. You two look after him.
Chai, let them do the dangerous stuff.
You be careful.
This is your first mission.
Don't disappoint me.
Sure, sure.
Wait. Your pants.
When's my luck going to change?
Little kid, don't litter.
If you were an adult,
I would have arrested you.
What's the matter?
He dumped my ice cream!
You're not done with it?
Don't cry.
There.
Still brainless at your age!
I'm sorry.
Don't cry,
mom will buy you another one.
Well?
I don't know. I may not be free.
Let's wait till the time comes.
Just forget it.
I'm not a man
if I don't react in this situation.
Were you the one who whistled just now?
Yes.
You're such a creep!
What did you say?
Looks okay, but ugly manners.
Don't make me mad!
Mad? Can you?
Forget it. Let's go.
Freeze! I'm CID!
Should've said so earlier, partner!
Did I hurt you?
Do I look like I get hurt easily?
You should be glad I didn't hurt you!
Are you alright?
Look how frightened your girlfriend is.
She's always afraid,
I might hurt somebody.
Let's go!
Bye.
Are you done fighting?
Not fighting, just practicing.
Don't hit on girls next time!
Hitting on girls?
Do you think my taste is that bad?
That whistle was meant for you!
If you don't believe me...