When I was a child...
I remember seeing
a big rainbow over the river
Go away!
At that time my mother told me
"A rainbow is the door to heaven
When people die
they go to heaven through that door"
When I was a child my father passed away
And my mother went abroad
I wanted my mom to remarry
but she didn't want to
My name is Ji-hae
and my blood type is O
And since I was seven
I learned taekwondo
Are you okay?
This box contains
my parents' letters and diaries
Every time my mother
read the letters, she wept
The refined letters and
the scent of the past...
My mom's first love is in here
Hello?
Ji-hae?
It's me, Soo-gyung
Why are you calling so early?
Wanna go to the art museum
and a play with me and Sang-min?
Hey, are you making me tag along?
No, dummy! Sang-min asked you to come
Really?
- I'm serious
- I got to know
Sang-min through Soo-gyung
She one day asked me to write e-mails to Sang-min
For two months, I wrote
letters to him for Soo-gyung
Today, I saw you reading a book by the bench
It looked like a picture in a postcard
That's childish
Rewrite it?
No, I like it
I like it being childish
If you still want to marry
I'll give you a curse for a dowry
Sang-min, I sent you a letter
without missing a day
Afterwards, Soo-gyung signed up for theater
So that she could get close to him
Good-bye
If you still want to marry
marry an idiot instead
The night stained with
pain kept me awake...
The gloomy moonlight has
unexpectedly made your shadow suspend
on my window
No, that's not it!
The gloomy moonlight has
unexpectedly made your shadow suspend
on my window
Jordan is touched when Emily comes back to see him
You have to feel both
happy and heartbroken
Do it with more feeling!
When I look at him I feel breathless
But he never once looked at me
I'll put a spell on him
Look back! Look back! Look back!
Hey!
Music
When I saw you for the first time
you already stole my heart
But now that you came to me
I feel like we'll be together forever
Good
My heart is yours forever
He doesn't make a lot of gesture
Isn't Sang-min fantastic?
I love guys who are into their work
Saw him?
"No, that's not it!"
The gloomy moonlight has
unexpectedly made your shadow suspend
on my window
Talking about me?
It's nothing, Sang-min
You know Ji-hae, right?
She was with me when I first came here
Right, it's been a while
Yes...
Hello
A lot of girls like him
Not just Soo-gyung
Even the woman working at the student's hall likes him
Sung Joo-hee
Yoon Tae-soo
Oh Joon-ha?
"When I opened the window this morning
the romantic breeze signaled autumn coming
I'll put that wind
in the letter and send it to you"
Romantic breeze?
That's so cliche
I guess I'll look at it as a classic
Oh Joon-ha!
Tae-soo came to me all of sudden
whom I've never talked to
Please write me a letter
He heard the rumor that I write for others
Tae-soo is a friend who grew no less than
36 centimeters during the winter vacation
To who?
To my fiancee
Fiancee?
She's my dad's friend's daughter
They set us up on their own
You're lucky
You don't have to ask girls out on dates
I'm sick of it
I'm not the type to date one girl
If she mails me he wants to check it
He wants to know everything
He acts just like a FBI agent
Oh no
She's pretty, huh?
But since she's a congressman's daughter
she'll be shallow
Drive! Drive!
You let them slip out between your legs
City boys are slow
Suwon isn't a city, Seoul is
Oh Suwon...
But we have a city hall
You catch them and I'll draw them
Look carefully, idiot
Let's go
What are you doing?
She's Old SUNG's granddaughter
I heard she's from Suwon
- Wait, you're from Suwon, right?
- Yeah
We can never dream of having her
Old SUNG's son is a congressman
So she's a congressman's daughter
Then is she a congressman's son, idiot?
- Oh...
She's...
- She's waving
- Let's wave back!
Hey, wave!
- Hello!
- Hi!
I found one!
Let me see!
Let's see
It stinks
I got one
It's a big one
It sure ate a lot of cow shit
It's a beetle
A beetle?
But I've never seen one
Do you want this?
You wanna bet?
It's cow shit, it's dirty
Have you seen the haunted house across the river?
What?
Yes
Can you take me there?
Do you know how to row?
Sure
Then let's meet at the ferry at twelve tomorrow, okay?
- What did you say to her?
- She said something...
City boys are surely different
Hey, teach me how to row!
You'll teach me, right?
Grandpa told me a lot about it
but forbid me to go
It's strict where ever I go
I really wanted to go,
but I had no one to take me
If I ask the people here
then they'll tell my Grandpa right away
But the boat isn't moving
Gosh!
To be honest this is my first time rowing
My name is Oh Joon-ha
Oh my, I forgot to introduce myself
I'm Sung Joo-hee
You're from Suwon?
Yes
I'm from Suwon, too
I came here to visit my Uncle
Really?
What a coincidence
Or maybe fate?
- Pardon?
- Oh, nothing
Is there...
really a ghost?
Have you seen...
a ghost before?
Of course
Every day
What?
In the mirror
Actually, I'm a ghost
Stop it
- Are you okay?
- Yes
I think I sprained my ankle
Get on my back
Hurry and get on my back
It's a shower
It'll stop soon
Dry yourself with this
When the rain stops we'll go along the river
Then we'll reach the ferry
Although it's a bit far
I'm heavy, huh?
Nope
You're not heavy at all
But I weigh a lot
And I eat a lot, too
Don't worry
I can carry you on my back and go anywhere!
You're lying
I'm not lying
Yes, you are
No, I'm not
I caught it
Open your hands
Hold the firefly for a moment
You gave me a firefly and carried me
But this is all that I can give you in return
Please give me the firefly
Thanks for today
She was sick for a few days
and left for a big hospital in Seoul
After her mother died she got really sick
But when she came back from the countryside
I heard she got healthier and looked happier
It's done
Let me see
It was painful to write the letters for Tae-soo
Because of her
I had a lot to tell her myself
It's great
Can I thank you by showing you my specialty?
Yes
Wait a sec
You have to open your mouth
When we close our mouths
people will think we faked it
Watch carefully
Know what song this is?
"Moonlight of Shilla"?
You punks!
Why haven't you finished your chores?
Are you bastards playing hookie?
I'll check later
so make it spotless!
And what's this smell?
Did someone take a shit here?
Joon-ha!
Oh Joon-ha!
Are you crazy to scream in a library?
Look, it's an invitation
Is everyone here Oh Joon-ha?
Nosey bastards
Thank you
Next is sophomore
Sung Joo-hee
She will play Beethoven's Sonata 8 on the piano
Welcome with warm applause
Joo-hee, you must be hungry
I bet you're hungry
- Thank you
- Congratulations
Is your ankle better?
Yes
And your cold?
I was very worried about you
And I enjoyed your performance
I have to practice more
Everyone's waiting
I snuck out
I still have the firefly
It's in good health, like me
Hi
Sorry, I'm late
Mmm...
Hi, Ji-hae
Sang-min, I won
We made a bet
I bet you'd come and Sang-min bet you wouldn't
You have to treat dinner
Okay, I will
What are you looking at?
I have to go
Why are you going so early?
Sang-min is treating us to dinner
Three's a crowd
You bad girl
You're too smart
Sang-min!
Ji-hae said she's leaving
But you should eat with us
And we can talk about the play, too
Ji-hae never changes her mind
Right, Ji-hae?
Right
See?
That's too bad
It would've been nice if you came
Ever seen Sang-min treat
anyone like this?
He's doing this because you're my friend
He's just being nice so you can go, It's okay
Wait!
I bought presents today
I also got you one,
so you wouldn't feel alone
I bet you won't be able to sleep tonight
This isn't like Sang-min
It's because you're a good friend
If it wasn't for me you'd never get this
Pick one
Ji-hae!
Ji-hae...
I like your present better
It's okay to switch, right?
Bye!
"When the sun shines
on the sea, I think of you
When the dim moonlight is on the spring
I think of you"
Really?
Is that what it says?
Gee!
Oh my gosh
Sang-min must really like me a lot
You have to give it
to me tomorrow, okay?
Okay
I have no reason to see him anymore
He wants to be with Soo-gyung now
When the sun shines on the sea...
When the dim moonlight is on the spring...
Are you done?
Wait a little longer
Hand in your manure
in an envelope after lunch
- Got it?
- Yes, sir
Those who didn't bring it hurry and go take a shit!
Got it?
Let's get together!
One! Two!
Joon-ha
I'll close my eyes and run so you guide me, okay?
I'm really closing them
Okay
Joon-ha
Wanna come with me to learn the folk dance after class?
folk?
I'm gonna meet Joo-hee there
It's my dad and his friend's idea
They want us to meet at a healthy recreation
A lot of girls will be there
so you pick one up
- Gonna come, right?
- I don't know
Tae-soo!
Joo-hee, this is my friend Oh Joon-ha
She's the one I told you about
I'm Oh Joon-ha
Nice to meet you
Hello
Are you two friends?
Know each other?
No, we don't
He's my best friend
This is my friend, Na-hee
Hi, I'm Na Na-hee
- I'm YOON Tae-soo
- I'm Oh Joon-ha
Everyone please have a seat
Come on!
Anywhere is fine
Today I will teach you the folk dance
- Sounds fun, right?
- Yes
Folk Dance is...
I missed you
Me, too
I didn't know you were Tae-soo's friend
I want to be a woman anchor
So I always practice my speech
Can you do this?
Peter Piper picked
a peck of pickled peppers
Did I do okay?
I can do it faster
Peter Piper picked
a peck of pickled peppers
Shall I do it faster?
Peter Piper picked
a peck of pickled peppers
Give it a try
Peter Piper a pecked
of peppers pickled...
You'll need a lot of practice
Repeat precisely after me
Peter Piper picked
a peck of pickled peppers
We should split up now
I'll take Joo-hee home
so you take care of Na-hee
Okay?
See you later
I had fun
Good night
Bye, Joo-hee
What are you doing?
Let's get going
Joon-ha
then try something easier
Try this
She sells seashells by the seashore
Easy, huh?
Give it a try
Pardon?
I said give it a try
Give what a try?
She sells seashells by the seashore
Give this a try
I can't
Please don't ask me to
You can't do this?
She sells seashells by the seashore
It's easy
- Have a good...
- Yes...
Good-bye
The card
I should've known there'd be a card for me
Ji-hae?
Oh, hello
Where are you headed?
To the library
That far?
It's not far
I won't get so wet if I stop at each building
Then I'll take you there
With my special umbrella
Think of that building as a shed and run
One, Two, Three!
How are you?
Thanks so much
But you're soaked
I was going to get wet anyway
I should be going
Thanks again
- Okay, I'll see you later
- OK!
I didn't think we'd meet again
But why does the library have to be so close?
She hasn't mailed me back yet
- Joo-hee?
- Yeah
- Why not?
- I don't know
I'm not the type to fall in love with one girl
But I must really like her
Tae-soo!
Tae-soo?
Hi
What are you doing here?
I was waiting for you
Please take these flowers
I like you, Joo-hee
Please write to me
It's so strange
Is it because I'm too tall?
Why do I keep fainting?
I'm out of breath
It's because of Tae-soo, right?
What do you think I should do?
Tell me
Tae-soo is a rotten bastard
No, Tae-soo is nice
He's a rotten bastard because he's too nice
Tae-soo is waiting for your letter
There's no hope
There's nothing we can do for us
Don't say that
There's a way
No, there's nothing more we can do
Nothing
We'll only get hurt
It'll work out
I won't see neither you nor Tae-soo anymore
I'm serious
I won't see anyone
Hey, limousine boy!
Come here
Limousine boy!
Forgot to bow?
So you don't wanna bow
is that it?
If you have a chauffeur you don't have to bow, huh?
Your badge is upside down and your shirt's unbuttoned
Fine, today I'll give you the worst beating ever
I'm gonna beat you all starting from the left
The first one gets hit once the second one gets hit twice
From the third shout out your turn
- Got it?
- Yes, sir
- You sissies, I can't hear you!
- Yes, sir!
Seven
Stay still!
- Ouch, my back
- Stay still, or I'll break your arm
You get one more beating
Get into position!
Listen to what I said and get into position!