Leaving?
Hsiao-tsing...
Hsiao-tsing...!
So windy!
Ning!
What happened to your eyes?
Afool punched me!
Who?
Kneel down!
What are you doing?
It's pouring!
It's OK. I'm always getting wet
Let's go to the temple
You are in danger
That bearded guy is a killer
Come in first
I'm back to tell you to be careful
lt's dripping. Come
Did you come to rescue me?
I miss you!
The seller said
the girl died long time ago
Don't mention this
Don't forget, I'll get married in 2 days
It's also in the picture
Give it back to me
It sounds beautiful
Give it back!
You know kung fu?
Go!
What upset you?
Go away quick
I didn't know it was so important to you
Please don't be mad
I didn't mean it like that. To be honest
I'm not a human being
Don't say that
If you're not human, I'm not either
I'll take responsibility for what we did
Don't follow me!
Go find the bearded guy
He's a murderer
I'll get killed
You'll die!
Hsiao-tsing...
Don't follow me
You can't go
Where's Hsiao-tsing?
Hsiao-tsing!
I'm not coming for you
Heaven and earth are limitless
Ning!
The bearded guy killed your sister
Let's report him
I can't go with you
I don't care, I must get you out of here
Hsiao-tsing!
Hsiao-tsing's gone?
Court!
Someone is coming to pay you money
Yes!
Did you get the money?
Not yet!...
Master, sit up properly
Clean your teeth, Master
Wash your face, Master
Master!
Disturbing me at this hour
Beat him up!
Double the strokes
Stop, stop hitting!
l'll forget everything
Did you get the money?
Yes, of course!
Nonsense?
Beat!
I saw the murderer Liu
Liu?
Who's he?
He's a fugitive
But we got him 3 hours ago
I'm a greedy man
You're worse than me!
Want to take my money?
l'll beat you to death
Beat!
I really saw him
Did you?
Who's in the jail?
Yes, it's Liu!
Guilty!
Beat!
Master!
I think you got the wrong man!
We always get the wrong man!
Really?
Yes!
Get Liu!
If he's really Liu
Then we'll make a loss!
Don't plead guilty. Beat!
Yes!
Beat!
Why are you still hitting?
Stop it!
Killer!
Liu...
Liu?
Not robbing. l'm poor!
Mr. Chiu!
Yin?
l'm docking your pay
You don't know Yin?
He's so famous...
In 26 Province
He hates greedy Master
I'm not involved
Swordsman Yin, are you coming to get me?
I don't care for politics
I'm coming to see my brother
Don't listen to him. He's not my brother
Hold it!... Maybe it's wrong
Your honour, Liu is here
Master, Liu is in jail
Take him away! No reward
Go home!
Go away!
Yes!
You must protect me
He's a murderer.
Nonsense!
This case is too complicated.
It'll be triple the price
Right!
Where's the killer?
That's him!
I'm not a killer
I'm tired
What's happening?
lt's serious. Add some more
Listen, no dead body, no case
Our action should speak for itself
You are wasting our energy
It's worth paying more for a good show
Why are you such a fool?
Just be smart and pay it
I want to, but I don't have money
You can go and rob
Your honour, let's cancel the case!
He's so generous
Pay quickly and cancel the case
Where's the crime scene?
Speak up!
Orchid Temple
The one who died is not a human being
I saw you chop off that woman's head
Not a woman, a ghost
Ghost?
Anything not of this world
is not my concern
Right!
Then I don't charge you?
Right
Let's adjourn without charge...
Adjourned without charge...
I know that woman
Her family lives behind that Temple
It's now deserted
Behind it is the grave
Grave?
Because of the chaotic situation
the people in town have all left
The spooky sounds at night
are made by ghosts
Ghosts? I don't believe it!
If you don't believe, I'll take
you to see them
See for yourself!
You believe it now?
If she was a ghost
why didn't she kill me?
Maybe you still have some use
Really?
Only a ghost can tell
Ghosts use each other like people
Get out of here before it gets back
And you?
I'm staying. The world
is too complicated
lt's simpler to get along with ghosts
I'm staying
Go now!
I've thought it over
You'd better stay
Stay? Those female ghosts may hurt me
So much the better
I can wipe them all out
If they come to you, ring this bell
and I'll come to your rescue
You want to use me to kill Hsiao-tsing?
Yes, they got fed up with me and
won't tolerate me anymore
This one is powerful
Can you cope with them?
Sure, evil can't conquer good
Hold this Sutra
What language is that?
Sanskrit
Remember, concentration invites Buddhism
What's the first line?
Pao-Yeh-Pao-Lo-Mi
You know Sanskrit?
No, but I know this principle
Remember to ring the bell
when you see the evil
Pao-Yeh-Pao-Lo-Mi...
Don't keep reciting that!
The evil may not appear then
Who?
Who is it?
Say it, or I'll open the door
Why are you back?
Old Evil knows you are here
Are you a ghost?
Yes!
Did you kill those men in that temple?
I had no choice
I had to do it under the circumstances
Keep away...
Keep away, or I'll be nasty!
Did you hurt yourself?
Don't be afraid, I won't hurt you
Why don't you believe me?
Have I ever hurt you?
A ghost is evil
Can I trust a ghost?
But some men more scary than ghosts
Sometimes, they are more harmful
Some ghosts are unable
to vent their grievances
That's why I'm wandering
In fact, some ghosts are better than men
Why did you kill then?
Old Evil forced me to
She's a 1000-year old tree monster
lam from a good family
but I was murdered
My father buried me under that old tree
He was later also killed
Then Old Evil controlled my body and
used me to lure men to
absorb their yang elements
She's now selling me to that old monster
Stop!
Hsiao-tsing!
Bastard! Why don't you ring the bell?
Are you still afraid of me?
No, I must deliver you from Old Evil
Really?
After tomorrow, take my ashes
to a family before dusk
and I will have a chance
of reincarnation
Rest assured
l'll unearth it early tomorrow
and deliver it
Damn! Go quick!
That Taoist will fix you!
Old Evil asked me to hurt you
She doesn't trust me
She may come to kill you. Go now!
Don't worry! We are blessed
l have magic
Damn Taoist, you fooled me...
Pao-Yeh-Pao-Lo-Mi
It won't work?
Why doesn't it work?
What's this?
Old Evil's tongue
Ning Tsai-shen!
Hsiao-tsing...
What's this?
Hsiao-tsing!
Shut your mouth or
the tongue may get in!
This way!
Hsiao-tsing!
Leave me alone!
Ning Tsai-shen!
Follow the cloth; don't ever look back
Hsiao-tsing! l...
Go?
Ning Tsai-shen...
Hsiao-tsing!
Ning Tsai-shen!
Old Evil!
lt's you, damn Taoist!
Who else, if not me?
Where have you been?
Why didn't you come?
Why didn't you ring the bell?
I nearly got killed
How dare you take away my meat?
I don't mind your killing those bad ones
But this scholar
who is so pure
but weak and good for nothing
What good is he to you?
Don't compliment me!
I can't convince her without bluffing
Killing him means not giving me any face
What about your killing my maid?
That's not giving me any face either
Damn old woman, let's not
talk about face
Well, let's fight it out!
Let's see who is stronger
Her tongue's longer than yours!
Go away!
Pao-Yeh-Pao-Lo-Mi!
Blessed sword!
Watch out!
No scruples in Heaven or on Earth
Hsiao-tsing!
Ning Tsai-shen!
Keep away!
Hit!
Don't kill her!
Hsiao-tsing
Bastard! Come back quick!
Help that Taoist fight with Old Evil
Where?
Anywhere will do!
What if I hit?
Hit!
My bum!
She's coming again!
Run! Don't dawdle!
Hsiao-tsing!
Watch out!
I want your lives
l chop!
Hsiao-tsing!
Hsiao-tsing...
Are you mad? You know she's harmful
Why have you fallen for her?
She was forced. Don't misunderstand
There's a boundary between
men and ghosts
Men should avoid ghostly affairs
Not get involved
I've broken her century-old magic
She's powerful
but can only wreak havoc in a century
If nothing happens, she won't interfere
I must keep my promise
I must bring her ashes
back to her birth place
So that she can be reincarnated
Swordsman
I know you don't want to get involved
a lot of highlanders are
on the way to town
I can't make it without your help
Swordsman Yin, I beg you
Help me take her ashes back
Give her a chance. Please!
On your feet!
I retired
because I hate dealing with mean people
Sol hid in this temple
l pretended to be a ghost
in front of a man
and a human in front of a ghost
and now I don't know if
I'm a man or a ghost
I'm not a swordsman
Swordsman
Ridiculous!
What's so funny!
I don't want to be a man
But Hsiao-tsing wants to reincarnate
Don't say that!
The most important is to get out here
I don't understand all this nonsense!
Alright, I promise you!
I found it!
Why so much?
How strange!
Which one?
No time to sort out now
Take them away!
Where should we put the Sutra?
In the satchel!
No, keep it to make
the spirits follow us
Follow me closely!
I can't, you're riding too fast
We're in a rush
Yin, something's wrong!
Why are we still at the same old place?
Must be those evil spirits
What then?
We must get out of the forest
before it's dark
Pao-Yeh-Pao-Lo-Mi!
Follow me
Someone's celebrating!
lnn keeper!
Why is it deserted?
All gone to hell?
Who died?
What are you doing?
We want to stay the night
You can go!
Don't shout!
Hsiao-tsing, come out if
you're among them
Master, looking for me?
Master, looking for us?
No sign of Hsiao-tsing
Maybe the wrong ashes!
Grab your things and get lost
Don't wreak havoc anymore
Thank you!
Vanish!
Last chance
This is the last
Hsiao-tsing, come out
if it's you!
Come out!...
Master, looking for me?
A male!
No chance!
Why do you keep calling me?
It's the waiter
You scared me!
Damn!
Why did you appear so abruptly?
Come out!
Hsiao-tsing!
Ning Tsai-shen!
Thank you for saving my life!
Well...! Stand up!
Don't be formal. We're friends
You're wasting time!
l'll replace 2 horses
for the journey tomorrow
What a pair of lovers!
That's his style
He must do it before leaving
lt's frosty all over the lake
Time flies when all goes grey
Facing the moon alone, I need company
Lovebirds fare better than fairies
This picture is the only thing I leave
I'll keep it forever
We must be in town by dusk tomorrow
or I won't be reincarnated
You should be happy for me
It's a wonderful chance for you
But we must part before dawn
and forever
Heavens! Don't ever get dark!
Pao-Yeh-Pao-Lo-Mi
Evil in the air!
Blood bun!?
A ghost wedding
Stop dawdling!
This inn is haunted
Pack up and get out of here
I'll get the golden pagoda
Hurry up!
Oh, I forgot the painting!
Ning Tsai-shen!
Today's a good day in hell
They must've got Hsiao-tsing back
Old Evil's coming to collect the bride
Scholar, it seems we have to storm Hell!
We must rescue Hsiao-tsing
We can't go back when the day breaks
Remember, close your eyes!
Pao-Yeh-Pao-Lo-Mi...
Can I open my eyes now?
You must, if you want to find her
Hsiao-tsing's inside
Hsiao-tsing!
Ning Tsai-shen!
Why can't I get hold of her?
Hsiao-tsing...
In the mundane world
men can't see ghosts
ln hell ghosts can't see men
Hsiao-tsing can see you now. Go now!
They're going to hell!
Go!
Hsiao-tsing!
What now?
Go into hiding
Go and rescue Hsiao-tsing at once
Me?
Let's go!
Pao-Yeh-Pao-Lo-Mi
Heaven and Earth are limitless
Here I am!
Don't mind me, run!
I'm here to help you
l'll cut it for you!
Run!
The magic powers!
Swordsman Yin, watch out!
You go first, I'll stay behind
Find another exit
Pao-Yeh-Pao-Lo-Mi
Swordsman Yin!
Why have you come back?
We can't get out of here!
Old Evil has blocked the exit
You can't get out of here
Help me get an arrow
Draw the bow
Let loose!
Pao-Yeh-Pao-Lo-Mi
Damn, we're not his match
Pull at him. This is 1000-year old Evil
He may drain your soul away
Swordsman Yin!
Concentrate!
Recite! Pao-Yeh-Pao-Lo-Mi
Lord Black, please let them go
Break the golden pagoda
and be my company
Hsiao-tsing, don't be taken in
Concentrate! Recite!
Pao-Yeh-Pao-Lo-Mi...
Don't!
l'll rescue you!
Hsiao-tsing!
Yin Che-hsia, Ning Tsai-shen
I'll take your lives
Don't
What's this?
The Sutra?
You've done enough
l have to get rid of you damn evil
Damn old Evil!
Swordsman Yin!
The way's clear! Help Swordsman Yin out!
Swordsman Yin, we're back on Earth!
Damn, it's dawn!
Hsiao-tsing's not yet here!
Help her out
Swordsman Yin, lend a hand!
Hsiao-tsing!
Keep her from the sunshine
Or she may evaporate and
can't be reincarnated
Hsiao-tsing, come back to
the golden pagoda!
The sun is rising, I've got to go!
Hsiao-tsing, be a good human being
l'll remember you always
I can't even see you before we part
Take care!
She's gone!
Hsiao-tsing
Hsiao-tsing, I'll take you back
Wonder if she has been reincarnated
In these times, an unlucky man
may fare worse than a ghost
Look ahead
Let's go!