You keep your work station
so clean, Jerome.
It's next to godliness.
- Isn't that what they say?
- "Godliness."
I reviewed your flight plan.
Not one error in a million keystrokes.
Phenomenal. It's right that
someone like you...
is taking us to Titan.
Has the committee
approved the mission?
There's been talk of delay.
You shouldn't listen to talk.
You leave in a week.
You've got a substance test.
If you have been notified
for substance analysis...
please report
to the testing center.
Jerome. Never shy.
Pisses on command.
A beautiful piece of equipment there, Jerome.
Have I ever told you that?
Only every time I'm in here.
Occupational hazard.
I see a great many
of the course of any given day.
Yours just happens to be
an exceptional example.
I don't know why my folks
didn't order one like that for me.
By the way...
have I ever told you about my son?
- No, you haven't.
- Remind me to sometime.
So you're about to go up.
One week left.
Please tell me
you're at least a bit excited.
I'll tell you
at the end of the week.
Congratulations, Jerome.
Thank you.
How many launches are there
in a day? A dozen?
Sometimes more.
You're the only one
who watches every one of them.
If you're going to pretend
like you don't care, don't look up.
The most unremarkable of events.
Jerome Morrow,
navigator first class...
is about to embark on a one-year
manned mission to Titan...
the 14th moon of Saturn.
A highly prestigious assignment.
Although for Jerome...
selection was
virtually guaranteed at birth.
He's blessed with all the gifts
required for such an undertaking.
A genetic quotient
second to none.
No, there is truly
nothing remarkable...
about the progress
of Jerome Morrow.
Except that
I am NOT Jerome Morrow.
I was conceived
in the Riviera.
Not the French Riviera,
the Detroit variety.
They used to say that
a child conceived in love...
has a greater chance of happiness.
They don't say that anymore.
I'll never understand what possessed
my mother to put her faith...
in God's hands rather than
those of her local geneticist.
Ten fingers, ten toes.
That's all that used to matter.
Not now.
Now, only seconds old...
the exact time and cause
of my death was already known.
Neurological condition:
60% probability.
Manic depression:
42% probability.
Attention deficit disorder:
89% probability.
Heart disorder--
99% probability.
Early fatal potential.
Life expectancy: 30.2 years.
Thirty years.
The name for the certificate?
- Anton.
- No!
Vincent Anton.
Yeah. That's a good name.
I know he'll do something.
From an early age I came to think
of myself as others thought of me.
Chronically ill.
Every skinned knee and runny nose...
was treated
as if it were life-threatening.
I'm sorry.
The insurance won't cover it.
- If he fell--
- But I was told, that everything--
I really wish there was
something I could do.
Like most other parents of their day...
they were determined that their next child
would be brought into the world...
in what has become
the natural way.
Your extracted eggs, Marie...
have been fertilized
with Antonio's sperm.
After screening, we are
left, as you see, with two healthy boys...
and two very healthy girls.
Naturally, no critical predispositions
to any major inheritable diseases.
All that remains is to select
the most compatible candidate.
First, we let's decide on gender.
Have you given it any thought?
We would want Vincent
to have a brother, you know...
to play with.
Of course you would.
Hello, Vincent.
You have specified hazel eyes,
dark hair and fair skin.
I've taken the liberty of eradicating
any potentially prejudicial conditions.
Premature baldness, myopia...
alcoholism and
addictive susceptibility...
propensity for violence,
obesity, etc.
We didn't want--
I mean diseases, yes, but--
Right! We were just wondering if...
If it's good to just leave a few things to chance?
You want to give your child
the best possible start.
Believe me, we have enough
imperfection built in already.
Your child doesn't need
any additional burdens.
Keep in mind
this child is still you.
Simply the best of you.
You could conceive naturally a thousand
times and never get such a result.
That's how my brother, Anton,
came into the world.
A son my father considered
worthy of his name.
What did I tell you?
See how he's grown?
By the time we were
playing at blood brothers...
I understood that there was something
very different flowing through my veins...
and I'd need
more than a drop...
if I was going to get anywhere.
Our favorite game was chicken.
When our parents weren't watching,
we used to swim as far out as we dared.
It was about who would get scared
and turn back first.
Come on, you coward!
Of course,
it was always me.
Anton was by far
the stronger swimmer...
and he had no excuse
to fail.
Maybe it was the love of the planets...
maybe it was just my growing dislike for this one.
But for as long as I can remember,
I have dreamed of going into space.
700 million. 750 million.
800 million.
850 million.
How many astronauts are there anyway?
I bet I could be one.
If I wanted.
Hey, don't eat that.
It's Pluto.
My goals didn't change a lot
in the intervening years...
Vincent...
much to my parents' dismay.
You have to be realistic.
With a heart condition like yours--
Mom, there's a chance
there's nothing even wrong with my heart.
One chance in a hundred.
- I'll take it, all right?
- The trouble is, they won't.
Listen. For God's sake...
you gotta understand something.
The only way that you'll see the inside
of a spaceship is if you will cleaning it.
My father was right.
It didn't matter how much
I lied on my resume.
My real resume
was in my cells.
Why should anybody invest
all that money to train me...
when there are a thousand other
applicants with a far cleaner profile?
Of course, it's illegal
to discriminate.
"Genoism" it's called.
But no one
takes the law seriously.
If you refuse to disclose...
they can always take a sample
from a door handle or a handshake...
even the saliva
on your application form.
If in doubt, a legal drug test
can just as easily become...
an illegal peek
at your future in the company.
You sure you wanna do this?
You know you're gonna lose.
It was the last time
we swam together...
and out into the open sea...
like always, knowing each stroke
to the horizon...
was one we'd have to
make back to the shore.
But something was very different
about that day.
Every time Anton
tried to pull away...
he found me right beside him.
Until finally,
the impossible happened.
Vincent!
It was the one moment
in our lives that my brother...
was not as strong as he believed
and I was not as weak.
It was the moment that made
everything else possible.
Like many others in my situation...
I moved around a lot in the next few years,
getting work where I could.
I must've cleaned
half the toilets in the state.
I belonged to a new underclass...
no longer determined
by social status of the color of your skin.
- Welcome to Gattaca, gentlemen.
- No.
We now have discrimination
down to a science.
All right!
There's your cleaning material.
Start from the front,
clean all the way back.
And I wanna see my smiling face
on that floor.
What about you, Your Majesty?
You dreaming of space?
Come here.
You can start by
cleaning this space right here.
I was never more certain of
how far away I was from my goal...
than when I was
standing right beside it.
When you clean the glass, Vincent,
don't clean it too well.
What do you mean?
You might get ideas.
Yeah, but if the glass is clean, it'll be easier
for you to see me when I'm on the other side of it.
For all my brave talk,
I knew it was just that.
No matter how much I trained
or how much I studied...
the best test score in the world wasn't going
matter without the blood test to go with it.
I made up my mind to resort
to more extreme measures.
The man who
showed up at my doorstep...
didn't exactly advertise
in the Yellow Pages.
Stand straight.
- How did you hear about me?
- People.
Any distinguishing marks?
Tattoos, scars, birthmarks?
No. I don't think so.
You're serious about this?
I hope you're not wasting my time.
No, I'd give 100%.
That'll get you halfway there.
That's an old edition,
but I know it all by heart.
By heart, huh?
You realize the commitment
is binding.
You have somebody in mind?
For the genetically superior,
success is easier to attain...
but is by no means guaranteed.
After all, there is no gene for fate.
And when,
for one reason or another...
a member of the elite
falls on hard times...
their genetic identity becomes a
valued commodity for the unscrupulous.
One man's loss is another man's gain.
His credentials are impeccable.
An expiration date
you wouldn't believe.
The guy's practically
gonna live forever.
He's got an I.Q. off the register.
Better than 20/20 in both eyes.
And the heart of an ox.
He could run through a wall.
If he could still run.
Actually, he was
a big-time swimming star.
You could go anywhere with this guy's
helix tucked under your arm.
What did I tell you? You look so right
together I wanna double my fee.
- We don't look anything alike.
- It's close enough.
When was the last time anybody
looked at a photograph?
You could have my face on your name tag,
for Christ's sake.
- How do I explain the accident?
- That's the beautiful thing.
It happened out of the country.
There's no record he ever broke his back.
As far as anyone's concerned...
he's still a walking, talking,
fully-productive member of society.
You just have to get him clean
and fill in the last year of his life.
You're a foreigner.
They don't care
where you were born, just how.
Blood has no nationality.
As long as it's got
what they're looking for...
it's the only passport you need.
Who lives up there?
Well, I certainly don't.
So began the process
of becoming Jerome.
Myopia is one of the most obvious
signs of a disadvantaged birth.
Isn't there another way?
Surgery's no good.
They'll see the scars.
It's contact lenses or a white cane.
Besides, the color doesn't match.
He's right.
My eyes are prettier.
You understand
I take 25% of everything you make.
If for some reason it doesn't work out, all this
equipment must be returned within seven days.
And you don't get your deposit back.
- Wait, wait! I thought you said 20%.
- He told me 20%.
- Twenty percent.
- It's not negotiable.
I guess that's it.
Not quite.
- Why? What?
- There's still the matter of the height.
- Why, how tall are you?
- 4'6".
How tall were you
before the accident?
Unfortunately,
his profile says he's 6'1".
So I'll wear lifts.
Even with lifts,
you're not that tall.
So, what?
No... no...
No, we never discussed that.
I thought you were serious, Vincent.
I am serious. I'm not doing that.
I won't do that.
Jerome never
questioned my commitment again.
I took my mind off the pain
by reminding myself...
that when I eventually did stand up
I'd be exactly two inches closer to the stars.
You all right?
Yeah.
You wanna go dancing?
You had to be a right-hander.
I guess no one orders
southpaws anymore.
Jerome Morrow.
It's a nice name.
- It's my name.
- I can't be you without it.
What makes you think
you can be me at all?
Look at this.
Look at it.
It's nice.
Impressed. Is it real?
Are you colorblind too, Vincent?
- It's silver.
- So?
Jerome Morrow was never meant
to be one step down on the podium.
With all I had going for me...
I was still second best.
Me.
So how do you expect
to pull this off?
I don't know exactly.
Your signature needs work.
It soon came time to put
our preparations to the test.
Jerome had been engineered with everything
he needed to get into Gattaca...
except the desire to do so.
Do you really wanna be in there?
I don't wanna be in there.
I wanna be up there.
What's up there?
That's what I wanna find out, Jerome.
Call me Eugene.
My middle name.
If you're gonna be Jerome,
you better start getting used to it.
I gotta get going.
Where's my sample?
In the refrigerator!
Door on the left!
Which pouch?
Oh, any of them.
Should I test it?
If you like!
- What's wrong with the machine?
- Nothing!
It's a hot sample.
You've been drinking again.
- I haven't!
- Oh Christ, Eugene, it's 8:00 in the morning!
I haven't!
This is no joke!
My interview is in an hour!
There is more vodka in this piss
than there is piss!
I'm sorry.
I had half a glass to celebrate, I'm sorry.
Try Friday's.
That one will be okay.
- There's only Wednesday left.
- Wednesay... That's the one.
Listen. It's not too late
to back out.
This is the last day that you're gonna be you
and I'm gonna be me.
Well?
Congratulations.
Well, what about the interview?
That was it.
I got it.
Of course you got it.
And that's the way it was.
Each day, I would dispose of as much loose skin,
fingernails and hair as possible...
to limit how much of my In-Valid self
I would leave in the Valid world.
At the same time, Eugene prepared samples of
his own superior body matter...
so that I might pass for him.
Customized urine pouches
for the frequent substance tests...
fingertip blood sachets
for security checks...
and vials filled with other traces.
While Eugene supplied me
with a new identity, I paid the rent...
and kept him in the style
to which he'd become accustomed.
Eugene never suffered from the routine
discrimination of a "utero"...
a "faith birth" or "In-Valid"
as we were called.
A "Valid," a "vitro," a "made man",
he suffered under a different burden.
The burden of perfection.
I was now a member
of a relatively new...
and particularly detested
segment of society.
One of those who refuses
to play the hand that he was dealt.
I am most commonly known
as a "borrowed ladder" or...
a "de-gene-erate."
In the guise of Jerome Morrow...
I have risen quickly
through the ranks of Gattaca.
Only one of the mission directors
has ever come close...
to discovering my true identity.
Strange to think, he may have more
success exposing me in death...
than he ever did in life.
We apologize for any inconvenience.
- Well, I think we can rule out suicide.
- Excuse me, Sir?
Nothing.
Thank you.
This will take a while.
We might have to push things back.
Irene, I want you to
assist the investigators.
My work, Director.
That would put me behind.
I appreciate your sacrifice, Irene.
Will you see that
I don't lose my place in line?
Your place is assured.
So, will you kindly inform
the authorities...
that we will cooperate
in any way...
although we can't tolerate
a major disruption.
- Director--
- Thank you, Irene.
Thank you, Director.
Director, how will this affect the mission?
Oh, we're still going ahead
as planned.
The launch window's only open
until week's end...
and tragic though
this event may be...
it hasn't stopped
the planets' turning, has it?
- What happened?
- I'm going up.
When?
End of the week.
End of the week?
That soon?
What about the mission director?
He's dead.
Are you serious?
They found him in his office this morning
beaten so badly they had to check his name tag.
You are serious.
So that's it.
There's nothing between us
and ignition.
I'm going up.
- The man was murdered.
- So? I didn't do it.
I didn't say you did, but if the man was murdered
the place is gonna be crawling with Hoovers.
I'll take my chances with the
"J. Edgars" over the mission director.
Besides, what if they do find something?
I'll gonna be slightly out of their jurisdiction.
We have to get drunk immediately.
- Good evening, gentlemen.
- Good evening, I hope our table's ready.
- I understand you're leaving us, Mr. Morrow.
- Yeah, looks that way.
- We're going to miss you.
- You've opened the wine, I hope?
- Of course, sir.
- Pour yourself a glass, Cavendish.
Thank you, sir.
How old?
- Me?
- The specimen.
I kissed him five minutes ago.
A real good one.
I'll see what I can do.
- You want the full sequence?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Good luck.
Some samples may be consumed
in the sequencing process.
9.3. Quite a catch.
Yes. Quite a catch.
God, how many times
have I told Cavendish?
This can't have been opened
more than five minutes ago!
A wine like this needs to breathe.
Remember that.
You know, they say
when you're weightless...
it's the closest thing
to being in the womb.
I can't believe
you pulled this off.
They're sending you up there.
Up there, for Christ's sake.
You, of all people.
I hate to think of you
alone in that room for a year.
Don't think about it.
Anyway...
the room I'm stuck in
is bigger than your tin can.
You know what I'm saying.
What are you gonna do?
I have my books.
I go places in my head.
- I'd be happier if you had company.
- I have visitors!
- Yeah, well. None that you don't pay.
- I wouldn't have it any other way.
Seriously,
what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna finish this.
What's Titan like
this time of year?
What's Titan like?
Titan is exactly like this.
All the time.
It's got a cloud around it so thick
nobody can tell what's underneath.
Maybe there's nothing there.
There's something there.
You should be going
instead of me.
Why is that?
Because up there
your legs wouldn't matter.
I'm scared of heights.
I'm sorry!
Do you want this?
I'll save some for you, shall I?
- I'm so sorry. I'm really sorry.
- You're not that sorry.
I'm really, really sorry.
Don't give me a hard time.
Give me a break.
Come on!
- I'm sorry.
- Help!
And I wasn't drunk.
- What do you mean "you're not drunk"?
- When I walked in front of that car.
What car?
I stepped right out
in front of it.
I'd never been more sober
in my life.
- Go to sleep.
- Couldn't even get that right, could I?
"If at first you don't succeed,
try, try again."
Go to sleep.
I'm proud of you, Vincent.
You must be drunk
to call me Vincent.
- How much do you need?
- Twenty minutes.
You can go.
It's all right, Irene.
You're excused.
We found our man. It's the only
specimen we can't account for.
Every ten years or so,
things go our way.
The eyelash?
What do you know about him?
He's an unregistered In-Valid.
He was a janitor here until a few years back
when he disappeared out of sight.
So the specimen could have
been here since then.
Well, take a look at the floor. So I don't think
anything lays around here for very long.
It's also the matter of motive.
Is a janitor gonna come back here after all
this time to kill a man he never knew?
Well, his profile does suggest
a violent temperament.
If I'm not mistaken, his profile also
suggests he's a sick man.
There's a 90% chance the owner of this eyelash
has already died himself of natural causes.
Then there's a ten percent chance he's still alive.
It's a lost-and-found case, sir.
All we have to do is find the man who's minus an eyelash,
we have the murderer.
I'll do a cross check,
find out about his family...
I've already run it. There's no record
of any living relative.
Well, that's a damn shame, sir.
I want you to check the entry log,
alibis, grudges.
I look around,
I see a lot of dry eyes.
The mission director
was not, uh, universally loved.
He was leading the cutbacks
in the program.
With all due respect, sir...
Whatever you say.
Jerome, Jerome,
the metronome.
I could play the piano
by that heartbeat of his.
Mr. Director, you will be pleased
to know that we have a suspect.
That is a relief.
Who is it?
We found an unaccounted for specimen
in the south wing and here's his picture.
- An In-Valid.
- We are still following other leads.
Be that as it may,
I'm having this posted immediately.
I'm curious, Director.
An advantage, I should imagine,
in your line of work.
Your hiring practices.
Our recruitment philosophy.
Who do you have to be
to be here?
Naturally, our standard is beyond
that of the common citizen.
Even amongst your people, you must
have varying levels of excellence.
Occasionally we've been forced to accept
candidates with minor shortcomings...
but nothing that would prohibit
someone from working in a field...
such as law enforcement,
for example.
But now there are enough
of the right kind of people...
to warrant a new measuring stick.
Bodies with minds to match.
Essential as we push out further
and further.
Yet you still
closely monitor performance.
We have to ensure that people
are meeting their potential.
- And exceeding it.
- No one exceeds his potential.
If he did?
It would simply mean we did not
accurately gauge his potential in the first place.
- Are you all right, Jerome?
- Terrific.
This is the entry log
for the last seven days.
What about you, Irene?
Do you have an alibi?
- I was alone.
- I find that hard to believe.
Excuse me.
I'll take care of that for you, Mr. Morrow.
I see I'm not the only one
who looks up every time there's a launch.
- Hello, Jerome.
- Hello.
It's awful about the director.
Awful it didn't happen sooner.
Didn't the director threaten to cancel
your mission more than once, Jerome?
- Yes. He did.
- Somebody did you a favor.
Do they have any idea whose hand
I should be shaking?
They found an eyelash
in the south wing.
- Does it have a name?
- Just some In-Valid.
Jerome...
I had you sequenced.
I read your profile.
I'm sorry.
Seems you're
everything they say you are and more.
What about you, Irene? You're engineered
just like the rest of us.
Not quite like the rest of us.
"Unacceptable likelihood of heart failure."
I think that's what the manual says.
The only trip I'll take in space
is around the sun on the satellite right here.
Well, if there's anything wrong with you,
I can't see it from where I'm standing.
If you don't believe me...
Here. Take it.
If you're still interested,
let me know.
I'm sorry.
The wind caught it.
Jerome, is this the approach path
that we discussed?
Absolutely, Director.
Quite right. Quite right.
Listen to what I'm saying to you.
I want what I ordered.
It's a completely different color.
Now, I'm bored of talking to you.
I'm bored.
I'll call you back.
That was the company
that sent us your hair dye.
They sent me "summer wheat"
instead of "honey dawn."
Any fool knows
it's two shades lighter.
She said.
"Why don't you try a change?"
I don't want a change.
We can't use a change.
Now I'm probably gonna have to pay
for the five boxes they've sent me.
We can't stay here.
Idiots I have to deal with,
you wouldn't believe.
They think I killed
the mission director.
- What makes them think that?
- They found my eyelash.
- Where?
- In the corridor.
Oh well, it could be worse.
They could've found it in your eye.
They've got my picture
plastered up all over the place.
I can't turn around
without seeing my own face.
- They'll recognize me.
- They won't recognize you.
I don't recognize you!
They won't marry the eyelash to you.
They won't believe
that one of their elite...
could have suckered them
all this time.
No, no, no.
We change nothing.
We do as we planned.
You're Jerome Morrow.
Navigator first class.
I'm not Jerome Morrow.
I'm a murder suspect.
What are you doing?
What are you doing!
That's more than a day's work!
- Wait.
- We can't stay here.
Stop that!
Oh, fine!
Fine!
You leave if you want,
but you're not taking that stuff.
That stuff is mine!
I could've rented myself out
to somebody with a spine...
if I'd known you were going to go
belly-up on me at the last fucking gasp.
You can't quit on me now.
I've put too much into this.
What do you want me to do?
Wheel in there
and finish the job myself?
Eugene, they're going to find me.
You still don't understand, do you?
When they look at you, they don't
see you anymore. They only see me.
Keep your lashes on your lids
where they belong.
How could you be so careless?
I'm going out.
Where are you going?
If I'm gonna get arrested tomorrow,
I'm gonna go out tonight.
- You sure that's a good idea to go out?
- Well, it was your idea not to change anything.
- Who's going?
- Just everybody.
Everybody.
If I don't go,
it'll look suspicious.
You don't want
to look suspicious, do you?
Thanks.
Who ordered this?
What are we doing here?
I'm following a lead.
Forgive me, sir, but that's what I do.
I'm a detective. I follow leads.
What makes you think
the owner of the eyelash is here?
He's an In-Valid, sir. Where do we look
for In-Valids but where In-Valids are?
He's an In-Valid?
He's an In-Valid clever enough
to go unregistered all these years.
Do you think he's likely
to lie down for us now?
- Well, what would you suggest, sir?
- Move the inquiry...
back to the scene.
Draw a five-mile radius around Gattaca,
sweep again, random stops.
You're a navigator?
At Gattaca?
That's what it says, doesn't it?
It doesn't say you're crippled.
I'm not crippled.
I hurt my leg training, you moron.
How dare you question me?
Yeah, right.
- What's your number?
- All right, forget it.
What's your number,
you fucking flatfoot?
I said forget it.
What do you want, an apology?
It gets to you, doesn't it?
It gets to you that I can do
what you can only dream of!
I'm getting off this ball of dirt!
How dare you question me?
- That's harassment.
- My mistake.
What's your number?
What's your number!
May I remind you
that this is a crime scene?
What's this man doing here?
- What are you doing, old man?
- Uh, doing my job, sir.
- This is evidence.
- But it's just trash.
You didn't know?
- Oh, yes. Yeah.
- Wonderful. Wasn't it?
Twelve fingers or one,
it's how you play.
That piece can only
be played with 12.
What's all this about?
Uh, it's probably nothing.
You better not. I don't want to give you
a contaminated specimen.
Get my meaning?
Thanks.
You never know
where those swabs have been.
I want to show you something.
Come on!
We'll miss it!
Come on. Come on.
We'll miss it, come on.
What did I tell you?
- Strange.
- What?
- Your eyes look different.
- I guess it must be the light.
Must be.
Positive match.
I'm impressed.
The cup was definitely used
since the original sweep?
Two samples. Two days.
Either the suspect went back to the scene
of the crime to get a drink of water,
or I don't know anybody that thirsty
or he still works there.
I thought we checked
all the service staff.
I don't think he cleans up
the place anymore.
I have a feeling he might be there under false
pretenses. Playing somebody else's hand.
A borrowed ladder?
At Gattaca?
It's far-fetched,
but it's not a ruled out possibilty.
I find it hard to believe
he could be one of their elite workers.
Even if he got pass the security system,
he wouldn't have the mental faculty
or the physical stamina.
Maybe you're underestimating him.
Maybe he is an impostor,
and maybe the director found out about it.
That could be his motive. I say, we sample every
employee within the parameters intravenously.
Two-thirds of their work force
fall under that category.
We would closing them down for days.
No. A fingertip sample or urine should be sufficient.
I suggest blood from the vein.
I hope I'm not out of line.
It's only a matter of time, sir.
Only a matter of time.
What's with the plungers, Lamar?
You open up a blood bank?
The gentlemen of law enforcement
are concerned...
that my testing methods
may have been compromised.
- Goddamn!
- Jerome, I'm sorry.
- Are you out of practice, Lamar?
- Here, let me look at that.
It's all right. It's all right.
It's all right.
Luckily, it looks as though
we have enough.
If you need more,
you can always get it off his shoes.
Irene
So you didn't do it, after all.
Oh no, I...
I guess somebody beat me to it.
I guess.
Um...
I leave in two days.
I guess you know that.
But...
That's the last.
- Something's not right.
- He's not here. It's a blind alley.
No, we missed something.
I say we test again.
Test? I cannot allow you
to disrupt operations any further.
You're not at all concerned about having
a murderer in your midst?
Right now your presence
is creating more of a threat.
The window for our latest launch
is open for seven days...
once every 70 years...
so it's rather crucial
we leave on time.
The mission means a great deal
to you, doesn't it?
And your late colleague
opposed it, didn't he?
Take another look
at my profile, Detective.
You won't find a violent bone
in my body.
My apologies, Director.
We won't trouble you any further.
This is not the only place
we can look.
OK
Let's start making our rounds.
I'm luckier than most.
Not as lucky as some.
- I know something about that.
- You, Jerome?
What heart problem
did you ever have?
Did you get yours broken once?
I had this crazy idea...
that you were more interested
in the murder case than me.
You're right.
That's a crazy idea.
Would you like to dance?
It's funny.
You work so hard...
and you do everything you can
to get away from a place...
and when you finally
get your chance to leave...
you find a reason to stay.
A year is a long time.
Not so long.
Just once around the sun.
Hello, everyone!
Nice to see you.
I'm your detective for the evening.
Please don't leave the premises.
I said nobody leave! Am I speaking
in some kind of strange foreign language?
Check for hairpieces, lenses, dentures.
I want napkins. I want cigarette butts.
I want the saliva off teacups.
That's a familiar face.
Check him out, will you?
I thought you wanted to dance.
- Excuse me. Where are you going?
- Oh yeah, I know. Just a minute.
Jerome!
- Are you insane?
- Come on!
Where did they go?
Where did they go!
Come here. Come on.
- Don't you understand? I can't do that.
- You just did.
Don't touch your face!
Don't swallow! Don't spit!
Let's clean his teeth.
Vincent
Vincent!
Who's Vincent?
I...
Don't say anything.
What happened?
The scars on your legs?
Oh, uh...
You remember the '99 Chrysler LeBaron?
This is the exact height
of the front fender.
I looked left instead of right.
Did you just make that up,
or do you use it all the time?
I use it all the time.
I know you had something to do
with the director's death.
That's not true, Irene.
Isn't that the man from last night?
He's nobody.
He's one of our best.
I'm certain he has nothing
to do with this business.
Jerome Morrow.
You don't look well, Jerome.
Why don't you go home?
- Can I help you?
- I'm looking for Jerome Morrow.
I'm sorry. He's ill with nausea.
It's quite common before a mission.
Really?
I ought to pay him a visit.
I understand you can show me the way.
You don't know who he is, do you, Irene?
Hello?
Eugene, I need you
to be yourself for the day.
I was never very good at it,
remember?
The investigators are coming by.
I'm supposed to be sick.
So you keep telling me.
How long have I got?
Not long.
I guess he's not home.
- Hello?
- I'm here to see Jerome Morrow.
Yes. That's me.
Come up.
I guess he's home.
Come in!
Come in
Hello, sweetheart.
Where's my kiss?
Good to see you're feeling better.
Of course. Now that you're here.
Who's your friend?
How can I help?
It's about the director.
Oh. Again?
- I hope it's no trouble.
- No, no. No trouble.
Forgive me for not giving you
a guided tour.
- Couldn't we do this another time?
- This won't take a moment.
Maybe he can tell me what I've got.
Who were you expecting?
- Yes?
- We have our man, sir.
- You have him?
- We have him in custody.
I'll come right away.
How are you, Jerome?
Not bad, Jerome.
- How the hell did you get up here?
- Oh, I could always walk.
I've been faking it.
Irene! Irene...
Irene
- Don't touch me!
- Listen to me, Irene.
I don't even know who you are.
I'm the same person I was yesterday.
I can't hear any more
of your lies, Jerome.
My name is Vincent!
I am Vincent Anton Freeman.
I'm a faith birth, de-gene-erate,
whatever you want to call it.
But I am not a murderer.
You're a God child?
But we do have one thing in common.
Only I don't have 20 or 30 years left in mine.
Mine is already 10,000 beats overdue.
- It's not possible.
- You are the authority...
on what is not possible,
aren't you, Irene?
They have got you looking
so hard for any flaw...
that after a while
that's all that you see.
For whatever it's worth...
I'm here to tell you
that it is possible.
It is possible.
Congratulations, sir.
We did it.
His spit was found
in the dead director's eye.
While I was busy obsessing
about an eyelash, your instincts...
took us in the right direction.
So the In-Valid had nothing
to do with this?
No. Our friend here acted alone.
This mission meant everything to him.
Didn't it?
If they miss this launch window,
he won't live to see the next one.
And since nothing can stop the launch now,
he's being very very cooperative.
So I imagine...
you'll be celebrating tonight, sir.
Of course.
I think she likes us.
Yeah, sure. Just give her a little time.
She'll get used to the idea.
- What was he like?
- Who? The cop?
- He was just a cop.
- Did you catch his name?
Actually, my name was the topic
of conversation.
Yeah, well, he'll be back.
You heard what they said.
They have their man. It's over.
No, it's not over.
I have to meet him.
Vincent?
My God, you have changed.
Has it been so long
you don't recognize your own brother?
Are we brothers?
Our parents both died
thinking they'd outlived you.
I had my doubts.
What are you doing here, Anton?
I should ask you that question.
I have a right to be here.
You don't.
You almost sound
as if you believe that.
I committed no murder.
You must be disappointed.
You committed fraud.
Listen, you've a lot of trouble, Vincent.
I can get you out of here.
Do you have any idea
what it took to get in here?
You've gone as far as you can go.
Come with me now!
There is still a few million
miles left to go.
It's over!
Is that the only way you can succeed
is to see me fail?
God! Even you are gonna tell me
what I can and can't do now!
In case you haven't noticed,
I don't need any rescuing.
But you did once.
Well, you've got all the answers.
How do you explain that?
You didn't beat me that day.
I beat myself.
Who are you trying to convince?
Do you want me
to prove it to you?
It's not important, Anton.
It's forgotten.
I'll prove it to you! Do you want me
to prove it to you? I'll prove it to you!
I do.
Vincent!
Where's the shore?
We're too far out!
- You wanna quit?
- We're too far out!
You wanna quit?
No!
Vincent!
How are you doing this, Vincent?
How have you done any of this?
- We have to go back.
- It's too late for that.
We're closer to the other side.
What other side?
You wanna drown us both?
You wanna know how I did it?
This is how I did it, Anton.
I never saved anything for the swim back.
You couldn't see, could you?
That night, crossing the street.
You crossed anyway.
If you're still interested...
Let me know.
Sorry.
The wind caught it.
You're flying today, aren't you?
Look at what a mess you're in.
Come on.
I have your samples ready.
I don't need any samples
where I'm going.
You might when you get back.
Everything you need
to last you two lifetimes.
Why have you done all this?
So Jerome will always be here
when you need him.
- Where are you going?
- I'm traveling too.
I don't know how to thank you.
I got the better end of the deal.
I only lent you my body.
You lent me your dream.
Not until you're upstairs.
What is this?
New policy.
Flight got you nervous?
Well, there's a problem, Lamar.
I never told you about my son, did I?
He's a big fan of yours.
Just remember...
that I was as good as any
and better than most.
He wants to apply here.
I could've gone up and back,
and nobody would've been the wiser.
Unfortunately, my son's
not all that they promised.
But then, who knows
what he could do?
Right?
For future reference...
right-handed men
don't hold it with their left.
Just one of those things.
You're gonna miss your flight, Vincent.
For someone who was never
meant for this world...
I must confess I'm suddenly
having a hard time leaving it.
Of course, they say every atom
in our bodies was once part of a star.
Maybe I'm not leaving.
Maybe I'm going home.