(BREATH TREMBLING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(WHIMPERING)
Kaylie!
Shh!
(GUNSHOT)
And I fired.
As many times
as I've had this dream...
...it's never been me before.
Holding the gun.
I know.
That's very good.
It implies a true, deeply-rooted
acceptance of responsibility.
And it tells me that you haven't
only overcome your delusion
in your conscious mind...
...but in his
subconscious mind as well.
It's my opinion that Tim
is a healthy adult
who represents no danger
to himself or anyone else.
And I believe he should be discharged,
as the state requested,
on his upcoming 21st birthday.
(FOOTSTEPS)
WOMAN: ...going once...
...eleven-five twice...
(GAVEL BANGS)
Sold to the gentleman.
Congratulations to you, sir.
That's bidder number 131.
All right, and our next item for bid
is a gorgeous antique mirror,
recovered from the Levesque Estate.
The Lasser Glass
is a well-traveled gem.
It spent several seasons adorning
the walls at Balmoral Castle,
Scottish home
of the Royal Family.
This is the original glass
and the original frame.
The mirror is in remarkable condition,
save for a small hairline fracture
down in the lower right-hand corner.
The frame is carved out of one piece
of Bavarian Black Cedar.
And we will go ahead
and start the bidding
at a conservative ten thousand dollars.
Do I have ten? Right here
in front. Thank you, sir.
DOCTOR: Your sister
is picking you up, then?
Her message even said something
about helping me find a job.
That'd be wonderful for your transition.
AUCTIONEER: We're at
12,000 dollars on the phone...
You sure you don't want me
to come with you?
- Some moral support?
- No. But thank you.
I think I better do this part myself.
- Wait up for us.
- Of course.
Remember what we talked about.
You've had a support system,
a mandated support system,
to help you get well.
Kaylie had to get by on her own.
It's very important that you
reconnect with your sister.
But it's more important
that you protect your recovery.
- Sixteen thousand.
- Sixteen thousand on Skype.
That is sixteen, going once.
Sixteen twice.
Sold. Please pass along
our congratulations.
- See you tonight.
- OK.
(DOOR BUZZES)
Son, just pull the door when it buzzes.
Hey, little brother.
Your half of the estate.
Oh, apartments.
So all the studies say
that you should transition
to a place that isn't necessarily large,
so I printed off some listings
for studios.
But in the meantime,
until you find one you like,
we would love it if you stayed with us.
Kaylie, I don't know how to thank you.
Well, I wanted to talk to you
about all of this sooner.
But suddenly they wouldn't
let me in to see you.
It wasn't...
It wasn't that they
wouldn't let you in to see me.
I just had some things I needed
to figure out for myself.
I get it.
I'm your family.
The only thing that matters
is that you're here now.
(WHISPERING) I found it.
- What do you mean?
- You know.
It wasn't easy.
I tracked it down mostly
through second bidders,
people who lost at the auctions.
It was in storage, part of
an estate collection in Bremen.
It took me a year and a half
to get it into our warehouse
and it lasted less than a week.
It's about to ship out to a new buyer,
so we only have a few days,
but it should be enough.
A few days for what, Kaylie?
To keep our promise.
And kill it.
(DOG BARKING)
OK, guys, the couch can go there.
And those boxes are kitchen.
- Barn! Barn!
- Tim, we don't shoot the movers.
And as soon as I get my files
organized, you will have them.
(PHONE BUZZING)
Yes. Shoot.
Can I call you back?
Jeff, I am so sorry
I didn't return your call.
I've just been slammed.
It's a lot easier when you have a staff.
- Kaylie's under arrest.
- She's not here, buddy.
(TOY GUN FIRING) Sneak attack!
You are so dead!
Honey?
And this goes? OK, against the wall.
Watch the molding.
Thank you. OK. OK. It's fragile.
(KIDS CHATTERING)
- Hey, guys! Take it outside.
- But, Mom...
The alternative is moving boxes.
GIRL: Oh, come on. Come on.
So we'll talk soon. OK.
WOMAN: Thanks, guys. OK.
I'll be right out.
So you expanded the furniture order?
I don't know if I'm
loving this desk here.
Were you gonna tell me or just
wait till I saw the Visa bill?
Hold on.
I was hoping to smooth that over
with a three-piece vanity set
that is supposed to be here...
Is it not here?
(LAUGHING)
I get it. OK.
Do your office however you want.
- Thank you.
- MM-hm.
It's a bit ostentatious, though,
don't you think?
I'm confused,
because you wanted the antiques.
And I said I was fine with IKEA.
Yeah, I wanted to get a few
pieces to upgrade the place,
not turn it into a showroom.
Listen, we got a new home,
a new company,
so we get new furniture.
Makes sense.
Same old wife, though, right?
Well, I told you I was fine with IKEA.
- Kidding.
- I'm not IKEA.
(SIGHS) You sure you prefer this?
Our guest room is a lot nicer than this.
Yeah. I think it might be best.
My own space.
You promised me you'd never
forget what really happened.
You promised.
I was ten years old.
Well...
I'm doing it tomorrow night.
And... I could really,
really use your help.
Good night, Tim.
I feel like my scar is more noticeable
now than it was ten years ago.
Let me take a look.
I'm a professional.
(GASPS)
(KISSING) What scar?
(CHUCKLING) We're nowhere near done.
So?
You've only put together the bed.
That wasn't easy.
(KISSING CONTINUES)
(SIGHS)
(FOOT BANGING)
(GRUNTING)
Damn it.
Shit.
(DOG BARKING)
(GASPS, CHOKING)
No! No! No!
(SCREAMING) No! No! No!
It's OK. It's OK. It's OK.
(SOBBING)
(PANTING)
It's OK. It's OK.
It's just one of your night
terrors. It's OK. Shh...
Shh...
(BREATHING SLOWS)
(KNOCKING)
- Hey.
So I requisitioned you your own printer.
You don't have to share anymore.
- We'll take you off the network.
- OK.
Because I guess there were
some complaints about people
printing out their sales reports
and finding some really...
...graphic crime scene photos
from, uh...
...your computer.
I noticed you put in a transfer
order for the Lasser Glass.
- Yeah, as a repair.
- Oh.
I thought Warren said no repairs.
He changed his mind.
Got to be honest, I'm really
just waiting for an explanation
for the corpse print-outs.
I know things have been
strange at times.
And you know I'm dealing
with some dark stuff,
some parental stuff, with Tim out.
I'll never expect you to
understand that part of my life.
Just bear with me a day or two more.
Things will get back to normal.
I promise.
I don't usually get transfer orders
to third-party repair houses.
Oh, yeah, the buyer wants his guy
to look at it before it ships.
- But we both know you'd do it better.
- No argument there.
I'll take it there myself.
Babysit it every step of the way.
Better get some furni pads
if we're going to move her.
Hello again.
You must be hungry.
I hope this still hurts.
(INHALING QUIETLY)
You're all set.
(GASPING)
You all right?
I'm great.
The guys will wrap her up
for you in a bit.
Thank you, Warren.
I'll see you at home.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
My car is by the loading dock.
- Hello.
TIM: - Hey.
- Got a phone.
- Cool.
You just need to sign the order.
I don't feel good about the way
we left it last night.
Can we meet up somewhere and talk?
Of course.
Can you come by the house?
Sure. What's your address?
No. The house.
Yes, I have it in front of me.
I don't know, probably half an hour.
Does that work?
OK.
Speak then.
(INDISTINCT OVERLAPPING WHISPERS)
(RUSTLING)
(TOY GUN FIRING)
Oh, crap.
I'm gonna get you, you little brat!
(FIRING CONTINUES)
The answer is still no.
Oh, my God, Ally has one
and Maddie has one.
I'm the only kid
in my class without a phone.
That is terrible.
Thanks for nothing, Marie.
(LAUGHING) Oh!
I'm going to run out and get one
for you right now, daughter,
love of my life, fruit of my loins.
Well, I wish I'd been a pineapple.
Hey kids, do me a favor and don't ever
chew your nails like your father.
- It's gross.
KAYLIE: - Hey, Dad?
OK... He's Dad. I'm Marie.
Who was that lady in your office today?
Yeah, Dad, who was that lady
in your office today?
What lady?
I don't know. Just some lady.
I don't know.
(DOOR OPENING)
It looks so small.
- Go on, Dog.
- You named your dog, Dog?
No. He doesn't have a name.
Are you OK?
Oh, of course.
You haven't been here since...
Why don't you look around?
(CHAIN RATTLING)
KAYLIE: The house just sat on the market
while I was in the foster system.
Released to me when I turned 18.
I was the only homeowner in the freshman
dorms when I started school.
I'm thinking we should
try and sell it, though.
You know, after.
So will you help me with
something before you go?
How the hell did you expect
to get this thing in here yourself?
To be honest, I didn't.
I always thought it'd be both of us.
Over here for now.
OK.
(PANTING)
What's that?
Yacht anchor. Kill switch.
So, uh... (CLEARS THROAT)
...I understand if you
don't want to stay.
I accept that,
but I got to get started.
I'll stay for a little bit.
Excuse me.
(CAMERAS BEEPING)
(EXHALES) Hello.
My name is Kaylie Ann Russell.
I'm 23 years old.
I'm with my brother,
Timothy Alan Russell.
Alan, of course, after his father.
He's...
He's 21 years old.
It's 4:15pm on October 13th,
and we are at 2705 Hawthorne Way.
I'll begin by detailing my precautions
before I place and uncover the glass.
There are three cameras, each
on its own independent power circuit,
so if any anomalies occur,
there can be a lucid, objective record.
I have private land lines for today's
experiment, along with my cell phone.
And I will now ask
my brother for his phone,
so that I can control
all electronic devices.
I just got this, you know.
Thanks, Timbo.
This alarm is set to go off
every 45 minutes
to remind me to change
the tapes in the cameras.
This alarm is set to go off
hourly to remind us to eat.
And we're fully stocked
on water to prevent dehydration.
Now, as for the house itself...
each room is fitted
with its own thermostat,
from which data is collected by software
designed to track and record
temperature fluctuations in hospitals.
Any temperature changes greater
than five degrees in either direction
will set off an alarm.
A third precaution is also in place,
but I'll get into that
in a few more minutes.
So...
The purpose of today's experiment
is to prove that the object
behind me, the Lasser Glass,
is home to an observable,
predictable supernatural force.
There's no scientific equivalent
for the word "haunted,"
so we'll just say this object is
responsible for at least 45 deaths
in the four centuries
of its recorded existence...
Can I just stop you for a second?
Don't ever turn off a camera.
Sorry.
The origin of the
Lasser Glass is unknown,
so I can't provide a complete history,
but the trail starts in London in 1754.
Philip Lasser,
the 17th Earl of Leicester,
acquired the mirror and hung it
over his fireplace, and...
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Another precaution.
Hi, sweetie. How are you?
Well, I'm checking in,
uh, as requested.
- You all right?
- Everything's fine.
I know this is silly to ask,
but could you try to call on the hour?
It's about seven past.
- Uh... Sure.
- I'll talk to you in 53 minutes.
And I love you.
I'm expecting regular calls
from my fiancé, Michael Dumont.
I told him I'm nervous to be
spending time with my recently
un-incarcerated brother,
with instructions...
- to notify the authorities immediately
- Wow.
If I do not answer the phone.
- In the room.
- Nothing personal.
So, in 1755, Philip Lasser was
found in their grand fireplace.
Burned beyond recognition.
While his estate was dismantled
and scattered
throughout southern England,
one of the family's stewards claimed
to see Philip reflected in the mirror.
An allegation apparently taken
seriously enough to warrant
a Church investigation into the house.
The glass, thereafter known
as the Lasser Glass,
is sold in public auction in 1758.
The next known owner
is an American rail road tycoon,
named Robert Clancy, 1864.
Clancy apparently weighed
over 300 pounds.
In fact, while attending
university in Connecticut,
he was known as
the South Windham Whale.
He hung the glass
in his ballroom in Atlanta.
Later that year,
Robert Clancy is photographed
by a local newspaper and, uh...
Well, he's dropped a few pounds.
His obit was printed a few weeks later.
Doesn't list a cause of death.
Unfortunately,
he and his estate and the glass
are presumably destroyed in Sherman's
march to the ocean in 1865.
And after that, the glass is lost.
Until it resurfaces
in turn-of-the-century New England.
The next case of note
is Mary O'Connor, 1904.
She hung the mirror
in her private bathroom.
Two weeks later, her niece Beatrice
finds Mary dead in the bathtub.
Now, the official coroner's report lists
the cause of death as, get this...
...dehydration.
The woman died of thirst while soaking
in a full tub for three days.
The next case of note is Alice Carden
in Lake Geneva, Wisconsin, 1943.
Neighbors reported hearing screams
and loud bangs from the house.
The police found the children
drowned in a locked cistern.
Alice herself was in the nursery,
and both of her legs
are completely shattered.
Her left arm is broken in four places,
and six of her ribs are crushed.
In her right hand is a large hammer
she's been using to break her own bones.
They find her just as she's going
to work on her skull.
Her right arm, though,
is completely unharmed.
Because she needed it.
To wield the hammer.
Alice later says she believed she was
tucking the children into their beds
as she sealed them into the cistern.
She never recovers from her injuries.
And, oh, the family kept
several dogs at the farm,
including an Australian shepherd
for the children.
(DOG APPROACHING)
(TIMER BUZZING)
Let's eat.
Who exactly are you talking to?
On those tapes?
All the people who stared, pointed.
The kids at school who always found out.
I guess I'm talking to everyone
who ever called Dad a murderer.
Called you a murderer.
Look, Kaylie, we were just kids.
We made up a scary story
so we wouldn't have to accept the fact
that our father was a murderer. He was.
He was a sick man who
tortured and killed our...
You can call me crazy all you like.
But you're not allowed
to talk about him that way.
Tobin Capp, 1955.
Starved to death in his own bedroom.
The mirror was hung over his dresser.
He had a pet Dalmatian.
1965, California.
The mirror hangs in the lobby
of the Hill Trust Bank in San Diego.
A ten-year teller, Marcia Wicker,
locks her manager in the bank vault
and then chews
through a live power line.
- 1975, Marisol Chavez...
- Kaylie...
...dies in her bedroom of
hemorrhaging due to a miscarriage.
In her nightstand, they find
every single one of her teeth
in a little plastic bag
and a pair of bloody pliers.
- 2002...
- There's a huge difference
between causation and correlation.
I know the difference, thank you.
OK then. In 2001,
Mom and Dad bought that new couch.
Same year, Grandpa had a heart attack,
Robbie Schultz got hit by a car.
And our cat ran away.
How much of that
do you blame on that couch?
Can I get back to this now?
Sure, but let's get to it, Kaylie.
Let's talk about why we're really here.
(WHISPERS) Let's.
2002.
The Lasser Glass adorns
the home office of Alan Russell.
Software designer. Husband to Marie.
Father to Timothy and Kaylie.
Within two weeks of its arrival,
Marie suffers an intense
psychological breakdown
and is tortured and murdered
in the family home.
By whom?
By her husband.
So say the police reports.
And her husband was shot
to death by her own son.
Right in front of her daughter.
I intend to prove that none of
the people I've just described
were responsible for their actions.
Alan Russell was not a murderer.
He was a victim.
One of many, as it turns out.
Victims of the supernatural force
that resides in that mirror.
So why don't we just end it right now
and smash the goddamn thing?
You really don't remember, do you?
(BOTH YELLING)
Remember what?
Please, smash it, by all means.
Okay.
You know, I've learned a lot about what
happens to people when they can't...
...can't process something horrible.
The mind creates all kinds
of protections to help them cope.
And once that belief's taken root,
the mind takes random information
and forces it to support that narrative.
How many thousands of records
did you have to pore through
to find 12 or 13 that support your case?
Why did you put the stool down?
Because I'm trying to have
a conversation with you.
Uh-huh. Only one person
I know of was ever documented
trying to break the mirror.
Oliver Jeffries. 1971.
A teacher at Manhattan's
Duhame Academy,
where the mirror hung
in the central lecture hall.
One morning he reportedly ran
at the mirror with a fireplace poker,
shouting about how it needed
to be destroyed,
but he never struck a blow.
According to the students,
he stood there quietly
for almost a minute
before walking out
of the hall and into traffic.
It's clearly capable
of defending itself, and...
(WHISPERING)
...I think it just disarmed you.
You know why I didn't
smash the mirror, Kaylie?
Besides you getting fired or charged
with destruction of property?
It isn't mine to break.
No one can break your delusion for you.
You have to do it yourself.
Which leads me to my final precaution.
You're looking
at a 20-pound Danforth anchor.
Another 20 pounds added with barbells,
attached to a modified ballast rail
and a spring pin lock connected
to a mechanical kitchen timer.
No electricity, which is important,
and we're about ten seconds away.
If the timer is not manually
reset every 30 minutes,
that is, if no one
is here to stop it...
(TIMER TICKING)
(LOUD CLICK)
The mirror goes right there.
And the only thing to prevent that
from happening again
is our continued survival.
You know why we don't have to wait
for it to come out and play?
Because we've got
a loaded gun to its head.
And I expect it'll be eager
to defend itself.
(TIMER TICKING)
(SIGHS)
Aah!
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
FEMALE VOICE: (WHISPERING)
It doesn't hurt. It doesn't hurt.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON TV)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACH)
ALAN: Hey guys?
Come into my office for a second.
I thought I was pretty clear about you
guys not messing around in here.
We don't.
I don't like it in here.
All right, well, what is this?
We didn't do that.
OK.
You know, I can hear you guys at night,
messing around in here.
I was a kid once, too. I get it.
I know the move has been difficult.
This isn't gonna happen anymore.
OK?
And if you're messing around
with your mother's plants,
you're gonna cut that out, too.
TIM: You know what dead plants
are evidence of to me?
Problems with the water supply
and maybe a bad tank.
I seem to remember drinking
out of a Brita filter.
Oliver Jeffries,
dead plants in the classroom.
Tobin Capp,
dead plants in the bedroom.
Garden service at Hill Trust
Bank couldn't understand
why they had dead plants
all over the place.
Live plant.
(SCOFFS) Live plants in the living room.
Live plants, plants that have life.
- These are your rules, by the way.
- Give it time.
It always starts
with the low-hanging fruit.
It wasn't just the plants
it fed on, though.
There was another variable, too.
Dog! (WHISTLES)
Sorry, Dog.
(TIMER BUZZING)
Hydrate.
(DOG WHIMPERING)
- Come on, boy.
- Come on, Mason. Go fetch.
- Come on. Mason.
- Go fetch.
Chase the stick.
Come on. Go. Go.
(SIGHS)
I mean, the whole reason
I got this thing
was because you were freaked out
that we weren't safe.
Said you saw somebody down here.
Yeah, but that doesn't
make me feel safer.
Quite the opposite, actually.
(ALAN SIGHS)
OK, I will lock it up, unloaded,
where I'm sure it'll come in very handy
in the case of an emergency.
Grotesque cow.
What did you just say to me?
I didn't say anything.
(INDISTINCT VOICES WHISPERING)
(MASON BARKING)
(GROWLS)
Ow! Jesus!
Alan!
(RATTLING DOOR)
ALAN: I'm working!
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
(ALAN MUTTERING)
Who are you talking to?
Were you gonna do something
about the damn barking?
There's something wrong
with the dog, Alan. He bit me.
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
(SIGHS)
You know, you are just
lost in your own world in here.
I'm not lost in my own world!
I'm working!
MARIE: I know that.
I've supported that.
This isn't you working hard.
ALAN: When you start your own
business, it's all on you.
- I know that, Alan!
- I have to do this!
ALAN: Guys. Listen, you got
to do me a special favor today.
I have a golf session with a client.
And I'm gonna need you
to stay out of my office. OK?
OK, Dad.
All right. I love you guys.
(WHIMPERING, BARKING)
(SIGHS)
Fine. You wanna go in, you're going in.
Go shit on the CEO's carpet.
(MASON WHIMPERING)
Shit.
Why can't we let him out?
Mom says Mason's grounded.
(DOOR OPENS)
Hey, squirts.
Why are you, uh...?
We have got to do something
about that damn dog.
(SIGHS) A hello would be nice.
He was a wrecking ball all day.
I had to lock him in your office.
Well, tether him up.
Where is he?
Well, there's the problem.
You're remembering it wrong.
I promise.
I'm not remembering it wrong.
- You are, though. Mason...
- Alice Carden's Australian shepherd,
Tobin Capp's Dalmatian,
the pets were never found. None of them.
Do you remember Mason toward the end?
Vomiting, accidents all over the house.
My therapist had me
research Parvo virus.
- Oh, my God.
- It's a fatal canine illness,
flagged by nausea, aggression,
infected urine and stool,
which, incidentally, can kill plants.
Mason was sick.
(RAPID PANTING)
All right, I'll take him
to the vet tomorrow.
ALAN: Bad news.
I don't think we're both coming home.
Mom, where's Mason?
Uh, he's grounded.
Are you saying you remember
it happening that way?
- Are you really saying that?
- Why not?
You're wrong.
I saw Mom lock him in the office
and I sat outside that door all day,
and nobody went in or out.
Have you ever heard of the fuzzy trace
theory of human psychology?
No. But I'm gonna guess you have.
I'm the star
of a psychiatric article about it.
Our brains actually encode
information as fuzzy traces.
More like a general meaning
than an exact record.
- This is horseshit, Tim.
- Adults are more likely
to combine those traces
into false memories.
You saw Mom put the dog
in the office on a number of occasions.
My God, what did they do to you?
Way before Dad forbade anyone
else from going in the office.
Those traces fused
with your memory of that day.
- I feel sorry for you.
- OK, what's more likely?
That you're misremembering events
from 11 years ago,
or that the mirror eats dogs?
Oh, look! It's Dog!
Give it some time.
(SWITCHING VIDEO TAPES)
A little time.
ALAN: There's nothing going
on here, woman! You're really losing it!
MARIE: I can hear you talking
to someone, and it sounds like a woman.
ALAN: - You know what, you're crazy!
MARIE: - I'm not crazy!
I can hear you talking to someone.
ALAN: I mean, listen to yourself!
"I can hear you through the door."
MARIE: Why would I make this up?
I'm not crazy!
ALAN: The water supply is poisoned?
And we got a burglar?
You're losing your mind.
I'm sorry that we woke you up.
Are you and Daddy fighting because
of the woman in the office?
You got to remember that woman.
You saw her too.
I convinced myself
I saw a lot of things.
But what did we really see?
Mom yelling at Dad
in the middle of the night.
Mom said she heard voices, but it was
probably just Dad on the phone.
(TIMER BUZZING)
Doesn't explain the woman
I saw through the window.
But when did you see her?
The first time?
We were playing in the yard.
Was Mom at home?
Mom was always home.
Are you sure about that?
Because I'm not.
- Oh, shit.
- Shit.
Get back. Get back.
(TYPING)
He was having an affair,
saint that he was.
It was a bad marriage.
Look how it ended up.
- No.
- Our father was a cheater,
- and it drove our mother crazy.
- Stop it.
He snapped and he killed her.
He was gonna do the same to us.
Oh, yeah. A bad marriage.
That explains how Mom had no teeth,
no hair, no mind left,
by the time she died.
Yeah, a bad marriage.
That explains those other people we both
saw in the house that last night.
He was withdrawn, secretive.
All signs of an affair.
I had access to all
of Mom and Dad's stuff.
While you were
getting brainwashed, I looked.
Not one credit card receipt,
phone call, flower order.
Nothing to suggest an affair.
He was smart enough
not to leave a trail.
(DOG BARKING) Quiet!
I talked to his friends and Co-workers.
If there was another woman,
she was a ghost.
Yeah, I agree, he was withdrawn,
secretive, suspicious, sure.
All signs of an affair, fine.
I'm not saying he wasn't seduced.
It's a matter of what seduced him.
(DOG WHIMPERING)
And things have been happening
in here while we argue, you know.
You know the temperature
in here has risen by three degrees?
- Three degrees.
- Two people in a small space,
lights burning, electrical equipment...
Phone lines are probably down
by now. Why don't you check?
OK, then. Let's have a look.
Dial tone.
Static?
Look, Kaylie.
You can deal with this. I did it.
You want to redeem the family name?
You don't need to do it for Mom and Dad.
You only need to do it for yourself.
Oh...
They did a bang-up job
on you in there, didn't they?
You were perfectly normal
when they locked you up.
You had to go bat-shit to get out.
(DOG WHIMPERING, BARKING)
Mason, stop your goddamn whining!
You know what? That's it. I'm done.
I know I'm supposed
to wait around for you
to find your own
way out of this.
But I'm not gonna stand
here and let you torture a dog.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Listen to it!
Stop it! Stop it.
(SLAMS CAGE DOOR)
(BARKING)
No! No! Wait!
What?
- You didn't need to do that.
- Oh, yes, I did, Kaylie. You're sick.
Nothing you said would
happen tonight has happened.
The plants are still alive,
the mirror is just a mirror.
The only thing threatening
that dog was you!
And it's not your fault.
Like it wasn't my fault.
I had help, and you were alone.
These kinds of problems
are hard to overcome,
but they're nothing to be ashamed of.
They run in our family.
Kaylie, I'm sorry.
Look...
Let's get out of here.
Go some place else and
talk about how to move on.
(VOICE BREAKING)
Where can we go?
Oh, Kaylie...
Where?
Let's go turn off those cameras,
disarm that anchor...
...and we can go
anywhere you want.
Go talk to your fiancé, maybe.
He'll want to help. You know he will.
Kaylie?
(BREATH TREMBLING)
There it is.
Ha!
Yes.
Yes!
Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes!
I'm now reviewing the tape
of the last few minutes.
TIM: He was having an affair,
saint that he was.
It was a bad marriage.
Look how it ended up.
Our father was a cheater,
and it drove our mother crazy.
- Stop it.
- He snapped and he killed her.
- He was gonna do the same to us.
- Yeah, a bad marriage.
That explains how Mom had
no teeth, no hair, no mind left,
by the time she died.
Yeah, a bad marriage.
That explains those other people we
both saw in the house that last night.
I don't remember doing that.
Do you? You don't.
The temperature in the room has
increased another two degrees
to 78 degrees Fahrenheit...
- but the alarms didn't go off...
- My phone.
We've lost the ficus
and the blooming plants.
- My phone.
- Which tells me that the dog
provided at least enough energy
to bait the shark.
I'd better call the doctor.
Tim. If you're gonna make a phone call,
you need to do it outside its radius
of influence.
Otherwise there's no way of knowing
who you're really talking to.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello? Hi. Yeah.
Everything's fine now.
I'm sorry about earlier.
I'll talk to you in an hour.
50/50 that was even him.
We need to get out
of this room for a while.
It must've gotten more
from the dog than I guessed.
Its radius of influence
appears to be... 30 feet...
...which means we're still good
to go in the kitchen,
laundry room, garage, master bedroom,
and the yard, front and back.
Oh, but I doubt for very long.
Tim?
Tim!
VOICE RECORDING: Your call
cannot be completed as dialed.
Your call cannot be
completed as dialed.
Please check the number and dial again.
Your call cannot be completed as dialed.
(PANTING)
KAYLIE: Tim.
Tim.
How did I get back in here?
What do you mean?
You walked over here and you sat down.
- I was outside.
- No, you weren't.
Did you think you were?
Would you mind saying that on camera?
(PANTING)
Hey. Hey!
It's because you're still here
that I know we're gonna win.
Do you hear me?
Do you understand?
(VACUUM CLEANER WHIRRING)
(VIDEO GAMES BEEPING)
(THUMPING)
(VACUUM CLEANER CONTINUES)
When's Daddy coming home?
I don't know.
You don't know
when Daddy's coming home?
I don't know where he is.
I know where he says he is.
Kaylie.
Tell me more about the woman
in the office.
I haven't seen her.
I have.
(MOUTHING)
(EXHALES)
When?
Last night.
She wasn't in the office.
She was on the stairs.
What was she doing?
I didn't look.
I was scared.
But I think she went back in the office.
I think she lives there.
You two go upstairs and play.
(HINGES CREAKING)
(SNIFFLES)
(YELLS)
(SNIFFLING)
(YELLING)
(LOUD WHOOSHING)
(FAINT WHISPERING)
(WHIMPERS)
(WHISPERING INCREASES)
(MARIE SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
Mom?
Mom!
(MARIE WHIMPERING)
Tim!
Mom!
(YELLING)
Go! Go, Tim!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(BOTH PANTING)
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
Mommy, stop!
Please stop, Mommy!
(POUNDING CONTINUES)
Marie?
Hey! Hey!
Baby?
Sweetheart, you're bleeding.
Hey, hey, hey!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(DOOR CLICKS)
(SOBS)
(PANTING) Sweetheart,
you gotta go back in your room.
But, Mommy...
Your mother's fine.
She's going to be all right.
Just, please, go back inside.
Shut the door, OK, baby?
Fuck.
(DIALING)
Yeah, I have an emergency with my wife.
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
OVERLAPPING VOICES: Everything is fine.
- Is Mommy OK?
- Go to bed.
(CHAIN JINGLING)
(CRYING)
(DISTANT POUNDING)
Tim?
Tim.
Snap out of it!
(TIMER BUZZING) Are you here?
Are you here with me?
Tim?
Guys, your mother is very, very sick.
And, uh, she's gonna need to stay
in bed for a while, to rest up.
So she can get better.
But we don't want you two bothering her.
We?
So, Champ, Princess...
...we're gonna have
to stay clear of that room.
Is that understood?
What does she have?
Now... (CLEARS THROAT)
...you are welcome to...
...hang out in here
and play video games.
I thought you said
we weren't allowed in here.
(TIMER BUZZING)
Eat.
Come on, I need your help.
KAYLIE: Tim!
Tim, snap out of it!
(ECHOING) Tim!
(FOOTSTEPS)
Is that for Mom?
Tim?
Nice.
(GLASS SPLINTERING)
(GASPS)
(BREATH SHUDDERING)
(SPITTING)
(GAGGING)
(WHIMPERING)
(GASPS)
TIM: Kaylie?
(EXHALES)
Maybe we should stay together.
(EXCLAIMING) She still loves me!
(MUFFLED THUMPING)
I'm hungry, Kaylie.
(SIGHS)
You need to go grocery shopping, Dad.
What's that, Princess?
- Food.
- That's on my list.
The TV is out.
What's that, Princess?
We need to call a doctor for Mom.
That's on my list.
(LOW RUMBLING)
(HUFFS)
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
This is stupid.
I'm gonna tell her we're out of food.
- But Dad said...
- I don't care what Dad said.
(TAKING DEEP BREATH)
(HINGES CREAKING)
Mom?
(GASPS, SHRIEKS)
(GUTTURAL MOANING)
(SHRIEKING)
KAYLIE: She needs a doctor!
You told me she was sick,
but she's not...
You know what your problem is?
You don't listen!
I told you not to go
into our room, didn't I?
What do you do? You disobey me.
Why?
You disobeyed me,
so now you get grounded.
You and your snot-nosed
little brother over there
are not to step foot outside
of this house.
Now, get out of here.
KAYLIE: OK. Thank you.
Bye.
TIM: What did the doctor say?
He said to have our father call.
Like the last one.
Exactly like the last one.
Same voice.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hi, Bob.
BOB: I'm really sorry to hear that.
I hope she gets better soon.
ALAN: Thanks for that, Bob.
You know what? I'm just sorry
she brought you all the way over here.
I mean, she's... you know,
using her mother's illness to act out.
Wait till she starts driving.
This is nothing.
Well, so sorry to bother you.
I hope Marie is up and about soon.
Thank you.
Hey, you know what?
Give me a ring next week
and we'll play
the front nine at Arrowhead.
Great. We'll do it.
- See ya.
- Take care.
KAYLIE: Timbo.
We're gonna have
to get really, really brave.
(TIMER TICKING)
(PANTING)
Very clever.
Tim!
(TIMER BUZZING)
(TIMER CLATTERING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(TOY GUN FIRING)
(EXHALES)
(LAMP BUZZING)
Kaylie?
And we've lost electric.
Predictable.
A dead plant.
It isn't real.
Daddy?
(SLOW TYPING)
Could you fix the lights?
(TIM SCREAMING)
(HISSING)
(PANTING)
Nice tricks.
(GASPS)
MICHAEL'S VOICE: Kaylie...
(MICHAEL GASPS)
Oh, my God.
Do you see him?
(PANTING)
(KAYLIE SNIFFLES)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
MICHAEL: Just checking in,
seeing how everything's going.
I'm fine.
OK, I guess I'll talk to you
in an hour. Enjoyed the chat.
That's a trick.
I didn't kill him. I couldn't have.
The plate, it wasn't real.
I didn't kill him
because the plate wasn't real!
(SOBBING)
(PHONE CLATTERING)
Michael.
What did I do?
TIM: Come on.
We're getting out of here.
Come on, let's go.
Hello?
I need police and an ambulance.
2705 Hawthorne.
OK, OK.
Help is coming. They'll be here.
We'll straighten all this out.
Kaylie, we're OK. We're OK.
Michael, Michael, Michael.
When was the last time
you reset the kitchen timer?
- I don't know.
- Your plan was solid.
We don't have to do anything.
All we have to do
is just sit here and wait.
No more than half an hour.
Your kill switch.
- You called for help?
- Yeah.
We're done. It's over.
We get to stand here
and watch that thing die.
(BREATH SHUDDERING)
It's a trick to get us back inside.
What if this is a trick
to keep us standing there?
- I called for help.
- Call again.
MAN: 911. What's your emergency?
Yeah, hi, I just called.
2705 Hawthorne.
You're going to have to
have your father call.
The doctor will be there tomorrow.
(DISTORTED) Timbo...
KAYLIE: No!
(PHONE CRUNCHES)
What do we do?
We could do nothing. Just wait.
And watch ourselves get...
We're gonna have
to get really, really brave.
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
He looked at the mirror
and took out a gun.
We're gonna have to smash it.
(WHISPERING) That's not real.
ALAN'S VOICE: I thought I told
you not to play around in here.
It's not real.
(BOTH YELLING)
(WHIMPERING)
Shh!
(GLASS CRUNCHING)
(CHAIN RATTLING)
Kaylie?
(GASPS)
Is he gone?
He was never here.
It just herded us upstairs.
We made the right call outside.
It's really trying to keep us away.
It'll try harder.
We have to get downstairs
- before that anchor swings.
- You have to make sure he's gone first.
He's gone. I promise.
See, he's...
(SHRIEKS)
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
(BOTH WHIMPERING)
(POUNDING CONTINUES)
(POUNDING CEASES)
We've got to get downstairs.
She's not gone.
- I'm gonna open the door.
- No!
I'm gonna open the door.
If she's not gone...
...I want you to run
right down the stairs.
- What are you gonna do?
- Don't worry about that. Just run.
You ready?
I'm gonna open the door.
You run right down the stairs.
You trust me, right?
I trust you.
One... I love you.
Two... Straight for the stairs.
Three.
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH SHRIEK)
(GROANING)
(PANTING)
(WHISPERING) It's not real.
Just a trick.
You're gonna arrest me, Timbo?
(LOUD GUNSHOT)
Timbo?
Tim!
(FAINT WHISPERING)
(VOICE SHAKY) Tim?
(MOUTHING)
(SCREAMS)
(CRYING) Mommy, please, no.
(SCREAMING)
(GASPING, COUGHING)
(WHISPERING) Kaylie?
Kaylie?
(GUNSHOT)
Mommy!
Come on, Tim!
(SCREAMS)
(GASPING SOFTLY)
(INDISTINCT WHISPERS OVERLAPPING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
It won't let us.
ALAN: I thought I told you
not to play around in here.
No.
This isn't you.
It is me.
(WHISPERS ECHOING)
I've met my demons,
and they are many.
WHISPERING VOICE: I've seen...
I've seen the devil...
WHISPERING VOICE: And he is...
...and he is me.
(YELLING)
Dad!
Let her go!
(GASPING)
Run.
No! No!
Daddy!
(SOBBING)
Come on.
(BOTH WHIMPERING)
(TIMER BUZZING LOUDLY)
This isn't real! This isn't real!
This isn't real!
(BUZZING FADES)
Kaylie!
TIM: (DIS TANT) Kaylie!
(SNIFFLING)
MARIE: Kaylie.
Mommy?
(TICKING)
(WET THUDDING)
(FAINT GURGLING)
(KAYLIE GAGGING)
KAYLIE: Tim. Tim look at me.
I want you to promise me,
that when we're big and we're strong,
we will make this right.
(DISTANT SIRENS APPROACHING)
We have to kill that thing.
For Mom and Dad.
I promise.
(STAMMERING) Kaylie?
Kaylie?
Kaylie! Kaylie! Kaylie!
(SIRENS GROWING LOUDER)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
He called it in?
Yeah, he called 911,
and then he did this.
Where are you taking me?
No, it wasn't my fault!
- It was the mirror!
- Tim!
Wait! Stop! It wasn't me!
It wasn't me. It was the mirror!
It was the mirror!
Please! Please!
You have to believe me!
It was the mirror!
Please!
Hey! Hey!
KAYLIE: Don't forget!
Don't forget our promise!
Don't forget.
(SIREN WAILING)
(WHIMPERING)
(RADIO CHATTER FADES)
(HEART BEATING)