During the war, I captured 10
North Koreans with my bare hands.
Whatever.
You're the biggest coward
in the world!
What? How dare you to talk like
that to your mighty husband!
- Mighty husband? That's funny!
- What's wrong with you?
- Are you gonna hit me? Hit me!
- Shut up!
C'mon, hit me!
I'm really gonna hit you!
Are you thinking
about Soon-duk, again?
Why do you always
bring her up?
Why do you get so sensitive
whenever I talk about her?
- Stop talking about her!
- Soon-duk!
- Shut up!
- I said shut up!
- Soon-duk!
- Shut up!
- Shut up!!
- Soon-duk!
Cops are searching for their car.
We should hear something back soon.
- Please find the car
- we'll try
Don't worry. They'll be fine.
You don't have to.. Thank you.
The sky is like a garden of stars.
Oh, dear.
It's beautiful.
Mr. ROH, what do your children do?
My children?
This is kinda embarassing but...
I'm...
still a bachelor.
An innocent bachelor..
- Shut up!
- Soon-duk!
- Shut up!!
- I said shut up!
- Soon-duk!
Tell me. How far did
you go with her?
All the way!
And we did it anywhere
at anytime!
Some days, we did 3 times a day!
I can't sleep.
- You should be embrassed
- Shut up!
Mr. GOH, have you
ever been to a zoo?
- A zoo?
- Yes.
I can't forget that one time when
my mom took me to a zoo.
I begged her to take me there
I was so excited.
It was my first
visit to a zoo.
I saw tigers, elephants,
deer, monkeys, seal and..
What's that bird
with big eyes that
stares like this?
An eagle?
No. The one that sits
like this on a tree.
An owl.
No, it's..
- Korean wood owl.
- No, that that one
No, it's 'something-op' owl..
Something-op? 'Top?' 'Cop?’
No, not 'cop..' 'Hop.. Sop..'
Oh! Sop owl!
- Scops owl.
- No, sop owl.
It's scops owl. The one with sullen
face that sits on a tree like this.
It's scops owl?
Anyway, it was really cool
seeing a scops owl.
Among all the animals,
I liked leopards the best.
There was
a motherless baby leopard..
and he looked so sad.
After looking around for a while,
I told my mom
I wanted some ice cream.
She told me to stay where I was
and went to get some ice cream.
I waited..
for hours and hours..
But, even when it started to
get dark, she didn't come back.
I looked for her everywhere,
but I couldn't find her.
I was so scared, I wanted to cry.
But I didn't.
Finally, I realized
she wasn't coming back.
You don't know
how much I regretted
asking her to
buy me some ice cream.
I didn't really have to eat it.
I was 7 then.
Since that day, I've
forgotten what she looks like.
Maybe it's because I'm dumb.
I can't remember at all.
I wish I had a picture of her.
That's all we talked
about in orphanage.
We had some weird kids there.
There was one called Booger.
He picked his nose everyday and he
stuck his boogers everywhere.
Sometimes his nose bled, too.
One day, he started to collect
his boogers in a small jar.
And after 7 years, the jar filled.
He proudly carried it in his arms
as he walked out of the orphanage.
All his boogers in thatjar..
That's why we called him Booger.
Thank you for your hospitality.
Thank you, again.
- Were we too loud last night?
- Yes.
No. We slept very well.
Stay on that road and
it'll lead you to the village.
There, you can catch a bus to
Seoul or make a phone call.
And take this.
No, we can't accept..
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Bye.
From the back seat,
he took his bandage and..
- I'm worried.
- About what?
About Hwa-jung?
Don't worry about her.
- She doesn't like you anymore.
- Really? That's nice.
- But I'm not talking about her.
- Then, the beauty salon girl?
No. A new one
She's a bartender
and she's incredible.
she's...
I think you're incredible.
She lives like a nameless fish
at the bottom of the ocean
Then one day,
she receives a phone call.
No. I think 'a letter' works
better than 'a phone call.'
- 'A letter' is better!
- Right.
and it zooms in like this..
As she takes her last breath
in the midst of snowy mountain,
the dying woman
dreams a fading dream.
One fine summer day
a man is watering
his garden with a hose.
Children play gaily underneath
the cool water stream.
From the porch, she watches him
playing with the children,
with a gentle smile on her lips.
As her spirit prepares herself to
leave her cold body..
she smiles for the last time.
The smile of..
sweet dreams.
- How is it?
- Hot
- How does it taste
- Good
This is the only thing
I can cook really well.
You hold your chopsticks funny.
- I'm fine like this.
- But it looks too weird.
You gotta hold it like this..
Like this. You try it.
No. Don't cross them.
They gotta be parallel.
Forget it. I like my way better
I think it's weird if a writer
can't even hold his chopsticks right.
Don't worry about it. Just eat.
You wanna eat pizza tomorrow?
Do you like pizza?
No. Let's eat noodles.
Ok
Are you surprised to
see a card on your wall?
Today is my birthday.
I'm super excited since
it's my first birthday here.
Tonight, I'm throwing a birthday
party at the coffee shop
I hope you'll come.
Birthday party?
Good day, sir?
Nothing special.
You're gonna propose to
your girlfriend tonight?
Me? No.
It's obvious!
Look, you even got
champagne and flowers!
It's not what you think.
- C'mon. Don't lie.
- Are you embarrassed?
We can tell.
- It's ok.
- Shut up!
Pull up over there.
There?
7,900 won, please.
What?
You picked up 2 other customers
along the way and took a detour.
I'm gonna report you in.
What's your cab number?
Have some conscience!
How can you charge me
for the full price?
Take 6,000 won
I didn't take a long detour.
Wait!
The bouquet!
- I hope you like it.
- Thank you so much.
What is it?
- So pretty!
- It's so cute!
Mr. GOH, you didn't
bring a gift?
Gift?
I got something and..
Let me guess. A poem!
When I retired from teaching,
he recited a poem for me.
How romantic!
That's so cool!
gas 23,000 won
groceries 11,000 won
Title.. 'Zoo'.. by GOH Seon-guk.
Going to a zoo
on a warm spring day
The lion,
king of all animals..
and tigers..
and elephants..
and giraffes..
and donkeys..
and..
orangutans..
chimpanzees...
and panda bears..
and deer are..
locked up..
in a small cage..
with countless scratches.
In front of a leopard's cage,
a little girl waits for her mother
eating her ice cream.
A motherless leopard
steadily gazes at her.
Soon a leopard and
the girl become friends.
A leopard, who lost his mother
in a vast prairie of Africa,
consoles the little girl.
In the darkness of the night,
in an empty cage,
the two motherless souls
welcome the long sleep
of their mothers' wombs,
Then, her mother's
voice awakens them.
As the girl bids farewell
to her dear leopard, with her
hand in her mother's hand,
an escaped scops owl flies
over her head
towards a distance sky.
Thank you.
That was beautiful.
ﬂ Kiss me, kiss me much,ﬁ
E in the stillness of the night,
when the lilacs fade and fallﬁ
ﬂ Kiss me, kiss me muchﬁ
ﬂ Please bring me the sweet
smell of lilacﬁ
ﬂ Kiss me, kiss me much,
my sweet little girlﬁ
you're my lonely St. Mariaﬁ
ﬂ Kiss me, kiss me much,ﬁ
E in the stillness of the night,
when the lilacs fade and fallﬁ
ﬂ Kiss me, kiss me muchﬁ
ﬂ Please bring me the sweet
smell of lilacﬁ
Hwa-jung, it's me.
What are you two
doing in my house?
Mr. GOH, I was just giving Hee-gu
some advices on his troubles.
I thought you a decent boy, but..
- Teacher, it's not what you think.
- No. I understand.
It's natural for young kids like
you to like each other. But! why here?
Mr. GOH, it's not what you think.
Hee-gu likes someone else.
Not you?
How many girls?
You must be pretty good, huh?
Tell me. Who else?
- Do you really want to know?
- Yes.
Hee-gu likes..
you.
Done!
- It's finished!
- What's finished?
What? What?
- Where d'you come from?
- Sorry
- You scared me
- But, what's finished?
- Nothing. What do you want?
- Me?
I need you to come with me.
Hee-gu, you have to stay still.
Why do you think
they put this on you?
- You have to rest.
- Where is my teacher?
He said he'll come.
Give him a few minutes.
He's really angry, right?
No. He worried about you so much.
Don't worry.
Is this ok?
Teacher..
How are you?
I have to stay here for about 2
months, but I'll be fine.
You said you have
something to tell him.
Don't worry about me.
I'll be back at work in no time.
You know what?
I don't want to
coming back to work.
You love me?
You make me wanna puke!
You dirty bastard!
Mr. GOH..
- I'm going.
- But..
- What's wrong with you?
- Hee-gu...
You should feel grateful for
being loved. No matter what.
- You...
- Mr. GOH, say something.
Mr. GOH..
Wait! Can I talk to you?
I have nothing to say about him.
I feel gross.
- Please don't do this.
- Do what?
You're his teacher.
Can't you just embrace
your student as a teacher?
Just this once...
I'm not his teacher anymore.
Finished?
Mr. GOH!
Why do you have to be so cruel?
Go back and tell him you're sorry.
Why should I?
And stop telling me what to do.
Giving me a story doesn't give
you any right to butt into my life!
Besides, I don't need that crappy
story, anyway. I don't need..
You're writing that into a novel?
No.. I mean..
Did you lie about
Mr. SHIM's illness?
- No.. It's..
- Was it all lie?
How can you do this to me?
I really believed you
but you lied about everything!
Why?
Fine, I lied! I lived my whole
life lying to everyone!
But, you're no better than I am.
All you do is pour coffee and
seduce men. Dumb and vulgar..
Is that what you think of me?
Is that really
what you think of me?
I'm not as terrible
as you think I am.
Did you know next week is the
49th Day of your father's death?
No. And I don't
really care to know.
You should forgive you father.
He wasn't as a good father
or a good husband
as your portrayal of him
in your book.
But I still like him
as who he was.
After how he hurt you?
I lied to you
about something.
Do you want to know what?
What?
I told you
your grandpa was a pimp, right?
And I told you your father slept with
a girl who worked for grandpa.
I know. I don't wanna hear it again
Well, that girl was...
me.
When I was 13,
I was sold by my father
for his gambling debt.
When I first got there,
no one was nice to me.
Even the ornamental hairpin
which my mom gave me
was taken away from me.
I worked all day long.
It was hard living but
I was grateful for not starving.
When everyone went to bed, I would
sit by the kitchen fireplace and
think about my mom and cry.
That's when I met your father.
He was very compassionate
and kind.
He was the only one
who was nice to me.
After a year, I was sold
to another household.
Whenever life got too difficult,
I thought of your father.
Then in Masan,
I met your father again.
It was he
who finally freed me
from all the debt.
So, how can I ever forget him?
Oh, I have something for you
Before he passed away,
he gave that to me.
So I could live rest
of my life comfortably.
But, I don't need it.
I'm old and I have no use for
all that money. It's yours.
Think of it as your
father's last gift.
There's one more...
This..
Lately I've been seeing
your father in my dreams
and I think it's time
for me to go join him.
When you meet
a girl you love,
give this
ornamental hairpin to her
It's a present from me.
Mom,
stop talking non-sense.
You're not gonna die.
You know..
when I see your father again,
even if he has...
another new wife,
I'd very much like to
live with him again.
You want some pizza?
No, I gotta act more natural..
You like pizza, right?
- Pizza for you!
- Thank you!
- Thank you, Mr. GOH!
- You know how I think about you.
Mr. GOH, thank you!
Thank you, thank you!
Hwa-jung.
huh?
I'm sorry for
not saying 'goodbye'.
I appreciate
all your kindness.
Goodbye. Hwa-jung.
Hi. What brings
you here at this hour?
Where is Hwa-jung?
She's gone.
You didn't see her?
- To where?
- To Namwon. Why?
It's just...
She didn't clean up the room
before she left.
But, anyways..
Waiting at the Zoo
When the warm spring breeze starts
to blow in Serengeti Park,
all the wild animals
begin to emerge
from their winter hideouts.
Winter in Africa doesn't get too
cold. However, to all animals,
there's nothing more delightful than
a tickle of warm spring breeze.
With arrival of spring,
animals start their search for
their partners.
The mating season
starts in full swing.
This massive male hippopotamus
have found his female partner.
Giraffes, known as the gentlemen
of Serengeti, are not exceptions.
It's delightful to see greetings
from baby giraffes.
Even an orangutan, the lord of the
jungle, has found his female partner.
This is the season of love
for all animals.
However,
there are always exceptions.
Leopards don't have specific
mating season.
This lonely leopard is Amur
Leopard.
Unlike other African animals,
who travel and live in groups,
he takes pleasure in solitude.
He also wants a partner, but
he's not ready for one, yet.
What are you doing here?
- I can't go through with this.
- What?
You only got 30 min.
till the wedding!
Did you..?
I didn't know at first
but more I see her
I want to be with her.
You'll forget her
when you get married.
When you don't see her
you'll forget her.
But I can't not see her.
Who is she?
Jin-sook..
She's my wife's sister.
You understand me, right?
You're a piece of shit!
You don't deserve to love anyone!
Get your hands off me!
You don't deserve to be in love!
Do whatever you want!
Love may come easy to you,
but if you can't keep it,
it's meaningless.
What the hell do you
know about love?
You've never been
in love your self
I know.
I know the feeling
of not being able
to sleep at night and
spending the whole day
doing nothing because..
because I can't stop
thinking about her.
I know now.
You fell in love.
1, 2, 1, 2, Good! Good!
Hello.
How's your leg?
Good
This is my boyfriend.
How do you do?
You guys look good together.
How's Hwa-jung?
Good..
- Hi
- Hello
Waiting at the Zoo
- Hwa-jung
- Huh
- Another delivery.
- Again?
- Yeah
- To where?
Kwanghanroo, near the gazebo.
I don't know why anyone would
order coffee from there.
That's ok. I'll go.
- Bye
Pretty cool, huh?
Hundreds of years ago, on
a fine spring day like today,
Mongryong sees
Chunhyang on this swing
and fall in love with her.
They endure much
suffering and pain,
but they let it blossom.
My heart aches just thinking
about them.
Doesn't yours?
Blossom what?
Their love!
Mongryong sees Chunhyang
from that gazebo over there.
The gazebo is called Kwanghanroo.
Shall we go over there?
I'm here
but nobody ordered coffee.
Alright.
I'm going back.
You look
just like someone I know.
Except for the bear.
Hwa-jung, it's me. GOH Seon-guk.
I ordered the coffee.
Mr. GOH?
What are you doing here?
And what's up with your beard?
Well.. I got lazy
and didn't want to shave..
I was bored and
just came out to
get some fresh air..
What's that? Wasn't the mole on
the other side?
Huh?
I put it on this side,
today. It's removable.
Depending on my mood, I put
it on different spots.
I see.
Are you...
Still really mad at me?
No. It's ok now.
I'm thinking
about starting a new novel..
and can we write it together?
Like the last time?
Your name will be on the cover.
If you don't want to, then it's ok.
Oh...
This is for you.
What is it?
My mom got this from her mother and
she wants me to
give it to you.
Are.. you..
proposing to me?
Well..
It's not.. I mean..
I went to see my mom and..
since I don't have a girlfriend..
you know I don't have
women at all...
I don't know any women and..
We're close,
$0..
What are you watching?
That man
is about to propose to her.
That's so romantic!
That man is about to
propose to that woman.
Even a pizza is too big
to order when you're alone.
Should we go somewhere else?
Well..
You can do it!
He said, you can do it!
He said, you can do it.
To be honest with you,
well..
Honestly...
I didn't think much of you
when we first met.
But, more I got to know you..
I became...
Do your best!
Till the end!
He said, do your best
till the end!
You can do it!
You can do it!...
I like..
I like you.
What?
I can't hear you.
I really like you.
And I can't live without you.
Me, too.
I need you
And I can't live
without you, either.
Ah.. even after hundreds of years,
the spring breeze of Choson Dynasty
is still blowing.