Want a room? Yes
A deluxe room for two
Please give us two seperate rooms
Two rooms, yes of course
Enjoy
The moment when we strike
you leave first, alright
We have someone seated at this table already
Would you mind...
I want to sit here for the fireworks
This Inn is for everybody
That is alright
I would like a new friend
I don't need friends
I have this whole Inn for tonight
But...
I've been following that tribe of merchants for a long time
Don't you dare touch them
Since I have the chance to meet Qinglong today
I, the Judge of the Desert, must see how great he is
Before it goes down, I will beat you
Go
Are you alright
Yes
No problem
Before this bowl stops spinning
I will beat you...
as well
Don't move
Qinglong
Draw your sword
I have no wish to fight you
But I will tell you this
They have a thousand taels of gold
They may win in numbers
But we can work together
Here is the map to the post
Let an arrow be our signal
to attack
How will we split it
I don't want any of it
I want something else from them
Why should I trust you
If the plan fails
I'll end my own life
We Sky Eagles have our own rules
The day
we rob something that is worth giving up our lives for
That is the day we turn in to righteous bandits
Qinglong
What are you after?
My dignity
Let's go  Go
Yes Sir
He said if I were ever to come, I should stay here with him
He said he would make up for everything he has ever done
I'm really here now
But with a Jinyiwei instead
Here is the money that I owe you
Go look for your fiance tomorrow
You want me to go back to him
Am I of no use to you now
you are of no use to me now
I took advantage and now finished
Why are you here alone?
I do not have family
Who am I here with if it weren't with myself
I am fortunate to have your company tonight
Many are after me
but their luck runs out
and I am always the only one left
That is depressing
The ones after you don't have it easy either
The more you understand the one you are looking for
The more you will treat him as a friend
Watching your friend goes down
How is that for depressing
The worst occassion
was when I killed my own brother
Do not worry
Your nightmare will soon end
I am mentally prepared each day
That before I go down
I must complete what I have set out to do
Whom ever stands in my way
No matter friend or foe
Will have to go down first
Fireworks have started
Take this inside
Where did you come from
Do not play here
Outside Outside
Big sister, our money
Thank you, big sister
Captain it must have been a long trip for you
Assisting Prince Qing to acquire three districts
Took me a lot of effort
My deepest gratitude, Sir Jia
I thank you on behalf of Prince Qing
Has Sir Jia brought
what we wanted
Is the Scroll here
I must take a routine look at it
Sir Jia, before I left
Prince Qing made some amends to the Scroll
It is Mid-Autumn Festival
Our first Emperor made his move on this day
and founded the Ming Dynasty
Prince Qing wants
the Imperial Seal of Approval on this Scroll
So that he can come forth into the city
What rubbish
This is a blatant revolt
You dare not to be understanding
Do you not fear for your head?
Xuan Wu, take the Seal
Xuan Wu, you...
Sir Jia
Did you not once say
When people see the glory of your success
They will forget the sinister nature of your means
I work for Prince Qing now
Sir Jia, thank you for teaching me that
Ready
Shoot
Tell our men to be on guard and secure this place
Kill anyone who comes in
Yes
Captain, Please hand me the Scroll
We should stamp it with the Seal
Kill
Here comes the Sky Eagles
Qinglong
Captain
This is family business for the Jinyiwei
Whomever stands in my way today
Will go down
I am stronger than any one of you
Am I wrong to pursue what I want
I know
You have always treated me like a brother
But did you not
kill your own brother too
Yes, and that has left me
a life more painful than death
The suffering
is a nightmare
that will never end
You will not want a life like mine
Kill him
I hate bullies
Judge of the Desert
I thought you only knew how to rob
I love to rob
but I love to fight more
Take this
Your carriage is behind the guard post
There is food and water
Enough for five days
Here is your gold
It is all mine?
It is all yours
The concept of robbing for anything other than riches
I really do not understand
If you've ever up for something like this again
Remember me
I will
Leave
Qinglong
Leave quickly
Go without me, leave quickly
Quickly
Quinglong, we count to three
One
Two
He will not
give up the Seal for me
Three
I'm sorry
Because of me, you lost the Seal
Did you not once say that everyone has a choice
How did she manage to capture you
After I went to find my fiance
I went back to find you
That is how she got me
Sorry
I shouldn't have asked you to find him
I should've personally delivered you to him
This is where...
we saw Qinglong fight with the girl from the West
Qinglong lost and he fled in our carriage
Brothers from the desert in the North also saw
war drums hoisted by Prince Qing's palace
A troop of ten thousand were standing by
ready to attack
At the same time, there were about three hundred fire shooters
aiming towards the City of Sky Wolves
Their intention unknown
The entire city is trembling in fear
Zhao Shenyan is to be excuted for losing the Imperial Seal
Qinglong has lost the same item during his mission in the city
Then
it must be the same Seal that Qinglong has taken back
It's not only the Seal
that Qinglong is after
The fourteenth and the last blade of the Jinyiwei:
Fulfill your mission or, failing that, lay down your life
Taking back the Seal doesn't just concern you alone
Qinglong, although you are the best fighter among us
There is one thing that we excel in
And that is we know our way
We know routes inside and out
There is no time... so let us help you
Yes
If they stamp the Seal on the forged Scroll
Prince Qing will be able to take his men into the city
The people will suffer a long and painful war
So before the Seal passes through the border
We must take it back
For Tuo Tuo to pass through
She must go through City of Sky Wolves
Prince Qing is careful
He will do everything to aid her
Do you have an idea?
Must draw Tuo Tuo away
Divert their attention and the Seal
City of Sky Wolves is famous for its labyrinthian passage
I know a shortcut
that will enable us to pass them
Brothers we must hurry
CITY OF SKY WOLVES
Stop
Xuan Wu
You deliver the Seal
I will take care of Qinglong
Let's go
Check it out
HERE LIES THE BODY OF XUAN WU
Have the fire shooters dimount and chase
Up
Go after them   Yes
Let us split up here
Go  Yes
Fire
Cease fire
Retreat
Charge
The Seal is here
I cannot turn back now
Kill me
Brother
Qinglong, go to Qao Hua quickly
We will handle this here
Qinglong fooled you into dying for him
Here comes the Sky Eagles
Judge
I said scram
Scram
Tell Qinglong for me
If you see me upon this sandy horizon again
Do not be overyjoyed
It is she that you see
After going through here
You can pass through the border
Aren't you coming with me
The road for a Jinyiwei is short
Mine has come to its end today
You told me
We would deliver the Seal together
And then you would leave with me
I promise you
From now on, if you need me
You only need to ring the bell on your wrist
And I will be there for you
Let me tell you a secret
That day
After I saw my fiance
I came back for you
I wanted to tell you
I have declined the proposal
Whatever you tell me to do
I will do it
No matter if you are lying to me
I will wait for you
After I take care of Tuo Tuo, I will come immediately
Wait for me
Before I complete my task
Whomever stands in my way
No matter friend or foe
Will have to go down first
In the end, I safely delivered the Seal to General of the West
Just like I promised Qinglong
The conspiracy was found out
Prince Qing killed himself before execution
It is rumored
that Prince Qing has never cried in his life
But upon hearing the death of Tuo Tuo
He shed a tear
The people were most thrilled
that the Emperor held court again
Sir Zhao was released
Brother Huang, this way
Yes, boss
Prepare food fast
Must continue after lunch
Hurry, hurry
Before father passed away
he said that Justice Escorts
must remain open
For all that is just and
fair in the world
He also let me know a secret
That his wine is not for bruises and wounds
But for him to remember
The sweet memories of the past
When I drink this wine
I am reminded of a friend I met in the desert
I feel very fortunate to have met him
Because I am witness that the Judge
has turned for the good
Of course, I will also think of him
And the roads we have traveled together
I may not know the ways of the world
He once told me that I only need to ring a bell on my wrist
And he will appear
Whatever he tells me to do, I will do it
No matter if he lying to me or not
It is fortunate to have hope