How do you write the
"freeze" incantation?
I didn't spy on him.
I didn't even know he was outside.
Better tie your heart down.
Otherwise, it might fly away
If I could tie it down, I would!
This is how you do it...
It works!
This is the "freeze" incantation.
If you see that monster,
do this and he'll freeze in his tracks.
Like this?
Don't do it haphazardly.
This spell is hard to reverse.
- Give me your hand.
- Yes!
Sister, what's that sound?
- It's coming from up there.
- Windy!
Windy, give me your hand.
Elder, shouldn't you be calling me Sian?
Whether I call you Sian or Windy,
there's no need to be bashful.
I'll never reveal what happened just now.
I was really anxious on your behalf.
Actually, I kissed you
because I couldn't control myself.
Fortunately you made a quick get-away.
Otherwise, if Moon had seen you undressed
and with me...
it would be hard to explain,
even if I were Elder Chu.
Give me your hand.
Moon?!
Moon, what are you doing here?
I was looking for you.
Don't bother explaining.
Moon!
No, Windy!
Give me your hand
We're not fated for each other.
I'm betrothed to Lord Ma's son.
You're betrothed?
We weren't meant for each other.
You should be looking for Moon, not me.
Windy, one at a time.
I'm after both of you.
Miss Moon, it's getting dark.
Give me your hand.
Go to my sister instead.
I'll go to her next.
Quick, give me your hand.
Elder, aren't you the playboy!
You can only choose one of us.
I'm not going to compete with my sister.
No need to compete.
When I finish with you I'll go to her.
Elder, there is something I must tell you.
Actually, love is a strange thing.
My heart beats wildly when I look at you.
I don't even have the courage
to glance at you.
I'm afraid that my heart
would jump right out.
Help!
What's that?
Hurry up!
That monster is back.
Go inside and search.
Yes!
Inside there's a huge creature.
I don't know what it is.
Be calm!
Use the "freeze" incantation.
Together: Freeze!
It sure does!
We froze it in its tracks.
Everybody, jump up there!
The archery machine!
- Be careful!
- Elder!
Moon, go and rescue Elder.
I'll lure away that monster.
Yes!
Put out the net.
Your hand...
Let's retreat from here.
See what's going on up ahead
Yes!
Soldiers!
Hu, they've set up an ambush
Windy, Moon?!
It's father!
Lure the soldiers into the villa.
Use the archery machine
to mow them down!
Trying to get away?
The monster destroyed the archery machine!
We're surrounded by our toes
Let me out!
Right!
Let Elder go!
Elder, what should we do now?
We'll stay on the sidelines.
When the enemy comes in,
the monster will deal with them.
Obviously a fake ghost.
Unmask it.
- Let's rescue father!
- Yes!
You're hopelessly outnumbered.
I'll save you!
Swords are too dangerous!
Let's use our fists.
I told you that swords are too dangerous!
Father!
Get out of here.
Don't worry about me!
Rescue father!
The monster is here!
Abracadabra!
Hocus pocus!
Abraoadabra!
Windy! Windy!
- Possessed by evil spirits?!
- Sister!
- What happened to Windy?
- She's been possessed by evil spirits.
What should we do?
Still a lot of soldiers around.
Better get inside.
Don't move!
Press down on her!
Sister!
Think of a way to save my sister.
She's possessed by the evil spirits.
She could turn into a giant monster
at any moment.
It's your fault, you traitor.
I'll kill you!
Wait!
His troops are still out there.
We must keep him as a hostage.
She's turning into a corpse monster!
Sister!
We must kill her immediately
- Otherwise she'll turn into a monster.
- You can't kill her!
Are you a good person or evil?
You won't kill Hu,
but you'll kill my sister.
Kill Hu!
No matter how many you kill here,
you still won't save the kingdom.
The emperor has no idea
of the suffering of his people.
Take my head to the emperor.
Maybe it will move him.
He'll be convinced
of our sincerity and loyalty.
Father, if you die
we'll have no one to lead us.
Take my head instead.
No!
Take our heads.
Bastards!
What good is it to cut off your heads?
Who are you, ordering people about?!
I am the learned and brilliant Elder Chu!
The learned and brilliant Elder Chu.
Please guide us.
None of you are permitted to die.
Please explain!
Explain?!
Your severed heads
will mean nothing to the emperor.
You'll have died in vain.
Need I explain more?
Stupid pigs!
What about her?
To exorcise her,
she needs a dose of "yang" energy.
I am not powerful enough.
We better do something soon
or it will be too late.
What can we do?
Try this magic charm.
It may or may not work.
Hurry up and pull Miss Windy down.
OK.
I order the evil spirits to be exercised.
How did this happen?
I've forced the evil spirit from her.
If she gets a quick dose of "yang" energy,
there will be a gleam of hope.
Hurry up.
Hurry!
I'm a monk.
I must not get too close to women.
Don't be afraid of her ugliness.
- How do we give her "yang" energy?
- With your mouth, of course.
Mouth?
What then?
Your ears?
Send me to her.
Abracadabra!
Hocus pocus!
Sister!
A real man is afraid of nothing.
Lord, a golden-robed priest
is on his way here.
A golden-robed priest?
Put your swords down!
Not enough!
More!
Lower your swords!
Put all your swords down!
There are evildoers
behind every country's downfall.
Take my head and collect your reward.
The way that you look death
calmly in the face,
proves that you are loyal to our country.
Even though our political views are different,
I'm still willing to help you.
The golden-robed Taoist outside
is the High Priest.
The High Priest?
All the rites and rituals in the palace...
the emperor consults him for guidance.
If he speaks on your behalf,
justice will triumph.
Father!
Lord Fu, if you trust me,
let me go to him.
I'll explain the true situation.
Father, he might betray you!
He could have killed me had he wanted to.
Still not awake?!
Enough!
I'm going to puke.
Elder!
I am here to pay my respects
to the high priest.
Lord Fu is not a traitor.
He is a loyal subject, a patriot.
I hope that you will uphold justice.
There are many
who cannot tell between good and evil.
They do not know the hardships
of the imperial court.
The purpose of my journey
is to pacify the people.
I'll intercede at court on
behalf of these loyal subjects.
Amen! Amen!
Thank you, High Priest!
How are you, Autumn?
Women are very tempting.
If I didn't exercise self-control...
my energy would have been dissipated.
Hu is treacherous
and disrupts the High Priest's harmony.
Please stay here.
The convict Lord Fu is here
to see the High Priest.
I pay my respects to the High Priest.
Amen! Amen!
You have a murderous air about you.
Put down your weapons.
I've been framed,
but I am concerned about our nation.
You're so merciful.
Guide the emperor to save the nation.
Life is chaotic.
Mistakes can always be corrected.
In my former life I was evil
so I must do good in this life.
Release my soul from purgatory.
Evil chanting?!
Don't be tricked!
Sit down!
His mercy is false!
Don't be tricked by his devilish voice!
Abracadabra!
Freeze!
I order the evil spirits to be exercised!
I am the absolute Buddha.
What kind of evil spirit are you!
Even before Buddha
you refuse to reveal your true appearance!
The spirit of evil?!
I am what I look like!
I don't believe you are Buddha!
Let's go over
and see if you're real or false.
Don't!
Abracadabra!
Hocus pocus!
Elder!
The bastard Hu betrayed us.
I'll take care of things here.
Leave quickly!
Abracadabra! Hocus pocus!
The universe revolves.
May Buddha be in your heart.
I knew he was false,
but couldn't conquer him.
I failed!
I can't perform my magic with you here.
I'll open a tunnel in the earth for you.
Hurry!
Autumn!
Hurry up!
I can't hold out.
Hurry!
Abracadabra!
Father!
They've escaped for now
but I'll get them in the end.
Guard the three we've captured!
Yes!
What about Lord Fu?
They have admitted their errors.
They have departed.
People should acknowledge
the immensity of the universe.
I just heard a fight going on.
Your ears aren't clean!
Vacate your mind
to attain perfect peace of mind.
I'm very cold.
Sian!
Don't leave me!
Don't be reincarnated so soon.
It's too hard to be mortal now.
You're so good to Sian.
I never realized
how much you missed her!
Frost fills the sky over 10 Mile Lake.
Silken threads anxoius of youth.
Looking at the moon and feeling lonely.
Envious of lovers, not of immortality.
Sian!
Sian, what are you doing here?
Hide!
You can't let the sun shine on you!
If the sun shines on you,
your soul will be scattered.
You would never be reincarnated!
Why don't you listen to me?
Sian!
Oh, it's you!
I'm sorry.
Once again I've made a mistake.
I mistook you for her.
So there really is someone named Sian!
Is she the one in the painting?
Do you miss her very much?
She's already dead and buried.
We'll never meet again.
If you want,
you can call me Sian for now.
For now?
I understand.
You're betrothed to another.
When I knew Sian,
she was also betrothed to somebody else.
It's beyond my control.
Sian said exactly the same thing.
You are mortal; she's a ghost
But you're both exactly the same.
Are we very much alike?
Too much so.
You gave me false hope.
Anyway, false hope is better than none.
Excuse me!
Here's your tea.
Your meal will be served presently.
Please make yourselves at home.
I've seen that man before.
He's...
The tea is poisoned!
This inn is run by thieves!
Really!
Is the water boiling?
The blade sharpened?
Everything's ready.
Put the man in the cauldron immediately.
Save the woman for tonight,
to warm our cold beds.
Kill!
Slice them up good!
Right on!
Stop!
Watch where you're stabbing!
They escaped through the window.
It's dangerous here.
This is no way to escape!
Better jump into the tree and hide.
I still haven't recovered.
No energy to jump.
Don't worry about me.
Run!
No, I won't leave you.
This time there's no escape!
I never thought we'd die here.
Elder, it's our fault for getting you involved.
I'm not Elder Chu.
I'm just a poor scholar.
No matter who you are...
I feel fortunate
to die with the one I love.
We'll never be parted again.
Hold me!
Let me be on the outside
so that the wolf eats me first.
You're wonderful.
So are you.
If we could be like this forever,
it would be great.
Orchid - Monastery!
Orchid Monastery!
What's the Orchid Monastery?
How could I have forgotten about Yan?
Who is he?
The bearded man in the Orchid Monastery.
A wizard in the occult.
If we find him,
we can deal with the High Priest.
Isn't the High Priest
returning to the capital city?
Why go to his palace?
He needs a tranquil place to meditate.
Only holy people may enter this sacred place.
Stay where you are.
This is the hour of the eclipse.
My body is changing against my wish.
Why are all the officials
of the imperial court here?
Lord Chiang! Lord Yang! Lord Lee!
I was escorting Lord Fu back
to the capital...
But couldn't complete my mission.
Allow me to explain
Lord Chiang!
A hollow shell?
Lord Yang is a hollow shell, too?
What kind of a place is this?
Are you demons?
What did you do
with the flesh and blood of these officials?
You demons, come out and face me!
What did you do
with the flesh and blood of these officials?
What evil intentions do you harbour?
Are they all hollow shells?!
I'm going to destroy
all of you evil monks.
Strange, where have they hidden?
Autumn? Moon? Lord Fu?
Lord Fu!
What happened?
Where are the others?
I was wrong to believe you!
You've caused so much harm!
What other plots do you have
up your sleave?
We were tricked.
The High Priest is a demon!
He turned many officials
into walking corpses.
We must report this to the emperor.
Otherwise,
the kingdom will be beyond redemption.
Oh, he's the one
who instigated this calamity!
No wonder the court is in upheaval.
We must hurry to rescue the others.
We can talk later.
Moon!
Autumn!
There are demons in the court,
so I must get involved in affairs of state
Everyone must do his bit.
Hurry!
There's danger everywhere.
Let's get past this hurdle first.
These demonic monks
have great magical powers.
Once he's awake
we won't be able to escape, so hurry!
Autumn, get out of here!
Don't fight anymore!
This is a scene of desolation.
Lord, ride my horse.
More chanting!
I'll use my powers
to help you concentrate.
Come back, Hu.
You'll never beat him.
Put down your butchers' knives.
Bow before Buddha!
Hu, don't sacrifice yourself in vain!
I mistakenly trusted these demons
and slaughtered righteous officials.
To atone for my sins,
I'll fight him to the death.
Don't!
I'm headed for hell anyway.
Hu!
Yan, why does the wind
suddenly blow so violently?
It's hard to tell
which direction is which.
Yan, what should we do?
Evil spirits pervade this road.
Our lives hang by a slender thread.
We mustn't stop.
Follow me!
Oh, boundless heaven and earth!
Help me!
Recite the scriptures with me!
Prajna paramita...
The Diamond Sutra incantation?
Ignoramus,
behaving so boorishly in front of me!
Prajna paramite...
Ning, Windy... get out of the way!
Oh, boundless heaven and earth.
Help me!
Buddha is present!
If you dare to impersonate Buddha,
what would you not dare to do?
You think
you can hoodwink the people forever?
I'm going to let everyone know
what you really are!
The masses love to worship their idols.
Why set yourself against the people?
It's their ignorance
that has allowed you to succeed.
I'll never let them worship demons like you.
You'll never decieve the people again!
If you refuse
to follow my shining beacon...
you will be destroyed!
What crap!
Look out!
Justine for all!
Swords are part of the infinite!
We've only destroyed the false cuter body.
He can come back and attack us at any time.
We must use our swords to fight back!
Let me introduce myself.
I'm from the Kunlun sect...
At a time like this,
let's not separate into sects.
We're all fighting the same enemy.
Destroy this demon!
Chant with me!
Prajna paramita...
The old demon has stolen into the earth
and broken through our ring of swords.
What should we do?
Watch!
What kind of demon?
Come with me!
Hold on to me as I fly.
Ning!
You pulled my sleave off.
What are you coming back for
What happened?
Gone?
Be careful!
Moon, look after your father.
I'll help Yan.
Autumn, be careful!
The demon's actually a giant centipede!
That worm can never be a dragon.
Elder!
I've never had to deal
with such a giant creature.
What should we do now?
Pierce the crown of its head
Ning!
Windy!
The flying sword!
Prajna paramita!
Exercise the demons!
Oh, boundless heaven and earth.
Help me!
Elder!
Autumn!
Two heads are better than one.
Abracadabra.
Hocus pocus.
I've been in the Orchid Monastery for so long...
I didn't know
the world was so full of devils and demons
It's hard to separate the living from the dead.
The world is in chaos.
It's a good thing
you hid in the Orchid Monastery.
Otherwise I might never have found you.
We share the same ideals...
We should roam this world together
and fight for justice.
We should work together.
What are you saying?
I've always led a solitary existence.
Last time, I almost died
trying to help you save Sian
This time, I've helped you
battle the demons...
and almost lost my life.
It's better if we go our own ways.
When you need my help,
I'll return and save you.
Be careful, Autumn!
We're locked in.
We must think of a way to escape.
You're right!
I've really caused you harm.
Our bodies are restrained.
We can be saved only if our souls can escape.
Souls?
Will we have enough energy
to later let the souls back in?
This is the only way!
Chant along with me.
The spirit of Buddha conquers all!
Goodness is indestructible.
Oh, boundless heaven and earth.
Help me!
Hocus pocus!
Autumn!
- Yan!
- Autumn!
Yan!
Soul, return!
My soul can't return to my body!
Autumn, catch the soul!
His power isn't strong enough.
I'll help him.
Prajna paramita...
I can't catch it.
Moon!
What's all the hubbub outside
What hubbub?
I don't hear anything!
Who's getting married?
Such a large golden pig!
It's a gift to Lord Fu from the emperor.
Since he exposed the traitors
in the imperial court,
he performed a great service for the emperor.
It's a wedding gift for Lord Fu's daughter.
Moon!
Ning!
Is Windy getting...
Sister is already married.
Don't cause her any trouble.
I'm about to start on a journey.
Give her my best wishes
for a happy marriage.
I will.
Take care of yourself.
Adieu!
It's hard to differentiate
between true and false hopes
Now I understand
why you stay away from our mortal world.
Mortals are forgetful.
Good deeds fade like the wind.
No matter what you've done,
it's soon forgotten.
Is forgetting good or bad?
Should we have hopes?
You said you'd cherish no hopes!
Sister, don't hesitate!
Go to him!
Windy?!
Ning!
Let's go, hurry!
You go back.
- Farewell!
- Take care!
Let's go!
The path of life
Are dreams, like the length of the path
The storm on the way
Pass by as you go along
In the world
How many ways can one dream?
Looking for dream-like love
And the path goes on
Life is what
Dreams and desires are made of
Somewhere in the dream
There are traces of tears
Where to go to?
To find where my heart wants to go
The wind seems to sign in the dream,
and the path and I go on.
The path of living
The happiness of youth
The path is full of difficulties
That no light can be seen
In the dust,
how many ways can one find happiness
The wind and rain pass like a dream,
and the path goes on.