That camera again?
I hate that.
It hurts.
Our...
...sex?
One photo a day.
Today's looks almost the same as yesterday's.
But her corpse
will continue to change from day to day.
It's almost as if it were alive.
Go back!
What?
A zoo? You must be joking.
Go back.
What a shame.
Say... do you think this happened;
Suddenly one day, the animals
surpassed man's mediocrity...
...and all left this place?
How did they do that?
You need a key to open these cages!
You are the key to your own cage.
Is it open?
This reminds me of one time when I was a child.
I gazed at a zebra this way for a long time.
When I looked fixedly at the black and white pattern...
...as if it was sucking me in,
I couldn't take my eyes off it.
When I awoke, nobody was around.
I got lost.
Alone, I walked around and around,
but couldn't find the exit.
I felt like I was lost in a labyrinth.
Sorry.
Don't take any more pictures.
I told you I hate it, didn't I?
- Let's break up.
- Don't get angry!
You must be a little tired.
Let's go rest a bit.
If you prefer to stay right here,
I'll keep you company.
Didn't you hear me?
I said it's over between us.
Don't you understand?
I can't live without you.
Then...
go ahead and die.
You still don't get it?
You're not the only man around.
After that,
where had the zebra vanished off to?
The zoo...
I can't find it!
You still don't get it?
You're not the only man around.
From then on, someone other than
me took her picture.
A picture a day.
One by one, they became like a poison.