Why is it that a father is
never able to tell his son...
how much he loves him?
He's never able to embrace him
and say 'I love you my son'?
And the mother?
She keeps repeating it, whether
her son listens to it or not.
But that doesn't mean
a father loves his son any less.
No one can fathom the amount of love
that a mother has for her son...
not even the mother.
Because there is no measure
for a mother's love.
It's an emotion
that can only be felt...
a mother's emotion.
Rahul, my son... my life!
The match between Woodstock
International and Manor House...
is at a very interesting turn.
5 runs and one ball...
Can Woodstock International's 9-year
victory spell be broken in just a ball?
Captain Vivek Singh spreads his field
towards the boundaries...
...and the two batsmen
take their positions.
The excitement among the students
is rising.
The tension is mounting.
Manor House needs five runs
in one ball... Will Rohan do it?
It's up to Rohan to break.
Woodstock International's nine-year
spell of victory... Seems impossible.
Nothing is impossible. The entire game
rests on Rohan's shoulders.
Manor House is confident that
Rohan will do it!
if you want to be someone in life,
if you want to achieve something...
if you want to win,
always listen to your heart.
And if your heart
doesn't give you any answers,
close your eyes and
think of your parents.
And then you will cross
all the hurdles...
all your problems will vanish...
victory will be yours.
Only yours.
Hey, Mom and Dad...
I won I won...
I was the Man of the match...
Hey Dad...
I watched you on CNN.
You looked great.
Now I know where I get
my good looks from.
Anyway, I have just completed
my final term and...
I'm coming home for Diwali.
Can't wait to see you guys.
Lots of Love, Rohan.
P. S... Before I come home
I'm stopping at Hardwar to meet...
my two favourite girlfriends.
Hardwar?
Who are these girlfriends in Hardwar?
My two grandmothers...
maternal and paternal!
...8 a.m.
Are you watching the photograph and
crying again?
Where am I crying?
Of course not...
Where are you crying?
That's one truth and the other one is
that you are very young...
Stop joking with me
early in the morning...
What's the matter, Lajoji?
I remember Rahul
very often these days.
Even I remember him.
But in the last few days...
I have been feeling
very restless with his memories.
But why?
Listen...
We have lived our full lives.
Speak for yourself... I have
a long life ahead... Touchwood!
Yes...
But I have to reach God's abode...
How will I face Him there?
How will I explain the reason, why
I couldn't unite my scattered family?
That I couldn't bring
my grandson back home?
How will I show my face to Him?
Don't worry about it.
You are not going to meet God anyway...
- Why?
Because he doesn't meet anyone
in Hell...
God... again your jokes
early in the morning...
Hey you sweethearts...
Rohan!
Naani.
- My child.
What's the matter, Naani?
You look very sexy.
I know. Everyone says the same thing.
May you live long.
You have become very weak my son.
Now everyone can't be
as healthy as you are.
Oh! Just Shut up now.
What's the matter, Naani?
- What happened? Is she crying?
Then it's fine. I get very worried
when she doesn't weep.
Just see... Rohan!
- Oh now stop it you two...
Please stop crying Lajoji...
Please stop.
Your tears will raise a lot of
questions in Rohan's mind and...
we won't have any answers
to his questions.
What do I do Kaur?
What do I do?
Whenever I see Rohan,
I think of Rahul even more
Don't you think we should
tell him everything?
How can we tell him, Lajoji?
Yash has warned us against it.
Rohan was not even in town
when Rahul left home...
He doesn't know anything.
I think we should
tell him everything.
Where do we begin?
What do we tell him?
He doesn't even know that Rahul was
not born to Yash and Nandini.
He was adopted.
Rahul was two days old when
Yash and Nandini brought him home.
His tiny footsteps made a place
in all our hearts.
He became Nandini's lifeline and
Yash's dream was fulfilled.
Nine years later,
when you were born...
we felt that
our family was now complete.
I still remember
the astrologer saying that...
you fought destiny to be born.
You would be our strength.
Did Rahul bhaiyya know
that he was...?
Rahul was eight years old
when he got to know.
That was when Yash decided that...
the matter would never be mentioned
again in the house...
Never again...
Rahul was our son.
The eldest son of the house.
It was a truth that could
never be changed.
But the fact was mentioned again...
Suddenly.
And that was Rahul's last Diwali with
his family... Last Diwali.
Oh Allah! Rohan baba,
you have become so fat...
that nothing fits you anymore.
What's DJ? Say Daijaan.
"It's all your blessings"
whether smiles or tears"
"We shall never part,
through smiles or through tears."
"I feel you in every breath
of mine..."
"my life is but under your shadow"
"I feel you in every breath
of mine..."
"my life is but under your shadow"
"I pray to thee as long as I live"
"It's all your boons...
Whether smiles or tears"
"We shall never part...
through smiles nor through tears"
"We light the lamps of love
at your feet"
"We see you everywhere
in everything we see"
"Our lips chant no name but yours"
"Let our hearts be filled
with nothing but your love"
"It's all your boons...
whether smiles or tears"
We shall never part...
through smiles nor through tears"
Hey maa... How do you always sense
my presence much before I arrive?
Rahul... just tell me one thing...
Emails, letters, faxes...
I sent you all of these and you
didn't reply to any... very rude.
MBA is a tough job, Naina!
Was it only MBA that kept you busy?
Or was there something else?
I mean someone else.
Well... It was more than just
one... you know me...
Ha... You stud you.
- Ya... me stud me.
Tell me Rahul.
- What do you think?
I think...
I think, Rahul...
- What do you think, Naina?
Rahul, I don't think anyone other than
me can waste her time with you.
In any case what do you know
what to do with a girl.
Oh really?
Is this done with a girl?
Stop it Rahul...
- Tell me...
Did you remember me at all?
Should I tell you the truth or lie?
- Lie...
If I have to lie then I'd say I did...
not remember you at all...
How sweet!
- Let's talk about you.
Are you still the same or is
some mad guy interested in you?
What do you think?
- I think...
What do you think, Rahul?
I think...
- What do you think, Rahul?
I think, Naina...
I will beat you to that door.
Really?
- Really.
Don't bet on that.
Yes... yes...
Don't you have to go to school?
Thank you... C'mon,
eat this... What's the score?
104 for 6... isn't that great?
- Damn good yaar. How many overs?
God, bhaiyya... I think
India is going to kill England.
Anything can happen
at the last minute.
You can't bank on them too much.
You never know with India, Rohan.
Here... take this...
Out Out... What\92s the big deal?
England was out of India in 1947.
DJ... that was a PJ...
Oh Allah...
What are these? Legs or...?
He still hasn't learnt
how to tie his shoe laces?
So what? He's a child yet...
He'll learn...
But if you don't allow him to do it
himself, how will he learn? Fatty.
Why did you come back from London?
What's happening here?
Mom you have over fed Rohan and
turned him into a pumpkin.
Yes, yes please laugh at me...
When I go away to...
the boarding school you will all
remember me. Nobody loves me.
By the way Fatty...
Mother loves me more than you.
- DJ... Just look at him.
- Calm down. He's jealous of you.
Mom, I missed you.
- I missed you too, baby.
You won't leave me again
and go, will you?
I won't, but promise me, you will not
feed me the way you, this pumpkin.
Nandini! Nandini!
Yes... Coming.
You have forgotten me
as soon as your son has arrived.
Who will knot this tie?
- Can't you do even that without me?
Here... Now you truly look like
Mrs. Yashvardhan Raichand.
This is for you my son.
From today, the Raichand Empire
belongs to you.
Oops, Sorry Dad.
That's your grandfather. Salute him.
You know Rahul,
Thirty years ago he said...
certain things to me in this chamber,
which I will now repeat to you.
He said life offers you many
paths to choose from.
You must always choose
the one that is right...
the one where you don't have to
bend... where you don't fall.
Never take a step in life...
that will bring shame to
your family name or prestige.
Anyone can make money but earning
respect is not everyone's cup of tea.
I have not forgotten
his words till today.
Even you should not.
Promise me that you will follow
the traditions of the family.
Promise me that you'll never compromise
with the self-respect of our family.
I promise papa...
that I will always keep
the family name flying high.
I promise you that I will always
keep you happy... always Papa
We have won.
Pooja, Pooja
- What happened?
We have won the match.
God, Sachin played so well...
100 runs not out.
Ok now listen, take care
of the shop I will be back.
Haldiraaam!
What a game!
What a game! What a game!
What a game!! By the way
what game are we playing?
India has won the match!
- Oh so we have won... How nice.
If you didn't know,
what were you dancing for?
I was dancing because
all the laddoos...
that my wife made
have been sold.
Sold out? How come?
There was a customer who told me
he wanted to eat laddoos...
that would drive him crazy.
Eating her laddos can cure
people who are insane and...
those who are normal become...
- Clean bowled!
It was just a joke...
- Stop it now...
Haven't even started it yet...
- Come on...
Rukhsar!
- Stop shouting so loudly...
The groom's side has come to
see Rukhsar for marriage.
Sit down. Salute them.
Grandmom... wake up...
the bride has arrived.
Oh! Masha Allah Masha Allah...
Her face is bright like
the full moon.
She is just what I had imagined.
Well... it's not me... its...
This is my daughter, Rukhsar.
What? Fever?
Not fever... mother,
She's Rukhsar!
Oh Rukhsar!
What happen?
- We have won the match.
My daughter's very
quiet and introverted.
We have won.
- Allah! What happened?
Quiet and introverted... eh?
Incidentally, what is her age?
Hundred.
- Grandmom, she says...
- she's hundred years old.
- What? Nine years old?
She's going to turn twenty-one soon.
- Well... the blossoming of youth.
Actually we live in Lucknow.
But this is Chandni Chowk,
I guess... anyway I forgot to
tell you, my son's name is Ashfaque.
Sachin!
- Sachin?
Sachin? In case there's
someone else in her life...
No! No! Please don't say such things.
It's... her uncle Sachin...
her late uncle Sachin.
She was very attached to him.
She always remembers
him on happy occasions.
Sachin...
Poor Sachin...
C'mon you girls...
I'll teach you a lesson...
Oh God, Is everything alright?
Forget about me...
tell me what has she done this time?
Ask me what she hasn't.
A nice wedding proposal
would have slipped out of our hands.
What?
180 by 100...
your blood pressure is high.
You mean BP is high-wigh!
Yes, it's high and it's
'why' because of you.
I have just increased the dosage.
Please get these medicines.
Om Bhai, you must take care of yourself.
- This won't do...
Yes, Aunty... he just doesn't
take care of himself.
You just keep quiet...
I don't want to talk to you...
Why?
- Why? What is Sayeeda saying?
Oh! I wasn't serious at all.
I was just joking.
That's surprising...
You have spoilt my two daughters...
Aren't they like my children too?
Anyway, leave all this aside.
The good news is that
they liked this mad girl...
they have accepted the proposal.
- They have accepted?
Didn't they see you properly?
Shut up!
So you will leave us and go...?
Some day all you girls have to leave.
No way am I leaving
my father and going anywhere.
Even I'm not going.
- So then should I leave?
Why do you speak like this, father?
Some day you have to get married,
my child.
The only prayer
I have to the Lord is that...
the man you marry must
love you even more than I do.
C'mon...
I don't think such
a man exists in this world...
Am I not there?
You did not eat, dance or even talk
to anyone at the party tonight.
You didn't even tell me
how beautiful I look tonight.
You look very beautiful, Naina.
Really? How sweet!
I'm sweet and I also lie very well.
Just go...
- No.
Hey Naina, you look very beautiful.
Are you lying or telling the truth?
- What do you think?
I think...
I think Rahul...
- What do you think?
Rahul, I think you should go now.
In any case I wasn't planning to come
with you. But thanks for the offer.
Bye... I was lying to you.
What's happening, Mom?
Nothing much except planning
for Dad's surprise party.
Nothing stays in
this child's stomach.
That's because there's already
so much in there.
Rahul, How come you are
back so early?
Mom... These society parties are
very boring.
Really?
In that case you have not taken
after your father in these matters.
He used to love such parties...
because there used to be
a lot of girls there...
Nandini
He used to get very happy
watching those girls.
Nandiniji... If I hadn't
watched those beautiful girls...
how would I have found you?
- What did you do?
Your father brought
Nandini's proposal...
When he saw her for the first time
he was very pleased...
And said, he approved of her.
But he said we would have
to ask for dowry.
He insisted that the girl should
bring from her parents' house...
lots of love and a long,
long ladder.
It's a great tradition.
The elders of the house choose
their daughter-in-law.
One can't trust these mad children.
No, Mataji... All that was then.
These days everything has changed.
- Nothing has changed, Nandini.
But these days children make
their choices themselves...
Nothing has changed, Nandini.
What I meant was...
- Nothing has changed.
But...
- I said it... didn't I?
That's it!
Your beauty is going to steal
his sleep in the nights...
Shut up!
- You shut up!
Where is your Ashfaque?
I haven't even seen him yet.
Introduce him to me.
Let me see how he looks.
He is arriving from
Lucknow today and...
he will come to meet you
as soon as he comes.
Tell me what you thought of him.
Stop this coy bride act now...
By the way,
what does he do in Lucknow?
He is a poet.
- A poet?
Then I'll get
along very well with him.
Really? Why?
That's because I write
a bit of poetry myself.
A ha... Ustad Anjali Ali Khan.
Let me say a few lines...
- Go on... Go on.
What heartache have
I gone through for thee...
On one end is Rukhsar and
the other is Aunteee...
Shut up, you brat.
Do you know that the morning papers
have carried a photograph...
- of my boss and his son?
- Really? Can I see?
Wash your hands first...
- Oh God!
Tomorrow is his fiftieth birthday.
There's going to be a big party.
There will be lot of people.
I made it very clear to Bhabhiji
that the desserts will...
come from Chandni Chowk. That too
specially made by dear Anjali.
Really? And what did she say?
- She agreed.
But now you make sure that
you don't mess things up.
Both Rukhsar and you come to
the party with the kulfi.
Yes we will. Oh God, but
tomorrow is Bauji's birthday too.
So what? Come a little late.
In any case their party is
not going to start early.
Oh Allah! Oh Allah!
Do I have it?
No!
- You don't know anything.
Please dress appropriately
for tomorrow.
Yes Ammi, I will wear my new
shimmering, embroidered outfit.
Of course... You must.
After all everyone in the party
will be dying to know...
what Rukhsar is going to wear...
- Really?
C'mon Rukhsar... the gang... Please.
- No... not today.
Rukhsar please.
- No... Ammi is not feeling well.
I'll return it.
Your groom is coming
to visit us today, isn't he?
Where have we come now? How tacky!
You brat. Mother has sent some
medicines for Daijaan.
I'll back.
Ammi... Stop it now and
go to sleep...
Come back.
- Coming, bauji.
Where has Bhaiiya gone?
The shop's closed for now.
It will open only at 10.
Ashfaque miya.
Let me say a couplet.
So what if the evil wishes harm...
nothing can happen
The only will that triumphs
is the will of the Lord.
Your turn...
Eh, Look up there.
Eh, Laddoo...
You can't enter Chandni Chowk.
Why?
- Just...
And if you want to enter,
you have to say this:
Chandu's uncle fed Chandu's aunty on
a moonlit night in Chandni Chowk
in a silver spoon,
some Chatni... Say it fast.
What exactly am I supposed to say?
Never mind... You don't say...
Can I say another one?
Love is not an easy path,
understand ye all...
It's a trial by fire
to be crossed bravely.
Chandu's... spoon's... uncle...
You have come to meet me...
haven't you?
Not really...
I came to meet Daijaan.
So you call her
'Daijaan' lovingly... eh?
Of course...
She has brought me up.
She has brought you up?
In that case even I must have been
your played in her lap.
Chandu's spoon... silver uncle...
Look up there!
Catch him.
When's the wedding?
- Who's?
Of course yours and hers.
How can I marry Daijaan?
You have a great sense of humour.
And you are cute too.
Bhaiyya... save me.
I'm going to tell Rukhsar that
I liked her Ashfaque miya.
Who is Ashfaque miya?
You are asking me
who Ashfaque miya is?
You have a great sense of humour...
Do you know where
Sayeeda begum lives? No?
Do you know?
- What do I know?
You seem to know everything.
Do you know my Aunty?
Your would be mother-in-law...
Sayeeda begum... Do you know
where she works?
Big businesses of the big people.
Have you heard of the Raichands?
How could you have heard of them?
Their photo has appeared
in the newspaper today...
Really?
- Yes...
Have you seen it?
- No...
Then come with me...
I'll show you...
I don't read the newspapers.
- Here it is.
Yashvardhan Raichand...
a big snob!
And this is his son... God!
He looks exactly like you.
Show me.
Ah Ashfaque miya.
I'm a dead duck...
- Not at all...
You have a great sense of humour.
Bhaiyya... I have some
goons running after me.
My younger brother.
Listen... You really do have
a great sense of humour.
Greetings... I'm Ashfaque.
- And I'm the Queen of Jhansi.
Before I raise
this toast to Papa...
I want to say something
to all of you.
I had a dream since childhood...
A dream to be like Papa.
To walk like him, speak like
him, sit like him...
To do everything the way he does.
Like the way he is
standing right now...
Can't do it.
I know I can't do it.
And maybe I will never be able to
do it because...
there's no one in this world
like my Papa.
I know that someone up there is
happy with me to have bestowed on...
me the right to say that
I am Yashvardhan Raichand's son.
Say it proudly.
We just want to say to you that
we love you very much.
I'll just have a look.
Grandmother, you come with me.
"Your gilded beauty shines through,
and so do your golden anklets"
"They tinkle in melody,
to wound the hearts of millions"
"Your kohled eyes speak
a mysterious language"
"the immortal language of love"
Say "shava shava"
friends say "shava shava"
"My gilded beauty shines through,
and so do my golden anklets"
"They tinkle in melody,
to wound the hearts of millions"
"My kohled eyes speak
a mysterious language..."
"the immortal language of love"
Say "shava shava"
friends say "shava shava"
"Ever since I laid my eyes
on you for the first time..."
"my heart beats faster every minute"
"What have you done to me?
Oh lord, what have you done to me?"
"Your sweet words
make me weak in my knees"
"I think I'm falling
in love with you"
"I will die without you"
"Oh God, I will die without you"
Say "shava shava" friends
Say "shava shava"
"May my last breath
be at your feet"
"May my love for you
surpass that of the lord"
"May the lord forgive me,
may the lord forgive me"
"You are my heart,
you are my soul"
"You are my heaven,
you are my earth"
"What will I ever do without you"
"Oh lord, what will
I ever do without you"
"Say " shava shava " friends
say "shava shava"
"Your gilded beauty shines through,
and so do your golden anklets"
"They tinkle in melody,
to wound the hearts of millions"
"Your kohled eyes speak
a mysterious language"
"...the immortal language of love"
"Say " shava shava " friends
say "shava shava"
That's enough now.
It's been too much.
God... Mad girl...
Come on now...
I'm a dead duck...
Rukhsar, This one is...
Excuse me Sir!
This is our Anjali.
She has come to apologise to you.
Apologise?
Oh... That's not necessary.
Wait! Wait!
How can you say that Sir? She has
caused such a big loss for us...
She must apologise. And to tell you,
she is quite a madcap.
Even in her own house...
- Aunty! Can I speak?
Yes... go ahead... apologise.
You know sir,
When I listen to film songs...
I tend to get a little filmi.
And that Khandala number
is one of my favourites.
Shut up!
- What am I saying?
What did you want to say and
what are you saying?
Apologise.
You?
Come on leave right now from here.
Me?
- No... no... not you.
Oh! Sir, I was responsible for
smashing your big pot.
Vase.
- Yes, vase... shaz whatever it was.
I'm ready to pay you the
money for it.
By the way how much
was it for?
Now... I don't know...
Sayeeda, Why don't you explain.
Shut up!
- Shut up?
This is all because of you.
- Because of me?
No... no... not because of you.
God, everything is going wrong.
You see sir...
Bauji always says that no one becomes
small by asking for forgiveness.
And the one who forgives
owns a big heart...
You have a big heart don't you, Sir?
- Now...
So you have forgiven me?
- Yes... I have.
Big businesses of big people.
Ok I'll take your leave now.
Please say a big hello to Madam.
May the Lord protect
Greetings. To you too!
Quiet now...
Pot... No, Not a pot... a vase.
Sayeeda... Take her now...
Come on now... Come on...
- Not a pot... a vase. Sorry.
A pot!
Isn't this that Laddoo's school?
- C'mon lets go and hit him.
- Yes... C'mon.
These are the same goons
I was talking about.
Hey, you speak Hindi, don't you?
What? And you didn't do anything?
They were too many of them Didi...
I couldn't do anything.
Here you roam around like a don.
What happened to you there?
Oh! Didi.
- Oh! Didi.
But what was the need for
her to go into the school?
Lord Almighty!
What are you saying?
She just entered the school...
not murdered anyone.
What was the need for them
to say all those things?
If I was there I would have caught
each one of them and bashed them up.
Yes. They have hurt my sister.
Let me meet that
Laddoo and that Fattoo...
I vow on Sachin Tendulkar that
I don't hang them upside down...
in the middle of Chandni Chowk
I won't call myself Bauji's daughter.
Anjali!
You don't know, Bauji...
Rich in money but poor at heart...
Can never find place near the Lord...
That's a good line.
Did you write it yourself?
Yes.
Greetings to you.
- Greetings.
Anjali, they have come to
our house for the first time...
Get them something to eat.
I'm sure they have had
their meals before coming...
Haven't you seen the size?
Don't worry sir we have eaten.
How can you say that? I'll just
get you something in a minute.
No. No sir,
Please don't take any trouble.
And you also... don't bother.
What's the name?
- Rohan!
Not yours, hers...
- Pooja...
You are a real Laddoo. Come on.
You must never hurt
anyone's feelings.
Specially that of a young girl...
and not...
when she's so beautiful.
Come on, say Sorry now.
Besides, Someone has told me that...
apologising doesn't make
anyone smaller.
And the one who forgives
owns a big heart.
Isn't it?
What are you looking at?
C'mon, apologise, Laddoo.
If those two can become friends,
why can't we?
Friends?
- Yes...
I just want to be friends with you...
Do you have a problem?
Really?
Friends, ji? C'mon just do it.
I can't see Bauji...
He went to get some food...
Bauji is inside...
I'm telling you, Rukhsar...
There's something fishy going on.
Anjali, you think he's...
- What?
He is...
- Yes... even I think the same.
Don't you think?
- Correct.
Even you think the same, don't you?
- You are on the mark Rukhsar.
He wants to take away
my shop from me.
Oh Allah!
What do I do with this girl?
I'm saying that he might be in...
Iove with you...
- Love?
Wow, Rukhsar begum,
you are really great!
You think all the girls in Delhi
that he will be in love with me?
No one loves me
here in Chandni Chowk...
Why would that Yashvardhan's
son be interested in me?
Don't joke it away now,
I'm telling you.
Ya ya...
you keep telling...
Take her away.
- What are you saying?
It was a joke.
- Stop it.
So you don't want to
buy the sweetmeats?
When did it shift?
Red Fort shifted to Agra
a long time ago and...
the mental asylum from there
has shifted here.
Not a dime in the pocket and wants to
know the whereabouts of the Red Fort.
Bharat Sweet Shop.
Sweets for all occasions...
whether an engagement or wedding.
- Both will happen in due course...
what's the hurry?
- Who's that?
Who? It's me, who else?
- Who's me?
What do you mean, who?
It's me your new friend.
You know, the children have made
a plan to go to the fair...
I was thinking if you could join us,
it would be great fun!
What fair?
The fair at Chandni Chowk,
which else?
This fair?
Don't you think...
its importance would reach too high
if you visited this fair?
Actually, my importance will increase
manifold, if you could join me.
Tomorrow at 4 in the evening.
Bye.
- Bye Shye.
Chandu's uncle fed Chandu's aunty
on a moonlit night in
Chandni Chowk in a silver spoon,
some Chatni. C'mon say it.
Stop it!
Wearing a suit and his boots
Kanhaiyya has arrived to play a band.
Wow! You sing very well.
Yes... By the way,
do you always wear such clothes?
Yes... When I wear clothes,
I wear these.
Otherwise most of the time
I'm in the nude...
No... no... I asked because
we have a proverb that says,
'He who wears a kurta from
Lucknow and Pathani salwar...
stands for a true man and the one
who doesn't, who knows?'
Very good! By the way your hair
looks beautiful when left loose.
Isn't it a coincidence that both
our fathers share the same birthday?
Twins?
- Of course. One with a large heart...
the other with a large pocket
to pay the bills.
Let them be.
They look nice.
Bangles? 'Fair are my wrists...
make me wear those green bangles...'
'...Make me yours, my beloved...'
You... Sorry, I mean Mr...
Ah! Don't be formal...
Say \91you'... makes me feel closer.
Closer? This is getting too much...
Now listen to me Mr. Raichand...
- I want to say something to you...
- I'm listening...
What I want to say is that
I can't give you what you want.
Why not?
- I just can't.
At least give it a try.
I can't give...
Bauji won't allow it...
I'll ask for it from Bauji...
Lord save me! Why would
Bauji give you our shop?
What's the big...? Shop?
What shop?
Our Bharat Sweetmeat shop, which else?
- What shop are you talking about?
It was alright till friendship but
what is all this intimacy about?
You sneaked into my house.
Lord save me, even that is over.
After all there's a limit
to friendship, isn't there?
Shut up!
There are many bonds
other than friendship.
Bonds that we don't understand...
that we don't need to understand.
I hope it's not hurting you.
Bonds that are nameless...
that are just to be experienced.
I hope it's not hurting you.
Bonds that don't
have any boundaries...
no limits.
I hope it's not hurting you.
Bonds that bind the
hearts together...
bonds of passion...
bonds of love.
Hurt you? Me too!
And one more thing...
I'm definitely going to
take over your sweetmeat shop!
"The sun dims into twilight"
"The moon beams simmer brightly"
"I stand still as the earth
moves around me"
"The heart beats faster
as my breath goes deeper"
"Is it the call of first love?"
"My love, is it the
call of first love?"
"The sun dims into twilight,
moon beams simmer brightly"
"I stand still as the earth
moves around me"
"The heart beats faster
as my breath goes deeper"
"Is it the call of first love?"
"My love, is it the call
of first love?"
"Savour these beauteous moments,
when everything changes"
"Our dreams blend into
the realms of reality"
"I wonder if our love,
travelling through centuries..."
"has bound us in its silken threads"
"Let this season of love
remain eternal"
"let us meet through lives
and lives, like today"
"I stand still as the earth
moves around me"
"the heart beats faster
as my breath goes deeper"
"Is it the call of first love?"
"My love, is it the call
of first love?"
"The colours of our souls
has melted into one"
"I can't say which of me is you
and which of you is me"
"O beloved, it's the waves
of the your love that drown me"
"before transporting me to the shore"
"It's the thirst of the ocean,
It's the dream of the night"
"The hearts of the flames
have been set afire"
"I stand still
as the earth moves around me"
"the heart beats faster
as my breath goes deeper"
"My love, is it the
call of first love?"
"My love, is it
the call of first love?"
"The sun dims into twilight,
moon beams simmer brightly"
She's slightly mad.
Actually she's completely mad.
She makes strange faces,
she talks a lot.
And she has some lovable mannerisms.
And wherever she goes
she breaks a vase a pot
Pot?
- That's what she calls them.
But whenever I'm next to her,
I don't know what happens to me.
But she's slightly mad.
Actually she's completely...
Mad.
What's the name
of this mad hatter?
I wanted to know your opinion.
I'm very happy with this alliance.
Naina is a very nice girl.
Have you spoken to Rahul
about this?
What's the need to speak to Rahul?
He can't take these family decisions.
Naina will be the daughter-in-law
of this house... our house!
DJ... Who will do all
this for me there?
Dad, Why can't I stay with
all of you here?
Why are you sending me
to the boarding school?
Traditions, my child...
traditions...
Your grandfather went there,
I did, so did bhaiyya.
You can't break the traditions
of the house, can you?
No...
Always remember
one more thing...
Mom loves me more than
she loves you.
You have given me so much already...
I can't take all these.
Sayeeda... If Rahul and Rohan
can be like your sons...
then don't have a right
over your daughter?
Of course you have...
But all this is too much...
Just tell me what time
is the actual wedding?
Rohan... listen to me carefully.
Take care of your food and sleep.
Rohan, he has reached
his school.
Hey! What's all this?
Tomorrow is Rukhsar's wedding...
So the two of us...
Congratulations to you Sayeeda!
If you need anything just ask for it
- Thank you sir...
I'd be very happy if you and bhabhiji
could attend the wedding tomorrow...
I have asked Rahul to attend the
wedding, he will be there.
Ok.
Rahul baba must have come now...
Let me just check.
I'll just be back.
Listen to me.
Tomorrow is a big day for Sayeeda.
I think we should go too...
- How can we go there, Nandini?
I can understand... But still we...
- We cannot go there.
Please think about it again...
- I said it, didn't I? That's it!
Eh! What happened to Chandni?
Haldiram, What happened?
- What happened?
Listen... let me say a couplet.
'Kurta from Lucknow or a pathani salwar
does not make a man...
He who gives away his
heart stands for a true man...
and the one who doesn't...
who knows?'
"Oh the brides decorated hands"
"Oh the brides bejewelled finery"
"Oh she looks like a floral ornament"
"Oh the brides kohled eyes"
"Oh she looks the
most beautiful of them all"
"Oh the bridesmaid..."
"She looks like a silken thread"
"she peeps from behind,
and steals a glance"
"Whether she admits it or nay,
she's stolen my heart"
"Oh lord, this damsel oh my lord"
"These lanes of my childhood,
I shall never depart"
"Put some sense,
into this crazy man's head"
"He is hurling himself onto me"
"Oh lord, this young man oh my lord"
"Whether thy lips speak or not..."
"your eyes divulge the story"
"You can't hide love in disdain..."
"you can't hide love in disdain..."
"A veiled silence speaks
more than a thousand words"
"Words don't always
do justice, my friend"
"What's in the heart,
only the heart knows"
"Or then the lord"
"Oh lord, this damsel oh my lord"
"Oh my lord,
this young man, oh my lord"
"You can't demand,
a hand in betrothal"
"pairs are ordained,
already in heaven"
"Pairs are ordained,
"Leading a wedding procession,
I will take you from your doorstep"
"It's been destined so,
"Oh go away and stop day dreaming"
"Oh my lord,
this young man, oh my lord"
"Oh the bridesmaid...
she looks like a silken thread"
"She peeps from behind,
and steals a glance"
"Whether she admits it or nay,
she's stolen my heart"
"Oh lord, this damsel oh my lord"
"Oh lord,
this young man oh my lord"
"Oh lord, this damsel oh my lord"
Agreed!
- Even I agree.
You love her don't you?
- Yes, Papa.
Didn't I tell you, Nandini?
What did I tell you?
I'm very happy,
today Rahul... very happy.
Just promise me that
you will keep her happy too.
You will keep my daughter-in-law
very happy.
You will keep Naina very happy.
You face has fallen as
if we are already married.
By the way this expression appears
only after a man gets married.
Eh Rahul, What's the matter?
What's her name?
Naina!
I wish that was the name.
But it isn't.
Naina... it's just...
- Rahul!
Ever since I can remember
I have loved you...
Loved you very much.
But it isn't your fault.
Just because I dreamt of marrying you
doesn't mean you have to marry me.
And if you are worried
that I will miserable...
yes I will be.
I will feel very bad...
it will hurt
a lot too.
But life doesn't stop, does it Rahul?
Perhaps a few years from now
I can laugh at the fact that...
I loved a certain Rahul
who could not become mine.
Because he was never mine!
And my love story remained incomplete.
But do me a favour Rahul.
Please complete your love story.
You will, won't you Rahul?
For my sake.
Now say something quickly
before I cry more.
Even me.
Raichand.
The name and the respect has been
given to us by our ancestors.
To honour and respect
them is our foremost duty.
And I will never tolerate
an ordinary girl becoming a hurdle...
in performing that duty.
You didn't even think once...
about the background of the girl,
her status... her breeding.
You didn't give a thought to whether
the girl will be able to understand...
our culture... our traditions.
Will the girl ever understand
our rituals... our rites?
Will the girl understand our
ethics and principles?
Will she adhere to
the values of our family?
Will she...?
How did you even dare to think
that she can be a part of our family?
That she can be a
part of my family?
How did you think?
Where did I think, Papa?
I didn't think at all.
I just loved... love.
Love?
It's such a pity that. I made
a mistake in knowing my own son
I thought he knew me.
That he understands
the traditions of this family.
He understands my emotions...
he understands every breath of mine.
I was so wrong... so wrong.
I was really proud of you.
You were my self-respect.
You were my strength.
You have taken all that away
from me... everything.
You have hurt me,
You have hurt me.
I never wanted to hurt you.
I only wanted to bring you happiness.
What have I done?
How could I bring tears to your eyes?
How could I bring tears?
Don't ever forgive me.
Please don't say that
I have hurt you.
Don't forgive me.
I will do as you say
just as you say.
Bauji... Bauji...
Please don't leave us and go.
Get up Bauji...
Don't leave us, Bauji...
Will the girl be able to understand
our culture, our traditions.
Will the girl ever understand our
rituals... our rites?
Will the girl understand
our ethics and principles?
Will she adhere to
the values of our family?
Today...
today you have proved that
you are not my blood.
You are not my blood.
You have proved that
you are not mine.
Papa!
You have lost the right
to call me that!
Made me a stranger in a moment.
Made me a stranger in just a moment.
Does that mean I have no
place in this house anymore?
I am right... am I not, mother?
I'm right, am I not?
Then let me go... Can I go?
"Through smiles or through tears"
"We shall never part,
through smiles nor through tears"
"My blessings live with you..."
"to protect you from evil eyes"
"My wishes for you..."
"wherever you go"
"May happiness and joy,
kiss your feet forever"
"It's all your blessings"
"Whether smiles or tears,
we shall never part"
"through smiles or through tears"
Promise me that you will never let
tears come to his eyes... promise me.
Now go!
Rahul... we didn't take
blessings from father.
We don't have father's blessings...
Rahul we didn't...
Go Sayeeda.
Go with my son.
Wherever he goes...
I don't want him to miss the warmth
of a mother's affection.
If you want to be someone in life...
if you want to achieve something...
if you want to win,
always listen to your heart.
And if even that doesn't
give you any answers...
close your eyes and
think of your parents.
And then you will cross all the hurdles
all your problems will vanish.
Victory will be yours.
Only yours.
You will remember all this,
won't you Rohan?
Why are you going, Bhaiyya?
Why? Please don't go.
Promise me Rohan that after today
you will never ask anyone...
why I left and where I went...
promise me.
Take care of mother.
Get selected in the cricket team.
And thus Yash's ego and
Rahul's stubborn stand broke...
the family into two...
broke the family into two...
I will bring you back Bhaiyya.
I will bring you home Bhabhi.
To your home... our home.
Nandini...
- Yes?
You have forgotten me
as soon as your son has arrived.
Where is Rohan?
I don't know where he
left early this morning.
Greetings for Id.
- Greetings for Id.
Greetings to you too.
Wow... you are glowing.
I feel so happy that you have come.
Greetings for Id.
God! How big he has grown.
- Yes... Both have grown quite a lot.
Stop it now...
- Just a joke.
What's his name, Haldiram?
- Ghasitaram!
Hello! Salutations.
Greetings for Id.
Greetings to you too.
- Recognise me?
Well...
- I'm from... there.
Ok... yes yes.
He's just spinning yarns. He's just
come to have some free drinks.
I don't seem to see your mother.
- That reminds me...
What's the news about Anjali?
- They are all very well.
I just spoke to them in the morning.
- Please give them lots of our love.
Rukhsar!
- You all chat... I\92ll be back.
What a life Anjali is leading!
From Chandni Chowk to...
Yes. From Chandni Chowk to...?
- To...
To... where?
- What where? Chandni Chowk?
That's in Delhi.
- You said she went somewhere.
Where did she go?
- Brother... Where she went?
- Where did she go? Where she went...
Where did she go?
- Where did she go?
Where- did- they- go?
- Where-did-they-go?
Didn't you say they went somewhere?
Probably America or somewhere...
Oh! Have they gone to America?
But they didn't live there earlier.
- Exactly.
Where did they live earlier?
- In Chandni Chowk.
After that... Where?
- America... Didn't you just say?
And in between?
- In between whom?
In between the two...
- What is between the two?
What is between the two?
- The place between the two...
What's the place between the two?
What is he talking about?
Wonder where these people come from.
- I'm trying to tell you, the place...
What place are you talking about?
- What place? Where?
Silence! Come here.
Haldiram has lost his marbles.
She has gone to London.
Someday even I will go there.
You have just come back, son.
And you want to go away again?
I feel incomplete here, Dad!
Why don't you study for MBA here?
There are a lot of universities here.
Why do you want to go to London?
- Traditions, Dad... Traditions.
Grandfather went there, you did...
So did Bhaiyya... So how can I break
the traditions of this house?