I am Nameless,
Prefect of Leng Meng County
Please allow me
to fight this assassin
She is on His Majesty's
most wanted list
Now that she's here,
I will arrest her
The assassin and I have agreed
To fight one on one
Should I be unable to defeat her,
Please apprehend her
I seek your permission
Draw your sword!
Hail! Hail! Hail!
Make your move!
I die willingly
Make your move
Hail! Hail! Hail!
How swift thy sword!
I believe you and
Broken Sword also fought
And like your fight with Sky
It was not real
But rather it was
A battle in your minds
A fight to honor Flying Snow.
My master wishes you
to have his sword
Why?
Broken Sword and Flying Snow
are bound in life and death
They will never part,
nor will their swords
It is his dying wish
That you take his sword
for your mission
Sky, Flying Snow and Broken Sword
Sacrificed themselves
So you could be
within ten paces of me
All three gave you their lives
The best of friends
could not give more
Therefore you are
The most dangerous assassin of all
How did you uncover my plan?
The flames of these candles
Are disturbed by your murderous intent
All of you
Are willing to die for a cause
I am ashamed to say
I'm not that committed
Your Majesty has seen through our plan
If I had realized this sooner
I wouldn't have allowed you so close
A citizen of Qin would not do this
Who are you?
A man of Zhao
Your Qin soldiers killed my family
I wandered into Qin
And was adopted
I discovered my real identity
ten years ago
And set my heart on this plan
You've come to avenge Zhao
I see
I would like to know
If your special skill has a name
As Your Majesty guessed
There is only one crucial move
What is that?
"Death within Ten Paces."
A good name!
All my guards
are one hundred paces away
Outside the palace
You are within ten paces
It would seem
That today I am doomed
But I sense your hesitation
Your Majesty is perceptive
However
You too have underestimated someone.
Who?
Broken Sword
I needed to prove to them
That my sword was fast and accurate
Within ten paces
My sword strikes
with surgical precision
If it enters
at precise pressure points
It will not cause any fatal injury
If one of you would take a blow
Before witnesses,
we can fool the King
Such a blow is hardly child's play
How is Sky now?
Fully recovered
His trust in your sword
was extraordinary
The King's security is impenetrable
There was no other way
His Imperial Guards were useless
He should have died three years ago.
What went wrong?
I abandoned the plan
The King must not be killed
He said that?
Yes
Why?
I also asked him
What did he say?
He would not explain that day
Broken Sword is the strongest
of the three
He and I are probably equal in skills
What he told me later
Greatly unsettled me
While I'm alive
I will stop you
from assassinating the King
I will help you
He let the opportunity go by
This time, we must succeed
I'll see you tomorrow
at the Qin camp
Please do me a favor
Help me fight Broken Sword!
Master!
What are you waiting for?
Although I had agreed to help her
Attack from behind is dishonorable
So I couldn't draw my sword
But we both knew
If we did not stop Broken Sword
We would never succeed
Moon, don't!
You're no match for him. Stop
I knew this would happen
You can't stop me now
Even wounded, I would still stop you
Then I will kill you!
Did I hurt him too much?
Your special medicine
Should heal his wounds in a day
Have you delivered it?
I tended to the wound myself
After the battle, take my sword
And follow Nameless to see the King
Yes
They won't treat a servant harshly
If the assassination succeeds
Wave a red flag on your return
If it fails, a yellow one
If something happens to you
my message will be useless
I will smile from Heaven
If I see a red flag
How is Flying Snow?
She is resting
She doesn't know I've come
You said you would stop me
Please abandon the mission
You know I'm a man of Zhao
So am I
Doesn't Qin want to conquer Zhao?
Yes
Isn't the King the enemy of Zhao?
Who are you trying to defend?
You call yourself a man of Zhao?
Flying Snow has asked me that too
When we first met
I was living a carefree life
She is the daughter of a Zhao general
Who died in battle against Qin
She inherited his sword
She wanted to avenge her father
I promised to help her
Calligraphy and swordplay
Share the same principles
We did calligraphy to
inspire our swordplay
And to heighten our powers
She knew I'd drifted since childhood
Calling no place home
Once we had killed the King,
She said she would
take me to her home
We would be swordsmen no more
Only a man
And a woman
The essence of calligraphy
is from the soul
Swordsmanship is the same
Both aspire to truth and simplicity
Gradually I recognized a greater cause
Three years ago
we perfected our skills
Flying Snow insisted on going ahead
Together, we stormed the palace
She asked why I had
abandoned the mission
I told her the King must not be killed
That is what calligraphy taught me
I didn't kill the King
After that she refused to talk to me
Please abandon your plan
No
Was your sword forged in hatred?
Yes
For ten years,
that hatred has never died
I can't stop now
How can I dissuade you?
Only by killing me
Are you that determined?
Yes
Allow me to convey my conviction
In three words
These words express my heart
Please consider
Moon, give my sword to Master Nameless
Flying Snow and I will never part
Neither will our swords
Master Nameless
Though I am just a humble servant
Allow me to say a few words
I have been with my master
since I was eight
He taught me martial arts
And how to be a decent person
Whatever my master does
Is for a good reason
The words he has given you
Carry a deep meaning
Master Nameless,
please take his advice
What were the words he wrote?
"All under Heaven."
All under Heaven...
Broken Sword said
"The people have suffered
years of warfare"
"Only the King of Qin
can stop the chaos"
"By uniting all under Heaven."
He asked me
to abandon the assassination
For the greater good of all
He said,
"One person's suffering is nothing"
"Compared to the suffering of many"
"The rivalry
of Qin and Zhao is trivial"
"Compared to the greater cause"
The person who really understands me
Is my most feared enemy
Alone, I have endured so much criticism
So many attempts on my life
No one understands my intentions
Even my court officials
See me as a tyrant
But I never imagined
That Broken Sword, my arch-enemy
Would truly understand
And appreciate my real motives
I would like to know
How you mean to kill me
without your sword?
By capturing yours!
This sword has protected me
Through all my battles
Having found a true confidant
in Broken Sword
If I die, I am content with my life
Let "All under Heaven"
Guide your decision
It just dawned on me!
This scroll of Broken Sword's
Isn't about sword technique
But about swordsmanship's
ultimate ideal
Swordsmanship's first achievement
Is the unity of man and sword
Once this unity is attained
Even a blade of grass can be a weapon
The second achievement is when
The sword exists in one's heart
When absent from one's hand
One can strike an enemy
at a hundred paces
Even with bare hands
Swordsmanship's ultimate achievement
Is the absence of the sword
in both hand and heart
The swordsman is at peace
With the rest of the world
He vows not to kill
And to bring peace to mankind
Your Majesty,
your visions have convinced me
That you are committed
to the highest ideal
Of ultimate swordsmanship
Therefore I cannot kill you
Remember those who gave their lives
For the highest ideal:
peace with no more killing
Nameless went to within ten paces
of the King
He could not have failed
There is only one explanation
He must have abandoned the mission
What did you say to him?
I wrote three words
What words?
"All under Heaven."
That is all you care about!
And you
I don't believe you
How can I convince you?
Draw your sword
You've misled Nameless
You've ruined Sky
and the Kingdom of Zhao
Draw!
When we first met...
I had to prove myself to convince you
What can I do this time?
Just draw your sword!
Why didn't you fend off my sword?
So that you'd believe me
I always wanted to go home with you
Sadly, it won't happen now
Take good care of yourself
Why didn't you defend yourself?
Why didn't you?
No more drifting, no more roaming
I'm taking you home now
Our home
Your Majesty, permission to execute?
Permission to execute?
He conspired
to assassinate Your Majesty
Show no mercy!
This is the law of Qin!
To conquer all under Heaven
The law must be enforced
Set an example for the world!
Execute him! Execute him!
Execute him!
Hail! Hail! Hail!
Nameless was executed an assassin
but buried a hero...
Sky gave up his sword
in honor of his fallen friends...
In 221 B.C., the King of Qin
conquered all six kingdoms
and unified China.
He ceased all expeditions
and built the Great Wall
to protect his subjects
from the Northern Tribes.
The Qin Empire became the first
dynasty of China...
And Qin Shihuang...
the First Emperor.