Hey Rahul!
Want to be friends?
She's just like her
father. Isn't she?
Tina's very critical Rahul.
She doesn't have much time.
We tried our best.
She had severe internal bleeding.
We couldn't do anything.
She knew there would be
complications in her delivery.
She also knew how much you
wanted this child.
She loved this baby more
than her life.
I want my daughterto now me.
Who her motherwas,
what she was like.
I want herto be able to answer
all these questions herself.
I am leaving these 8 letters
for her...
...1 each of her 1st
8 birthdays.
These letters have everything
that I want to tell my daughter
These letters are going
to be her memories.
You are very bad.
Rahul, Want to be friends?
Promise me you will never cry.
Anyways, you look very bad
when you cry.
Also promise me that...
...you'll name our daughter
Anjali.
I am sorry Rahul.
I am really sorry.
Don't go.
Promise me you'll name
our daughter Anjali.
Hi! I am Anjali...
...and you're watching
channel Anjali.
I am going to grow up
and be a V. J...
...you know just like
Neelam.
Hey cut cut cut.
Ooops I'll be back
afterthe break.
My hobbies are eating
chocolates...
...beating up boys,
irritating granny...
...and reading mom's letters.
Hey I'm late.
I have to get ready and
go to meet papa.
Watch me.
Hi, Anjali, listen to me.
Look.
Look... I'm only...
...2 hours late.
Right.
- Okay. Sorry. I was busy.
So was I.
I haven't even watched
television today...
...because I had to come
to do your shopping.
I can't handle everything.
I'm your daughter not yourwife.
Why?
Lf I can be both your dad
and mom...
...why can't you be both...
Okay.
What?
- Felt bad?
A bit.
Sorry
- Okay.
That is why one says...
...there is only one god
in many forms.
No matterwhat form,
he knows our devotion.
It is important to keep
this bond with god.
She speaks so well, doesn't she?
So, that's all fortoday
Now we'll have...
I got this gift for
St. Valentine's day
Rupa!
- Me?
Rupa will chant the
divine hymn.
Me?
Chant Rupa.
The divine hymn...
I forgot it.
What?
What are you saying Rupa?!
Can you believe that sisters?
She has forgotten the divine hymn.
My dear if you don't pay
attention to prayer...
...what will you teach
your children.
The way we think and
the things we say...
...have a deep impact
on our children.
Granny.
Speaking of children...
Namaste. Hi! Sexy.
Who taught you that?
- Papa.
Go get ready for your
School function.
Granny... the letter.
When is your birthday?
- Tomorrow.
Come on, hurry up.
Yes, there are our seats.
- Come sit.
Come Mr. Khanna, sit.
Good evening ladies
and gentlemen.
Welcome to the Just
one-minute competition.
It's a strange competition. Children
have to talk on the stage...
...and the topic is given right
there in some strange bowl.
On the spot sir, on the spot.
Stop it Balbir, control yourself.
- Never mind. It's ok.
Every student will be given only
one minute. Just one minute.
Just One Minute?
Only one minute to speak?
Exactly. Very unfair.
But yet ourJassu wins
every year.
She's so talented you know.
Best of luck Jaswinder.
- Same to you.
OurJaswinder is the best.
Actually Anjali is also
taking part.
She'll come second.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
- Oh welcome!
Our first contestant is
Jaswinder Singh.
Oh! My sweetheart.
My topic is Prayer.
Every morning we pray
to the lord.
Papa says prayers will
keep god happy...
...and he will protect us.
Mummy says that by praying
Grandma will get impressed...
...and will leave the big
house for us in the will.
Prayer... yes, my favourite
actress's name is Puja...
...and even my best friend's
name is Puja.
Wow! My daughter is
the best.
Next we have Anjali Khanna.
Pick yourtopic.
Second!
Yourtimer starts now.
Say!
Mother!
I am sorry.
Mother...
A mother is someone
who loves us so much...
...that we sometimes can't
understand it.
A mother is someone who makes
us realise how good we are...
...there is no one better
than us.
Her happiness is in our
laughter...
...and sorrow in our
sorrow.
She is someone we can't
live without...
...she is everything.
Only we don't have her.
But we have papa, and
he is quite nice too.
Then you give me a hug.
That's number one!
Rahul, you remember
Mr. Shama? He had phoned.
Who?
Our neighbour in Delhi.
He has sent a proposal.
Forwhom?
Me.
Shut up.
He said the girl is
sweet and beautiful...
...but I refused flatly.
I did the right thing, didn't I?
- Yes.
I did the right thing?
I was right?
Yes mom.
Well I must have done
the right thing.
I never do anything wrong.
So what if the girl is
sweet and beautiful.
Everyone is beautiful these days.
Who wants to get married?
Mr. Sharma has gone mad.
Keeps sending me proposals.
Why doesn't he get himself married
and just leave me alone.
What's wrong mom?
I just find this family
incomplete.
Why? You are there.
L'am there...
...Anjali is there, I don't
find it incomplete.
When I go out with my
friends...
...they all complain about
their daughters-in-law.
I can't even do that.
This is a big problem.
So you need a daughter-in-law
to complain about.
No son.
I just want you to be happy.
I am happy mom.
So you won't marry again?
Mom, we live once, die once,
get married once...
...and love once.
We don't do these again.
You are fine, but what
of Anjali.
Why? What's happened to her?
You don't feel she needs
a mother?
She's okay.
She's just fine.
She's got something which
even I don't have.
Her mother's letters.
Happy Birthday Anjali.
My dear, Anjali.
You are 8 years old today.
I'm sure you look just
like your dad.
That same smile, those
same eyes.
No. I look like you.
Does your father still go
Old habits die-hard.
Today you are a big girl and
you will be able to understand...
...what I have to tell you.
Today, I will tell you a story...
...about your father, me and
Anjali.
Anjali?
You're late again.
Can't wake up so early.
Can't wake up orwere
you scared.
Rahul Khanna is never
scared.
But loses to Anjali Sharma
everyday in Basketball.
Don't want to play?
What's the point, you
will lose again.
I won't lose today.
- You say that everyday.
We'll see.
If you can't play
atleast don't cheat.
Don't call me a cheater.
Anjali, don't call me
a cheater.
Rahul is a cheater
He is a cheater, cheater.
I am not a cheater.
- Cheater.
Stop screaming like a girl.
- Hey! Don't call me a girl.
You're right, you're not a girl.
Atleast betterthan those
girls you run after.
Excuse me! I don't run after
them, they run after me.
Wow! Rahul's so cute.
- Yes.
He's so sweet, he's so
handsome.
Not as handsome as you,
you have a better moustache.
Was that a joke?
- What if it was?
I don't like jokes.
- I don't like you.
Shut up
Rahul and Anjali have
fought again.
Rahul and Anjali
have fought.
have fought again.
"What sort of a boy is this?"
"What sort of a girl is this?"
"What do I do with him?"
"What do I say to her?"
"He fights with me!"
"She irritates me!"
"He troubles me"
"She gets upset"
"He is crazy"
"She is crazy"
"But he is your best friend dear"
"But she is your best friend dear"
"Oh my! Oh my! This boy.
Oh my! Oh my!"
"Why does he play these pranks?
Ask him please, why"
"Sometime he fights with me,
sometime he quarrels with me"
"Stay away from him"
"This boy is crazy"
"Crazy... Crazy..."
"Oh my! Oh my! This girl
Oh my! Oh my!"
"Why does she play these pranks?
Ask her please, why"
"Sometimes she fights with me"
"Sometimes she irritates"
"Trouble her, but only
from a distance"
"This girl is crazy.
Crazy... Crazy..."
"Only she understands
what she says"
"No one else can
figure that out"
"She's like this
and she's like that"
"No one can figure her out"
"So run for your life,
she is surely upto some mischief"
"This girl is crazy.
Crazy... Crazy..."
"This boy is crazy.
"He teases us
as he comes by"
"He does not listen"
"Look, look, he is crazy
beware of him"
"He is weird and yet
he is dearto me"
"This boy is crazy.
Crazy... Crazy..."
"This girl is crazy.
Oh God! Just look at
this room. Filthy.
These girls will drive
me crazy.
Hey! What is this mountain
on your head?
These are rollers, Rifat bi
Rollers don't impress boys.
You can take that from me.
Then how do they get impressed,
Rifat bi.
Oh god! What are you wearing?
Come on tell us.
- I don't know.
Tell us please.
- No!
Tell us.
Okay! Boys get impressed by
a girl's mannerisms...
...herwalk, hertalk
And?
And I don't know.
You girls talk to much.
Come on, clean up this mess.
God! What do I do with
this girl, Anjali, what is this?
What are you wearing?
Lt's cool Rifat bi.
Cool? Try to be feminine once
in a while atleast.
Not like them but...
Rifat bi, you say the
same thing everyday.
You know, I beat Rahul
in basketball again.
Stay away from that boy.
Why? He is my best friend.
He is my buddy.
When best friend becomes
boy friend...
- one doesn't even get to know.
- Rahul? Please.
Yes, yes. I know all about that.
Here I've got you some pudding.
Don't tell anyone.
Oh! Thank you Rifat bi.
- Leave me, mad girl.
No short skirts in the
college please.
Good morning Ms. Briganza.
Good morning boys,
Nice colour Piyush.
L'll complain to your
parents that...
...you wear short skirts to
college in orderto excite the boys.
Excuse me!
I said no short skirts
in college please.
Oh! Ms. Briganza.
You said something Malhotra?
Oh! I was just saying, that short
skirts are not allowed in college.
What? But this is the
latest fashion...
...infact, some girls don't
even wear skirts these days.
Don't tell me Ms. Briganza.
- Yes!
And am I not looking
nice today?
You're very queet. Queet?
Cute.
You're very cute.
But if you expose like this,
then these youngsters...
What do you mean by these youngsters.
Am I not young?
You're... young. Very young.
But you wear very boring
clothes.
I Know. Till Mrs. Malhotra
was alive...
...I would occasionally wear
fancy clothes.
Really?
But now there is no point.
- What do you mean?
Mr. Malhotra... Ms. Briganza...
Mrs. Malhotra.
Happy friendship day.
Sharma. Always scaring me.
What are you doing now.
- It's a friendship band sir.
Besides being your student,
I am also your friend now.
Oh! Good!
Sir, you look very happy today.
What do you mean?
- Just generally.
Oh! Generally. Well, my daughter
is coming home today.
Your daughter?
- Tina.
- She is coming back from London.
- From London?
She was studying at
Oxford University.
Oxford University?
We used to all live there.
But when Mrs. Malhotra died,
I couldn't stay there anymore.
- So I came back to my country.
- Tina didn't come back with you?
No. She had to finish
her education.
But I miss her, so I told her
to complete her final year...
...in our college, after all
we are no less than Oxford.
Yes Sir!
You'll take care of Tina, won't you?
- Of course sir.
Happy friendship day.
- Thank you sir.
Who? Rahul?
Yes! I'm the first girl forwhom
Rahul has tied a friendship band.
Isn't it exciting.
- Of course.
You know I am tying a friendship
band only for you.
Really Rahul?
- Really Sonia.
That is because you're the
nicest...
...and most beautiful girl
I've known.
Really Rahul?
- Really Sonia.
Oh Rahul! You are telling
the truth, aren't you?
Really Tanya.
- My name's Sonia.
See! I got so lost in
your eyes, I forgot your name.
I just can't believe this Rahul.
- Trust me.
Oh Rahul!
- Oh Sonia!
These fell off.
- You cheat, you liar.
Hey come on... Tanya...
What's your name?
Sonia.
- Go away! Wasted my half-hour.
You don't get tired running
afterthese stupid girls.
Hey! I don't run after...
I know. Can't you find one girl
with beauty and brains?
Beauty and brains?
Where will I find
such a girl?
I'm only passing my time with these
girls. I haven't found her as yet.
Her?
Her.
I'm looking for a girl who
makes something happen.
Makes what happen?
Makes something happen
in my heart.
Makes what happen?
Something happens.
You won't understand.
When she walks, the
world looks on.
And when she stops, time stops.
And when she smiles...
She, she, she. What will you
do when you find her?
What will I do?
- Yes.
L'll kneel down in front of
her, spread my arms and say...
...Hey! Whoever you are...
I love you.
- Sorry?
Don't be. I love you.
Excuse me.
Tina!
Tina.
Hi! I'm Anjali and you are...
Rahul.
Tina! Right?
- How do you know?
This morning the principal...
Ya! Ya! Don't take that old slob's
name first thing in the morning.
So Tina! Your first day in
college?
Yes. She just got back from London.
- How do you know?
Rahul, this morning the
principal...
I just told you not to talk
about that baldy.
Baldy!
- So Tina...
- Where were you studying in London?
- Oxford University.
Ox... How do you know?
Rahul, this morning the
principal...
Yeah! Yeah! Let the
Baldy be.
We have this grouch of
a Principal. She's his fan.
Grouch?
- Grouch is right. But forget him.
Tell me how is your
first day in college?
Great.
Good morning Archana.
Feroze... cut your hair.
Short skirt... Oh god.
There's groucho.
Morning Sir.
Short skirts are not allowed
in college, you know that?
You know I just got back
from London...
...and haven't had the time
to unpack.
Sir, it's Tina's first day here,
she's just gotten back...
...from London and hasn't had
the time to unpack.
- She wore whatever she could find.
- And how do you know that?
Sir, I've known Tina
since childhood.
Since childhood? Really?
Really Papa.
- Really Pa... Papa?
Mr. Malhotra I need you here.
Not there sir, in the
staff room.
He's an old slob, a baldy,
and a g...
Great? Good?
Grouch. But he's not
all that bad.
Happy friendship day.
We've only just met,
friendship is a farthought.
So... something happened?
No, she's not my sort.
- Why?
She's not Indian enough.
She's born and brought up in England.
And these London returns
are little weird.
A girl should be one you can
take home to your mother.
No. She's not my type.
She's not my type.
You won't find anyone this way.
Why? You're there.
Me? Just shut up.
If I don't find anyone else,
I'll marry you.
See. Anyway no one will
marry you.
Here, this is for you.
What's this?
This is our college sweatshirt.
Cool?
Thanks.
Anjali... May I ask you something?
Sure.
Why is everyone staring at me?
Why the boys are staring,
you know!
And the girls are wondering
what the boys are staring at...
...and that is why even they
are staring at you.
And look if you have any
problems...
...just come to me or
to Rahul.
Rahul? The one who yesterday...
Yeah! He's my best friend and
we sort of rule this college.
This is Rahul.
We have a rule in this college.
We make every newcomer sing.
You know Do Re Me...
Rahul, she's the principal's
daughter.
So! We can't break our rules
for anyone. Right?
But Rahul?
- Shut up,
You have to sing a song for us,
forthis college, in Hindi.
Hindi?
Why you forgot how to speak
Hindi in London, is it?
Sorry! One minute.
Rahul how can she sing
a Hindi song?
Why? She's the principal's
daughter.
If he can't teach her
then how will he teach us...
...and you shut up.
So, Tina, you will sing
a song in Hindi...
...and fast because we don't
have much time. Right?
Living in London and studying
and growing up there...
...has not made me forget
my roots...
...and you don't forget that.
Hey! You're sitting in my place.
- Oh! I'm sorry.
No it's okay. Hey Adi move.
Good morning class.
Good morning Ms. Briganza.
Today we are going to start
a new lesson - Romeo & Juliet.
An eternal love story.
Before we begin, I want to
ask you all ...
...What is Love?
Tina? You tell us,
What is love?
Me? I don't know.
You tell us, what is love?
Love?
Anyone?
Rahul... What is love?
Love is friendship.
If she can't be my best friend,
I can't be in love with her.
Without friendship there is no love.
Love is friendship.
Thank you for sharing
that with us Rahul.
Love is friendship.
So! Want to be friends?
Oh my head! My feet.
Oh Sorry Mr. Malhotra,
Ms. Briganza here.
I hope I didn't disturb you...
...and even if I did
I'm sure you don't mind.
Of course not Ms. Briganza.
I called to tell you that
the rehearsals are complete...
...and our college will
come first tomorrow.
Rest of the teams don't stand
a chance. You know what I mean.
This is all because of
you Ms. Briganza.
And it's all for you Malhotra.
Really Ms. Briganza?
Really Malhotra.
Oh Ms. Briganza.
Oh! I have fallen.
And the next college is
our college... St. Xavier's.
What! Oh my god.
They can't make it?
Ms. Briganza, there is a
curfew in their area...
...and they can't leave.
Now what do we do?
Mr. Malhotra let me think
please. Idea...
Idea.
You have to do this or else
you both are going to fail.
Bur Sir, how can we sing and dance.
We don't know anything.
You know these students,
they will skin us alive.
Of course it's a good idea.
Nothing will happen to you.
The students who were
going to perform today...
...have recorded a tape of
their rehearsals.
L'll play that tape and
you just have to move your lips.
Like in the films. Okay.
It won't work.
What do you mean it won't
work. Of course it will work.
My name is Chin Chin Chu
Moonlit sky, you and me,
Hello Mr. How do you do?
Anjali, you don't have any concern
forthe reputation of your college?
Come on Rahul, it is for
the college.
Come on, help us Tina.
- No, I'm not coming.
What are you saying?
Why are you asking her?
Let's go.
What do I play?
This must be it.
"You are a foreigner,
You are a foreigner,
You won't be here with us
for long..."
Looks like, I have put the
wrong tape.
"I found someone"
"I found someone?"
"What's come over me?"
"Why do I feel so lost?"
"Either I was insane earlier
Or I've just become so."
"Dreamy eyes and unkempt hair,
What have you done to yourself."
"I found someone..."
"I've lost my heart..."
"What can I tell you my friends..."
"I am all shook up..."
"I've found someone..."
"I don't know
what's happened to me?"
"People have begun
calling me Romeo."
"And why is that so?
We should also know."
"What's happened to you?"
"Till yesterday I was
quite fine."
"My heart was filled with
happiness divine."
"Then why are you upset?
What are you disturbed about?"
"Have you lost something?"
"I have found someone..."
"Who is this disguised
as a cloud?"
"Who has come and taken
over my heart?"
"I would like to say it
but I can't name it."
"Don't name it but say
something."
"Give us a slight clue."
"It's in my eyes
It's in my heart"
"What can I tell you friends..."
"I've found someone..."
"I don't know what's happened to me"
"Why am I so lost"
"Either I was insane earlier
or I've become so now"
"Dreamy eyes and unkempt hair"
"What have you done
to yourself"
"I've found someone..."
"I've lost my heart..."
"What can I tell you my friends..."
"I'm all shook up..."
"I've found someone..."
Anjali, what's wrong?
Don't know why, I am
missing mom today.
How can you say this when
I am here for you?
Stupid, tears don't
solve anything.
Anjali how long have
you known Rahul?
From the first day at college.
You know what I did?
I defeated him in arm wrestling.
Eversince we've been
best friends.
Rahul is your best friend,
isn't it?
I am Rahul's best friend.
Aren't you in love with him?
Hi! Shall I go?
- Where?
Today's Tuesday...
Rahul goes to meet his
relatives every Tuesday.
But I'll stay if you want.
No, you go Rahul. You'll get late.
- I have some time.
No Rahul you'll be late,
go, go, bye!
God please see that I don't fail
in my exams this time as well
I am a bit weak in Chemistry.
So, you take care of it.
Hey! Look forward.
So, your relatives
stay here?
Yes, here... here... here...
So, Rahul Khanna comes
to the temple every Tuesday.
Yes.
- How sweet.
Why did you lie at college then?
Actually boys don't go to
the temple. So!
But you do...
- Yes.
You come every week?
How sweet...
- Don't call me sweet.
Actually my dad used
to say that...
...don't tell this to
anyone at college.
He says that a Man should
bow to 3 women...
...to mom-to one's mother,
to the Goddess Durga... and...
And?
- And...
Wear it. What do they say,
cool, you'll look cool.
I was just trying. Don't
know, how they wear all this.
There's nothing wrong in looking
girlish once in a while.
Here, your mother's letter.
You were missing her, weren't you?
And listen, take this too.
- What is this?
Present.
Hey Tina.
Rahul... what are you doing
here at this hour?
Actually I couldn't sleep and I
thought even you won't be asleep...
...and would be thinking of
me, so I came...
Do you like flowers or chocolates?
- What?
I haven't got either,
I was just curious...
Got chocolates too...
...don't you think
it's too hot out here?
Okay! Lf you insist.
Hey sit down... feel at home.
Isn't this the novel where the
butler murders the married couple?
Why are you wasting yourtime
reading such a thick book, ask me!
Rahul, you didn't finish
your story.
This couple goes on a holiday and
leave their butler behind...
Later one finds out the
butler is...
Not this story...
- Then?
The one you were telling me
at the temple
Which temple? I don't know
any temple.
The story about a man bowing to
three women...
...one's mother, the goddess
Durga, and...
- And?
- And...
Papa?
- Groucho...
Shut up. Rahul, papa's coming...
Congratulations.
- Shut up Rahul, go from here.
No... not from there,
go from there.
Rahul!
And.
L'll climb this ladder
and catch the culprit
What is it?
- Torch.
Throw it.
- Okay.
Groucho...
Who hit me?
A ghost! L'll become a ghost as well.
The ghost will also get scared of me.
Where has the ladder gone?
Malhotra!
Why are you sneaking into
your own house?
Rahul, what are you doing?
- I was on my way to see you.
Me? Why?
Hey look, a shooting star.
Where?
- Not down here, up there!
They say if you make a wish on a
shooting star, yourwish comes true.
You believe that?
- Let's try. Come on.
"You came close to me"
"Smiled ever so sweetly."
"You gave me dreams."
"These days my heart is neither
awake nor asleep"
"What should I do?
Somethings happen in my heart."
"Oh! What a feeling this is!"
"What is this unquenchable thirst?"
"I know not, this drunken stupor
of love that's consuming me?"
"No one knows, why one loses
one's peace, when in love"
"What should I do?
Somethings happen in my heart."
"My prayers have been answered"
"God knows when and how
I fell in love."
"I wonder how,
I found peace in turmoil."
"I sit alone, weaving memories."
"What should I do?
Somethings happen in my heart..."
Butler's the killer...
Hey! Look at that.
Hi guys! How do I look?
Just like Tina, right?
Here? Okay.
I'm mad, aren't I?
I wanted to look beautiful
like you...
...but I don't even know
how to.
You are beautiful, Anjali.
You're lying.
Didn't you hearthem
laughing?
Those people are...
...idiots like me.
Actually you're the most beautiful,
because you're very special.
Atleast you're not like those
girls, I keep running after.
You know, you can have
any boy you want.
Anyone?
- Anyone.
But he has to be cockeyed.
Where did you get this
lipstick?
L'll bash her nicely.
Love is strange,
love is weird.
It's unaware of happiness
and pain.
Papa
Rahul.
- Papa?
What papa?
You can't keep secrets from me.
But Rahul? Couldn't
you find anyone else?
Come on papa.
Actually, I would have felt
as bad...
...even if it were someone else.
Why?
Because I'll have to share
your love with him.
I love you papa.
That is the problem.
I love you too.
Have you told him as yet?
I just feel that Rahul
and Anjali...
Tina, Rahul only loves you...
...and Anjali is his best
friend, nothing else.
No papa.
Somewhere hidden in this
deep friendship is deep love...
...and I don't want to come
in the way of this love.
The whole college knows that...
...Rahul and Anjali are just
friends and nothing else.
Go tell him that you love him.
But I don't even know,
if he loves me.
Don't keep matters of the heart
a secret. Go and tell him.
I love you.
I really love you.
I neverthought I'd say
this to someone...
...but I really love you.
I hope I can get myself
to say this to her...
I wanted to say it to her
so often...
...but couldn't get the
courage...
...and whenever I meet her
I decide to, but... somehow...
Tell whom?
- Tina. Who else?
Let's do this again.
L'll be Rahul you be Tina.
I love you.
I love you too.
She'll say the same thing,
won't she?
Ya.
- Come here.
Shall I tell her?
Shall I go right now?
"O! My Lord, love comes with
so much pain"
"The heartfelt remains in
the heart..."
"and does not escape from
one's lips"
My first love is incomplete Rifat bi.
My first love is incomplete.
I love you.
"You did not remember me,
there's nothing more left to say"
"The heart cried and the eyes welled up
There's nothing more left to say"
"You did not remember me
there's nothing more left to say"
"The heart cried and the eyes welled up
There's nothing more left to say"
Mother!
"I gave you all my joys,
gave you all my smiles"
"Your locks enticed me, bidding
messages of faithfulness"
"You couldn't care for my love.
There is nothing more left to say"
"You did not remember me
there's nothing more left to say"
Anjali... Anjali.
Rahul you look ahead,
I'll look there.
Anjali... Anjali...
One minute.
Where are you off to?
Home.
- What?
I got a letter from mom.
My father's not well...
...and there is lots of work
in the new house.
Have you gone mad? You got
a letter and you're leaving?
You're not going anywhere.
- Rahul, I have to go.
How can you go in the middle
of the term?
Rahul please...
- Go afterthis semester.
Rahul I have to go.
- You can go afterthe final exams.
Rahul I might not come back
even forthe final exams.
I'm not coming back Rahul.
You are leaving college,
leaving me...
...and you didn't even tell
me about it.
Rahul please...
- I don't want to know.
Rahul I'm going.
- So go.
Rahul I'm not coming back.
- I don't care.
Anjali don't go.
Who'll I play basketball with?
You used to lose everyday, anyways.
But why are you going?
My parents need me...
- And I don't?
Now you irritate Tina. You've
bothered me enough.
L'll fail.
- Then fail.
Anjali...
Stop chasing those stupid
girls now.
L'll miss you Anjali.
- L'll miss you too.
That day I realised that
perhaps...
...I had come between
Rahul and Anjali.
Perhaps, I had come between
two friends...
Anjali's silence told me
everything.
And that day I was sure...
...that she loved your father.
Perhaps even I couldn't
love him as much.
Anjali neither called norwrote.
She had gone away from
our lives. Forever.
Yes. I became his friend but
could never be his best friend.
Your father is alone now
but won't say anything.
He needs a friend, he needs
love...
that friend is Anjali,
that love is Anjali.
Get Anjali back into
your father's life.
Return Anjali her first love.
Anjali and Rahul are made
for each other.
This is the truth and
this is my dream.
Will you fulfil your mother's dream?
Get Anjali back in Rahul's life.
Get Anjali back in your
father's life.
Make my dream come true.