- Dr. Snow?
- Yes?
- Dr. Bartholomew Snow?
- Yes.
General Pratt would like
a word with you.
- General Pratt?
- Yes, sir. On official business.
- Well, Dr. Snow?
- Yes.
My identification.
Forgive the unorthodox approach.
Can't be overheard here.
National Security Agency?
We're just two friends who
stopped to chat in the park.
Five years ago you treated
a scientist, Arthur Vincenti.
- Arthur Vincenti?
- A Theoretical Physicist.
Arthur Vincenti. Yes.
Neurotic symptoms. Deeply disturbed,
responded well to treatment.
- Yes, I remember.
- Correct.
Vincenti is working for the Government.
An extremely sensitive position.
He need your help again.
Urgently.
Anything I can do, of course.
Send him around.
That's the trouble, I can't.
I have to take you to him.
- Where is he?
- That's classified information.
Top secret.
I'm all for security, General,
but I can't treat a patient
- even a top secret patient...
without knowing where he is.
That's what I must ask you to do.
To put yourself in my hands
and come into this blindfolded.
- This is unusual...
- Good, I was sure you'd cooperate.
What about my practice?
I have patients...
We want you to continue
in your normal routine.
We don't want to call attention to you.
We'll preempt some of your evenings.
Mr. Barker will be your contact.
He'll call for you at your house at six.
- Tonight.
- That's right.
I'm sorry,
I have an important engagement.
- Personal matter.
- Cancel it.
Nothing is as important as this.
Six sharp.
Wear a black tie,
as if you were going to a party.
Makes good cover.
Grateful to you, Doctor.
And not a word to anyone.
Our security must be air-tight,
a work of art.
Yes, General.
One more thing:
call me George.
Yes, George.
Miss Farrington's line
is still busy, Doctor.
- Thanks.
- And I wish
when you want one old file,
you'd ask me
- instead of just taking it.
- This one's reactivated, I'll keep it.
- And keep trying Miss Farrington.
- Yes, Doctor.
I beg your pardon. I mu... must have
come in through the wrong door.
I wanted to make an appointment.
My name's Fitzpatrick.
- Miss Smith.
- This way, Mr. Fitzpatrick.
Miss Farrington is on one.
Hello, Pam.
Look...
I won't be able to make it tonight.
I know we were supposed
to announce our engagement...
It's an emergency.
What?
I'm not trying to back out.
I have the ring right here.
Pam, I tell you I just can't.
It's a military secret.
No, it's not a ridiculous excuse.
No, there's not another woman.
Why have we always to get
into these shouting matches?
All right, call the newspapers.
All right, your mother warned you.
She said you were a Bluebeard.
She said you were nuts,
like all the psychiatrists.
She said what?
She said all the psychiatrists
are nuts?
Let me tell you something
about your mother.
Congratulations.
I wondered how you were going
to get out of that one.
You'll like Mr. Fitzpatrick.
Typical Madison Avenue syndrome.
- I'll make the diagnosis.
- Yes, Doctor.
Smitty, I've told you 50 times
to throwthose photos away.
Why do you want to keep them?
I'm sentimental, that's all.
I don't know where we're going,
but I like to see where we've been.
Shall I return the ring
to Tiffany's again?
No, I'll return it myself.
You're getting
a lot of mileage out of it.
Miss Smith,
just because I've suffered
several disappointments,
you have the impression
that I am emotionally shallow.
On the contrary.
It's precisely
the warmth of my emotions
that causes these difficulties...
Mine is a tender spirit,
eager for love,
easily wounded.
Yes, Doctor.
Don't bleed on the rug.
- You wanna make a statement?
- No.
Doc, give yourself a break.
In the column tomorrow
Penelope Peek will say you're a Bluebeard!
- A Bluebeard?
- What kind of a doctor acts like this?
- I couldn't care less.
- Don't, Doc!
I'm trying to do you a favor... Doc!
- Are we being followed?
- Probably not,
but the General
always goes on that assumption.
Right on time.
Enjoy your ride?
Yeah, all three of 'em.
Sorry, Doctor.
In this business no one knows
any more than he has to.
Barker doesn't know
where the plane's going.
The pilot doesn't know
where we go after we land.
Only one person knows it all, me.
Security.
The Russians must be anxious
to get their hands on Vincenti.
Who said anything about Russians?
They already have
good men in this field.
Then why all the...?
What's the most valuable commodity
in the word today?
Brains.
The Arthur Vincenti kind of brains.
Every country in the world
competing for them.
Sooner or later someone was bound
to smell money in it. Big money.
We're up against
an International black market in brains.
Not political, in the usual sense,
but a business enterprise.
Scientific geniuses bought,
sold, traded,
and if necessary, kidnapped.
We learned about it
a few months ago
and they offered us a Russian
biological warfare expert
for a million dollars in gold.
- You bought?
- Last year's model.
Our people weren't interested.
We've been tipped off
that the next target is Arthur Vincenti.
In his present mental state,
he'd be a natural for them.
Can't be much of a market
if the Russians don't want him.
Whoever tipped us off didn't want
the Red Chinese to have him.
- Are you saying...?
- I'm not saying anything.
Except that it's a more complicated world
than some people think.
Especially in our game.
It's going to be a long night.
Put your feet up
and get some sleep.
I intend to...
Above all, don't worry.
You reassure me.
How often I've told my patients
not to worry
in exactly the same tone
of ringing sincerity.
Captain Davis
of the Medical Corps.
- How do you do?
All right, Doctor.
Wait a minute, what...?
I didn't know you meant
this blindfold business literally.
I'm not likely to try to find
this place by myself.
We want to spare you the temptation.
Let's go.
- This way.
- Watch your head.
- Thanks.
- Watch your step.
Your notions of security puzzle me.
- Why?
- These people can see us.
Here's the car.
Step up six inches
and watch your head.
Sounds like a party!
Do you always tie knots
in cellophane?
That's a symptom of something?
All obsessive behavior
is symptomatic of something.
- Are you a psychiatrist, Captain...?
- Davis.
No, I'm an internist.
The General want a medical man
until a specialist could take over.
That's a bridge.
- Sorry, can't help playing detective.
- Very good.
We crossed
one of America's 50,000 rivers.
Somebody holding choir practice?
- Here we are.
- But where?
Obviously some place on the South.
You're the detective.
Let's call it Base X.
This way, Doctor.
- Is that an unlisted number?
- Yes. We can call out
but nobody calls in.
He's all yours, Doctor.
Hello, Arthur.
Arthur...
You know me, don't you, Arthur?
Yes.
I knowyou.
Dr. Bartholomew Snow.
Dr. Snow.
The famous psychiatrist.
The traitor!
Traitor!
- Put him on the bed.
- Let me go!
Wait! Let me go!
Let me go!
- Black, all right?
- Yes, fine.
There you have, Doctor.
We're the enemy.
His co-workers, me,
Captain Davis, now you.
He's security gone all haywire.
He's security turned
inside out, upside down.
He tried to destroy his own work.
Two years of priceless stuff.
Sedative's working.
He'll sleep now.
- Your coat.
- Thank you.
Here's what worries me.
Is it possible for all this
to operate in reverse?
If we're the enemy and
they should get hold of him
in his present state,
couldn't they brainwash him into
thinking they're his real friends?
It's possible.
We all need to trust in someone.
- They could reach him that way.
- Could you reach him first?
In time.
Given a regular course of treatment.
You've just talked yourself
out of a lot of sleep.
It'll be down
before we get back to New York.
At eight o'clock you're on that bridle path
for your usual ride.
What?
It's essential that there be no break
in your normal routine.
I don't care how many times
we have to come back here.
Why here?
Why not a military hospital?
Because all of this is illegal.
lllegal?
Vincenti's a civilian.
We have no right to restrain him.
If we want to commit him
to a hospital,
there's the whole routine
of medical boards, lawyers,
and the press might get wind of it.
Might even have to release him
and then our friends could grab 'im.
So for his own safety,
I grabbed him first.
Put out a cover story
that he'd gone fishing.
In law, I'm a kidnapper.
And I'm an accessory.
Here's to crime!
Good morning.
- Are you all right?
- Why didn't you blowyour horn?
You crossed right in front of me.
I couldn't avoid you.
Bicycle are not allowed
on the bridle path.
Horses shouldn't be allowed
Bridle paths are for horses.
Read the signs: no bicycles.
Keep out of this.
My knee...
It's probably broken.
Come on, break it up here.
What's the matter, Doc?
Can I help?
- No, thank you.
- Did you say doctor?
Yes, this is Dr. Bartholomew Snow.
If you're a doctor
don't stand there.
I'll have a look at it.
I'm not that kind of a doctor.
What are you, a horse doctor?
It doesn't seem to be broken.
I could recommend
a good Orthopedist.
I need a good lawyer.
You saw it, Officer.
He was speeding.
Failed to make the proper hand signal.
You did see it?
Yeah.
Ya oughta watch it.
I've noticed that in the last week
you fall asleep at the wheel.
I've been working nights lately.
What am I explaining to you for?
Who's this girl?
Vail, Victoria Vail,
the ballet dancer.
So you haven't heard of me.
But you will. You would have,
if you hadn't run over me!
I didn't run over you.
I'll never dance again.
A talent nipped in the bud.
Crippled for life.
- I'm terribly sorry.
- All because of you...
and that hay-burning hot rod.
Miss, please don't cry.
This is an emergency.
So that's an emergency.
Now, we'll look at that knee.
Excuse me...
I'm sorry.
It seems to work perfectly.
We must consider the possibility
that your symptoms
are psychosomatic.
I know what that means.
There's nothing wrong with the head.
The knee!
I can't fins anything wrong with it.
As a knee, I fins it
above criticism
in every way.
Mr. Barker is calling.
I'll take it in your office.
Excuse me, Miss Vail.
Excuse me.
Snow speaking.
Just a minute
he'd like to speak to you.
- Doctor?
- Yes, General.
Call me George,
the party's off for tonight.
I can use the sleep.
What's wrong?
Nothing serious.
Our friend took a little walk
after supper last night.
He escaped?
Not on the phone!
We found him
and he's back home.
We had to lull him to sleep.
We'll meet tomorrow
at the usual time.
All right, fine.
He thinks he's a General.
Nowthen, Miss Vail.
Miss Vail?
Where is she?
That's what I'd like to know.
Mr. Barker, please.
Just went out?
Have him call me the moment
he comes in. It's urgent.
This is Dr. Snow.
Thanks.
- Care to fill me in?
- I can't.
- I have to find that girl.
- Now, Doctor.
Nueva York is knee-deep in girls.
She said she was a ballet dancer
and she looked like one.
Broadway, the theatre and all that...
There's no Victoria Vail.
I need someone who knows that world.
What's the name of that creep I can't stand
and who works with Penelope?
- Lippy?
- Yeah, find him for me.
You must have it real bad this time.
A real exclusive.
Dr. Bluebeard's Number 7.
- But she said ballet.
- That's what took me so long finding her.
You want Victoria Vail,
be my guest.
Roger, we'll pick him up.
Doc, doc!
Make it quick, I've got a date
at the police station.
I would like to have
what you took out of my office.
You mean this?
No, you don't. This is evidence.
Evidence of what?
That you helped kidnap my brother.
- Your what?
- My brother.
Arthur Vincenti.
Why would I want to kidnap him?
To brainwash him, that's why.
Arthur called me last night.
Does that surprise you?
He said he was being held
by a bunch of spies.
Some phony general
and you, Dr. Snow.
Do you think the police would believe
such a ridiculous story?
So they didn't,
but now I've got proof.
You can't go to the police,
it would mean publicity.
Everything we're trying to avoid.
Let go of me.
- What goes on here?
- He assaulted me.
You nasty man!
Bluebeard, look over here.
A beauty!
- What goes on here?
- Nothing serious.
Our friend here had a drop too much.
- We'll see that he gets home all right.
- College reunion.
No, you don't.
He assaulted me
and I'm preferring charges.
Officer, do your duty.
- You want to make a formal charge?
- I certainly do.
He's an un-American activity.
Whatever you say.
- Wait!
- Come on.
You've gotta make up your mind.
Is he a sex maniac or is he a spy?
Both, and he broke my knee.
How did he break your knee?
He ran over me with this horse.
He ran over you with this...
Lady, this is Dr. Bartholomew Snow.
Everybody knows him.
The Commissioner's wife
is one of his patients.
You want me to book him?
- You ever hear of false arrest?
- He knows where my brother is.
We've got no evidence?
But you've got this file.
The Doctor explained
that he treated your brother 5 years ago.
But he hasn't explained
why some of these entries are fresh.
One of them was made today.
Yeah.
We talked to the Commanding Officer
at that Army Base.
He says this Arthur Vincenti
is off on a fishing trip.
He says lay off, everything is okay.
- But it's impossible.
- You heard the man.
- I'm sorry you were inconvenienced.
- Thanks.
Let's go, Miss Vincenti.
Thank you.
Dames...
- What'll they think of?
- Yeah.
But you know something?
The Doc was Iying, too.
Your coat, Miss Vincenti.
I hope you're reassured.
Arthur hates fishing.
Even in a rowboat he gets sick.
You don't believe the United States Army?
I believe that phone call form my brother.
And I'm going to do something about it.
What, for instance?
You're news, Dr. Bluebeard.
In this country we have a free press.
Boys!
Hold it, boys.
Hold it.
Let me tell them.
Gentlemen,
I wish to make an announcement
that Miss Vail and I
are engaged to be married.
¡No, es mentira!
¡No lo conozco de nada!
¡No le conozco!
¡No le había visto nunca!
Taxi!
- Can I drop you?
- Like a hot potato.
71 West Park.
It's real.
Why'd you pull a cockeyed stunt
like that?
I had to keep you from talking.
Then you kidnap him.
You don't really believe that, do you?
- But he called me.
- How did he sound?
Think about it.
Sort of mixed up.
He said he'd gotten away.
He was calling from some gas station.
He said you were after him.
He's in good hands,
that's all I can tell you.
- Then you have seen him?
- I'm treating him.
At the Army's request.
I can't say any more.
- Trust me.
- I do.
When you said we were engaged...
Such a cockeyed stunt.
A spy wouldn't pull
a cockeyed stunt like that.
- Would you?
- No.
Only a congenital idiot.
It'll be spread all over the papers.
Do you mind?
Publicity?
In show business? It never hurts.
Even for a ballet dancer?
Listen, Mister.
On the level I'm studying ballet.
I don't intend to spend
the rest of my life on a chorus line.
I trust you, Doctor,
but not that far.
Bluebeard, down.
Doctor?
Doctor.
We're here.
- Would you like to come up for a drink?
- Not your home, mine.
Wait here, will you?
- Well, good night.
- Goodnight.
- Are you sure that Arthur is all right?
- He's all right, believe me.
I'm stuck with believing you.
Let me.
The ring.
Bluebeard, what you need is
an adjustable engagement ring.
I guess you'll have to bring it
to me tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
I really ought to check up on that knee.
Sure.
Well.
Doctor.
My key.
Of all the cockeyed stunts!
Why'd you have to draw
all this attention to yourself?
Security.
You call this security,
Vincenti's sister?
It was the only thing I could do
to keep her from talking.
You didn't have to get engaged to her.
It's my behavior pattern.
I keep asking girls to marry me.
Other men feel compelled to drink,
gamble, get into fights.
- I get engaged.
- The engagement is off.
Break it at once!
That's an order.
- Yes, General.
- And don't call me that!
- Call me George!
- Yes, George.
Good afternoon.
Mr. Fitzpatrick.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Mr. Fitzpatrick.
Come in.
Make yourself comfortable.
- Do you mind if we record?
- No, no.
Then, we have
a little background here...
Sometimes it helps to say
the first that comes to your mind.
The first thing that comes to my mind
is that I'm keeping you up.
CIA.
You are clever.
That stutter of yours
sounds authentic.
It's authentic,
I used to stutter but I cured myself.
- Will power.
- You cured the symptom.
Laymen often make that mistake,
under strain you may stutter again.
I'm not here to discuss my symptoms.
I'm here to check on the disappearance
of the certain Vincenti.
You do know him?
I believe I once had a patient
by that name.
You say he disappeared?
He was kidnapped from his apartment,
near the base where he worked.
But that...
Where you about to say, Doctor,
that it wasn't a real kidnapping?
I was wondering
if he's disturbed
why he couldn't have just wandered off?
What gives you the impression
he's disturbed?
His medical history.
He was my patient.
Arthur Vincenti
today is completely sane.
And completely loyal.
Even fanatically so.
He'd resist any attempt
to make him talk
or to brainwash him.
Even a plausible attempt
carried out with in all innocence
by a reputable psychiatrist
such as yourself.
Are you accusing me
of brainwashing him?
I'm accusing you of being the key.
The innocent key with which the man
you know as the General,
hopes to open the closed mind
of Arthur Vincenti.
Shall we stop playing games,
where is Arthur Vincenti?
I don't know.
I even know how many trips
you've made to the place the General
calls Base X.
I understand the nature
of your dilemma.
Undoubtedly the General
showed you credentials,
but did you check them?
You can check mine. Here.
It's the CIA number in Washington.
My section Chief is Mr. Gilmore.
Call him.
What's the point calling?
I see no reason
to check your credentials.
Very well, if that's the way you
want to play it.
I'll be back tomorrow with the US Marshalls
and a warrant for your arrest.
Doctor,
when you're with the General
at the Base X,
better not mention my visit.
Once he learns we've made contact
with you, you'll be of no further use to him
alive.
Have a pleasant trip.
- Hello?
- Mr. Barker, please.
Hello?
Who is it?
Smitty!
Get me this number.
No, get it from the operator.
Get what?
The CIA. Central Intelligence Agency,
in Washington.
Yes, Doctor.
And this man showed you credentials
issued by this office?
That's what I'm trying to find out.
Do you have a James Fitzpatrick
in your Section?
I'm not authorized to give you
our information regarding our personnel.
Who is authorized?
Mr. Gilmore, but he's out.
Out of the office or out of town?
I'm not authorized to say.
Look,
can't you just tell me whether
or not you have a James Fitzpatrick
in your Section?
I'm sorry, I'm not authorized.
- Smitty.
- Yes, Doctor.
Get me the Military Intel...
No, the National Security Agency.
No, sir.
For security reasons keeps
no central file on personnel.
If you wish to communicate
with this General Pratt,
write him a letter.
I don't wish to communicate with him.
I'm meeting him this evening,
in an hour.
I want to know if General Pratt
is or is not with your Agency.
This is hardly a matter
that should be discussed on the phone.
I don't wish to discuss
any of your secrets.
I just want to know
if you know General Pratt.
If General Pratt exists.
I'm not authorized
- to give out that info.
- To give out that info.
- Is there anyone authorized?
- No, sir.
Is there anyone authorized
to authorize you?
Just one person.
Who is it?
The President of the United States,
if you'd care to call him.
Yes. What's his phone number?
Doctor.
Good evening.
All right, Doc.
No, no.
We're not getting anywhere.
- We're using the wrong technique.
- General.
Hold it.
You've accused Dr. Snow
of brainwashing you.
Do you think your own sister...
- General, I don't think...
- Don't interfere.
Is it true, Doctor?
Is Vicky going to marry you?
Yes.
I guess...
I can use a little help.
There you are, Doctor.
That's enough for now.
- Why are you stalling?
- Stalling, George?
Yes. We just made a breakthrough.
We could have reached him.
- Why you destroyed the connection?
- Because it had gone far enough.
The mind's a very delicate mechanism.
- You can't operate on it with a meat axe.
- It worked.
Vincenti accepts you because
he thinks you're engaged to his sister.
Can you imagine the traumatic effect when
he finds out the engagement's a phony?
What do you mean, phony?
- If I'm to break it off tomorrow...
- Break it off?
- Who said that?
- You did and said it was an order.
You'll do nothing of the sort.
You're engaged to the girl.
And that's an order!
No, thanks.
I have to meet somebody.
Sorry to interrupt your ride,
we won't keep you long.
I suppose these are US Marshals
and you're serving that warrant, huh?
Businessmen, like psychiatrists,
can't always tell the truth.
You're a businessman
and these are...
your board of directors?
These Homburgs?
These are my salesmen.
Sell him, gentlemen.
And that's just the opening pitch.
Where is Base X?
I don't know.
Fellows!
Doctor, any man
can be made to talk in time.
Where is Base X?
I knowyou've been taken there 5 times.
You don't think the General
fooled me for a minute?
He did better, he fooled me.
Every time he took me there
I was blindfolded.
- Blindfolded?
- That brought back the symptom, didn't it?
Mr. Fitzpatrick,
I couldn't tell you where Base X is
if my life depended on it.
Get him!
The Navy!
- What?
- The Navy!
Let's go!
Miss Vincenti...
Hey, come back!
- Forgive me, I'm terribly sorry.
- No. Never!
- Why do you want to do this thing to me?
- But I didn't...
No, fellas.
That's my fiancé.
No, please, fellas!
That's my fiancé. No.
Listen, darling,
maybe we should stick around.
No, that's all right.
No, we'll make out all right, fellows.
Listen.
Remember,
not a word to anybody, okay?
- You can always count on the Navy.
- Okay.
Take it away, James.
- Bye. Thanks, fellas.
- Bye.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye.
I ought to call the General.
May I use your telephone?
Sure.
Anyway, it's time you met the family.
Does your family know
about your brother?
I didn't want to worry them.
All they know is that we are engaged.
How are you going to explain all this?
Let's see. This could be icing.
We were pricing a wedding cake.
And fell in?
Come on.
Mama.
Oh, dottore, dottore.
I am so happy for my little girl.
- Zio, zio!
- Cosa c'è?
- Come quickly, see who's here.
- Va bene.
Mario!
A little wine?
We will have a drink to celebrate.
Aren't you going to ask
what happened to us?
In Italy I would ask.
In America I have learned
parents should be seen but not heard.
- Ma chi c'è?
- Doctor Snow.
Oh, Dr. Snow...
You do our family a great honor.
My uncle Michelangelo, the sculptor.
I'll get something for your face.
- Michelangelo? Any relation...?
- No, no. No relation. And no threat.
- For you.
- Thank you.
- Salute.
It is a shame Arturo is not here.
We are very proud of Arturo.
Arturo is a scientist.
I bring him from Italy myself
when he was just a little boy and now...
- He's an important man for the Government.
- We should not speak of this.
And this is my other son, Mario.
Dr. Snow.
- Hello, Mario.
- Hi, Dr. Snow.
Psychiatrist, huh?
- One of your patients slug you?
- You could put it that way.
I'd be interested to have your views
- on the merits of the post-Freudian schools.
- Mario!
Later.
Dr. Snow has to make a phone call.
- May I, please?
- For the new son of the house, of course.
I think Dr. Snowwants privacy.
Use the telephone in my studio, downstairs.
Very private, you know.
This is the first time
I've ever had this experience.
- What experience?
- Well...
When I meet a girl's family,
I feel an overwhelming compulsion to run.
- Not this time?
- No.
I wonder why.
Probably because
we're not really engaged.
There's the phone.
You see...
I hate to...
Here I am.
Your uncle's sculpture?
It's easy to guess who the model is.
What were you going to say?
I hate to play
such a dirty trick on your family.
I mean...
When they realize
the engagement's a phony...
Aren't you going to make your call?
Ah, yes.
I realize it's tough on you, too,
having to make this...
pretense.
- How long do we have to go on pretending?
- Till your brother's well again.
- Reception.
- Mr. Barker's room, please.
If it's for my brother...
And for your country.
- It's my duty as a citizen?
- The Stars and Stripes forever.
Oh, say, can you see.
Will you marry me?
- What?
George.
I have to talk to you right away.
35 years in the service.
I've seen foul-ups:
ordinary foul-ups, extraordinary foul-ups,
joint Army, Navy and Air Force foul-ups,
but this is the foul-up
to end all foul-ups.
I've checked with the CIA.
The real Fitzpatrick
is on his way to Singapore.
- Why didn't you tell me this?
- I thought maybe you were the phony.
I was the phony?
His credentials looked as good as yours.
I'm only human.
That's always the problem with security:
human beings.
- If we could just eliminate...
- People?
I guess that is asking too much.
Lipstick?
Mercurochrome.
Doctor, there's no way out.
- I'm gonna have to riff you.
- What's that mean?
Reduction in force.
Replace you.
You've become a liability
to the whole operation.
You might inadvertently give our enemies
the information they want:
the location of Base X.
But I don't even know it.
I even convinced Fitzpatrick I don't know it.
They know more than you think.
Every trip you've made to Base X,
your mind has stored up information.
- It's all there, in your subconscious.
- But what about my patient?
- Are you still indispensable?
- No...
Any competent man
could handle it now.
Got any ideas?
You know the qualifications.
Dr. Robert Burford of Bellevue.
You couldn't make a better choice.
Good. Barker'll drop by your office
and pick up the files.
Goodbye, Doctor.
We'll not meet again
and you have no further connection
with the case or the Vincenti family.
- What about my engagement.
- Break it now, tonight.
- Why?
- Do you want to endanger the girl?
- No, but couldn't I just tell her...?
- Tell her nothing.
The less anyone knows, the better.
Air-tight security. No holes anywhere.
Thank you.
- Everybody decent?
- If you call this "decent"...
Come in.
- Hi.
- What's the matter? Bad news?
- No.
- Good news.
- That's why you are laughing?
- I've been taken off your brother's case.
- This is good news?
For you and me. That's off too.
You mean
we're not engaged anymore?
It's no longer necessary.
- Nothing like freedom, I always say.
- So do I.
I suppose you want the ring back.
I've been thinking about it.
Why don't you keep it?
Keep it?
- Do you think I am a gold digger?
- No, I didn't mean...
You break our engagement
and try to give me an expensive ring.
- What am I to think?
- I don't mean I want to break it off.
- I was just trying...
- I knowwhat you're trying.
- Anyway, it's still stuck.
- Have you tried soap?
Soap? Is that what you used
on the others, Doctor?
- What others?
- "What others"?
One, two, three,
four, five, six fiancées.
You have a great deal in common
with a yo-yo.
- That's not fair. This is different.
- How is it different?
- Well...
- Here, pull.
- Take it easy. You'll get your ring back.
- I don't want it back.
It doesn't matter what you want.
You'll get one engagement ring.
You'll get it if you have to amputate...
- I hope it fits her better than me.
- Who?
- The new one, number eight.
- There is no number eight.
- Ha!
- What do you mean "Ha"?
- Just "Ha".
- Look.
There is no number eight.
They may never be a number eight.
And as far as I'm concerned,
there was no number seven, either.
- Good night, Miss Vincenti.
- Good night, Dr. Snow. And goodbye!
Nowyou tell me.
I think that's all, Dr. Burford.
It's time we left for the airport.
And remember, not a word to anyone.
Our security must be perfect,
a work of art.
Right, George.
I won't open my mouth.
Have you ever considered
of consulting a colleague?
I mean like having your head examined?
I agree with you, but there isn't
a damned thing I can do about it.
Dr. Snow's office.
Yes, he's here.
It's Dr. Burford.
Hello, Bob.
What?
Where?
I'll be right over.
You told me this business
was hush-hush.
I thought the General would want to know
why I didn't make it last night.
- Someone slugged you?
- No, nothing like that.
I slipped on a wet patch
coming out of my apartment house.
Couple of fellows helped me
and called an ambulance.
Did you knowthese fellas?
Never sawthem before.
I thought, in case the General called you...
He didn't.
- Maybe this wasn't an accident.
- What do you mean?
Were you carrying any papers?
Identification of any kind?
In my wallet, in my coat...
No wallet?
These fellas that helped you,
can you describe them?
I was pretty well out.
Ordinary fellows.
Dark suits. Well dressed.
Those hats, you know.
- Homburgs?
- Yes.
Not registered? Are you sure?
This is Mr. Nelson of FBI.
I see.
No, thank you.
The hotel has no record of any Mr. Barker.
Of course. When they riffed me,
they broke my contact.
Mr. Nelson,
I am not suffering from hallucinations.
You knowwho I am?
I do have some reputation
in my profession.
Yes, we knowwho you are.
- We're trying to check out your story.
- But there isn't time.
They wanted Dr. Burford's papers
so one of them could take this place.
They've probably
penetrated Base X by now.
And you have no clue
as to where this Base X is located?
I tell you I was blindfolded!
You're the FBI. Can't you
pick up the phone and call the NSA?
You've to get through to General Pratt
if he's still alive.
Or Mr. Barker or somebody!
You've got to find Base X!
Dr. Snow, on security matters,
even the FBI must go through channels
and with the proper authorization.
- I repeat, I'll check out your...
- Don't bother.
I'm beginning to think
even the FBI can't break through
this rubber curtain you call "security".
I'll find Base X.
You sit there and check out my story,
but I'll find Base X.
I've got it all up here,
in my subconscious.
Get me the Federal Aviation.
What's the matter with you?
Good afternoon, Dr. Snow.
Good afternoon, Mr...
Detective Second Grade Harrigan.
132nd Precinct.
Oh, yes.
The Lieutenant
wants to ask you some questions.
Like why Arthur Vincenti's landlady
says he didn't go on no fishing trip?
Where you been spending your evenings,
staying out until 3 or 4 am?
Don't tell me you're reviving
that ridiculous kidnapping charge.
Do you come quietly or
do I have to pull you in?
Do you mind if I change clothes first?
- No. We got all day.
- Maybe you have, but I haven't.
So this is where it all happens, huh?
The yak-kity-yak?
No, in there.
The couch, huh?
Imagine just Iying here and busting off
your trap to some perfect stranger.
Not me!
Why not you?
We all suffer from feelings of inadequacy.
To some extent.
That's for the birds, Doc.
I got no complaints.
Then why do you make a point
of referring to yourself
as Detective Second Grade Harrigan?
So I been stuck in Second Rate for 6 years.
You wanna know why?
That's easy.
Because you're such a stupid...
- Get the clothes, quick.
- Yes.
Let me guess...
You're the victim of a conspiracy.
How did you know?
Why don't you tell me about it?
I had a happy, normal
American childhood.
My old man used to beat me up
when he got a loan on.
You should've seen my old man.
He had a hand like a catcher's mitt.
Those were the days.
Putting the arm on the kids in school,
then putting the arm on me.
But I was the biggest
and pretty soon nobody
got to put the arm on me.
So I decided to go on the cops.
You thing I made the right decision?
Doc?
Doc!
Looking for someone?
Is your niece at home?
- Well, she is and she isn't.
- What?
The answer is no!
Dr. Snow, don't pay attention to her.
Move over.
- Who is that at the door?
- Nobody.
What a nice surprise!
Would you stay for supper? Risotto tonight.
- No, thanks, I just want to talk to Vicky.
- A lovers' quarrel, huh?
- You've come to kiss and make up.
- That's right.
I will not kiss and make up.
I'm not at home to Dr. Snow!
Please, I just want to talk to you.
- The human comedy always fascinates me.
- Listen.
Stand by the window.
The police are after me.
- On the level? What's the beef?
- Kidnapping.
Kidnapping, Miss Vincenti,
remember?
I hope they give you life.
I hope they give you the hot sit!
- Seat.
Miss Vincenti.
Vicky...
Will you listen to me, please?
They've found Base X.
Now, help me.
How do I know he's a crook?
He don't like no crook.
He flags me down.
I take him where he wants to go.
What's that make me, stupid?
The trouble with you is
you suffer from feelings of inadequacy,
so shut up and drive.
All right, thank you.
The FAA has no record
of any such flight plan.
But we have the average time
and the cruising speed of that plane.
Base X is somewhere
along that arc.
It's a start, anyway.
We've eliminated 44 states.
You forgot Alaska and Hawaii.
I think we've picked up
a little fuzz.
- I'll bet that's your friend Harrigan.
- It was a mistake.
You don't know him.
Hey!
Hey, Doc!
Back door.
- All made up? Friends again?
- Yes.
- You'll stay for supper.
- No, I'm very sorry.
We have an appointment.
Mario, please, answer the door.
Open up!
In the name of the law!
- Come on, hurry up.
- I'm caught!
Take it up with the Commissioner!
- Can I help you, sir?
- Out of my way, Small Fry.
The boy didn't do anything.
Doc!
Your pants!
You're under arrest, Doc!
Papa?
- And nowwhat?
- I don't know. Head south. Ask questions.
How do we get out of New York
with the police after us?
Why do you make
so many difficulties?
- I make difficulties?
- Wait.
What's the matter?
Those people, that party...
- What people?
- Those!
Those are geese.
- Geese?
- Geese.
Geese!
Geese, yeah, geese.
Pillars of the avian community.
Intelligent, hardy, resourceful...
Is it true that they follow definite flyways,
from north to south?
And vice versa.
Could you trace the point
where the flyway intersects with this arc?
I think so.
The Atlantic Flyway.
Yes, how often I've followed it...
It will intersect your arc here,
in Chattawottamie County,
the goose capital of America.
- Chatta... where?
- Chattawottamie County.
Chatta-wottamie County.
- Check the real estate agents?
- Real estate agents?
Yes, whatever you say.
But, may I ask why?
Because I'm trying to find a house.
If anyone knows houses in a district,
it's the real estate agents and get
a phone book for Chattawottamie County.
Meet me at the King Arthur Hotel
at the telephones.
Roger.
I think you should know
you're on the radio.
- Kidnapping. Also assaulting an Officer.
- Yes, I know.
Just as long as you know.
It's a Colonial house,
probably pre Civil War.
- It's approached by a plank bridge...
- It's on an island in a swamp...
Then there's a circular driveway.
The living room has a large red chandelier
and red willowwall paper.
But are you sure?
Thank you.
Are you sure
there's no such house?
- I want number 3-7-6...
- I see, thank you.
Hello? Hello?
Yep, this here's him.
- Big living room, a great grand glass...
- Operator, code number 3-7-6.
- Number 6-2-2-8-7-8-1.
- ...and it has a circular driveway.
You have?
Bingo, Doctor!
I think I've got it!
Just a minute, I'll put my boss on.
Mr. Yancey, of Turkey Crossing.
- Hello, Mister...
- Yancey.
Yancey?
I'm most anxious to see that house.
We're driving now,
we'll be there sometime tomorrow.
You'll be there?
Of course.
- Mr. Oz Yancey.
- Yes, thank you.
- Good luck.
- Oh, yeah.
- Where to?
- Jersey, where else?
- What's in the back?
- Dummies.
- A wiseguy, huh?
- No, no, no.
You think that...
No, my cargo is undie dummies.
I am Michelangelo Vincenti.
- And I am Leonardo Liebowitz.
- How do you do?
Okay, wiseguy.
Go ahead. Come on.
- I beg your pardon, Miss Vincenti.
- Don't mention it, Dr. Snow.
- I'm terribly sorry.
- That's all right.
Miss Vincenti,
I've been thinking...
- This matter of our engagement...?
- Please, Dr. Snow.
I'm only here because of my brother.
Our relationship is strictly business.
Yes, Miss Vincenti.
It's all yours.
I'll take the ferry back. Ciao.
- Good luck, Doctor.
- Ciao.
Buona fortuna.
Seven miles to Turkey Crossing.
Mr. Yancey?
Yancey.
Dead?
- Drunk.
- I'll make some coffee.
Mr. Yancey.
It will take hours
to bring him around.
Come on!
Look, someone made a little fire there.
The flare path.
This is where we landed.
- We've found it!
- We've found a place to start.
If the plane landed this way,
we went out...
that way.
- But I was blindfolded.
- My scarf.
- I'll drive.
- Good.
Go ahead.
If we're on the right road
we should cross that bridge soon.
One bridge coming up.
Now...
Look for a road on the right.
Somewhere along here I heard singing...
like choir practice.
There's a church on our right.
Then, take the next left.
- Which?
- What do you mean, which?
Have a look.
This way.
That way!
This time three of them.
Take that one down
toward the water.
- You said towards the water.
- I didn't say into it.
Let's see if we can
get this thing out of here.
Balordo...
Come on.
Are you all right?
Look, Doctor.
Hey, son.
Do you know of a big old house
around here on the water?
There's one over yonder.
- How can we get to that house?
- Round by the other road.
We'd better stay of the road
from now on.
Can we cut straight across?
On foot? That swamp's
full of snakes and gators.
- Will you sell me that mule?
- He's Puppy's mule.
Suppose I promise to return the mule
and give your Pappy five dollars?
- Where do I leave it?
- Leave him loose. He come on home.
- What's his name?
- Hinry.
Hinry?
Son, give me a hand.
You sure ain't done much riding, Mister.
Hinry is cross-wired.
You want him to proceed,
you hold him back. He stop.
Anything else I should know?
Any other fine points of mulesmanship?
Yes, don't never tech Hinry's tail.
He's kinda sensitive back there.
I won't.
Hinry's tail shall be inviolate...
Thank you, son.
Whoa, Hinry.
See anything?
Naw, a couple local peasants on a mule.
- Any sign of the cruiser?
- Not yet.
Proceed, Hinry.
Whoa, Hinry.
Whoa, Hinry!
There's nothing more stupid and ornery
than a stupid and ornery mule!
Quicksand...
- Miss Vincenti, please!
- ¡Avanti, avanti!
Avanti, Hinry, please!
I guess there's something more stupid
than a stupid mule.
Hinry, my apologies.
We'll never get the mule across all that.
Come on, honey.
Tie him up and we'll pick him up
to the way back.
- So long, Hinry.
- No!
What happened?
You were warned, remember?
You teched Hinry's tail.
No the way he teched mine!
Listen.
That sound...
- I heard it before.
- By the swamp... over there.
Base to Air boat.
- What are you doing? Do you see something?
- No, just alligators.
Mamma mia.
- Please, this is not time...
- Look!
Captain, no!
- Doctor...
- Captain.
Am I glad to see you!
And the General?
- He was hit, but I think he's still alive.
- Are you sure my brother's all right?
- Of course, Miss Vincenti.
- They wouldn't hurt him.
How many men does Fitzpatrick
have on the island?
Seemed like a hundred when they jumped us,
but I suppose ten or fifteen besides himself.
We'll have to go back and get help.
- Reinforcements?
- Worse than that.
They're getting ready to move out.
Probably to a ship waiting outside.
I'm sorry,
Arturo gets terribly seasick.
That settles it.
No time to go for help.
Captain.
Can you operate that air boat?
Yes I can!
Hey! You!
Let's go!
No!
Help!
Base to Air Boat.
Base to Air boat.
- ¿Yeah?
- Did you see something?
- No, just alligators.
- Fuh... Fuh... Fuh...
Fitzpatrick is annoyed.
Come on.
Let's go in right here.
Hurry!
Finish up, we're leaving.
- Get them ready.
- Him too?
Of course.
You'll make a nice dividend
for my clients, General.
A highly profitable deal.
Hey, buddy.
What kept you?
- Got a match?
- I don't smoke.
- Here are matches.
- Fine.
This way. The cellar door.
You come with me.
You stay here and watch them.
It's the cruiser!
Now.
Vicky!
Good girl.
- You better give me that, Doc.
- Come on.
- Who?
- Dr. Snow and that girl.
- Snow...
- Come on up to the house, move!
Dr. Snow.
I know you're there, Dr. Snow.
It's empty.
We better get out of here
before they surround the house.
I'll try to keep him talking.
All paranoids love to talk.
- You heard the doctor.
- Go on!
Dr. Snow!
Fitzpatrick.
Listen to me.
All right, Dr. Snow.
I'm listening.
You're a businessman.
The General and I'll make a deal with you.
Why should I make a deal?
You have nothing I'm interested in buying.
- You have no assets, Doctor.
- We have a few...
You've lost your transportation.
Before you can even send for another boat,
help will be here.
I don't buy it.
If help were on the way, you and the girl
wouldn't have come in here alone.
- Don't you think I called the Army first?
- Of course you did.
And you couldn't find anyone authorized
to tell you anything...
Or even to listen to you.
Because General's security is so airtight
that nobody knows what he's doing.
Am I right, General?
You mean you planned it all this way?
That was very clever of you.
I've made a fool of the General from the start.
I made his habits part of my plans.
My whole operation depended on the General
behaving how I predicted he'd behave.
And I keep the same sort of book
on every major security officer
in every civilized nation in this world.
I'm the world's greatest authority
on security techniques.
That's my business.
Now, do you come out
or do we come in and get you?
There he is!
Get the cars. Block the roads.
They can't get far.
Spread out!
Get around them!
Come on, let's go!
Leave me alone. I've had it.
You three make a run for it.
Wait.
Brought some transportation.
His name is Hinry.
Biggest mistake the Army ever made,
mustering out the old mules.
- Come on, giddap, Hinry.
- No, wrong code. Whoa, Hinry.
Hurry up!
This way.
Whoa, Hinry.
Don't shoot!
All right, Dr. Snow.
Let's go!
Hey! There are ours!
That's it, men.
Go get them!
Go and get them!
That way, that way!
All right, get me out of here!
That's it, Mammoths!
All right, Dr. Snow.
You win,
but you can't take it with you.
Doctor, doc...
- General!
- Barker!
It's good to see you all.
Wait a minute.
How'd you know where to find me?
- Well, we got a good...
- There's a leak in security?
- From the FBI.
- Heads are gonna roll for this.
- Well, Dr. Snow...
- Never mind about Dr. Snow.
Dr. Snow?
How did he know where to find me?
Dr. Snow? Dr. Snow?
Put the lights over there.
Security, huh?