Hey look,
Look at that hunk on stage!
Single
26 years, 38 months
A body of
40.05,
25.52,
36.36!
Are you lonely?
- Want to know him?
- Yes!
Any age or gender
He'll be your teacher
Right
He's Dance Fit Studio's...
Philip Wong!
We've combined keeping fit
With self-defense
A new idea!
Join our Studio today!
Join our Dance Fit Studio!
You're watching 100 women
performing this kung-fu dance
Combining
Kung-fu and dance
It will be so hot
- Don't block my shot!
- Stop!
Sit down
I'm crashing, with your girl
That's double trouble
Give up and shut down
Your students can come to me
At King King Dance
Like she did
King, spare us
Don't ruin our show
Get out! Shorty Henry!
I don't know what you are talking about,
Anyway, no fighting here!
This is a dance contest
That's fine
Clear the stage
Music!
- Come back!
- I'm a friend
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
No entry!
Useless!
Sorry. You okay?
Are you okay? Sorry
Bye
Who are you?
Your surprise guest
Bye!
A drink, Handsome?
I don't drink
Cigarettes?
I hate smokers!
You're so tall
I can't buy you drinks
- You're so tall!
- Ass!
Yes?
- Soda
- Two, please
Hi, Philip!
We came to see you
You're too cool
And you're hot
When can we go out?
Call me,
I'll turn off my phone
You're too cool
And you're hot
Help me out
When people talk
Entertain them, okay?
Fine
Hi
My name is Juliana Francoise Roberts
What's your name?
Long name. Is it foreign?
Your dad is foreign? Your mom?
Which country?
You're mixed? Impossible
You don't look it
You're faking
What are you?
How rude
I was still talking
You're so wasteful
of Earth's resources
Fulfill a man's role
Comfort a woman's lonely heart
Not picking on them
I'm like that
He is like that
What's wrong? He's frank
I pity you, Henry
No woman likes you
You, go away!
- Thanks
The surprise guest
You don't know her?
You've asked 20 times
I don't
She's pink
Pink?!
Are you kidding?
True pink
Felt like it
Your dad named you well
Shut up
Dreamy Wong!
Yes, Dreamy Wong!
Cheers
Here's to our
Happiness!
Happiness?
I wish
By all standards,
I should be happy
Like
I look okay
Business going well
I'm big
Not there
Big-hearted
Well, I shouldn't be unhappy
But
One thing makes me very sad
I'm colourblind
Totally
I don't see colours
Only black and white
My thoughts are all gray
Dazzling... cool... proper
I feel I'm dull
Insecure
But there's dancing
When I dance
I'm in control
Just a little
Look at that
I'm horny
How strange
He's crazy
Henry
- Henry!
- Philip!
You know I can't see
What's on my jacket?
You hate rejection by woman
To avoid them
I prepared a jacket for you
Your jacket says...
What?
I'm horny
I'm horny?
Help me
Surprise guest?
What is it?
They are after me
- Japanese?
- He says, beat it
What's going on?
Let go
No fighting!
He hit me!
These Japanese...
Stop! You first
They are after that girl
What girl?
Where is she?
- Gone
- Gone?
Again
You're lucky this time
They didn't arrest you
So strange
Seeing her
I felt...
A fireball
A pink fireball coming at me
Pink?
Fire is red!
It felt like fire
But
I've never felt that way
It's as if...
There are colours
Colours?!
Your eyes have recovered?
You're doomed!
Pink means women trouble
Stay away from her
Superstitious!
- You're worse!
- You are!
- You!
You're worse!
We've been here 2 hours
Where's she?
Millions of people in Shanghai
It's hard to run into her again
But I did, twice
Surprise guest!
So plump?
Sorry, Miss P
You know her?
Yes
Her name is P?
For Pig
Women like your look
But they find you boring
To fulfill you
Play quick
A one-night stand
Sorry, not without love
I'm different from you
Not again
I was cursed
For saying the wrong thing
Don't be my stepmother
Daddy says stepmothers eat boys
Traitor!
I'll curse you all
You'll never know women's love
Once they know you love them
They'll leave you
You won't find true love!
That's a mighty curse
Since then
All Dad's women left
My words I love you
Scared women away
Even now
My romances end badly
So
Isn't that a horrible curse?
It's not the curse
They dumped you because...
you're boring
And if those nonsense could kill
You deserve to die
1,2,3,4
5,6,7,8
And right
Left, once more
Left
5,6,7,8
1,2,3,4,
5,6,7,8...
1,2,3,4...
How's your head?
Fine
You left that day
I was worried
I forgot to thank you
I'm Yuri
I'm Philip Wong
Dreamy Wong, right?
Your students told me
Funny you came to my school
After 2 chance encounters
I came to see you this time
To see me?
I need a bodyguard
Bodyguard?
I've been followed since I arrived
They want to kidnap me
Those Japanese?
Why you?
Why Japanese?
You're Japanese? Rich family?
You called the cops?
You have many enemies?
Why so many questions?
All right, I'll answer
My family has some money
And some enemies
I'm the chairman's daughter of Japan's...
Sakura Department Store
So no cops, no publicity
You answered more than I asked
We'll get along
I thought I'd bore you
No, this is fun
I do that, too
Thanks
You appreciate me
No need to be that grateful
It's no big deal
Why me, as a bodyguard?
I'm new in town; I know nobody
You seem silly and nice
You fight well
And look nice
I have questions
Ask
Are you Japanese?
You speak Cantonese
Japanese dad? Or mom?
And, Yuri is not Japanese
Tell me
I went to school
in Hong Kong
My full name is Yuriko Sakurada
From HKSG
HKSG?
Dad's dad is from Honshu.
Dad's mom, Kyushu
Mom's mom, Suzhou.
Mom's dad, Guangzhou
So, HKSG
I'm going to Suzhou; come
Of course!
Anywhere you go!
No need to pay me
Why not?
You appreciate me
I'll show you around
Thanks!
We'll meet here, 9 a.m.
You okay? Come out
Sure
You're cute
If my husband hears about this
I'm going to Suzhou with you
He'll die!
What?
Husband?
Not yet
End of March
Isn't this a huge,
sparkly diamond?
Very sparkly
From my fiance
After this Shanghai trip
I'll return to Japan
And plan the wedding
You really okay? Come
Congratulations
You're hoarse
You wanted to flirt?
You're disappointed?
Will you still be...
...my bodyguard?
Should I go tomorrow?
Should I?
Such a decision...
Needs some serious making
1, I go. 2, I stay
Channel 3?
Please go
I can't
Please
Go to hell!
Bad omen
Heads, I go
Tails, I stay
A coin from heaven!
What was that?
Two
Even...
...means I go
I cannot escape my fate
No! Try again
It's the sixth time
I counted wrong
Use these
Runes
I'm not superstitious
You're not?
Be her bodyguard; it's just a trip
Why the fuss?
Just go
You know I like her
What if...
I like her more?
She's getting married
Then, don't go
If anything happens to her
I'll never forgive myself
So, go!
Didn't you hear me?
She's engaged
I can't have feelings for her
Keep your thoughts pure
If I can't control myself?
Then go...
...to hell!
Then I'll miss my date
I must at least tell her
I can't go
Listen
All right?
He hasn't much hair
Even, I go. Odd, I stay
Stay still!
Go to hell!
Wake up
Today is very important
What?
Seriously, which shirt?
Which bag?
This bag... with this shirt
Any bag will do
You were right, simple friends
On a simple trip
Keep it simple
I never said that
It's in your mind
I can tell
Can you?
I'm with you
Yes, you are
Hurry, go
- It's late
- It's not
It is
It's only 7!
I'm early
because she may be too
A cup of coffee
Freshes me up
Two and I'll be fresher
It's still early
Make it three
Four, I'm super fresh
It's nine
She'll come soon
Not now
Oh, please
Don't go
Stay here
She'll be here any second
It hurts!
She can't see me like this
Hurry...
Done
Did she come?
Did she leave?
Two whole minutes
She's gone
I stood her up
Stupid coffee
Stupid restroom
I should have stayed
- Been here long?
- No
Afraid I'd stand you up?
No
Come here
Morning, Dreamy!
King? Why are you here?
We met last night at a disco
You know him?
You fight well, he knows the way
I'm safer with you both
And it won't look like a date
Yuri, he shouldn't go
Three's a crowd
I have relatives in Suzhou
I paid you to rent this?
My cousin got married yesterday
I borrowed it for luck
Fine. Who's driving?
Good move! You drive
Get in, King
What's wrong?
I don't have a license
I know why
You're cute
I try to be
Let's go!
Yuri
Didn't we buy candy?
- Yes
- Get them out
Here
Tell Philip to get a green one
We like the green ones
Pick a green one. They're good
I... like them all
Come, pick one
Well?
Can't?
That one?
Isn't it good?
I said the green ones are best
We like it.
Yes, it's good
You said he can't
He was lucky
Are you hot?
Yes, very
Turn on the air conditioner
Yes, he's sweating
I'll turn it on
Sweaty after one candy?
I don't have an address
It's hard to find
I want that well
Why?
I exist because of it
No well, no me
Years ago, grandma's mom
Refused to let her wed Grandpa
One night
They attempted suicide by...
...jumping into a well
Chor-Sing
You'll do anything for me?
I...
What? Tell me
One second
Hurry
I'm hurrying
Then say it
Wait
Right
We are in love
I'll do anything!
Really?
Yes!
You jump, I jump
Let's jump together
Yes
- You are...
- Jump!
Someone jumped into the well!
A woman came by
and rescued them
Their parents...
...were moved
And let them wed
If I find a man...
...like Grandpa
I'll marry him
You jump...
I jump
What?
I mean...
Your fiance'
He'll do anything for you
Of course!
Or I'll strangle him
- So noisy
- Where...
Where are we?
Your uncle's diner
And we have no food!
But
Hurry
Let's go
To the kitchen
Come
It's hot...
Well?
Smells so good!
You've never had this?
It's soy sauce chicken
My favorite
Have some soup
Sure
Taste it
Smells good
Well?
Delicious!
Try the chicken
Thanks
You eat green chicken?
It's green, Colourblind
Food colouring is edible
And the tea
I was joking
You're really colourblind?
You were so lucky
You picked the green candy
By luck
No wonder...
...you can't drive
How do you cross the street?
Can't see the traffic light
Oh, I'll bet you
Look at the symbols
Great idea
He has...
...no other choice
Are you angry?
He's upset
Stay
Sorry, I didn't mean it
Don't be angry
Sorry
I was joking
You shouldn't be insecure
Onion is blind and deaf,
but brave
Who? You know him well?
I saw it in a movie
Happiness is most important
Self-confidence will follow
Don't be angry
It's just colours; sorry
There she is
They're after me
Good moves!
Come help us!
No, thanks
He left us!
Let's go
This is fun
This way
- Hurry
- Here
Hurry
Go, hurry!
Go to hell...
You bully...
Go to hell!
- Let's go!
- Are you okay?
Yes
It's fun
Excuse me...
Excuse me
Quick!
Where are they?
Over that way
What?
Isn't this exciting?
Hold on to me
- I can't
- No!
Are you okay?
Yes!
You're sure?
I fell, you fell
You're right
You're all dirty
Look!
The moon! Trees!
This must be my grandparents' well!
Most wells can see...
...the moon and trees
I say it is!
I'm so happy I found it!
Congratulations
Not angry any more?
A little
That's just to thank you
I know
Your phone
I know how to get out
Coward! I despise you!
I don't want to see you again!
That's all?
I risked my life returning
Give me more severance
That's not... enough?
Bitch!
You deserve each other
Rot together then
Coward!
Sit over here
There goes our ride back
Great, we'll stay another day
Sure
Hungry?
Of course
I'll buy some food
Isn't this romantic?
I thought you like to talk
You were quiet
after we made fun of you
Actually...
I'm a bad talker
I always make mistakes
So I'd rather talk less
I'm also that way
Follow your heart
Speak your mind
You're insecure with everything?
Dancing
When I dance, I'm in control
That's easy
Dance your words
You'll be confident
Like, I want to...
...take you out
Or better still
I love you
I can't say that!
No?
Then, show it
Dance it out
Express
Your feelings
It's easy
Good idea
Yes!
You dance badly
Do you know that?
I do
You can teach me
Sure
An easy one
Para Para
- You can do that?
- Sure!
Para Para describes leaves
Floating to the ground
Float, float
Like our cherry blossoms in Japan
Floating like snowflakes
Short-lived
But glorious
If only love...
...can be like that
Do you agree?
Would you go for that?
Short-lived but glorious
- Come, teach me
- Sure
Watch
Do this, here
Step...
Slow down
I can't follow
I'm stupid
Here, turn your hand in
Like a floating leaf
Softly, down...
Stop staring
Teach me
Step, 45 degrees
And here, then turn...
I can't follow!
Watch
We'll miss the train!
I'm not ready to leave
Let's stay longer!
Sure
This hotel is famous
Yes, it is
It looks interesting
Let's spend the night
Sure
In separate rooms
Fine
Two single rooms
Yuri, run!
Let him go!
Now!
Call the police!
Wait
Wait?
They are my bodyguards
Bodyguards?
Mom dislikes me traveling alone
She made them follow me
Like ghosts
I had hoped you could...
...help me lose them
Why didn't you tell me?
You wouldn't have joined me, then
I wanted drama, fun, excitement
Yes!
Madame wants to speak to you
Mom
I know
Yes
Bye
What did she say?
I'm flying to...
Japan tomorrow
Tomorrow?
So soon?
Don't be mad
At what I did
I'm not
I ran into you twice
That's fate
Stop here
There is where I live
Thanks for the lift
I'm on the third floor
It's been nice
Have a good trip
Will you come to Japan?
Pretty cherry blossoms
Cherry blossoms?
April
You'll be married
Come to my wedding
Goodbye
- Let's go
- Yes
Come see me off at 9
Goodbye!
Bye!
The TV's on
Well
Channel 1, I go
Channel 2, I stay
2, then I stay
1, it's telling me to go
So I'll stay
So I'll go
No
I've had it!
Choose a channel!
I like to surf
You're confused
I saw everything
You want her, go chase her
How can I?
It's been only 3 days
There you go
Insecure again
Give up then
Hide under the bed and cry
Stay sad
Play the tragic hero
You're in too deep
Sorry, sir
Once more
You're so tall...
How can I...
So rude!
I'm polite
But you're not
Soda
See Lu Lu
She can break the curse
No
Why not?
It can only help
- Go!
No!
Go!
- Can't harm
- Don't push!
I said no!
I'm not superstitious!
Hi! I'm Lu Lu
Thanks
Let's break this curse
Isn't that great?
Like opera
Pay attention
He can tell?
The crystal ball
Tarot cards, star charts
All predict
A woman for you
Actually, she...
...has been with you
Your destinies are...
...very closely knit
Look near you
Bye bye cure
Not me, I like women
Not me either
Look there
I don't ask much of love
He doesn't have to say...
...he loves me
I'll be the woman behind him!
Are you all right?
Fine
I'm very friggin cold
Frigid cold?
Redundant
Hong Kong people...
...speak bad Chinese
Frigid cold!
Stupid!
I am very frigid cold
Coco is high-strung, so what?
Your dance school in Hong Kong failed
In Shanghai,
She founded Dance Fit here with you
And so successfully
She deserves it
Let yourself be loved
Enjoy it
Let Coco in
Okay?
Of course
She wined and dined you
But
I have no feelings for her
Why are you so stubborn?
I like being stubborn
Suit yourself
Mr. Stubborn
God!
For your cold
Chest out, belly in