Hey, Mister
Get up if you're not playing
What the hell you hit me for?
How dare you wake me up?
Have you no fear, you little twit?
Don't you know who I am? Well, do you or not?
How could I?
Oh, you don't! Great!
Give me a cigarette
Lighter!
You're dead if you sit here
What?
Are you deaf?
You want me to make this place like before?
Okay, okay
I will put these coins over there
Hope Employment Agency
Please meet me.Sir.....
That fucking cop hung up on me! Fuck!
Open the window when I smoke, you idiot!
They are all fucking idiots
Huh? Stop the car
Bite! Bite! Bite, fuck!
Good afternoon, sir!
When did you get out?
ln... in the morning, sir
Then why are you showing up now?
What's that?
This? A toaster, sir
So you go to a Game Room after such a fuss?
You idiot don't know the situation
Kangjae! Kangjae! You fucking idiot!
You should think
Think, I said!
Why the fuck is it closed so early?
Shitheads! And how they work!
Oh my god!
You fucked?
Oh, no
Don't give me shit
You think this is a hotel?
In my store of all places...
Now, I manage this shop
What? You manage what?
Who authorized it?
Yongsik did
He ordered me to manage this place
And never to let you, Mr. ldiot, come near here
What did you just call me?
Mr. ldiot?
What a fucking bastard!
Have you no respect for your senior?
Leave it there, you bitch!
When you were suckling on your mama,
I made the foundations to this gang with
a knife in my bloody mouth
Don't you have any respect, you bastard?
Fuck you!
Don't shout at me
Go complain to Yongsik
Stop it!
All right, you mother fucker!
I'm gonna ask Yongsik right away
If he says otherwise, it'll be your last day
You fuckin' shit!
Is it okay to treat him like that?
He's not worth my respect
You bastard, take this!
Hey, Kyungsu! The cops are here!
Hide those things, quick!
Fuck you! Fuck you!
Thought you could fool me again?
What? Fuck me?
Is that how you treat me when
I just got out of prison?
You are a real son of a bitch, you know that?
Hey, mongrel!
Shame on you!
10 days imprisonment for selling
porn tapes to teenagers!
You'd already be dead cold without me
See whose clothes you're wearing
So what?
Shit, these really stink like hell!
Shut up and bring me some beer
There's no beer left
Then go and buy some
No way! It's damn cold so you go!
Besides, looks like you've already drunk
What? I'm gonna break your neck
Okay, okay, I do have some
Where?
Just wait
That's better
Here you go! Take this!
By the way, I met Yongsik today
He was mad as hell
Is he PMS-ing or what?
Tell me about it! It's red alert
While you were in prison,
caught for illegally immigrating Chinese
The whole city was a mess!
Even our agency was shut down
Besides, the D's kids are trying
to eat up our club now
So Yongsik's in the pits, I bet
And they call this a gang
Wouldn't take it even if they call me boss!
When you met Yongsik,
didn't he tell you anything?
Tell me what?
He wants you to be a bouncer at the club
You know what a bouncer is, right?
Humiliating, huh?
Tell him you want to be a waiter
Unless you want to get frostbitten
Put it away, you bastard!
That bastard!
Nothing's left
What a rat!
U-hm! The latest version
That dirty bastard! Never washes the dishes!
This bastard tries real hard to bait chicks
You bitch! Do you think with your tits?
You should've worked harder
when the sales dropped in half
How dare you take two days off work
just to hang around D's club?
Honey...
You guys heard her bitching, right?
This is why we're in the shits right now
There are reasons why D's kids eat
into our area
You idiots!
Now look!
Look, I said!
Look at it, shitheads!
Can any of you put these pieces back together?
No one can! When it's broken, it's too late
You understand?
While I'm gone to piss, think about it hard!
And you, bitch!
Today's your last day of your life
Where is Yongsik?
I've got something to tell you, sir
What is it?
I'd do better as a waiter than a bouncer
Kangjae, you bastard! That's exactly you
You know nothing but to talk
When I tell you something, do as you're told
What an idiot...
What a parasite
Who put that idiot in?
They should get rid of him
Because of that bastard
Just eat your noodles
If Cha Bum-gun was young again,
he would never play like that!
You are a real noodles!
Cha is a coach, not a player
You fool! You don't know a thing
When Cha was young, he scored three goals
in the last 5 minutes
Oh, yeah? Then do you know Bae Dong-sung
in short tracks?
Then, do you know Pro wrestler Kim l1?
How about Yeo Gun-bu?
Who?
The legendary Yeo!
You'll never know
Pro wrestling is only for show!
As for wrestling, Shim Kwon-ho is the best!
Here's the uniform!
Wow, yours is fucking big!
Are you talking about wrestling?
Give me a parterre position
Parterre? Okay, parterre!
Don't hold it, you idiot
Okay
Take this!
Fuck!
Hey, it's rotting?
Shit! No more!
Do it again!
Parterre!
You idiot, are you ready?
A whistle! You bastard
How's this
Oh, you're tough
You can't beat me! No!
You bastards, freeze there! You don't bow to me?
Who's in the offices?
Go check yourself
Hey, if you have any problem, ask me for help
ey, Kangjae! We've got a real problem
Can you help us?
This is too much
The interest has doubled the original sum
I can't give you any more
So you're saying you won't pay us back?
Auntie, this is Kangjae
Look at me, You should listen to me
Don't make excuses
Do whatever you want!
You shouldn't do this to me
Remember what I've done for you
when you were hungry
I fed you noodles and bought you drinks
I don't remember anything
Stop babbling and get to the point
Are you going to give it or not?
You ungrateful bastard!
Is she a Yakuza or what?
Are you paying back with violence?
Give me few more days, I beg you!
What the fuck!
What?
Hey, sit down!
Watch your mouth to your auntie
We should respect the elders
Auntie, please come over there
Please give me a break, will you?
So you're saying you want a couple
more days, right?
Yes, yes
But how can we?
We'll be going to the States tomorrow for good
you motherfucking bitch
How can you call me like that?
Don't you have parents to teach you manners?
No, I don't! I'm an orphan!
So what you gonna do about it, you bitch?
Hey! Hey! Get out and wait
Get out of my way
Pour it around
I like it!
Hey, auntie
Your last chance
You want me to drop this
Just do it, huh?
Bye! Thanks for the noodle
How humiliating is!
Be careful not to become like him
What are you talking about?
You seem to have a fun life
You can't even handle that old bitch
Are you going out with her?
Why are you so soft on her?
If you have no guts,
just shut your fucking mouth
What did you say, you bastard?
Fuck! How can I call this scum my senior?
Go away, just go
Let's go
What did he say?
I don't know
He can do nothing but talk
Stop it!
Little shitheads, how dare...
Stand upright! Upright!
Upright! Upright!
I did nothing, sir
Don't make excuses
Come closer, closer!
Stand up!
Sir!
Stand up, idiot! Up, up!
I'm sorry, sir
Get out of my sight!
Right now!
Why are you still here?
Get lost! I don't want to see you
You're not even a human
Even if I was born four-legged,
I wouldn't live like you
You should mind your own business
Why did you go with the kids and fuck up?
But the auntie treated us...
I told you not to talk about the past, didn't l?
But...
You're shit! I'll finish you today
Just take it with one hand
That's all right, sir
Hey, call me by my name when we're alone
I'm your friend
Bottoms up! At one go!
Have some more
Kangjae, isn't it a fucking world?
I know how you feel
We started out together
And I became the boss and you're still a minion
You know why?
That's because you're not made for this
You have the tiniest guts and
you're so weak at heart
And you're not responsible enough to
carry out your duties
fishing with your brother
You talked big about going back with a boat?
You that you talked big about
going back with a boat?
Please take my glass, sir
You bastard...
Drink it
What the hell are those bastards doing here?
Think this is their home or what?
Call the kids... No, I'll take care of it myself
Hey, you son of a bitch
How dare you come into my area?
So what? You fucker...
What? You're dead!
So the bastard wants to die!
Die you fucking bastard! Die!
Die! Die!
Yo... Yongsik
Hey, get up! Hey, you!
Get up, you bastard!
Yongsik!
Have you heard the news?
That bastard rose to the surface
We should've hung something heavier on him
What should we do now?
There's got to be a way out, surely
If we work together, there's nothing we can't do
Kangjae...
Would you save me, I mean, us?
I'm not trying to put the blame on you
But if I go in now, it'll be the end of everything
You know what I mean?
I'm begging you now on my knees
If only you would do this for me, then...
You said you want to go home with a fishing boat
I'll buy it for you
This is the first and last favor I ask of you
as a friend, Kangjae!
I need some time to think about it
Actually, you're partly responsible, too
Since you're cleaner than me...
If you turn yourself in, it won't be longer
than 10 years
But for me, it'll be at least 20 years
and then my life's over
I can't die alone
My hometown must be bustling with squid
and shrimp fishing now
Driving me crazy..
Why? You want to go back?
Every time you get drunk...
Go back if you have the nerve
I'll definitely go
With a small fishing boat...
Yeah... a hundred years later
What?
You think I can't do it?
Buying a boat is a piece of cake to me
This shithead thinks I can't afford it
Hey, give it to me!
Give it to me! I'm gonna show you that I can!
Give you what?
Your cell phone, you idiot!
Then what?
Yongsik?
It's me, Kangjae
Yeah, it's Kangjae who you beat up
real bad yesterday
Yeah, I'm drunk
How can I not drink after getting beaten
up like that?
I'll get to the point
Were you serious about what you said
the other day?
Yeah, I will go in, yeah!
lnstead of you...
Only on one condition
Give me the money first
Yeah, send it to my bank account
If not, you will be fucked up
You think I'm nothing
Hey, Yongsik! Keep your promise
Give me the money first
Will you?
10 years for a boat isn't that bad, shit!
Are you Mr. Lee Kangjae?
Well, I was just about to...
Ms. Kang Failan is your wife, right?
I'm sorry but she died yesterday
It's been over a year since they moved to Canada
Haven't you contacted them before coming here?
They're my only relatives
Do you have their phone number?
No, I am sorry about that
Go back to China
It's hard to live here without any connections
There's no one there, either
Hope...?
Come on in! Relax!
That's too bad
How can I help you?
I'd like to earn some money
But how?
I studied Korean in China
I'm confident that I can do anything
But there is a problem
You can't stay here longer than allowed
If you don't get a visa, you'd get arrested
There is a way
Could you untie your hair, please?
It's okay
What style!
Look at this red scarf, how embarrassing!
Shut your mouth and give me the money
Okay, okay!
Here it is... deducting my fee
Are you ripping me off?
Am I crazy to do this for nothing?
Give me your documents
Is there all that we need?
Sure, Sayonara!
Your wife is inside, Wanna see her?
No!
Come on, just have a look at her
That's your wife, there
Where?
Over there, wanna do her?
That little chick?
Yeah
Shit
Why, not your taste?
You do her yourself
Where are you going?
To the turf
Going there again?
What is it?
Give it to the little chick
Caring for your wife already?
You said red looks embarrassing, didn't you?
Don't worry
I'm not gonna hurt you
Thank you!
We have his picture here,
would you like to have a look?
Maybe it's all for the better
Why don't you go cool off your head
Let's finish our deal when you're back
You haven't changed your mind, have you?
Give it to Kyungsu
He's at the station
He first took the girl there
Have some fun with this
No, I have money
Take it with you
No, thanks
Just take it
Yongsik
Why?
You'll keep the promise?
Of course I will
Hey, you don't bow to your senior?
You don't bow to me, you asshole?
Kang Failan, 781 01 1 245431 1
Kang Fai, right? Fai?
Kang Failan, 781 01 1 2454...
22454... 2454... Hey, look at the snow there
22454... 2454... I don't know
You really hate using your brain
Her hometown?
How can you smile when your wife's dead?
Should I cry then?
Why did that bitch die to hassle me like this?
And when was it that you were overjoyed
at getting money for it
You have to memorize this
What if the cops ask you about her?
What kind of a husband doesn't know
about his wife, huh?
How many guys memorize their wife's
social security number?
I just think that's over the line
Did you see her at the agency?
You didn't, right?
Here is her picture
I don't want to see it
You should know her face not to be suspicious
lsn't she pretty? Even better in person
Why?
Does she get to you?
Moron...
Hey!
She's pretty
Hey, hurry up! Hurry!
Come on in
It stinks... Come on in
Just relax, it's all right
Sit down
What the hell is this? Hey, isn't she great?
Shut up and give me a minute
She's perfect
Have a seat
Not bad, quite good
Yeah? You should pay a lot
Bullshit!
Oh, that bastard! Whenever he gets drunk...
Come here, you bitch
What is it?
Leave me alone, you bastard!
What the fuck is that?
Just sit down
You bitch, you...
Let me go, shit!
Who's the guy?
I don't know
Whenever he gets drunk, he's crazy like that
It runs in his family to be like that
What's taking her so long in the bathroom?
What if she took off?
Here she comes
Say hello to your boss
Hey, what the fuck is that?
Is this how you do your business?
No, it's not like that
I almost got fucked up
Do you think this is a blood donation center?
No, please have a seat
Don't give me shit!
Hey, hey, please!
What do you want me to do now?
She's sick!
She coughed up blood
I don't know... Looks like some
contagious disease
Shit, I'm really out of luck
It wouldn't have mattered if she coughed it
up after the deal
But she did it right in front of him
How could I cheat on him right then?
What? Which agency?
Okay, give them a call first, all right?
You don't know how hard laundry is
How such a fragile girl can do the work?
I guarantee it
You can't find anyone like this girl
You're really lucky, lady
In the past I washed many clothes,
I am good at riding bicycle
What did she say?
See? She says she was a pro laundress in China
She can ride a bicycle, too
But we can't even communicate
You don't need much talk
After I left home, I will work very hard
She'll do whatever you order.You are so lucky!
Work hard, don't slack off
Lady, don't give her a break
Don't say that
Good bye
It's cold, come on in
Thank you for your present
What did she say?
Thank you for the scarf
Hey, tell her that it's a wedding present
from her husband
This scarf is given by your husband,
you should thank him
You speak Chinese well
When I was young, I had a business there
She has a disease or something, right?
Nonsense!
It's small but good for one person
And tell me if you need anything
What can I tell her? This is frustrating
Good morning
Hi
Uh, Hi!
Oh my god! You're a walking washing machine
How could you wash all these with
such a thin body?
Laundry...!
Good.Welcome!
"Welcome
Haha..Thankyou!
"Thankyou!
Haha... Did you have dinner?
Did yi o dinor?
Hahaha... I can't help it!
Did you have dinner?
Did yio dinor?
How can I have her work?
I can't do this any more, I quit
Thank you!
Laundry...!