Can you do this?
Anything you can do I can do better.
Do you think they can manage it?
A bunch of lazy bums.
Five, ten, fifteen
Oh, no
Don't trespass?
Consider yourself lucky.
- Tong!
- Uncle!
It's late. Go to bed.
Must finish it before tomorrow.
Uncle!
Hurt yourself!
Sorry to have got...
you into this.
I don't mind.
Come on, get up!
Be quick... it's ready.
Get out!
Out of my way.
Master!
Who's that kid?
Tong, the Cripple's nephew.
I must win, and win well.
That can be arranged.
No!
- What's happened!
- Stupid fool!
You can't lose.
Today's our...
saint's birthday.
So we stage a game to celebrate.
All participants...
must come unarmed.
They must climb up here with hands tied.
Then across the bridge.
And win the ball with their feet.
Prizes are roast pig and some cash.
On your marks.
Ready!
Wait for me!
Tie your hands!
- Ready!
- Wait!
Glasses are not allowed.
Dumb fatso!
Don't worry! I'm supporting you.
You again!
- What's the matter?
- He...
I've made it!
I'll pay you more.
Got no time for you.
- Great!
- Tong's good!
I've got it!
Are you alright?
Murder! Grab him!
Take these money and run!
Go there...
if you need help!
I'm staying!
Why? They're after your blood.
- What is it?
- Where's your nephew?
- Haven't seen him all day.
- Are you sure?
- Look around!
- Yes...
Where could he be?
It was a nasty blow for master.
- What are you about?
- No!
We'll wait for him.
- Guard the doors.
- Yes!
Tse Wong Terrace.
"Forced to move! Horrible!"
Big Brother!
This is a matter of life and death.
We must...
beat the Indians.
- If we lose...
- We'll lose our livelihood.
- No more shoes to shine.
- No more cars to wash!
Take him off!
Where's...
your stamina?
Big Brother!
What's so funny?
How could you missed an open goal?
Where's your fighting spirit?
Otherwise, we wouldn't have lost.
You must keep moving on the field.
Send more crosses over.
Why just standing around?
Pass it to me!
Try the sliding tackle!
A goalie must not afraid of injury.
Terrific!
Blood! I smell trouble!
Don't let him go!
Stop him!
Wait!
Look for him!
Wine, glorious wine!
Welcome, King of the football maestro!
Welcome!
King of the football maestro!
Stop pushing!
Who is he?
Do you know our idol?
Ladies and gentlemen.
We are every honored today.
For the presence of King,
our football maestro.
To officiate
the opening of this stadium.
A big hand for king!
He has done well with football!
Want to buy...
a lottery ticket?
This is the chance...
of a lifetime!
Luck has never...
been on my side.
But I'll give it another try.
I've also finished for the day.
Thank you
- Give me one of those.
- Okay!
Want to buy a lottery ticket?
The last one?
You're dishonest!
Go away if you don't want to buy.
Take me for a fool?
Here comes the fool!
I'm no fool!
- Mister...
- No!
Not!
"Cannon" Sun, 26 Tse Wong Terrace...
That's my old address.
Are you blind?
- Pickpocket!
- Where?
- You slashed my wallet!
- Go to hell!
You go to hell!
Give me back my money!
- I'll make you do it!
- No.
What is it? Stop!
You are disturbing the peace!
But he slashed my wallet!
Do you know who I am?
Who are you?
I'm a cop!
Come with me!
- What about my money?
- It'll be used as exhibit in Court.
They're from the same gang!
Give me back my money!
What happened?
- Who threw it at me?
- I'm sorry!
Here you are.
- Hurt yourself?
- Making a fool of me?
- They are coming...
- Run!
Run!
Stop!
- Run for it!
- Where are we going?
To my home!
But I've never met you before.
You've got all my lottery tickets.
Is this yours as well?
Yes!
- 'Cannon' Sun?
- That's right.
He's my dad.
What a coincidence! Where's he?
- He's going...
- Gone abroad?
He's gone two years ago.
My mother went before him,
They're both dead.
I'm sorry about it.
It doesn't matter.
Move over!
Don't block the way.
How come we're here?
Damn it!
You?
Brother, you...
He's your brother?
I didn't mean it.
It's okay. Why did you run away?
I want you to join our team.
I don't know how to play football.
But you've got a powerful shot.
We'll be invincible if you join us.
I...
I know a good player when I see one.
Head.
We can't afford to lose.
What about me?
Play up front, of course.
You mean I'm a forward?
Stop him!
Tong, I'll stop him. Go!
Kick it! Tackle him!
Tong!
Go for it!
Why can't he stand straight?
I told you?
Mine!
Tackle him!
- Look!
- A goal!
This is unbelievable!
Well done!
You really can't play football?
Go to hell!
Tackle him! Don't let him score!
Let me stop him. You go...
- What are you doing?
- Nothing at all.
Go to die.
Don't stand around...
like a penguin!
But I'm a forward!
Him again.
Oh god, a goal!
This goal has been disallowed!
You're biased!
Want a fight?
- Are you alright?
- I'm fine.
We're in big trouble now.
Just have a little tolerance.
Beat him up!
Run!
Can you make it?
I can't!
A real foot brawl!
Give it to me!
Where are you buddies?
They're the first to run.
I'll share this with you.
Why hang around those bums all day?
Find yourself a job.
Just ignore her.
No, I want a job.
Try your luck...
- with a football club!
- Right!
The first time...
you chased me out of town.
The second time I was beaten up.
- The next time...
- Next time?
I may even lose my life.
But if we sign...
on with a club.
We'll have a chance to become famous.
Then what?
Then we'll be rich!
We may even have our own cars.
We will have nothing...
to worry about.
How can we be famous?
Ask him!
"Lung Wah Sports Club Player Recruitment"
Great...
Excellent, six out of ten.
Right, just like Pele.
Thank you!
Thumb down?
You've not got Pele's footwork.
Taking the Mickey out of me?
Think you can make it?
You can tell by my look that I've failed.
- Next, Lee Tong!
- I'm not going.
- Lee Tong!
- He's calling you.
If you can't make it...
Go try your luck.
- No...
- Go!
- Lee Tong?
- Yes!
Perform the same routine.
Wait!
Have I seen him somewhere before?
Remember me?
So he's a friend.
He's the best player around.
He makes all decisions for the club.
I can't lower myself to beat him up.
This is his club.
Thumb up.
I know you're a natural born player.
You're in.
I bet he has pulled some strings.
Good.
Have we met...
Forget the past. Think about the future.
What future?
You're now a member of the Lung Wah Club.
He's here? The maestro's here.
Tong.
Lee Tong, the Player of the Century.
Is he really a natural born player?
I wasn't too bad.
Maybe that's fate.
Take you chance.
You'll make it if you work hard.
Don't let me down.
Let's begin today's training with...
Boss!
I'm taking this session myself.
You're...
in luck today.
I'll turn you...
into men of steel.
A player...
Must be tough.
- Lee Tong!
- Yes!
I'll show you how to play.
The boss likes...
good young players.
Tackle me!
What is it?
Don't close in...
when you tackle!
Remember it!
- It's important
- Okay!
Let's reverse our roles.
This is a foul!
So you must think of a better way.
The referee won't notice
things like these.
These are deliberate fouls.
Don't use them.
What's his best position?
He sure can take some sticks.
- Put him on the ground staff.
- You're getting very smart.
This is too tough.
Give it up.
I disagree.
Success won't come easy.
You must have hurt yourself...
doing acrobatics.
This is not too bad.
I'm sorry, Tong.
Fanny, come here.
Let's go...
and see Tong train.
But let's leave him...
now to rest.
One day,
I'll be as good as you.
I've found a job.
Everybody treats me well.
I hope you like the walking stick.
Stand closer!
Don't be afraid of the ball.
That's right!
- Give me the ball!
- Yes!
You forgot?
Use your hands!
Not your feet!
- Throw it to me, ball boy.
- Yes!
- Ball boy!
Good
- Boss.
- Let's call it a day.
Right, dismiss.
Give me those!
Have a cup of tea, boss.
Where did he go?
- Boss!
- What did you try to do to me?
No!
You're out, forever!
But boss... I beg you.
I've got a scapegoat.
What are you...
staring at?
You're staring at me, too.
Want to see who has got a tougher leg?
Chicken!
Coward!
Give me a towel!
Don't be late tomorrow!
We're almost there.
Tong will be...
- a star real soon.
- Are you kidding?
I can even...
offer you membership.
Don't believe you.
"Authorized Persons Only"
Here we are!
Come on!
We're not allowed in.
Let's try the main entrance.
This is a big ground.
Tong! He's in there.
Tong, over there!
Be quick!
Tong, we're here!
How are you?
- Fine.
- Improved?
How long have you been here?
I hired you...
as a ball boy.
So go do your job!
- He's a ball boy.
- He doesn't even have a jersey.
I thought he was a superstar.
- It's all a lie!
- Let's go.
Tackle him, closer!
"Changing Room"
Be quick!
Take a shower! Get changed!
I've avenged you.
A very pretty little girl, boss.
That's what...
you said the left time.
But this one is Danish.
She just arrived...
in Hong Kong.
She's fantastic!
I'm sure you will enjoy her.
You'll come back for more.
She sounds delicious.
I must carry on and learn.
That's right!
I must improve my stamina.
- Come on.
- Here you are!
- Look at this.
- It's mine.
Left and right, here!
The God shows me the way.
- Wonderful!
- That's nothing!
Who are you trying to fool?
Go!
Left and right!
That's excellent!
I'll show you more!
- Watch out!
- I will!
- Give me a kiss!
- No!
Don't be afraid. Come on!
It's a misunderstanding.
No wonder...
you're still wearing a hat!
I back Lung Wah to win!
Yes, me too.
Me too...
Even money for Lung Wah to win.
I can't see Lung Wah lose.
Check carefully.
No mistakes!
Thanks!
Fifty cents for Seng Sun to win.
Save it for an ice cream.
Lung Wah again, good!
I'll put everything on Lung Wah.
I know!
Give the boss a call.
Lung Wah's favorite to win.
Don't worry.
Accept all bets.
Yes, boss.
Why didn't you wait for us?
- Have a drink, King.
- Okay!
Buy me a watch tomorrow!
- Sure!
It's a promise!
Go away!
Good!
$50,000 as usual!
Is that all?
I'll make it $70,000
What did you say?
With the high cost of living...
Okay! $100,000.
I'll make it look real.
Is this okay?
Just put it here.
Let's drink to us!
We'll make a good team.
I want to make the ball boy a reserve.
But he can't play.
That's what I like about him.
I've brought...
you Lulu and Mimi.
They're the most beautiful girls here.
Lee Tong...
I'm sorry, coach.
You're in luck.
- Boy!
- In Luck?
"Substitute Lee Tong"
That's me?
King seems to like you.
I've made it!
- You're crazy!
- Coach!
- I've made it!
- I've done it!
You're lovely.
They're beautiful!
You like them?
They're yours.
What about you?
I've got another pair.
He treat them...
like his concubines!
Try them on, you'll need them.
How much money's in the pool?
It's huge, and the money's
on Lung Wah to win.
Look!
Excuse me.
- Let's go!
- Shut up!
- Lung Wah's not a certainty!
- 20 dollars, Lung Wah win.
Can't you say something better?
I'll place the bet for you.
Don't push me!
$20 on Lung Wah to win.
- He's pretty smart!
- It's done.
- Fine!
- Twenty cents please!
- Sure, it's worth it!
- Thanks!
- Good luck!
- I hope so.
I'll place your bet for you.
Lung Wah to win!
Where's Lee Tong?
He's on the substitutes' bench.
Be careful, boss.
Sit...
Manager Mr Fok.
How do you rate...
Seng Sun's chances?
We're on a big bonus to win.
My boss wants...
to be famous.
I'll be rich if we win.
That goes without saying.
That's all.
It's not even time yet!
King beats one of...
the Hsin Sang defenders.
And another, with a beautiful dribble.
He's now being surrounded
by three players.
Another ten yards.
And they cannot...
dispossess King.
He's now into Hsin Sang's twenty five.
A great pass to the left winger.
A long cross
to the other side of the field.
Now the ball's back in the center.
A good pass can...
put King clear.
King is clear
with only the goalie to beat.
He's now in the penalty area.
He collides...
with a defender.
The defender looks badly hurt.
But King seems alright!
No, he's gone down again
and looks in pain.
What a tragedy.
I wonder how the referee will decide.
Good.
Lee Tong, you go on.
- Ah Tong!
- Tong!
He bumps into the referee.
Maybe he's too nervous.
Why sent him on?
- Who?
- I'm sorry!
Go on your own!
Lee just received the ball
from his goalie.
He sure has some...
nice touches.
But he is going the wrong way.
He passed the ball to Chan Ming.
A reverse pass from Chan to him.
The pass was too long...
but Lee still gets it.
He slips two defenders.
Now he passes...
the ball back to Chan.
And Chan passes it...
back to him.
Pass it back!
What are you trying...
to do?
We've lost the match!
Let's go!
Take it easy!
- Keep you voice down!
- Take it easy!
Pass it over!
Not this time!
I'm not going to pass it to anyone!
Go...
He has dribbled past many players.
That's a wonderful dummy!
And over-head kick,
it's a goal.
One all!
He sure has nice footwork!
And he scores!
It was an accident!
Over there!
- I'm queuing to collect my winning!
- Great!
They just can't rob him of his ball.
The defender collide and fall.
Within shooting distant, it's a goal.
Lung Wah lead two one thanks to Lee Tong.
Looks like it.
We've won!
Great...
What's the matter with you?
- You've spoiled everything!
- Beat him up!
I wouldn't have sent you on
if we want to win.
Boss!
So you were trying to fix the match!
Take care of him!
Don't go!
I promise...
I'll break your legs!
Good to see you here.
Our boss wants to see you.
- Sure, I've got nothing to hide.
- This way please!
Calm down! Take a seat!
Drive on!
Let's talk here.
We like you style.
Want to join our team?
No!
I rather go home and be a farmer.
Giving up football?
We want to make you...
the new maestro.
Say that again.
We want you to be a superstar!
Then it's different.
No more match-fixing, okay!
We never fix matches!
Stamina is important...
in this game.
I was once a superstar.
Know why I want to take up coaching?
It's because I do not have stamina.
So you must work hard on your stamina!
"Who makes me bleed and sweat?"
"Who forces me to stride on
with clenched fists?"
"I do get tired,"
"wanting to throw in the to throw
in the towel. It's tough!"
"But there is no choice."
"Tired to the marrow,
I must keep on going."
"It's I myself..."
"who goads me on the thorny path."
"I challenge myself to new heights,
whatever the battleground."
"I have to throw."
I order to crack a tight defense.
We must use our wingers more!
The full backs...
should also attack!
"They says I'm pigheaded,
bleeding and sweating."
"Keeping on the path of pain
with clenched fists."
"Yes, I am tired, very tired."
"Yes, I have had enough of it."
"But I have no choice."
"Tired to the marrow,
I must keep on going."
"It's I myself..."
"who goads me on the thorny path."
"I challenge myself to new heights,
whatever the battleground."
"I have to throw."
I didn't do too badly, did I?
You did well to find them.
What is that?
- Make yourselves at home.
- This is lovely!
Look!
- Not bad!
- Right!
You can stay here if you want.
Great!
I've made it!
Come and enjoy life with me!
Seng Sun are odds on favorite to win.
I'll back...
Seng Sun.
$15 on Seng Sun!
$20 on Seng Sun!
Come on!
Push him down!
- Hold on!
- Push him down!
Just hold on a little longer!
Push him down!
Bear...
Here's the money!
It's been paid for by that gentlemen.
Just look at the size of Wong!
He's really quite useless.
He's here with a mission.
What does he want?
I don't know!
- Come over here!
- I...
Do as I say, okay?
What is it?
- I want you team to lose tomorrow.
- You mean...
I little bit more, maybe.
You've heard him! More!
Not nearly enough! More!
I said more!
- This is out first time!
- Well, it's up to you.
A little more!
Come on! More!
It's not enough. More!
Come on, hurry up! More!
You don't need to hesitate!
Just keep them coming!
- Don't ask if you can't take it!
- Right.
I didn't realize what he was doing.
What shall we do?
Who do you think we are? The Maestro?
- Tong, are you alright?
- I'm fine!
Fatso wants us to fix the match.
I told you! Get changed and go!
Who does he think we are?
The Maestro?
Let's try to score...
as many as possible!
Let's play in...
a 4-3-3 format!
Fall back!
Blood?
Go!
What happened?
We looked like fools!
You must've got the wrong people.
It's possible.
He and Suen is really
a perfect combination.
Now on the field,
Lee Tong gets the chance again.
18 yards away from the goal, a kick.
8 to 0, Seng Sun sweeps the board.
It's really shows the teamwork of Suen
and Lee Tong is welcomed by everyone.
"Players' Cafeteria"
Coach
Here you are, boss!
Have a seat, boss!
Cool it!
He's just a ball boy.
Why compare yourself with him?
We'll get even with him later on.
This was reserved...
for press conference.
The press?
I guarantee this will work.
Wait!
No...
Yes...
It was a terrific match!
Any plan for your next game?
Well...
- That's a team secret.
- Right!
- Sit over there!
Let's take a picture of you two.
Good!
A little closer please.
They're just two country bumpkins.
How can they host a press conference?
Maestro!
Seung sun will take you on soon.
What are you tactics?
Do you think they can beat us?
I doubt...
if you can make the finals.
More about our...
plans later.
We'll get him later!
- But where?
- Come on.
Take it easy!
Come again soon!
Will you follow me please?
This way!
Have a seat!
Take good care of our guests.
I thought...
King virtually live here?
Don't worry. He'll be here.
He's over there! Let's live it up!
Do you have any favorite?
We want to spend some money here.
Sounds good!
Let me!
- Who's that?
- It's Lee Tong!
He's lovely!
They've won another match today!
A ball boy in a ball room!
He's staring at us!
- Don't be afraid!
- Keep clam!
Have a smoke!
Live it up!
Cheers!
Looking good!
He's showing off!
Cheers!
Look at King's ring! It's great!
It's big, isn't it?
- It's big.
- Give it to me as a present!
You're out of your mind!
What time is it?
- It is wonderful!
- Pretty, isn't it?
It's made of sapphire!
- Take it!
- A look.
You are putting me on!
I like it very much!
- Can you give me one?
- Please.
Lee Tong has one bigger than yours.
He's losing his temper.
Clam down! Cool it!
We mustn't let him steal the show!
Show him what you can do!
Okay!
Great!
He's great!
What are you looking at?
I've never seen Tango like this.
Shut up!
He can even do it kneeling down.
Damn it!
She dropped her skirt!
Don't try to stop me.
Stop it!
I beg go!
Just who do you think you are?
I've always been...
a better player.
Better in match-fixing.
Stop it now!
Call a truce!
- Resume your duel.
- On football field!
Have the guts to take me on?
I admit defeat if you win or draw.
But I want your leg if you lose.
It's a deal!
Start practicing with this now.
Let's go!
Lee Tong wins even if it's a draw.
Confident of winning?
I think I can do it.
Where are you going?
I'll go seek advice...
from my friends.
Don't worry about me.
Who is it?
When did you arrive?
It's been such a long time.
Have I changed?
Come with me.
There are that...
I've got for hard work.
And this one...
It was presented to me by the Governor.
- What are you doing?
- Leave me.
Uncle!
Come home with me at once.
Do you think you've done well?
I was once a proud footballer.
I refused to fix a match.
Thanks!
So when I went home one night.
What are you trying to do?
I became...
a Cripple since.
Tong, everybody's here.
We've to mark King out of the game.
Don't be afraid to tackle.
They're weak on their left side.
We've discovered...
their weakness.
We'll attack down...
the left flank.
Count me out of tomorrow's game.
But why?
Are you scared?
Remember how King treated you?
Remember how King fixed a match?
We must get rid...
of people like King!
I don't have you as a friend.
- Play!
- Who are you?
You must play not matter what happened.
This is a private match arranged by King.
They're using their legs as wager.
Let's do our best!
We can have a side bet, right?
This is going to be a real match!
How about $1,000 for one goal?
Sure, but don't forget...
this match is not fixed.
Substitutes are not allowed
in this match.
And no audience is...
allowed in.
I am the only exception.
The game is on.
Lee passes to Suen.
Suen does well to keep...
the ball in play.
It's a foul...
but the referee plays the advantage.
The ball is still with Lee.
The rebound is high...
and Lee will shoot!
It hits the woodwork!
And the goalie throws...
himself at the ball!
Lee was just one step too late.
Lung Wah's...
on the attack now.
King and Lee, what a pair!
King is now marked...
by two men.
And King will try anything he knows.
King's in possession now.
And he passes the ball...
to the right wing.
And the winger passes it back to him.
King dribbled past Lee
near the goal line.
And he scores...
with a banana shot!
- Great!
- King's really good.
What a great shot!
- Well?
- Calm down!
What do you think?
Want to carry on?
Boss!
Lung Wah lead...
by one goal!
Lee's having a private duel with King.
It's a throw in.
I know your tricks!
Suen gains possession...
in the penalty area.
And he passes the ball to the left.
Great teamwork
and the ball's back with Suen.
He evaded three men...
and passes the ball to Lee.
Lee's here... good.
A couple of great...
dummies from Lee.
Down the goal line and a great cross!
It hits a defender and falls for Suen.
He chips it forward
and Lee scores with a header.
They've pulled one back!
Be alert!
We have made a score.
Hsin Sang...
on the attack now.
It's a foul!
They have seized the ball.
The goalie saves well...
from Lee.
Suen tries to score from the rebound.
And King knocks it on to the crossbar.
And King saves the day again!
Be alert!
Now King's have a go at the goalie.
Block the referee!
The match is turning...
into a fight.
Like kung-fu, with a shield.
King and Lee are having...
a go at each other.
And the referee booked Lee.
- I'll sent you off if you do it again!
- Referee!
Suen is not happy about it.
Have you seen this before?
And the referee blows the whistle
for halftime.
Lung Wah launch attack after attack.
But they're stopped by Hsin Sang.
Lee dribbled past several players.
He forgets about teamwork now.
It's a private duel between Lee and King.
King dashes into the penalty area.
But he was dispossessed by Suen.
Suen starts a counter-attack.
And he was fouled from behind.
Sorry, I didn't mean it.
It's not Suen. Maybe it's Bao.
Stand closer!
Take a few steps backward!
A free kick for Hsin Sang
and another name in the book.
Suen and Lee are having a conference.
They put one of their own men
in the wall.
Lee moves away from the ball.
Suen shots and
hit the player in the face.
It look like he has lost a tooth.
Here come Hsin Sang again.
Suen kicked Chan Ming.
The two are having a tussle.
But the referee waves play on.
Play on.
Are you ok?
Just go, mark King.
King has taken control of the game.
He is ready to send over a cross.
Hsin Sang must reorganize the defense.
King ascores with a brilliant...
first time shot.
We scored a goal.
Two-one, we're leading.
Now Sue retaliates!
He has...
three players on him!
Lee Tong is there, he can't shoot...
He plays a one two with Lee.
And Suen collides with the goalie.
But the referee waves play on!
Lung Wah are on the attack again!
Go on... move.
King has a great chance...
to score again.
He rounded...
the goalie.
He's not shooting. He's too proud.
And he makes it three one.
The referee has gone over to Suen.
Are you alright?
It looks like...
he is badly hurt.
Help him out.
The referee has summoned for a stretcher.
- We lost one player.
- Yes.
Still have chance.
Light it.
Let's see what Lee can do without Suen.
He dribbled past a few players.
He sees there is someone on the right.
Pass it to the right and get it.
But he does not have Suen
to meet his pass.
The ball is robbed and Lung Wah attack.
There are only a few minutes to go.
Lung Wah are leading...
by three one.
Hsin Sang are still trying to draw level.
Or reduce the deficit.
And the ball is now back with the goalie.
Lung Wah are using time-wasting tactics.
Defeat Hsin Sang.
Lee is now on his own.
He has no one to help him.
More time-wasting tactics from Lung Wah.
And they're passing the ball back...
and forth between them.
He's leg is mine.
Are you spitting again?
I'm sorry!
Again!
No, it's raining!
They just have to try their luck.
The ground has become very slippery.
It's muddy, too!
Let's see if they can score.
Lee takes the chance.
Lee have a go with a shot.
But is was saved by the goalie.
But the goalie dropped the ball.
It's in Hsin Sang's possession but...
King slipped...
and Lee robbed him.
It's turning...
into a real farce.
But time is running out...
on Hsin Sang.
Here's another chance...
for them.
Shoot...
But Lee slipped
just when he was about to shot.
He has even lost...
one of his boots.
Time is running out!
Lee is now bare footed.
But he plays on!
He dribbled past two defenders.
And another one!
He has King...
a front of him now.
His shot hits...
the goalie.
An overhead kick.
It's a goal.
Another score.
They're now only one goal behind.
Lee can surely play...
without boots.
He's quick.
Can they draw level?
Everybody is falling about...
on the pitch.
Only Lee can...
stand firm.
Lee's attacking on the right.
A great shot from the edge of the area.
But it was blocked by a defender.
King takes off his boots.
He looks like a monster.
Lee's now in the penalty area.
He shoot against a defender...
and the goalie saves.
Lee tries again but no luck.
It looks like...
Hsin Sang will lose this match.
The referee
has been knocked off his feet.
Where's my whistle?
Lee is charring towards goal.
But King robs him of the ball.
Lee shoots...
and the goalie saves.
Lee shoots again!
But King saves on the goal line.
You are going to lose.
He passes...
the ball back to the goalie.
But the ball bounces
over the goalie's head.
We call it being hit by land mine.
And it gets stuck...
in the water.
It is not a goal.
The ball is loose.
Both Lee and King are racing towards it.
King beats Lee but it's an own goal!
The final score is three all.
You'll soon vanish from the scene!
Break both his legs!
We did it at the very last moment!
Thanks to King who scored for us!
You're in luck today.
King deserved to be punished.
Left or right?
Both!
Like him?
Can you spare a dime please?
Just like him!