I don't feel anything.
It's graduation.
Mr. Carroll ridicules me all
year. Then he writes in my yearbook:
"You're a live wire.
Love, Mr. Carroll. "
He wants to go on good terms.
When he uses "love,"
I look for a new word.
Lloyd, she's being difficult.
- I'm taking out Diane Court.
- Not likely.
- Is the movies a good second date?
- You never had a first.
I sat across from her in a mall.
We ate.
- Sharing an important physical event.
- That's not even a scam.
- A scam?
- Going out as friends.
- No, scam is lusting.
- Then what's a date?
A date is prearrangement
with a possibility for love.
Then what's love?
I'm gonna call her.
She doesn't date guys like you.
She's a brain.
With the body of a game-show hostess.
She doesn't know she's pretty.
- That's what's cool about her.
- Brains stay with brains.
If a bomb goes off,
their genes form the same cliques.
- I wouldn't get my hopes up.
- I'm sorry.
You're a really nice guy.
We don't wanna see you get hurt.
I wanna get hurt!
"It's almost over. We've gone
to school together for three years."
- I might cut that part.
- Why? That's fine. It's nice.
"Having taken courses at the
university, I've glimpsed our future.
And all I can say is:
'Go back.'"
"Go back"? What a great line.
- You like it?
- Yeah.
- I didn't think anyone would get it.
- No, it's wonderful. It's...
No, don't worry about it.
You're very funny.
- "Go back." That's great.
- No more. I'm gonna save it.
I decided long ago
Never to walk in anyone's shadow
If I fail
If I succeed
At least I live as I believe
No matter what they take from me
They can't take away my dignity
Because the greatest love of all
Is happening to me
I found the greatest
Love of all inside of me
I love you guys!
Thanks, pal.
Party at Vahlere's.
Gonna be eight kegs. Be there.
Thank you, Joe.
Thank you.
And now it's time.
I just can't introduce this person
without saying, "History...
...oceanography, creative writing...
...biochemistry. " I think
you know who I'm talking about.
We'll remember this student who said:
"Hey, worid. Check me out!"
Giving a speech entitled
"Soaring Ahead"...
...Miss Diane Court.
Thank you.
The real worid.
Look at those eyes.
We're all about to enter
the real worid.
That's what everybody says.
But most of us have been
in the real worid a long time.
But I've something to tell everybody.
I've glimpsed our future
and all I can say is:
"Go back."
Well...
...it's almost over.
We've gone to school together
for three years...
...and we've been through a lot.
But with that training net
of high school gone...
...what's gonna happen to us?
We all know what the answers are.
We wanna be happy, go to college,
work hard, maybe raise a family.
But what if that doesn't happen?
I have to be honest, though.
I have all the hope
and ambition in the worid.
But when I think about the future...
...the truth is...
...I am...
...really...
...scared.
All right. Get up on it.
Yay! All right.
- See you at home.
- Okay.
Do yourself and everyone
who loves you a favor.
- Don't talk to Joe.
- Mom...
Stop, okay?
- Bye.
- See you later, Mrs. Flood.
- Look at those eyes.
- Give it up.
- Take a picture of me with her.
- Lloyd.
- That's just embarrassing.
- Please?
- All right, okay.
- Do it.
- Wait till I get around to her.
- All right, man. I got it.
Your graduation present
is parked right over there.
Are you kidding? That?!
- Lloyd?
- Hey, sis!
I'm sorry. I had a new crown,
three root canals...
...and Jason has a sore throat.
Your graduation and no one was there.
I called Mom and Dad,
and it's like they were there.
- I hope you understand.
- Hey. Bad throat, huh, J-man?
Yeah.
He's not at full "Yeah!" strength.
Poor little man.
Why do you eat that stuff?
There's no food in your food.
- Too loud. The red line has a purpose.
- How do you know how to draw it?
It's loud enough,
and the neighbors don't complain.
Good thing there's not
a red line on you. Yeah!
- Yeah!
- He's back!
My brother, can I borrow
your Hey, Soul Classics?
My brother, you gotta go buy your own.
- Hook it off the jab.
- Can't you be an uncle, not a playmate?
- Jesus Christ.
- What?
Get in a good mood. How hard is it
to decide to be in a good mood...
...and then be in a good mood?
- Gee, it's easy.
I'm sorry Mom and Dad
made you take me in.
If it's a big deal, I'll go.
But you used to be fun.
You were warped, twisted
and hilarious.
I mean it as a compliment.
I mean, I'm sorry...
...that T-l-M left you.
But I am not T-l-M.
- I was hilarious once, wasn't I?
- Yeah.
I still am.
- You gotta teach me stick shift.
Promise.
Come here a minute.
I want to show you something.
What are you doing?
Since I'm both your father
and your friend...
...I had to get you two presents.
- God, this is ridiculous.
Here's the only thing
your mom gave me that I kept.
Now it's yours.
Go ahead. Open it now.
I don't need all these presents.
I don't know any kid who got a car.
Oh, God.
Wow, it's beautiful.
They really applauded
for you today, honey.
Looking at all the people,
I felt like they didn't know me.
Maybe I shouldn't have taken
all those courses off school...
...because everybody thinks I...
- Forget it.
- Wait a minute.
- Everybody thinks you're what?
- Everybody thinks I'm a priss.
Diane, in a million years,
you could never be a priss.
It's all working out for you, honey.
Do you see?
It's working out just like we planned.
All the summer schools,
the vacations you gave up...
Stop it. Stop it. Stop it.
Sorry.
- I love you, Dad.
- I love you too, honey.
Come on, come on, come on.
Yah! Yah!
Diane Court!
Suck it.
Come on. Get the bag.
An exciting kick.
My brother. Let's go.
Yah! Yah! Yah!
You're headed for daycare, buddy.
- Be tough, J-man.
- He's a mess!
I'll be in my office.
- I just washed this shirt, didn't I?
- Yeah!
Please, not in my ear. Not in my ear.
Jim Court.
- Hello. May I please speak with Diane?
- Sorry, Diane isn't in at the moment.
- Oh, okay.
- This the guy with the Mustang?
- No.
- Guy with the Datsun?
- The truck?
- No, not really.
You don't know me.
I'm a friend of Diane's.
I sat with her yesterday at a mall.
I drive a blue Chevy Malibu.
I'm pretty bad at this,
but what I want to do is, can I...?
Give me your number.
That's usually how it works.
Okay. Lloyd Dobler. 555-1342.
It's 555-1342.
- 555- 1342.
- Okay, I'll get her the message.
- She's pretty great, isn't she?
- What?
- She's really pretty great, isn't she?
- She is. Good luck, kid.
Good afternoon. Okay, bye.
Jim Court.
No, this is her father. Can I take...?
What?
No, I didn't get the letter.
Yes!
Yes, right away.
Yeah, thank you. Goodbye.
Ricky, don't lose that number
Don't call nobody else
Send it off in a letter
To yourself
Ricky, don't lose that number
Oh, Mr. Taylor.
You're a vision in green.
I'll mail this for you. You can trust
a man who writes a letter daily.
- Diane here? I gotta talk to her.
- She's upstairs.
I gotta tell you this carefully.
Would you mind?
- Just a few minutes.
- Yes, sir.
Great. It won't be long. Thanks.
What?
- I had a phone call.
- Tell me.
- Is it bad news?
- Just listen.
You won the Reed Fellowship.
Are you kidding?
You're not kidding?
You're not kidding!
You'll study at
the finest institute in England.
- The toughest fellowship in England.
- I won?
You're gonna take a big step.
I want one thing from you.
You stand up straight.
Admit you're special.
- God. I'll have to go on a plane.
- Worry about that later.
Now, come on.
Tell me that you're special.
You're too good at making me nervous.
Listen! You're the best
in the country, don't you understand?
It's like a pyramid.
It starts with everyone...
...and it narrows through your life.
The competition narrows it down
to one brilliant person...
...who is so special they celebrate
you on two continents. It's you.
So tell me something.
Where's the flaw in that?
There is no flaw.
Hello?
Yeah, just a second, Corey.
Oh, sorry.
Diane Court.
- Don't go in there.
- Forget it. It's mine!
It's too bad.
No noise, no sound,
no movement, nothing.
Hello. Diane?
Hi. You called me?
I read about your fellowship,
and I'm glad you called me back.
I just wanted to congratulate you...
...and tell you I thought
your speech was incredible.
- Thank you very much.
- Whoa, what a day, huh?
Yeah. What a day.
- Yeah.
- Do you know who I am?
- We sat together at Bell Square.
- You remember.
- No, I read it on the message.
Okay, so it's Lloyd and let's go out.
- You wanna go out?
- Thanks, but I'm busy.
- Busy.
- Things are pretty hectic, but thanks.
- You busy on Friday?
- Yeah, I have to help my father.
- How about Saturday?
- I have things to do around the house.
So you're too monumentally busy?
Well, not monumentally.
What about tonight then?
You going to Vahlere's party?
You can't leave the country
without going to Vahlere's.
The gentleman is 22 and comes out
of hiding once a year for this...
...dressed as the Lakeside Rooster.
He makes Purple Passion drinks...
- I think that...
- You're not in England yet.
I lived in England for three months.
My parents are in the Army,
so we lived in England and Germany.
I could give you many English tips.
- Well...
- I won't give any tips of any kind.
- I'll go.
- Pardon me?
- You will?
Excellent. This is great.
- You will, really?
- I'll go.
We're going out. It's a date.
It's a scam. Whatever. All right.
- I'll pick you up at what, 8:00?
- Eight.
Eight o'clock.
- Goodbye.
Lloyd Dobler...
Thank you, little man.
Now work that bag, J-man.
Hook off the jab. Straight left hand.
- What do we love?
- Pain!
Work that jab! Work that hook!
Okay, take a break.
Be right there!
Hi. Lloyd Dobler, sir.
- Pleasure to meet you.
- Hi.
Heard about the graduation gift.
Really quite a car.
I know you're busy
so no need to entertain me.
You can trust me. I'm 19.
Was overseas for a few semesters.
I rarely drink, as I kickbox.
It's the sport of the future.
Don Wilson? Benny Urquidez?
Your face says no.
Your daughter will be safe with me
for the next seven to eight hours.
Fine, Lloyd.
- Come in.
- Thank you.
- How you doing?
- I'm...
- Is she around?
- Honey?
Whoa.
Hi.
- Would you hold this for me?
- Yeah.
- What are these?
- Bavarian Dutch-style pretzels.
Um... Would it be terrible
if I wanted to go home early?
No.
You're not gonna believe this.
- Oh, my...
- Oh, my God.
Hi, Lloyd.
You okay? Want a drink?
What's up, Lloyd?
- What's happening?
- What's up, man?
Hey, Dobler!
We are out of control!
That's not happening.
Now I gotta go to summer school.
How you doing?
- It's gotta stay purple all night.
- How you doing?
- You know Diane Court?
- Diane! Well...
- I need you to be the Keymaster.
- I was just...
He's very responsible. Thanks a lot.
- I was gonna move around. Thanks.
- "Keymaster"?
I gotta judge who can drive
and who can't, and keep their keys.
- So it's an honor.
- No.
- We finally graduated, big-dude guy!
- All right!
I'm so glad you came to this.
I've always wanted you
to come to one of these.
I wish you'd done that
without the keys!
- Come on. There are so many cute guys.
Let go of me!
- I love you, man!
- I love you too.
- Homeboy! Mike Cameron. How you doing?
- Hey.
- What?
- Mike Cameron. This is one fresh jam.
I don't know you very well,
but I wanted to ask you...
...how you got Diane Court
to go out with you.
- I called her.
- But how come it worked?
- I mean, like, what are you?
- I'm Lloyd Dobler.
- Great, this gives me hope. Thanks.
- All right.
Key?
I wrote 63 songs
about Joe this year...
...and I'm gonna play
every one tonight.
I just saw Joe. He's here.
Don't be so dramatic about it.
You did try and kill yourself
because of the guy.
What was it like afterwards?
I've always wanted to know.
She explained it
in "Wake up, Seattle."
Stop. I am fine now. I am all right.
All everybody does is ask me
about this. I am fine.
Did Joe come with Mimi tonight?
Keys.
Keys, everybody.
- All right, Keymaster.
- Right.
- How you doing?
- Good.
I got you!
- How are you, Mrs. Evans?
You missed every
career counseling session.
Call me obsessive-compulsive,
but we must do this now.
- No way!
- Lloyd.
- What?
- You must...
- Get away!
- What did I do?
- Don't even follow me!
- Don't do this.
Don't make me sound like a counselor.
I've got statistics and graphs.
I got all this stuff
that say the same thing:
"You have to decide on a career."
My dad's an Army colonel.
He wants me to join.
There's no possible way.
Take a look at Seattle Junior College.
- You the Keymaster?
- I'm not gonna go there.
I'm looking for something bigger...
...a dare-to-be-great situation.
- Only your record is blank.
- Do people really know what they want?
Many think they have to know.
But inside, they don't.
I don't know.
But I know that I don't know.
Hang tough, Lloyd.
We were "ultra-competitive"...
...but I just want to say
if it wasn't for "Diane Court"...
...I wouldn't have gotten in Cornell.
You made me study twice as hard.
So thanks.
- You did the same for me.
- I did?
Did you really come here
with Lloyd Dobler?
- How did that "happen"?
- He made me laugh.
Yes.
He's okay, Dad.
You're welcome.
I always call you. You know that.
Stop being so grateful. All right.
I'll be home before dawn, okay?
- Bye.
- Dawn?
- Would you guys sign my annual?
- Sure.
- Would you sign mine?
- Did you have to call your dad?
- God, how nightmarish!
- I promised.
- Will he wait up?
- Say nothing.
I come in crying. He leaves me alone.
I loved your speech,
about being scared.
Lloyd Dobler. All right.
He...
... likes giris...
... with names...
... like Ashley...
... and Tamerlane
I'll be in the kitchen, Joe.
That'll never be me
That'll never be
Never be me, no!
That'll never be me
Joe. Joe.
Sex, love...
She's written 65 songs.
Sixty-five. They're all about you.
- They're all about pain.
- So, what's up?
So stop playing
with her mind, you know?
She's a human being.
She's very talented.
Why do you think I keep her tapes?
They're gonna be valuable someday.
No
Never
No, never, ever, ever
Don't you ever think it
Oh, my God.
Joe was my first love, my first sex,
and the whole time he was dating Mimi.
He'll never break up with her.
But if I see him, it's:
"Hi, Joe. How are you?"
And that is it.
I'll be okay.
Don't worry.
He's at the other end of the house.
It's too bad more guys
can't be like Lloyd.
He checks up on me. Look.
I got some more songs.
Joe lies
When he cries
- So we can finally talk.
- Yeah.
Well... What?
Lakewood, Lakewood, have no fear!
How about another year?
- He does this every year?
- The worst job since Keymaster.
Hi, Joe. How are you?
I love you.
I love you too.
You invade my soul.
I wanna get back together.
Mimi's gonna go to college,
and I'm gonna be alone.
But I'm gonna break up with her
before she leaves.
Have sex with me.
Goodbye, Joe.
Every year I throw this party.
Every year nobody helps me clean up.
- Why am I yelling?
- I don't know.
- We're out of here.
- Thanks.
- Maybe we'll help you clean tomorrow.
- Diane, everyone loved that you came.
- You're a great rooster.
- Well...
- Sign this?
- Okay.
Hey, Corey.
So I'm single now.
Everything's changed. I hate it.
- Give me my Firebird keys!
- You must chill!
You must chill!
I have hidden your keys! Chill!
- I love you!
- Love you too. Go to sleep.
- We're full-on buds.
- Yeah, all right.
You're a great person.
I'm a good person,
but you're a great person.
- We're out of there. See you tomorrow.
- See you. Bye.
- Bye, Diane.
- Bye.
Hey, drive safe.
Thank you.
I surrender my duties
as Keymaster. A beer.
Certainly.
I'm happy to say that this sack
is officially empty.
The back bathroom. Let's go.
- Look at this gentleman here.
I gotta get home.
Excuse me.
How you doing, brother?
I don't even know where we are.
I'm gonna play three hours
of commercial-free rock...
- Oh, I love this album.
- This is a good one.
Like it?
Do you recognize anything yet?
Anything?
Lord, have mercy.
Three hours of
commercial-free rock...
That's my house! I live there.
Have a good sleep.
Bye.
Thanks a lot.
Hey, you guys are the best.
Give me a call or...
- Look at this one.
- Did you...?
So, what did they write
to Diane Court?
Listen to some of the things
they wrote me.
"Glad I finally met you.
You always seemed nice."
"Wish I'd known you more."
Mine says stuff like,
"Lloyd, see you around, maybe."
- Nobody knew me before.
- They knew of you. Now they know you.
I feel like I fit in for
the first time, you know?
Like I just held them far away
from me, so they did the same to me.
That's cool then.
Yeah.
I'm so glad we did this.
We can walk from here.
- It's just you and your dad?
- Long story.
- You don't wanna hear it.
- Sure, I do.
Well, my parents split up
when I was 13 and...
God, I actually had to go to court
and choose between the two of them.
So I chose my dad. Just felt
safer that way, you know?
Watch out for that glass.
Thanks.
- But either way it's still...
- Twisted.
You know what? You're a great date.
I've never gone out
with someone so basic.
Basic?
- What's your job this summer?
- Being a great date.
- No, I'm serious.
- So am I.
I wanna see you as much as I can.
I said it!
- I only have something like 16 weeks.
- That's a long time.
- Then call me tomorrow.
- Today is tomorrow.
- Then call me later.
- Okay.
Thanks.
I'll call you later.
Morning, honey.
Dad, I'm so glad I went. Good night.
Wait. Wait a minute.
How was Lloyd?
Lloyd was a gentleman.
He was funny, nervous and strange.
I met people I'd never met before.
Then I blew it. I called him "basic."
- Can you believe I did that?
- Well...
I don't think he's reeling
in embarrassment.
Good night.
Lloyd is doomed.
- Meaning?
She made this date a family audition,
the kiss of death for Lloyd.
- Why?
- Too much pressure. Not his crowd.
What's wrong with her?
- I told him to be himself.
- He has that nervous talking thing.
I told him not to speak.
This is a strange thing to say,
but maybe Diane really likes Lloyd.
If you were her,
would you honestly fall for Lloyd?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Should I wear this dress?
- Yeah.
- Or I could always wear this one.
- That's nice.
I forgot to tell you
who'll be at dinner tonight.
My dad's accountant and two women
that work in his nursing home.
I know you don't know them,
but it'll be fun.
- Boy, this is a mother dictionary.
- I know. I've had it forever.
I used to mark the words
that I looked up.
Or I have this one.
- Nice one.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, you should wear that.
- Think so?
- Better get downstairs, huh?
- I'll change.
Great meal, you two.
- You look beautiful, Diane.
- Thank you.
Same features. See what
a few millimeters can do?
What airline are you flying?
- A charter.
She's not the greatest flyer.
- When she was 8...
- Dad.
- Now, why can't I tell the story?
- What story?
- If you're gonna tell it, let me.
- Well, let me start.
I decide to take her
on her first airplane.
I knew how planes flew
but I was nervous.
Crash paranoia.
I had a list. If babies were on
the plane, it couldn't crash.
But their crying meant
they knew something.
They closed the doors and she screams,
like nobody I'd ever heard.
- You said, "Turn around."
- They did.
- Let me finish.
- Okay.
So two federal marshals
meet the plane.
They take our address and ask us
never to fly the friendly skies again.
- You never flew?
- No.
But there's more!
There was somebody on the plane...
...who worked in a recording studio.
He's making a sound effects record,
and he wants to record her scream.
Which they did. And once
in a while on a commercial...
...you can hear me scream.
You two are amazing. You know?
The way you... The way you talk.
I'm just like that...
I'm not like that with anybody.
- Stellar jukebox, sir.
- Thanks.
- How do you obtain one of those?
- What did we pay for the Wurlitzer?
The guy didn't want to part with it.
A matter of $9000?
- So you graduated Lakewood, right?
- Yes, sir.
- What are you gonna do now?
- Yeah, Lloyd.
What are your plans for the future?
Spend as much time as possible
with Diane before she leaves.
Seriously.
- I'm totally and completely serious.
- No, really.
You mean a career?
I don't know. I've...
I've thought about this quite a bit,
and I would have to say...
...I don't wanna sell, buy,
or process anything as a career.
Or sell anything bought or processed
or buy anything sold or processed...
...or process anything
sold or bought...
...or repair anything sold,
bought or processed.
My father's in the Army.
He wants me to join, but I can't
work for that corporation.
So lately I've been kickboxing.
Which is a new sport,
but I think it's got a good future.
As far as career longevity,
you can't really tell.
Eight and six as a fighter is no good.
But I can't tell if I'm great
until I've had pro fights.
I haven't been knocked down.
I can't figure it all out,
so I'm gonna hang with Diane.
Hello.
- Mr. James Court?
- Can I help you?
I'm Mr. Sims. This is Mr. Talbot.
We're special agents of the IRS.
We'd like to inform you that you're
under criminal investigation...
...for the tax years
1982 through 1986.
Jesus. What, I live in
a palace, right?
I have guests here.
- Understand the following...
- Speak with my lawyer.
You won't answer questions?
Just come down to my office.
I have guests.
We will be contacting a number
of your business associates...
- This evening is over.
...and your former wife.
Mom, please.
I do have a history with this man,
and it's not the greatest.
I see you so seldom.
I'd rather hear about you.
This is me telling you about me.
I don't know if you have a boyfriend.
What could be more important
than what's going on with Dad?
If we could talk about boys,
everything would be so much easier.
Your room is always ready.
You can always come home if you want.
All right. What do you want me to do?
If they ask you questions...
...would you please say
something nice about him, Mom?
Help him?
- All right.
- You will?
Okay. Oh, here's Ray.
Talk to him. When you don't,
your mouth turns down. Hi!
Hello, pretty ladies.
Hi, Diane.
Hi, Ray.
What are you doing after work?
I have a break after dinner,
if you wanna stop by.
- Wanna do something later?
- I know you think my job's strange.
- You don't like old people, do you?
- Sure I do.
Come on.
I used to work at a smorgasbord.
Old people came, and they love to eat.
They jammed their mouths, ate with
their mouths open and it was too much.
You think about how short life is...
...and how maybe life has no meaning.
You're frying burgers.
Then you're like 60, you die
and what are you doing?
I don't need to think about it.
That's the reason I was...
But I'm not sure I'm right.
That's ageism, being prejudiced
against people because they're old.
- Maybe their mouths don't work well.
- Really?
Well, you're really
turning me around here.
I was looking at it
the wrong way, I think.
- Should I still come by?
- Stop by later.
- Okay. I will.
- Okay. Bye.
I'll see you later. Bye.
You have to meet Bess.
She's amazing. She's 93.
She's a writer.
- And I told her about you.
- You told her about me?
What did you say?
Just meet her.
- Hi.
This is Bess. Lloyd, Bess.
- Hello.
You're too tall.
She likes you.
Okay, how you doing?
I'm Lloyd.
We're gonna watch Cocoon. I haven't
seen it but I hear it's good.
I hear it makes you happy,
so I figure that's a good film to see.
Some older people go to space...
Hope I didn't spoil it.
It hasn't started yet, Mr. Taylor.
- Thank you.
Good!
You gonna stay?
Sure.
Why can't I eat popcorn?
I'll get you something.
Okay. So here we go with Cocoon.
- So they're cool.
- That was good.
I feel so bad being with you.
I feel like I should be spending
more time with my dad.
Half the time I'm with you,
I'm thinking of other things.
Everybody does that.
I just don't want it to get too heavy.
I feel really overloaded.
I have a theory that good things
always happen with bad things.
I know you have to deal with them
at the same time but I just...
I don't know why they have
to happen at the same time.
I wish I could work out a schedule.
Am I babbling? Know what I mean?
No.
I just can't have a social life now.
Don't worry, we're just
having coffee. We'll be anti-social.
- Be friends?
- Yeah. With potential.
Friends with potential.
Keep going in first.
Feel the clutch. Put it in a little.
It'll come out. Then you'll feel...
A little more.
That's right. Go around, in first.
Keep it in first.
It's kind of all right.
When you feel you're confident,
if you'll just ease into second...
All right. Well, put it...
- Am I wrecking my car?
- You are a little bit.
But listen...
...when you feel it start to give,
put the clutch in.
- I was putting the gas on when...
- Because... Little more gas.
Ease it out. All right.
Don't worry. Minor setback.
You feel confident? You feel better.
Now go into second. Little more gas.
Yeah.
You'll get this. No problem.
Now, maybe, you downshift. First.
- Does this sound normal?
- As you get better, you'll hear less.
Brake.
Let's switch. Wanna switch?
I'll drive?
I'm sorry.
- Let's go. You want to?
- Yeah.
Are you comfortable?
- Yes.
Are you shaking?
No.
You're shaking.
- I don't think so.
- You're cold.
- I don't think I am.
- Then why are you shaking?
I don't know.
I think I'm happy.
Here's some blanket.
Listen to this song.
It's a really good song.
Good morning.
- Dad, I'm sorry.
- You should be.
- I should have called.
- You bet you should have!
Don't make me call the police.
Don't make me call hospitals.
Dad, I'm so sorry.
I know this is a bad time.
I'm not asking what you did.
I wanna know...
...if you're okay.
- I'm fine.
You wanna make things easier?
Tell me where you were.
This is bullshit!
- You can say anything to me, you know.
- I know that.
I spent the night with him.
- Lloyd?
- Dad, yes.
And I'm scared to death of what
you must think of me right now.
Sit down.
Dad, do you know what he did
the first night I went out with him?
We were walking across by the 7-11...
...and he pointed out some glass
for me to walk around.
I think of that when people say,
"What are you doing with Lloyd?"
And I never get nervous around him.
So we started spending all
this time together, as friends.
But I could feel him getting anxious.
And then...
...I knew that there would be
a confrontation over getting physical.
He started to get that look
at the end of the night.
Do you know that look?
You know it will be an issue.
So I went through all the feelings
and arguments you go through...
- Did he ever get rough with you?
- Dad, no.
But I didn't want any problems,
so I decided not to sleep with him.
But then I attacked him anyway.
It always feels good
to tell you the truth.
Because...
...if I can't share it with you,
it's almost like it didn't happen.
Did you sleep with her?
- I admit nothing.
- It's us.
- Look at his face. He did the deed.
- You're an inspiration, Lloyd.
All right, calm down.
Nothing's different.
Lloyd, listen to me. Everything
has changed. You've had sex.
Nothing will ever be the same
between you two.
You might be 60, you'll see her,
talk to her, whatever...
But what you'll really
be thinking is, "We had sex."
- Your point?
- Do something special.
- You gotta make a statement.
- Wait...
Show her respect.
Show her you're not like Joe.
- Wait...
- Above all...
...just because this happened
gives you no right...
- You never let me talk.
- What? I'm sorry. Talk.
Forgot what I was gonna say.
Okay, I remember.
- Let him do what he wants.
- All right.
Send her flowers
or write her a letter.
I already did.
- What's it say?
- Just read it.
I can read it?
Oh, man.
"Dear Diane:
I'll always be there for you.
All the love in my heart...
...LIoyd."
I've never gotten a letter
like this. Have you?
- I dream about it.
- So, what do you think?
- You think I'm...?
- Get ready for greatness, Lloyd.
The Cynthia Bramson estate
was worth how much?
- Her family...
- Family? Never heard from them.
I sold her house for her.
Made her money.
Your income, Mr. Court...
...hasn't changed substantially
in 17 years.
That's right.
Why would you stay so long
with an operation...
...that is clearly not
a growth enterprise?
Caring for people
isn't a growth enterprise.
Write that down.
I'd like your boss to read it.
Diane!
Ticket to England came today.
Maybe I shouldn't go
with all that's happening.
You're going.
If a friend were in the same position,
I'd tell her to stay.
- You're going.
- It doesn't feel right.
- I don't even have the right luggage.
- Bon voyage.
- You're not listening to me.
- Let's stop this right now.
Let's not put our energy
into something ridiculous.
This isn't smart thinking.
Why are you acting this way?
Is it because of the other morning?
You love him?
- I like him a lot.
- Now, I know you like him.
He's not like those
frat kids you dislike.
But when the excitement wears off...
...what are you gonna talk about?
You'll be in an
international think tank...
...and he's gonna be
kicking punching bags.
I think you should break up with him.
Unbelievable. This is a nightmare.
It'd be best to get on
that plane with no strings...
...because once you leave,
things will change.
I've talked about this
with you and with him.
It's well-covered territory.
I'm not asking you to sever
all relations with the boy.
Give him a present. Here.
Let him know you still care.
Give him this pen.
A pen?
Dad, in a million years,
I would never give him a pen.
Why can't I have fun? I like him.
"I like him"? I'm talking
about being honest and decent...
Dad, I love him.
Great.
No, that's great.
It's great to hear
you say that because...
I don't know.
What, am I being selfish?
Why am I so fixated?
Maybe because I've got
a lot of troubles with...
Is that it? Am I being selfish?
I want you to have everything.
Is that wrong?
I owe you an apology.
I've just got a few weeks
left with you and we...
I don't know what I'm trying to say.
They think I'm guilty.
Some computer spits out your name
and another honest man...
What's the goddamn point?
Live your life.
- I love you.
- Oh, Dad, I'm so sorry.
All right now, power left!
Power right!
- Who's worid champ?
- Don "The Dragon" Wilson!
Lloyd! Telephone!
Keep kicking.
Hello?
Hi.
How you doing?
Yeah, they actually pay me for this.
I'll pick you up in an hour.
See you later.
Check your mail tomorrow.
I sent you a letter. A blue letter.
- It came yesterday.
- It did?
- It was wonderful.
- You didn't tell me?
- I never sent a letter like that.
I sent it... Well, I don't know...
I wanted to say something
but I didn't.
But I think I want to now.
But I'm not sure.
Many say it and don't mean it,
but I think I do.
- So I wanted to say...
- We don't have to say it.
- How do you know what it is?
- I don't...
...but thank you.
- I love you.
- I said it.
- I know.
- Let's not put things on this level.
- What? This is a good level.
Isn't it?
- How can I look at you and say this?
- Say what?
I think we should spend
some time apart.
- What's wrong?
- Well...
...I need to study...
- You need to study?
How much time do you need?
You'll be leaving soon,
so I'm just asking.
We'll see.
Okay.
- It's good knowing this.
- Yeah.
Wait a minute.
What did we just decide?
- We decided...
- Did you break up with me?
- It sounded like it.
- We decided to be friends.
It sounds terrible but...
If we're friends,
can't we see each other?
I think that we should stop
going out on dates.
Oh.
I feel like a dick.
- You must think I'm a dick.
- No.
- I don't.
- You do.
We shared the most intimate thing.
- You shared it with a dick.
- No, I didn't.
- Is this because of your dad?
- No.
Did you talk to Corey?
- Why? Did you tell her?
- She figured it out.
No, she'll tell everybody,
but that's fine.
- Did you tell anybody?
- Just my dad.
You told your dad?
You have Corey and D.C.
I have my dad.
I'm sorry I said that.
I said what I thought I meant...
...but forget it.
- Lloyd.
- "I love you." Okay?
- What are you doing with your hands?
You're talking like that girl Sheila.
Don't be mean!
This is hard for me too.
Then don't do it.
Shit.
Would you just take this pen,
please, and write me?
I don't believe this.
You just broke up with me.
Hello, Constance? It's me, Lloyd.
Nothing. I'm just driving around.
She broke up with me.
What do I do? How can I get her back?
I can't get her to talk to me.
It's all so fucked up.
I feel like crying.
She gave me a pen.
I gave her my heart.
Just come home, okay?
I'll be home soon.
Most don't know what
to do after graduation.
But I've got guaranteed
skill training. In the Army.
Reserve the Army's sought-after
technical training...
... 12 months in advance.
It's me. Cruising around.
I know I haven't called you lately.
I didn't wanna be reminded of Diane.
I've wiped her from my mind. I don't
remember when or where I knew her.
Here's the site of our
controversial first date.
I met her in a mall.
I should've known
our relationship was doomed.
To our left, we have...
...the street where we broke up!
Here's the path we took.
Corey, I guess I blamed you
for letting me send the letter.
But I thought it was right too.
I think I know too many giris.
I should hang with more guys.
I should be like those guys who hang
at the AM-PM or the Gas 'n' Sip.
But do guys like that
know the answers?
No babe is worth it, you know?
We'll teach you bibles of truths.
You can't trust them. Know what it is?
They spend your money and tell
their friends. It's economics.
You gotta find a girl
who looks just like her...
...nail her and dump her.
Get her off your mind.
Diane Court is a show pony.
You need a stallion, my friend.
- Walk with us and walk tall.
Walk tall.
- Bitches, man!
Give him a complex.
- Dude, I better bail.
Okay, man.
- Later, Luke.
- Be cool, man.
I got a question.
If you know so much about women...
...why are you at a Gas 'n' Sip alone
on a Saturday, with no women anywhere?
- By choice, man.
- It's a conscious choice.
We're choosing to be here.
- I'm choosing it.
- Dude, where'd she dump you, man?
- My car.
- Your car?
- Dissed in the Malibu?
- Oh, heinous!
- That's your castle, man.
- No chance with a girl like that.
Hey, man. I was in love once, man.
I got hurt really bad.
I never wanna go through that again.
- You're bringing me down!
- Shut up, man!
We're going to a kegger.
We'd like you to come.
We're gonna find you a babe, man.
We're gonna find you one hot babe.
Instantly! Promise!
One hot babe for you!
I won't meet a girl
like Diane at a kegger.
She was different. We didn't even have
to go out to go out. We'd just hang.
The girl made me trust myself, man.
I was walking around,
feeling satisfied.
Can you imagine that?
And then she cuts me loose.
I don't know why. She won't say.
Who knows the reason?
Maybe it's her father. She won't
talk to me. Won't look at me.
Come on!
- Christ, what's up with you?
- You're freaking out!
- Chill, man!
- You're wigging.
He's wigging, man
He's wigging
I don't even feel that way
about my car.
He's wigging every day
Dude, name a babe, okay?
Any babe in Seattle. I'll set you up.
Diane Court!
Dude, I can't do it, buddy.
Lloyd, Lloyd
All null and void
Listen to the truth
You're trying to avoid, Lloyd
That was a mistake.
The rain on my car is a baptism.
I'm the new me.
Ice-man.
Power-Lloyd. My assault
on the worid begins now.
I believe in myself. Answer to no one.
You got it all figured out.
If you start out depressed,
everything's a pleasant surprise.
Look, why don't you
just call Diane again?
I stop at seven unreturned calls.
Understand that her family
is being ripped apart.
Like you and she were ripped apart.
Like Joe and I were ripped apart.
- Visit her at the home.
- I'm not going back there.
- I don't even know her.
- Why are you like this?
- Because I'm a guy. I have pride.
- You're not a guy.
I am.
The worid is full of guys. Be a man.
Don't be a guy.
If she wants me, she can come to me.
Hi. Lloyd.
- This is my eighth and final call.
- Pick it up if you want.
I've thought about it all, and I've
decided to give you another chance.
Maybe only your father is listening.
Hey, Mr. Court. Hello.
- If I get it, we'll get back together.
- Then don't.
Maybe I didn't know you.
Maybe the worid is a mirage...
... and everyone's hurtling
toward necropolis.
Maybe there's good in this.
You're probably screening.
Just one other thing. The letter
I wrote you. Could you rip it up?
Nuke it. Destroy it.
It hurts me to know it's out there.
Could you do that for me?
All right. Later.
Hello?
Hi.
- Is it for your wife?
- I'm unmarried. It's for my daughter.
- Going to school?
- She won a fellowship.
Good for her.
- I'll take the whole set.
- Excellent.
You got the best smile
I've seen all week.
Thanks. I like yours too.
I don't know your name,
but what are you doing for lunch?
I'm sorry, but they
turned down your card.
Oh! Well, here.
Let me give you another card.
Thanks.
I'm afraid I can't accept this either.
There's a decline code.
I'm supposed to confiscate it...
...but why don't you keep it?
- Keep it.
- Are you sure?
Yeah, I don't want it.
Thank you very much.
You've been very kind.
Dad, are you okay in there?
I'm just finishing up in here!
Regarding James Court?
Room 14.
I'm supposed to be leaving
on a fellowship...
...that I worked for my entire life,
and I don't even care.
I met this boy over the summer...
...and we can't talk because of this.
I can't talk to my dad.
I wore these clothes. I thought...
...if I looked right,
someone would talk to me.
But I look and feel awful.
Could you please talk to me?
Be a little decent.
We believe your father
has a large pool of cash...
...from phony billing, phony patients.
We've been investigating him.
When they die, he takes their money.
Pardon me?
Check it out for yourself.
See if your father fits the profile.
- What's the profile?
- Take a look around the house.
Are there a lot of rugs,
pieces of art, stereo equipment?
Things bought with cash?
Does he give lots of gifts?
- Do the major items in your house...?
- You want me to say something.
Don't let his business
infect your life.
- How can you say that?
- He's guilty.
No. He's not.
We have the records.
We have the proof.
I'm sorry to have to tell you this...
...but it's going to get worse.
If I were you,
I would take that fellowship.
Dad?
Anybody home?
They made me doubt you.
What happened to you?
Did you do it?
Did you take that money?
Sweetheart, no. Don't be ridiculous.
- Swear to God. I need the truth.
- Honey!
- Swear to God.
- I swear to God.
I found the money.
It's not what you think.
- What am I supposed to think?
- About what?
You stole from them! You lied to me!
- How do you think I feel?
- You know what this money is?
No, you don't! It's not for me!
It's for when you
get back from England...
...so you don't have to
depend on anybody.
I take better care of those people
than their families!
I care for them, give them flowers,
feed them, wipe their mouths!
- But you stole from them!
- I make their lives better!
You let me defend you.
You knew you were guilty, and you
let me become a part of it! How...?
Go ahead. When I'm old, give me
someone like me, but go ahead.
I trusted you. I stood up in court
five years ago and picked you!
Why are you being so hateful to me?
Because of Lloyd?
No. I told you everything,
and you lied to me.
- I would've done anything for you.
- Work it out.
No! I will.
I won't leave anything out
because I can say anything to you.
- You're a liar and a thief.
- Easy. I'm the only dad you got.
I'm so ashamed.
Don't say that. It's not good for you.
You're right.
No, talk... Diane!
Wait a minute! Talk...
Someone's here to see you.
Lloyd?
God.
Lloyd, I'm sorry.
What do you want?
I'm sorry.
My father's guilty. He lied to me.
He lied to everybody.
I just left home.
I need you.
You do?
Everything else means nothing to me.
If I hurt you again, I'll die.
Hurt me again? Not a chance.
- Don't worry about it.
- I love you.
- What?
How many more times
do I have to say it?
One more time would be nice.
I love you.
Please.
One question.
Are you here because you need someone,
or because you need me?
Forget it. I don't care.
I need you.
I love you.
- $ 75,000 fine and no jail.
- I can't do that.
This guy has been ripping off Grandma
and Grandpa for 17 years.
- I'd love to hear his story.
- $ 100,000 and three months?
125,000 and nine months.
I can accept that.
- The state takes the home.
- He can serve immediately.
- I can put that together.
- I'll confirm this with my client.
- I'll push it past my boss.
- All right.
Just sleep.
I brought her here,
but she won't get out of the car.
I wanted her to see you.
If you go away...
...and not deal with
your family stuff, you just...
- You going to England with her?
- Let's discuss that.
Are you?
Am I going?
Am I going to England?
I realize what I should do
is carve out a goal for my future...
...and find out what I want
to do with my life.
Diane and I can wait
for each other, right?
She's gonna run off
with some English guy? No way.
I admire you for not hitching a ride.
- She's not like you.
- I know.
- She's very successful. Very talented.
But then I reconsidered. Because
what I want to do with my life...
...what I want to do for a living,
is be with your daughter.
I'm good at it.
You're a distraction,
not a permanent part of her life.
I'm the distraction
going with her to England.
- Are you all right, sir? You okay?
- I'm incarcerated, Lloyd!
I don't deserve to lose
my daughter over this.
I don't deserve you as my go-between.
I can't fathom how she could
choose mediocrity...
...the way she has with you!
I have a letter from your daughter.
Do you want it?
- Thank you, Lloyd.
Visiting hours are now over.
All visitors must check out
at the main office.
I don't know which version she sent.
- "The disappointment I feel..."
- I know this part. Keep reading.
She can't still be angry at this.
- It's gotta get better.
- It does, if it's signed "I love you."
Just her name.
Just knowing that version exists,
that she did write "I love you"...
...that's a good thing, right?
It's gotta be a good thing.
Hello.
Hi.
I don't know what to say,
except goodbye.
You could have told me the truth.
I'm so sorry.
I love you, Dad.
Write me.
Wing adjustments.
It's like a roller coaster.
Everybody likes them.
- Blink if you're fine.
- I'm fine.
Good, it's all very normal.
- Very standard for a 747.
- Okay.
If anything happens, it usually
happens in the first five minutes.
So when the smoking sign
goes "ding," all is okay.
Good to know.
I'll keep talking until that
"ding" happens, which is soon.
Personalized flight kit from Corey.
Books, cassettes, magazines?
Not right now, thanks.
How's it going?
Nobody thought we'd do this.
Nobody really thinks
it will work, do they?
No.
You just described
every great success story.
It's all right.
I know.
- Where's the "ding"?
- It's coming.
Any second now.
Subtitles by
SDI Media Group