See you later, hon.
Didn't you find the note?
Why aren't you replying?
Three Months Later
It's a sprout!
Fast and easy loans like shopping.
Don't lose hope.
Banana flavor.
Don't you think?
It's gotta be.
It has to be meant for me.
Then why else
would it be there?
It said, 'Hello'.
You know what that means?
Think about it.
It means someone's been
watching me.
A freak? A psycho?
After 3 months and 17 days.
I finally got a reply.
The images and sound
are slowly getting clearer.
You're sleepy.
That's right, a pen-pal.
Writing to someone you don't know.
Then you get curious
and imagine who it might be.
It's an international pen-pal
cuz it's in English.
But it's the best
when you don't know who it is.
It doesn't matter who it is.
Right?
Hey, pal!
Startin' to ignore me?
What's wrong?
Going through puberty or somethin'?
Corn... Corn!
See this?
We can make noodles
with corn powder!
It's corn! Corn!
Corn!
Yes, hello.
You know Bam Island on Han River?
How much for the duck boat?
Damn it!
Damn! Why me!
Hello!
Anyone here?
Black bean noodles delivery.
Black bean noodles...
Hey!
Ah, some woman sent this.
Regular black bean noodles.
Black bean noodles with onions.
Seafood black bean noodles.
And this is on the house.
It's true...
We're supposed to
deliver anywhere.
But this is going way overboard.
Enjoy your meal and...
keep the dishes.
Wait!
The woman...
What does she look like?
Man, I'd like to see her face, too.
Hey, wait!
God damn it!
I don't care!
Deliver it yourself,
eat it, or throw it out!
My legs are all cramped!
Wait!
What's with you two...
That man...
Didn't he say something?
What did he say?
You two are really somethin'.
You're breaking my heart.
He told me to tell you...
a bowl of black bean noodles is...
hope to him.
I'd stay away from him.
And keep the dishes.
Hope.
I haven't heard that
in 100 years.
I'm tasting the giant hope
the man sent me.
It is truly the taste of hope.
Truly.
Truly
Are you awake?
Do you need anything?
Then I'll be going, now.
Wait...
I'd like to raise some corn.
What?
Corn.
Corn?
Can you get me the seeds,
pots, and other things?
Sure.
I'll get you the corn.
Me, too.
How long do I have to
keep doing this?
Congratulations.
Hello?
How are you?
Fine, thank you.
And you?
Where are you from?
Korean? Really?
Oh my god!
Me, too! I'm Korean.
From Do-bong-gu.
And... I...
I hope to see you.
Who are you?
What's going on?
Where is it?
Where's the bottle?
This looks familiar.
That's my friend!
Who are you!
This is a fake homepage, people!
I saw the real one!
Crazy bitch! Die!
Why...
Why!
Hey!
Fierce winds and heavy rainfall
is expected overnight.
Let's turn to the weather
for the details.
Reporter HAN?
A typhoon warning is in effect
in the southeast.
It's okay! Don't worry!
It'll pass in a flash!
Don't worry!
Everything will be okay.
I can't even have this?
It's not much...
Just about to start, sir.
Don't worry. Bye.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
You're not allowed to be here, sir.
Must be homeless, sir.
We came to clean...
Stop!
Stop right there!
What's going on?
Catch him! Get him!
This is my land!
I have to stay here!
Catch him!
Bastard!
This is a conservation area.
It's restricted to the public!
Let me just stay here, please?
I won't do anything bad.
I gotta get the replies.
Put some clothes on him, first.
Give it up, mister.
Let's go.
Come on! Let's go!
Let's just go.
63 Building
He's practically Tarzan.
Like a savage.
Does this go to the 63 Building?
Is something up?
No. Nothing.
Attention citizens!
This is the Civil Defense Corps.
This is an air-raid drill.
Once in spring and in the fall.
That day comes twice a year.
Something is up.
My...
...name is...
KIM Jung-yeon.
Who are you?