This jade imperial seal was stolen
from thief ghost by kung
to present to the city master.
There is also a rumour amongst
the kung-fu world.
That imperial agent dragon 9
is searching for him.
Good.
Then l will make a gift of this seal
and return it to its owner.
We only see our three dumb brothers
in Tianshan.
lt is boring us to death.
The smell of snow just fallen
is really good.
Oh really?
Oh, yes!
Smells quite good.
That's enough. You won't be able
to smell of a man anyway.
Big sister, who are you laughing at?
Among the four of us, you flirt the most
when you see young masters on the street
you just stare
without blinking your eyes.
Who said it?
l just want to meet more friends.
Don't be shy!
We are normal girls.
lt's just normal to want
to meet our Prince Charming.
What's so funny?
That's right! Ziqing is most frank!
OK
My second sister, of all the masters,
who do you want to meet most?
Simon the snow blower.
Simon the snow blower?
The one who kills and
spills no drop of blood.
l heard he is very difficult to approach.
No. l would say he is very dangerous.
So l've heard too
there are lots of legends about him.
They say he is the god of swords,
a unification of man and sword.
l am very curious and want to know
if he is really that dangerous.
That's better, so he doesn't practice
the book of the sunflower.
What does that mean?
You really don't know?
Do tell me quick.
The book of the sunflower...
Ok, l'll tell you alone.
That's enough, you bitch,
don't talk nonsense.
lt's true!
Master!
Of the seven sons of tianshan,
l've only brought the four of you down.
My aim is to preserve justice
and arrest thief ghost.
l have heard that
the biggest suspect is coming uphill.
Who is this suspect?
Dragon 9
He has a dual status.
He is the thief ghost.
Go get ready.
Yes, Master!
l never thought...
...there'd be such a refined tea-house
in such wilderness.
Great
Waiter!
Coming!
Sir, what would you like to drink?
The "daughter Red",
as red as your cheeks, you have it?
Of course!
Good! you look fecund.
Good!
Pardon me, my hand slipped.
Good wine!
Oh, who would have thought
you have put poison in the wine!
l am Lin yunhe of the tianshan Clan.
Today l am going to do justice
and capture the thief ghost.
l am not the thief ghost!
you wronged me...
Four sons, go ahead! yes!
Hold it!
You Lin yunhe are the real thief ghost.
You use your status as leader
of the tianshan Clan to hide your crime.
You leave your big bum pupils alone!
Cut the bullshit! Go ahead!
Oh... shit!
Wow! Big bum. l like it!
Kill him! Yes!
You can bear children but not kill...
Go!
What a big snow ball,
l need girl but not ball.
Master!
Go away!
Why don't you come tomorrow?
l have long wanted
to test your sword skills.
Live or die?
Big!
Live
Master...
Sister!
You use your disciples as your shield!
How despicable!
Sister...
Hey! don't just keep courting women!
l want to fly!
Where do you want to fly?
Where can you fly?
What are you shouting?
l am going with you!
lt's not that easy!
l can get everything.
Even the Monkey king.
l like your rudeness.
Hey, here comes another adulterer, you!
You always take advantage
of me with your words.
lf you are smart enough, marry me.
Why should l marry you?
lt's better to go to the corner
at the wall and do a little caressing.
Come along! Come!
What's wrong?
Last time you said l was great.
l am not going to play with you!
The minister is afraid you might take
the blame and not finish the mission.
Have l ever failed in my missions?
Where is he?
He is waiting for you
with dragon 6 and dragon 7.
l will go in and find them,
then come back to you.
l have only been away
for a while and you look awful!
How can l kiss with you
as your teeth are dirty.
We are getting short of people.
lt is in critical moments that
we realize the more people the better.
l really miss dragon Fat (8)
too bad, he has now become
the god of the foods.
lf you miss him so much,
l let you see him.
"Fat Choy"!
We have three out of four.
We almost died without you here
to fill the place. "Red sword"!
l win!
It's "thirteen odds"!
lmperial Agent! lt's only a beautiful
name. We can't really live on the salary.
lf you don't help me a bit,
l'll be broke.
You even win the "thirteen odds", aren't
you afraid of being denounced by god?
You will lose your good luck one day.
l just got rid of the thief ghost,
do l have to be scared of losing my luck?
Minister, be careful of what you play.
lf you let him win, l have to pay, too.
You are his left player and
you don't watch him out.
You are also to be blamed!
What's this?
This is a western telescope.
Best used to peek on others.
Let me have a look okay
lt really works!
This invention was left here
by the ltalian Marco Polo.
You can even use it to zoom.
Can we have wide angle?
You try it
Can you see any woman in the bath?
Yes! l see one, it's your mom!
Shit!
lt's really a woman!
Here's the mouth, big eyes...
What are you peeking? Want to die?
So it's the loose-tongued on
a close look and Princess Phoenix
with three mouths on a far look.
so it's four eyebrows on a far look
and a dumb face on a close look!
why don't the four of you engage
in some self-criticism?
Playing mahjong during office hours
you want me to inform the emperor?
then...
your highness Princess Phoenix
Please mind your tongue...
No, l mean please be lenient
to us in what you say
ok, give this to me then
No... give it to me!
No...
she is being destructive again
she has broken the telescope
Princess Phoenix, l heard that
you are practicing on Mount Holy girl
How come today...
Me! My master said that l have
learned all her martial arts already
so l come back
so there would be chaos
in the palace from now on
dragon 9, you making fun of me?
l wasn't talking about you
It's... him only
dragon 7, any new inventions lately?
yes, your Highness!
we have just set up a creative group
we just have a new invention,
the flying kite
dragon 9 has tried it, it's quite good
depends on who sits on it
we have a great creative group
Members include they are,
dragon 1, dragon 2...
dragon 3 and dragon 4
And l am the convener
so these are
the four world-famous dragon 1 to 4
who use to scare the hell out
of the bad guys
that's right
but who knows what sacrifices
we have to make in this business!
Look at him
once brilliant and handsome...
and now, all that is left
is a pair of silent eyes
nothing more!
Look at dragon 2,
seems to be strong and reliable
but then, he is only a limp
l don't need to explain
about the third one
Poor broken arm!
And the fourth is...
He...
He can't be dragon 4?
He used to be 180cm tall and
weighed 200 odd catties
l was beaten and had internal wounds
l have shrunken to this size
there's still the fifth!
He's disappeared for one year
we put in a lot of ads looking for him
From central to local,
searched everywhere
but still no sign of him
that's why all the complicated cases
are now handled by me alone
dragon 9!
Have you forgotten this "great Umbrella"
that has been with you
through life and death?
Princess, this is the latest product
"great Umbrella"!
there's two buttons here!
don't push!
l told you not to do that
the great Umbrella has 82 uses
the gun is only one of them
Really?
Let me try this button
Hey! No!
the second function
of the great Umbrella is
to shoot out 49 pins
in the shortest time
this function is named
the "Fairy Maiden's spike shower"
l like this one!
so what if you like it
this was made specially for me
give it back!
l want it
l want it! give it back!
give me! l want it!
don't fright for that
don't do that, it's messed up
Hand off
she is princess
you'll be damned if you hurt her
No, don't
Minister, there are a lot of invaders
in the square
who have the guts to step in here!
l'll go and have a look
who's there?
what a nice
"Hovering Heavenly Fairy" stance
you are really learned
you must be dragon 9 with four eyebrows
there's no one except
white Cloud City Master Cool-son yeh
who can strike such a powerful stance
in the kung-fu world
Cool-son yeh?
Royal Uncle Pingnan, it's me, Phoenix!
so you've grown up,
you know how to address people now
Everyone grows up
one can't always be a kid
ln my heart,
you will always be a small girl
yes, she's not even weaned
Uncle Pingnan, what are you doing here?
l'm here for two matters
the first is already written on the wall
Heavenly Cool son,
like a fairy swordsman
Fifteenth the first month,
moon shines like the sun
we fight just this once,
atop the City Forbidden
l don't get it
ls simon the snow blower your friend?
of course not
He is my very very very good friend!
Please pass on these six phrases to him
lf anyone of you here is a friend
of simon the snow blower
l welcome you to pass on my message
lf you want to fight in the palace,
it's difficult to explain to the Emperor
simon the snow blower and
me are regarded...
as "god of sword" and "sword saint"
such a sacred fight must be fought
in the noblest place
l think it is a bit difficult
tell your friend not to be late
Cool-son yeh,
you said you are here for two matters?
what's the other one?
the thief ghost stole
the Jade lmperial seal from the Emperor
lt's now with me
and l want to return it to the owner
I heard that your "buddha's Pointer"
Can catch any weapon in the world
you think you can catch this?
thank you!
that's really an ace
your Majesty
this Jade lmperial seal
has been returned by Master of Pingnan
the imperial seal passed down
by ancestors, lost and found
Congratulations!
Uncle Pingnan is highly skilled
in martial arts
and he is also loyal to me
l am thinking
what l should give him in return
brother, why don't you ask him to come
to the palace to teach me martial arts?
lf you call that a gift it's worse...
then asking him to kneel on glass
as a penalty
How dare you be so rude to me
in front of my brother!
l don't dare
the Powerful Four are
all gathered here today
you must have something to tell me
ls that right, Manager Liu?
you are so wise, your Majesty!
your Majesty,
Master of Pingnan Cool-soon yeh...
has send a letter inviting
simon the snow blower
to have a fight with him on the 15th
January on top of the Forbidden City
Just up above?
this could be fun!
your Majesty, this is outrageous
who cares if he is Master of Pingnan
or the best swordman
this cannot be allowed!
A fight between two great masters,
it's a rare occasion
lf l stop it,
it will disappoint everyone
so your Majesty want to print
some tickets to earn some money?
Jin guangda, with the men you have
how many can you let into the palace?
with the number of men in the palace,
only eight
okay then
l will issue eight gold medals
with a special sign
whoever holds this medal
can enter the palace
but there're millions of great masters
in the kung-fu world
and only eight medals
who is to decide
to whom these medals are to be given?
you!
Hey! you...
dragon 9! tell me
who is going to win between
simon the snow blower and Cool-son yeh?
tell me! don't go!
tell me, please...
Hey! don't go!
l am an lmperial Agent, l am famous
lf you pull me on a big street...
and l fall down in the new year,
what face do l have?
then why don't you just tell me
who is going to win?
tell me!
you tell me!
l'm asking you, tell me quick!
one is my good friend
one is a senior in the kung-fu world
l admire...
lt must be Royal Uncle Pingnan
why?
He's cool! He has personality
l believe
there is no one who can beat...
...his "Hovering Heavenly Fairy" stance
don't go! you still not answer me
you're bad! you're so shameless!
Please tell me who will win!
lf you follow me
l will deal with you here!
oh! dare you to bully me?
How can you do that?
you are the princess,
how dare l bully you?
you have also learned all the kung-fu,
l can't fight you then
How about that? grab two eunuchs and
use a candle to burn their ass
that could be fun!
l don't want to play that!
you tell me who is going to win first?
Cool-son or simon?
l have important things to do?
l'll answer you when l come back, okay?
okay. Let's go
don't follow me! Hey!...
you are so irritating! Please
l've been busy!
l know you are busy,
so l dare not find you
l only miss you everyday
Actually, l have written a letter
Let me see
No. l am afraid you will look down on me
l will only be touched
How about that... you read it out to me
No...
lf you say no, l'll never miss you
okay, but you mustn't laugh at me
brother 9, haven't seen you for days,
l miss you very much
you know
l'm not a scholar
so l don't know what to say
Am l a fool?
l just wish you would come
to see me soon
Lastly, l wish you
all the best luck and longevity
that's it
this is the most touching love letter
l have ever read
Really?
you take it?
total charge 50 taels
50 taels?
you give to me?
we have played this two times already
Last time l cried severely, this time
there's only two drops of tears
shall we play something new
and more exciting?
what shall we play then?
l heard there is a mouth trick spreading
around among the people
seems to be great fun
lt's called...
what's that?
It's called "Ice Fire", you understand?
you are bad!
No, we'll play another!
okay, we won't play "Ice Fire"
we'll play crossed pair cards,
or zigzag arrows...
you bad boy! you play with someone else!
disgusting!
what's this thing?
lt's so long?
you hurt my skin,
but you still haven't touched my flesh
so if you think this is not new,
we'll play some brain games
don't you know l am the lmperial Agent?
l've solved numerous mysterious,
l'm called the god of Logic
you play these games with me?
okay, l'll play with you
Ask me a question
okay, l test you
A woman has two limbs for the arm
and two limbs for the legs,
that's four limbs
so how many limbs do men have?
of course they have five limbs
so when you add a man and a woman,
how many limbs are there?
when they are making love?
yes
they should have...
Nine limbs?
Not exactly
Eight?
No, not eight
Nine is not correct either
the correct answer is...
...eight and then nine,
eight and nine...
Eight limbs and nine limbs?
Eight limbs and nine limbs...
but the one l have been used to is...
...eight-and-a-half and eight,
eight-and-a-half...
what's the matter?
there are a lot of people outside
looking for Master dragon
doesn't seem to have come
with good intentions!
okay!
l have to go out
Hey! you will expose your spots
what's wrong with exposing myself,
it's only if you expose that
we have to charge extra
l'm not going out!
Let's study this...
...seven limbs is good,
so is eight limbs, nine limbs...
Come out! Come out...
don't be so nervous. Relax...
l'm not here to check your license
or to close your business
l come here as a hooker,
just like all of you
l'm a consumer
l'm here to take a bath with her
l pay full price
Moustache gold, you bastard!
you expose my status?
Right! l am an lmperial Agent
And Moustache gold,
he is a triad leader of the capital
we used to mind our own business, but...
we are good adopted brothers!
He's also my adulterous brother
good brother!
good adulterer!
lt's only because you court her that
l have not protested!
Master gold!
Hey, it's just a brothel,
do you need to be so heavily armed?
Right, l've come here for you
who are you? you look a stranger
l am the one who is good at drinking,
gambling, and whoring...
Cut it off!
you are lmmoral wu,
the one with everything
but a moral character
Coming!
you placing a bet with him?
yes, we are betting on all we have
l buy that our good friend
simon the snow blower will win
and he is buying for Cool-son yeh
this time l can't help you
simon the snow blower is invincible
How can he lose?
He may be before l met Cool-son yeh
when I saw his
"Hovering Heavenly Fairy" stance...
was it powerful?
Very powerful
Really very powerful?
Very powerful indeed!
then, l must...
you are a gentleman,
you said it before so many witnesses
you can't go back on your words now
you won't know before the duel!
we are good friends
of simon the snow blower
No matter what the chances are,
we still support him!
simon work hard! simon work hard!...
simon Qing work hard!
simon Qing work hard!...
where do you find a simon Qing?
lt's simon!
simon work hard!
simon work hard,
simon work hard, simon...
dragon 9, l haven't finished
Actually, l've come to look for you...
damn you!
you go to a brothel for prostitutes,
why do you look for me?
l want to buy a medal from you!
you know about it?
the lmperial guards asked you
to issue the eight gold medals
so they can enter the palace
to watch the duel
the whole kung-fu world knows about it
Everyone knows?
these are matters of the rivers and
lakes and the paparazzi are interested?
there'll be no secrets
in the kung-fu world from now on
l am placing such a large bet
with Moustache gold
of course l am qualified to watch...
who said you are qualified?
lt's not up to you. lt's my decision!
so are you selling?
How much?
ten thousand taels
you go around the corner and say it
499 times more! ten thousand taels...
Listen everyone, pay attention
Cool-son yeh is meeting
the three tang brothers to negotiate
at Chun Hua House
Let's go and watch, shall we?
great!
Let's go!
Have they started fighting?
Little master, tell me
why are you all so cool?
don't you see?
one main character is still missing
Haven't seen
what a coincidence!
you are so late,
l thought you wouldn't come
why?
give way!
In a while Uncle Pingnan will use
the stance "Hovering Heavenly Fairy"
And stab tang Fei and tang Ao
in one blow. How impressive
No wonder, no one sits on the seats
around tang Fei and tang Ao
l was surprised. Let's go over
sit down, drink some tea and
wait for Cool-son yeh
the tangs in sichuan are famous
for their poison
that's why no one dares go near
those two guys are sweating
on such a cool day
dragon 9, don't you sell me the medal?
get off!
this lady must have something
l wish we can find simon the snow blower
as soon as possible
we must take revenge ourselves
and not let him die
in Cool-son yeh's hands
Cool-son yeh!
Every time Cool-son yeh appears
he has to make a fuss
He must spend a lot of money
on the girls
so you are tang Fei
Cool-son yeh, l will take revenge
for my big brother tang Ling today
the sichuan tangs have
four famous brothers
l killed tang Ling
there's you two, where's tang yong?
you let him look for you everywhere!
Cool-son yeh, either you die...
...or l die today!
you deserve?
l have brought the greatest
Hidden weapon of the tangs,
the "Net above snares below" Pin
what's that?
there are altogether 199 pins
when we throw them out, not even
a mosquito can escape within 30 feet
Friends, this matter only concerns me
and Cool-son yeh
others please give way
None of my business
l'd advise you not to fight
we sichuan tangs' poisoned
hidden weapons are scared
by everyone in the kung-fu world
l'm not scared, l just want to tell you
once l pull out my sword,
it will shed blood
don't regret it
you're really not scared?
How can a bit of dust be poison?
oh, Cool-son yeh, you are god,
god of sword
oh my god!
How can he finish off
Chun Hua House with one blow?
our bet has been concluded
you can't back off!
brother!
l said it, don't force me to fight
wait for me!
there's something wrong?
what is it? the problem is...
...l don't know what's wrong
Come out!
Come out
Hi, you were great!
you're hurt? Are you okay?
lf you can keep the secret
l won't kill you
lf you ask me not to tell
of course l won't
l don't know anything
Are you alright?
Hey, come over here
Are you okay?
you better leave,
this place is too dangerous
Remember, you promised
you would not tell others
that l am hurt
otherwise, l will be chased...
l can find the tianshan snow Lotus
it can cure all kinds of poison,
how about l bring some back to you?
you must keep it well
sorry, but...
you are in hiding, how can l find you?
Leaf?
l'll come see you when l hear this sound
this can make sound?
A leaf can make a sound?
Let me try it
try again
you have to be gentle
Let me!
l know!
ls that right? Right!
Cool-son yeh, l will find
the tianshan snow Lotus to cure you
so you can fight simon the snow blower
in good condition
wait for me!
did you awaken?
you have lost your consaiousness
for ten days
you want to kill me, no need to hurry
why did you save me?
duty
do you know
this is worse than death for me?
though my master killed my three sisters
still he has brought me up
what has that got to do with me?
why am l the only one left alive?
And l am at the house of my enemy,
what would people say?
Naive
to prove my innocence...
today is New year's day
this cake is famous in our simon House
lt's called the wife Cake
Come to buy fish, it will make a fortune
you give red packets to everyone?
lt's the new year,
they only have to say Happy New year
l give them red packets...
How much is in each packet?
lt's 100 taels in each packet
100 taels! you don't even know them?
l will lose all my fortune to
that bastard anyway...
lt's the New year
lt's lmmoral wu
l'll spend whatever l can
so you are saying that our
simon the snow blower is bound to lose?
Haven't you seen Cool-son yeh
at Chun Hua House?
you really believe
someone can be quicker than him?
think about it! l really regret it
what's wrong?
Right, Cool-son yeh's
"Hovering Heavenly Fairy" is powerful
but... I really think
there is something wrong
what's wrong?
l don't know, we'll find out in the end
but your friend simon the snow blower,
you think he would come?
lf he doesn't show up,
then the duel can't continue
then l don't have to lose my fortune,
that's good!
Have you been listening?
two bastards are on my way!
Hey! so it's you!
Come, Happy New year!
Here's a red packet...
dragon 9,
your good friend simon the snow blower
He's going to show up today?
why do you ask the same question?
you conspired with him?
you don't belong to our group,
who are you?
they are two of the sons
of the "seven tianshan sons"
the one who keeps talking is yen Zizhun
and the dumb one is Xiao Zichong
you and simon the snow blower
killed my master
we brothers are going
to get even with you today
you can't say that
one has to bear his own consequences
your master is a serious criminal
and l am an lmperial Agent
of course l have to arrest him
what's wrong
if l hit him when he resists?
My master is definitely
not the thief ghost, he was wronged
Hey, your sister ye Ziqing
is still alive, go ask her
About how he killed her three sisters
bullshit!
simon the snow blower killed
our three sisters
ye Ziqing is licentious,
she survived and has an affair
with simon the snow blower
lf l see them, l'll kill them too!
keep your words here, if he hears you
then...
then what?
then, he only needs to touch
their heads gently
and they will explode
bullshit!
simon the snow blower is not here today
dragon 9, you die first!
Come!
that's the "telepathic Microsteps"
and "buddha's Pointer". Powerful!
l'm really worried about my fingers
l deal with a lot of novices like you
lf l am not careful and break
one of my fingers, that's real trouble!
you two are creating trouble,
inviting death!
How do you want to deal with them?
they are just acting on impulse
Forget it