Original Story by
JEON Kyeong-lin
KIM, Yun-jin
LEE, Jong-won
GYE, Sung-yong
ARDOR
My name is Lee Mi-heun
I married a senior classmate
the year I graduated from college
We had a daughter and spent
eight happy years together
I devoted myself to
my house and family
My husband loved this about me
This was how we planned
to grow old together
Not finished yet?
Let's wrap it up and go to bed
Leaving this unfolded can
bring bad luck tomorrow
December 24th, 2000
Even on the night she came over
I believed my life
would always be this peaceful
Hello?
Yes, it is
Yes. Go ahead
I bought some beer.
I didn't want to come empty handed
I thought I should see
Mr. Kim before I leave
I owe him quite a lot
I wanted to stop by earlier
Anyway, we had a party
around here
He's the only one
who didn't show
It's not that I had to
be there
I'm leaving early tomorrow
Are you going far away?
Incheon
You know what a foster home is?
It's for abandoned children
I'll be living there with them
Sounds like a difficult job
Nice apartment
How big is it?
Oh, there's a flag
in the house
My daughter drew it
in pre-school
Something is wrong with it
But what?
Isn't it upside down?
Right, it is!
I knew something was
wrong with it
How silly!
It's drawn upside down
Sweetie
- She doesn't know anything
- What the? What are you doing?
Can't you stay with me tonight?
Miss Jung, stop it.
Are you drunk?
But I'm really leaving
tomorrow!
Aren't you sad at all?
Don't do this, get off me
No, I wanna stay with you
Can I sleep here with you?
Sweetie, huh?
Young-woo
Can I sleep here with you?
I haven't slept in days.
Let me stay, sweetie
Don't you miss me, honey?
Smell me
I know you love me, huh?
You two, if you need to
talk, go outside
No, Mi-heun, that's not it
Let go
- She's just drunk, that's all
- Let go
You crazy girl
This house
This house not here!
Don't you know that?
Get out! Get out, now!
Sweetie?
How disgusting
Was it fun fooling around?
Mi-heun
Get out. It's over now.
Stop it
Let go!
What the?
Wanna know what
he said to me?
He said I pull him
in all the way
He said he'll never forget how
I squeeze him tight inside me
We weren't just fooling around
I even got pregnant
Last month,
I had an abortion, and he
Your husband, I mean
He waited outside the operating
room afraid I'd get hurt
He worried I wouldn't wake up
and he'd never see me again!
We loved each other like
more than you could ever dream of
And you want me to leave?
You gotta be kidding
I've got as much right
to be here as you!
You!
I didn't know there was a knife!
- I didn't know, sweetie
- Daddy?
Su-jin! Go back to your room
Mi-heun, open your eyes!
What the hell did you
hit her with?
Mi-heun! Mi-heun!
Open your eyes!
6 months later
She just moved here
from Seoul
and doesn't know her
way around
- So help her adjust
- The countryside's best for kids
We had a bus for them
until last year
- But the school funds have depleted
- I see
- The head wound is fully healed
- There shouldn't be any problems
Nothing will stop your headaches
I'll prescribe a tranquilizer
You know what a drug addict is?
Snap out of it, Mi-heun, please?
Ma'am? We're at Butterfly Ville
This is where you get off
- Get on
- No, you go first
- Oh! It's you!
- Hello
Coming from somewhere?
- You're getting around well
- I went to the school
- Taking off
- Oh, mister! I'm coming on
Honey? I picked Su-jin up
from school
- Daddy, what's this?
- Oh, that's a TV
If you press here, we can
watch TV Cool, huh?
Mommy, look!
Daddy came to school in this!
- You bought a car?
- Oh, you're up
Well, you'll need a car too,
to get to the hospital
You can use the other car.On
weekends, we'll go around in this
- How's that sound, Su-jin?
- Great!
Wonderful?
Hello? Yes, professor,
this is Hyo-kyung
I'm here for good
I handed over the
publishing company to Chang
and took over the
bookstore over from Dae
No, nothing like that
Well, with my wife's health
No, it's nothing serious
She just needs clean
air and rest
Yes, I think so
I'll come by sometime
Take care, professor.
Bye, sir
Hi, Mommy!
I couldn't quit, no matter what.
Even after getting lung cancer
Rest stop
A bottle of water, please
- Hey!
- Yeah?
You put a novel
under Reference!
Ah-huh
Don't sit around doing nothing.
Go clean the windows
Fuck the nice weather today
Hello?
Are you the owner of this car?
There's something wrong
with it
What's the problem?
I'm not sure, it just stopped
When's the last time
you put gas in the car?
Pardon?
Didn't even know that
it's out of gas
15,000 won, please
- What about the gas can?
- Excuse me?
You have to return it, but
You're not from around here,
huh?
- Just visiting?
- No, I live here
- 3000 won more for the can
- What?
You know doc,
but I don't know you
I ain't never seen you
3,000 won!
How's country life so far?
You moved into the house
downhill?
Didn't change
your car plates yet?
I didn't know
you lived uphill
I was surprised to see you
come out of that house
It's famous around here.
Did you know when you went in?
That does it
Seems like your thoughts
are always somewhere else
Are you okay?
Live here for a month, you'll see.
It'll bore you to death
No mall, no theatres
It's an hour from the city
If you sit around doing nothing,
you'll just go crazy
Doesn't the Mrs have a job?
You must have made
a lot of money
You should come out more
People are saying
you're sick
since you don't
come out Rumors!
Oh, I didn't know that
Don't be offended
It's different
from Seoul around here
Anyway, did you meet him?
Up the hill?
When they moved in,
it was worse than here
Wondering why a young,
handsome doctor
would think of coming here
Do you know the bamboo house?
On the way to So-Jung li?
What about it?
I heard something
happened there
The village was turned upside
down last year
A stabbing!
A woman killed her father-in-law
in broad daylight
The son was such a nice man
I'm telling you.
The wife ruined him completely
She had some nerve
being butt naked with her
lover in broad daylight!
When the old man caught them
she grabbed the sickle from him
and Gives me chills
just thinking about it
Mommy!
- Wasn't it fun today?
- Yeah, science class was best
Mommy! This is Oh Mi-sook.
She sits left, right, up from me
She takes the bus a long way
Can we give her a ride?
Where do you live?
Seven stops on bus #2
My house is right there
- Bye
- See ya
- Take care, Mi-sook
- Bye
You!
I told you
never to get
in a stranger's car!
You brat! Go inside, now!
Wow! She's scary
No, she's not
Greet her politely next time
Okay
Can I play
at Dong-wook's house?
Okay, but be back
before dinner
Yes
- Did you have fun at his house?
- Uh-huh
What are you doing?
Let's eat
Daddy, I already ate
Did you eat, Hon?
Mommy's sick again
- You said you ate, right?
- Ah-huh
- Let's get ready for school tomorrow
- Okay
Honey?
Why are you crying?
What's the matter now?
These people can die doing that.
Why would they do it?
- It's so stupid
- What?
Maybe you should've died
before she came over
Then I might've died
along with you
No, it would've been better
if I died first
Then I wouldn't have found out.
That would've been nice
I can't do it
I can't go back
to the way we were
But why am I here, in this house,
still sleeping next to you?
Life, it feels so empty
so boring that I'll go crazy
Nothing's worth living for
everything's a waste
Just stop it!
How many times
do I have to tell you?
It was just an accident
I apologized over and over!
I gave up everything
to be stuck here
running a tiny bookstore!
For what? I dedicated my life
to you and Su-jin!
Frankly speaking
you always lay around
like a corpse
but did I ever complain
about you?
You're really something,
Mi-heun! Really something
You're not going to sit here
wasting away your life, are you?
The weather's too nice
for that
Would you like some coffee?
Su-jin, turn down the volume!
Mommy's head hurts
Yes, Mommy
Su-jin, let's go
Kim Su-Jin, quickly
- Where are we going?
- Mommy has to go into town
Quick, go to Dong-wook's place
Okay
Let's go
What's the problem?
My head
it hurts so much
I can't do anything
Let me take a look
Breathe
All right
That's fine
- Does it hurt like this often?
- Yes
Since when?
Since last December 24th
Were you hurt?
Did a specialist look at it?
Yes it's nothing serious
- But your head still hurts?
- Yes
Let's check your blood pressure
I was treated by a neuropsychiatrist.
They're vascular headaches
Please just write the prescription.
It's Xanax and Diazepam
Write it, please
All right
Let me just see your
health insurance card
Lee Mi-heun?
I'm Choi In-kyu
What do you do most of the time?
Sleeping?
Your head hurts because
you stay in sleeping
I really have to get going
Uh, yes, that's right
You shouldn't take too much
Diazepam or Barium
Thank you
Ah, Mi-heun?
Want to play a little game
with me?
Having fun is the best
medicine for headaches
For four months,
until summer's end
let's pretend we're lovers
We'll have fun together
and have sex
Sound intriguing?
But there's one rule
If one of us tells the other
"I love you", then it's over
We can never meet again
So I'm not proposing
a relationship, just a game
Why would anyone play
such a game?
Life's full of changes
I don't like being tied down
Or, maybe it's because
I know I'll never lose
And mostly,
because I find you attractive
Do you play this game often?
Not often, but once in a while
Why can't there be love?
Confessions of love, marriage
Typical steps before sex
I hate it, it's like insurance
I'm not a person
who can fall in love
So how about it?
You look bored, too
I know you'll play it.
You have nothing else to do
They have the best mushrooms
here. Let's get some
Mushrooms, please
Your mom's not out
waiting today
Bye
- See you tomorrow, Mi-sook
- Bye
Mommy!
- Mommy!
- You bitch! Come here!
- Mi-sook!
- Mommy!
Come here, quickly
Hold on
You bitch! Come here!
You fucking bitch!
Hey, get over here!
Get back here!
Shocked?
He's my husband
I met him working at a bar
the first customer
I slept with
He'd drink and then beat me
Went in and out of jail
No matter how far
I try to run
he somehow ends up
finding me
Crazy, ain't it?
Looks like it will rain
It's the typhoon coming
there's always one
around now
Mi-heun?
Hi, Mom
I called
because of the typhoon
Is your place okay?
It's okay
If you're fine,
then bye for now
- Wait, Mom?
- What?
- How's Dad?
- The same as always
- I see
- Then, I'll see you soon. Bye
Each time you played,
have you always won?
There's no winner
in this game
just a loser
Have you ever lost?
Only once
to the woman who first
proposed it to me
What happened then?
I asked her to live with me
and to get a divorce
Threats, stalking
I turned worse than scum
Who would play such a game?
Bored women?
Ruined women?
There are women
who want to be ruined
Like you
Open your eyes
Don't look at it
No, yours is so beautiful