The Ping River
You're sure this Jahalang is
son of the North Ho House of Yu?
Yes, sir.
Tai Yang Lake
Perhaps I should pay
Shao Xing a visit.
Splendid work, everyone!
A toast!
To victory!
Got that Mongol bitch
on your mind, Jahalang?
If not, mind if I take her
to my bedroom tonight?
You're requested at a meeting
in Lady Jin's room.
What kind of meeting is this?
Take a seat.
Since neither of us like being
in crowds,
Let us celebrate on our own.
If this is what you called me for
I'm leaving now.
There's something I want to know.
Jahalang, I know you well.
Now that you've fulfilled your aim,
the coming fight
will have no meaning for you.
Now what will you fight for?
The 'trophy' in the lady's chambers?
Or perhaps you could fight for me?
Not for you.
You shouldn't be outside yet.
You play very well.
I'm not that good.
Uncle plays much better...
You mean the man who saved me?
Alisu! Tell me who he is!
How can I see him?
He sometimes comes
to the cave behind the house.
He's there now...
Thank you for taking care of him.
You have quite a fate, Jinha.
A father who can't reveal
his face or voice to his own son.
Let me speak to him!
This must be fate, too.
My name is Namgung Sung.
I am grateful to you
for saving my life,
but I dare ask another favor of you.
Take me as your apprentice, Master!
I must take revenge on
a man called Jahalang.
Get out.
Sullie...
I'm not the one you used to know.
What do you want me to do?
Everything ended the day
you came to me as a killer.
Sung is alive.
Once we take the Nan Xi River,
we'll never have to see
another Mongol in this land.
Jahalang, once again
we trust in your skill.
Call in Yeo Jin.
Once again, I put my faith
in you for this mission.
Remember each of your duties.
Welcome, Marshal Heo.
Greetings. I came to bring you news.
What is it?
Is it true you are interested
in the Mongol girl?
If so, it's such a tragedy.
She's dead.
A great fire swept through her room.
Everything is burned. You can't even
distinguish the bones.
I can't believe you came.
Did you do this?
l wanted you so much!
Come away with me.
I'll abandon everything.
You... All I need is you.
You're the first to remain standing
after being poisoned with Mihon.
Seize him!
What did you say?
He crept in at night
to kill Jo, Baek Seung,
but was caught and executed.
The Mongols must have paid him off.
That's ridiculous.
Do you continue to side with him?
Let's be frank.
I'll talk to the governor.
Now that the Ten Swordsmen
have no marshal,
we'll need a new one...
What do you think?
Not bad.
You're smart.
You must follow the current
to make your way in life!
I just lost my chief.
How can I trust a scoundrel
like Jo, Baek Seung?
Do as you please.
No one on earth can save you now!
If you wish to stay alive,
tell me where you keep
the Bichun Secrets!
So you were after the Secrets?
Why else would I take in
a Koryo like you?
It's not in his room.
Then go after his Koryo friend!
If Jahalang doesn't have it
then he probably does.
You know the place, don't you?
Yes, sir!
Sajune, go with them!
Make sure it's done properly.
That's all the information you have?
He's alive but
you don't know where he is?
It's difficult, since
it's in Qing Chen Bang.
I'll look into it again.
No, I'll go myself.
What's going on?
Run, quick!
Sir!
Remember, Sung!
You're of Koryo blood!
You must guard the master's
Bichun Secrets!... Alisu!
Brother!
You're awake.
Good thing I came when I did,
but you're something else.
Alone against three men!
Brother...
You should leave now, sir.
No need to stay for long in Shao Xing.
Do you think it's true
that Jo has killed Jahalang?
People have coveted
the Secrets for a long time.
I'm sorry, Lai.
I must leave to finish some task.
Please take care of yourself.
This is for Yu, Jinha!
It's remarkable that
he's still alive.
The poison has spread
throughout his body.
That's enough, you may go.
My lady, it's too late to cure him.
You could get infected yourself.
That is none of your concern.
I wasn't able to
cure you completely.
If you use your sword before
regaining your strength,
the effects of the poison
will recur.
Please... wait until you recover.
They were hiding in a cave.
Brother!
Kill them!
Uncle! Uncle...
What did you call him?
Uncle? That's a lie!
That's Jahalang! Not my Master!
My master isn't a murderer!
Please stop it!
You shouldn't treat him that way!
He...
He's your father!
The area is in chaos.
We must do something, quickly.
You've found the Mongols?
Yes, sir.
Get the girl first,
in the name of revenge.
And Jahalang?
Once we have the girl,
he's as good as ours.
If all goes well, you will be
our next governor, my lord.
Are you awake?
Lady Sullie has killed
Jo, Baek Seung.
She's staying in the house
behind Yu Hua Pagoda.
You should rest.
Changlyong...
Thank you.
Look closely, Namgung Sung!
This is your master's true identity.
What are you waiting for?
Tell me. Did you do it to
punish my mother?
Your mother did nothing wrong.
I didn't understand the world then.
Listen to me well.
You are Namgung Sung!
Do you understand?
Follow me.
You shouldn't have come.
What do you mean?
I am your husband
and you are my wife!
We've lived together for 10 years!
You don't understand...
Why I made up my mind to live.
Sung is not your son.
I wanted to mix his bloodline
with the House of Namgung.
Because I hated my father...
and I hated you.
I knew that.
I thought that I deserved it.
I'll never forget his eyes when
I pushed him toward the cliff,
out of selfish desire
to have you for my own.
I never thought I'd be able
to speak of it...
I'm not sure about you,
but I was happy.
Come back as my wife, Sullie...
I'd rather you killed me.
Then we'd both be free of Jinha.
I wonder about the bond
between you two.
If there's such a thing as fate,
that must be it.
I wanted to say thank you.
Sung!
It's been a long time, Jinha.
Let's not stand on ceremony,
shall we?
If I die, take care of Sullie.
Sullie is your wife!
Lift up your sword.
Lift your sword
and attack me, Jinha!
Now we can remain friends.
Welcome.
Jahalang's end is near, my lord!
You should see them, sir.
No need.
I've ordered the men to stand by.
It's a personal matter.
We'll part ways here.
I can't do that.
That's an order, Changlyong!
Yes, sir.
Take care.
Where is Jinha now?
He left.
Where did he go?
He's looking for a place to die.
Go back!
What about Sung?
Who'll take care of him?
I'm sorry.
I'm leaving you again...
Sullie...
Sung...
Take care of Sung...
My name is Sullie. Sullie.
And you?
Jinha.