And his tail drew the third part of the stars of heaven
and did cast them to the earth:
and the dragon stood before the woman
which was ready to be delivered,
for to devour her child as soon as it was born.
Revelation - Chapter 12:4
Just like in the forecast data.
Excuse me.
I hope the anesthesia did no harm to her.
Sir, Deunan Knute is secured!
Such a beauty...
8 hours 12 minutes, she slept so long.
This legendary soldier is so cute
even when she's asleep.
About what happened to your body?
She will be surprised!
When we get to the Utopia.
Utopia, eh...
Did we get the landing permit from Olympus A5?
Don't get too close before ID is confirmed
or the multi-legged cannon will fire at us.
Here is Olympus A5.
Lading permit confirmed.
ESWAT109 landing.
Briareos
I'll take a look up ahead.
I will go with you.
You stay here.
Don't worry. I'll be back soon.
Briareos...
Such a detailed inspection this time.
According to the order from legislative institute.
Still sleeping... perhaps wrong dosage of anesthesia?
Don't move or I'll break your neck!
Deunan Knute, second team captain, stand down!
Briareos
I can't believe it.
Can't blame you. But this is the truth...
So after such a large scale World War,
there is no winner?
Yes. After that, the previous administration took over.
In other word, Olympus is now controlling this world.
That means I blindly
kept fighting for months with no cause?
That's how war is, isn't it?
But it's different here.
Olympus is the ideal government
that mankind has search for ages.
Why brought me here?
Because you are an elite soldier.
Your name on the top of ESWAT's human enhancement list.
My mission is to bring people on the list
from outside world to Olympus.
ESWAT?
I know you must have lots of questions.
But, please take a good rest tonight.
We will continue tomorrow.
I will show you around the city.
I'm sure Deunan you will fall in love with our Utopia.
Here is the bedroom.
Haven't slept on a soft bed for a long time,
haven't you?
I'll pick you up at 10 am tomorrow.
You are Hitomi, right?
Yeah.
Haven't we meet before?
I don't think so. Good night.
When...
In the battle of North Africa,
I lost my body.
It's been over one year.
This is Carl's...
It's what your father left behind.
Don't let them get it.
Call me if you have trouble.
Briareos
Do you know those who attacked me?
No.
So sad.
Athena you arranged that attack, didn't you?
It's impossible for the mercenaries
to confront with ESWAT.
Did you forget the mission of Bioriod?
If the military knows,
General Uranus will be pleased.
We won't be able to control them by ourselves.
Gaia might have reached its limit.
Athena, we don't have much time left.
Nike
They've found out.
I'm so sorry.
Nike
We need our man inside ESWAT.
I'll prepare right now.
But the worst is,
we didn't find that thing.
Then
It's not yet the time to use the last resort.
But the fire has to be put out before it grows.
Secure Deunan Knute by all means!
Yes sir!
Human is such a strange creature
that will fall into its own traps.
Never thought Captain Hades will be here personally.
Imagine how ESWAT is chasing
after the fake information...
Preparation is 98% finished.
Wonderful...
The problem of special part on the leg was also solved.
General Uranus will be pleased.
Now, Bioriod won't be able to do as they wishes.
We should not be protecting wolves.
instead we should protect the sheep like human,
shouldn't we?
Indeed that's the principle
for our first generation Bioriod.
However some wolves are under sheep's skins.
No matter if it's a wolf or a sheep,
there should not be any sacrifices.
So sad. We've already known the answer to this.
Even then, we have to debate with Gaia like this.
Then let's continue to debate with Gaia.
Deunan
Briareos
Morning, Deunan.
It fits well. Come on, let's go.
Your entry permit was approved this morning.
So Deunan you are offically a member of our Olympus.
Beautiful city, isn't it?
Comparing with where I was yesterday,
it's like a dream.
From today on, this is the reality.
Everyone seems happy.
Because in this city 50% population are Bioriod.
Bioriod?
Man-made human.
Clones?
No, not simple clones,
but man-made human with carefully selected human gene.
Does it mean that the city is controlled by clones?
It's not polite to say "clone".
I am a Bioriod myself.
And, although being elite,
Bioriod doesn't control human.
Bioriod aims to coexists with human peacefully.
and become an integral part
of human to human relations.
Half of them are Bioriod...
This car is sort of strange.
The experimental ultravibrate gravity system
is installed on this car.
Ultravibrate gravity?
Yes, like hovering.
It's said the driver would have a longer life.
So the ultravibrate gravity control technology
is finished.
But, you control the car by that steering wheel?
In this city, the use of automation technology
has reached such level,
this wheel is a symbol of the "for the people" idea.
Simple theory, complicated structure,
makes human more human.
What's that all about?
City planners used to say that.
That is the symbolic building.
Tarutarus and Tartarus.
Inside there, an enormous I.N. structure
that controls Olympus.
I.N.?
Means "Intellectual Network".
Commonly called Gaia.
Gaia grows with the network
and monitors all of Olympus.
Especially we Bioriod.
Why?
Human has emotions.
They argue and start wars.
Bioriod is restrained on emotions.
They don't hate others
so there won't be any fighting.
On the top of Tarutarus,
there is a perfect defense system
protecting the "D-Tank" virus storage system
It is said that if the virus is spread out,
all Bioriod will die.
It's the product of human defense instinct.
But it's a insult to Bioriod.
You mean human is more dangerous.
So the balance between human and Boiriod
is more important.
Gaia monitors the effect of the Bioriod with human.
But the one being monitored are still human being.
You spoke like General Uranus.
Who is General Uranus?
General commander of Olympus military.
An extremist that hates Bioriod.
An being that's unfit in Utopia.
Bioriod controls Olympus.
Premier Athena is a Bioriod too.
Athena?
You know her?
Probably not.
Premier is just like the president.
However the military is controlled by human.
Scary, right?
Recently the ESWAT under Athena's control
is growing bigger.
The relations with military has gone from bad to worse.
But all decisions of Olympus are controlled by Gaia.
Something wrong?
We've got company.
Hitomi, are you okay?
Sure.
But they are...
They sure know what to do.
So I am the target.
No question about it.
Such is the reality.
Briareos.
Cannot unseal the Apple Seed.
How are you doing, grandpas?
Hitomi, are you alright?
Are you hurt?
I am okay.
And I bring you the long awaited Deunan Knute.
Ahh, the legendary beauty!
Goddess of fighting.
You have the same eyes like Carl.
You know my father?
Not only that,
Most Bioriod in Olympus have inherited
part of Carl Knute's gene.
That means Hitomi is your sister.
We heard you met some unpleasant things.
Recently,
it's very complicated to control people from outside.
We are worried that the balance will be broken.
First let's introduce Gaia to you.
Enemies of the general...
The legislative institute and administrative institute
began to confront each other
over the issues of Bioriod population increasing, etc.
Athena is really targeting Carl's daughter?
Absolutely. All the preparation is done.
Degree of the information source?
It's level 5.
General, Please make a decision!
Human cannot be the tool of souls any more.
This is Gaia.
Gaia lets the network grow and controls Olympus.
Gaia speaks with the seven elders and the conclusion
becomes the consciousness of Olympus.
Gaia is the combine product of many scientists'
intelligence and consciousness.
However a machine is a machine.
It's absolute stable,
a reliable tool.
But it has no emotions and no feelings.
Only if combine with seven elder's feelings
Gaia could think more like a human.
But recently
you have very different opinions with Gaia.
Our work is to argue with Gaia.
The conclusion of the debate can lead Olympus
to the correct direction for future development.
Deunan, you were still in battlefield yesterday,
right?
What did you fight for?
Well...
Human being will not stop fighting
as long as there are emotions and desires.
That's why we built Olympus.
The last hope for human being
is the coexistence of human and Bioriod.
Gaia continously monitors this balance.
Bioriod is totally different from human.
Without the reproductive ability,
they cannot have children.
No sex.
No love, no desire, and therefore no hatred.
However if the life-prolonging procedure
is not performed regularly,
they will get old really fast and die.
We wanted to make Bioriod different from human,
so we supressed their reproductive ability,
and changed their life cycle.
Hitomi,
aren't you late for the life-prolonging procedure?
No problem, I will have it done there soon.
Hopefully, someday Bioroids
don't have to go through such troublesome procedure.
Kudo, all your team members are dead.
You are still too young, sorry for that.
Started with only one knife,
she killed 16 men in ten minutes.
You brought in a really good newcomer!
You bloat too much.
Your team members might save your life some day.
You shouldn't say those words to them.
So long haven't seen you,
can't you say something else?
Something nicer?
Such as "how have you been in two years?"
Or "Nice to meet you again".
Someone has an interest on you.
I know. But why would any one be interested in me,
and who are these people?
I don't know.
What is "Apple Seed"?
I don't want hear such mechanical answer.
Sorry.
Right now, my mission is to protect you.
Mission...
Tomorrow we meet at 9.
So... you are the legendary fighter Deunan Knute.
It's said that you died during the Great War.
Your story at the War of North Africa became a legend.
May I sit here?
Sure.
Deunan, how about your father Carl Knute?
He died before the Great War.
Sorry to hear that.
Your mother?
I cannot remember anything about her.
My father didn't tell my anything either.
You and Briareos were lovers, right?
That's when he was still human.
So the body is more important for love.
That's not what I mean.
But to men, the body is a sex symbol none the less.
Well...
What is it like to be in love?
Ahh...
You know Bioriod's emotions are restrained.
So we don't know what love feels like.
I can learn about it from the readings...
But I never experienced personally.
So I become more and more curious.
On this point, I really envy human beings.
People in love, what are they like?
The feeling of love someone.
You bastard! You are only a Bioriod!
How dare you be in front of human!
Olympus military, annoying guys.
Always make a scene.
Synchro-test finished, No problem found.
Only thing left is to adjust the safety belt.
I want to confirm one more time before that.
The reason for the reduction of shock-absorbing is...
I said that already.
Dynamic structure can absorb shock.
But the cartilage has many structures,
joints,
bearings and depressor mechanism are self-restrained,
they will dislocate under too much stress.
Yoshitsune, don't worry. This is Deunan Kunte.
But usually no woman can operate a Land Mate.
Ok, let me try. Help me adjust the safety belt.
Deunan, Yoshitsune is the best mechanics in Olympus.
Only limited to Land Mate though.
Now you are studying the Hecatonchires structure,
right?
Next time let me see the inner structure please.
Forget it, I am blushing.
All secured?
Hmmm, no problem.
Ok, this is the start switch.
First you need to practice, slowly.
Right.
What's happening?
The emergency launch alarm.
Unidentified Land Mates invaded Gaia Research Center!
ESWAT launch immediately!
Stop wasting time, let's move!
Ok like this is fine. I'm moving out.
Like that?!
Deunan
Stop!
The are coming...
Targeting is...
Deunan
Hold on, don't come here!
Drop the weapon!
Briareos
Sorry
Such foolish actions.
The third generation Bioriod are all destroyed.
The DNA system for life-prolonging procedures
are all destroyed as well.
They came in from the underground elevator shaft.
Seven levels of security system are broken through
in one shot.
No sign of insurgents from outside of Olympus.
We don't know who owns those land mates.
This is too much!
Looks like it is fate that we have to take on
the burden of today's human reality.
No other choice.
From now on,
block all surrounding of Tarutarus and Tartarus.
No one is permitted to access the D-Tank on the top.
Yes.
Emergency meeting right now!