Ladies and gentlemen, from the picture,
you can tell easily that
she is my dream lover
To impress her, I'd take this chance
I'll show her some of my martial arts
She is not touched!
Come back!
No girls...
will refuse such things
I've told you for 28 years!
You can't fall for that girl
Who are you?
Why do you stop me from dreaming?
I don't want to see you!
OK! I'll send you back to your world!
Shut up!
The same dream?
You've dreamt it for 28 years!
Yes. But I don't know why...
I think the girl is fond of you,
otherwise she won't come
to your dream every night
I think so. But she'll leave soon
Look at you! My god-father!
If you don't dress well,
I do want to leave you! You know?
To keep you and my dream lover
to stay with me
I'll change!
What'll we practise today?
Make it abc!
ab...
c!
Smart boy!
The alarm!
What's the matter?
Go and search for it
OK!
You've mistaken it!
Sorry! Sorry!
Ready?
Yes!
Change position!
Jump!
Your turn!
Come on!
I'm coming!
I'll go and have a look
This is so dark!
Can you see anything?
Yes I do!
What have you seen?
Oh! There's something!
Forget it!
Just take it easy!
What?
Turn on the light
What is it?
Look!
I think,
doctor must have done something wrong
If not, he would not have scared us
Let's wait for his appearance
Come out!
I know you are here!
Just tell us what's in your mind!
What you've done wrong
I'm your god-son, I'll give you face
Well, don't beat me, ok?
Ok!
I'm sorry! I did something wrong!
What is it?
Just go ahead
I...
Come on!
I lost 5 cents yesterday in the market
You!?
Go to hell!
How can you lose 5 cents!
Damn it!
Do you know it's your fault?
Yes, I do...
If you can't find it back
I'll teach you good lessons
until you get it back
Shit! Let's go!
I've got it back!
My turn now!
Come and eat breakfast!
Yours...
Why don't you eat?
You've taken revenge, haven't you?
Are you kidding?
Although we misunderstood you,
you know I'm growing!
It's not enough for me to eat
such a small egg
This is not for your breakfast
but for our experiment!
What?
Kidding?
For experiment?
I tell you, if it is successful
It'll be enough for few meals of yours
I won't believe it
So am I!
Don't you?
I'll show you now!
This is my newest invention
It's microscope!
Yes, it is
But it's not a common one
I've taken long time to design it,
it is...
ridiculous!
It's a super microscope made by me!
Touch this button,
put it above an object
all will be changed, see!
See!
It's microscope!
Yes
Look!
I'm successful!
It's enough for any kind of growth!
He really makes it!
But what a pity that
we can't take other food for few days
I don't feel I'm full!
What? Let me help you
with your new invention
Here is an attractive advertisement
part time job!
to earn over 10 millions!
We're going to be rich
This is the scroll...
which recorded all legends of the world
this is the sutra of lama
so is it
this is special
What is it?
this is the sutra of lama too
shit!
how about this?
It's great!
this is the treasure
we are going to find out
this is the virgin's mountain
from the scroll, it's stated that...
the virgin's Ice is hidden
If we can get the virgin's Ice
We can change it for big money...
from the evil's palace
If we breathe in the "essence air",
we can live forever
Wait!
What's the matter?
our stuff maybe stolen if we are leaving
if we can't get the ice
then,
we'll suffer double loss!
right?
that is
so you agree?
don't worry!
my new invention...
two to one vision obstruction liquid
With its help, it'll be fine!
What is it?
two to one...
It makes things invisible, got it?
got you!
do your work!
It's fixed!
What's wrong?
let's go!
the liquid is really great!
how about the money? Destroyed?
I've solution to make it visible!
let's go!
hey tim!
this way!
I'm coming!
hurry up!
We won't wait for you!
Wait for me!
doctor, isn't it here?
It's stated that, below the virgin's
mountain, there is a life terminal
Yes! It's right!
let me have a look
It's stated that there is a calabash and
a word "bar" next to it
It's the location stated!
let's go!
ok!
no, there is a plane flying towards us!
We can't take this way!
no! Someone is coming
how about this side?
no!
there are motor cycles!
great! A car is drinking water
What so funny?
there is a horse drinking oil
It's real! We'd find another exit
Why?
there is car!
may I know your name?
ruby!
What song would you like?
I want to hear "dream lover"
for you dream lover?
but he is not existing!
am I silly?
silly or not, it's of no difference now!
Why is he not existing?
because he is my dream lover!
so he is not existing in my world
about your dream lover,
is he having...
any visible figure?
sure!
he is as strong as...
arnold schwarzenegger
he's having a baby face as michael fox
he is as tall as richard gere
he is as charm as tom cruise
I love his roman nose most
What a perfect match! I think
it's hard to find one in this world
that's right!
so you've to make more dreams
I know I can only see him in my dream
miss ruby, what are you doing?
doctor, how can we get up? It's too high
I think there won't be any car
this is something white in front,
what is it?
What's the matter?
nothing! I've just scared it away!
let's go up!
Is it the correct exit?
It's written in the scroll!
Wait for me!
damn it!
they just sneak away
after peeping my bath!
try my super scissors legs! Go to hell!
What is it?
It disappears soon!
I've seen something flying towards me!
me too!
maybe it's ghost! Let's go!
I've to worship god when we go back
let's go!
I'm coming!
how are you? Miss ruby?
I'm fine,
I think I've just seen my dream lover
but he is a little bit short
don't be that selective!
It's a rare chance
You're right!
I've to make use of this chance
don't get angry
It'll harm your health
don't be that angry,
it'll harm your health
don't be that angry!
someone is stealing!
Where?
Wait for me! Don't go that fast!
stop it!
are you new?
do you know your job?
that means you don't know
Look! All the men want...
to get the virgin's Ice
haven't you told her?
I'll let you tell her
no one can...
return safely
Why?
It's simple! It's impossible for them
to get to the virgin's mountain
and any of them can get the ice
before sunset
therefore,
why not take their money?
or, their money will just stay
in the mountain with their skeleton!
that means cheating?
cheating?
no! It's technique
should I seduce them?
here is the life terminal
that means
the men will go to heaven tomorrow
just take it as beneficence
and, leave the man...
with roman nose to me
such cool feeling,
I can get from him only
I love your roman nose
I hate others mentioning my roman nose
You deserve it!
serve you right!
no one is capable of being our opponent
I think even they can get to the top,
they still can't have the ice
Why don't we rob their money?
no! We can't use this way
no! Then we can steal
no way!
that's a very filthy behavior
Why not! Anyway
they won't be able to come back alive
after tomorrow
I want to help them...
to keep their money
good deed! Good deed!
stephen chow sing-chi?
no, I am...
tim chow ha-chi!
What are you laughing?
chow did the same
I've mistaken it!
I don't want to play this, but...
guessing game!
ok, let's bet a million
deal!
We don't have so much money to bet
sure win!
sure win?
deal!
get ready!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6
7, 8, 9
how poor are you? You're so slow!
do you have money to pay?
What did you cover?
It's a nine
are you sure it's a nine
Yes!
sure?
open it!
It's not nine, but there is a line!
bingo!
she lost!
bingo! I've make it!
I always win!
You mean giving me money?
so, I can hire somebody to carry me
instead of walking up
to the virgin's mountain
let's see who plays first
sure
I want head
ok
It's head, lady first
sorry, me first
after you
make the bet $500,000 for it
I don't think
no one wants to play with me anymore
You're wrong! I want to play with you
hi
to make me scream,
to make my heart beats
It's your name!
to make me scream...
the angel of the corrupt age?
may I know your name?
I was called davis in the past
now, I'm called hungary
head or tail?
head
I want tail
What a strange smell?
It's fixed!
sorry, it's mine
never mind
tail, me first
sir, are you martial-artist?
don't be nosy!
Where is the ball?
What?
sorry!
change it!
how can it be?
that's too powerful!
I see! I see!
Watch out!
don't get angry, it'll harm your health
now, there are 25 marks left
on the table
If I get that ball, I'll win
shit! What to do then?
I've got any idea
super microscope!
It's fixed!
how lucky are you!
thanks!
What is it?
nothing!
super microscope
he's smart!
this is quite difficult
bravo...
I think you'll lose that $500,000
thank you!
What?
You'll lose that $500,000
but if you don't have money,
I'll take you in return!
stop dreaming!
Watch out! Don't miss it
I won't let you hit it
I prefer eating it
are you kidding?
give the ball back to me
give it now!
how bad you are!
super microscope!
are we going too far?
my turn!
the ball is broken!
change it!
get lost!
can you stand it?
I think I should use my own cue
I've fixed up all the pockets!
thank you!
hold it!
You mean it?
cut the crap!
come on!
tim, it's your turn!
the chinese kid is really great!
We win at last!
my god!
arrest them!
go!
It's dead end!
You can't go!
Why?
because you are my dream lover
many people love to use such excuse!
You are great!
Your dream lover is not me
It's should be michael fox
You are my dream lover!
should I listen to you?
arrest him!
go!
admit it, or we can't escape!
admit it!
ok!
since we'd use this trick,
I've to reveal my heart
by writing a letter with my blood
hold it!
What have you done?
I help you to increase your speed
really?
You can go now!
Isn't it that kind of you?
but be careful!
come back!
What's it?
forget it, let's go for the Ice
let's go for the dream
go!
see you!
I'll wait for you
I can't stand any more!
You are useless!
let us help you
thank you!
You are welcome!
cause you are old!
We are young, so we'd help
What flavour is your food?
banana, what's yours?
mine has a flavour of durian
really? Let me try
great!
Isn't it right?
It's true!
mixed fruit punch?!
It's tasteless!
how can you believe such nonsense!
What was it in the past?
It was a river
now it's frozen
a helicopter!
someone wants to take our picture?
no!
they know
we'll be successful in getting the Ice
so they are shooting the process
for a tv special
are you kidding?
I am serious!
my god!
many people will know me! I'll be busy!
according to the scroll
after this river,
we'll reach a narrow valley
Isn't it?
be careful
Watch out! Beware of slippery
forget it
be careful!
after the valley, then comes a cliff
be careful of slippery!
Why didn't you warn me earlier?
What you've said, we all went through
What's next?
there is a slope ahead
after it, there is a slight slope too
just slide down
that is!
let's go!
the slope is just in front
go down!
come on!
It's rather steep!
Isn't it a slight slope?
how long will it take?
according to the scroll,
it'll take over an hour
kidding?
You've said we'd soon get there!
I don't know!
how far will it take?
You liar!
It's the scroll...
which misleads me!
It's cold!
Watch out for your head!
Where are you going?
I'll have a look!
be careful!
kids always love speed!
let's go to help!
ok! Come on!
follow me!
Where has he gone?
Who is he? He looks familiar to us
I think it's tim, naked tim!
put on the clothes!
damn it!
how dare you undress me?
I just want to help!
Yes
What time is it?
11 o'clock. It's dark!
It seems to be dangerous!
let's leave here now!
What?
the scroll stated that
we'd get here by 11 o'clock!
really?
It's true! Let's go!
Watch out!
doctor
shall we come tomorrow?
do you want to get rich?
You can come yourself tomorrow
god-father!
ching Yan...
are you fine?
how are you?
forget about me! You'd better leave now
don't panic
I'll ask for help
no, I want to stay here to accompany him
Well, you can stay here
no! I want to go with you to seek help
so, let's go, quick!
I feel like staying in my dream!
shit!
I can't see!
It is getting dark
can I stand it?
Ching Yan!
Ching Yan! You can't sleep! Get up!
my god! He falls asleep!
he'll be dead if he can't wake up!
I've to enter his dream!
ching Yan, get up now!
ching Yan!
get up!
I'm in danger! Get up!
he wakes up!
madam...
don't come over
Your majesty, I've checked that
3 men have taken the virgin's Ice
that's good!
What'll we do now?
You stupid ass!
When they come down, rob their Ice
Yes!
If you can't rob it
all of you should die!
Yes sir
We'll get it
to give you the "essence air"
long life to Your majesty!
ching Yan!
answer me!
Where are you?
he left the shoes!
You dumb bell!
he is covered by the snow!
go and save him!
don't go that fast! Wait for me!
I've to catch you up
are you fine?
god-father, are you ok?
ching Yan
god-father!
are you fine?
are you alright?
are you ok?
my god! He means yes by nodding his head
look the way you're hitting him!
You idiot!
are you alright?
I'm fine!
You are great!
sure
What did you say?
the virgin's Ice?
Where is it?
the virgin Ice!
that is!
that's it! Take me over there!
It's beautiful!
Isn't it the virgin's Ice?
sure it is!
We'll be rich then!
If we sell it to the king of evil,
we'll get 10 millions
I've got another idea
I want to do our own business!
melt it and mix it with water,
sell it to those rich old man
to give them ever lasting life!
then we'll get more from it, right?
good idea!
sure
bravo! Excellent idea!
I'm sorry!
You can't sell it!
Why not?
Why?
It can help me to search
for my dream lover
Who is going to sell it, I'll kill him
don't!
shit! He's got crazy!
let's prepare ourselves to cheat him, ok?
for your dream
for your lover
for our friendship
We prefer supporting you...
to the money!
What a real friend!
fantastic!
the three on the ice, you're surrounded!
drop the Ice,
or you'll be killed!
What's it?
drop the Ice
go!
You can't rob our Ice! Let's go!
drop it!
they've no time to listen!
let's go to the forest!
they all hear it!
stop...
I shouted so loud that,
would they chase after us to the forest?
I don't think so!
let's go!
keep your balance!
doctor!
don't go!
are you giving order?
You are nosy!
don't go!
take care of god father!
come up!
come up if you've guts
quick Whirl-wind
come on!
What are you doing? Scaring me?
It's ghost-shadow fists!
You want to kill me?
I will treat you the super microscope!
super microscope!
sing long fists!
super fists!
Where is my Ice?
ching Yan, they robbed the Ice!
give me the Ice
You'd better leave first!
don't come over!
drop it
damn it!
Increase the speed
that is a fake one made by doctor!
come down!
do you mean it?
Yes, he is waiting us in the plane,
hurry up!
let's go now!
let's go!
Where is the Ice? Did doctor take it?
he did
Where is it?
how do I know?
I make it invisible!
thank you
Isn't it an ordinary ice,
or it contains the secret
of my dream lover?
please tell me!
ching Yan
Is the Ice touched by my sincerity?
this way!
It's your door which is touched by me
When you left me last time,
you left a love letter
I was touched after reading it
I didn't send you any love letter
What do you want to do here?
do? I haven't done anything!
You want me to do that?
Why did you turn off the light?
I feel shy!
me too
no one can see it
It's so dark! We can do nothing!
Where is he going?
sorry!
don't go! Don't hide up!
You can't find me in darkness
come down!
miss!
I won't surrender!
You are too hard-hearted!
miss!
I treat you so good,
I can't imagine you are so cool to me
I can't imagine
I don't want to leave this room
Why do you want me to leave?
I can't imagine that
I am willing to leave this room
so many things that are unexpected
ruby is right!
so many things are unexpected
in this world
to get this virgin's Ice
It's out of my expectation
but about madam,
about my love to you,
can you even feel a little bit of it?
It's pointless! It's not reasonable!
Want a riot?
I am not ruby
Your virgin's Ice,
it is now in the life terminal
I can live forever!
I will be beautiful!
let's go!
It's ching Yan!
god-father!
forget about me!
doctor, take it
What happened?
What a mess is it?
Who are you? How dare you come?
don't get mad
go, hurry up!
tim, go!
What shall we do now?
If you don't want to die, drop the ice
shall we listen to him?
Why don't you ask for my opinion
in other matters?
since he is not paying attention to us,
make it invisible first
I will block their way
don't let them go
tim, open the door, quick!
It can't help, turn back!
shit, I am caught by them
ching Yan, save me!
hold it
let them go!
damn it!
give me the Ice,
then I will let them go!
damn!
shit!
no big deal! I have fixed them up!
the Ice is robbed by them
Yes! Yes!
give me back the Ice!
I have got the Ice now,
you are useless to me then
go to hell!
are you fine?
I am alright
You are useless!
try the gastric juice of mine!
I suck!
be careful!
ching Yan, save us!
doctor!
It's hot!
I want to burn you to death!
no way!
hold on!
use some force!
doctor, madam appears!
ching Yan
help me...
the virgin's Ice?
give me the "essence air"!
I won't give it
to a cruel monster like you!
no! I will kill you one by one
take ching Yan away, hurry up!
If you don't give me the "essence air",
I will take it myself
eat this, god-father
how are you?
the medicine isn't that good to him
do you have another type?
another type?
hurry up
Yes, I have some others
just try this
I don't want it
here it is
come on, take this
eat it, it's gyrophora
It's useless
come on, take this
save it when it is needed
I know it's useless,
but it can last for a short time
doctor is great,
he will save you
I am useless, I have no idea
You always have many inventions!
now, you have not even one solution!
I won't care!
If you can't think out any method,
he will die
think out some ways!
tim, man will die anyway
I am older than you,
I will die before you
I am even older,
why don't I die before you?
buy, anyway...
It's me who is nosy,
it's me who is greedy for money
If not,
we would not go for the Ice
You would not have met your dream lover
You would not die
don't cry!
In this world,
how many people can fine his dream...
before his death?
luckily, I am one of them
I am too happy!
I want to thank you
don't die!
I miss you most
I miss you two!
tim, after my death
You should take care of yourself. Got it
do you remember the morning exercise?
no!
I won't remember if you are not with me
You can't do that
I will teach you once more
follow me
hold me, come on
are you ready?
Yes
You are getting smarter and smarter
doctor, I feel regret for one thing
tim and I haven't taken
any picture together
can you take a picture for us?
please! Come on
ready?
let me take a look!
Why? Why?
get up, god-father!
get up, don't leave us!
god-father...
It's your fault!
give me back my god-father!
stay calm,
your god-father has just passed away!
since he is dead,
I want to accompany him
I have sent him the "essence air"
You mean the air...
which the king of evil wants
by all means?
Yes, he will soon recover
so you can stay with god-father forever!
forever?
the essence air means my life
I will die soon
madam!
If ching Yan knows it,
he will be very upset
When he wakes up,
he is protected by the essence air,
nothing can harm him
but he can't defeat the king of evil,
don't let him go
how are you?
don't let him see me!
all because of "love"
madam...
Where is doctor?
doctor, tim!
doctor, doctor, tim!
I know you are here!
come out! Come out!
don't you want to come out?
I will wait you here
I will wait till you come out!
until you tell me...
where my madam is
We won't have food!
If you don't tell me where madam is,
I won't let you sleep,
I won't let you eat!
come out!
I am hungry!
surrender!
We can't compete with the power of love!
no!
Well, tell me where madam is
then I will let you eat!
You want woman? I can find you some!
tell me!
ching Yan, take it easy!
It's just a dream!
for your dream, for your madam,
you have nearly lost your life!
Your madam have made us in a mess too!
do you agree?
Yes...
suicide?
If you don't tell me where she is,
I prefer dying in front of you
You will regret it
she may be inside
pal, although the truth may hurt you,
listen to me, stop seeking your dream
thank you
get lost!
pal, although the truth may hurt you,
listen to me, stop seeking your dream
get lost!
pal, although the truth may hurt you,
listen to me, stop seeking your dream
get lost,
pal, although the truth may hurt you,
listen to me, stop seeking your dream
get lost!
madam
go now, she won't see you
Why?
What happened?
tell me please
Where is she?
If you see her again,
you may not love her anymore
no
no matter how she has changed,
no matter what has happened,
I love her, this is the truth
come in
granny, look
these are the information
about my dreams
from the day I was born
every night, I see madam in my dream
We grew up together
We went to school together
We love each other
We fall deeply for each other
till we get marry, I swear!
even she is 80 years old
I still love her
I think you understand my heart!
You are madam
madam!
do you still love me?
marry me!
I am really touched!
I was wrong to tell the king of evil
where the virgin's Ice was
but, this time,
I am so generous to send them present
for their wedding,
I think ching Yan will forgive me
they captured madam!
ching Yan!
after the swim,
I feel better now
really?
kidding! Why they need
such a big fire for barbecue?
no! God-father is on fire!
What? Our ship is on fire!
god-father!
ching Yan!
let me go in!
don't! You will be burnt!
ching Yan, where are you?
ching Yan, don't die! Don't leave us!
What are you doing?
I am sleeping!
Why did you wake me up?
the ship exploded!
You were burning!
What?
Why didn't I hurt?
madam!
I wonder what madam told us was true
let's try
fine!
madam... how are you?
how can I face others?
my face is ruined!
no matter how you changed,
I still love you
my god, my face is ruined!
let me have a look!
Who are you?
I am ruby
Why did you pretend to be madam?
I just want...
cut the crap,
let me cure your face first
can you?
sure!
let me try
he is not hurt!
he is fine!
What are you doing?
nothing, just practise kung-fu
ching Yan!
madam is caught by the king of evil
kill me!
If he knows
the "essence air" is kept with you,
he will tempt you to save madam
It's dangerous for you to go alone
I don't care, I just want to save madam
I hope you can help me
guard the exit of the evil's palace,
don't let anyone go out
You should take care
I don't care who you are
If you don't hand me my madam
I want you to die terribly
You do have guts!
give the "essence air" back to me
give me back my wife,
and I will let you go
come to the horrible valley with me
if you have guts
damn it!
madam!
madam...
Wait for me, madam
doctor, kiss him!
god-father, give madam the essence air
ching Yan!
madam!
It's not long enough, longer!
save madam, quick!
ching Yan!
help me!
bravo, the king of evil is killed!
bravo!
ching Yan!
go now, he will soon explode!
how are you? Answer me please!
ching Yan!
I am still alive!
before I meet madam,
I won't die!
You are the same as you are in my dream
It's not necessary for you to do so!
do you know?
there is a butterfly,
it can live only 24 hours, it is born
in the morning, and die at night
It lives for finding its better half,
understand?
I am willing to do so
god-father...
ching Yan!
I saved him
he saved me too
the essence air is enough
for one person only
how can we share it?
What shall I do?
give him to me
from that day onwards
We have never seen them
because she sent ching Yan...
to the coldest place of the world
to keep his life
do you know where are they?
an adventurer did see a couple
near the cliff in the south pole,
I think they are the couple mentioned